Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Your doppelganger is Buck Angel.
- That's not true.
- Yeah.
- I also was saying that my doppelganger at the gym
looks like me but has hair.
- Buck Angel.
- Buck Angel, does Buck Angel have hair?
- I don't know.
- I don't even know.
- Has hair down there.
- That's not--
- On his pussy.
I don't care about if he has hair on his pussy, man.
That's not my, I'm talking about a doppelganger.
- Wait, you have a doppelganger with hair down there?
Is that what you're saying?
- I didn't see the down there.
There's a guy at the gym, he has almost the exact same--
- Where he was in the shower where you saw his hair?
- The showers are closed at Blink Fitness, actually.
- Okay, so you were in-- - Why?
- Because of what I did. - His shower.
- What?
- You were in his shower to see his hair.
- Yeah, I was in his shower.
- Or he was just naked on the machine.
- Yeah, he was on the naked squat rack,
showing his asshole at the bottom of the squat.
my favorite machine at the time. Me too. I love waiting for that machine a lot. I love
going and waiting. Yeah, when it's my turn I go, "Oh, never mind." I actually just realized
I have to go to lunch. I'm too nervous. I actually just realized my weakness would stop
me from using this machine, so I have to leave. Yeah, I have to leave. But you can go ahead
of me. Yeah, go ahead. Actually, I'm waiting on somebody else. We're going to do a double
squat on this. Yeah, so go ahead. So just go ahead and do naked squats on this machine.
And my text ringtone is a camera sound, so don't worry about it. It's just playing like
a cannon how do you make that with your mouth you know that's how I learned that
sound is the winder you're a wine no way at the bottom wait that's the winder
it's not the shutter holy fucking shit it wasn't the shutter it was the winder
that I always wondered that I thought that must be the shutter cuz I got the
power winder we're gonna get fucking asshole we never wondered that we're
just saying bullshit oh jeez don't put down your Patrick I have the perfect
thing to cheer you up. Me and Caleb are working on something. Don't roll over my charger.
I think you're really going to like it. I'm sorry. I care about it if it's a one. Alright,
you're breaking something I can't talk about. Don't get near my, don't slap me. Do you even
want to hear this thing that Caleb and I prepared for you? Getting these rolly chairs is like
the worst. I shouldn't be sitting in this. Yeah, I don't know why you are. I just didn't
feel like anyone else used. I didn't want to move that. Then don't. Yeah. But me and Caleb
prepared something for you. He really doesn't care and he doesn't want to hear it.
That's fine. I guess we'll just, you know what, let's end the episode. We'll do a two minute
and fifteen second episode. Okay, that seems like what Patrick wants. Okay, just hit stop
record Patrick. You can say whatever you want now. Okay, I just, okay, it's paused.
It would be funny if we did put out like a two minute episode and then another one hour
one, but. You fucking idiot, I didn't pause it. That was all caught on tape. Now the fans
hear you for what you really are. And now one of these other podcasts is going to steal
I'm actually going to pause it now.
Okay, it's paused.
Go ahead, say everything you've always wanted to say off air.
What the hell?
No, of course not.
I'm going to have to cut that out.
Okay, I'm actually going to...
We pretended to pause and then had to cut out whatever Patrick said.
Okay, I'm actually going to pause it now, Patrick, so you can say whatever you want.
it
I actually paused it.
Can you pause it though?
I have to pee.
He doesn't have to pee, he's lying.
Okay, it's paused Patrick.
Yeah, go ahead.
Go pee.
How are you so quick with that button?
I did it twice.
You didn't have to pee, I fucking knew it, you fucking liar.
You just wanted to give him a pause.
I wanted to give him a...
Okay, fine, I'll pause it.
I'll pause it.
Okay, it's paused.
It's paused.
It's paused, bro.
Say whatever you need to say.
- Hold on, can we restart the episode?
- You wanna restart the episode now?
- Yeah, we can restart the whole thing.
- Okay, we're restarting right?
- Okay.
- I'm in a sour mood. - Okay, I just restarted it.
- I'm in a sour mood.
- I just restarted it. - Why are you in a sour mood?
- 'Cause I just feel like fucking shit.
- Why do you feel like shit?
- Depression and anxiety.
- A combination of the two?
- A combination of the two.
- Are they interacting with each other?
- They're interacting in a very harsh way.
- That's a deadly combo.
That can actually kill you by suicide.
Have you ever thought about just killing yourself,
just ending it all?
(laughing)
- Just fucking ending, just ending it all.
Either one of you.
- I started seeing--
- If you guys ever just been like,
"Oh fuck, I'm just gonna fucking kill myself."
- I started seeing a psychiatrist
'cause I was talking about getting on Adderall again
so I can actually focus.
And one of the first screening questions was like,
"Have you ever thought about killing yourself?"
And I was like, "Well yeah, duh."
- Yeah, I did.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- What kind of fucking psycho goes into a--
- Doesn't, yeah.
doesn't want to kill himself.
Not even want to, but doesn't say like,
"Oh yeah, no, I've actually, wow, you know what?
I've never even thought about it."
"I've never even, that's never even crossed my mind,
killing myself."
The fact that I even said, the fact that I said "duh" too,
like, I said, "Yeah, duh," and then she wrote something down.
"Duh, have you ever thought of killing yourself?"
She wrote something down, like, immediately,
and I was like, "Oh, fuck."
One of the worst things as a...
And then I got, and she was like, "I think I'm gonna put you on Wellbutrin."
a straightjacket. One of the worst things about being a psychiatrist would have to be when
you're giving someone a screening like that and you ask them, "Oh, have you ever thought
of killing yourself?" And they just go like, "Oh!" And a lightbulb goes on over their face
and they run out of the office. I don't think I need you anymore. Are you using these scissors?
That'd be a really horrible way to kill yourself is running with scissors. Yeah, it'd take so
damn long. We used to get in elementary school, in elementary school we used to get these
stickers if they were called they were the the South School Hawks like the
Hawks stickers. Go Hawks. Go Hawks dude. Go South School Hawks.
So they were they were the red white and blue stickers there's the red
for respect white for responsibility and blue for safety and if you did something
Is that what the flag stands for? Yeah. Wow. The South School Hawks flag. Okay. So the you would
get the stickers for being an exemplary,
being an example of those three things
in the mission statement.
- Any one of them or all three combined?
- If you got all three in one day
and you were walking around with red, white, and blue,
you were a goaded student.
- Holy shit.
- But I saw, one time I just looked at my teacher
and I was like, hey, I just had an idea
'cause I think I had a red sticker
and I was like, I know how I'm gonna get a blue.
I know how I'm gonna do it.
And I was like, I walked up to my teacher and I was like,
I think when you walk with scissors,
you should walk with them facing down.
(laughing)
And then the kid sitting, I got back to my seat
and the kid who's sitting next to me is just like,
I know you only said that for the sticker.
It's like, yeah, fucking of course
I only said it for the sticker.
- Did you guys have show and tell in your school?
- We didn't have show and tell.
In German class, we had cultural tidbits,
where we would have to bring in a thing about Germany
that we learned on our own.
We had, at my school I went to until like sixth grade,
we had like mandatory show and tell.
That's fire.
Everybody had to bring something in.
And I had some pretty fucking fail show and tells, bro.
Yeah?
Yeah, I was bringing in fucking DVDs.
(laughing)
I was bringing in whatever, bro.
I was showing my lunch.
Oh yeah, dude, we, what was this?
My friend Ian in first grade brought in the,
I think we were, I want to say, straight up, I know this isn't true, but I want to say that
we were learning about eggs.
That's not a crazy thing to learn about.
But then he brought in his GameCube copy of Billy Hatcher.
You know what we need to do is get a homunculus growing at the office, get an egg and put
all of our, we could just do like a sperm box.
I'll take it and I'll administer it with a hypodermic needle.
I'd rather you administer that in front of us.
i really want you know what i was i don't know i don't waste your guys time so you
guys get is not in like a vile here i'm very protective of my spurs you know
yes a lot of them again not in a cardboard box
whenever i know that you know plastic bags there any female fans would be
interested in buying a combination slurry of the three of our spurs
splitting
and we could just see what the kid looks like who who's from one
we have competition
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Buying the slurry of sperms.
Why would you even...
Some fucking psycho is gonna message us.
I don't think so. I don't think...
Some psycho is gonna message us and say
"Give me your sperm slurry now!"
Wouldn't you be interested to know whose sperm was the fastest and won the competition?
Well, I already know it's me.
And I don't need...
See, that's what I mean. I know it's me.
I don't need some crazy woman and I know I actually know that it's camera it
shoots out really fast it's not that my sperms are fast but they're really
clever the other ones really good tortoise in the hair I don't want I don't
want to race straight to the egg and get tired of minor my number two guns - I
don't want messages from crazy women saying drain your sperm into a bag and
send it to me. A bag? It would be fucking, first of all, a latex bag. First of all, we get a contract. A latex bag with an udder.
You get a contract that says no matter whose sperm it is, we ain't helping with that baby. That's right. Even a little bit.
And you can't abort it. Yeah, you can't abort it because if you do, we'll get kind of mad because we won't know who it looked the most like.
There's a clause in it that says if you abort the kid. You must raise it to at least 18. And then you can abort it. Yeah.
The I for an I clause, if you abort the kid, we...
We abort another baby.
We abort a baby at random.
Yeah, no, I was going to say we abort you.
Oh, shit.
We get Agent 47 to abort you.
And that's the I for an I clause, and that's legally binding.
I have a strong feeling that kid's going to pop out looking like Agent 47.
No.
Yeah, I think so.
I think until it's like three, maybe it'll look like Agent 47.
No.
I think until it's about...
That's true.
Caleb has an edge right at the beginning.
Yeah.
Oh, it looks just like me.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, but if it's a girl, it would look like you two downstairs.
That's all I'm saying.
Sorry?
What are you so concerned about a baby's downstairs for?
You are.
Okay, reverse.
Didn't say that.
I didn't say any of that.
Draw four.
You're about to draw four for my son who is going to come out of this woman.
Green seven.
You're going to draw four because you're teaching him alphabets.
Green 8.
Green 9, fucking easy.
Ok, green 1.
Yellow 1.
Black 2.
Black 2?
There's no...
He means draw 2.
No, I mean black 2.
Oh, then yeah, you're cheating.
He made his own fucking card.
He made up his own card.
Dose, that's what I'm playing.
Holographic 2.
Oh, uno.
I forgot to say uno.
Oh shit, fuck you.
But, you guys don't think that's a good idea?
Did you ever do a Dose rule?
No.
In Uno?
What's a Dose rule?
You have to call Dose too.
Uno's so fucking fun.
Uno is fun as fuck.
Uno's fun as fuck.
We used to play Uno at the lunch table in high school.
In high school?
Yeah, one day someone was like, "Hey, I just found a bunch of Uno cards."
And I was just like, "Alright, fuck it.
We're gonna play Uno."
I didn't go to public high school.
And then we kept doing it.
I thought by then everybody was just fucking fingering each other and shit.
Yeah.
I also went to a very small high school.
know it's a everyone I guys are worried yeah you guys are kind of hillbillies
your bumpkins playing uno yeah everyone else is playing pong yeah at their lunch
table we had a guy behind the time what was sex ed like for you guys up north
cuz down south we had a celibacy based we it was like do you can it was like
this is how it works but it's yeah there was definitely had a very the curriculum
was definitely like about about abstinence but then there would always be
that the teacher who's like and they want me to tell you that abstinence is
the best thing but I'm gonna tell you also
well if you are
yeah yeah and hardest that's that's what
um... the fuckin the
seventh grade is like the year that we all learned about like sex stuff
and uh... great how did you guys have did you guys have the sex challenge
yes you can last a long as you know the other yeah
uh... lost
a really i thought it was my first time for another immediately no we we had
this like bald teacher
sounds good uh...
Mr. G and he was like, he seemed like he was on,
Mr. G seemed like he was on Adderall all the time
and he was just like, he had just very wide eyes
and he was like, he seemed like a very like sex posse guy.
- Swag.
- And it was just, I don't know, it was kind of weird.
It was kind of like, I feel like he was like a guy
who did like nude yoga with his wife.
- That's cool.
Oh, that's cool, man.
- Yeah.
- The older I'm getting, and I'm getting old, right?
The older I'm getting, I'm starting to re-imagine
all the things that i think are cool in this world
uh... and i'm thinking stuff i used to think was
cringe i think is based basically that's the truth you know i i don't like the
verses a lot of golf
i want to buy i want to buy a rolex i six hundred dollars in my bank account
about rolex yeah yeah i have a few hundred or thirty eight dollars as of
this moral of a lot of hundred thousand dollars that's fucking riches for so
we're going to be a cheap rolex one of the chief one of the cheapest rolex
thirty seven hundred bucks that's it which is just after the office we share
it
That's a good idea.
That is a good idea.
Maybe we can get like a--
Oyster Perpetual Rolex.
Like a, what's the other one?
What's the other brand?
Patek Philippe.
AP.
Cartier.
Audemars Piguet.
Is it Cartier?
I started getting Cartier watch ads on my Instagram.
It thinks I'm rich.
It's kind of made me go like, oh my, oh.
You're gonna join the 700, or the 500 club?
Yeah, 'cause I'm gonna turn 500.
What's the 500 club?
Is that the, if you work for a Fortune 500?
Or is that just--
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Yeah, I'm not sure I do either.
- I don't even know what I'm talking about.
- The Fortune 500, you're saying it's,
so there's a Fortune 500, but then if you work for that,
you're in a club?
- You're in the club, the Fortune 500 club.
- I mean, now listen, buddy,
I know about the Mile High Club
and I've been a member since fucking sex ed.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah.
- I don't think putting all of our sperms
in a slurry would work.
- I think it would be fine.
- I think that's a fucking very valid way
of deciding stuff. - I think that the,
i think the we have to the thing about it and we have to construct kind of a a
perpetual motion type thing
uh... where but you know we don't have to know what it is a cold i don't know
don't hold on hold me on him telling you something this okay technology because
whoever goes first
in this and when we're sperming into our boxer bagger whatever
their sperms are going to be on the bottom okay make so we need is that we
need something exactly a permanent swisher that's constantly switching
centrifuge. We get a centrifuge. But it needs to be constantly growing.
So it's just pure sperm. So we kind of just give this woman like basically a little Lego
piece cube. A sperm rock. Yeah, yeah, and say put that in you. Yeah. And well she has to
buy it. Not stepped on. So we freeze the sperm into a cube and then it just all the moisture
inside. It's not frozen, it's just all the moisture. I'm not having no fucking caveman
sun. He's fresh, never frozen. It will just be a solid rock because we take all the moisture
out of it with scientific machines. Yeah, a centrifuge. Yeah, or other machines. Stop
saying, what you're talking about is a centrifuge. Like a permanent swisher. When I was like
nine or ten, I learned about jacking off and I went at it for like an hour in the bathroom
and I looked in the toilet and I saw a hair and the reflection on the toilet bowl made
me think that I'd shot out one big sperm. You thought you shot out a single sperm?
Single giant sperm. Was it a long hair? Was it like a woman's head hair?
It was like my hair. I had long hair as a kid and I saw it in the toilet.
You know when you look in the toilet bowl and there's like light reflecting down and
you can see the reflection of the hair? I thought that was a sperm.
I'm with you. I thought sperm was going to be like a tape worm or like the tendon in
chicken. That's what I thought it was going to be like. Yeah, and I didn't even, I couldn't even nut
at that point. Yeah, well you thought you did. I thought I was done because I saw one sperm and I
was like, "Oh, I'm pretty young." Yeah. I'm pretty young. That's what it'll look like. Sperm can't
run around on its own. Yeah. Not yet. If you put it on a flat surface, it's not going to run to the
side. I don't think it starts popping like a magnetic fluid, no. My uncles, one of my uncles,
is like I had a rotating cast of uncles growing up and my one of my uncles left
a photographed Kama Sutra and shit and they it was but they couldn't show the
they couldn't show the actual stuff that was going on so I just assumed that it
was all done in the butt until I was because I found it when I was nine I was
like really what is the vagina look like I'm not gonna look it up on the computer
because I don't get in trouble I never thought of the butt as any kind of
sexual thing until I thought it went in and then it go and then it went around
what probably the Mia Malkova way explain I thought the sperms went in and then it
swam back down into the sperm went into the butt and then when they swam and I
thought you know the vagina was like a center inside the yeah and that you
would nut in the butt I didn't know swim around okay no one really my parents are
Irish Catholic they didn't teach me what I said that at first I thought you meant
that the guy puts his dick into the butt and the dick goes around and out and in
Yeah, that's what yeah, cuz that's what it sounded like you said what I first
You thought that a guy's dick could be as long as a tube yeah, and it would go around
I thought the miles gonna grow into a big it'll be like weaving a basket. Yeah
Okay, I'm glad I didn't learn about sex very much
Yeah, yeah, it's too scary when you're I guess I saw too much adult media as a kid
And then it I'd learned about sex stuff, but didn't know what sex was yeah
You learned about stuff like saying like yeah, just got some pussy. Yeah
Yeah, I was like nine years old saying like he got a dirty Sanchez. Yeah
Yeah, I had a similar thing cuz I had older brother. Yeah, I was walking around saying
I'll get some pussy with pubes on it
Extra pubes on the pussy, please
Pussy and butt for my nut. Oh my fucking happy trail into a fucking girls. Puss. Yep. Yep
And he would I gave her a I gave her a reverse Sanchez a reverse Sanchez. What's that one got clean one?
You give her clean what is it dirty Sanchez you put who you split it you put
I thought you put poop and then you put the poop penis on the girl's upper lip make it look like a mustache
I don't think that's what it is. Well, that's something that's the Caleb then
That's the Caleb. It's someone put that on dirty derby dictionary
They should have called it dirty. You should be able to just say anything on the
Urban Dictionary and say this is the meaning of this. There should be
Wikipedia style editors who say this is good, this is bad. It should be
like a Merriam-Webster thing. There should be one or two experts.
Just some urban experts. Urbanologists. Yeah, urbanologists. I mean I
consider myself a part-time so I mean if I pursue some kind of graduate degree
maybe I'll be eligible for the position. You've been talking about damn sex too much this episode. It's my fault. You brought up the
sperms thing but then I just kind of ran with it. All right then fucking stop
talking about it. What do you want to talk about? I don't even know. I don't know
what people want to listen to us say. It's not about these people.
Pretend the people don't even exist because they might as well not.
Tell me what you, what is on your mind Patrick Doran? I have a tooth
problem right now. Really? And I'm very tired because I was up all night
with tooth pain. Really? You were up all night with tooth pain? See this is why
understanding each other so yeah you said you were tired and we should have I
would assume that you were maybe at the 40/40 Club Jay-Z getting tipsy no no no I
wasn't at the 40/40 he's up well where were you with tooth pain in your bed I
was in my bed with two okay that's fucking awful yeah and I was rolling and
I was gonna roll you were rolling mmm like rolling rolling rolling just a joke
I that would probably make the pain less bad Molly I don't know anytime I've done
Molly I've just been like scared of TV a little more yeah yeah it's not really my
favorite drug it's okay just makes you good at dancing I've never time I've
done it I really like to take it and watched I watched Spongebob with my
cousins really yeah my cousin brought Molly and I was and we were just
watching Spongebob why would you do Molly to watch Spongebob you're supposed to do
it just wasn't like it makes the joy of the laughter you're supposed to use it
like a listen to dubstep I don't like dubstep scary sprites and fucking
monsters is fucking shit you're supposed to go listen to dubstep and put like
like those speaker the the what is it called the UV meet what's a fucking you
know what I'm talking about like the shirts the shirts that have the speaker
you connect your iPod to it and then it has a no to speaker about the iron man
the audio spectrum. Yo, getting into the Iron Man suit on Molly though.
My reaction?
Whoa!
I'm flying!
Those like shirts that they used to sell at the mall
where you could like plug
Spencer's gifts and you would plug
your phone into it. Captain America on Molly
Captain America on Molly. I love you so much
the Hulk. And it was like
it was like an applause
meter on your shirt and it would have like
the lights going up to the music.
yeah hulk on molly
all uh... dallas
uh... all units
i'd like
i a m
i'm gonna do a big whole place but i'm not
appealing to the people of the local you know i was going to a green oak
voice
you know what i can find some more of a chilled out at the so i still have some
fucking someone pressures earlier for the uh... british most ever
earlier it was pretty good is like
welcome to me is terrible
nice pop it all the rules i i lost it was like
where well-documented for what he did well i can't imagine and i i i i can't
imagine having it wasn't that but i think it is to happen
so i guess i can i get interest in a flaming man who
a flaming that's a little kid
yet to paint live on air
he's making a fucking warrior failure i know what you are not going to bring a
thing of oreo with me of oreos oreos is what got me in this problem
please sir can I have a flaming Moe? Homer Simpson come home and get away from Moe's
if the Simpsons were in England they'd probably be named the Thompson's well
they need to do you know they did the Mexican Simpsons shout out to Mexican
Homer who fucking died Mexican Homer yeah they did a Spanish version of the
Simpsons like like Spanish version of the like like they dubbed it like they were
called like the Hernandez's. No, they were not called the Hernandez's.
It's as if the Simpsons is like a common name in America.
When I was watching The Simpsons on Disney Plus, there was some glitch with my
Disney Plus that kept putting the the audio language into German for some
reason. Oh, it happened to me too. Yeah. Subtitles? No, not the sub, the like
actual like audio. Like it would kept playing a German dub of everything.
And it happened probably three to four times that I would turn on a Simpsons
episode and it would open with Homer being like, "Grrr, grr, grr, grr!" and I'd be like, "This is an interesting choice for the episode!"
And it happened so many times and every time I fell for it.
Mmm, very funny. Oh wow.
You're one of the Conan years.
This is weird.
Mmm.
Just a completely different voice of Homer.
Yeah, it was crazy and I did fall for it every time.
They need to do a British version though,
because they did the Spanish version and like, the Brits
don't fucking know what a duff beer is, you know?
you know? No, they'd have a Duff pint. They'd call it a Duff pint. I'll have a Duff pint. I'll have a pint of Duff.
I'm Homer Thompson. I'm Homer Thompson. This is my son Bartholomew. Marguerite.
Marguerite. Marguerite. Margella. Margo. I don't know. You know how like
sometimes like British people will have like an Italian name or something?
Or like oh oh no never mind I'm thinking of Nigella that's not Italian.
Nigella, oh shit, the cook who was really hot when I was a little kid.
We'd watch those YouTube videos. You ever see that? You ever see that YouTube poop
with Nigella? No, you never saw that one? Are you thinking of Gia De Laurentiis?
No, not Gia De Laurentiis. Nigella was another one. My dad didn't know how to clear the
history. Oh, Giada. Giada De Laurentiis. Yeah, my dad didn't know how to
clear the search history. Oh man, that's a bad dad trait. I saw Giada De Laurentiis
sexy in the search bar. We're gonna have something, when we get older and we have kids, we will need to be, we need to remember that lesson. I saw that when I was seven.
I was like, uh oh. We need to remember that lesson when we get older because
there will be something like that that dads don't understand. Definitely. That we will
have to be like, fuck my dad didn't know how to. I taught my dad how to use
incognito browsing see we need we need we need to stay ahead that's the only
reason I found fake taxi in it to my dad is a
alone dude he's fucking your mom listens to this leave your dad you don't want to
put it put on blast for fake taxi you think your mom's gonna sit there being
like fake taxi he thinks it's funny about it and fake taxi fucking via me on
the fucking pot my friend chowder taught him what fake taxi shut up Taylor his
Shut the fuck up.
We called him Chowder.
Okay, then it was Taylor, it wasn't Chowder.
Dude, it's Chowder.
Fuck you.
This is, fuck you.
It's his name.
His name's Chowder.
No, his name is not Chowder.
You said you'd call him Chowder.
I'm fucking dissing you.
We called him Chowder unless we were mad at him, then we'd call him Taylor.
I'm fucking mad at you right now.
I'm gonna call you Chowder.
Why are you mad at me?
'Cause I had a friend named Chowder.
You're just making up bullshit and fucking pissing me off.
My friend Chowder.
My friend Chowder taught my dad what fake tax he was, and then my dad looked it up later,
and then we had me and my two brothers had like a Mexican standoff in the living room
saying...
A Mexican standoff?
He's just adding more letters.
Oh my god.
We had...
You remember that book A Million Little Pieces?
You're doing that shit.
No, we were all standing in the living room.
Oh, it's a million little...
Oh, I'm fucking addicted to heroin.
We were standing there and I was like, "You look at dogs' dicks for money."
You looked it up.
No, you looked it up.
It was me and my two brothers and we were yelling at each other.
You're a million little pieces right now.
I can show you.
You are a million little pieces.
I will show you.
You're on Oprah right now.
You're lying about your fucking drug use.
You're a piece of shit.
I'm not a piece of shit.
Chowder.
Chowder showed my dad fake taxis.
Shut the fuck up.
Chowder skis.
Don't put his at on.
Why?
People might, what if they like skiing?
That's true.
Yeah, it's cool.
Chowder.
Fuck you.
That's his name!
He goes by Chowder.
You made a fake Instagram.
I made a fake Instagram?
I filmed a bunch of GoPro footage of me skiing.
You did.
this you can't make so Regina's gonna hear about this who Regina don't tell
Regina I didn't make you know what I think about I've been pretty I've been
pretty crass on this up now I think it felt falls in the confines of the comedy
podcast but at least are you familiar with clowning yeah clowning when you do
this podcast you know we kind of all are yeah I'm kind of finding an inner see
we're not we're not really ourselves right and see if Regina's listening yeah
Regina Carey our HR rep. She's not a rep, she's our HR person. HR representative.
Yeah, just HR manager. Okay, manager. She's like she's probably gonna ding you for
that too and every time that she dings you I have to pay her $5,000 so just like
really yes just like maybe. Regina, we just paused the recording
after that and while it was paused Patrick said I want to ding Regina. I did
not say I want to ding Regina. I'm not saying that about fucking Regina. Let's move on.
Does Regina listen to everything?
Because she's, what do we have like 290 episodes or something right now?
She has to comb through, yes. Does she have to comb through everything?
She'll probably find this. Because if she has to comb through everything, there's a big long stretch of episodes
where you are saying that you want to fuck my butt
and you're saying that you want to put me in a dress and fuck me
and like you want to turn me into like a sex slave for you.
I didn't say sex.
You want me to become a footrest that you can nut on.
That's fucking lying.
That's what you said.
You said stuff like this.
That's fucking lying bullshit.
It's not lying bullshit.
You used to talk about wanting to have sex with me.
I used to have a fucking big crush on you and everyone knows that.
You said you wanted me to grow my hair long so that you could pull on it when you fucked
me from the back.
I don't think I said that.
I think I said certain things.
I said you would look really great in one of those dresses that teachers wear that have
pockets.
That's what I said.
(laughter)
With an apple, a denim dress with an apple at the bottom.
Yeah, you'd look really fucking pretty in one of those.
And I would laugh.
Would I fucking lift it up and fucking ram your head into a bathroom stall and fucking take you?
Yeah, if the time was right and the moment felt good.
You can't say, "Regina, please jot down 2920, that's where Caleb sexually harasses me."
I think Caleb, I remember Caleb also saying something along the lines of,
of I would like to invite you over for a dinner party
and do the popcorn trick to you but with Jell-O.
- What's the popcorn trick?
- The popcorn trick from the movie theater but with Jell-O.
(laughing)
- If we make it even louder noise,
it'd be the most conspicuous possible.
- You can see it too.
- Yeah.
- Oh, I can just--
- Clear Jell-O.
- Hey, if you want us to Jell-O with your hand.
You wanna grab some of this Jell-O out of my lap?
(laughing)
- It's like--
- It's jiggling.
It's a big cube of jello!
Sir, can I have some of your jello to enjoy? I love jello with my movies.
Oh yeah, go ahead and reach in.
Help yourself!
It's like a big, green block of jello!
Like it's ballistic jello!
It's ballistic jello and somebody's putting their hand through it!
There's a slow-mo cam on it like Mythbusters, too.
We need to invest in something.
Hey can I, can I...
You hold up the block of Jell-O like that with your ticket in it.
Hey can I, can I have some popcorn?
I'd love some popcorn.
Yeah you can have some popcorn.
Oh, I think I just dropped the last of my popcorn in the bottom of my soda.
So you'll have to reach into my soda cup.
What about just a briefcase?
That should be enough, right?
Yeah.
To get away with the...
That was what was in the Pulp Fiction briefcase.
A little movie reference for all the movie heads out there.
Marcelo Wallace's penis was in there.
Marcel the Shell's penis was in there.
Yep.
Chicken Marsala Wallace.
Chicken Marsala Wallace?
I want some chicken Marsala right now.
Tikka Masala?
Different food.
Yeah, I'm just thinking of different salas.
Tikki Mahalo.
Let's go surfing in Hawaii.
Shana Masala.
What's Shana Masala?
It's with chickpeas.
Oh yeah.
I kept trying to prepare this and
I kept trying to
- Q us into this and Caleb just drives it with them.
- I was just teeing it up.
- Oh yeah.
- He doesn't even want me involved in it anymore.
- No, I want you to get--
- Wait, what was that?
- Can we introduce it, Caleb?
- Can we introduce it then?
- What was that song?
- Can we give it its--
- Yeah, go ahead.
- This is a song, Patrick, that me and Caleb
have been working on today before you got here.
- Did you write it for me?
- We wrote it, well, for you,
but also for anybody else in the world who likes it.
- Oh yeah.
- It's about partying.
- That's like the first part of it.
- Oh yeah.
we're not really this is the same as i got this is a maybe
because sounds fucking good
uh...
to assert you don't know
well do the dance that i came up with the idea that i would have to do that
and here you know i do the day yet
see we had this on video this would look amazing it looks like he's pushing away
something yeah as i say
yeah it's a it's like a party to what's the dance called
only a lecture
arts called oh yeah yeah the other than the pusher would be a good name for the
dance within the song is already a pusher oh yeah oh yeah pet parent that
it called the pusher dot the pusher dance which are done did it but we're going
to go yeah and then in front of the at the only i did it is the rap part
all you had to push it down did it
got a major make it go sexy with it
uh... yeah you go
got my ass
writing checks up in it
asso big my pants can't fit it
got a bbl
i'm spinning it around like a spinner comma fidget
spinner comma fidget
got a bbl as a man used to be four hundred pounds now it's all in my ass
that's all my can
that's all i'm not going to get that's very uh... yeah
they should that's all i have your parents now it's not my can't wait so
they're not a good idea i would have had
waste the size of the computer pan waste the size of peter pan
uh... look like we're squidward ate the burgers
uh... look like squidward when he ate the burgers
i don't want to remember the other day to read the petties
what it was i got big
i don't remember it sponge was the cook and squibbers a server
uh... we're really not all hollow
something about something
about murder
mister i do not want to commit murder and i do not condone any murder held
this back to earth they thought they'd murder
and then
you're going to be the
singer of the song
scraped a song on my mac book refurbished
scrubbed she's a missus his name is scrubs any scrubbed any knows name is
scrubs like cuz he named himself after his favorite show that's his that's his
producer drop oh shit his bonus uh-huh his producer producer drop is I can't I
can't do this all on my own I think I just invented it I actually just said
that's bonus bonus could also mean being extra no bonus no it's good good
Dude, that shit was bonus.
That was bonus as fuck.
Dude, that's fucking good.
That's perfect.
That's the next slang, yeah.
That's bonus as in like, doing the most.
Like after you have sex, you're like, "That sex was fucking bonus."
That was bonus.
Bonus.
That shit was bonus.
That food was bonus as fuck.
Damn, like, yeah.
I just think that's a good, we need a new fucking thing.
Yeah.
You know, we're getting fucking, I'm getting sick.
You're trying to do a frindle right now, and I'm here for it.
It's not a frindle 'cause it doesn't replace a word.
And also, I accidentally said it.
And it's just a cool slang.
a friendle right now and I'm here for it. It's not a friendle because it doesn't
replace a word. And also I accidentally said it. It's just a cool slang.
Yeah. It's more like a bussin than a friendle. Yeah.
But sometimes that friendle is bussin. Did I ever tell you guys I invented
bussin? I think that I was the first guy who said bussin. I think honestly we
could get bonus going and people could start. We could see in five or six years
people saying Twitch streams. Definitely. People will say bonus. Like damn that's mad bonus. That's a bonus.
Like that shit was just bonus as hell.
Yeah.
But it's kind of close, it's like the opposite of bogus I guess,
because it's got a, it's like instead of the G you swap it for the N and now it's bonus.
Bonus or bogus.
Yeah.
That could be like a thing, that could be a sys thing.
Oh my god.
So we're going to find out today if this is bonus or bogus.
That's so good.
That could be like a new segment we do.
Hot or not, need it or keep it.
Bonus or bogus?
Remember that app Hot or Not?
No.
You put your picture up there and people rate you.
Rate my poop.
Just like that but for people's faces.
I was getting it perfect tens.
I put a picture of myself on Hot or Not and it was my face in a flatbed scanner and I had
a 4.
You had a 4?
Mhmm.
Wow.
Out of 4?
Mhmm.
I remember kids would use that app when I was 16.
Other 16 year olds would use this app.
And then it made people, it was like a self esteem ruiner for like 16 year olds.
There were so many apps like that when we were growing up.
That's just what every app is.
Poppy jump.
Poppy jump, yeah.
Can I jump?
I'm such an idiot, I can't jump.
I've never even jumped on two or three platforms.
I can't even cut this rope!
Fuck me.
I wanna fucking kill myself.
Where is my water?
I can't find it.
What was that other app?
Yik Yak?
They brought Yik Yak back though.
They brought Yik Yak back?
Yeah.
I used to, when I was at my first year of college, I used a lot of Yik Yak.
I've talked about that.
I used to just, every time I'd take a shit, I'd do like a fucking 300 word thing on it.
And then Yik Yak just became people complaining about this guy who started raiding his shits
every time he took them.
And then there was copycats too.
And people started pretending that they were me, being like, "Wow, I just took a fucking
awesome shit in this place."
But they weren't as eloquent as I am.
Yeah.
So you just write about you pooping?
And I'd describe what it looked like.
You couldn't add pictures to Yik Yak back then.
I remember.
Yeah.
And so I would just be really honest.
I would spam.
I think I would describe my critiquing style as like,
honest but fair.
You know?
- Yeah.
- And so I was doing it.
- There weren't a lot of people.
- I think, I mean.
- There weren't a lot of people back then.
The population's basically doubled.
- I think you could've taken it to the next level.
- See, I got cut off.
I was about to say the thing, but you can go.
- What's up?
- He started making fun of me for saying
there weren't a lot of people.
- No, I wasn't making fun of you.
- He was making fun of me completely.
- I wasn't making fun of you, I was just agreeing.
What was your point?
- I'm so confused.
What's happening right now?
Basically me and him are having an interpersonal conflict that's gonna get kicked right up to Regina.
Okay.
Okay? So, but you're completely out of it and I would call you a mediator at this point.
Okay, I wasn't gonna mediate.
So you don't have to, so just tell me what you're up to.
Okay, I was just gonna say that...
So you're just like a bystander.
Right, or just like a...
An accomplice.
Yeah, or like Batman.
Yeah, right.
Or Iron Man.
I was just gonna say like, I feel like you could take that to the next level and I think that it would be great...
you should bring this back and maybe rate other people's poops and they could pay you.
I would do that. Yeah, I think that's disgusting. Why? I would do anything for money. Yeah. Yeah.
That would be a good way to kind of flex your writing chops. I wouldn't do that. Yeah. Yeah.
Because that's about attention. Thomas is on there. I would do anything anonymously. Yeah.
For yeah, for money. Okay. Like maybe, like I would get. I would do an anonymous cameo. Yeah.
I would make a cameo account and it says you could be anybody. Yeah. That's good.
It's like behind a sheet so it's just a silhouette and it's a through a voice
changer. I'm just going like happy birthday to Jacob I may or may not have
been in your favorite movie. I could be anybody. Yeah I could be anybody. Marilyn Monroe.
Muhammad Ali. I don't know. Yeah yeah it could be literally anybody living or
dead. That's a great idea and you can make that fucking crazy expensive. Yeah I know.
Yeah, I just feel like and you don't have to tell it because if it's really expensive people assume that someone really yeah, exactly
Yeah, yeah, and then you could put do little hints like I hope you're I hope your birthday is is fucking great
I I wish I could be there, but I faked my own death. Oh, or did I?
Did I just say that?
Teehee and people might assume that you're either Michael Jackson or Tupac Tupac said T
Yeah, a couple times.
Yeah.
So it's a pretty good idea.
It is a good idea.
And yeah, you can charge five or six hundred bucks a pop.
Yeah, because people...
And then people also can't be mad if it ever leaks who you are because it's like, yeah,
we're anonymous.
Yeah, it could be anybody.
I remember Norman Dowell had a Cameo account and it was like three hundred dollars and
I was like, "Fuck you, man.
I'm not paying three hundred bucks."
But he knew, "Oh, I'm going to fucking die."
he was like I'm gonna make it really fucking expensive so that people people
don't know yet but there's gonna be a fucking deal okay yeah yeah so maybe you
could do that and then you could just fucking I mean back to pass away yeah
kill yourself yeah right yeah you could do a cameo that's really expensive and
it'd be like it could be like I'll do one cameo and then a media and then I
will kill myself so you will have the most valuable video in the world that'd
be a pretty good way if you were planning to kill you selling video of
some guy who is dead.
Telling video of strange long hair guy who died immediately after.
That's probably if they remade Breaking Bad today.
Cause the meth problem is pretty much unsolved.
It'd be freaking OnlyFans.
Yeah he probably would have done a fucking...
"Jesse we need to fuck."
Yeah he probably would have started fucking Jesse on camera.
It's kinda disgusting when you think about it.
That is, yeah.
And Gus would have like a whole empire.
and they're trying to work with Gus,
he's like, "I need to work with you."
I need to work with Heisenberg.
He fucks that team.
He fucks that hoodie team so good.
- That is crazy that Jesse Pinkman
is supposed to be like 19, right, when that show starts.
- Especially if you watch El Camino.
- Yeah, so funny.
- And he's 50 or 60 years old.
- Fat AF.
- Yeah.
- I wouldn't even say he's fat,
he's just got a huge round head.
- Whatever that other guy's name is, got fat AF.
- Mike.
Oh the guy who plays Todd. Yeah, Todd. What's his name? Oh, Jesse Plemons. Jesse Plemons. Yeah, he puffed up really really funny. That's hilarious
Yeah, it does a piece of shit. Oh, yeah Todd or Jesse Plemons. You know, I'm trying to see a Skylar
He didn't answer me who
Todd deserves it or Jesse Plemons deserves it Todd
Jesse you realize Friday Night Lights, you know, I did bad things in that - no, I didn't know what you know
Damn in fuck yeah in like season three the whole shows about football and then season three he covers up a
Him and a girl cover up a murder bro out of nowhere. Well, it's it makes no sense. That's not true
That's what we call the industry jumping the show just starts. Are you sure you didn't just accidentally watch season three of Breaking Bad?
The first two episode the first two seasons were like look how fucking hot these high school football players are don't you want to fuck?
Like look at these guys their abs are fucking unreal. They're popping their bicep veins
We're literally popping out 3d on screen right and then third season
It's like look at this fucking guy this fucking 80 IQ idiot kills some guy and covers it up that happened
Players man, there's a similar thing in this other show
I'm spongebob where it starts out and it's like about like sea animals about it with restaurants
Yeah fry cook, and then it's like you know seasons in or whatever you're like what the fuck is the Flying Dutchman doing here
Yeah, that's true. This is not a sea animal the flying. This is a green bit of jump in the shark
Yeah, it was like okay. I guess
You have jumping the shark is there a shark in sponge I was thinking about it yesterday, and I don't think there is I literally
Know there's a shark in the salty spittoon. Yeah, he's waiting in line, but there's not like a shark like
How could he be fucking be eating them?
That's true
It's kind of a cop-out to put us if you have like a sea show but a fucking
Octopus or a squid is like one of those like an apex predator
Yeah, but he doesn't look like like yeah Squidward is a squid, but you're not like immediately like like they did something creative with
Yes, word is a squid
Yeah, Squidward's a squid, but they did something creative with his like design. That's true. They should have just been a shark character though
I agree man
You guys you guys ran out of ideas for sea animals, and we got we have we have a freaking squirrel down here
Yeah, or a shark. I think it was a piece of plastic
piece of I read something I read something that originally Sandy was
gonna be Sandy the shark is that true she's gonna be a shark and she was gonna
still live but how would she be from Texas yeah well yeah it made no sense
for her to oh it was a juxtaposition it was a juxtaposition yeah yeah
Helen Berg that's a guy fucking must have been on fucking acid mm-hmm yeah I
I read that SpongeBob was very much inspired by the album
The Mollusk by Ween. I thought the Mollusk came out after SpongeBob. No. Really? The Mollusk came first.
I thought the Mollusk was like 2001. No.
2001 was when the Ween made Quebec. Oh. Or yeah, I think 2002?
2001? The Mollusk is you can you it sounds like a SpongeBob album. The first song? Yeah. What's that song?
I'll be dancing in the show tonight. Yeah, it's all that sounds like SpongeBob and Patrick. It's basically all just SpongeBob music. Yeah
You imagine being a ween and being like that most impactful thing we ever did was SpongeBob. That's not true
Yeah, it is. Come on. SpongeBob is a way bigger cultural phenomenon. Yeah, what else than ween? What else they were in the movie?
It's Pat no way
SpongeBob I think without SpongeBob probably most people our age would be very different. Yeah
There would be no reaction me mostly the big the big show imagine YouTube poop
Well the first YouTube poop ever was toys gone wild which was Toy Story
So without - okay, so without Toy Story and Spongebob. Yeah, what about yeah and without cartoons or animation?
If there was no TV, we'd all be a little bit different. I'll say it tunes are good tunes
Are you really good good for you? Yeah, I've been saying that for fucking years. I can't wait tomorrow morning
See kids in central. Oh my god. Oh Saturday Saturday morning. So I feel like I feel like the people who listen to this show
Don't listen to it exact right when it comes out because that's when all yeah, we need to change the schedule. Yeah
Using a whole audience there's like a bunch it's like splitting the ratings. It's like obviously our audience is heavily tuned
Tuned fans. Yeah, so they're fucking - splitting off. They're sitting in front of their why do we release this on Saturday morning?
on the TV cabinet, they're like a bowl of cereal on their stomach, they're on the ground, and
they're watching fucking tunes.
Yeah, you know like a balanced breakfast, like cereal, banana, orange juice, two pieces of
toast, bacon, eggs.
And a go-gurt.
And a go-gurt, yeah.
And a go-gurt is big.
The healthiest thing you can eat.
I think we can change these Saturday episodes into tunes, and then we can put them on TV.
You are a fucking genius.
Put them on TV, then people will, even more people will flock to them.
You know what I think?
So it's a Saturday morning tune.
I think instead of putting them on TV, we need to put you in the fucking White House.
I won't say no.
Okay, you can't say no.
Because you're the fucking president.
You should be the president.
Oh, as the president?
You're a fucking genius.
Yeah.
I thought you meant as a visit.
Fuck no.
Dude, that's a lot of responsibility.
I don't give a shit.
You need to do that.
Because you could probably save every single part of this world.
I guess I probably could.
Yeah, especially when you have ideas like, we could change tunes.
Like, that would fucking blow minds and send ripple waves.
I would be giving a speech and I would say we need to change tunes and I would do the politician hand.
Yes. And you could do it as an homage to Dr. Martin Luther King Jr.
Uh huh. I have a dream that tunes will be changed.
Yeah. To be Saturdays and Sundays.
And every day. And every day after school though so that it doesn't interrupt your morning routine.
or very early before school so that it teaches kids to wake up early. I'm not
gonna lie I used to watch a couple of tunes before I went off to school.
I used to play I would either watch baby looney tunes or I would play
Ocarina of Time. Bro I would play Gameboy. It's almost like we had three
fucking like separate but parallel upbringings. Wow. Yeah. Did you guys
ever go to after school program? Yeah. Do your after school program have game boy time? I
tried to get my mom to take me to boys and girls class. I didn't have an after school
program as much as it was called, so like the periods of our day was like A period through
A through H period or whatever. And I had something called I period which was a, I had
to stay after school and do my homework in a classroom because I wouldn't do homework.
like after school. What kind of kid does homework man? Yeah. That's bullshit. I used to have
to stay after school because they were like you aren't doing your homework and you need
to do homework in a room with a teacher who doesn't, who wants to watch the Beatles on
YouTube the whole time. This is a big memories episode. Yeah. A little bit of a flalalala.
Back into time. Flalalala. Like that's the sound that it makes when you remember stuff
like this. And we go and we got back into our childhoods. Yeah. In my after school everyone
bring their Game Boy and their Nintendo DS or like a few the few kids who had like a Nintendo DS would
bring it and everybody else they would have the new Pokemon game that just came out and everybody
else would sit would gather just a huge crowd of people around them and just watch them play it and
be like do that do that do that and then eventually the that like after school program was like okay
now you can only we're creating Game Boy time where you can only play it from this time to this
time because it's all anybody does and I really I would love to I miss the experience of standing
behind the kid who had whatever Pokemon game just came out and being like, "What is that
Pokemon?" I really wish that maybe people could do that on the subway or something.
I do that. You can watch me. You can come over to my house and watch me play Arceus.
I need a big crowd of people.
Okay.
I need, I want, I want...
Or we should just do fucking Madison Square Garden.
Yeah.
That works for me.
Do you guys think in a year's time, if we do, you guys are familiar with like Jim Carrey's
whole philosophy, right?
No.
Which is like, if you say stuff into the world, it happens. So can we just say like a year
Law of Attraction. Yeah Law of Attraction. That's Jim Carrey's philosophy? I call it Jim Carrey's
philosophy. Why did he say that? Because he just said that once. Oh. He said one time
he went on the top of a mountain when he was like 19 and he was like I would... He
went to the top of a mountain, are you thinking of the Grinch? No he was like I
fucking hate Christmas and then he ended up making the Grinch later. Well I think
it's not what you said. What did he say on top of the mountain? It sounds like he sounds like he was
it happened in the Grinch. I could be misremembering this I remember him saying
at some point. He's such a dickhead. He went to the top of a mountain... he's dope. I heard he
assassinated his girlfriend. Yeah, with herpes. No, he assassinated her like
literally fucking Hitman 2, like one of the options. Like he speed ran. I heard
you put her casket down a water slide when the cameras were off. He went to the top of a
mountain when he was not a famous actor. Right. He probably did a crazy thing with
his arms and legs and made a weird Scrooge face and he said I want to be a
famous actor that's okay and then it happened so I want to be a famous
explain that with anything scientific or spiritual so what I'm saying is spiritual
we need to say outside preferably so that more of the world hears us next
year we want to do a fucking full Madison Square Garden live show with
sold out and so it sold out, maybe a flame and rides and a ride rides and
rides. So the carnival now we don't want to do a carnival that cheapens it. It's
a sir in Madison, sir, sir, sir, to podcast about lists. So we'll have so
we'll have different stuff.
We'll have tons of animals. I'm talking dogs, cats. That's like the best idea
you've ever had. Cirque de podcast about lists. I know we've talked about having
a carnival before but circuit the podcast about list is like next level that is
ingenious that's like camp vlog not level genius it's better than camp
probably yeah that's a way better fucking suck my dick camp vlog no I
don't want that picture like it was like they some guy like going around doing
like fashion photography of people at camp vlog now and there's that kid who's
wearing like head to toe and golf like golf of the floor shit and just looks
like like fucking shit. It's so funny like the whole like it's so funny that
that's what Tyler the Creator turned into. I'm pretty sure we've beaten this
conversation to death but just like every song that he has now is just like...
We've definitely talked about this aspect of Tyler the Creator a million times.
Yeah where it's like every song used to be like "I'm gonna rape a triceratops and call it a f***"
turn it into turn it into a porcupine this guy sounds a lot like scrub daddy
does it Tyler the Creator kind of did rip off scrub daddy I think maybe cuz scrub
daddy is like an OG from the bay scrub daddy was bonus and Tyler's bogus yeah
basically yeah Tyler the Creator you bogus scrub though scrub daddy was like
like ten toes down basically ten toes down hyphy as a yeah he's thizzing on
As I would say he was like people would call him the slow e40
Yeah, cuz he already was so fast e40 is fast within scrub. Daddy was like I
Love to rap
Not that fast. Yep. I write a song it goes not to it goes long
Yeah, because of how long it takes me to think of a word
I'm the slowest freestyler in the bay. Yep
I'm not fast like a horse. No, do I eat? Hey, no, do I know?
Nor do I eat hey, he's one of the first rappers to say nor yeah
And now
Staples nor neither all that song nor nor yeah nor or yeah
Completely ripped off scrub daddy. I agree also all these a bunch of female rappers were because scrub daddy had many saw even a whole
Album called my my big butt and now female rappers are releasing songs that are called things like my big
But he has a thing about getting a BBL and nobody knew what a BBL was in 1993
Yeah, he was in the bay. They called it a bay a bay area, but lift back
It was be it was called the BAB got it done in a fucking it was called a babble
Yeah, I got it done on the BART train. Yeah area
Yeah, I still have my if anyone wants my Clipper card
What's a clip?
The Bart I have
775 I took the bus one time did Bart when you were riding the Bart train over there in the Bay Area. Do you ever think?
Bart I did really yeah
Actually, I don't think was the Bart. I think no it wasn't the Emory go-around the one the one in and
The the public transit in Atlanta's got a Marta. Yeah, I always think of it as just like oh
Driving down the highway and see Marta go over heading I was on the bar
I was on the Bart going to
Fart from my Bart I was on I was on a Bart train I'd ride first-class. Hey here comes the meal
What is it but my shorts?
I was on the bus. Holy fuck. Oh my god, this really is the Bart Train. I was on the bus going to Berkeley for something and
Bart Bus? Berkeley?
The bus driver stopped at a stop. There was like three people there.
Holy shit.
And he didn't open the doors for them. He just stopped the bus in front.
Maybe his route was done or something, but he stopped the bus in front of these people
people and then sat, laid down on like the handicap seats and just started watching a
video on his phone for like five minutes and then he just got up and drove the bus and didn't
even pick those people up.
That's sick.
Wow.
That was like, I remember I was sitting there just like...
Probably the wrong route.
Sitting on my butt on the BART bus to Berkeley.
My butt takes up too many seats.
I gotta sit in the handicapped space.
I have a rhyme here so you basically just ruined it and said handicapped space for no reason
Doesn't rhyme. Yeah, you're just waiting on my butt on the Bart bus to Berkeley. My butt is weighing down the bus
It can't move quirkily
See and instead you said that too quick. That doesn't sound like screw
This sounds - I should have done it slower so you could have interrupted in the first half of my sentence
Slow
Fist bump destroyed fucking destroyed
Regina will be hearing about that. He said fuck you to me.
What? I didn't even fucking catch that. Yeah, you said F-U-C-K to him? He said fuck you destroyed to me.
Destroy? Regina, right? 56-42.
All right, so you got a couple of timestamps. So that's fucking $10,000 out of our paychecks. Yeah, it's funny
I will say also, I mean don't want to point throw blame here
But Patrick was also making some interesting jokes about handicapped spaces right before this one.
- Well, I'm disabled.
- I think Regina will have to, you know.
- I'm completely disabled.
- We can let Regina kind of look over your--
- And I'm laughing at my pain.
- Your medical documents and figure some stuff out
about that.
- I'm chronically ill.
- What's your disability?
- Fibro...
Dialga.
(laughing)
- Really?
- It's a different from fibromyalgia.
- Yeah.
- It's what you get when you sit on the couch
and play Pokemon for too long.
- What are you talking about?
I have to sit on the couch and play Pokemon
because of my disability.
5729, Cameron making fun of my disability.
That's true.
All right guys, that's $15,000 that has been wiped out by Regina.
Not wiped out, sorry.
That's 20 now.
5739, Caleb diminishing Regina's job.
Stop giving the time stamps.
We're in so much debt to her already.
Belittling Regina.
You know what I should start doing?
I should be like Mark Cuban.
You know?
Where like Mark Cuban, he does an NBA interview and he says, "I'm a fan of yours, I'm a fan
of yours, I'm a fan of yours, I'm a fan of yours, I'm a fan of yours, I'm a fan of yours,
I'm a fan of yours, I'm a fan of yours, I'm a fan of yours, I'm a fan of yours, I'm a fan
what I should start doing is to be like Mark Cuban, you know? Where like Mark Cuban,
he does an NBA interview and he says, "Yeah, all I wanted was the
fucking win." And then the news person or whatever says, "Well, you know you just
said the F word on live TV so the league is gonna fine you $50,000 that goes to
charity." And he'll go, "Oh yeah? Well, fuck it, fuck you, fucking bitch."
Whoa. It's pretty fucking badass. That is crazy. Yeah, because then he's giving $200,000
to charity right and he doesn't know the charity could be some fucking pro slatery
fucking charity. It's probably a charity for swearing. Donald Sterling
Defense Fund. That's what it was back when they filmed that it was
Donald Sterling's Defense Fund. The DSDF. Yeah. Yeah. What was his whole thing?
Donald Sterling. He was the Clippers guy. He was the Clippers guy and he would complain
about his girlfriend talking to the black guys on the team or something. Oh
- Oh yeah.
- I think that's what it was.
- He said the N word too.
- Yeah, yeah, he said the N word
and then there's that interview
with his girlfriend or something.
I forget what she says,
but it's the funniest fucking thing in the world.
Do you remember that one?
- Honestly, I think I got into basketball
the year after all that stuff.
I got in like 2014, 2015. - Really?
I never got into basketball, but I love drama.
- Yeah, you are a bit of a drama hog.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- 5908, Caleb making fun of my weight.
What? That wasn't about your weight. You look fucking really good.
I almost said it earlier, but then I was like,
"Nah, he's gonna think that's a sexual harassment thing and fucking write it down."
59, 17, Caleb sexually harassing.
*gibberish*
I'm saying that you're-
59, 22, Cameron making fun of my speech impediment.
I'm saying that your body is looking very healthy-
Joke's on Patrick.
And like you've lost some weight and you look fucking-
You look like...
You look good.
59, 33, Caleb's fatphobia.
Joke on Patrick.
- Because of all the weird pausing stuff we did,
that timer is not right and he's giving wrong timestamps.
So Regina will not be able to find any of this.
- Okay, so you tricked her,
so that means that I can keep doing it.
- 59.48.
- I wish you were fatter so I could put you in a corset
and bind parts of your body to my liking.
Just completely model you like clay.
- I guess I'm completely stumped here.
- Yeah, 'cause you can't do anything.
- Yeah.
Wow.
Caleb wants me to not be able to do anything so then he can have his way with me.
I'd say that's about accurate.
Yeah.
Yeah. I want you in a wheelchair.
What?
So I can sit on you.
You can't say that to somebody with fibro-dialga because that could actually happen one day.
One day. I think when you hit 30 or...
When I turn 30 I'm going to be in a rascal scooter.
Mm-hmm. I'm gonna be in a rascal scooter cuz I can't walk around the mall and he's gonna go around saying I'm gonna give you the
most aggressive lap dance of your life
Not in my rascal don't give me a lap dance in my rascal scooter we're gonna give you a tracheotomy
60 minutes when you're somewhere in the around there Caleb says he's gonna give me a wheelchair. I'm gonna I'm gonna slam my butt down
on your car i don't know if there's a rascal it's gonna turn your wheelchair to
a t_p_ it's a rascal scooter it has a basket in the front so i can put all the
bags of chips and other stuff somebody in the house if they hang on your body and
daggering on some of the i'm gonna get a but pogo stick involved yet
seriously you know and i was all here's a restricts the uh... i'm going to go on
installed and i'm gonna get involved with it
i'm a pack your body like a fucking bird
uh... i'm gonna do appears perry style trick to you or a shoot
coconut out of my butthole and your head. A coconut wouldn't fit in your fucking beautiful
tight butthole. It's not that tight. I'm gonna Mario Ground pound you. I'm just gonna fall
on you, trust fall like a fucking thwomp. The past two minutes. Yeah, legendary podcasting.
The past two minutes we owe Regina so much fucking money. I think at this point we owe
her $75,000. I'm looking at your hat and it's reminding me that I meant to get a stinger
installed that shoots, that infects you with my cum.
70, uh, $80,000.
I'm gonna get, I'm gonna get like, I'm gonna get, I'm gonna get like cyborg clamps on the
backs of my legs so I can sit on your lap and you can never get me off.
But I'm gonna get you off.
I'm gonna put you on, I'm gonna give you a house arrest anklet, right?
But it only, it goes off if you leave my diaper.
$100,000 to Regina.
We owe her $100,000 because she's going to have to look into all these disputes.
No, this is all fair use.
There's no dispute here.
This is all fair use.
This is fair use.
Because I'm going to use you and it's not going to be fair.
Do you think they have fair use in sexual harassment claims?
I don't know, but I...
Your Honor, I plead fair use.
I plead I was doing a parody of a sexually deviant co-worker like Rob Schneider.
You're gonna get a pair of these.
You're gonna get a pair of those.
I'm pointing to lingerie and you're gonna be stuck in them.
They're gonna be fucking super glued to your body, right?
Gorilla glue actually, right?
And I'm gonna put got to be glued in your hair so you have a mohawk.
Wouldn't really be a mohawk because you'd have to shave the sides of my head down.
I was going to get to that.
I'm going to shave the sides of your head down.
I'm going to give you a mohawk.
I'm going to spray the Jordan logo into it.
With spray paint, not the hair kind.
Right?
So it's going to be permanent.
I'm going to be a Bugs Bunny cannonball into you.
I'm going to be a bug on you.
And I'm going to play a game where you have to swat at me away.
Bite your butt.
Wow, I can't believe all this is falling on your fair youths.
I'm going to rename myself the bed bug.
I will. Me and a lot of friends are going to bite you. And you're going to walk in, it's
going to be me and my crew 5,000 deep in your bed. Right? We're going to be rolling hard.
I'm going to get trapped in an industrial machine and become Flat Stanley and I'm going
to hide inside your entire outfit. I am going to put glue paper down around the office so
I can't catch you. And you're going to get stuck. And I'm going to forget that you're
here. I'm going to go out of town and when I come back you will have gnawed your legs
off. So, yeah you better be fucking excited for that. And I'm gonna come back and be like
"Ah fucking god damn it, I didn't even catch him, he ate his legs and died."
Oh no. Shit.
You would have my feet.
Well, hey buddy, you're gonna talk like Elmer Fudd when I'm done with you. You're gonna
be fucking, every other word you're gonna be mispronouncing, right?
I'm gonna turn you into a Christmas tree.
I'm gonna put a Christmas tree...
That's it.
Yeah, we can leave it at that. That's fine.
Alright buy tickets to the live show. Oh, yeah, Halloween. Hey if you're listening to this
Yesterday night. I'll be on a show tonight
so
I'll be on a show while we're recording this. I'm mostly telling this to Caleb and Cameron
Can you guys please come to this show? I can't do it tonight. I'm sorry. I have other where is this
We'll do this off. Yeah, I don't I can't feel like you put me on the spot here
Yeah, you're trying to put you on this place trying to be like with everybody with thousands of people listening what will you?
Yeah, will you hang? I have a date night tonight. I can't I'm sorry. I can't do it
You can't go on a date to bite didn't watch me before. Yeah, that's a pretty common date to be fair
It's going to be better perform. He's pretty much. I mean he's basically an effort
It's locked in my funny set I can't do it tonight if you would if you schedule a different night
I posted it on Instagram all week!
On my stories! I posted it on my stories all week and you didn't see it!
He's not watching my stories!
That's what I was gonna do.
And he's not a good friend.
You can't have to do this while recording, it's very rude.
I think it's ruder to ditch out on your buddy.
I'm not ditching out, I...
I'm doing it in a costume.
a whole fucking costume. What's the costume? Aristocratic costume. I'm gonna be dressed
in a powdered wig and stuff. I'm gonna be dressed up like a judge. A judge? A classic aristocrat.
Yeah. A southern belle. Southern belle. I'm there. Okay. Go buy tickets to the live show.
- Go buy a ticket to the live show,
and then we also have,
no, nevermind.
- What?
- We have a Twitch channel,
and Jubio runs it. - Yes, that's true.
- Is on that, okay.
What else do we have?
- Don't you have a show?
- I don't think so, maybe, I don't know.
- Do you?
- I'm definitely not.
- Do we have tour dates?
- No.
- Not yet, I mean, except for the show
that we already know about on how--
okay yeah i guess it's our only toward it
yeah we're gonna be a lot of all
yeah i will be in at the there isn't anything coming up though actually you
have to go see the halloween show yeah and there is never be anything after
that so that there is a lot of being so i think there's nothing
thing.