Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- I do think it's, I feel like it's un,
it's un-gentlemanly to be,
to let people hear your shit.
- No.
- Yeah.
- I just don't.
- I think it lets people's guards down.
- You guys don't have the sound.
- It's female.
- You're not dealing with the sound that I am though.
- Yeah, well.
- My sounds are.
Do you think that that faucet is loud enough? Yeah, it's nothing
We need a faucet that just goes like yeah
Yeah
Get in my Ford Focus and the Bluetooth automatically connects
Because it's cuz it starts with yeah, it's 1,000 parts so it starts with a number so it plays it first
I don't want that
You want that or if the uber guy is like you want to play music?
I'm like, I want to hear for like you want like regular music or like fart noises. Yeah, I asked him that
He doesn't know what I'm saying. He's yeah
Yeah, you have you have to have also you know those the like
the adapters that people have for their cars where it like goes over the radio signal or whatever.
Yeah.
You just look through their car window and see what channel they're tuned to and use the app
on your phone and play fart noises into their car.
Telling the Uber driver like, "Oh yeah, like I have a... I've been writing this song for a while."
And then just loading up the first 1000 farts in a row by Caleb.
One time me and Neil got into an... I may have said this before. Me and Neil were in an Uber once
and...
Oh, I've heard this.
The guy was playing just, you've heard it so I gotta stop?
Yeah.
The guy was playing just an audio, just audio book of some guy speaking in another language
and we didn't know what it was. And Neil was like, "What is this? I really like it."
And the guy was like, "It's the Quran." And he was like, "Oh yeah, can you send it to me?"
And the guy was like, "You want me to send you the Quran?" He was like, "Yeah, yeah, yeah."
I don't think they ever linked up after that though.
Yeah?
Yeah. But it did sound cool. It was like music playing behind it.
The Quran sounds really cool.
It was fucking dope. It was just fucking cool made up words.
I think it was like Ocarina of Time got, there's like a lost...
Aquafina.
Oh yeah.
In the soundtrack.
Cause it's like literal like a verse from the Quran.
I think that there are a bunch of old video games where...
He didn't realize how evil it was at the time.
He just slipped it in.
For some reason it's in the Shadow Temple.
It's, you know, it's all fucked up.
And they deleted it?
Yeah, they deleted it.
That's fucked up.
like Osama bin Laden listening to the soundtrack and be like this is
disrespectful. Yeah. Also there's a David Byrne and Brian Eno song that is just like
verses from the Quran. Osama bin Laden was listening to that. That doesn't even piss me off even a
little bit. Osama bin Laden probably also would have been pretty pissed off at how
feminine Link was. No he wouldn't. Didn't he love like... that has to be fake right?
the like Osama Bin Laden, the hard drive. Yeah, obviously it's all declassified by the CIA.
They're gonna throw like little like, like, oh yeah Osama was looking up like Tom and Jerry naked.
He was, he was, he was typing into a text note document just a hundred times a day. I am evil,
I am evil, I am evil, I am evil. But did, what, didn't he, wasn't he also like watching
The Simpsons and stuff? That's pretty cool. That's, that's normal, yeah. Yeah. He had a
Tom and Jerry clip on it. I remember Tom and Jerry specifically. Well, the thing is, we don't know
of whether that was on his hard drive of stuff he liked or stuff he hated. That was
kind of Obama and him. Yeah Tom and Jerry action. He had custom Tom and Jerry episodes made to edit out the
racist stuff. Yeah. You know call him what you can but you know he was not a racist
by any means. No he was a lot of things but not a racist. Was a good guy. Do you think he
saw Iron Man? I think he saw Iron Man when he, minutes before he passed. When it
happened in real life. Yeah. To him too. I feel like they only get like he could only
pirate like sequels or something like Iron Man 2 and 3 it was like they got to
make like an origin story I feel like I'm just dropped into the middle of the
action what is going on where is the second Iron Man in here yeah we have
Thomas with us also oh yeah what's up Thomas oh hey yeah Thomas in the big
city are you scared of how tall the buildings are here the first time it
I almost got dizzy. I'm used to being able to see just like, I'm not used to hills really at all.
You know, I go up a hill, I don't know what's on the other end.
And the streets are all, you know, you can't even see the sky that much.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Are you talking about being inside?
Are you saying inside you can't see the sky?
Outside you can't see the sky that much.
As much of it.
Because the buildings are blocking the sky.
Right. Oh, sky's too tall here.
If I if I could change two things about New York, I'd say make it less walkable.
Yeah. Mayor Thomas, let's let's Mayor Thomas is awful.
You know, every place that people want to hang out, they're like, oh, it's only
like a three hour walk.
And yeah, it's only like six miles.
And then you can go there, you can get it like half a beer and a cigarette.
Like it's such a good time.
And you go there's just a regular bar.
And then they're like, well, there's this other bar that's close.
It's only two miles walking wise.
Yeah.
Awful.
Yeah, that's pretty bad.
Yes, Thomas does not want to hang out with me.
What else are you changing as Mayor of New York?
I would say we need to rezone a lot of stuff.
In what? Which direction?
If we could, I think we should demolish a lot of like Bushwick and stuff and put like more like
high-income like high-rises there.
Stuff like that.
And maybe like a six-lane freeway through the middle of Manhattan.
Yeah.
There's a lot we could do.
Definitely.
Just straight down the middle.
A lot of potential.
It's not connected to anything. It goes into everything.
Yeah, just Fifth Avenue turns into six lanes.
And it has a cul-de-sac at the end maybe.
Right. I think too, maybe more factories.
Factories could be good.
I mean, you always are saying,
"Oh, this would be a great place for my factory."
I've been looking for a good spot to put my factory.
So far, I think,
top, top of my list, so far,
Yellowstone. I think it would be a perfect spot.
There's a lot of... Also, there's already so much
fucking smoke going in there.
There's some shit going in the air there.
fucking million clouds of black.
Yeah, there's so much water in Yellowstone that you can just
contaminate with like,
I would say my second choice would probably be the entire
surface area of Guam. Yeah, Guam is gone. Factory Island. I
used to be big on Guam. But like, I don't know. I don't even
go there that much anymore. Really? Yeah. Damn. I feel like
it fell off. It changed a lot. Yeah.
Yeah, honestly, got guys.
Guam got gentrified to fuck. And it's all shit now. It's fucking
Bullshit over at Guam there used to be fucking dope ass bars that had like mechanical bowls and shit. Yeah, all that's fucking gone
That's my girl said as micro breweries and Astro pose. I'll get a Michelob ultra
Guam weird, right? Yeah, then the only way the only way to keep Guam weird is to you know
I guess just let more of these fucking like pieces of shit move in. Mm-hmm and now
They don't even have Dave and Buster's there anymore. Yeah, which is like a cool weird indie thing. Yeah
Yeah, half the people there don't even speak Guamese anymore. Yeah, so almost a lost language. Yeah, it's almost like no one even
It's almost like it never existed. Yeah, you go up to someone you'll be like
And they don't even say anything back. They say you're being weird man. Exactly. They give you that
Yeah, I'm stare you try and order the big special. Yeah
Thousand yard stare. Yeah
It's basically bullshit now and I see that same thing happening in New York City now. Mm-hmm. Yeah, yeah
no one speaking Guamese. Almost nobody speaks Guamese here anymore. You go to
Chinatown and you start speaking Guamese and they act like you're some kind of
complete stranger. Yeah. They act like they're not even friends with you. Yeah.
They act like they don't even speak Guamese. Yeah. You try and order a
chopped cheese, mock, Guamese style, yeah you're getting kicked out of the
establishment. That's right, yeah. Yeah, because the Guamese... Well, because they speak and they don't
like that you're talking about. Guam is northern Canada. It's like there's around like where
the ocean is. Oh, so it's like, okay. Well I was gonna, okay. Well I fucked myself over.
I was gonna say that Guamese style chopped cheese is just, it's in between two banana
leaves. Well it's near Guamatala. Yeah. Around where Central is. It's like it's peninsula
- The peninsula as well.
- Oh, so it's the peninsula of Guamatala.
- So it's attached to that, but it's on a different,
but there's a border.
- Yeah.
- And the river as well.
- Yeah, it's also, it's kind of close to Planet Crazy.
- Yeah.
- Which is a place that doesn't even exist.
- Do you think if you traveled outside of the US,
like Europe and Canada excluded,
do you think you would get sex trafficked immediately?
- Me?
- Yeah, all three of us.
- No, not me.
- No.
Why would any of us get sex traffic? I'm a dime a dozen in Europe a guy like me.
Yeah. Yeah. You might get sex sex traffic. Where?
To Romania I think you might be a Romanian slave. Do I have to be?
You might be like yeah you might be like a werewolf kind of. Yeah.
I think they might honestly burn you if you went to a small Romanian village.
You you look like you already. Yeah no I'm the one.
You look like you would capture him. They'd ship you back to like a vampire circus.
Cameron would be like a dungeon master for Andrew Tate.
yeah he's like cranking the old yeah i like
many past if i didn't know what the wheel went to that would be my dream job
back
it was a there's a there's a outlaw so i couldn't wheel cranks like a user here
what was going on but i just got to turn the wheel and feel it go
i agree and to be that way she had a right to get tighter
and then you do instead of what ok one more night in your free time
no that uh... those of the wheels are a bit higher than a decade ago we'll get
fucking tighter. And then they make you stop turning the wheel and then a few hours later
you start turning again and it feels completely different. Exactly. You do that 20-30 times
a day. I think I work at some kind of orange juice factory or something. I don't know what
this is. Oh my god. Yeah you have like a big iron gate and it's like a bunch of like ring
light ambience behind you just coming from all the rooms. Yeah the shackles, I mean I
would hate to have to clean the shackles because they're always getting blood on them from
And that blood is gonna cause rust yeah, it's a liquid on a metal, and it's not like a nice patina. These aren't like copper
Shackles there. They're war made out of just dog shit steel. Yeah, they put dog shit in the smelting process
Yeah, I'm you can't make
girls out of metal
Yeah, that'd be bad. Yeah. Yeah, what would be like a reason why they be that be bad though because of rust
Like when they got older yeah, yeah
Women had rust when they got older yeah on top all those
Would yeah, yeah, there are they already get like uglier yeah, and also really gross they get disgusting yeah
There's so much added texture on top. He was a penny. Yeah
And a penny the reason it's that color it's rust my grandma looks like a penny though. Yeah, you have a brown grandma
tanning skin cancer oh
Like a dime oh oh
She was completely silver and she started to run and now she's her it's in her urn leave her outside for too long
She turns green - yeah
It's true. That's what happens to grandma
My grandma my grandma's as beautiful as ever we saw your grandma two weeks ago. She's lovely dude. I love my damn grandma
Mm-hmm
Well, I think she's dying in a storm right now
She's flooding. She told me she just moved to a place and she was like, yeah
We just moved in this house and the owner said last she was like pointing at the ground
She's like last time there was a hurricane
She said they just whole thing flooded about six feet into the house and she was like and we got this storm coming next week
So who knows I was like don't tell me that just let me find let me find out you died from a phone call
I don't want to be like anticipating it right like you know, yeah, just that place that she was at this
That's definitely gonna flood dude. Yeah, she lived in the bottom of a crater. Yeah, yeah, that place was crazy. Yeah, the address was
Yeah, they could do worse
worse. She doesn't even know I do this. They could do way worse. They could become her new
grandson and her new favorite grandson. I think they have pretty tough competition because
I'm not even her favorite grandson. It was also crazy. Who's her favorite grandson? The
other three, Ty. When she was telling us too that last time they had a hurricane at that
house the winds blew all those battle axes and swords off the wall. They were flinging
them around the room. I said, "You gotta get rid of this collection." She said, "They're
antiques. Yeah, this is an antique boulder. Yeah, this is an antique spike that I hang
right above my bed. And all the electricity from the walls came out. Well yeah, she let
it all out. I said, "Why are there frayed wires everywhere?" She said, "Those are antiques."
Yeah, it's antique crash box merch. Those are called electricity shooters. Yeah, this
used to be Thomas Edison's house. They shoot electricity. Yeah, I have those because they
shoot electricity. My house has a superpower. It's so cool they named a whole city in Jersey
after Thomas Edison. Yeah that's really fucking cool. It is cool. It's cool they named a whole
city after him. You invent one lightbulb and everyone's like damn okay. What state is it?
Jersey. Pennsylvania, they got a, I mean it's way cooler they named it after Hershey. Yeah.
That's a way cooler. Yeah you're right. Who gives a fuck about Edison? And that lady,
Kitty Hawk. They named the whole place after her. I don't think so. I don't think that's
I don't know that was way before women could have things named after them really now you got everything about a named after Mary's Bank
Mrs.. St. Mary was not even a woman dude what she's a fucking saint. It's different. Yeah
Yeah, I guess if you you become a saint you renounce all the only girl saying stuff. Yeah, there's a little bit
St.. Elizabeth St.. Elizabeth, and then that's the last one oh
I think you're thinking of Queen Elizabeth who read no no
No, cuz saying that st. Elizabeth was the hospital. I was born at
That's not a girl then. Oh really? Yeah. Because it's a hospital? It's a hospital.
Alright, that makes sense. That does make sense. I was born at New Hanover County
Hospital. Which saint is that? Huh? That's not a saint. I think that's a free clinic.
New Hanover County Hospital? Yeah, you were born in an urgent care? Yeah. That
That would make a little sense, I think, with my head shape.
It's just an urgent care.
It's like a John Mellencamp song.
"I'm calling in an urgent care."
I gotta give this guy a rash medicine, I'll be back to deliver your baby.
There's multiple people in here with gunshot wounds.
You can just push that out yourself, I think.
I didn't go to the hood.
Yeah, you did.
No, I didn't.
I was giving you a layup there, you could have said you were born in the hood.
Okay, I was born in the hood.
He said, "Man, I ain't delivering no white ass babies."
They did say that.
And then they saw me and they were like, "I'll make an exception."
"I'll make an exception."
They saw you?
Yeah, they saw me.
Because I just started coming out, they saw my feet.
I have black feet.
They saw me and they knew I was going to be different.
Nobody in the whole room helping you?
(laughter)
- Yeah, it was pretty awesome getting born there.
You were born in a bathtub.
- No.
- Oh, swimming pool.
- Regular hospital.
- Regular hot tub.
- In Weatherford, Texas.
- I thought you were a home birth.
- Me too, for some reason.
- I thought that you were born in an inflatable pool
inside of a house.
- I thought you were--
- That's not true.
- Are you Saudi Arabian or am I wrong on that too?
- I'm completely white.
not even saudi at all
not only were born into a shoebox either
regular shoes in a bed in a hospital at the award whatever they said that they
got
in the hospital you know it's only a line here's making you know you know
whatever happens in hospital you were born in a fucking saudi arabia that you
were born in a sleeping bag i don't think saudi arabians take regular baths
whoa
well you can say that because you are saudi
That's true, yeah.
No, they probably have some weird kind of bath.
Scrooge McDuck jump into a bunch of, whoa.
I don't know.
What?
Dog blood?
I've heard about it.
(laughing)
You can read the article.
You've heard that?
(laughing)
Is that a Vice article or something?
No, I wrote it.
(laughing)
On the way here.
Oh my God.
So you could bring up the anecdote.
I was interviewing a guy at the store
and he told me all of that.
Oh wow.
Yeah.
Wow.
Have you been, I know that last time you were here,
you some got you got you seem like a magnet for crazy people from everything
I could hear
I'm attacked at all yet no I really got attacked on the train
we didn't get attacked we got we got into a mild argument
which was settled peacefully yeah I'm
you know that you were gonna I said I would I think I threatened to fuck that
guy
yeah you know that's how you I'm the negotiator
yeah yeah yeah closer exactly for kind of
(laughing)
- We were on the train, our friend like,
didn't get his footing right,
accidentally bumped into a woman twice
and this guy started freaking out at us.
- He bumped into a woman twice?
- Yeah, like he wasn't holding onto the pole.
Yeah, the guy was like, "Do that shit again!
"Do that shit again, I'll beat the fuck out of you!"
And then, fuck, what else?
The fucking, it was going on for like 20 minutes.
- And then you started negotiating.
- Yeah, then the negotiation--
- And that's a smart move 'cause in New York
you never know who you're talking to.
You might be like, if you don't stop, I'm gonna fuck you.
And then the guy says, son, I'm actually the CEO
of Bain Capital and you're exactly the kind of go-getter
we need in the boardroom.
- I remember you looked at the guy and you said,
he started laughing in your face, I remember,
and he went, ha ha ha, ha ha ha ha,
and then you said, I'm rock hard right now.
- You know, that's what we call the jester's gambit.
in the negotiating team.
That's something they teach you at West Point.
- I forgot about that.
- So you're doing like hostage stuff?
- Yeah, usually like growing up we'd kidnap people
and then just for like pranks,
and we'd have like a walkie talkie.
We didn't have batteries for them,
but we'd just stand close to each other
and we'd negotiate.
And usually it wouldn't work and we couldn't let them go.
But towards the end there,
like last couple years we had several people let go.
- That's great.
- You ever kidnap a child?
- Not that I can remember.
- Hard to negotiate with a child.
They're fucking, terrible twos.
- I don't think you usually negotiate
with the person you kidnap though.
- Well, but if they had kid parents too.
- That's a good point, I didn't think about that.
- I mean, I guess that doesn't make any sense.
- Honestly, I wish I had gotten kidnapped as a kid
'cause I could have taught my way out of it.
- I really was just, I was pretty--
- I could have danced my way out of it.
- I was pretty afraid of getting kidnapped as a kid,
but I was like ugly and fat kid.
Like people wanna kidnap the beautiful children.
- I was a sexy kid but I had a little belly on me.
- Oh really?
- So I don't know.
- Who do you think I would've been?
- Are talented kids at higher risk?
You think a kid walking out of a piano recital or something?
- Yeah, they're like we're gonna get that kid.
- Yeah, that's what happened to JonBenet.
- What?
JonBenet wasn't talented at all.
She was a fucking hack.
- Oh, at this girl?
- Yeah.
- JonBenet sounds like a skateboarder.
I forgot that was a groundsman's famous kidnapping case.
I follow somebody who has that as their avatar on Twitter and I thought that was just a picture.
I thought it was just a following a girl.
Turns out it's a guy?
Yeah, it's a guy.
A guy who has a picture of JonBenet Ramsey.
It's a pretty odd choice.
Right, but then the Supreme logo too.
Oh, that's funny as hell.
Anyway, it turned out to be a different person than I thought it was.
You followed this person on the basis of like...
is John's name. No, no, I just, I might be thinking of a different person. Oh, okay.
But it turned out to be a missing person, like a famous one. Oh, damn. Yeah. Not that I
found them, it was, like I said. Did you guys ever know anybody who went missing? Or had cancer? Yeah, well,
yes, my grandpa. Grandpa? No, a kid. Oh. Oh. I think my grandpa had cancer. You think so? I don't know,
when he was a kid? As a kid? I saw people on the street the other day. With cancer? No, with a
giant sign that said like help this little kid he has cancer and it was like
it didn't look like a photo you would take of it it was like too nice of a
photo well it's probably a book I if I if I was taking a picture yeah I would
take I would put them in a little clown costume I'd paint a tear next to their
eye and I'd have them holding a drooping flower I would face tune the kid giant
eyes huge frown yeah right arrow through their head uh-huh like save this kid has
brain cancer yeah and we tried to cure it using holistic methods and now he also
has an arrow in his head. A bow and arrow with a little it dipped in a in elderberry syrup
we're in a huge amount of medical debt to dr. William Tell who failed to cure my
child of brain cancer. I didn't give him any money. Yeah. Yeah. Why not? Because I
didn't have any cash and I think if I we have a Venmo QR code. I was like okay. If I
got to the point where I'm holding up a sign like that to try
and get someone to pay for curing my kid's cancer, I would just take my
child to a magician. Tell you what, I'd rather my kid fucking die than me beg
for money. Yeah. Yeah. Preach. Who's gonna give me money? I'd rather my kid
fucking die in an agonizing way than me fucking out there on the streets begging
for money. It's disgusting. Let my kid die. It's also it's just so much work. No one's
gonna do anything. Why don't you go take a chance? Doctors are so busy
nowadays. Yeah, I can't even take him to a hypnotist or something. Exactly, yeah. Make his last moments fun.
They have open schedules. Yeah, I don't need to. I mean it might work. I would say
quality of life. Same thing as like old people. It's like quality of life. Yeah,
Growing up I had asthma. You didn't see me complaining about it. No. Do you still have it? Yeah, I complain about it now
But you know, I knew I had to wait till I had a platform. Yeah, like that's true
Sometimes I hit my vape too many times in a row and then when I go up the stairs, I start coughing a little bit
Mm-hmm
It's gotta be hard Gary Vee says like I used to work at Burger King and now I have money
Yeah, this is the same thing you're doing with asthma
Yeah, I'm like the Gary Vee of asthma. Yeah, I like when he rips off old ladies it at a
Garage sales. Yeah, they'll have like a they have like an Oscar statue that their son won or something and they're selling it for $2
He's like, can you do $1?
Yeah, and then he sells it for 400 bucks he goes is he the paperclip guy?
Is that how he what the guy who like he's like?
"Oh, I traded a paperclip for this, this for that."
- No, you think that's how he became a billionaire?
Was it?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
That must have found a lot of paperclips.
- He's the guy who did,
he did paperclip to house trade,
and he was like, "Oh, I can just do that in front of--"
- Hold up, wait, is that the guy,
is he the little worm that drives the Apple car?
- I don't think so.
I think that you're thinking of a made-up character
from a Richard Scarry book.
- Okay. - Yeah.
- Imagine how many, you could re-up though,
imagine how many paperclips you could buy
if you sold your house.
That's true.
And then infinite money.
And then you get each of those paperclips up into another house.
Realistically, how many paperclips do you have to have before you're making good money off
selling the paperclips?
Probably like a billion paperclips.
However many Staples has.
How did Gary Vee get where he is?
I think he invented Facebook.
Is there like a series of videos and books I can watch or read to find this out?
If there was some kind of method, then maybe.
But I don't think there is, no.
I don't think there's a book about his method or anything.
I'm looking to do what he does one for one one-to-one recreation. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I'm trying to he says it
You got to go to the garage sales. You have to rip off the old ladies. You have to steal you have to steal
I got it from stealing. Oh, yeah. He's a bank robber. Yeah
He found a bunch of pies that were sitting on window sills and he would go to the market and sell them
Yeah for a hundred thousand dollars. Yeah. Yeah within weeks. He was a millionaire. He sold one paperclip for millions of dollars
There's this one clip of his I was watching where it's like, he's like all these parents
are yelling at their kids for not going outside.
And he's, what do you think, what world do you think they're going to grow up in?
You're not letting them become like amazing eSports players.
I thought that was so fucking sick.
It's true dude.
Gary Vee is spitting just facts.
Yeah, just like oh yeah, kids nowadays have to be in eSports, they have to be on TikTok,
your kids stay inside all day. That's the way out. The screen for a lot of these kids is
good. That's right. It was for you. It was for me. It was for Cameron. Yeah. That's right.
Thomas grew up. I did. Thank you. In a tree. Yeah, you grew up in a tree. Growing up it
was. You used to ride leaves down the trunks of the trees. Growing up it was either eSports
or Lockheed Martin. Yeah. Or otherwise you weren't getting out of the hood. And you stuck
with. Lockheed Martin. Lockheed Martin. Yeah, I designed missiles. Really? Yeah, I'm working
I'm working on one right now and it's white and it has a red tip.
Okay.
And it says Acme on it.
And there's this one guy who lives out in the desert and he's been buying them by the
pallet.
Do you ever get worried about what he might do with that?
No.
I don't really get paid anymore.
It's just more of a passion project.
Yeah.
When you were making money, you just stopped caring about it, right?
You're just like, "I don't care."
They told me I needed a social security number and I was like, "How about this?
I work here for 20 years. On the 20th year, I start working here. And after 20 years working
here, you know what? You hire me. And I'll work here for 20 years.
So they know that you're like a grinder.
Exactly. You're in it for the love of the game.
It was the only time frame I could think of. So I just said it a few times so I don't have
to find another job.
And they just said, "Well, sure."
Yeah. And they ask you a question like, "Where do you see yourself in 20 years?" And you're
like, "Starting working here."
Yeah, I say in 20 years. I'm gonna be working here for 20 years. Yeah, I'm working here for 20 years starting in 20
So Lockheed Martin is Acme
It's a no. It's the guy we'd sell to on the desert
His his name is like coyote. Oh, okay thing he likes custom branding
So he has that do you guys also make those little holes that you've put on the ground and something? Yeah people falling we paint
Sometimes we'll paint like a road onto the side of a mountain for him for this guy, right?
I don't know what he uses it for but yeah, God only knows. Yeah, are you also do you guys also work on those really delicious carrots?
Oh, yeah, the one really good
Loud, they're so loud carrots. Yeah, you the candles do
The candles candles. Yeah the candles do you do?
Do you do big red knots in people's heads also? Yeah, they're kind of a merge. Yeah, we had this layer
The only thing we've had to discontinue was our ink wells.
Oh yeah.
And also our...
Your car exhaust pipes.
Yeah, those probably didn't age too well.
They did not.
They were very popular for a certain time frame, and after that it became clear that the market
was no longer interested.
Definitely.
Right.
Thankfully, we didn't get too much backlash from that thanks to our PR team.
Y'all really cleaned that up.
Yeah.
We sell a lot of mousetraps.
mostly mousetraps are hitting the fingers. Right, yeah. And a lot of mousetraps are
designed to kill. These more make you go, "YOW!" Right. I think it is fucked up that
Lockheed Martin is sending so many mousetraps over the Middle East. Oh yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Dropping them for... I mean, these kids are walking around, right?
They're walking around playing on playgrounds. There's a mousetrap hidden
underneath the sand, right? Yeah, it's been there for like 20 years. All of a sudden their toes are red.
And let's be honest, these mousetraps are meant for the mice, but 80% of the time
these mousetraps we put overseas they're ending up on a cat's tail yeah yeah or
one of those bastards from jackass is jumping around on yeah he's dressing up
like a mouse hey going into a room yeah there's a reason there's a reason they
called that show that yeah first of all they're wasting mousetraps yep they're
wasting cheese the cheese that from the mousetrap yeah and then they're wasting
a precious time of animal trainers you could be out exactly training a crocodile
or a snake instead they're training a crocodile to fucking bite a man's thing
yep you know and it's disgusting I don't really and they're wasting the talent of
a man who is perfectly suited to crawl through air conditioning shafts can you
imagine if if mini-me was an HVAC guy mini-me yeah speaking of it oh yeah no
mini-me mini-me yeah mini-me is we'd be a bit
so we man you're thinking of no mini-me okay from jackass if he was an HVAC you
what are you saying? What are you saying? It's Minimi. Minimi is from Oxfam, yeah. He's a miniature
version of Johnny Knoxville. All right. He is. When I was like eight years old and I saw like a clip
from Jacket, I did think that Minimi was supposed to be like a mini version of Steve-O. You thought
Minimi was supposed to be a mini version? It's not that they were like, I was like, oh it must be.
It must be the joke here.
Wish I was really small.
I remember when my dad...
I wasn't tall.
Before ever watching...
Before ever watching Jackass, my dad was telling me about it one time.
I remember him saying like, "Yeah, there's one guy named Wee Man."
I'm thinking, "What the hell kind of a name is that for a guy?"
It's a good... It's good because as an American, I'm thinking this has got to be a piss.
Yeah. It's got to be made out of piss.
And then you find out his real name is John Midget.
it yeah and you're like well I see why they went with we yeah yeah it's a
little too on the nose right I don't know why that was and none no one else in his
family is a little person yeah it doesn't make sense it's kind of just one
of those things just stars aligned kind of thing yeah I heard the nickname what
came before he was small really yeah I shrunk I heard he got shrunk and I heard
he did too much too many psychedelics and I heard he used to be called we man
because he would do skateboarding tricks and he go oh he liked roller coasters
then he got and then he got he fell and he got yeah he's be a tall skinny guy
and he fell on his head and his whole is he just he's not that small right yeah
he's like yeah 510 yeah that'd be so scary a guy that tall with those
proportions are you saying that's what you are yeah just legs as wide as your
your arms. Well Peter Dinklage is like four foot eight. Don't bring him up.
He's like not that, he's pretty tall for a little person. Like his head is
legitimately massive. Yeah, legitimately massive. Yeah, it's not illegitimately
massive. It's not photoshopped in the movies to look bigger, which for
most people that's what they do. Yeah, they photoshop it in the movies. There's a music
teacher at my elementary school named Mr. Woodman.
Mr. Wid-man. Wid-man? Wid-man. So you guys... Widdle-man. And he was a little person.
Really? Yeah. Wish he was Mr. Weed-man and you'd probably be smoking that grass up
in the class. Mm-hmm. Yeah. And he ended up dating one of my classmates moms and
then he moved. Holy shit. Yeah. He hit it and quit it on a classmate's mom? Was she
a little person? No, no, no. They moved together. They got married and left. Oh, wow.
And she was a tall lady.
How tall? Well, I think you have to go like abnormally tall if you're really tall.
And he also played the trumpet.
Did they get married in class?
Yeah, in the school.
I know that day was crazy.
Yeah. Oh my god, leave your backpacks at home.
I guess he was in this band that would play at the restaurant my mom worked at.
So...
He was in a band too?
He was in a band.
This guy sounds dope.
They're called Sold Out. S-O-U-L-E-D.
Whoa. Oh, Sold Out.
you play quite like the show is sold out
was it was it was a good idea to get to the show time a lot of songs really
yeah
he teach you smoke on the water me uh... was a song
i don't know
forget this
to sing on down to the lab very big enough book check it in check it out
what this is a lot of the time it has not as i don't think i've ever heard
It's a song about the library.
I believe he taught you that.
That's not an agreed upon song.
Nobody's ever heard that song before.
He taught me that song.
Was that a sold out cover that you--
No, it wasn't.
No, sold out was a cover, Ben.
They would just do like, you know, like, hold on, I'm coming.
They would do that song.
To the library?
Hold on, I'm coming?
By Saban.
You know that song?
Hold on, I'm coming.
Oh, that's that-- and you went, hold on, I'm coming,
instead of the recognizable part of the song?
both the parts of that song of the most ready to be needed to it in tune with
the song you know
all-around common
well they didn't play it into
uh... it is a good it was a recovery they're doing like a bluegrass twist on
it
yeah
i feel like i said too much about this guy
yeah it was pretty easy to identify now you know if you would you know look him
up but i mean hell if you look at my thing that man is a hell of a trumpet
player says my mom says your mom she said he's in the fucking it's like he's in
that band it's like the Beatles in Germany yeah it's fucking doing his
thing doing this thing at whippersnappers and yeah very New Hampshire
honing his craft that place doesn't exist anymore so I can say that yeah
Germany sure London Derry New York Germany does need to get fucking Germany
I I went I visited I was in the bay German I was in the bay no
But I kept seeing all these fucking German people he's fucking German all these
Looked like to German I was like all your bloodlines like to pure German like like to German like they look like
They have really tight pants with some like fucked up running sneakers running a polo shirt
- Oh, so they're just like super fit.
- Super, yeah.
- So you're saying they looked perfect.
- They looked too genetically pure.
They looked 100% German.
- And you're saying--
- There's something in your family tree
that you're not telling people about.
- Right, German DNA.
- Yeah, some going back to the 1940s.
- I don't understand what you're saying.
- I'm not sure I understand either.
- I don't know what you mean.
- I don't think they're that old.
You're saying these people were 70, 80 years old?
Yes.
And they had a little mustache.
Really?
Yeah.
They shared it?
They all shared this little square-- well,
when you do the math, I mean, dividing up that mustache--
They're attached to the lip.
True.
You think there was other guys who
had the other parts of it, that mustache?
Yeah, I think Hitler and his friends from World War I--
Maybe they would all--
They were like, let's all have one little part of a mustache.
And there's a guy who had just this.
Yeah.
Just that.
That would have been way more iconic of a look if Hitler had just right side, just that.
Yeah, that would be nice too because then people could wear that little fucking toothbrush
one.
Bring that thing back.
I wish I could go back in time and tell Hitler to do that.
Yeah.
Well that's a hard part of a mustache to grow and his was like, his was strong.
Yeah, I think he probably grew there because like the other sides of it like just, you
think it was all patchy.
I think if there's a popular style though in the 30s.
Yeah, because of Chaplin.
Michael Jordan.
I think if there's a nuclear war and all of our the internet is wiped out and all of our
information goes back to the stone age I'm going to find every picture of Hitler and I'm
going to erase the mustache and put it on the side just so the next generation that
mustache is free.
Yeah, yeah.
You can use the Hitler mustache again.
And that mustache now becomes.
That mustache is evil, yeah.
Yeah.
Because nobody's ever had a mustache like that so it's okay to make that evil.
You could rock that all day.
And who knows maybe we don't want pictures of Genghis Khan he could have been fucking
rocking that.
He could have rocked a normal mustache.
There's this band Sparks.
There is.
brothers Ron and Russell Mail and I think Ron Mail just fully in the 70s just
fully had a Hitler mustache. They tried to get a Hitler mustache up until the 90s.
I'm also... Then he found out. And then he was like "Ah, shit." He's a rocker. He dropped out of school.
Exactly. When I'm messing with all the Hitler pictures I'm also gonna put horns
on Obama. In the pictures where they're with each other. Yeah. Which there are many of them by the way.
They're gonna be a lot more too. Mm-hmm. Yeah. I would love to be
though have all the information in the world and be in control of it. Yeah.
- Yeah.
- You probably need a second phone.
- Yeah, or even I could have--
- Yeah, you'll be busy.
- I wanna be in a big room like from the Matrix,
where they find the creator of the Matrix
and he's in the big room with all the computers.
I want a room like that, but it's everything on the screens.
- You wanna be God.
- Yeah, I would love to be God.
- It's too much responsibility for me.
- You actually do.
- I'm mainly just down to fucking chill.
- Yeah, I would just chill too.
I would chill on it forever.
I thought if something's funny, I would basically do it.
- You'd do whatever was funny?
- Yeah.
- What if whatever was funny was like,
I'm gonna fucking make people have turds
their head. That sounds funny. Turds in their head. What if it killed the people?
Then I'd just make new people who could have turds in their head.
If you could make turds in somebody's head you could also just clone
that person and just do it infinitely. I could just make it so that everybody
likes having turds in their head. That would be so stupid. Yeah. That doesn't make any sense.
That's literally the worst idea I've heard in my entire life.
Well I would do a lot of stuff so not all the ideas have to be good. Name one other thing you would do that
it makes any fucking sense besides put turds in people's heads.
By the way, it was my idea, so if it's a good idea, I actually get credit for it.
You said it was a bad idea.
It was a bad idea, but now if you're saying it's a good idea, then I don't even...
I didn't say it was a good idea, I said it was a bad idea.
No you didn't.
I said not all of them have to be good, that's exactly what I said.
Did you just put a turd in Caleb's head?
I wish I did.
You couldn't, there's no way into my head.
You would look so good with a lobotomy scar.
No turds in or out.
Oh my god.
A lobotomy scar?
Like if you had the fucking...
You'd give me a turd lobotomy?
You had like a, if you're like the guy in the wheelchair from Nightmare Before Christmas.
Yeah you would be.
Dude with screws in your head, that would rock.
Nah I'm gonna tear your, speaking of turds, I'm gonna tear yours up, I'm gonna rearrange
yours and you're gonna be in a wheelchair.
My turds?
Yeah I'm gonna.
What?
I'm gonna rearrange your fucking turds.
That's right.
I'm gonna go in there, I'm gonna move around like a Rubik's Cube and then I'm gonna come
back out and you're gonna be in a wheelchair.
I'm not gonna be in a wheelchair.
You're gonna be in a weird chair.
They're gonna have to invent a new wheelchair for your fucking fucked up ass.
It's red.
It's a red with blood because I rearranged his turds and I hit a couple of fucking...
There was some traffic cones I was knocking over in there. I'll say that much.
So, do you have anything else to say, God?
Or did I put you at rest? Are you so stupid you really think I'm God?
No, I'm actually smart. He would definitely make up a new word for God if he was trying to do that shit.
If he was trying to be God, he would call himself, like, "Sporker."
Sporker? That's a fucking awful name. That's the worst name ever.
that's by a good name is why he was genuinely playing with his keys
the back of the lady
uh... i can't actually books dot and i was promised for a record people like
also spurgle
here is for a door also that much of a yeah
spurred by getting a test for that soon
asperger's
you know you can only have asperger's
media you can use that so you know you're so sorry dude
he's a show you know it's a shy streak he's not sees not asperger's shadow
Yeah. I wouldn't know. I want to get tested for that just to see if it would make sense.
I don't think there's any test that you can ever get that will make you happy.
Yeah. Yeah. You just got to deal with it. I'm not saying I would be happy if I found out. You would
be so happy if you found out you had Asperger's. You'd be like, "Oh my god, yes, I get to be so
annoying now." That's the only reason you ever get that test unless you're two years old. Yeah.
You'd be like, look at him, he just moved his hips like that.
He's already thinking about it.
He's already like, oh yeah, I have Asperger's
and I'm just gonna scream and then say it.
- I thought when I was on Adderall when I was a kid,
I was like 16, not really, technically a kid.
- That's a kid to me.
- Yeah, but I took an Asperger's screening quiz online.
- That's always a good idea.
- And I was like, holy crap.
Holy crap, these sound like things that I'm doing
not thinking like oh my god like a pill that's making me like read Wikipedia for
like you ever do oh my god I I have the same personality as Luke Skywalker oh my
god Lee I would be Pikachu just cry walking away it's like you are Darth
Vader walking into my parents room crying cuz I got Fez from that 70s yeah
taking a quiz as a 12 year old and you're like fuck I'm a sex addict I knew it
yeah I think every everybody's had that taking one of those and it's like it's
like you're a psychopath cuz you're like fuck you I don't like three days any
fan about taking off it's like fuck this is taking over I love coming I think I'm
addicted to having a great big bone yeah what personality type are you guys
Myers-Briggs status. I'm a triple X. Don't lick the mic like that. Stop licking the mic. He's actually LGBTQ.
Yeah, he got it. That's fine by me to be LGBTQ in that way. That's cool now. Yeah.
Socially I'm fine with that kind of thing and that's the same thing as triple X.
Socially and legally. Legally I think that it should be completely legal and not
up to the states. I think the state should have no say in that, personally, and I'm for real.
I ain't clowning. And pornographers types should be able to do that. Yeah. Right?
That should be allowed. And California and the rest of the country as well.
I think the California laws should be everywhere. Yeah. What are the California laws?
Just like, I think there should be a tent city in the middle of Ohio. Yeah. There's just a giant
Well, hey, I got some good news for you
Okay, what's the good news? There's a lot of tent cities
in Ohio
real looks like you just agree with yeah, Caleb I
Disagree you agree with me. I agree. Mm-hmm. I think we should do it. I agree
We should just Sim City cloning tool with San Francisco. Just make the whole country San Francisco that I should be kind of fire
That would actually be yeah
A lot of people would lose weight because of the hills. They would lose weight because of the hills and the weather would be perfect year-round.
The dwarves would love it. The dwarves would not love it. No, they would all the mountain.
That's true. That's so much more mountain, dude. Oh, I don't think San Francisco is quite a mountain. No, it's a mountain. Dwarves are small enough.
It's basically like at the top. Do you think there's dwarves in the middle of San Francisco? Just like fire and moldy lava?
No, they're under. They're hidden. Yeah.
Like in the core of it, how do you think the train they're hitting axes on the on the thing? I don't watch them
Yeah, well you you think they would invite me to probably not you're too tall or even halls wouldn't fit in the hole, right?
You know is I mean I can't I'm not invited there. They got wooden mugs right there. They're cheers in the yeah everywhere
Well, what I mean, that's the plumbing. Yeah, they are there and there's coal. Yeah, there's
cards no I guess no I don't think so no I went to Ohio and like 2015 what do you
do how is that you see LeBron I don't have to tell you about it
where is a cron Akron is it you saying it like a con yeah it's Akron it literally
is that's a that's on with an R. I feel like you it's a it's a Acorn but you've heard you
have to you have to have heard somebody say Akron before. No. Never? I just read the word.
Because of LeBron James. Right. Is he from Ohio? He's from Akron. Ohio? Ohio yeah. Okay.
Acorn. Is Cleveland Cleveland is also Ohio right? Cleveland is from Quahog. Quahog's
Let me yeah, let me call my G my Matt professor. Okay. All right, give him a call. Call your man
Yeah, and what's his name right now president map? That's a fucking shit name. No. Well, I didn't choose it for him
You think he's my you hang out with president map. You think that's my son? I don't know
You think I'm the father of the president you think I'd be sitting here. He's the president
His name is president. His name is president. It's I gave him the I didn't give him the first
President president maps it's a shit name. I don't think you have his phone. No, I feel like you're not gonna call him right now
He doesn't have a phone. You have to look on a map to find him. That's you have to is he's the ex
right
Not my ex. No, maybe your ex maybe you dated him and kissed him. What the hell he's getting returned around on me
Yeah, maybe he's around on you. Well, he was rubbing up on your stuff up in the front. Yeah, he was rubbing on me
I was doing nothing. I was just right you were taking it
Now it's asleep you were pretending to be asleep. Listen if president man fuck you you reply was asleep
Okay, and I didn't notice you had your eyes were just barely open you're playing possum
And you know I wasn't playing possibly under the covers now
And you had a little had a little sly grin
I've never done a slide you had like you had a little a little fruitcake in your pocket
All right now you're saying fruitcake, and I'm getting fucked by president map
I know thing about this is LGBTQ which you already identify as we've discussed. Yeah five to six minutes
Which is fine by me, huh? Right, it's fine. Yeah, so you're fine with getting fucked in your sleep. No, I are you be okay with that?
That's yeah. No, sure. I'm fine with it. You're a big. Yeah. No, I let no it's fine by me to get fucked in the sleep
In the sleep in the sleep fine by me. It's not a problem. I get booked in the sleep
Sometimes I get pushed by you should you get fucked in like, you know
Yeah, what's this what's this impression of a fucking mirror that you're looking into bud no cuz mirrors don't speak typically
Well mine do you speak while you're looking into it?
Technically speak on
What a black mirror can speak a phone if you're talking into that's true, but usually the screens on it's a black mirror
It's your mirror that you look at
Because I'm black
I don't know, right?
Yeah, maybe you are.
Yeah, I mean, maybe I am.
I don't know.
I don't know either.
Me and Cam do want to do a DNA test, though.
Yeah.
And I think-
You've been talking about it for years at this point.
Well, no, I mean, just like, I think- I don't- The thing is, it sucks because there's no
way-
There's no way identical twins-
I would like to make it a competition, but there's no way to do that without doing some
kind of like-
Eugenics, yeah.
Ranking of the races.
Well, yeah.
I don't want to do that.
You can- I mean, the only-
And I feel like the way it works is you have people place bets on what the results are
going to be.
Yeah, I guess we have to do it like that.
There has to be no value judgment at all.
Yeah, yeah, because once we do that we're in trouble.
Yeah, you have to let everyone else put the value judgment on it.
Is putting down stuff like, it's like, because then you're like, "Oh, I fucking hope that
he's not Italian."
That's what I'm saying, then that's on them and it doesn't matter.
Yeah, me and you, we're happy for him.
payout whatever comes out of that crazy that crazy website that's true yeah I
don't give you like an over and under on how Chinese both you are yeah yeah I mean
I think I have a little more Chinese yeah yeah we just got to pick an arbitrary
one be like whoever's the most of this but odds are probably neither of us are
Chinese at all yeah well you never know that's the thing about it that's a good
point yeah somebody could make like a million bucks off we can play what if we
50% Chinese.
What if we did like--
The odds on that is unreal.
what if we did like guess who, right?
With all the different parts of what kind of race we are.
So like we know, but the other person doesn't.
So it would be through 23andMe, right?
Yeah.
So we set up little--
You can see on that, they have things on there that's like,
oh, you have this much Neanderthal DNA,
or like this much.
Like you're prone to having black hair.
- Yeah.
- Or stuff like that.
- You say lack hair?
- Black hair.
- Oh.
- Yeah, you might have black hair later in life.
- Yeah.
- That'd be cool.
- Prone to it.
- Kinda sprout, second.
- It just comes back like pure Puerto Rican.
- Yeah.
- Perfect.
- Just perfect.
- Just hair line right here.
I have one inch of forehead.
Be sick, dude.
- I didn't have black hair growing up.
- So you got cursed probably by some kind of pyro?
Yeah, look at his head.
It's pretty dark.
It's dark.
It's jet black.
I just had, he's usually got a hat on.
Jet black hair, long black boots.
Remember that song?
Good, nice.
That'll work.
Do you see this?
Holy.
Wow.
That's a sideways hat.
Your mustache is kind of like reddish though, right?
Yeah, my beard and everything grows in red, but then.
Yeah, that's silly.
Yeah, it looks bad.
What color are your pubes?
Are they black or brown?
Jet black.
Really?
Really.
You have black pubes?
like even yeah of course they're curly I would hope my nursery straight pubes yeah
really long and straight they go down I got a girl down there dripping everything
in a wave cap all day and it looks like a dumpling my pubes are curly but not as
much as I want them to be I'm gonna be real yeah yeah they probably got one
good curl in them and then they're just you know like just kind of turn in a
it's kind of yeah they don't puff out as much as I want I want to have like a
lump in my shorts if you wait if you wait like four years four years untouched
untouching them non-touching my pubes all day you fucking pervert no no I mean like
not trimming them or shaving I trim my pubes what am I a fucking animal you get
it or not an animal you know get ingrown hairs after a while I get him I just
leave him there don't puss up and shoot all over fucking disgusting right
sometimes fucking yeah I think what you could do too is maybe my laptop on my
lap and it'll just just pop a bunch of them yeah I think you wanted to look like
like operation down there. Let them grow for a while and then kind of twist them all together
and they can fuse like a rhino horn. Yeah. Or like an elephant. Dreadlock Rasta. Yeah.
Or like more until it's just like a kind of a horn. I could do a full... Specifically
a horn. I could do one solid dread coming out of my pubes. I want to get hair plugs
up towards the head just to hide my thing completely. Yeah. Just make it just look caterpillar.
Just look like a weird rat. Yeah. Because the tip is still... Are you cut or uncut? I'm cut.
My man. My man. There he goes again. He's not part of the tribe. Team Morskine. I got a lot
of it down there. I don't know why that was gross. My foreskin? Baggy. Baggy as hell. He's
got the JNCO foreskin. Yeah dude. My shit hangs out. It takes me a while. When I pee
I gotta roll this thing up like I'm cuffing my pants.
So it looks like calamari.
Yeah.
It's just like a flat, like a tapeworm.
You gotta iron it in the morning.
Oh yeah.
It's like a sorcerer's sleeve.
It's wrinkly and I can tie it up in a bow.
Make a balloon.
I was just about to ask.
I can tie it in a bow, I can throw it over my shoulder.
Forget the other word to and fro to and fro you can fit a hot wheel in there. I put a I put a gem
Wow, you put a gem a gem a complete gem in there and I hid
I hid a gem from cuz you're a kid you had to have been putting funny stuff in there
I would I put a quarter in there really put a quarter
That's normal. I feel like
It's gross. I
I would just put like a yeah put like I think I put a quarter in there just to see if it would shoot out like
It was a Johnny Cash song. Yeah, do you think you could train it like?
You think you could train it like put a quarter in there for like a week and it's like gauging then you put like a
Gold dollar. Oh before you know it. Yeah, you've got I don't know in a bill. Yeah
The skin looks like oh, you know you should put in their glass eye. Yeah. Yeah, we're just broken glass
Oh, yeah, you could scare. Yeah
You pull your pants down and you're talking to police that was just my stock. Yeah
You can put a boot in there make it look like it's a foot yeah
You should put a pocket pussy in there and then you're completely just coming all this just cut off most of it
You know you need a lot of yeah, and then it would would you let me put my penis into your foreskin?
No, why what if it was not sexual?
Yeah, right if it wasn't sexual you'd let me do it probably if it's not sexual
Yeah, could I what do I have to put we'd have to put novocaine into them?
It would hurt what about would you like it would hurt so bad not for would you let me do it both?
Pat would you let me do it? No? No, no, it wasn't can mean can't - at the same time
I'm telling you what if what if okay?
What if me and Tom what if me and Thomas do it at the same time and it's not sexual for you?
But it may it might be between us, but you don't know how about is sexual how about?
You three of us big enough for two guys not sexual for you
Uh-huh, or it is sexual for you, but we're doing it like his buddies
Yeah, it's like yeah, we are talking and for you. It's like cold and clinical. Yeah
It's like when you go to the urgent care and you have to get your physical and the doctor has a boner
But like you just need your balls checked. Yeah. Yeah, that happens you doctor my doctor my peter's supposed to
Yeah, yeah, what pediatrician passed away recently really yes, he wasn't that good at it. Yeah
He is it's kind of weird because it's like I feel like something he's probably touched my penis more than anybody in the world
Including yourself. Yeah
He's probably tested my my paint my balls for lumps. I don't think I've been to a doc actually, you know what?
No, that's a lie. I went to a doctor at August 1st. That's nice
Yeah, that's huge after not going for five years. Nice. Yeah, and they touch your penis
You just immediately walk in, it's been too long, you forget to get over here, just pull
your pants down, let's get this over with.
The guy, you haven't touched it any in the five years, so it's like, it's just like a
swollen...
It looks like an old pier, it's got marbles on it.
It's like when an old man in India grows his fingernails to be six feet long.
Your penis hasn't been trimmed back in so long, it looks weird.
You haven't pruned it, yeah.
Yeah.
It's so, yeah.
I hate having to fucking prune my dick.
He's probably tested my penis more than anyone.
Really tested it smell test like a bull like a like a whole five panel
Oh, I got a checkup every weekend. He was a high HPV risk of the child. Yeah, really? Yeah
All right
Is it what he did
What did I do you were just fucking a lot? Yeah? Yeah, you were a bit of a pussy. He's in the club kid
Yeah, we all knew that one pussy kid. Yeah, just who it you would go over to his house, and he would fuck you yeah
Nine kids from the class over and he'd fuck them all yeah, yeah
Kid was dope yeah
He'd always have the sickest treehouse, so it's like yeah, I'm gonna get fucked there was a kid
I thought I was trying to fuck me, and he did have a treehouse he had blow-up furniture. Yeah, whoa no
he never fucked me yeah okay yeah I didn't know he never did have he had edible
edible toothpaste he had toothpaste you can swallow yeah and I remember and I
just I'd never seen that before and I just ate it yeah I went in his huge
bathroom you know there's his own bathroom to himself and he had this
toothpaste it was like a gel and it was like fruity yeah and he was like you
need that and I said okay I have to take a poop now but I didn't I just ate -
it's a toothpaste yeah there's a kid there's my cousin had this like sleep
over one time and there's this kid who was like yeah guys I have a wreck
basketball game in the morning you all have to be quiet and so we put icy hot
on his face while he was asleep oh my god that's so bad for the kid's gonna see
his skin is fucked forever yeah yeah we did it back then he was completely was
like like I'm gonna go to sleep in the other wasn't his house he was just like
Like I have a game at 7.
Then don't go out bro.
That's right.
Exactly.
Don't go to the sleepover if you're gonna fucking.
Oh yeah.
You gotta catch a piece of shit.
And then because he was the first to sleep we were all fucking with him and then he woke
up and ran into the room and my friend Alex was like in a chair far away from him and
because Alex was like he thought of Alex as like weaker than him he just ran over and started
trying to wail on Alex even though Alex had nothing to do with it.
no way I'm glad that you got us caught on them. I was one time with my cousins and then I
woke up and they said I woke up to them putting a phone in my face they're like
look at this video Caleb fucking video of all of them farting into my mouth and
I've never been in such a rage and I just started attacking whatever the
closest one was and this is only about four years ago. Well he, he attacked him. I could legally drink at the time. He attacked him but he Alex was far away in the
room. Alex had no involvement. He was far far away. He was far enough that as soon as he
went over and started trying to wail on him everyone was just like, "Alright, what the
f- why'd you do that?" Yeah. Uh huh. Yeah. Oh he said "Fuck you, cocksucker" and then
he tried to kick him off of him and he said "Only pussies kick" and then he started kicking
back and then we kept saying that all weekend and he got really mad and he went home. You
You sounded like you were bullying us, kid.
We weren't bullying.
You're a bully.
No.
Bully.
Bully ass.
Oh, I'm fucking scared of you, Pat.
You're fucking...
You're gonna bully me.
No!
Don't kick me and fucking hurt me.
Don't kick the table.
I just...
Yeah.
I thought it would...
That's beyond...
That's beyond what's okay.
That's not...
This table is...
That's inappropriate.
Let's give it two weeks, man.
Okay.
Yeah, I am starting to...
On this side here, we gotta fill this in.
No.
You...
It's as is.
Okay.
I'm done.
It's a good table.
Alright.
Leave it alone.
Okay.
There's just a little crack here.
Tom, do you have anything to talk about and tell people about?
Go check out Pindeo Time.
Yeah.
You and old Jake.
Old Jake.
Yeah.
Who's talking about this the other night.
Jake, if you're listening, I'm sorry that when we slept together in a bed I got a huge
boner.
I don't think he knew about that.
He knew.
I think he knew you were like ripping ass the whole time.
Yeah.
I wasn't farting.
No, that was me.
That's why my penis smells when it gets hard.
- From what his account, both of you were ripping ass
the entire night. - Liar.
- He's a liar.
Don't believe him if he said I had a boner either.
- That was like a comic.
- No, he didn't.
- I don't think he has a memory of you having a boner.
- Apologize to him for me having a boner in the other room.
(laughing)
- There's just something about that damn house.
- Otis also had a boner.
That's all right.
Anyway.
- Otis is a cat.
- Yeah, Otis is a cat.
Yeah, I realize I have to, just saying Otis.
Nobody knows.
groundskeeper
He's why he looks in the window
Where do you want me to put this
Anyway, we don't have any shows coming up or anything, but yeah, I've been day all time go check out
Thanks for having me.
Of course.
It's been a pleasure.
What do you think of our awesome office?
I think it's pretty sick.
It's cool you guys have your own little space and everything.
You think it looks really good right now?
I think it looks, it's probably the best place I've ever seen.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Would you say it seems like big things are happening?
Not really, it seems like everything's going downhill but there's space to do it.