Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- You weren't able to produce correctly today.
- You honestly--
- Actually, no, I think you'd probably--
- This is, I've never seen some, like one article of,
- You look like--
- Even your face is different.
- You look like Donald Fagan right now.
- You look so fucking cool with these glasses on.
- You look like you were supposed to be in a,
you you look like you play bass in a seventies band
he was not even saying he's not saying a god damn thing you know he looks like
the saxophone player from the muppets god damn you look cool
uh...
holy shit i feel blessed i feel really blessed i feel like
something just came out of you this feels like we're doing a live at daryl's house and we're
interviewing him about his music
i don't know who daryl is daryl hall
i don't know who daryl is oh my god he just yawned
he's bored we have to keep him on the line oh my god he put his mic down
no no no no um okay uh here I go I'm
I'm singing my song here I just look at me
sing the candy song
gotta have my candy yeah yeah
gotta have my candy gotta have my candy yeah yeah gotta have my candy yeah yeah
even I gotta have a peppermint
he likes this peppermint
oh my god he's saying peppermint yeah that kind of ruins it is your voice is
actually fucking lame AF. There's this a cool guy could have that voice. Do you
remember that show on Nickelodeon Kablam? I remember watching Nickelodeon going
kablam yeah when Amanda Bynes went 17 remember that? Well I was
actually young at the time that she was young I'm actually older or younger than
her she's older than me that's so it's fine for me to jack off to her if
someone is even one day old oh my god get out get out Pierce
why is Pierce here's what are you doing here Pierce Pierce he just left he
completely left that was fat he tried to break in yeah I was gonna work on
something with him but that was at like 10 a.m. and he didn't come so now you
- He tried to break in and steal stuff from us too.
- Bastard.
- Oh my God, the handsome intruder.
Handsome invader.
- Holy shit, the beautiful invader.
- Beautiful invader all along.
- There he is.
- All along.
- Do you guys think that when we were--
- Why'd you just look at the back of your hand like that?
- He wrote it down.
- No, I don't write down my ideas.
- He wrote it down in Morse code.
- Yeah, those dots, those are Morse code dots.
- I do not.
Guys, if you're saying that I write down all my ideas
for the podcast and none of it is extemporaneous improv,
you're extemporaneous oh my god I can see that on the other I can see that written
on his watch no I didn't write down that sentence and I didn't write down the
sentence I'm saying right now just in case of an emergency you wrote that down
- no I didn't write that down you did wrong down but yeah do you guys think
that maybe when we were like little kids we would have been friends like that we
are now or do you think we would have probably hated each other cuz I just saw
I saw a picture of you, your Slack picture,
and I was like, I think me and this guy
might have been, probably would have been
really good friends and then maybe had a weird
kind of sleepover sexual interaction and ruin it.
- Yeah, my senior photos, those are the only thing
close to professional headshots that I have.
- Those are the only thing close to perfection.
- Yeah, I think I'm gonna use those
if I get booked on standup shows.
- Those are your headshots?
- Those are my headshots I'm gonna use,
'cause I took those at the mall
like the place where you like take your baby to get a picture of the baby done.
It wasn't called Baby Picture Mall, but it was something like that.
It was similar to Baby Picture Mall, but there's a lot of really good photos of me at 17, just
like very confused as to what the photographer wants me to do because there's like a baby
block behind me.
Why don't you just play with the baby block?
it's a baby block is it just a block
it's like a block that has letters on it. Is that like a thing somebody else would know about?
am i in the dark here? A baby block?
yeah, because there's adult blocks. It has like an A
yeah, oh, an alphabet block. No, but sometimes it has numbers on the other side. Or like a picture of babies.
It's a baby block. It's like if it says the letter B, then you know who he was talking about.
I genuinely thought that it was some kind of... You're being an asshole.
You're being a fucking asshole for no fucking reason.
it was like a of photo thing
but there's a new put the baby on or something no it's a baby block it's
not going to play with the baby i don't know if they can't play with those
blocks i wasn't my brain space was a good thing that you play with it was a
great process it would be a dick
no i'm running everything i was asking a question you're being a day to be a
decade
no being as i was a question of i was
if anybody else knew the baby block was there if i was the one who didn't know
and clearly everyone else knows what it is.
- He's still on this.
- Fucking ass, you're the one who's still on this.
- Ass hat.
- You're talking.
- Dickhead.
- No.
- Shitter.
- No, I was, I asked a person
a perfectly reasonable thing about maybe a baby block
as a set piece at a mall.
- You're being a cunt.
You're being a cunt hole.
- Guys, no I'm not.
- You're being an asshole cunt.
- No, I was just curious if a baby block--
- You're being a fucking ass,
you're being an asshole cunt fucker.
- Maybe it's like a pedestal that a baby--
- You're a pedestal.
- Maybe you guys all go lower.
- Huh?
the
shit on you. I actually I you do you wanna I'm a cunt I'm a cunt so I'm a fucking cunt
I guess I'm a cunt I don't know. He's turning into Homer kind of. Hey I guess I'm a cunt.
So my daughter is a fucking cunt. I'm a cunt! I guess my daughter's a cunt with diarrhea on her mouth I
I don't know.
Oooh.
That's Homer CK.
Homer CK.
It works.
The CKs.
Yeah, can I, uh, you know, um...
Woohoo!
Hello?
Hey, what's up, homie?
Homie, are you touching yourself?
I don't like that.
(laughing)
- I don't like Homer C.K.
That's a, I mean, those are two legends of comedy
that I still wanna insult.
- You wanna keep them separate from each other.
- This, I swear to God, this Coke Dream World,
I'm trying to, since I've been on Adderall,
I've been trying to cut back on all caffeine
'cause it's not good for your heart.
And so I've been drinking just plain soda
'cause it only has like a little bit of caffeine.
I'm weaning myself off.
This tastes exactly--
- He's weaning himself off right now.
- This tastes like hoisin sauce.
- It's like Homer C.K.
fucking waning yourself off.
This tastes like hoisin.
Hoisin?
Like...
I'm sorry I don't have enough money to go shop at a global grocery store world market like you.
There is a...
I know what hoisin sauce is.
There is a supermarket next to the bodega and you could have gotten there and got me a diet coke.
Do I look like I'm made of fucking feet and I can walk everywhere for...
I wish you were made of feet and I could massage every single one of them.
Oh my god.
You wouldn't.
I would.
If I was like one of those bucky balls...
Yeah.
No.
Uh huh.
Just with feet? You wouldn't do that.
that go in and put a friend with a color on my penis don't you dare I know I what
is it I know I know what I know I've heard it before I can't call the picture
in my brain what is it you're screaming like an asshole at me right now tell me
what it is right now this is workplace of Regina right John you hear about this
there you guys are keeping a secret from me like what I'm gonna I'm gonna pick it
at you I'm gonna use you mentally you are being rude to me so I'm gonna
physically is it what is it does it have spikes yeah it's a spike that you give
to a kid it's a slight ball it's like the top of a mace yeah there's balls that
look like that that's a toy you don't know you don't know what you don't know
what a buckyball is either no what the fuck is a buckyball fuck you I think he
made it up I was just a toy I made up okay I feel like a buckyball before I
think it's the one that goes like this
buckyball but then that doesn't make sense for the visual yeah what are you
because the visual of you made that's why I was on the spikes yeah the visual of
you made no it never mind it's those little magnetic balls what is it to
these
these are buckyballs. That makes absolutely no sense at all. Yeah, that makes complete zero sense. They're buckyballs. Completely zero sense.
You look just like a buckyball. Oh wait, see I'm thinking of this when it's all put
to
had a friend link but clear right now. Friend link is different from knowing everything
all the time. Plus my hat is, I don't know where to put my hat. On your head. But then
I can't think as well when I have a hat on my head. Yeah you can't. I can think pretty
well. I think worse when I have a band of tight stuff around my head. I keep uh. To
nothing? Then why would I even wear the hat? Is there a red line on my forehead? Yeah but
I thought it was a tattoo or a birthmark. I keep, I don't know what it is, every hat
is too small for me now. I think I know exactly what it is that makes every hat
too small for you. Yeah I think it's your head. I think it's the size of your head.
Last night I fell asleep watching a vampire in Brooklyn and my
cat was in my like armpit while I was sleeping and I guess
my roommate came home I guess I must have rolled over in my sleep because my
roommate came home to Moe just in my armpit going "WAAA" just trying to get away
well you trapped killed you I almost rolled over and killed Moe yeah holy shit
goddamn that would have been we need a link up Moe and Phil that would never
work Phil Moe Phil Moe and we need to Phil Moe in the city of dope
wait why would that never work? nothing here but chips and soda
Nicky Nicky because it's a cat and a dog we found out that Phil's not even a
German Shepherd he's a he's a Belgian Malinois what is that? it's like a
a cousin to a German Shepherd but it's not the same thing. It's basically the same thing.
Yeah basically but we found out we found out... Did you do a DNA test on him? No but we
just looked at him and we were like he's not a German Shepherd he's a Malinois. You thought he must be a cousin?
A lot of people, Malinois get mistaken for German Shepherd
often but they have a different... Maybe because they're the fucking same breed. No they have a
different coat it's basically any time you see a German Shepherd with short hair you're
like oh that's a... Couldn't the short hair also be from some other type of dog?
in his lineage. There are four types of dogs. Yeah. Gug. Speak on it. There are four types
of dogs. Let's hear it. Run through them. It doesn't matter what breed they are. List
them then, asshat. Go. Big. Dickhead. You're being a dickhead to me. Dickhead. No. Dickhead's
not a breed of dog. Dickhead is a type of dog. I know what the next breed is. It's Caleb.
Caleb yeah I'm a dog yeah that's all four of them those three do you think I could
be mistaken for a dog I think that's the last animal you would be mistaken the
dog the dog community in my neighborhood could be mistaken for an egg yeah or a
Sphinx cat the dog community my neighbor is being shook right now a sphinx cat
with Down Syndrome. Down Syndrome? Yeah, a cat with Down Syndrome. Yeah, they can. Have
you seen that picture of the tiger with Down Syndrome? No, because I don't sit around saying
oh let me look up Down Syndrome animal. I didn't look it up. It's on one of those like
super fact or whatever. It's not a super fact. Ultra facts dot com. I don't think it has
Down Syndrome. I think, I feel like if an animal. Because Down Syndrome is named after
a guy who had Down Syndrome. Exactly. There's no cat named Down. I feel like that tiger,
that's the first case of like like downs in a in a tiger I feel like whatever that
Tigers name is what you name it after like it's like when they have like like
have you ever seen like a video of like a cat with like schizophrenia or something
I've never seen schizophrenia yeah he's cat so that's cats so free that's a
crazy cats are crazy so crazy and they gotta look at any any disease for an
animal that has a human analogous you have to change the name and I like it
cute. Analog. Snopes is uh... I don't care. Snopes lists... See he's been a dick. I've
made this mistake before. This guy's a human fucking... He's a walking talking Vox
explainer video. So Snopes says is this a tiger with Down syndrome and
Snopes says mixture so I'm right. Yeah a mixture of your cum and a cat's cum.
Yeah that's how the tiger was made. You gave it to... you passed it down. It doesn't have
Down syndrome. It's Napoleon Dynamite's favorite animal. Is Napoleon Dynamite... we were
talk about this the other day, Napoleon Dynamite can't have held up right? It's
got to be bad. Oh no it's so good I watched it. No it's definitely still good.
Really? I don't know why you said we were talking, I said it's still good and you
were just like. No we were talking about Napoleon Dynamite and I'm just saying my thing is I
think that it's probably bad. He tried to make me say that Napoleon Dynamite. It's definitely
good I think it's one of the best ones from that era probably. But just him just going like
"Caw da faw da wah bop bop" It just looks nice and it has a nice thing going on. I don't care I don't even see
I'm only listening propaganda. You're only listening to it. Yeah, that's true. I guess I didn't think maybe you a question would be
It is Napoleon dynamite hold up if you'd are only listening audio wise if you're only
Listening. Yeah, I mean maybe not because I'd be like I'd be like this is so boring
Seen a single person in like a fucking vote for Pedro t-shirt or something. I think it's like we should bring it back
It's died down. Yeah, you know what?
Napoleon Dynamite for Halloween.
It's probably right at that level where you probably could bring back a vote for
Pedro. Like, like Angelina Jolie could wear a vote for Pedro thing and people
would be like, "Oh my God."
She's too big now.
If Channing Tatum wore a vote for Pedro t-shirt, I'd be wearing one.
You'd be wearing one right now.
I think a vote for Pedro shirt, though, I feel like for some reason in my brain,
if I see something, like a lot of other stuff, if I saw someone wearing it, I'd be
like, "Oh, it's like, it's a joke. It's a fucking old t-shirt." But vote for Pedro,
be like oh they like Napoleon Dynamite I'd still just think it was a some but what
if it's a hot hoe and you say well Napoleon Dynamite, shout out Pedro. She goes what what are you talking about?
This is about my councilman. Yeah yeah. This is about Pedro Gutierrez. In New York City that's actually a
possibility to vote for a Pedro. When I was growing up in North Carolina we it
said vote for Pedro we just thought it was the funniest thing ever. It was like when
are you ever gonna see Pedro on a ballot but these days it actually is and I think
You can see Pedro on most ballots now. Mm-hmm yeah most ballots you can vote for
Pedro. And in most ballets. Yeah male dancers. Yeah there's plenty of male
dancers. Growing up in a... Which used to, when we were growing up, not a male
dancer in sight right? They would do the, they'd have to put a mustache on
somebody do the nutcracker. Growing up in New England the only Pedro we cared
about until Napoleon Dynamite was 45. And when I was growing up in Bristol.
45 Donald Trump. Oh my god. Mm-hmm. You have a choice if you want to vote.
Which 45? Which 45 are you going to vote for? If you're from Boston you have two 45s to pick from.
Yeah. Pedro or Donald Trump. We had a 45 caliber bullet. Yeah. We'd pass around in
school. That's sad that there's guns in schools nowadays. Well we were taught how to use guns in school.
It's just the bullets. It's fine when it's just the bullets. There's no guns.
you get in trouble for bringing a bullet to school? Not if it's wrapped around your neck and it was
your grandpa's. Call up the teacher. Let's ask her. There's a kid who got in trouble for having a gun in my
school. Yeah there's a same with same with my school. There's a kid like said. But I never saw
the gun I just always assumed it was like a cool new gun. It was probably like a grandpa like
like Pirates of the Caribbean gun. Yeah. And that you know. What are you gonna do with that?
I remember my friend was friends with the kid who brought the gun to school and he
claimed that it fell into his backpack. That's possible. Yeah. It either fell into
his backpack or he left it in his backpack. If he lives in a gun store with high
shells and he's knocking into them all the time. Or if he lives in like Pee-wee's
Playhouse. Yeah. It's like a giant conveyor belt. It's like there's toast on it and cereal.
and then also a gun, yeah.
You're thinking of his house from his big adventure, not his playhouse.
Yeah, I am.
It doesn't matter.
The point is, you right now are being a dick.
I'm not being a dick.
I'm just a peewee historian.
Because you understood exactly what I meant.
You have dickish, and both of you have just dickhead fucking asshole energy today.
You're a peewee pissitarian.
You eat piss.
Holy shit, that was actually fucking...
I think he's innocent for what he did in that movie theater.
He's definitely innocent.
He was at a porno theater.
What are you supposed to do?
Fucking hold...
Oh, guys, what am I gonna do?
when I go home I'm gonna jack off when I get you you fucking sit there and you
fucking jack off on your yeah your hand yeah they should they should you're
coming to other people's business party fell well if it's like a situation sold
out premiere what can I do man there's fucking there's guys every fucking two
feet I'm gonna nut a little bit on out and I'm getting some on me I'm not gonna
look over my neighbor and say oh buddy you better not jack off and come in the
movie theater because we're both watching the same fucking episode of TV. Which also
brings up the question like you ever see like one of those pornos where it's
like a lot of men in one room and one lady you imagine the smell. The smell of
a bukkake porno is what you're trying to talk about now? When we were just talking
about Pee-wee. Only Pee-wee, we're talking about how he's innocent, he was fucking he was
persecuted because he was gay. Well imagine he's watching that video. Huh? Imagine that's the video he's
watching okay screen so you want to smell a vision kind of scratch and yeah a
bunch of them are just like like but body musk but and the last one at the
end of the bukaku it's like 16 guys it just says like do not scratch at one
time and is everyone in the theater faints it's just one person's like an
episode of Spongebob? Yeah. What's the name of Pee-wee's guy? Paul
Rubens. Paul Rubens, yeah he was multiple times the LAPD tried to get him
on bullshit. Yeah, because he was gay, he was a gay guy in the 90s so they tried to like...
same with George Michael. George Michael was set up. What happened to George
Michael? He went to buy marijuana from from his uncle Job. Yeah. Yeah and
then he was set up and he got in trouble with his dad, Michael.
And then the guy's arm fell off. Yeah. Yeah, really? Yeah, it was a whole setup. Yeah, I had never even heard of this
You know, it's all filmed. It was a documentary Eddie Murphy Eddie Murphy got fucking they got him for they were like
It's they got him for just having a good time. Yeah, Eddie Murphy was why you going to jail because you're using
Prostitutes since when is that illegal? I think the big deal about that was that the prostitute was trained
Yeah, but like that's what I mean
that's why the only reason they got that he got in trouble and he stopped doing
stand-up we lost some of the greatest fucking most homophobic jokes of all time
he probably could have written yeah right and he and they threw it away and they
threw away one of them but then he made that album could have been the third in
the trilogy could have been fucking fucking that album which is I think more
there's a lot of a little bit more could have been a full trilogy I was singing
the other day. If you could ask Bob Marley one question, what would it be?
You want to smoke this? Damn, that's a good one. Mine would probably be like, what
does music mean to you? Yeah, I would probably be like, how can I
succeed in life and how can I get $100 and what's the secret of
life and how what's the secret of happiness and how can I be as successful
as you probably probably song answering all those questions yeah yeah I wrote a
scary story oh it's Halloween yeah it's Halloween to bring in a Bob Marley
ghost-ass yeah fucka yeah yeah he's in he's in the big island in the sky uh-huh
yeah the big Halloween castle in the sky no it's downstairs there's one I don't
know definitely he did smoke I think he's still stuck in purgatory cuz he has to
atone for all the weed that's true true I think that's maybe maybe but he also a
lot of people like limbo it's part of his religion
No, I don't think that's true. I don't think they do limbo in in reggae.
Okay, this is a story, a scary story I wrote for October for you guys and it's a
little, it's I just want to warn you beforehand, it's very psychological.
Should I go ahead and start chattering my teeth? Yeah, it's well, so that's the thing
is it's kind of nails that I can bite on. There's a bunch of nails over there. Yeah.
Yeah, we're not building anything. No, human nails.
Oh, well, there's no building happening here. This is more of a psychological type of...
It's like a head trip. It's very... It's heady, you know, it's high concept.
I'm into trip. So, it might take a minute to get it.
Right. It might even take a day or two to get it.
I'm already so scared I bit my tongue right there.
So, it hasn't even started yet. I haven't even told you the title of the story.
I'm already scared. My little brother bit right through his tongue.
scary. My little brother, he was riding-- I'm afraid of doing that. My neighbor had this
like big scooter. It had like BMX tires on it and he fell over on it and had his
tongue out or something. Did he like chop it off? He bit the impact of his-- the bottom
of his jaw like he had to get like stitches in his tongue and he like bit
through until like the final layer of his tongue. I drank a really-- So think about that
when you hear Cameron's story. Okay my story is not about that. Okay but think
about the mental pain that a six-year-old boy went through.
Right, there's no six-year-old boys in my story.
Which is what Cameron's story is about, Cameron, go.
It's not about that. I haven't even revealed the title yet.
I just got a dope-ass text from my stepdad.
Yeah?
Love you, bud.
That's nice.
That's sweet.
That's pretty nice. Not really the vibe we're going for here with this current moment right now.
Yeah, but I need a little palate cleanser.
You should have done that when the story was done.
Yeah, the pre-palate cleanser. Before dinner meant.
Yeah.
It's an aperitif.
Yeah, okay. So the title reveal.
Dad Perall Spritz.
Step Dad Perall Spritz.
Dad Perall Steps.
That's what I just said.
Tall glass.
This story is called
Psychological Horror.
What's so funny?
It's a scary name.
You are telling a scary story
to somebody who finds
to terror. Listen, you might, you okay, you might, you might, you might find, you might
find zombies, monsters, vampires amusing. Believe me, there's, there's very few of those
in this story. This is, this is, I don't know if you've ever seen a thriller by Mr. Hitchcock.
Who's a Hitchcock-y? David Hitchcock. A new nightmare from David Hitchcock? Yeah. Wow.
Oh, yeah. Sorry, I stepped on one of the things. That's okay. But so I'm just gonna, I'm gonna,
I'm gonna I'm gonna get into this here. Okay, bro, and it starts like a dark fairy tale from the mind of Guillermo del Toro. Okay
Once upon a time Wow now the Guillermo del Toro parts over
a woman lived in a house all alone and
She left the house every day to go to work or to do errands or activities if it was the weekend or a holiday like Halloween
But the one place she never left was her mind her psychology
Suddenly, the doorbell rang.
Or did it?
Maybe it was all just in her head.
Her tortured, twisted head.
The doorbell rang again like the tortured cries of a man screaming for help from his
friend named Ding Dong.
His friend in this analogy is not Asian.
He's white.
Named Ding Dong.
Did it really ring this time?
Maybe it did ring this time, but the first time was all in her head.
She decided to answer the door.
The decision tortured her.
If she went to the door and nobody was there, it would mean that the doorbell ringing was
in her head both times, which would mean she was insane, or that someone rang it and ran
away, which is scary too.
And to be insane is the greatest horror of all.
But if someone was there, then one of the doorbell rings at least could have still been
in her head, so she might even still be insane.
But then she went and answered the door, and it was a terrifying clown drenched in blood.
Or was it?
Maybe it was just her kindly old neighbor and her twistedly traumatized mind was hallucinating
him as evil.
Her mom and dad were evil to her as a kid by the way.
She was traumatized.
Should she shoot and kill this clown?
What if the clown was real but she was hallucinating the blood onto him?
Or he could be a normal non-evil clown and she was hallucinating that he was terrifyingly
evil but maybe also the blood was still real and it was blood from his food or something.
Maybe she was so insane that she believed food has blood.
Maybe I'm so insane that I believe that.
That's a fourth wheel break.
Oh my god, he broke the fourth wheel right in front of us.
So she used her service weapon to shoot the clown.
She was a police officer, by the way, this is a plot twist.
Or maybe she just believed she was.
Maybe she was actually a clown and a police officer just shot her and she hallucinated
that it was opposite day.
Could her tortured mind conceive of such evil?
What darkness doth the human mind contain?
What sordid sickness can fester in the folds of one's fetid brain?
Since the dawn of time, we have killed our neighbors with rocks.
We have slain our compatriots with bone clubs and pointed sticks and AK-47s.
We are all clowns.
We are all policemen, at least in the dark universe of our minds.
Is not the imagination more terrifying than a thousand vampires and zombies put together?
The woman went to jail that day and she got sent to outer space, one trillion miles from
anything.
Floating in the void with no external stimuli whatsoever, she heard a doorbell.
Yes, she was insane.
And actually, she was in the shower all along, and she was a supermodel.
And there's no such thing as clowns.
Credits roll.
Story written by Cameron Fetter.
Story idea inspired by experiencing the fucked up world around us in Ari Aster.
Woman played by Megan Fox.
Clown played by ItTheClown.
Police played by CGI.
Space scenes written on location at Fetter Manor.
Darkness and evil created by the human mind.
Holy fuck.
Fade to black.
Post-credits scene.
Of course.
heaven well God is sitting in his chair hmm I think today I will make there be
such thing as a clown cut to new title logo the clown Wars coming 2023 Halloween
it you could also do another post-credit scene where maybe the woman sitting at a
she's sitting at a bar right uh-huh sit in a bar and she and she slides the
entire stool up her butt yeah and blood and shit goes everywhere yeah
I actually had that in an early draft, but my editor said to cut it.
And then Tony Stark walks in and he says, "I need you. I need your butt on my team of
fuckers. I need that. I need my head in your butt." And she'd go, "Okay, but now, butt
head." 2024. Butt head.
head yeah I still that fucking that's chilling that video the lady with the
head inside of her butt I think that's a guy I think I don't think women have
butts like that I think I think about that all the time bummed I think about
that that was like a year ago I talked about that on the podcast to the day
yeah you're gonna go terrifying oh my god huh remember that video yeah I do
remember that one Julie sent you were doing some you were saying remember it
insane stuff to me at the time of just people getting suction cupped into the floor and shit.
Oh yeah.
That guy just gets...
You would always hold up your phone.
You would always suction bag and just put in the ground.
Yeah, you would show us...
That one is really good.
That honestly scared me.
But you would just show us videos of a guy like tying his penis into a sailor's knot and
then we'd talk to you the next day and you'd be like, "Yeah, I'm not doing so well.
I'm still really torn up about that penis video."
No, it was only the...
I'd be like, "Just stop watching the videos."
It was only the one...
of the soul for this section.
- The butt, the butt head one.
- That happened multiple times.
I won't say what some of the videos were,
but I know it happened at least three times.
- The butt head one was the one that stopped it.
'Cause I was like, the human soul is depraved.
- Yeah.
- The human soul is completely depraved.
- It's just so funny to feel badly a day later,
'cause you saw an account called like, butt head sucker.
- Yeah, watch that butt thing, huh?
- You were like, oh, I think I should watch this.
- Butt head sucker.
- I think you should look at every single thing
this person has ever posted, because it's weird.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I don't like weird stuff like that.
- I'm basically like an anthropologist.
- I do like psycho--
- For weird stuff.
- Anthropologist, huh?
I do like, you know what I learned?
I'd never heard the term uptalk until this week.
- What's uptalk?
- Nothing much, what's up with you?
- Yeah, okay.
- What's uptalk?
What's uptalk, bro?
- It's when people talk like this.
- Oh, yeah, okay, yeah.
- And I didn't know there was a word for that,
but yeah, I just--
- Or what's the one where you do--
- It's like new, it's only come out
in the last like 15 years.
People didn't talk like that before that.
for that yeah it's like a new is it the same as when someone when someone ends
everything like a question I don't want to be well that like an example of that
right now I'm going to the store that's like Jimmy Carr never people do that I'm
going I can't I can't just let's like don't do it you put me on the spot there
well I can do it's actually just so up talk is when you like research is didn't
research you came in with a ready to go research I asked a question he put me on
the spot and made me perform and I did a pretty good job yeah I didn't know what
the hell you're talking about I'm saying I'm not sure I like that people girls
talk like that girls have vocal fry now it's not vocal fry it's different it's
a it's your inflection you ever know a girl and you talk to her and you there's
normal voice and then you see her talk to another girl and she starts going
(mimics a bird)
- Vocal fry, I'd rather have some,
I'd rather have a Coke and fries
with my chicken than my burger.
- I agree, 'cause I don't wanna talk like,
I just don't wanna talk in any kind of weird way.
You know, I try to eliminate all kinds
of weird accents in my life.
- Diet Coke and fries.
- That sounds pretty good because you're balancing
one with the other, right?
Now if they made a diet fry, I'm getting a full fat Coke.
- They make a diet fry, it's a sweet potato fry.
- What the fuck are you talking about, bud?
That's the same fucking shit.
- I'd rather be a total spy.
- Yeah, I'd rather be a--
exactly against Ukraine I'd rather be a turtle guy I'd rather be a scrotal pie
there's a pie I'd rather have a scrotal eye yeah I can see the inside of my
pants I don't know what they look like in there I'm seeing the outside of my
pants all day I'm going yeah yeah that's probably about the same color Wow
they're dark botanist a botanist I want to try that would you ever would you be
a dark botanist who maybe does like all Venus flytraps and those things of the
sort I would get those those like black are those desert roses I don't know the
like the ones that look like a like a sarlacc thing I saw them in Oakland I
don't know I don't know what you're talking about a black desert black flower
and it like our legs like us it looks like a worm with like a big desert rose
is a song by sting that's maybe the inspiration a desert rose looks mostly
just like a flower. A saguaro? A cactus? It's not a saguaro I think. I'll search
flower that looks like sarlacc. That's what you said right? It looks like a
sarlacc? Okay well what I'm seeing here is a bunch of pictures of sarlaccs. What
is this damn flower? Sarlacc pit. I want to take a large black shit. Yeah yeah
pretty much that's just in the sarlacc's mouth. No he wouldn't even notice. He
would like that. The sarlac is an old old thing. It's been there a long time.
You know it takes even longer for the sarlac to
digest a human. Uh-huh, why's that? You get tortured in their body for millions of
years. By psychic energy or something. It keeps you alive. It like keeps you alive so that it can suck your
energy out. The sarlac pit is crazy. Also they blow up into cum. But a lot of
people talk the thing is it's so old a lot of people talk say mean things about
the Sarlaac Pit it looks like shit it's fucking stupid and it just rolls off its
back yeah it barely even notice like rolls into its mouth rolls into its
crack because it's kind of is it the whole the name of the animal is just the
Sarlaac yeah but it's so is it I thought the Sarlaac was just the planet was
Sarlaac and Tatooine is the planet. Sarlaac is what we got Neil deGrasse
fucking Tyson over here talking about these planets. Buddy, I don't speak
English please. Yeah and look he's doing that you kind of do look like
White Nails to Grass Tyson. The more I look at you, you kind of have the exact...
Oh my god dude. You have the exact kind of like shadow. I should be him for
Halloween then. Yeah, white definitely. It's gotta be white though. Yeah you can't do
that okay I guess that's a good idea not but dress up like him mustache yeah isn't
it do you think it's worse you have a mustache it's do you think it's worse if
you are a white person dressing up like a black character and you he's a character
he's a black guy hey you'll aggress Tyson meet him on the street you're my
favorite black character he's a character in conversation that man has
some quips yeah and that's what I meant but like dressing up like a like a
black character or like just a normal black guy no I'm not any specific
character guy I'm just a normal black guy do you think it's it's where it's
not it's not racist or a problem because I'm just a normal black guy you think I'm
not doing make it fun of anybody. It's worse if you do blackface or you remain white and you have it like a perfect afro wig.
You remain steadfast and white. Perfect afro. I don't think that I what do you mean which
one's worse? You're saying like... Because it's like you because then you're being
very meticulous. I think it depends on who you are I guess. Yeah. You know if you're
being well do you think also maybe maybe you yeah. That's probably pretty bad. You could so you're
dressing up you're doing blackface for Halloween. Yeah. Okay and somebody says
that's racist. Well you're not doing, you're not doing blackface. Okay this is my scenario. Okay. And my
scenario you are doing blackface. This is my scenario. Well you're quiet in this scenario.
This is my Arsenio. This is what I'm trying to do. And somebody tries to get you in trouble. Okay. Yeah. And you say well.
And SJW basically. Yeah and you're like well it's okay because I'm not, I'm not, I'm not
dressed as a you don't understand I'm not making fun of a black person it's this
is me as as black that's what the costume is okay me if I was black you know I'd
say all these are probably pretty gonna be a pretty big problem yeah yeah it's
like when I guess it depends if you it depends maybe what where what kind of if
you're doing it in a place where nobody has nobody can see you or knows who you
are no one knows you don't speak sing like in like on the moon or Mars or
Venus yeah you're in the middle of like the Grand Canyon there's no one around a
park rangers. The people of the Grand Canyon are looking down with binoculars. That's a
white black guy down there. That's a guy doing blackface in the middle of the Grand Canyon.
For nobody. I guess if you're doing it for somebody. If you're not doing it for anybody.
If it's just for yourself. Well that's true about most things right? As long as nobody's
getting hurt and you're just doing it by yourself it's probably fine right? Maybe you're singing
on the car okay so it's like like say I was gonna be blade for Halloween uh-huh
not they're not not not which boy you gotta go Wade that's bladey it's blade
I would say bladey let's pronounce play that's why I asked what can walk in
voxel buddy I asked which one it's an important question one of them is black
and one of them is a white elf. There is a clear... I'm clarifying! You knew what you were talking about.
We've never asked any joking questions before. That's a good point.
We'll keep it to real serious questions. He's getting heated right now.
He's getting heated. You're like worse than Tucker Carlson.
Oh my god, wait. He is cooler than a motherfucker. You're a fucker, Carlson.
Damn. I'm so intimidated by this cool look.
Whoa. That's less, you look more like your,
you look like, you look like the, no longer the
um, the saxophone player from the Muppet band, but you
look like Sergeant Floyd Pepper now. The main guy.
That's a bit of Muppet history. That's his name.
Moving on. Okay, so if, if someone, if it's a white guy,
It's a white guy dressing up like Blade for Halloween.
But which Blade?
Is it worse if he...
uh... don't do that. Don't do that.
Okay. I had to fix something. We're not fixing anything, there's nothing built here.
It's just a table. Is it worse if he wears the like, if he's just like Blade
and he's still white but he has an afro wig
like Blade's hair?
does this is a good thing to do is make a little later in the afternoon
it is like a i don't think it would have been after a while
uh...
it's not a good idea
like i have a lot of the other side of the pro i'm thinking of seventies blade
is it worse if the white person okay
is it worse of a white person mimics
uh... black hair
i don't think i'm going to tell you
yeah yeah i guess i'm asking the is this a kind of thing you just sit around
around think about all day. How much you can get away with?
Can I just do the hair?
You come to me and Cam and you're like, "Is this okay? You guys think this is okay?"
So I'm gonna be Blade. Should I leave the afro at home?
I won't do the skin or anything. I'm not gonna do a voice, but can I do the afro?
The question itself just got more racist as I progressed.
And I didn't mean for that.
Of course not.
And I will have a no jab of apology.
cannot dress up as Blade the rapper because he's Scandinavian and that's
racist to do that in any context. That's obvious. Yeah. That's racist. Yeah. I didn't know he was a Euro. I thought he was Asian. I think he is.
Can you be, but then the other question is can you as a white person dress up as like a black person for Halloween?
I don't think so. No. I mean I guess. Like if a character in a movie. What about, okay what if like.
How many times are you going to rephrase this question?
The point of Halloween is to be evil I guess.
We have to get to the bottom of this issue.
What if you're dressing up as a white character but making them black for the costume?
Okay, wait.
What if you dress up just as a white character?
Perfect, perfect, perfect, uh...
Can you dress up as a character?
Perfect question.
Is it okay to dress up as something you're not on Halloween?
You are four white guys and you want to be the Ghostbusters.
Okay.
You just gotta invent a new Ghostbuster.
Yeah, I think that's a costume for three white guys and one black guy.
white guys and one black guy yeah or or you got to cut the white guy you say but
there's not a fourth you can be you can be stay puffed you can also I know they
resolve that issue in Ghostbusters - when Rick Moranis puts on the suit at the end
yeah you could be Rick yeah I guess I guess that answers that yeah but then
people will immediately assume like this is the science episode I'm doing yeah
Patrick's a race science corner I don't know why I'm a racial this is yes I'm
very racial today it's not my bag very racial on October 31st very racial but
it's not your bag it's not my bag what's your normal bag you feel like I've
changed a little bit mentally Patrick I'm a little more racial that I've taken
I've started taking Adderall and now I'm thinking too much about things Patrick
took our took our advice to heart about not dressing in blackface for Halloween
and he's the Halloween show he's gonna be dressed as the brown Eminem yeah yeah
- Yeah, which is, that's okay.
You can be a brown M&M.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause that's an M&M, that's not, you know.
- I didn't do blackface for Halloween.
- But you can't be a brown version of M&M.
- No one ever said you did.
- That's a bad move.
- You're asking a bunch of questions about it.
- You can't dress up like M&M but brown though.
(laughing)
- That's, all of a sudden, that's really bad.
- Yeah, that's probably maybe one of the worst,
is to take a, to, to, yeah.
- That's bad.
- That's really bad.
- Especially M&M of all things.
- It's not that the other stuff isn't bad.
- Yeah, but that could be--
- But that's a--
- Let's just say people might get the wrong idea.
- That implies a deeper sickness of character.
- Exactly, yeah.
- In your heart.
- You could dress up as a sick character.
- I'm still on that question in my mind.
- Can we just talk about something else?
- I gotta think about something else.
- Can we just talk about--
- 'Cause this is like a moral quandary that I--
- It's a quandary?
- It's a quandary.
Something has changed in me mentally,
and I'm scared. - It's a dilemma.
- Yeah, I'm just kinda scared of the new you.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah, I really am.
- I've been philosophizing too much.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
and i turn this whole episode into and into an ethics class
and ethics classes what you're talking about
reasons
yeah it's just not really i don't think that's really our corner
no no i think we talk about poopy and we do poop and diarrhea
our corner is not we don't do any racial stuff
okay we'll segue out of we're gonna segue out of
we're gonna segue out of
out of racial stuff
and into pooping stuff
yet how can you dresses poop in a way that's okay yeah
uh... as this is a little bit of a here's a little bit of a little bit of skin just
full terry where turd outfit like a paper sheet or doubt on how i'm good
what do you want to be diarrhea for halloween
then i think how do you do it
can you be liquid your face is corn
you people liquid and you have to answer this year home i guess if you're hydro
man
no you're dire yourself you know i was diarrhea man that we really did not see
actually now that I think about it. So do you get... How do I do? I guess if I were
going for creativity I might get a big clear garbage bag. This year for Halloween I'm going
for creativity. You know some people do their dumb creative costumes where they say I'm an
Instagram feed or something. There's a lot of stuff like that. I feel like that's an accepted
type of Halloween costume. I would take a big clear plastic garbage bag or something and I would
fill it with brown diarrhea and I would be inside the bag and have arm and arm
and leg. So you get like a suit like an inflatable sumo suit. No, but my arms and
legs come out. It's just a bag that's only around my torso. You suspend yourself in the diarrhea like David
Blaine. Yeah. And you just kind of sit there suspended. Right. Well that's more of a magic trick.
Well, if I have infinite budget then I will just develop a kind of CGI that works in
real life. That's true. And you have exactly Heidi Klum's budget. She has
probably enough money to make her own CGI. I thought you were doing some real life CGI.
Heidi Klum's buh. I was getting pretty excited. Yeah. That would be really good for making
diaries. That is seals. Dude, imagine the amount of diarrhea I could make for my costume.
Unless they're divorced. I don't remember. That's the other thing on my costume. At the night my
plastic bag would start empty and I would keep diarrhea-ing into it over the course
and i don't know if i mean
you can get a_c_l_ or a firefighter leave i thought believe it
i believe that i can't i'm conflating blade was all
on that one
uh... no i feel like this is maybe not the road you want to go down here
yet right now that i have a lot of black person to think about i was thinking of
luke cage
i don't even know that i don't know what he i know i know who he is i don't know
what he looks like. He's a superhero.
Oh, well I guess that's...
That would be funny though, just a guy here.
Just a guy with an afro. Oh no, I was thinking that.
Cause you don't...
I'll type Luke Cage in right now.
Luke Cage 70's.
Why is everyone in the 70's had an afro?
My dad had an afro.
Maybe Blade did.
So I'm seeing Luke Cage
as bald.
Okay, now I'm typing in 70's.
Okay, he has a...
I wouldn't say like a full big afro, but this is acceptable, I think.
I think you saved yourself.
Yeah.
Oh, no, wait.
Here's Blade with an afro.
Yeah, he had one.
But we're thinking of movie Blade.
Yeah, I'm thinking of him, and you know what?
I was thinking of movie Blade, too.
Yeah, you just eventually just had an afro on.
I just like went completely racial.
Yeah, just blacked out and just went...
Hey, don't say that.
Well, that's what you you blacked out like you went and that see again. You're taking everything racially. Yeah, I know
It's I have it on my brain. Yeah
This freaking pill that I'm taking is making me
Crazy, I think this is my Roseanne Barr arc Roseanne
I'm taking a pill and I've gone racial did she take pills she took an ambient and went racial as hell
Yeah, what you don't remember that she tweeted. She's I don't remember what you tweeted
something very
Ambien? Well, that's what she said. She said she was on Ambien and she was
trying to make fun of a senator and said that she looked like Planet of the Apes.
Oh God. Yeah. She said Ambien did that? Doesn't Ambien make you fall asleep? Yeah.
But then it also makes people on Reddit make funny random posts. The like
come down of Ambien or like the the come up. Yeah, which one is it? Like once you're getting
really tired. Yeah. You get racial. You get loopy. Oh, so she's saying I just am so
confused. It was me being random. But isn't she also like, she's been racist for like 30
years. It is also funny to take the thing where it's like everyone just
every like month you'll see a post it's about like I did this while I was on
Ambien and it's like I nailed a cookie to the wall or something. It's like yeah
that happened to me too and I got so racist. Yeah it's just mostly it's a
random pill right? For her she was like no. My randomness is racialness. I guess
that's true about Roseanne Barr. Have you ever seen the video of Roseanne Barr
singing the national anthem at a baseball game and she just like yeah one of the
worst voices I've ever heard. She sings it bad on purpose and she gets booed. Sounds like she didn't have
Roseanne Barr's. Holy shit that's well she didn't rap nobody raps in the national anthem.
Well if somebody raps in the national anthem that'd be on. I don't want to hear what Roseanne Barr would say in a rap.
Yeah exactly. And I know what she would say. Okay go Pat do it. Okay she would say
My name's Roseanne and I'm here to say...
No, she wouldn't say that. She wouldn't say that, definitely not.
She's a comedian, she wants to have a TV career.
Yeah, that's true. Well, her TV career was ruined.
By?
They killed her off of that show.
John Goodman.
Yeah, they killed her off of the new Roseanne.
That's so fucking crazy.
I'm so mad at John Goodman for stealing that fucking show from her.
And then it was called, what was it called after that?
It was called Connors.
Whatever the family name was, it was called this thing.
And then it was on for like five years.
years yeah and it just kept going it's like it's her name it was named after her
yeah bro didn't it was anybody watching a show at that I was watching every
fucking episode I feel like I maybe have never met someone in my life who watched
Roseanne I've seen a lot of episodes Roseanne the old Roseanne was very
popular yeah yeah and everyone watched it yeah people and was it when was it
from 89 to 9 and the thing she got kicked off of was that like a reboot or
something? Yes. Okay. Yeah, that was a reboot. Let me see how close I was.
'89-'97? Yeah. That's a pretty big range. Late '80s makes sense. I think that was old
Norm's first writing job. Really? Yeah. Wow. '88. Okay. And it lasted for, holy fuck.
'97? May 20th, 1997. Holy shit. Wow. Dude, only a couple months after the war. Look at what
this Adderall has done to me. You've always been like that. Yeah, you always
- You always know all the dates for every show.
You just don't know like traffic laws and stuff.
- That's true.
- Yeah, so maybe that'll change.
- Maybe.
- Do you think we could get you behind--
- You know, I do know traffic laws
'cause I've passed my written driver's test three times.
- All right, let me give you some scenarios.
- I've never passed the driving portion.
- Let me give you some scenarios then.
You pull up at a light.
- All right, this is my driving test.
- Yeah, you pull up at a light, right?
- Go--
- Right, he said right.
No, we're not trying to do a trick question.
You pull up at a light, right?
- Turn right, 100,000 hours.
He said it again, that means it is a turn right going 60.
No, you turn, you pull up at a light.
Left.
Right?
And then you have a...
But I pull up.
No, okay.
He's with me.
Okay, so there's an op, right?
You pull up, okay, here's a traffic light question.
You pull up at a red light, right?
You see an op pull up at a car right next to you.
Are you reaching for your blicky or are you getting snatched?
Blicky.
I think he's a blicky.
You reach for the blicky, that's right.
And you pull that fire on him.
You put five in his head.
Okay.
Can you ask me some real traffic questions, not this stuff that you're making up?
That's actually, that was, that is on the test.
Is that a DMV now? Nowadays, yeah.
Because of gun violence.
Chicago?
No, it's everywhere.
In the whole world, even beyond America.
The whole world, there's ops and blickies.
Even beyond America and the planet.
Different countries.
Is that, is uh...
Indonesia.
Is op, that's...
Stands for op olympia.
Where's uh...
Stands for OOPA OOPA.
It stands for operator...
Blicky originates from...
He originates from rap genius.
Op is actually, it's short for operator and it's a reference to Marble Hornets.
Slenderman, because Slenderman was their enemy.
Shout out Marble Hornets.
I'm trying to think.
I can see that.
There's just like some, oh there was something I learned the other day, because my TikTok
algorithm thinks that I was born in New York, so it's all these videos that are like, people
being like, oh man, the streets in New York are getting so bad.
That sounded like a brag. The TikTok algorithm thinks I was
born in New York.
No, but this, oh, it was a video where somebody said, I don't
know where I'm going with this.
You wanted to say this.
No, I really don't know where I'm going.
The etymology of...
The etymology of a word.
Of blicky, that's what you're trying to figure out?
You know what? First time I ever heard the word blicky was in
that 6ix9ine song. Okay, so that's good. So I think the Blicky
originates in Bushwick. Wow! Blicky actually is from the 1700s.
That's what the Union soldiers used to call their guns. Yeah, the
old muskets we used to call them "Blickeys". Oh, I've got a Blickey for ya!
You know the rappers in the UK don't have guns? Yeah, they have knives.
They have knives. And machetes. They're not allowed to use a gun.
Yeah, I guess shootings with a gun in the UK is completely fucking illegal.
It's crazy that people get each other with machetes over there.
It's crazy dude.
It's so scary.
That's scarier than a mass shooting.
How much harder is it to be also just like a gang member who has to kill somebody and
you get paid to do a hit.
You have to look him right in the eyes and you have to fucking stab him with a pocket
knife because it can't be over three inches.
You have to go kill the op, right?
Make sure you get him when he's lying on the bed
with his girlfriend, and make sure you get him
with an arrow and you stick it from the bottom of the bed
up and it goes through both of them.
And then also when the other one is walking on his hands,
you should cut him with the machete down through his legs
and cut him completely in half.
- Dude, there's a bunch of the rap songs over there
that talk about how you have to get a,
like when you get a gun, you have to go--
- I need a license for my knife.
- If you wanna get a gun, you have to go buy it
from like a farmer, and it's like fucking,
I don't like pipes and shit.
And so like anytime, like when people get caught with guns
in the UK, it's always just like the most fucked up gun
of all time.
- Yeah.
- And they didn't even kill the guy.
- Like a zip gun.
- Yeah, pretty much.
- They used to have--
- It was used for like scaring away like a bird.
- Yeah, they used to have a tutorial on YouTube
on how to make a zip gun.
- What's a zip gun?
- Like a little like PVC pipe gun.
- It works once and most of the time it explodes.
- Yeah.
I remember watching that where a kid took a bolt from a deadbolt.
Do you think they're using potato cannons over the UK?
Oh, absolutely!
Air spray in the back of a BSC pipe.
"I got my arm pulled up in traffic!"
Dude, when you start your car and you see the baking soda volcano start to bubble in the backseat.
It's fucking over, bro.
In Northern Ireland, a potato gun, was that an Armalite?
Mm-hmm the east side slider say hello
On the op and I've got I've got a little I've got a little red capsule
Yeah, and I throw it into his cup of water and grows into a giant
What you gotta do is you gotta find the chair that the opposite said all the time
It's it's so one did in what is what is a bet suspected to be gang violence today in a Bristol classroom
I
Can remember dies of complete and I just I just killed by sitting on a whoopee cushion
I just killed my ops pet bug with an air Zuka
Gang members slip on banana peels all over the London streets tonight
in a massive hit two people dead of largest gang hit in UK history must be weird in the UK like they
I've never thought about like, maybe they're all drinking Guinness while they're doing
this too.
I don't fucking know.
What the fuck?
Dude, I've checked out.
I don't fucking know.
What?
Oh my god.
That was crazy.
I'm too worried about being racial now.
You're too worried about being racial?
Yeah, I think I said too much stuff.
Now you have racial regret.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't think that you were all that racial, so it's probably fine.
I think I said too much stuff.
Yeah.
i think i've said some things but if you want we can make maybe the episode
we could bleep out it we could maybe
i think we could maybe bleep out every time you said the word black so it's not
racial so nobody knows but just leave everything just leave everything
surrounding and just bleep out the word black so just everyone knows you weren't
being racist great idea i think we'll do that how did that
conversation started because you guys said i look like white neil degrasse
tyson you do kind of you know when you did the pose i think i think if someone
traced that pose it would look pretty similar to the
the rage comic. You just have a similar head shape and you have a nice little
it's mostly it's the face where you can make a Neil deGrasse Tyson kind of face.
Yeah and you have a mustache too. It rocked your world to be called a white
Neil deGrasse. Wow yeah. Maybe one day I'll be as smart as him as a scientist. I would love to be Neil deGrasse's white son.
He's a fucking genius. Yeah yeah. Can you imagine being his white son? Oh my god.
Making him proud but a little more proud. Remember that Key and Peele sketch about him?
No, no, I remember this one where they're like
Remember the one where a a rock you
Hmm a a wrong the substitute and you guys have some funny names
You're my crazy student a a Ron and it's all about the crazy student. You're my crazy fucking student
And then he gives them the bird. Yeah flicks in the bird
No, he's a crazy bird on fucking and he says their names and he says like
preening what preening hey no and i'm the crazy substitute is there someone here
named
pob yeah yeah and it's pronounced poob
yep yeah it's actually blablian
it's blablian it's blablian
we should do our own versions of a lot of the pnpl skits
turd hucking it's called turd hucking
yeah and it's actually a sport that i'm named after
Oh, it's funny. Yeah. Do you guys think you could ever be a teacher? Would all the kids
names be too freaky these days? Yeah, hey, is there someone in here named Feather? Are
you kidding? One kid makes fun of my shoes one day, I'd kill myself in the bathroom.
I kill myself. You have to be an actual... And on the wall I write his name and I say
it's your fault. You have to be kind of a psycho to be a teacher, I think. I feel like
That's it. I feel like most other jobs where you like help people you at least get like paid kind of good. Yeah
Yeah, and that one it's nothing you were
Horrible you have to they don't pay you you don't you have a horrible like life
basically
Have you ever thought about how many how many of your teachers you look up like you have the yearbook at home?
You're looking through like oh, yeah, that's mrs. Whatever. Mm-hmm. How many of them have like this smile?
Yeah, they do have that smile. They have that wide
- That three year old boy, you tell him to smile
and he's just like, "Ah."
- That apple stare.
- Yeah, that's right.
- That fucking apple stare.
- That apple stare those teachers give you.
- That wormed apple stare.
When you ask for your grade and all she gives you
is that wormed apple stare right back at you.
- Wormed apple stare.
- That's fucking awful, dude.
- Think about how many, if you don't have that smile,
you can't be a teacher.
- Yeah, we should try to poison our teachers.
- You know what it is?
You know what it is?
That, I think instinctively you see that as a child
and it's like, okay, this teacher could kill me.
- I feel like I would get--
- This is like a primal thing.
I immediately view my teacher as a threat and I must obey.
- I would become a teacher just so I could be
on the front lines of mass shooting,
like detection and elimination.
'Cause I do think that if,
it's because I feel I would get,
I'd have psychological profiles in my notebook
of every single kid, right?
One kid's getting a little too close
to a kind of Lanza style. - Kids are going crazy nowadays.
And I would either put him down prematurely,
right, like before a dog has really bad cancer,
it's like you gotta do something about this, right?
I'm not chopping the legs off, I'm putting him down.
- Yeah, you just put stuff in his lunch food.
- Yeah, or honestly, if I know that he's gonna do it
even years from now, it's like, bro,
just fucking plant something on him
and report it to the guidance counselor.
He's gonna be in juvie, right?
- Definitely. - He can't do shit in juvie.
And then by the time he's an adult,
not my problem anymore.
If he wants to go shoot up a fucking Ruby Tuesday,
that's on the manager that Tuesday.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- You know, that's not on me.
- And there's a lot of Ruby, there's a lot of--
- I'm about protecting my kids.
- There's a lot of defense forces on Ruby Tuesday.
- I'm about to say something crazy out of pocket.
- Word. - Okay.
- Okay. - Something crazy.
- Do it.
- But I feel like with these teachers,
all the apples they're eating,
you cut open their head, there'd be a worm in there.
- A worm running them like inside out.
- Yeah, or just a worm in their brain like an apple worm.
- Like a-- - Well, who likes apples the most?
- Probably a teacher. - Probably a teacher.
- A horse, so maybe that's what's behind
all these teachers' attitudes.
Maybe that's where their smile is from.
- And they be kicking those things back.
I had a teacher who had a horse's ass.
- Yeah? - Yeah, big fucking legs.
- I had a teacher who also had a--
- I saw a lady's tail flapping in the breeze
the other day. - Ass like a horse.
- You ever hear a guy say that?
- But she had a thyroid problem.
- She had a ass like a horse and a guy does this.
- Oh, she had a ass like a fucking horse.
- It's like, why you wanna fuck a horse, bud?
- On a human.
- Yeah. (laughing)
- Well, yeah, a horse's ass would be hot.
- It's not like it's a horse then.
- And she could, you know, it's two for one
'cause then, you know, normally you're having sex
and there's all these flies right above your penis.
He's swatting 'em away with her tail.
- Yeah, the other, well then, you know,
they also don't know how to hold their penis.
- Well, like, listen, here's what--
- Yeah, and they're stupid, too.
- Here's what I'll say.
If you saw a horse with a human ass,
you wouldn't fuck it 'cause that's a horse.
- Of course, yeah. - Exactly.
- So if a woman has a horse ass,
you could still fuck her 'cause that's a human.
- That's easy, that's an easy hookup for you.
- Yeah, that's instant.
- Yeah, it fucking fits in perfectly.
- Yeah.
- Or no, it doesn't fit in perfectly.
I know, and what you said--
Don't you feel like you wouldn't be enough for a woman with a horse's ass, because those
horse cocks are so big?
I'd use a machine.
Extenderer.
Oh, you wouldn't try--
They do make those.
You can get like a penis extension.
I have one with a drill on it.
Yeah.
Yeah, who hasn't looked into making one?
I've looked into it, and it always looks like the hole for the penis is too small, because
I-- trust me, my thing is wide, but it's short.
Mm-hmm.
Stubby.
Yeah.
It looks like I--
My thing looks like Walton Goggins.
Yeah, my thing looks like Shrek's thumb. It's green too.
But don't you want...
And I don't think that'll fit in a...
But you're like, your penis is like an octopus. It can fit through a thing the size of a dime.
Yeah, you can squish it.
But you have to put it in like hard.
Well, that's why, that's the point of the penis biggerers is because...
You don't even have to be hard.
You're like burning, or not, you're like tearing your penis muscles so that they grow bigger and stronger.
It's like working out.
Yeah, it's like working out, bud.
I don't know.
Work your ball or your dong out.
I don't think it's like working out at all because it's like...
like exactly like we're close to working out no yeah because it's more it's it's
like the it's more like wearing a fake bicep I think it's like when spongebob
gets those big arms yeah anchor arms yeah that's this that's what you're doing for
your penis I don't think so I think you guys are talking about two different
things yeah I think you're talking I think Caleb's talking about joking I'm
talking about joking no I'm talking I think any me and Patrick we're talking
like a bionic arm or d-
- Oh no.
- It's like a hollowed out-
- It's like a hollowed out penis.
- Oh no.
- No, I'm talking about jelking.
- I know, but we're not talking about that.
- It's a hollowed out penis.
- Oh, okay, I'm understanding.
So how are you gonna trick-
- It's a hollowed out plastic penis.
- It's not about tricking.
- Oh, it's just like a-
- It's just a machine.
- But it doesn't, then you don't get to fucking nut cum.
- It's just a simple machine.
- You get to nut, but it's inside of a plastic toy.
- Yeah, inside, so on the outside,
it looks like a transformer's finger.
It's a finger.
It's got a lot of these ones.
It looks like Optimus Prime's sword on the outside.
On the inside, it feels and looks exactly like a fleshy organ.
Fudge.
Do they have one that just kills the woman while you're fucking her?
It looks exactly like fudge.
Fudgy, fleshy, modge podge.
But is there one where you put it into the woman and it just instantly kills her?
Yeah, and it's real.
What?
A thing that you put on her?
It's the one that we're talking about.
There are some people in those videos where it's like the people are putting their heads
up their asses.
- Yeah.
- There's people who put like the really long ones,
like it's like they're really snaking out like a pipe.
- Yeah, I don't understand all that.
- And it's just a plastic penis that's going
all the way in their belly.
- It's hitting the roof of your mouth.
- Yeah.
- Go buy a Halloween show ticket.
We're gonna be wearing those live.
Like we said, I mean we said it before,
lots of cool people, Sarah Squirm, Pierce Campion.
- Eric Rayhill.
Eric Rayhill, Jack Bensinger, we got a whole squad on there.
Tim Allen.
Crazy video, you seriously cannot miss it.
Come in costume, bring a pillowcase for candy.
Gotta have my candy, yeah yeah.
I hope this episode didn't make you feel any less spanky.
And I'm stopping the recording.