Come here, come here, come here!
Let me see your butt!
- Premium content!
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
- You're a freaking monster.
(explosion)
- And welcome to Dr. Peppercast episode Pepper-soad 2.
- You already fucked it, you did a dry run
before we even started.
- And you still couldn't.
- And no, it wasn't, you did the same fuck up
that you did 20 seconds ago.
- I'm hungover today.
- Well, did you say well-cam just now?
- Welcome to the new Dr. Peppercast, Pepper-Sowed 2.
I'm your host with the most, Patrick Doran.
- Wait, do you have, we don't have any
Dr. Pepper this week, though.
- Yeah, I think maybe Patrick is doing
a Dr. Peppercast over there,
and me and you are kind of over here.
- We're doing our own damn thing.
- And welcome to Dr. Peppercast and Pepper-Sowed 2.
- You know what this is?
You know what this is?
Two birds and one stone.
- Oh my God.
- That's what this is.
(laughing)
Two birds and one stone.
- I did show up, so.
That's what I'm seeing over here. I'm a bird, because I'm spreading my fucking wings.
We're spreading our wings too.
We're two birds in a hand.
And this is a straight bush.
You're a straight bush bird today.
You're a bush bird.
We went, um, me and Cameron did.
Me and Cameron.
Bush bird, uh, yeah.
Bush bird behavior.
Bush bird, you're acting like one.
Me and Cameron did trivia last night, and we won.
yeah so tell me what so I was curious because I missed out sure on purpose I
yeah yeah yeah we did it wasn't an accident I didn't want to go because I
knew I had to be up early okay and and I didn't want to be a straight bush bird
like some of us or a stone like some of us well I mean take a look at me though
I will say I was I guess I didn't I maybe didn't stay out quite as late
after the trivia but I still attended trivia and still one and I'm here and
I'm bright-eyed and bird-handed.
- So it's almost like one bird, two stones.
- Yeah.
- I didn't realize this, but you're a stone as well.
- Well, I'm saying I'm not a stone at all.
- And you're a bush bird as well.
- I'm saying you can be a bird.
- And I'm a hand bird.
- No.
- And I'm flying around as fast as I can be,
as I've always been.
- Yeah, hand birder.
- No, I'm not a hand birder.
- The bird in the hand doesn't fly.
The bird in the hand is held.
- The birds in the bush jump around in the bush,
first of all.
- You're stupid.
The whole point of the hand bird is that you fly with it.
- No.
and you hold on. I don't think that's the point of a hand bird. The bird in the hand is better
than two in the bush because the bush, who gives a fuck if they're in the bush, if they're
in your hand you can fly around like this. The bush birds are bad because you can't have
them. You can fly around like this all day with your bush bird, or your hand bird. I
guess it should be a bird in the hand is worth two birds in the bush unless you have a bird
net that works on bushes. Alright. Oh my god, wait, why don't you know. Let's change it to
that. When, like, it's like when people say like why not make the whole plane out of a
a black box. Exactly. Why not make the whole bush out of your hand?
Yeah. People say why not make the plane out of a black box. You've never heard that
before?
Why not make the whole plane the black box? Like the black box is the only thing that survives the plane crash?
Man, I don't hang out with a lot of funny people, you know? Yeah.
Not really people who let go. That's not really a funny thing though, that's kind of boring. That's what engineers say.
I'm not really into observ... like I don't know a lot of people who like to observe
things and make
crack little jokes about it. I mean, I've seen my friend Jerry. Really?
Yeah, my friend Jerry, he's like that.
I don't know him.
He's very observational, you know him.
Yeah, Dr. Jerry.
Hangs out with George and his friend Cosmo.
Oh, fuck Jerry, that guy is fucking funny as shit.
Oh, and the fat Jewish.
The fat Jewish, that guy is funny as shit.
That guy is so funny. Anyone else?
Beige cardigan.
That guy's funny as shit.
Yeah, these are all guys we hang out with
that we moved to New York.
But what I was saying is--
Mr. Funny.
Mr. Beans Laughing Meme.
That's like he's a he's more of a low-key guy. Yeah, but he is funny
He's what he's like that funny friend who won't be who won't pursue a career and being funny, right?
And it's like you want him to so bad, but he's never ever gonna do that. Yeah, I know guys like that
Yeah, yeah all these guys end up being my friend Nanette
You think her name is Nanette yeah, I don't think so I don't know what I still haven't watched that
You never watched the Hannah Gadsby special?
I watched it.
I had to watch it because I'm part of the Golden Globes.
I think it was
an in-yo-face approach
to comedy. It was.
It was in-yo-face.
And not afraid to back down.
I liked it. It was like,
you know, she's a deaf-jam...
It was confrontational in a
hip-hop kind of way. Yeah, it was in-yo-face,
it was unfuck-wittable.
It's the kind of thing you'd hear
blasting from a boombox yeah that's right what the subway Showtime into Douglas
that's not how it starts it's a very sad yeah it's so you're a fucking it's
actually I'm trying to paint the picture but I don't know any of the joke what is
What is so fascinating too about Nanette is it's less comedy, more special.
Okay?
This is comedy where the goal is not to make you laugh and make you think and make you
feel a certain type of way about the world.
Hey, if you wanted to, what if it was a scary special and it was called Banette?
Like the Pokemon ghost type.
Oh, Banette.
What in God's fucking name are you talking about?
So it sounds more like that would be a Pokemon special.
Why are you speaking...
What is...
Oh my god, Banette has a Pokemon special.
How about Beignet?
Oh my god.
And it's a Popeye's.
By the looks of her, I bet she enjoys a couple of Beignets here and there now and again.
What about Bobette?
Or a Didat?
See, he is a little hungover.
Am I the only fucking sober gopher in the whole fucking world?
way he said that, that's just proof. When someone says Bobette, that's proof of a hangover.
No, I literally just said, "What about Bobette or Dadette?" and I said it soberly.
That doesn't make any sense.
That's one of the top ten hangover signs.
If your friend says Bobette or Dadette, or especially both of them in a row.
Yeah, that's how you can tell your boy's hungover if he comes in and says Bobette.
Have you ever convinced yourself that you were having a stroke, a full-on stroke?
Constantly, every single day.
I think I do that every single day. I'm sitting at my desk at some point and I think, "Huh,
My eye is just as different than my other eye right now.
And then I feel, and then my face starts drooping
and I lose all control of my arm and my leg on my left side.
- My, my, my--
- And then it turns out I'm fine.
- Both my arms go completely numb a lot.
- Yeah.
- I'll get the--
- All the way from shoulder down to hand.
- I'll get the chest pain out of nowhere.
- Yeah.
- You know, like--
- I have heart, I think I have,
I do think if I went and got a full checkup at the doctor,
he would say, "You've had 600 mini strokes
"and 50,000 heart attacks."
I've had basically a heart attack.
And you've survived every single one somehow.
A long heart attack this whole year I think.
Is that just everybody has that?
Why are we not all...
I think about it all the time.
Every single day I'm thinking, "I'm having a heart attack right now."
Is that...
Yeah, I guess is that normal?
I think it's gotta be normal if I'm doing it all the time.
I think the crazy thing...
I've been hanging out with you guys and thought I had a heart attack and I never told you
guys.
Constantly.
That's what I...
But you had hepatitis A for like six months and you didn't know?
Yeah, let's just tell everybody my business.
Let's just go around telling everybody my medical history.
Fuck fucking HIPAA.
- I tell everybody my medical history.
- And do I tell everybody your medical history?
- Yes. - No, I don't.
- You like to make light of it.
- No, I don't like to make light of it.
- You love to make light. - You shed the light
on my hepatitis A fucking diagnosis.
That's what you just did.
- Yeah, how'd you get it?
- And I think I've already said it before on the podcast.
- Yeah, you have. - But that doesn't mean
I wanna talk about it again.
- You have talked about it. - How'd I get it?
What do you fucking mean?
I was eating guys' shit.
That's how you get it.
I ate a guy's shit.
And I don't remember if it was on purpose.
That's how you get it, is you have to eat shit.
You have to get shit.
You have to get shit in your mouth.
Is that funny to you?
The only way--
- You have to.
- Okay, let me break this down.
I had hepatitis A.
- Draw a diagram.
- Okay, here it is.
Here's hepatitis A, okay?
Hepatitis A, H-A.
The only way to get that is to eat human shit.
shit is to get shit in your mouth one way or the other not just in your mouth you
have to go it has to be swallowed what if it's not does it have to be human can it
be any shit no it can't go down all the way and it has to hit you and you have
to be able to keep it down it can't come immediately back up yeah no I kept it
down cuz I'm a champ yeah okay I'm a fucking bro I'm not gonna sit there and
spit listen I what okay can I ask you a question though what does have been a do
to you it makes you I don't know I didn't know I had it until I didn't have
it anymore I got over it so probably nothing then because you didn't know
well I did but then I thought back and I was like I think I was sleeping like 12
hours a day and I couldn't think and I couldn't and I lost a bunch of weight
that's what happened when I when I had mono and I didn't know it yeah but you
Did you eat anybody's shit to get that disease?
No, I kissed a guy though.
On his shit?
Yeah, on his pooper.
Or on his mouth?
On his lip.
Okay.
But he could have eaten poop.
See, his back down pants lip.
See, that's the thing is I could have eaten it,
it could have been somebody,
this is the scenarios,
it could have been, that the doctor was saying,
it could have been somebody made some kind of food
at a restaurant and served it to me,
didn't wash their hands. Right, and had poop glove.
It could have been a guy--
Oh my God, wait, you were tricked
at a restaurant into eating poop.
It could have been that. It could have been...
No, 'cause I remember...
We served you...
I remember...
Caleb, we've served you a delicious baked potato that it looks like skin all the
way through.
It's one of these...
It's a all skin baked potato.
It's one of these Idaho varieties.
It's a triple baked potato.
No, it never happened to me. I... But it could have been...
And it wasn't... This chicken finger's burned, Caleb, but don't worry about it.
We left it a little too long in the oven, but it's fine.
I remember, Caleb...
It's about burned and soft.
I remember you were saying...
It burned but still tender.
You were saying like six months before the diagnosis, I remember you were saying, "I'm
going to this like fancy Manhattan restaurant tonight."
And then...
Oh yeah, what was it?
It was called Excretions?
It's Excretions by Jacques.
Well yeah, why did you go to Excretions by Jacques Pierre?
I just had a fucking Groupon just this morning.
Yeah.
It was a Groupon deal.
You had a Poupon?
Hey, you had a Poupon in your lips?
Yeah, I had a Poupon on my plate and I fucking ate it.
So it could have been I ate it at a restaurant or it could have been I just ate somebody's
- Shit. - Even the flour tortilla.
(laughing)
- It's a black bean burrito.
- This is not what I want to be doing.
- And hey, you know what?
I know he washed it down with a diet doctor pepper.
- This is my real--
- Okay, so then what's this,
and Caleb's like, okay, that seems normal, I'll eat this,
but what's this little white scrap of paper
that's stuck to part of the beans here?
And then Chet was like, that's some white rice.
It's white gold leaf is what he said.
It was white gold leaf.
That's a white leaf.
And we put corn in there too in the tortilla.
Yeah I get it.
I ate shit.
It was south west style.
It's so funny that I ate shit.
It's so funny that I ate so much shit that I got sick for six months.
Yeah that's really fucking funny.
That I fucking ate such an unbelievable amount of shit.
From some fucking stranger that I got sick so sick. I couldn't get out of bed someday
Because of how much fucking shit I was in your system
Yeah, it's funny I ate so much shit it ruined my fucking life laugh it up I
Bet that's fucking funny you immature fucking asshole
bitch
That's just not right. If you ate shit, I'd warn you. This chocolate shake is so thick. It's like not even liquid shake
I didn't eat a chocolate shake. I know what it was. I know what it was. It was a chicken and tomato pizza from the pizza place I live above.
I know it was because they fuck things up all the time. One time I ate a--
They fuck things up and they put a whole log of poop on it?
It wasn't a fuck up. That's not what happened. I just know the guy. I know he's not that clean. He's a nice dude.
But one time he also served me one where all the chicken was somehow completely raw. They forgot to bake it before they put it on the pizza.
You're walking back up to that you walked back into the pizza place and you're
like this is a kind of a weird request but could I have a spoon to eat my
coca-cola with? It's like really thick. It did not, no. It was a really thick. I didn't get a
thick coca-cola. This is, you guys don't, you've never been through a medical emergency.
What are you talking about? I had mono. I didn't complain about it.
Mono is way different than eating shit and having sickness from it for months
and months on end and not knowing until after it's already left your system.
My spleen could have ruptured at any point. I do a lot of physical activity.
I had death blight. You didn't have death blight.
I had death blight. Alright, alright. We had real serious medical
problems and you're over there making shit up just for fun.
I was not making up. I had death blight. I remember you got barnacled into a ship for
a time. You were on the side of a ship. You were
in cover. You were entombed in barnacles for some time.
Him and the other guys he was barnacled in with, beautiful voices.
when they would sing when they would sing when they would sing you're very nice
voices and I remember that you would be completely still and then when you would
come to sing you'd be like and eat all the barnacles would crack off yeah not
all of them some of them yes Bill Turner bootstrap Bill Turner was your dad I
also got frozen solid one time really into a block is that why you're from a
different time no no is that what you drink I didn't drink a chocolate shake
with a chocolate poop cake next to it.
Where, you don't see those red and white striped straws anymore.
What the fuck are you talking about?
You don't see those red and white striped straws anymore.
Did you ever see those?
I don't think I ever saw those.
Shaw's and Jimmy Neutron in the 50's movie.
So you know the 50's movie.
The 50's movie.
But you don't see them anymore.
You don't see them anymore, but they used to be a big thing.
- Jimmy, the straws, the white and the barber shop
- Yeah. - coal straws.
- Jimmy Neutron's red and white straw
used to be in every malt shop
and every shake shack in the country.
- I don't think that that, I think--
- Maybe it's just difficult to make like--
- A red and white straw. - Plastic.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Well, nowadays, they're trying to make these straws--
- I think it's just, I think it's out of style.
- They wanna make straws out of--
It was a fad. It was a they want to make sure I was out of water and air now.
Yeah. Yeah, and that's just not for me. It's crazy.
How stupid paper straws are they got to be the worst.
It's insane. It literally like no, it's correct.
Like it's the kind of thing where you see people actually playing about it and
you'd though at the continue.
Can yeah, what I'm not speaking to anybody right now.
I'm kind of speaking to a ghost that's in the room.
But what you're doing is extremely distracting and ruining everything.
Yeah, genuinely you got owned.
- Yeah, but I feel like you see people complain about it
and if you had never used a paper straw
before you would expect that someone was being a baby
about it, but they literally in 10 seconds,
they're unusable.
- Yeah, they turn into mush. - Yeah, it's crazy.
- Dude, they're the worst things in the world.
They'll give them to you at the bodega
and then like I'll get a Diet Dr. Pepper
and then I'll try and drink it and then--
- You're trying to pepper cast again.
You're just-- - It's not gonna happen.
- The only reason you brought this up--
- Wait, reference, stop making,
stop making the trying to make pepper cast happen.
- What's that a reference to?
mean girls. The mean girls. Yeah, which is what you two are. A couple of mean girls.
I'm so not a mean girl. As if. As if I'm a fucking mean girl. Wait, I'm a mean girl.
You are a mean girl. You're a machine girl. I just realized. In your shirt. I wear a machine
girl shirt on. Yeah, you're a mean girl. Long hair. Mustache. I mean, you got reasons to
be mean if you're a girl with a mustache I guess. Yeah, bearded ladies are usually
always very mean to me. I kind of like girls with mustaches. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Frida Kahlo. Frida Kahlo, hot. She's just had a hairy head. She's had a
unibrow. Yeah. Which, kind of nice. That's a mustache. That is a girl mustache.
I mean, the question of whether something is a mustache, if it's a
mustache in the Mii Maker on Wii, then it's a mustache and a unibrow is a mustache.
- Yeah, exactly.
- It was a mustache.
- Do you ever know anybody with a real--
- Antenna, that's a mustache.
- Real crazy unibrow, you don't have one, right?
- No, but I could have had one.
- You could have?
(laughing)
What does that, what could that mean?
- Just with like, what happened in my life.
- A ghost of unibrow past came to him
and showed him what if he had done something different
in his life, he would have had one.
- Yeah.
- Maybe I'll start putting like,
I'll buy some like Rogaine
and put it just between my eyes,
try to grow big.
I feel like that might be a nice defining feature.
Yesterday, I saw, I had to have seen 10, 15 white guys
with perfectly bald heads that looked exactly like--
- Together?
- No, just different, no, that would've been a little--
- 'Cause together you should report that.
- No, no, no.
(laughing)
That's stereotyping.
Together I would've joined them.
- Yeah, so we have to report this now.
- No, I don't have to.
No, I didn't see them together, first of all.
I saw them separately.
A couple of them had almost the same clothes on that I had.
- All Amazon essentials.
- It was a fully Amazon, fully good fellowed out.
just good fellow straight from Target with an Amazon essentials watch but I I
was thinking I was like I need something that isn't just being bald to being bald
it's not enough anymore everybody has micro plastic you get a head you get
like a one hoop earring and wear a white t-shirt no that looks stupid what do you
mean that looks if I got earrings that'd be too much you got you get one earring
you wear a white shirt all the same white pants you were that okay
- Those weren't all white for a minute, like God.
- Lip piercing.
- I'm not getting snake bites.
- You should get a nose piercing.
- No, just one big lip piercing.
- A big one?
- The one that--
- You should get a boob piercing.
- I'm not getting a nose ring, I'm not you.
Do you have a nose ring?
- No.
- For some reason I thought you did.
- No, I have one earring.
- Yeah, on your nose.
- Yeah.
- My girlfriend has a septum piercing,
but she doesn't, she flips it up.
- Yeah, a lot of people do that.
- Yeah, she doesn't want it anymore.
- I know.
- But she doesn't want to take it out
feel weird. My brother has that and he but he he just likes it because it makes his
nose look a little different. Yeah. Makes it look like it has a hole in it. Yeah.
Interesting. But yeah maybe I'll get a... Maybe you should get one of them. Maybe you know
what you should get. I'm thinking about body modifications and I'm thinking
about gauges and stuff like that and I think maybe the next big step for one of
us is to get the hole that they put in the side of cows. You know on our stomach.
We've talked about this. We've talked about this. I don't know if we talked about...
We know we've talked about the whole I know we've talked about the whole have
been talking about getting it getting ourselves.
Yeah. You told me about it and it scared me.
So did we talk about it as a fashion statement is what I'm asking.
I think that also.
What are you doing?
Get him off the screen.
Who is that?
That's LL Cool J.
Oh, he looks good.
You're saying that's Caleb?
Oh, I could do that.
This doesn't make any sense what you're doing.
Yeah.
You can't you can't do this.
We're not supposed to be acknowledging you.
Yeah, you're really, you're not even supposed to be here.
Yeah.
That's okay. Ghost.
That's what, just leave that up the whole time.
Look at your phone.
But the hole in the side of you, if you're a cow.
So we already did the cow one,
so I guess we should think of something else maybe.
Okay, so if you're, for your, of the three of us,
who do you think is the biggest candidate
for that being a combination of--
It's fucking obvious.
Why you?
I guess what are you going to say
combination of?
But at the beginning of that question,
I could I can't think of a
combination of fashion and function,
which is what that whole could be.
Yeah. Which is.
Yeah. We we talked about this
already. We just put the food inside
of it.
But I have an upset stomach all the
time.
I have a sensitive stomach.
I also have a sensitive stomach.
But I've learned recently I get
stressed diarrhea.
Do you? Everybody gets stressed.
I've never I didn't do that.
Didn't happen until recently, though.
Oh, you're dying.
Yeah, I think you're dying.
What was that?
Oh, my God. You're death rattle.
And then I die. That was a great death
pantomime. That was good.
You fully knocked yourself out for a
sec.
We should get a coffin for you.
Maybe. OK, what about here's my new
I'm coming back. We did the cow one.
Have we done this like
a 50s sci fi alien where
it's a glass bubble and you can see
the brain.
Oh, my God.
Like evil, evil.
And then a cool, ironic kind of trucker hat on top of that, maybe even.
That's fire.
Could be the next level for Brooklyn fashion.
To show your brain off?
Yeah.
I think I would be a bit embarrassed at how small my brain is.
Oh, man, that seems like a you problem.
It isn't me problem, but I'm just saying that's going to be a big bear.
But maybe that could also give you-
But you don't know, you've never seen your fucking brain, you piece of shit.
I saw my brain when I had deathblight.
Why?
But I think that-
I can literally see my brain right now.
That could also be incentive to make your brain bigger and stronger, to work out your
mind.
see it so and you'll study you'll want to study every night if you don't fuck
your bro my god guys I think I'm gonna fuck my brain stop don't fuck your brain
leave your brain on wait my brain just turned around it's twerking yeah my
brain is twerking at me is it a boy or a girl it just took off its pants okay it
has no it's plain it has no parts so how is he supposed to fuck this how am I
gonna fuck you brain. What does this say? Go back to your business. So now it's back.
Yeah, it's back. That was really good. I could watch you do that all day. Talk to your own brain with
your eyes rolled back. That was cool. It hurts my eyes now. Yeah, it does hurt your
really eyes. So does crossing your eyes. You guys good at crossing your eyes?
I'm not good at it.
I don't know if I can do it. That hurts my eyes too. If someone can do it without holding their finger up, I'm
very impressed easily I'm not sure if I can I think I can't I thought I used to
be able to do one eye I used to be able to as well this girl Kelsey taught me
yeah you're doing it a little bit yeah I'm not not not good at it no you're
doing? You look stupid. Hold that face. Don't laugh like that. What that look like? I know
it look like I'm crossing the eye. You just look dumb. What is up with you? You just had
bubble. I had a bubble because I drank a white monster. What is this thing that you got?
Super Elixir. Hero hydration. So you would say that you going out and doing trivia last
night and getting fucked up is heroic? Yeah. I mean, hey, I'm fucking dude. It's Marvel,
Brandon. I got some crazy questions right last night. Oh, here's my question. Last night
I insisted that the capital of Newfoundland was Newfoundland and Labrador.
He kept saying it over and over and everyone kept saying, "No, Patrick, the answer is the
city."
They're asking, "What's the capital of Newfoundland and Labrador?"
And he kept being like, "If the answer is Newfoundland and Labrador, and if I'm wrong,
you can kill me."
Over and over and everyone was like, "No, that's the question that they're asking."
And then it was...
What was the answer?
St. John.
The answer was St. John.
St. John, that's a fucking guy.
Yeah.
That's a bold statement if you ask me.
But I did get what gay blues singer was in Inconvenient Truth.
Who's gay blues singer?
Gay blues singer is Melissa Etheridge.
What?
Yeah, that was the answer.
Oh, gay blues singer?
Yeah.
Oh, I thought you, honestly, I thought you said gay blues singer.
Gay blues singer is this guy who keeps coming to the bar.
Oh, he doesn't sound very cool.
A really funny one, a mishearing of those that happened.
I was talking to I was talking to Pierce about Spy Kids 2. Like we were already
talking about Spy Kids 2 and then he said something about like Spy Kids 2.
Like I get he just said that phrase again and I was like what is spike and
stew? And I was so confused. Spike and stew? Yeah. That is crazy. We were literally already my brain was loaded into Spy Kids 2 and I still somehow. Oh my god. Yeah. You need to go to the, you did have a stroke.
Spike and Stu. Spike and Stu. Spike and Stu. Sounds good right? It does sound good. I can
picture it now. Spike is small and Stu is tall. But Stu is business class. You're thinking
STU. Stu is business class and Spike is economy. That's what I thought when he said it. I thought
I was singing S-T-E-W.
And I was singing it as Spiked.
Spiked Stew.
I thought it was...
There's different ways to do it.
Spiked Stew.
Do not taste of the Spiked Stew.
We did it again.
With you saying this story.
I thought you said Spiked Stew.
And he said Spike and Stew.
But he was saying Spiked Stew.
Oh my God.
Spike it's stew. Oh my god. Wow. Is there even a fourth one? Spike it's stew. Spike it's
stew. Spike and stew. Spike. Nah, it's not worth it. Speak and spell. Nah. Did you guys
have, was there any time last night where you, there was somebody who said something
about like sports or something on the trivia things and you were like, God I wish Caleb
was here. There was no sports. There was not a sports section but we fucking do. We crush
It's like words that end with Z or end or begin with Z and we said
You have to come up with a word
What no that was a category? Yeah? Oh, what was the word there was 10? Oh, you know what?
What was the one proud of me? Okay? I'm already proud of you, buddy. I
Got one of the answers was Zaza Petulia Zaza mm-hmm
Game seven mm-hmm. Do that's a guess I all-timer video one of the ugliest people. Oh my god
Zaza Pachulia. We're going to game seven! Nothing easy! Yeah he's awesome. Yeah. He broke Kawhi
Leonard's foot or something. Wow. Yeah it's pretty fucked up. That's crazy.
All right. The ghost is playing a puzzle. I was going to... I think we just can't
talk about the ghost or mention it anymore because it's feeding off of
our attention right now. That's true. So you actually have a bad fucking attitude. We're putting it a ghost
embargo right now. No ghost mentioning or looking at. I've already been doing this and you two
have insisted on talking to the ghost. I'm saying it to Patrick because I also was doing
that and Patrick said that the ghost was doing a puzzle which I was ignoring. You know what
I want to say some things about the ghost? Talk about them. It sucks. I don't like living
in a haunted office. I don't like living here period. I hate this haunted place. I would
really rather live at home with my girlfriends. I really don't know why I choose to live at
the office instead of at my apartment. Especially because it's haunted. It makes no sense.
I saw a cockroach. I don't even have a bed here. You saw a cockroach here? Yeah. Did you
say you saw a mouse here? Did somebody say that? I think that there's a mouse in there.
Oh, that's all bullshit. I think there's a mouse in the ceiling. Or in the walls. What
the fuck are you fucking talking about? Why? I heard like, I was here alone and I heard.
Don't tell me you heard a squeak and now you're saying, wow. You think that you heard a squeak
and there has to be a mouse? What if it could be a toy? Or a squeaker? Or a squeak?
That was a distinct mouse sound. You don't know, you don't live with mice.
Somebody could have been watching a mouse video on their phone. That's a good fucking point.
Flying on the floor upstairs and playing a mouse video into the floor.
Did I ever tell you guys that my, or did I not ever, but did I tell you guys that the mice are
back in my apartment? It's becoming a yearly thing. You should get a cat. Dude, I already
got a dog. My mouse. And buddy, they don't get along. That's like me having a dog and you saying
you should get a mailman. It's not gonna work. But I found Moe and he's
been living with me. Why are you talking about your cat like he's
like your gay boyfriend and we're your parents? I found Moe, he's been living with me.
He's been living, ever since he's been in the apartment, all the mice
have gone. I guess the other day. Yeah, they should be scared. Although he's the same size.
I keep he walked into the living room up to kneel with him
What he's so small that's killed it dude good for him. Yeah, and good for you. That's a right of passage for him
Yeah, the man now. That's that's secured his his space. I still have not even fucking met this kid. Yeah
He's a fucker
Is he big is he big now? He's getting big. He's pretty big now. What are you feeding him?
He eats like half a can
Every morning an entire like the metal and all like yeah, oh wow yeah, that'll be Jesus dude. He's a straight
He's a scrapper to a robot. Yeah, I wish that's a robot. Oh my god. You're debuting this character now
I can't do it yet
That's a little taste. Yeah, you'll see you guys will see it in future episodes
Yeah, big changes coming around here, and we might have Cameron doing a robot. Yeah, it's called. Don't say what it's called. Yeah, Mo
Don't say that. Okay, he'll be doing some kind of robotic character. Is that better?
Yeah, we put a
For I don't know why when you remember that couch that we had yeah
No one wants to get rid of that big couch cushion that came with it
We got rid of the couch, but kept the cushion for some reason
It's like a boogie board and now that just on the chair in the living room. It's just like up against the wall and
and Moe climbs to the top of it and jumps off.
- Trying to kill himself.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause he hates you so much.
- He doesn't hate me.
He sleeps in my bed.
- That's 'cause he wants you to fucking
roll over and crush him.
He's trying to kill himself.
- He's not trying to kill himself.
- He is.
- Do you think a cat could land on its back
if it wanted to or they can only land on their feet?
- I wanna see a cat while it's jumping
jump backwards like this, coffin style,
and then pull two deagles out and then--
- Damn.
(laughing)
They're firing on every house in the apartment. That could be some fucking Resident Evil movie shit.
And then land on its back.
And land on its back, slide across the floor, still shooting.
Then, kip up, right? Back into a backflip.
Backflip and back into the coffin.
Yeah, back into the coffin, lands on a guy's head with the guy's head between its legs, right?
Breaks his neck with his legs.
Twist, yeah.
And then he goes into a...
into oh my god then when he lands he says meow it's personal per all per its
meows in all or no yeah I just used the meow no wait what would he say if he's
an action cat a caption in the cat room stars if he was what fuck it a catch and
per action star clar a cat an action action clar an action claw if he was a
Caxton Clarke he was a brother squire so if he had the brothers score
Also before this whole scene there's a close-up on his eye and and it narrows a little bit then a close-up on his paw claws come
out yeah
And then claws go I cause weird claws go on get a gun
Oh, and he has a scar down his eye Moe has some kind of like we're not
I don't care about your real cat. I want to know what we're talking
This is what I've been picturing the whole time, but fucking what would okay?
What would all right? I said what mo would be doing all right?
What would most say we need a good phrase for him to say we want the dialogue for the movie because that's a lot of
People don't know a lot of movies. That's half the fucking movie is the dialogue and people fucking forget that
I'm I must have just gotten one kill per bullet and then he could say he cut somebody's throat with his paw
Yeah, and he says he needs some milk. He says that's what I call giving throat
I'm here to shoot bad guys and eat and eat
Purina or no, what's a good cow mix is a cow
I'm here. I'm here to sniff cat or eat catnip and kick ass. They don't eat and I'm all out of cat
They eat it. They don't eat it. They sniff it and they go crazy. They eat it
Oh my god, and even before all that's and he sniffs catnip and that's what gets him another kill
Oh shit, that's what gives him his power like fucking people in real life. It's like Bane with the venom
He smokes the catnip like a joint.
He has a syringe of catnip that he puts into his body.
He smokes the catnip.
Like a cigarette.
Maybe he could be like...
That upset Caleb I guess.
Yeah it seems like...
I can't do this.
If a cat can smoke a cigarette, I can't do this.
Maybe he could, maybe his line is he's pointing a gun at somebody and maybe he says something
like...
Careful, that's going to foam over.
He says something like, "Lights out furball."
yeah but he everyone in his head he doesn't like everyone looks at is a cat
to him yeah no also maybe he's putting in a mouse also yeah so a mouse has fur too
well okay so that's the other thing is well I guess we're just coming up with
at this point it's just cats versus dogs it's a movie this is cats versus mice so
it's completely there's a video of a cat smoking a cigarette holy shit he's not
smoking it that thing isn't even fucking lit not even it has the cigarette yeah
I mean he's not smart.
Poor performance.
Smart cat smoking a cigarette.
Purr-formance.
Oh my god.
Purr-fer-mance.
Purr-fer-mance art.
Purr-fer-man who is a cat.
Yeah.
Well what, yeah I guess what if it was like taken, what would somebody need to take to
uh...
His toy.
Like a sock or something.
Definitely his toy, yeah.
Or his owner.
He took my damn...
Or his daughter I guess.
He took my damn sock.
It could still be his daughter.
And my daughter.
about their kids. Yeah. Trust me. Maybe it's all of the kids. You took a damn sock that I
played with and I'm coming for you. I'm coming! Yeah. And then he would say I'm coming. I have a
particular set of kills, because this is more about killing than skills. I have a particular
set of paws that I can use to kill and claw your brains out. Yeah. And that's the thing, his gun
would probably just shoot claws. And then he could, right before he kills the final bad guy, maybe,
Maybe? Maybe.
Your litter to me.
Mmm.
And then he shits in his mouth.
Yeah.
Almost a jinx.
And then he does that thing where he
licks his nuts.
Oh, yeah.
They lift their leg up.
Post-credits scene.
They lift their legs up and they lick
their nuts on you.
Yeah.
He isn't neutered yet.
Post-credits scene, Linger by
the Cranberries is playing.
Oh my God.
And it's a romantic scene between him
and his own nuts.
Yeah.
Right. And it's like cross-cutting and
it's like, "With you."
Because earlier in the movie, his ops try to send him to a vet to get him neutered.
Oh my god, this is the movie. He gets sent to-- the bad guys capture him and they say,
"We're going to neuter you."
Right? They neuter him, and he calls him, he says,
"You got my damn ball sack over there at the hospital.
And I'm not coming for just my balls. I'm coming for my brother's balls, too!"
He comes in, he's doing a backflip, coffin flip, kills the vets, slices their fucking
necks off, and then it's a reuniting.
He gets, look at those cat balls, those are awesome.
He gets them off the pickle, out of the pickle jar, right?
He got his buddy who's maybe a smart ass parrot going, "I'll put your balls back!"
Right?
He fucking uses a nail gun, shoots them back into his body, and then Cameron's eyes went
cross-eyed for a second.
About this concept is it's so good and then and then
They're like he's with them. Oh my god a parrot is already fucking unlikely. It's a bird a cat
Yeah, but they're both pets been a mouse
No cats try to keep birds teams up or a parrot and a fish and a parrot fish and mouse but a parrot speaks English
But the mouse teams up can I get your post-credits scene for this version of the story?
Okay, but real quickly linger plays and he starts fucking licking his balls, and that's like the romantic fucking reunion
So they put these balls back on his body with surgery.
He gets the parrot, the parrot puts this back on with surgery.
Post-credits, post-post-credits, this is the very last thing.
And it's like, and he's like, and the parrot's like,
"I just realized something."
What's the cat's name?
- Chevin.
- "I just realized something, Chevin."
- I just realized something, Chevin!
- No, it shouldn't be Chevin, it should be Mittens.
- I'm not sure that those were your balls.
And then, because there were human balls all along,
the cat has--
- Oh my God, the cat has big human balls.
- The cat cat has big human balls,
the human testosterone pumps into his body
and he becomes a human hybrid.
- Or, you know what a good thing would be,
is he says, "I'm not sure those are your balls."
And then cut to, there's a Polish--
- The bad vet.
- The bad vet is driving away,
"Get your motor running."
(imitates engine revving)
And in the driver's seat, right as it goes,
"Bond to me, wah!"
The pickle jar with his actual balls in it.
- Oh, I was gonna say--
- And it says labeled at the top, "Mittens."
- Yeah.
- And he did a swap.
was here's what I thought here's where I thought you're gonna move is called the
no it cuts to the bad guy who they defeated yeah and he's like he wakes up
and he's like bloody and battered and he straps to a table he's like where am I
he looks down cat balls on his ball oh so there was a switch oh and in the next
movie they have to team up to find a third pair of balls to put on their
friend. Yeah. Could be pretty good movie. Does a snake, does a, if you did that with
any animal it would work except a snake so we have to cancel that. So we can't do
a snake version of the movie. Snakes don't have balls. They have testicles maybe, I
I don't know.
They have a chinchilla pee on me.
That's that's awesome.
Oh, no. And my roommate had a skink.
It's going to get so off topic.
But the snake version of his balls could be
well, look at snakes have a hole that opens up and their things pop out.
It's all just one thing.
OK, look up. Snakes genitals have balls.
They have two balls that function the same way a human do.
Take a screenshot of that.
Yeah, you need to screenshot that.
That is incredible.
Wait, snakes have two penises?
Do snakes have balls?
Two balls.
They have two balls that function the same way.
Yeah, they have like a slit that opens up,
and their penis and balls comes out.
Whoa.
Two balls.
I'm seeing here it says snake puzzle ball.
That's not a puzzle I want to figure out.
It's a puzzle trying to make these snakes fucking
cum these days.
Yeah, it's Chris Pontius talking about breeding snakes.
It does look like Chris Pontius.
I do think that maybe this is, it's just hard to have a snake as a boyfriend.
I think the snake balls movie...
Unless you're a female snake, of course.
The snake balls movie is even better because it's hidden whether or not they have balls
until you open up their little kind of genital area thing.
So there could be a lot more tension and suspense as to whether he got his balls back or not.
Let me tell you, their genital area...
It's bussin', bussin'.
It's bussin'.
Mine stinks.
I think there stays busting well in Udalla. Mine is similarly scaly and scuted.
I'm, my genital area this month, molting. One time I did, I've found, I've found it
previously, I've found just full scabs in my pubes. Yeah? Yeah, just full scabs. From
from grooming it? Or like dandruff maybe. Maybe dandruff. Just like came to the surface.
Do you have psoriasis? Probably. What's that? It's what my grampy had. Yeah, I have that.
did you how do you know about it he had stuff on his nuts he had like like
flaky hair on there you had like yes the grossest people my grandpa's pubes were
disgusting they were white and wiry ah wait you don't get white pubes when you
get older do you do I think you get gray pubes like Gandalf's beard
Jubo can you look up yeah thank you images images images for grandpa pubes
See, they go white.
None of these are white! Why are you saying they go white?
That is a lady and it says ginger pubes.
They just don't look... by the looks of it...
That's a guy...
Just google "do pubes go white?"
Just google "pubes of white all over them."
"White ass pubes."
Okay.
This is a guy...
Nasty boy is done.
That's a guy with his whole hole out.
He's completely bare.
He looks like he's made of silicone.
- He has no pubes.
- Yeah, he honestly looks like a gummy candy.
(laughing)
- Yeah, he does look delicious.
- I genuinely would eat that if it was in front of me.
(laughing)
- All right, yeah, now Google candy.
- Do you guys think it's okay to eat butt?
- No.
- I think that's wrong.
- I don't think it's right.
- We're gonna take that out of there.
- Yeah, I think it's--
- We're taking butt off the menu.
This is officially, we're stepping in here.
It's been some kind of fucking emergency thing
where people got the wrong idea about all this stuff.
And God never put that butt on your body
so you could fucking put it in your mouth.
Or put it in your wife's mouth.
- It is fine.
But for me, I'm going to the butt buffet.
- You're not going to the butt buffet.
- You're literally a munch, dude.
- You're a munch, dude.
- You're acting like a munch right now.
- You act, nah, dude.
- That's actually a compliment.
So a munch, being a munch is not a compliment.
- Dude, I would not even put my mouth on a woman's leg.
I'm not putting her butthole in my mouth.
(laughing)
- That's disgusting, dude.
- Now, a machine that goes into the butt is okay.
- That's fine, or a different guy.
- It would be fine if maybe--
- Or maybe like a fist.
- A machine--
- That's fine, I'll put my hand in there.
I've put my hand in the toilet before.
- Look, I'll put my hand in there,
I'll use her like a puppet.
- Yeah, that's fine.
- Yeah, maybe even just a puppet.
- That's disgusting.
- A puppet's mouth can go down there.
- I shouldn't have said that.
- A latex puppet.
- Yeah, that's fine by me.
- That's fine.
Did you see Jeff Dunham is still not canceled?
He's still not?
Speaking of puppets, that's the name of his new special.
Is still not canceled?
Jeff Dunham's still not canceled.
Didn't also Terry Fedor also have a bit of a...
Well, it's crazy that every single ventriloquist...
Culture war, you're saying?
Yeah, every single ventriloquist is like that.
And I guess it must be because they're doing...
It's like an antiquated art form, ventriloquism.
It is. I mean, honestly, it is genuinely impressive, like for Jeff Dunham to do to have a comedy
thing that is so unappealing that nobody cares about it enough to try and get mad about it.
Right.
But also has so many has a bunch of fans. That's so impressive.
It's like, is he does he actually care about being canceled or is it just because his audience
is like geriatric?
I don't think he'd want to get canceled.
What do you mean?
I think he's just I think he's just playing it up.
Cancel culture you're saying that Jeff Dunham. You're this is your theory Jeff Dunham might not have the
Best intentions yes, oh wow
Yeah, that's something about here. That's a tough pill to swallow
Yeah, and you know what he tricks his entire audience into thinking that there's a little man
Yeah, you go ahead and try to cancel a fucking wizard, buddy
See how that fucking exactly pans out for you you want to this guy can make a puppet talk
Right here gonna. You're gonna say hey, buddy. You got to stop doing you got to stop
Yeah, you're cancer right and then he does in your perfect voice makes your mouth moves. That's a pedophile
And then all of a sudden you're in fucking jail
Who's canceled now? Yeah fucking you absolutely?
This guy he can control he can cancel Jeff Dunham
You can't do it make a puppet talk with its mouth you do not want to see what this guy can do to a penis balls
But in between areas, I don't want to go against this guy
He could do pretty much anything under the sun. Put me and this guy on fucking Final Destination Super Smash Brothers
He's knocking me off, KOing. Yeah, he could hit fucking 300%
He's not moving an inch. I would not I would I genuine I would rather die than be in the octagon with Jeff Dunham. Me too
Oh, yeah, cuz he'll turn the octagon and he'll fold it up like origami
He's an origami expert as well. He's great at origami. And then I'll start fucking making it talk to me, right?
It is interesting. All of a sudden and I think I won the fight right all of a sudden I'm sitting there
I'm talking to Joe Rogan. Exactly. He's doing I realize he's a fucking puppet. He's doing
just puppeting every Jeff Dunham is making all the audience members cheer. Yeah. Or in
boo. Exactly. Yeah, different ways that make me think the fight is going differently. And
then he makes the announcer voice the fight is over. Please take off your pants. Wait,
I'm not knocked out. But I guess I'll take my pants off because a ref told me to then
his hand up my butt me saying I lost the fight. I surrender. And then I'm talking to the referee.
I'm saying listen peanut you're a great ref right but I just don't I I just
You're you're you're listen your your career speaks for itself. You've officiated so many fights. We know this peanut, but P. Listen up
Sit up P. I didn't get knocked out. I'm not slept. I barely we haven't even touched each other
He's telling me I got knocked out fucking bullshit basically. Yeah, he says you have to go back to my corner, right?
And I'm he says you were knocked out by Jeff a foot
I'm getting my towel or my head toweled off right and then my coach right he looks at
Caleb you gotta you just give up. I say Walter. Hey Walter. What Walter? Just just let me fight man
Just let me know you're already concussed
And then there's like and then the jalapeno is giving out jalapenos and then Ahmed
Yeah, and then Ahmed comes in blows up the whole fucking place. Yeah, you ever see the photo of
Jeff Dunham did like it's like
"Ahmed, this is your son."
And then he had like a half boy.
- This is not, don't pull up photos of Sean Evans, Jubio.
All right, I'm starting to like the ghost a little more.
The ghost is starting to make me laugh.
I can't lie.
- Can you pull up a photo of Ahmed, the dead terrorist's son?
- He has a son, oh, he does have a son, doesn't he?
- What, why do you look up, no.
(laughing)
- He's got a mind of his own.
he's not doing his job. Good for him. But Ahmed's son is like, he made
like a little boy that is half skeleton and he's like, "Hello
daddy, you blew me up!" He's got a British voice? Yeah. That's cool.
That's kind of a political statement. I think honestly for that he deserves to
be canceled, but you can't cancel him. How can you cancel Jeff? He's uncancellable.
Can you imagine the 10 apology videos he could make?
Yeah.
In a grid, playing at the same time.
He's sitting there with all the puppets in the room with him and he's doing their voices
but he's...
I don't want Jeff Dunham to apologize, I want the fucking puppets to apologize.
I don't give a fuck, what Jeff Dunham, Jeff is not saying anything.
I don't even know why he's on stage.
Why is he fucking wasting...
It would be nice if Jeff was cancelled, we could just have a show that's just the puppets.
Yeah, yeah, true.
That's a good point.
Get rid of Jeff.
Here's the thing, nobody ever liked this Jeff guy anyway.
Get rid of him, bring out Ahmed, bring out Jose,
bring out Walter, bring out Peanut.
That's what we wanna see.
- The four of them together.
And you know what? - How come they don't
all four do stuff together?
- We need to give them--
- They never watch the Jeff Dunham show on Comedy Central?
- But that has Jeff.
- Pick up these guys for SNL.
Why are we picking up Lonely Island shit?
- As writers, as writers go.
- As writers at first, but maybe they can work their way
onto the cast.
- Can you imagine the please don't destroy guys
in the same writing room as Peanut?
Oh my god, Peanut's pitching the greatest stuff
that they would turn out.
I need to see a video of those three with Peanut.
I do actually.
It may be lizo.
And Peanut, just Peanut, listen.
We all love you baby.
If you are listening at SNL, get Peanut.
Get Peanut in now.
Get Peanut on that damn show.
Get him on right now.
Because I think that he just like--
Your roster lost Kate, Kyle, AD, and Pete,
and we need Pete Nut.
Yup.
His name's not Pete Nut.
That's his full name.
full name. Oh, you know that if you know the Dunham lore.
Peter. This name isn't Peter Nut. It's Peter Nut. Shut up. And
his last name is Butter. Peter Nut Butter. It's Peter Nut
Butter Nut. Peter Nut Butter Nut. It's not his name. Peter
Nut Butter Nut. Peter Nut Butter Nut or Nut. Alright, I'm just
gonna. Yeah, his name's Butter Nut or Nut or Nut. Yeah, that's
his actually his name. You **** say this **** on my phone.
Yeah, cuz we're running circles around you know Peter butter not or not or what is it even say that a that I wrote
No, it's happy to say
Forgot somebody is pulling up a picture somebody says I look like Carl from
aqua teen
Do you think I look like that?
No, you know you kind of sound like him. What are you talking about?
He doesn't sound like that. I don't remember what he sounds like
long should I watch Aqua Teen Hunger Force? I never watched that show because to me it
feels like too much like a commercial for McDonald's and I'm above that. That is true it is
almost subliminal advertising. Yeah. Yep. Yeah. I'd rather I'd rather watch something
like the Matrix. And also on the topic McDonald's bring the meatballs back. I
used to love those damn meatballs. McDonald's meatballs? Yeah when they first
had this when Aqua Teen first came out it was supposed to be this whole oh yeah
fries and shakes and meatballs they got everything at McDonald's. Where are the
meatballs now I barely even remember what they taste like. I make meatballs. You know what they did
have at Burger King I think they still do is a chicken parm sandwich. Yeah they do.
I ate that when I was five and I puked and pooped at the same time. That's got to
be one of the stupidest most made-up stories I've ever heard in my life. It's not false. I ate
anything that says when I was five that any story that starts. That's the first time I got food
poisoning when I was five. You don't remember anything when you were five. I remember that.
That's a lie. We can call up my mom. This is the one person on earth who remembers it. Nobody remembers, you don't
remember anything until you turn 15 and then even then every other you know how
like when you try to remember my birthday. It's not I remember my birthday
from when I was seven years old. It's a why saying to me what happy birthday
he I mean it's hard and he put his feet in the cake wow and then he flew my
brother accidentally spit on the cake when he was younger because he was
trying to blow out the candles and then he's trying to blow out the candles and
and just fully just went and just like tried to spit the flame out.
That is the least interesting.
My brother was trying to blow out his candle and he did.
And he put some spit on it.
He spit.
He just like hocked the loogie on the flame.
Dude, when my brother breathed that one time he spit.
Everyone got mad at him because they couldn't eat the cake.
I'm going to say for 30 minutes you were a full stone.
Yeah.
And then you just went back to, or you were a full bird.
- You were a bird, you were a hand bird.
- A hand bird, and then you just turned into a stone.
- Yeah.
- That was a bush bird story.
- Bush bird moment.
- Yeah, that was a bush bird behavior.
- I didn't take an Adderall today.
- Really?
- So you can see a direct difference
between the episode before this and this one.
You can see my behavior has changed.
- Yeah, you're acting more erratic and almost sociopathic.
(laughing)
You are.
- Yeah, oh my God, who is that?
- Who is that?
- It's a picture of Ronald McDonald.
- Who is that, what is he from?
- Oh yeah, what's this?
Does anybody know what this character's from?
I used to watch this character on TV when I was a kid,
and I can't find him anymore.
Does anybody?
- She's fucking gorgeous.
- Oh my God.
That looks like a caricature of the Irish.
I don't appreciate it.
- I like it.
- I love it!
- Can you pull up--
- We're bringing it back, we're doing it again.
- Can you pull up Ronald McDonald singing?
Does he have a good smell it like that McDonald Mac what is this?
This isn't really Ronald McDonald, this is a drama alert Ronald McDonald this by racker. This is not right
I don't want to see yeah
Bird bush again. Yeah, you're a complete bush bird get in the hand bush bird there we go
I'm sorry TV series starring Andrea Savage. Thank you. That's better
Yo, I bet she's savage as hell if that's the name of her show
She's probably gonna probably gonna have to constantly
You know they call this website IMDB because I am to be in on this website all the time looking up the actors
They call it IMDB because I am
DB Cooper, and I'm about to steal their website. I'm gonna have my own dude. I would
Stole he stole the website from the plane. Yeah, yeah, but not from the web
He stole things literally stole a website as you know you wouldn't even know about a DB Cooper
because he'd probably be involved in probably crypto and intellectual property theft instead
of gold.
It's a lot easier to be a thief now.
Yeah.
Because you just live forever.
And his name would probably be like Graydon Cooper or something.
Yeah, if he was a fucking white guy.
Have you ever seen that movie, Without a Paddle?
Love Without a Paddle.
Love it.
Okay.
You've seen that.
In that movie, they don't have sex with these women because they have hairy legs.
Nowadays you can't have sex with a woman unless they're hairy.
Nowadays I can't get hard unless their head legs are hairy.
Unless they look like a bush baby.
Have you guys ever seen a movie without a TV?
No.
What's a bush baby?
I've never seen a movie without a TV.
Me neither.
A bush baby?
That's some kind of Australian animal.
That's a lemur type thing.
Really?
Yeah.
I can't have sex with a woman unless she looks like a lemur.
Skinny.
Lemurs are furry.
yeah I got something to tell you guys. I think a lot of lemurs have toxic
flesh. Wait! This is that fucking little one from Madagascar! Yeah! He's a
fucking bush baby! Yeah! Wow! Do you know the... Madagascar!
You looked up Madagascar. You completely looked up Madagascar. Just search lemurs
Madagascar. There he is! There's the guy. Voiced by... is that the one who's voiced by
Cedric the Entertainer? No, he's the one that's like, "Hello!" That one. That was Cedric the Entertainer.
They don't have enough... I guess the minions have kind of just monopolized it.
Yeah, but there used to be every year there was a kids movie and every year
there was like a little character like that, like, "Scrat, Scrat, this guy."
So what has changed between from, now that I'm thinking about it, from 1997 or 8 to
about 2012 to 2014 that now I don't see these kids movies anymore with little
characters. What is happening? What they would know I'm not aware anymore.
You know what I mean? You know what I mean? Like they kind of like it's like the
public consciousness. It's like everywhere. You think it's the public
consciousness? You'd see like like toys of them everywhere. Yeah we don't have
basically like yeah I haven't I've been barely watching any. I barely even look
at branded toys. Whatever happened to these kids movies. I barely see them in the toy
store when I go. Every time I went to the theaters I was watching one of these movies. Yeah.
And now I just don't see them anymore. Until like maybe 15 years ago or so. Yeah I just
can't. So what could that be? You turned off your mic. That's my bad. I have nephews and
I see these movies all the time. All the time? When I lived with them. And now they don't
have these little characters anymore. And they own the house. And they don't have. And
They're two and three years old.
- Wow, that's really impressive.
- That's very cool.
- No, but they don't, there's no little like,
scrats anymore.
There's no scrats.
There's no more scrats.
- It is just the minions.
- But I also would wager there are a bunch of scrats
that we do not see because we are adults.
- That's true.
- Yeah.
- I think that that is much more likely.
- I'm 15, 16 these days and I just am too old.
- I don't watch kids movies anymore.
- I'm just too old for that bullshit.
- I watch, you know what I just started watching?
- You know what I watch now?
Fight Club and Lucky Number Slevin.
Yeah.
Yeah. You know, I like fucking nice.
I like adult movies.
Yeah. And I like adult swim.
Locked up in two smoking barrels.
Yeah. Yeah.
Twenty one.
I love I kind of like
the Golden Compass, but only the
parts where the bears fight.
I only like the parts that are
anti-Christian.
Yeah. You know, and I like Fight
Club. I like I
like the Ace of Spades or whatever
that movie is.
The Ace. Twenty one.
Twenty one. I like twenty one.
I said it already.
Um, no, no, Aces.
I like soft-
Smokin' Aces!
I like Smokin' Aces.
I like soft boards.
The final chapter.
Kiss Kiss Bang Bang is actually my favorite movie.
It's actually fuckin' great.
Yeah.
Yeah, I love, uh, Snatch.
Uh huh.
That's my kinda movie, basically.
I did watch, I watched Snatch every night before I went to bed when I was in middle school.
That's just not true.
Every night before you went to bed.
Pretty much every night.
Snatch every night.
Snatch and Trainspotting.
And Mean Streets.
You watched three movies every night before you went to bed.
I watched three movies.
I learned how to pirate DVDs.
Actually, I didn't do that.
- You think that's so true.
- That never happened.
- I used to watch kids movies,
but nowadays I'm more into adult movies
like Memento and Nomadland.
- Same.
- Yeah, those are my two favorites.
- And The Limey.
I love The Limey.
- It's so funny when you're like growing,
getting older, you're growing.
- It's so funny when you're growing
And your legs hurt and your feet get bigger.
And you're like, you are starting to watch like more adult movies,
but then it's like, you're just watching like dog shit movies from like 2000s.
Yeah.
Cause you're like, yeah, I need to watch movies with the violence.
It is funny also by the time where you start watching like R rated movies and
shit, you like, for me,
I had already been watching like hardcore pornography every day for three years.
And then I finally was like, all right, I'm going to watch a movie.
I'm going to watch, uh, uh, uh, the fucking.
I do.
I do kind of wish...
We're Shauna the Dead now.
I do really wish I could like make myself have, wow,
I could make myself have the mindset again
of this feeling the same way when I was like 11 or 12
and seeing CGI gore in a movie for the first time.
And instead of watching it now, I mean like...
The Expendables?
Yeah.
Had some of the worst.
I remember the scene in Watchmen
when they cut the guy's hands off through the prison bars.
I was like...
That was so sick.
That shouldn't be in a movie.
Yeah.
Make you sick to your stomach watching that.
Yeah, I saw that with my dad. I thought the violence was fine
But then I tried to go to the bathroom during the sex or that when the guy's head gets
caved in and
Times labyrinth hot fuzz got me to when the thing falls on yeah, just like and when it goes into is
There's so many throw up so much stuff like that. I see it now. I'm like that's a computer
I'm trying to think of like what's the perfect movie that like when you're like
12 13 years old where it's like I'm gonna watch this cuz I'm I think it's Fight Club
No, to me that's like actual like like it's an act like like just some schlocky like
2000 oh my god from Paris with or the John Travolta bald movie like watching something like that when you're like
13 right and you're like I'm a fucking grown-up now. Yeah, I'm a grown-up and I've changed my taste
My personal ones are those are definitely fight club and watchmen. Those are the ones where I was like
Yeah, I watched this kind of stuff or that uh that Bruce Willis Morgan Freeman movie where they're all like super spies
but they're old. It's called like Red or something. Oh, Red. Is it just called Red?
Yeah, yeah. You know what the gateway is? The Dark Knight. Yeah.
That's the perfect, that's the in-between. I can watch that now. Well, I mean, yeah, of course.
This is a good movie. Yeah, but I'm saying that, yeah. I know when you're 12, we're talking about
one that is specifically bad. Yeah, it's like you see it when you're 12 or 13,
you're like, this is sick, and then you get older. See, that's hard for me to think of
one because every movie I watch is incredible and I never watch a bad movie. It's just a joy to watch.
miss when it comes to actually picking the movie. I don't think Hitch is one of those movies. Hitch is dope. Hitch is good. Hitch is fire.
Hitch taught me how to act honestly. Yeah. Yeah. Hitch taught me how to act like a player. I bet it's, I bet,
I think like a gentleman. You know what, it's definitely an action movie like like one of those or a really shitty
direct-to-video horror movie. Yeah. That like has a bunch of jump scares. Like a Conjuring.
Yeah, or like Insidious or something like that. The Butterfly Effect 2. Yeah.
I watched that on the Syfy channel and I was like I love actually the butterfly effect is that movie or like
I think we talked about it before. The poltergeist remake. Yeah, we talked about it before but like the butterfly effect and
Dance with the devil by immortal technique. Yeah are like the same. They're the same kind of feeling
Yeah, your friends older brother shows that to you and it's like you're gonna you're about to see something fucked up
And it actually does fuck you
Yeah, and it is fucked up and that book. You know there's multiple endings of the butterfly effect. Holy fucking shit. I
Didn't realize that yeah, does he lose his arm and all of them well
I mean the movie is the same the endings change
There's one ending where he goes in he goes back in time to when he's in his mom's womb
Does he ever chokes himself does he ever try to stop anything?
Other than just like a fucking lady dying or his friend getting fucked no
That's because it's the only things he can do is go back to his blackouts
I don't remember the movie. I watched it when he's a child. I watched it recently.
That's awesome. He would black out, and then he would come to, and like
things would be happening. Oh. Yeah, there's like a scene where he blacks out and like
sees his dad in prison, and then his dad tries to kill him. Okay, so that's fucking
dope. Yeah, see it's a messed up, fucked up movie. I think Taken is another one.
yeah taken's not dark enough I don't think it's about sex trafficking that's
fine it's pg-13 I think that is no but I think that is a movie you watch you go
I'm a grown-up yeah this is what I'm not grown up yet but when I do grow up this
is what I'm gonna do yeah I'm gonna take in people like I'd be fine to be on
either side of a movie that you walk into the house and you see your dad
watching on basic cable. Yeah. Is like always the... Field of Dreams? No, well I mean...
My dad watching Field of Dreams? That's different, actually that's a different experience. Yeah, like walk in the office, dad watching Field of
Dreams. Dad watching Field of Dreams or like Bull Durham. Blowing boogers into a
sort of a dirty boxer shorts he has. Yeah, right after your parents got divorced just
just snotting into boxers. Just snotting into boxers, pissed big fucking two-liter of piss
next to him yeah smoking cigarettes inside he's burning himself when my
uncle yeah yeah every Sunday he surgically removed his eyelids and lips
and then I'm like I'm badass as fuck I'm gonna watch Inception oh no do you know
what actually that just made me realize it was the Heights a Hellboy movie yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah but like you can watch the Hellboy movie now and you're
like this is still sick he's still red yeah he's still pretty and his friend is
still so blue. Yeah, it's the perfect friendship. And they sing Barry Manilow. But if you want
to see a guy who is red, you should come to our show on Halloween because there's a red
devil. Yeah, he might appear. And if you don't go to the show, if you don't go, I'm going
to kill you. And I'm also going to kill you if you don't go. And I'll fucking, I'll slit
your throat. And I'm gonna edit in like some rotoscope electricity out of our fingers.
Don't look up porn on Bing.
Woah, it gets cartooned so fast.
Wow. MILF porn.
But swagproof.com/showspeed. I suppose there's a trailer
for right at the museum, an awesome video
that will premiere there, and we'll play nowhere else
ever. Except for another...
You're only...
No. Shut up, because the only
time you ever literally will watch this video is
at the Halloween show, which we are trying to sell tickets
to, and you will buy tickets to.
See you there.
Bye.