Come here, come here, come here.
Let me see your butt.
- Premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership
immediately.
- You're a monster.
(explosion)
- Here I am.
- Come home.
- I've been fucking betrayed.
I've been cloned.
- I gotta get that keyboard.
- Shut up.
Stop changing the subject.
- I made a mistake while I was giving myself a haircut.
- I've had my swagger jacked.
First of all, mustache.
(laughing)
- Second of all-- - Are you kidding me?
You have to grow your hair out and then shave that,
or keep that, and then grow your hair out.
- You're not even speaking English.
I can't think of it.
Take that hat off right now.
(laughing)
You have a piece of tape stuck to your head.
- Oh, I still do?
(laughing)
- Giant black piece of tape.
Don't put it back up there.
- How does that look?
- It looks pretty, I mean, it's a piece of tape on your head.
What do you want me to say?
I'm not completely bald, all right?
I just gave myself like a whiffle cut.
- A whiffle cut?
- That's what my dad used to call it.
- Nobody knows what the hell that means.
- I've never heard that before.
- Well, one person's gonna know who's listening.
- Your dad?
- Yeah, I think.
Is it called, I don't know, whatever.
- I wanna do a head shape analysis.
- Yeah.
- Look to your left, you have a dent.
- Yeah, you have a dent, he has a dent.
- Pretty big dent in the middle.
(laughing)
Yeah, so I use the clippers that I have, have like one of those guides that's like you put
it around the corner of your ear.
Yeah.
And I didn't do it right, I put it up too high.
Why didn't you go straight low top fit or straight fucking like short on the side, one
on the sides and have a giant ass fucking thing on the top?
I should have done something like that.
Classic sports clips cut.
Yeah.
I should have done that.
Right off the menu.
But you know, whatever.
This will grow back.
No it won't.
It doesn't grow.
- I thought that too.
I thought, oh it'll grow back.
- I mean, look at my hairline right now.
Do you think that's growing back?
- Your hairline's fine.
It's better than I thought it was, honestly.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- It's better than I thought it was.
- Nice.
- I thought that it was way, way farther back.
- I thought you didn't have any hair.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- You thought I just like combed it over.
- Yeah, I did.
- Yeah, for a while now.
- Makes sense.
- I think you also, you are very secretive about it.
- Yeah.
- So then when you actually see it,
you're like, oh, it's not that.
The degree of secrecy that you undertake
with your hairline, I would expect you to have less hair.
- I just, it doesn't grow in the spots that it should.
- What? - Is what the,
like these two corners right here.
- Those are cool corners for it to not grow in.
- That's just how, that's a mature hairline I've learned.
That's what happens when you mature.
- Do you have, are you supposed to have a mature hairline
from the age of like 16? - Yeah, your hairline's
supposed to go, yeah, and it's supposed to go
all the way back here, and this is like a mature
kind of hairline is when it hits kind of the back ear,
right where your head starts to curve into your neck.
- Interesting. - All the way in the back.
That's a mature hairline.
- I'm also missing like a patch of hair right here.
- I saw you have a little like a scar.
- Let me see. - A bald spot.
- And then yeah, there's a scar
on the back of my head on this side.
- You had to have been abused.
Just looking at your head.
Just looking at your head, you got abused for sure.
- Yeah, but the back of my head--
- He changed the subject fast.
Oh, you had the back of my head.
- Back of my head right here, well, here's a story.
- Okay.
my older brother when I was when I was five he was six I got it was a Jango Fett
with a removable head mm-hmm like Phantom no not fan you fucked me up I
know it's not Phantom Menace I saw a bright light in my face and I said
phantom. Phantom! That was a really bright light. Yeah. But I wouldn't let my
brother play with it, my older brother, and he picked up this big Millennium Falcon
toy that we had and just whipped it at the back of my head. Is that what that's
from? That's what that scar is. Oh my god. It was like a couple inches deep. You have a
Star Wars issue with your head? I had staples put in my head with like a patch of like
something over it. They took the hair from up here in the front and they
stapled it over the piece of paper. You have a perfectly fine hairline if
they didn't do that. They did a follicular transplant. That must have
been what happened. Yeah. I think that is what happened. Yeah. Where is
this? I haven't looked. Hold on. You have an equal sign and you have
something that's like a cross with a couple extra legs yeah I talking to the
microphone that look good yeah that looks good yeah it's really good yeah
that looks good
Wow oh there's the scar I've actually never really I haven't seen it no really
this also is shave my head a lot in high school this is a lot of shit bald photos
of me as you already looked like you had a big head and this makes your head look
so much bigger yeah I disagree I think I think when no I think when you turn your
head to this I think profile it looks bigger no don't listen to him he's
trying to be mean I'm not trying to be me I'm trying to have fun it's cool to
have a look two against one this motherfucker looks like a girl pound
that out right now look at this shit on that I know y'all jealous pound that out
- I'm not I never had I look like I look like Jesse Pinkman and he looks like
Walter White yeah he looks like my jacket I have on yeah I'm not a kid named
finger I'm not a kid named finger Jesse there's a kid you're gonna go Jesse
you're gonna do you're gonna go to the fourth grade there's a kid named finger
you're gonna say hey class today we're gonna finger paint and there's gonna be
a boy named kid named finger. It's not gonna end no at first it won't make any sense at
at all. It's actually zillennial dadaism. Jesse, a shrimp actually fried the rice. That's what
you guys are doing. A shrimp fried the rice. That's what you guys are doing right now.
No, because we actually did a good impression and you're just going, "Andy, dada." I'm making
fun of you guys doing a good impression by doing a bad impression. You're doing that
girl, like a next level. That is actually dadaism. You're doing that girl haircut. I
seriously am not. You really can't get off of this because you are so jealous because
could get off on your hair because you look like a girl. You really could
easily because I got a thing off with that guy. Imagine you're Lucy Lou
Lucy Lou as red hair.
Yeah, I don't have red hair. You have bright red. You're talking about
you have bright head red hair like a like head rare. Okay, like I'm a hair
expert. Yeah, you should be. No, you've seen so much hair in the bathtub. No,
(laughter)
- No I haven't.
- Yeah, you serve a lot of hair.
- I was shaving my head and Moe came into the room
and tried to eat the hair.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
- Cats like eating hair, that's why they have hair balls.
- I didn't know that they liked that.
Speaking of Moe, he has a beaver fever.
- Hey, who doesn't these days?
Even girls have beaver fever these days.
- Nowadays, and they also, they used to have beaver fever,
And now they have beaver fever.
- Yeah, that's right.
- 'Cause they're all damn bisexual.
- And I thought beaver fever--
- Pretty much the same thing, yeah.
- I thought beaver fever was gay.
- I thought beaver fever had a beaver fever.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
I looked up beaver fever when Pat was saying
that his cat had it, and the way that you,
it's a sickness and you get it by eating poop.
- Why does every sickness, why does eating shit
give you every sickness?
- Well, so here's the important part is that it's,
you could get it by either eating animal poop
or human poop.
So there's a distinct possibility that his cat ate human poop.
My stray cat probably ate a homeless crap.
Yeah.
Ugh.
So.
Well, yeah.
It turns out that...
Found a new home in your cat's mouth.
It turns out taking in a stray cat...
Not that awesome.
Yeah, and nursing it back to health.
It's actually very expensive.
I found out I have canine stomach ulcers.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I fit all the symptoms.
Really?
Yeah, I don't...
What are the symptoms?
dog food or play with other dogs or go into my crate.
- Really?
- These days, yeah.
- Not even your crate?
- I won't even touch a bowl of dog food.
- Wow.
- Yeah, I got all the symptoms of canine stomach ulcers.
- Dog food, at least like the wet food that like,
they're like, oh yeah, we eat like a real,
oh my God, this diet.
- The other day I was so hungry that I was making Phil's food
and I was like, you know what, I'm just gonna go to bed,
I'm not gonna eat anything.
I'm just gonna go to bed.
And then I started making Phil's food.
I was like, fuck, I'm getting, I could eat this right now.
And so I had to boil an egg.
- It has to look, it,
- I had to boil an egg to keep myself from eating dog food.
- Dry food or?
- Well, I mix it with canned pumpkin.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- All right.
- I thought you were talking about,
no, like the wet food containers.
Like when it's like, oh, like a chef made this.
There's sometimes, you'll see a video where it's like,
a guy is making food for his dog
and he's chopping up like chicken breast.
- I thought I was gonna do that.
- He's making it in like slow comparison shit.
- I thought I was gonna be a quail egg
for my dog kinda guy.
- Yeah.
- And it turns out I just forget to feed him.
- Yeah, so it's a lot worse probably.
- I can't forget to feed Moe
because Moe literally has like a parasite in his stomach
that he's eating for, and he's eating for two because of it.
And I have to put stuff in his food
to kill the parasites now.
- He's a tapeworm.
- No. - Ringworm.
- He also has--
- Stomachworm.
- What did he have?
- Worm, tummyworm.
- He does have a tummyworm.
does actually have a tummy worm. Did they like find it on an x-ray? Yeah, they had to
collect a stool sample and ride on the bus with poop in my my tote bag. No.
Your tote bag? I filled my tote bag to the brim with shit. In that tote bag? In that tote bag I filled it to the
brim with shit. The one that Caleb's backpack is leaning on? Yeah. Oh come on.
That's why I have some kind of fucked up stomach issue. That's why I never put poop in my bag.
egg. You know what I didn't I'm a first time stray cat owner. Okay. I didn't know
you say it. You're a noob. I'm a noob to owning a stray. You're a total. I've
never had to bring a stool sample anywhere. Okay. Really? I'm a new I'm a
green horn when it comes to stool samples. I'll say it. You say you're very
horny when you come in. It comes to stool samples. No, I said I'm a green
horn. I don't know what that means. It means it's what it means to be green
with
to jack off with it.
- Juvio, come say hi real quick.
- Yeah, Juvio's in the house.
- We have a live studio.
- Grab the mic and say hi.
- Hi.
- There we go, that's enough from you.
You can sit down now.
- Get the fuck out of here.
- Wait, look at this.
Look at this.
- Don't blind him with a flashback.
- That's the Phantom.
Why do we have, oh right, 'cause the, nevermind.
- Listen, two times in one month,
a bee, I've been eating something outside,
and a bee has, okay, you're--
- Now you're ruining the episode,
'cause this is the second time I've tried
to tell this fucking story about my beef food a set there's a second time where a
bee has tried to eat my food really what I thought I'd been eating pollen and
yeah I haven't I've been having a similar experience where I about two
times in the past week I saw a bee really posing outside and where was it
headed one time it was remaining in that same location in there how do they do
that another time it was circling around a trash I saw both the times I was
walking by Wow train really I saw a B movie yeah that's that's too much I
really did see that I saw post-ironic zillennial humor of you okay yeah no yeah
I saw a B fucker or no B newbie yeah newbies I like newbies I saw a D newbie
Dnuthi. I love ventriloquism. Oh my god. Ventriloquism. Ventriloquism. I love ventriloquism. But yeah,
the bees, the bees are going on with them. Something is going on with them. The bees?
Recently that's making me see them. There was all these movies a couple years ago, what
the fuck is going on with the fucking bees? Yeah, they're dying quote unquote. I hate bees.
Bees suck. Who likes bees man? A lot of flowers. Not me. What picture did you take? You had
You have to show me what you took.
Close your eyes.
What the hell are you?
Is this a photo of me drinking in portrait mode?
I don't get why that's that funny.
Get ready dude, now that you have no hair people are just going to start taking photos
of you all the time.
Yeah.
Patrick just went teacher mode.
Yeah you did.
I'm not sure I see what's so funny about this.
Can you explain to me what's so funny about what you just did?
He's acting like a damn kid.
Explain to the class.
And guess who gets who's getting a spanking.
You look like a damn kid.
A baby.
This is so much fun to make fun of people with no hair.
I see why you guys do this.
Yeah, I'm trying to get out all the things
that I've always wanted to say.
- You've been practicing in your mirror.
- I hate my dad.
No, not dad.
(laughing)
No, I love my dad.
Your head looks really fucking no hair though, pretty much.
- No hair though?
- Yeah.
- Boy ain't got no hair though.
- I guess that's facts now.
- Yeah.
- Used to not be.
- That used to not be facts,
very quickly became fast was fiction now facts yeah I am afraid I've thought I
have come close I would say if maybe two times in my life to shaving my head but
I think that I every time I pussy out because I think I think I probably have
the most dented head of all time I think I think I think I do think if I shave my
head like it would look not think it's good it's corrugated I think it would be
really bad that it might be fun though because you could I'll do it I'm
probably do it eventually but I do I am really dreading seeing what it's what is
- You shave it with the same guard,
the whole way through so that there's like,
when it dips down in the dents,
that's like a different length
because you hit everything with the sabi fun.
- Yeah, that's what happened today.
- Yeah, let me see.
- So, what if I like, what if I shave my head though
and I have just red open sores on my scalp?
- Well then--
- That's what I thought I would see.
- And I have like white worms sticking out of them.
- There was like an itchy thing over here.
- I actually did have that when I shaved my head.
- Really?
- Because I had such terrible dandruff
that my scalp was just like bright red
and covered in just like rotting.
- Is that dandruff or is that psoriasis?
I wouldn't be surprised if I had like purple rotting skin and gangrene yeah on
my brain there there you two are literally acting like you two are acting
like children you're you were your audience you were acting like the you
either say laugh and applaud when you're supposed to applaud it's a oh yeah okay
no clap great thank you now leave and it stopped grabbing his penis don't grab his
penis with the grabber. Do you think this is fun for people to listen to? Yeah.
People are gonna be upset. The two people they could care about the least in the
world fighting with a penis grabber. And it's not a penis grabber until you make
it one. And you've been making it one this whole time. It's not supposed to be
for grabbing penises. It's for grabbing toilet papers down from the
bodega counter he shaved his head you know he shaved his head shave ice you know I
shaved my head you shaved my head these are the times these are the times when I
honestly wish the fucking Grim Reaper was real yeah yeah he'd come out of nowhere
and he fucking take you away I wish the Sandman was real so you could dance to
him off the stage dance to you that's right yeah that's exactly still the words
right out of my mouth I feel the exact same way that's the ball or the dragon
from the grand fairy tales to burn them alive
squirted cinders. Yeah, touching your head, yeah, scratching it. You know it's
not fun, dude, when someone else does it. Yeah, don't touch my hair.
It's that simple or my lack of hair. I don't like when people touch my bald
head. I'd like to publicly say that. I shouldn't have to sit there and take
that when someone touches my bald head. Because all of a sudden, if someone
touches my bald head and I go like, "Stop doing that," like, "Knock it off,"
they're like, "Oh, what? I was just touching your fucking bare skin."
You can touch my ass cheek, you can rub my ass cheek,
and you can pat that.
My head, man, that's where my thoughts live.
- You're gonna shake my head around?
You're gonna do that to me?
- I don't like that, dude.
Especially 'cause I've been taking a lot of fucking
Tanga Ali and Ashwagandha, and my natural testosterone,
my free testosterone, it's getting way too high.
So if somebody does that--
- Mine's already too high.
That's why I'm losing my damn hair.
- I'm probably liable to freak out
if next time somebody does that to me.
- What everyone says about me is my testosterone.
It looks like I have high T.
- Yeah, through the roof.
- That's why my hips are very wide.
- Yeah, it's through the roof.
- My legs are longer than the, long as the night.
- Yeah, long as the night is long.
- Long as the night is long.
- Long and dark legs.
- And my stiletto heels make my ass look amazing.
- Yeah, 'cause you're high T.
- High T, yeah.
- 'Cause of my high testosterone.
- Yeah, I'm high T, I got this big ass nose.
- Yep.
- I think T does make your nose big.
- What do you mean about?
What?
I've got a big nose, 'cause I'm high T.
When you take testosterone, like TRT therapy,
when you get older, it makes your nose big.
Like bulbously big?
Yeah, it gets like big and red.
There's like, when people take--
What the fuck are you doing, Jubio?
He hurt himself.
You know that Patrick is easily distracted,
and then you fucking do this shit.
Go sit on your iPad.
Turn on your iPad right now.
Turn on your iPad and draw.
Stop playing with toys.
And don't mess up anything on that desk.
unbelievable comes takes an unauthorized vacation request vacation
request vacation goes through the for request vacation vacations. I'm late. I
might need at least a full six way in advance. Ask me to approve it while I'm
by the way outside of business hours. It was like six thirty text me ask me to
approve. It says look at your email. I see it. I say yeah, but that's not going
to work. It's going to be a no for us. It's going to be a hard no and then I
message you again outside of office hours didn't have to do that. I'm not
getting paid for that work and then you throw a hissy fit and you send me
pictures of you in a diaper. You're loading it up with fucking what looks
like orange piss, you know, and I just think that's unbecoming of an employee.
Exactly. I know. I remember the first picture looked like orange piss and then
the second picture you could see the texture and it was more like yogurt.
Yeah, and it's like why are you putting yogurt in a dice and then the third
picture very clear. It's not yogurt at all, but it's it because it's like
- It was clearly coming out of his body.
- Also, it's in some way.
- Burya consummate.
- It was clear, I could see that you were--
- How do you say it?
- Bedia.
- Bedia?
- It was clear in the photos that you were using
like studio lighting, you had like a ring light, you know?
- Yeah.
- And it's like, why are you going through all this?
- And you could actually tell based on the glare
that he had one ring light at face level
and one from behind at his butt.
- It's disgusting, yeah.
- That apparently he uses for other uses during the day.
- Mm-hmm.
- God. - What is that?
- You need to leave us alone.
You need to leave us alone.
We're busy.
you have to go to the other side of the office and close the curtain. I'm getting pretty
excited. I really think that tonight when I go to this bath house it might be a game changer
for me. Yeah. I think I might finally get into relaxing. That does, and honestly it sounds so
nice. I have to say it's been growing since you first said it. When you first said it my first
thought was naked? Yeah. Yeah. And since then? Naked. But is there, what if, imagine just like
you go to a place in an Armenian guy forces you to relax
because that's what it is as far as I know you are forced to relax I guess
you're allowed to play play video games in there that's what I'm kind of hoping
I'm sorry I pad in with you yeah damn if I can bring my iPad in that I because I
think I I think I still have a warranty on that thing do my god I got into the
bath with me bring that it doesn't matter what happens oh my I was under the
I was under the impression that the bad to be in the bathhouse holy shit.
I was under the impression of the bathhouse was just a basically like a
water park like you pay and then you just walk around and get in the
different pools, but then I signed up and it said you need to arrive early
before your session. So I think they're going to fucking do something.
They're going to do something. I'm fucking terrified man. I think they're
probably going to do something to you. It's like a spa right yeah, but I don't
What do you do at a spa?
Well, I would assume...
Do they massage you?
I guess maybe you'd probably have to...
Do you have to get clean before you're on the baths probably, right?
I'm definitely gonna wash my butt before I go.
Yeah.
So maybe they do that.
Maybe it's something about that.
I don't want to have my butt all stinky for him.
I don't want to make the whole sauna stink.
Well, I'm gonna let him know when I walk in.
I'm gonna be like, "I washed for you."
I washed my butt for you.
Excuse me!
I washed my butt!
Are you here for the 930?
Yes, I am.
And I washed my butt.
but I washed it very, very good. Maybe they're going to shave your body so you
don't get any stray hairs into the bath.
They are going to might.
What?
Just go in there, go in that bath house with a ladle to get all that broth.
Oh my God.
You get all that broth.
Taking that home in a thermos.
Take that home in a thermos.
Dude, that's the ultimate.
That's the ultimate in testosterone boosting stuff.
Oh my God.
You talking about high T?
That's some serious free testosterone.
Talk about free testosterone, that's free.
Yep.
Also, take that home, okay?
Take that thermos home, put it in the freezer.
Put it in a little baggie.
That's an ice pack.
After you work out, you're sore, put the ice pack on.
Not only does it help you feel better, reduce inflammation, but it's also adding testosterone
and it's going to make your arm big like Popeye.
You could put it, once it melts a little bit, just a little bit, depending on who you are,
you could insert it rectally and let it melt in there.
and a slushy to yeah and a slushy to you and it could probably absorb even faster
through your rectal lining yeah probably if you had like a slushy and then a
straw that goes into your rectum and then maybe if you had trained
yourself to take it have air intake yeah through your rear end. I guess I'm just
worried about sharks at this thing. Yeah, I guess I'm probably worried about
about masked killers. I think that that might be a bad problem at a bathhouse.
house yeah in a bath house. Let's see what is my yeah. What am I the most
scared of it's probably getting a boner if I was gonna get a boner from an old
guy. Yeah, yeah, unlock. I think if there's any place in real life, you're
gonna get killed by Jason Voorhees. It's probably a bad house right. I would try
fucking a camp man. Yeah, so that's the movie. So I just said was real life. So
I was kind of doing a departure from the movies, which is in a my early departed.
If you keep talking down to me about flicks, I'd seriously I'm not even talking
about flicks. I'm talking about real life, which is the point I'm trying to
across here okay so maybe I don't even really matter that I like a
combination of real life and flicks no it's purely real life right now all right
when you watch a movie that's a combination of real life and flicks oh
you're right yeah flicks is the purest form of movie yeah movie is somewhere in
between flicks and reality yeah watching movie watching movie oh my god and it's
called flicks because of the shutter flicker it's called no it's called flicks
because of Netflix. Oh, okay. I sit there and I flick boogers onto my TV. Yeah, I flick my
bean. That's right. I'm watching Showgirls, unrated. That's got to be weird to touch your
bean. Yeah? Yeah, that's got to be really odd. Yeah, it probably feels weird. It must
tingle. I bet it like spreads through your whole body. It must tingle. It must! It must!
You do kind of look a little bit more like a villager or a slave with your head like
this.
Yeah.
Oh my god, I would love to put you in some burlap.
Doesn't he look like he's got chains attached?
I could see you rowing a ship, like a Viking warship.
Definitely.
See, dude, he's sucking his teeth.
He's so mad at this.
Oh my god.
He's like, "No, I'm noble."
I just have like a...
Dude, dude, dude.
I think my wisdom tooth is infected.
He's going to star in the fucking Northeast Man.
Holy shit.
The fucking Northeast Man instead of the North Man.
- A Northeast man, like New Hampshire.
- What's going on with your tooth, man?
- It's totally infected.
- Viking?
- I think it totally is infected.
- That is Viking as fuck.
- Yup, yup, yup.
- You have scurvy, bud.
- Yup.
I gotta get that wisdom tooth out.
- You need to stop eating cured meats so much.
- I know.
- I found out yesterday.
- Eating Iberico ham.
Is that what it's called?
- Jamon Iberico.
- You, um.
- I said that perfect pronunciation.
- You did.
Iberico ham.
- Iberico ham.
I think that we would do very well in Espana.
Right.
And what era?
Now.
Spanish era.
Okay.
Spanish Civil War.
Yeah.
I guess probably any era we would do pretty well there.
I would do well.
I would just, my brain was still in Viking mode, so.
I could do well now.
I'm doing pretty good, except for my teeth.
You don't want to go to Spain?
I'm worried that things would change for me in Spain, I guess is my main thing.
It's like if I went to Spain, could I bring my girlfriend?
Would I have to pay money to...
Is it more expensive to live there?
Is it cheaper?
Would my friends be with me?
That's your whole life.
That's kind of my questions I would have about moving to Spain, yeah.
I already got ahead of that.
Would I have to get a job?
Can I still do this job?
Like, would you guys be coming?
Would I have to do it remotely?
So you're getting too into the nitty gritty details.
Well, that's just the things I'm thinking.
What I'm thinking right now about if I do well in Spain, I'm just like, you know, like
would I have to change, would I get like health care?
Like how would that like...
So when I ask you about like, like what, would you rather fly or invisibility as your...
Right.
So I'm wondering like if my, for what my, yeah, if I was invisible, like yeah, would it affect
like my daily life like I mean I could be able to control the invisibility would
ruin my relationships with my friends or family or like what I still have what I
still have to work would I be able to make money just like being a hype if I
fly could I go like a thousand miles per hour don't really have to answer the
quite like it's not like that serious I guess right I'm just I mean that's just
what I think about when I'm I'm just trying to think you through these
questions like if I fly I probably save a lot of money on flying airplane flying
flying but what if your gas are you flying to Spain so if you could fly to
Spain on your own I guess then what about would I be allowed to fly back if
I go to Spain I mean I would just assume so I guess yeah I guess I do well in
Spain if I could come back really fast you said I was talking about getting a
passport GBO said that I could get out of the country without a passport but
you can't get back in is that true really is that true I don't know how it
works it's probably depends on the place right I don't know I have no idea that's
I just said okay that's very funny Juvio he pretended to take a photo and then
he showed it to me and it's three monkeys really really funny really funny okay he
turned his flashlight on to sell the photo effect it was pretty good that
okay this time is actually hi I said cheese okay it's the same same thing
all right well that's just fucking you're despicable mm-hmm yeah you're
not right have you ever been fired Juvio no you never fired I've been fired
You've been fired. Cameron, have you? I've quit every job I've done.
I've never been fired. I've never been fired. I've been fired and I've quit.
What's the- I've been dishonorably discharged. I've been fired.
I've quit. I've had a job that lasted three days and I thought that was my shortest job.
I thought it was like, there's no way I'll beat that. And then I did have a job where I only
lasted half a shift. And I just ditched all that. Which one?
It was the wax museum in downtown Boston. Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just got halfway through my shift and then I ditched all my I was like this
sucks I was sitting next to a fucking wax figurine of Peter Dinklage outside just
like begging tourists to not like kiss it and then I was like this is miserable so
I just walked inside I took off my polo put it in the bathroom and just walk
pieced out yeah yeah I've never been fired but I also have never no one has
ever said I'm a good worker I think I'm really good at finding the exact amount
to work that I don't get in trouble but I really am doing nothing I'm a horrible
employee but not enough that anybody gets mad at me. I think that's the secret.
I forgot to collect my tips all the time when I worked at places and
then they would have to call me during class and be like, "Hey, you have to come
collect these." And I would get like seven dollars in cash because they
distributed all the tips throughout the restaurant. What was your first job? My first job?
Yeah. Videographer for the London Area High School football team. All right, so
we're not counting that though. Like a first real job. Okay. You have to figure,
you have to fill out a form and stuff. First real job was Cracker Barrel. Nice. Yeah.
That's awesome. Dishwasher. Nice. And you lasted how long? A month. Nice. And then I was like,
they were like, well if you're gonna be, you're gonna be back on the weekends
right? And I was like, yeah but I really need to focus on my studies. Nice. My first
First job was I was a parking attendant and I was supposed to give people tickets, never
did it.
Yeah, you told us about the parking lot shutdown.
But then I also, another reason I quit was I just, I got hit by a car.
Really?
Yeah, twice.
That's cool.
And like once after the other in a row?
It was the same car.
Different, different.
Yeah, it just went.
Yeah, it went.
Backed up.
It hit me and then it went back.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I was like, you know what?
Or like in Sin City where one hits you and you go really far up in the air and the camera
follows you and then you go down and you bounce off another one.
yeah i went up so i had to move you know yeah but then i was like you know what
you know this place is made of cheese i guess i don't think about it i think
job would probably weasley dale would probably be moon scientist
i guess your dream job as for your for you know i just don't know that i think
of job i know i said now i think of it i think you know anything over your first
job uh... moon scientist i worked i did stuff of my local library but if you
mean
real job
i get this college college double counts as a religion read
I did I helped old people with computers, old people would come in and they
would be like they'd be like I don't know how to send an email and I got paid to
like show them how to do that and then every old person at the end would be
like you are so sweet. Do you want to come to my house?
And then everyone else would be like you have to leave.
I had never heard that before.
Yeah that's very funny, a really common problem.
He tried to get just a soft hit nap from one of these guys.
I think most of them honestly mean well, it's like old ladies and they're like no
You should come to my house and show me how to do this at my house because I my desktop computer
He's in a mill scenario. Yeah, but but then also there are some that are also definitely not
You should come to my house. Were you a hot kid? Were you like sexy? I don't think so. I
Think I was pretty surprised. Did you dress like slutty or no? I mean I dress you show some skin
I mean, I think you know how I dress now and you can probably extrapolate backwards. Yeah
like how it backwards have been he probably you're covered right now so I
think seven years ago I mean I'll give you the starting point to fill everything
in black it's a robe new balances a robe circle sunglasses yeah scar on the head
uh-huh all right let's see new balances yeah
black Nova one-piece bathing suit I get cut out yeah on the stomach and back
back astronaut helmet and an astronaut. I was just thinking that well that's why
they asked you to go because they didn't know you're your camera and yeah,
we got a baby face, you know, we're sitting in the library in like cowboy
boots and that fucking cowboy boots, cowboy hat and that praying bikini that
says father, son and Holy Spirit on it.
You're sitting there and you're like, does anyone need help with the computer
the the name of that program where it was like it was like specifically high
school kids help old people with computers the name of that program was
teen text I just now crazy name for that teen text teen text and old people are
coming far and wide teen tags on the weekend I have to get a teen tech this
this weekend. Hey honey, I'm gonna go down to the teen tech yeah, it's a
boy. Some of that stuff could have been so bad too, because a lot of I'm
coming. You know there was guys who went home after you taught them how to
do an email and their old wives are like hello honey. Whose hair is this
on your
the thing? It's like no, no, you want to say it was a teen. I feel like it
could it was probably it feels like a kind of reckless endangerment,
because a lot of those two you can see that because I mean half of half of
That's like I don't know how to log into my email and that stuff simple or
whatever.
But then I would say probably a good half, the other half would be like a
lot of guys who came in and wanted to figure out how to get photos off their
digital cameras.
See, that's what I'm saying.
That's really dangerous territory.
Now you're in one hour photo.
You could be turned into a psychopath.
That could be bad.
You're going to be talking to a kid about Evangelion.
It's exactly like one hour photo.
It could be really bad.
but yeah, I think you shouldn't let teens look at old people's photos.
Yeah, yeah, it is.
The other is it or the
it's like you were teaching like old men how to send email. I don't want to
touch an old man's feel. It is yeah, think about think of you're teaching
old men suck his feel on us.
You're teaching old men how to log into their email. Yeah, I know that you
teach you're teaching them how to just continue harassing you. Yeah, you're
like continue harassing you. I don't send email and what's your email
to log into their email and then you're also making them so susceptible to scams.
It's like, "Oh, I'm a..."
Yeah, old people shouldn't have that technology.
Old people shouldn't have email.
I think it's like, you should not let an old person, unless they're very smart, use anything
but a fax machine.
Yeah, it's probably true.
I'm not sure.
A jitterbug and a fax machine.
I was about to say like better email than like Facebook and Instagram, but maybe not.
Maybe email is the worst thing for them to have.
Yeah, yeah, because it's the...
Because there's nothing... it's... they're fucked.
Yeah, no, there's nobody checking in on that.
Yeah.
No, not at all.
Once they figure out how to use it for evil, they will.
Honey, I want a video camera.
Yeah.
I want a video camera.
All I have to do is give them my credit card for shipping and they're gonna send me it for free.
all of a sudden your inheritance is gone, man.
- Let's see what's in the spam folder right now.
- I did when I was like six.
- When you were six. - Sixth grade, seventh grade.
I signed up because I wanted a Sony Handycam
and I got a spam email and then it came
to the credit card portion and I didn't have a credit card
but I still gave them all my info
and then I just couldn't open up my email
'cause it was like constantly full of just like scammer,
like, oh, like, "Win a Sony Ericsson phone!"
Just shit like that for so long.
- I signed up for Spotify or something
with my grandma's credit card when I was a kid,
and I gave her a $5 bill,
and she didn't realize that it auto-renewed,
and then maybe two or three months ago, she called me.
She was like, "You know, I've been getting these charges
"for this Spotify thing."
It's been like 10 years she's been getting charged.
- Damn, that's crazy.
I was like I don't even I don't even know what account that is attached to it was
like some okay yeah she's just gonna until she dies she'll just be getting
charged for spotify. I just opened up the the podcast email spam because I was
like I want to see if there's any funny penis email and yeah and I have no idea
what this is. Maybe this is someone who would talk to a craigslist or something,
but somebody said it's an email that says says happy Halloween and then it
has it's October is a month for spooky movies. This film is a fun spooky movie.
happy halloween be safe crime traveler the adventures of dave slade and then it's
like this whole thing about this movie that and then it has an imdb link at a
to be like whoa what just emailed us a movie that they just
wanted to check it out yeah this has to be
somebody that we contacted from craigslist because that's what i'm
thinking channel see if we if we report it as not spam
it just this is just the last thing i expected to see when i open up this
yeah yeah yeah I'm traveler wait a good name what shit when did they send that
because I just reported as not spam and now I can't fucking I would assume
during October because it says happy Halloween it's a you know what that is
a minute stud observation thank you yeah but it could have been any year shit
yeah fuck damn okay wait I have to double check right now it was sent on
October 8th okay I just found it okay I want to watch that movie now though I
I will watch any movie. I wish I got a lot of spam emails like that. That's so much better than getting...
It is a guy that we contacted on Craigslist because the first video I'm
looking at here is a two-minute long video called "Dating Skit."
We'll pop her open. Let's see how this guy rolls.
[video]
It's not really a skit.
Let's listen to the monologue.
First time in a couple months,
I go to this really nice fancy sit-down restaurant.
And of course, she's got to order the most expensive thing on the menu.
A Delft Whopper with cheese and fries.
Okay, so we do it.
I spent more time in than out, it's cheaper that way.
But the hard part is, I was with my parents, she was with her parents.
It's hard to get alone time.
So finally I get a break.
She calls me up and says, "Come on over.
There's nobody home."
So I ran right over.
I almost got hit by a truck.
I stopped at the convenience store.
I bought flowers.
They were good.
So I go to her door, I knock on her door
and nobody answers.
She was right.
There was nobody home.
- Oh, I got it.
- So I sent her a text.
I said, "Look, we've been going out for over a year
and this really isn't working out."
So she responds with a text
and I got all these emojis that I'd never seen before.
and believe me they would make George Carlin wash so I've been on the down low
lately I got a little bored so I decided to take up magic he's on the down stop
pause stop pausing it a little finish it I can go into any room and make all the
women disappear I tell you relationships in the city it's really tough that is
true he's dude I mean that was good he's spitting fat was actually fucking good
That should be called not dating skip but maybe like facts about dating in today's modern. Yeah, my my
Thoughts on dating. Yeah, I've been called that data dating parentheses my perspective. He said that he's on the down-low though
That's why it's so hard for him to date. Yeah
Yeah, I guess that's true, huh? Yeah, he also almost got hit by a car or a truck. You got hit by a truck
Yeah, yeah, that's got to be hard. It's sad
I want I really want to see the flowers he bought they sounded so beautiful scary movie. He made yeah. Yeah me too
We should watch it. I would love to dude. Let's look at the spam folder a little bit more.
There's really nothing else. That's the only thing. I think we keep it pretty clean. You know, we're pros.
No, no penis ones. No, not even a single penis enlargement one. Not on the podcast. Have you
guys ever been curious about penis enlargement and about pursuing that field of study? Curious
about it? Yeah. No, I don't think so. Curious how? Yeah. Curious like maybe you fucking ordered like
Like a beginner kit, but not like the intermediate or like expert stuff.
Don't deflate it right now.
Where did you find that?
Why are you, I told you don't touch anything on that desk.
That is, you can touch anything in the office except the stuff on that desk.
It's fragile and it's, and now you're farting.
Listen to him fart everybody.
Oh, that's a long one.
Jesus Christ, what did you eat?
that does not a fart. It was a fart. It's not a fart from his
blue butt. Yeah, yeah, but what even were we talking about? It
doesn't matter. Let's just continue a new topic.
What was the craziest party you ever?
You're my party. I want to my birthday with the horse in the
room. Oh, yeah, you went to a party with a horse in a room and
then I got covid immediately after from the course. Did you
ride that? Bang? I wish I knew why there was a pony in that
room. I wish I was a Shetland pony just walking around the
thing. I think I know exactly why so that everybody could
leave that party and say OMG. I went to a party with the horse
at it. Yeah. Yeah. What if we made a statue made of ****
turds and put it in the middle of the room and I guess that's
piss on it. They also had a Fender Rhodes piano in there. I went to a party with a statue made of turds that had piss on it.
That'd be the front page of fucking Encore magazine in every local city.
They had a Fender Rhodes piano and I took a picture of it. You took a picture of a piano?
Somebody asked me what the fuck are you doing and I said I've never seen one in person.
A piano? It was a Fender Rhodes it was from like '67. He's from like '67. Shut up. Shut the fu-
you're my best friend and my brother as well and my cousin and my mom. You're
bald now. Two bald guys just chilling at the fucking table. You can't even be mad
at me. I can't it's impossible. Because we're kindred spirits. Yeah. I will
say this definitely modulates the earring. Yeah. The earring has been
modulated. I think you're right. Yeah the earring has been modulated. You have a
modulated appearance. I put the, this is the smaller one that I had. Yeah. I put
the smaller one didn't because I was I was walking around and I caught had a
big hoopie I caught the I caught the thing I caught it swinging in my in my
side profile and I went oh dear everyone's gonna think I'm mr. clean no
I don't know about that yeah I'm not so sure yeah maybe mr. dirty Tracy Ross
Tracy Ellis yeah that's what I thought when I saw if you were the big hoop
I'm hearing that's what I would think yeah kind of bill laker damn you would
actually know when I were talking about like being you being like a viking
slave before, but you could actually be a pretty good pirate crew member to oh my
God dude yeah, you could be the one with the parrot yeah. Well, that's the
captain. I feel like he tell that really pirates of the Caribbean. Why don't you
that's it? I guess you're right. Yeah, I think I would I think normally it's the
captain right they usually cuz no one else can afford a parrot you're thinking
of the steering wheel yeah no that's it has the steering wheel and a peg leg
yeah actually wait in the pirate movie treasure planet the parrot is a piece of
pink slur pirates those are those are a parrot is a piece of pink slime try
saying that ten times piece of pink slime piece of pink slime you I gotta
stop saying that cuz he always tries it yeah listen buddy I nobody wants to hear
you do that if you're not gonna fuck it up piece of pizza there we go that's
funny yeah the craziest party I ever went to is I went to a high school party a
birthday party yeah yeah and I just crazy I got kicked out yeah I got kicked
out I was just trying to recruit for my new
tic-tac hype house and I went to a high school party is crazy they tied me up
Tommy up and threw me in the backyard I'm a tic-tac dance called the worm come
check this out hey kids there's a new tic-tac dance the electric slide we do
you in the worm. You have to do it at my birthday. Come on to my birthday hype house.
I think that we could have done a hype house. Oh my god. If we had moved to LA instead of
New York City, we could have done a hype house. What do you think this studio is? This is
basically a hype room maybe. Perhaps. We're going to sleep. We have a sleeping guy in
in the corner just could be a sleeping snore on
didn't even blink. Oh, there he goes.
He got just bottled.
She got by hard.
Yeah, that's our new prank show. That's the closest. I've ever
actually do answers that this is the craziest party I've ever
been to. I saw someone throw a motherfucking bottle.
I did just get so hyper and now I kind of want to fucking talk
about stuff like Sonic. I almost bought a diet Mountain Dew earlier and if I did I
think I would have been a little crazier. I'm gonna Mountain Dew you. I'm so tired.
You're not supposed to say that at the awesome party we started. This is a pretty low energy episode I will say. I think
everybody's in shock because something changed. I was I was I was looking for I
was looking for something in my sleep last night. What were you looking for? I
have no idea I don't know I was looking I was I was awake in the bed and moving
everything around looking for everything and my girlfriend said go back to sleep
and I said no you told me to look for something I mean honestly knowing
knowing girlfriends she probably honestly fuck I love how I love how in
your sleep like no you told me to do this well I'm still asleep she probably
low-key fucking dead-ass did are you drawing don't draw on his head draw
anything no yeah yeah yeah you did yeah oh my god oh my god dude that is this
Christ, you have that on your head forever now.
What the fuck?
That's fucked up.
That's not cool.
There's nothing on his head.
It is funny how every single...
Every single story you have told about you sleepwalking,
in your dream state, you are the sassiest person in the world.
Yeah.
You're just like, "I'm..."
Don't close, don't open the window.
I want the window open.
That's literally what I do.
I know.
This is, all these stories...
So there those are there also stories. I know are probably only funny to me,
but I think it's the funniest thing ever. No, it is very funny. I will say
they're going to age to wake up poorly when there's a Netflix documentary
about how I killed everybody and that'll each poorly to
it is so funny to me to wake up and have someone tell me you were so mean to
yeah, you were asleep. Yeah, I miss I haven't been sleepwalking that much
recently. That was the first time in a really long time that I did it last. I'm
multiple times, apparently multiple times like like multiple multiple like
close to ten have turned to whoever is in the bed with me and and told them
that they were my apprentice.
That's like a move that I do when I'm when I'm sleeping sleep talking is I get
up. I look right out and say you're my apprentice and then I go back to bed and
then one time I told my brother to make me a milkshake after I said he was my
apprentice. Well, like you're my purse. You grabbed me one time. I do not
fucking grab everybody I talked about that with fucking time it was not it was
not like it was not well it wasn't like a spooning grab or anything though you
like you just you like monster grab me you just went like yeah yeah all of
Torea they're elected to sleep on the floor or don't know why you slept yeah
yourself you fucking lawnmower you sat there to go in John Deere and you think
you also you act like you act like you're the only person who grabs people
one tries to assault them in their sleep.
That's literally what we all do to each other all the time and
you're the only you're just too scared to do it.
Yep.
Me and Kayla Pierce love touching each other in our sleep.
We're friends.
We get our we're not intimate with each other.
I'm afraid to be in the same bed as you and grab you in your
sleep.
Yes.
You're afraid you're a pussy.
You won't do that.
You would rather sleep on the ground.
You're actually in your sleep and sound like a fucking like
the rock tumbler polishing a fucking stone. Yeah, then then actually come
here and grab it. So I honestly think that you probably have some like
list. I don't mean this as an insult. I'm serious. I'm fucking serious. Okay,
that's how you know he's about to say something really nice. It's really nice.
I honestly think after hearing you sleep probably fifty sixty times in my life.
You have severe brain damage. You have
There's no way that you do not have like like part brain death because of how
little oxygen gets into your brain at night. I don't know that's what that's
why you're probably where
I had no idea has to be like so bad for you with the sound that that's me. It
can kill you yeah yeah post Malone. It's killing it killed him. Yeah yeah. How
Did you know, did you guys know that Post Malone is like um...
His real name is
Poston. You know he has a face tattoo that's always farting?
Really? Yeah. That's sick. That's actually sick. He's like, I guess he's like a huge fan of
Magic the Gathering
and like for whatever, I think he's the highest profile celebrity that likes,
like publicly likes Magic the Gathering.
So Magic the Gathering make a ton of cards with just like him on them.
And it's like so crazy, it's so fucking weird. They make a card where like
they have like a normal wizard but they give him like post Malone's face.
Jesus.
He's dope dude.
And they sell him for like a hundred dollars.
He had a Bud Light collab.
That's how you know you've made it.
Oh yeah.
If I can get a Bud Light collab before my dying death then that would be a dream come
true for a guy like me.
Yeah.
Was it there was when Post Malone was first like on the up and up.
I wish he'd post his Malone online.
And like everyone is finding like his old shit where it's like you know there's like that
song where-
Yeah he used to be Rucka Rucka Ollie.
Yeah.
And then there's that one where he's singing that Bob Dylan song and everyone's like "Oh
my god he's actually a good musician."
It's like yeah he's like he just chose a different style of music.
Yeah but people were- I mean you- wait so you think-
So everyone was like-
You admit right now that you think rap is music.
You just admitted that.
What do you mean?
just admitted that you think rap is actually music and not just like
talking. Moving on from the most embarrassing thing ever said on the
podcast. It's rhythm and poetry. Yeah. Okay. And a melody? I don't think so. I have a song you should
check out. What's that? It's called Walk This Way by Run DMC. No that's pure rock.
Featuring Aerosmith. No that's a rock song bud. Buddy you're gonna be surprised.
Yeah, well you're gonna be surprised when I lay you down flat. No. Yep. I'm there's no way in hell
I'm going flat Noah is sleeping and looking exactly like cemetery in the
Every single second his hair in his face. Oh, he's rubbing himself
No, don't
Rub your thing. Yeah, no kicking. Oh, yeah, we have two fucking clumsy cartoon characters sleeping
Taking a picture every second. I know man. I wish
(laughing)
- It's Drake, picture of Drake.
I wish I looked like Drake.
I would say, if I could probably look like any person
on earth and still retain my personality,
I think Drake might be the one for me.
- I might say Superman.
- You wanna look like Superman but not be him?
- If you looked--
- No, if I looked like him, I'd probably be able to fly.
- If you looked like Drake--
- If I, I'll choose to look like Superman
while he's in the sky and then I will be able to fly.
- By the way, I don't mean be Drake,
I mean look exactly like him while Drake still exists.
If you looked exactly like Drake--
- You just get away with a lot.
- Wait, do you mean like--
- Like look like him and walk around
and people are like, "Oh, that's Drake."
- You're white Drake or--
- No, I would look exactly like--
- Exactly like perfect copy.
- If I could be born to be his--
- So, okay.
- I would become his--
- I was gonna say, he would just probably be like--
- I could be reborn--
- You would probably just work at Subway if you--
(laughing)
- If I could be reborn as his identical twin
separated at birth, but obviously we have a twin connection
and one day we would link up,
but that's a whole different story.
- He sees you working at T-Mobile one day.
- Exactly, he puts me on, right?
And then I start doing shows,
body double straight MF Doom style or a mom style.
- Every recessive trait in the family line.
So it's like--
- I'm him with the most fucked up hairline ever.
- Your hairline's way far back
and your teeth, or your front teeth just don't exist.
You're like, "You look just like me."
(laughing)
- Yeah, I wanna do that.
- You were my baby brother by a little bit.
I was born first. Yeah, I would do all that kind of 20 year old. Imagine if you made that
wish with the genie to look exactly like Drake. You look exactly like Drake. Okay, you got
your wish. You walk outside. Crazy homeless guy hits you in the face with a hammer. Oh
my God. Wish wasted. That would suck shit. Can you imagine how much that would suck?
It would suck even more than getting hit in the hammer normally. Do you remember that
photo? Remember that photo of the guy who looks exactly like Drake sucking dick? Yeah.
- That's Drake though. - That's such a funny picture.
- That is Drake though. - That is Drake.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Prove it. - Did you know--
- Look at the picture. - I don't know if you guys,
did we already talk about this?
How when you join the rap industry,
all the music executives--
- Oh, I don't know.
- They would get you-- - We have definitely
talked about it a bunch of times,
but I don't know if we--
- So it's crazy, I just found out this from this guy who,
I don't remember his name, but he was, I guess, a rapper,
and he was saying that apparently what happens is
You get signed by like, you know, Interscope or Sony or whatever, and then they get you
into a room, if you're a rapper, they get you...
That really does look just like Drake.
He's sucking after he's got cum on his face too.
But yeah, they get you in a room and they say like, "Yeah, we want you to sign a deal
or whatever," and then they fuck your butt and they get it on camera, and then they show
you the video and they say, "You have to sign a 360 deal right now."
And then that's why a lot of these rappers get messed up with their deals
because of their...
Who was the video who said that?
His name was like Knowledge or something.
Was that a Vlad TV interview?
I think he did do a Vlad TV interview, but he also just did an interview where he was...
Did he do a...
He was just like a bunch of guys in a room and they were mostly talking about like sports
and stuff, but he just randomly kind of chimed in with talking about this whole kind of factual
situation.
Yeah.
It was on Mad TV, you said?
No.
Vlad?
You don't know DJ Vlad?
He's not a DJ. He's a guy with a, um, he's a pervert with a GoPro.
He'll like interview,
yeah.
He interviews like rappers and says like, yo, like describe in detail,
like how much sex you have. Yeah. Yeah. Describe in detail,
like the craziest time you ever fucked.
That's a normal thing to ask a rapper though.
He'll interview like teenagers from Chicago and he'll be like,
so when you, have you ever killed anybody? Just straight up. And they'll be like,
I don't remember.
no jumper to like no like fucking he'll interview somebody and ask them to just
like you like say like the address of your op yeah and he's a big stupid guy
Adam 22 yeah can you guys say the address of your up what's your address
is one I'm not your name dude I would never fucking spin on you though yeah
thank you I think the day I spent on you is a day basically the whole fucking
block changes. That's right. The day I spin on one of you guys is the day I spin on myself.
I would rather spin on my own fucking grandma. I would rather slide on my fucking niece who's
2 years old. I would rather slide on the 100 cutest puppies in the world than ever slide
on my homie. What does your sign say? It's remotee. Hold it up. Remotee. That's in fucking
Spanish remote a hold it up remote they eat hold it up
oh it says we're gonna do it hold it up remote promote YouTube channel and then
the Matt episode okay so we still actually have a few minutes left so I'm
not sure why you're kind of the show to end right now by the way if you were
producer on a real show like the Rachel Ray show or the Bill Maher experience
this is not be there's no fucking way that you'd be yeah I do they can't write a
note you can't write if you were on listen if you are on fucking Rick and
Morty you cannot write a note as a producer on a piece of towel paper and
throw and show it to me and you definitely can't throw it onto the so
you might actually be able to do that on Rick and Morty because they're kind of
like alt yeah that could be like my funny kind of I think yeah they kind of
buck that the system a little bit and they do things a little different buck
- Buck the system.
- You're gonna buck Angel the system.
- Yeah, buck the police.
- Buck them?
- This is a ship.
- Oh, that's pretty good.
Yeah, you could be kind of a target.
- Tarjay, nah.
- Don't even.
- You see that shit, Target Ex Valenciaga?
- I don't know what you--
- That collab is gonna be fire.
- Sometimes when you speak--
- Look, the last three minutes,
we're gonna talk straight about fashion.
Shirts, which shirts are you wearing?
- T-shirt.
I got a T-shirt on.
I got the same Carhartt pants I wear every day.
I have Dickies on.
Whoa, okay, so some work wear boys.
And I have a t-shirt on.
All right, what else, do you got anything else up?
Yeah, what else are you going to ask?
And that's the end of the fashion corner.
You don't want to do accessories?
What about, yeah, well I have, what about this?
I got about a rack on the neck.
I have a hat.
I got about two racks on the wrist.
Whoa.
You know.
What is, actually, what is that?
You got a gold Casio?
I got the Patti on.
That's actually, look at my stuff, Patrick.
I got the Patti jacket.
and I'm wearing a belt on my pants. Okay, I got my pocket keys and wallet.
I'm not even actually got the right socks Adidas. Okay, the socks are
straight. My wife's accident. I'm realizing right now. I'm wearing my
wife's socks and Nike shoes. Okay, my shoes the hat the hat is a antique
store. The hat is antique antique hat from a different decade. Oh deodorant
My deodorant is Tom's.
Yup, yo.
Actually, me too.
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
No way.
We all have Tom's deodorant?
What?
Which one, the blue one?
Wait, yes.
No, I don't think I have the blue one.
Actually, maybe I wore the white today, but I have both.
I do too.
I have the blue one with the lavender.
Mine is red.
Or the white one in lavender.
Maybe it's not.
I think it's Tom's, but it's red.
Tom's is Maine.
You have Old Spice, boy.
I used to.
No, I definitely don't have Old Spice.
You're backing things up right now.
I used to have Tom's, at least.
I used to, no I definitely don't have Old Spice.
You're backing things up right now.
I used to have Tom's at least.
I just stopped using unnatural deodorant because the blue Old Spice stuff.
My girlfriend made me get natural deodorant because she didn't want me to die.
Everyone's girlfriend read the same fucking article about deodorant having aluminum in
it that causes armpit cancer or something.
And now everyone's girlfriend is making them use natural deodorant.
Who is putting this article out?
here's Jubio. Okay so he wanted us to say why don't you just sit here
come over here. Do your promote. Promote the white channel. Stand up. What is white?
Guys let's be completely quiet. Remember the show and the
live show and all that stuff too. Yeah okay so you're doing promo right now
ready this is the most important fucking part of the show if you fuck this up I
will beat the crap out of you. Okay my tickets to the live show the
Halloween live show. My dick is the light. What are you saying?
Shh, let him do it. Let him get a chance.
What? Let him get a chance.
Subscribe to the YouTube channel
for the Matt DeVita episode.
Start over. Start over. Start over.
Let him just get one try. You're completely
bald. And you look like shit.
Oh my god. Alright. Start over.
You look like shit. You look worse than Caleb.
Start over. Worse than Caleb? Why am I over here
catching strays? Why did we let him do this?
I got worse. You look like shit. I'm the new
Cameron. You look like the bumblebee from the Simpsons.
You talk like him too!
Now that I think about it, you fucker.
So go ahead and do your promo and show it off.
No, I don't want to do anything.
Redo the promo right now.
I don't want to do anything.
Start from the beginning and say it like you're a radio host, okay?
I want you to really fucking sell it.
Sell it or I'm going to dress stripes on your shirt.
Okay, you got it?
You got it?
Like, "And thank you for listening to the episode."
Do it like that.
So you just listen to Justin Bieber.
What the fuck!
We don't like, we hate Justin Bieber.
Oh, never mind.
I forgot.
Okay, buy tickets to the live show, buy tickets to Jubio's, buy Jubio's plane ticket home.
Buy tickets to Jubio's funeral.
Because we're selling Jubio's funeral tickets.
SwagTrip.com/shows.
And SwagTrip.com/Jubiodeath.
Yeah, because they'll be dead pretty soon.
and youtube.com/podcastaboutlist.
- And also check out Axis of Awesome on YouTube.
- Yeah, four chords.
- Four chords video, it's catchy.
It's funny but catchy.
- Pick up White People Taco Night by Axis of Awesome.
- All right, bye guys.