(siren)
(music)
The Dr. Pepper cast
(gunshots)
So, yeah, the theme song ends
Boom, boom, boom
Crazy, I just
myself by accident I'm afraid I just glued myself that'd be if he was in the
yeah and group right right what would the glue man group it would you do they
make like collage well first of all yeah they don't drum yeah no that's a blue
thing well maybe they drum once and then it gets yeah this is what the drumming
Sounds like this
Like that video the guy who glues his uh his diapers to his chair
No, no recognition
You know I've seen I've seen monkey fucks the frog
I've seen the caught the scary car drive down the thing yeah, I've seen about 400 episodes of equals three
That's it. Anything outside of that, anything outside of that.
He said about.
It's not about.
You know what? Yeah.
Law of averages.
If it's outside of that reference pool of videos, I probably have not seen that.
Right.
It's the guy, he puts Titebond glue on his diaper and he goes, "Boy, am I glued."
What?
I've shown this on stream before.
Not to me. I wasn't around.
- Well, you missed out on probably one of the most
moving videos ever.
- The only video--
- It's Sisyphean.
- The only video that I've ever seen
is Fox and the Hound ending explained.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- How long is that video?
- 30 minutes.
- Wow.
- Damn.
- I don't remember what happens at the end of that movie.
What happens?
Is it--
- Well, basically it's just like this whole thing
where the fox represents a friend.
- The hound.
- And the hound represents the hound's--
- The fox represents the hound's friend
the hound represents the fox's friend. And apparently, when whichever one of them dies
or is lost or whatever, apparently that is a sad ending.
You know all that SpongeBob how it's explanation?
SpongeBob how it's made.
Right. Apparently SpongeBob represents the main character of the show.
Krabby Patties is how it's made. That'd be a great episode.
Krabby Patties represent deliciousness.
I think our boy Babish already hit that one.
That's true.
Well, he had the role of double, triple decker or whatever.
They also make gummy Krabby Patties already.
Oh, yeah, they've been making those and those are yeah, those are great. That's what a crabby patty is. They're small. Think about it
Yeah, sponge Bob small. They are so good those gummy crab. Yeah
Yeah, I get 50 of those those are like the it's like the perfect mix of every single good gummy texture
Do you know what gummy I miss from my childhood?
But the last time I had them I didn't like it anymore
What is those gummy blue sharks that have the blue on top and white on the bottom?
Yeah, those are like the best fucking thing ever and I had one as an adult. This is disgusting
Maybe they change the recipe is that a possibility I think no I think I just can't handle that much sugar anymore
Yeah, cuz it's too big. It's too big in the texture. I see you eat sugar like a fucking like a horse
It's not like that no no
I
Think you have sugar you have not seen me eat cubes of sugar
I've seen you bring a bag of sugar cubes for lunch before that's not true
Yeah, he can yeah, and he says can you hold these for me?
Well, if even Patrick is saying it's too sugary, I think something's up.
See, it's just it's shitty.
Like realizing that like you hear all those jokes that like your dad says it like a barbecue or something is like, oh, fuck, I can't.
The kids want McDonald's. I can't eat that shit anymore.
And it's like, yeah, you just like eating McDonald's as a grown man genuinely is is one of the most like depressing experiences.
It's pretty mainly it's spiritually wrong.
I think eating McDonald's or any kind of candy as a grown man
I think probably you know how there's all these crazy people who say this thing's bad for you this thing's bad for you with food
Yeah, they're all right. Yeah, you just can't get obsessive about like seed oils being bad for you all that
Ghost in the office in the office in the office. What the hell is off that table? What was that?
It was that yeah cardboard tube
I saw it just moved for no reason for no reason at all for no rewind there was a reason time stamp
Reads I'm saying for away. This is basically the Halloween episode. Yeah, because it's coming out pretty close to Halloween
But we do have we have a Halloween thing yeah, but we're sure we don't have a hell. Okay, then we don't know that's coming
Okay, so but a ghost did just literally throw something in the office out of fucking nowhere
Ah oh, and he just yelled into this microphone as well that a ghost startled me. Sorry girls, okay?
No, stop scaring me, man. I'm not scaring you. I'm being we're not doing right now
I'm getting scared. I can't control it if I get scared. I scream and a ghost is fucking touching me on the back of my neck
It's raising hairs on my nape. I'm gonna wet my fucking my nape is made a nape my name
Did it just touch your nape
Yeah, the ghost nape to you. I got I got my nape rubbed didn't we do this before haven't you guys sat around screaming at me?
Before well move of that time we were messing you this yeah, I'm really scared this time
Okay, listen to my teeth chattering. We promised 21
(Screams)
Stop! I got close to listening to the teeth chatter and then you scared me!
We promised 21 jump scares this month.
Yeah, we have to throw them all in right now.
I think we are at, I think right now we're probably sitting at 14, so.
Yeah.
Okay, so how many did we have in the...
I don't know, I didn't count them.
Fuck, we didn't count them?
No.
That was your job.
It was your whole thing, it was a 21 jump scare. You can come up, you have to count them.
First of all, I was the one who came up with 21 jump scares.
And then he took control of it, pretended it was his idea.
I did not.
And then did not, and then did not.
Big surprise.
He said he came up with it on the episode.
- Oh my god.
- Something he's been doing lately
is he's been stealing everything from me.
He even wears the clothes I wear now.
- Yeah I do.
- All right, I'd like you to,
so go ahead and explain yourself.
- Can you compare the colors?
- Why have you been stealing everything?
- I just want to point out right now,
we're both wearing white t-shirts
with designs in black on them,
and who came into the office first?
It was me.
So Patrick came in after me, so he's copying me.
- I'm doing a Halloween thing, I'm doing a face-off.
- Both wearing black hats, you came in after me.
- I have a white t-shirt with a black thing on it.
- I was in here before you two though.
Yeah, I know. I'm just saying you're not wearing a black hat. So it's not really a full copy. It's only half
Okay, what look like? Yes, like you why your head so hot?
This hat is cooking my head. Yeah, what the hell that was like what the fuck's going on there?
I put that on your head, and it looked like like when you get like a
Like a hat for like t-ball, and it's clearly made for like a grown man. I didn't play I played
I went straight to baseball. Yeah. Yes. I didn't play t-ball either
I just went farm league and then you went farm. I played coach pitch
Yeah, I played that cuz a grown man had to go against a grown man. Well. Yeah, pretty cool cuz and he fucking
Whoop his ass. Yeah, yeah, he's throwing curveballs
I played for the Jutras team sports blue jays the hell in the Loffa
Farm League sounds like a sense like a lot of shit to me neither of you guys played peewee football, right?
I didn't I didn't play football cuz I
I played peewee football. I played in two weight classes in my in my my tenure in peewee football
midget and mini midget
This is the name of the weight classes
Why?
Sense
Because if you're putting on
Like little kids running around with all all that all those helmets and pads and stuff
- You don't know. - I guess from far away.
- Could be a little person. - From far away, yeah.
It could be a little person or it could be like a little person in age.
- Yeah, well it was the same as the ladder. - Right, yeah.
- Yeah. - Yeah, and I was barely...
- You need a ladder. - Yeah, when you're...
- To get those pringles off the shelf. - So how many...
I mean, like, but you start with peewee and then how many different...
I don't know the other weight classes, but how many different weight classes...
- Also, why is that peewee? - Well, yeah, then under that it's bacterium.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, and it's paramecium.
- I kinda wanna see what--
- Oh, is that where pee wee comes from?
- Yeah.
- Paramecium, plecium, paroicium.
- Yeah, and then the largest one is hummingbird.
- Yeah.
- I wanna see what the weight classes are.
- I'm in the hummingbird weight class.
- I'm in hummingbird.
- Dude, yeah, you have to, if you're a bacterium kid,
you have to watch out for those hummingbird kids
'cause they'll plow the fuck through you.
- Dude, those hummingbird kids, they--
- When they tackle you, you will fucking die.
- They're all sitting around that--
They're huge.
It's not even a-- it's a Gatorade thing full of sugar water,
that red sugar water.
Some of those Hummingbird kids are 30 pounds.
OK, so I was wrong.
They could snap in your neck.
I was wrong.
It wasn't mini-midget.
It was mighty midget, which is above.
So I-- so there's-- so they changed it now.
Now it's might instead of midget.
So now it's tiny might, mighty might, junior might.
Oh, might like a bug?
Yeah.
I guess.
I thought you meant--
Like mighty might like the superhero.
I thought you meant M-I-G-H-T.
M-I-T-E.
So it used to be tiny midget, mighty midget,
and junior midget.
i guess the other like what we can do this because the political correctness
so let's just go a thousand times smaller
well it must be to what's another what's another smallholding
besides a little person i guess i'm my dust might yet yeah i got a very i got
him to get what could we do this a replacement for a little person like
something where we don't say little person we want to book the same general
feeling that we want to know we want to have so small it's all about it
- People are allergic to them.
They're on pieces of dust.
- You find them in your cat's ears.
- Yeah.
They're parasites.
- A mite.
That's, I think, what we'll go with, a mite.
- Yeah, it was pretty awesome, dude.
- Yeah.
- I never played peewee football.
I did farm league and then I--
- Bro was in Farmville.
He's on his damn phone.
- What the hell?
- In second grade, I didn't play
because I told my mom I wanted to go to drawing classes.
- Yo.
And then my siblings made fun of me.
- And then in fourth grade I got into skateboarding
and then I never played like a team sport again.
- Sick.
- I did drive.
- I played some basketball in middle school.
- Really?
- Oh, I did play basketball in fourth grade.
Both of my cousins are like--
- I feel like you'd be good at basketball.
- Really tall.
- No, you were bad?
- Not as a kid at least.
- Yeah, as a boy you might be really good.
- I don't know.
- My cousins are--
- Too shy.
- Don't wanna stay on the other side of the court.
- Don't wanna be near the ball.
I'd never played a game of basketball.
The soccer kid who's picking grass, but in a basketball game.
Somehow picking grass on the court.
If you can imagine.
He brought a piece of sod in the...
Yeah.
Sitting on a single square of sod, picking grass on the basketball court.
And like too old.
Yeah.
And everyone else wanted to be there.
Everyone else is like, has a competitive spirit.
Everyone else is like, "I want to play basketball."
Yeah.
Yeah, I didn't know.
I played basketball and I only scored one point the entire time that I played basketball.
I don't think I ever scored one.
Accidentally for the other team.
I scored on my own basket.
This was the first thing's coming out of halftime and at halftime you would switch sides
Oh, yeah, and so I got confused and I scored on my own basket
My dad was like that day my dad was like all right. We're gonna take you to basketball
I don't think I ever even took a shot
You get just get nervous when the ball gets hands
Well, I think people also knew not to pass to me. Yeah, yeah
usually a sticky hand
Yeah, I don't know I showed up to the rather get blocked
(laughing)
and pass it to your wife.
Like you're just sitting there,
just sniffling and drooling on yourself.
Long fingernails, ugh.
I think I'd rather foul out.
- I showed up to like the first basketball practice.
It was like me on my like really tall cousin's team.
- We all played basketball.
- It was both of my cousins who were like six foot.
My cousin like is like six foot eight now.
And then his older brother is like six five.
And then it was like me and I was like,
I think like four foot 11.
They must have been like five.
If he's 6'8" now, that means he was 6'0" when he was 8.
That's the general rule.
Something like that, yeah.
But, uh, I showed up to the first practice in jeans and then realized I'd never played
basketball in my life.
You realized that?
Like you were thinking of a different sport?
I don't even know.
I showed up in jeans because I think I forgot that I signed up and then...
But you still showed up.
I went to the first practice and then didn't know how to play and then just like ran off
the court and went home.
Yeah, I thought that, you know, I'd probably only learned about basketball from like, uh,
like the local museum had a lot of like basketball history stuff.
So I was showing up at a ball made of fucking corn and there was a
yeah, I was thinking we're gonna be playing with a bucket, right?
Yeah, I thought it was gonna be a bunch of old white guys with their
pants hiked up.
All of a sudden I'm getting fucking dunked on, you guys nuts are in my mouth.
I showed up and I was, they started the game.
I was sitting at the top row of the bleachers with an N64 controller.
Yeah, I didn't understand.
Yeah, I'm playing basketball asshole.
Yeah, I control that guy, right?
Go! Go!
None of my team is not doing anything that I want them to.
Switch.
Go!
Switch sides.
Switch genders.
Turn into a full girl basketball team.
Yeah.
Speaking of scary Halloween stuff,
something scary happened to me that I haven't
been able to stop thinking about.
And it was that-- oh, am I boring you?
Yeah.
What an awfully timed yawn.
I know.
Yeah.
Such a mean yawn.
That's a mean yawn, asshole.
I didn't mean for that to happen.
- Well you did happen to be mean.
- I woke up early again.
I woke up at like 6 in the morning.
- And here we are talking about his early thing
instead of your scary story.
You woke up when?
- This is actually really interesting.
I do wanna hear about this.
- What time did you wake up, I actually am curious.
- Like 6 a.m.
- Why?
- 'Cause Moe bit my earring.
He bit my earring and tried to--
- Your dog is trying to have sex with you.
- Speaking of Ray William Johnson,
you ever hear that song, First World Problems?
- No.
That's a Weird Al song.
- Speaking of, it doesn't mean it has to be.
- Yeah, I was just speaking, I was just speaking of.
- You were speaking of, all right.
- Yeah, speaking of.
- You're looking for fault today.
- Yeah, you're in a mean mood.
- Yeah.
- Well, it's 'cause I took that Adderall.
- Admit this, admit--
- I took an Adderall that was too big.
- Say it right now in your microphone,
say, "I am rotten to my core."
- I am rotten to my core like an apple.
- No, you don't say like an apple.
- No, take out the apple part.
- Take out the apple.
- I am rotten like an animal.
- No, no, you say, "I am rotten to my core."
- I'm rotten to my core.
- "I am not deserving of love."
I'm an evil fuck. I am say I am hell-bound. I am a hell-bound sinner. There's no redemption
There's no redemption for a guy like me
Because of my I'm a complete waste say we got a waste of what a waste in matter matter
Okay, that's good. You would be better as a tree or a dust you would honestly be better as plastic
Oh, you would actually be better as maybe I'm like plaque from a tooth. Yes
Say I'm worse than plaque. I'm worse than plaque from a tooth because at least
plaque does something. Yeah, say I'm like a dream in a baby's brain of dust
that gets forgotten instantly. I'm like a baby's words. I mean nothing.
Yeah, yeah. I'm babble. Yeah, you are babble. That's it. That's right.
Okay, I feel a little bit better about your yawn now. I feel like you've
atoned, but there's still no redemption. But there's nothing good for
you over the horizon. The type of person that you are is the type of
of person that goes down in history as one of the most infamous and also
insignificant pieces of very tiny pieces of shit.
You will somehow be responsible for millions of deaths and so much.
Somebody else will get blamed.
Yeah.
I mean, you won't even get the credit for it.
Um, I, when we were at the bar, I walked into the bar, everyone was already there.
And I saw, I saw the grim reaper.
I saw a person dressed as the Grim Reaper, so full cloak.
Oh, I missed this.
Scythe.
Well, this is the thing here, right?
You were there too, right?
And I walked in.
I saw this person facing away from me.
So all I see is cloak, scythe, and I was like, oh, that's a
crazy Halloween costume.
That's nuts.
I walk into the other room to meet up with you guys.
I'm like, oh, did you guys see the Grim Reaper out there?
Everyone's like, no.
What are you talking about?
And then multiple people got up to go order food and get
drinks. Like I would say less than five minutes after I said
that and nobody saw the Grim Reaper.
- Nobody saw it.
- I straight up saw the actual Grim Reaper.
- You're actually going to die.
- I'm going to die.
- Yeah, wow.
- He saw the Grim Reaper.
(screaming)
(laughing)
- Stop, man.
What the hell?
- He got scared by my scary story.
It's not a big deal.
- That was not a, you guys.
- I'm terrified right now.
- You guys don't realize the difference
between a scary and a scaring scream, okay?
So you were not like, ah!
- Ah, yes, see that's a scaring.
- That's a scaring, but then a scare.
- A scary would be like, ah!
- Right.
- What I do, whenever you do that.
(screaming)
- Like that?
- That was more just--
- Yeah, like Caleb, like,
"Oh no!"
- Yeah, that's how I scream.
- "Oh no, I don't wanna die!
Put me down, King Kong!
(laughing)
Put me down right now!
Get me out of this building!"
- I don't bang on his chest.
- You're banging on his fist?
- Well, that's actually pretty impressive.
- "Put me down!
You're so strong!"
- Is that, that is a subtext of that movie
is that she wants to fuck King Kong, right?
I think you're reading it. I think it's the other way around.
No, I think King Kong wants to fuck her.
I think she's in love with King Kong.
But which one, the remake, right? The Dino De Laurentiis remake?
The 70s one? I never saw that one.
Does she fuck him?
I think she does.
You know, there's a, I may have talked about it.
Stop me if I've talked about this because I can't remember,
but there's a ripoff from...
You've talked about a ripoff before.
Fuck.
All right.
A ripoff of what? It might be a different one.
Of King Kong.
Oh, no, then you haven't talked about this.
There's an Italian movie called Yeti.
Yeti the Terror of... it's called Yeti and it's a King Kong ripoff and there's a scene
where the girl is being carried by the Yeti, like King Kong, and she's like scared.
Oh, you showed me this clip before.
I definitely showed you the clip.
I may have even posted it on Twitter, but she like reaches up to like grab onto something
and she just touches... they just modeled a gigantic nipple and she touches the Yeti's
nipple and as she's touching it, it like gets hard.
Like they like inflate it and make it get hard and they have an insert of his face and
and he like smiles and like raises his eyebrows
and goes like, "Ugh, ugh."
- No one ever touches nipples before.
- And then she looks back and sees that she's touching
his nipple and pulls her hand away.
And she looks down, her hand is like covered
in clumps of hair and she like shakes the hair.
- Whoa.
- So first of all, glue hand. - It's so crazy.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Like she's doing a 40 year old version.
- Sticky sweaty hand.
- She's doing a 40 year old version of them.
- Yeah, she's waxing them.
- I was gonna go back to the glue man group
they were talking about earlier.
- And say what about it.
- Maybe she's in it.
- She could be in it.
- It's glue man group though.
- Glue woman man group.
- We don't know what she is.
So, write that down, jot it.
- Yeah, jot that down, and just fucking shove it
in your mouth.
Okay, he's writing this down.
- Definitely hold your pencil the weird way that you do.
- Yeah, and he was just about to say that too.
Hold your pencil in your weird way.
What does this say?
- We don't know what she is.
- Okay.
- So I jotted that down.
- And above it, it says divine.
- Yeah, I actually did it.
- It actually doesn't say divine.
- Oh, it says--
(screams)
That didn't get me.
I'm dude it didn't yeah be honest with me. Did I start he moved?
I didn't move he moved and he giggled and that's a giggle counts as a reaction
Yes, are you one of those fucking assholes who walks through us haunted house ago like?
Yeah, like beavis and butthead fucking asshole see I go
I wish it I could I would that is what I do
I do. I laugh when I get startled too.
When I go through a haunted house, I kind of just, I look for the smallest details.
You look for the smallest woman working there.
I look for the smallest details and I'm thinking, man, they must have been so fun to put this
together.
No, you would not.
Because I've gone to the Universal Horror Nights once.
Seems like it's wasted on you.
Yeah.
You need to go to...
I appreciate it.
Seems like you might better like a museum.
I know that when it comes to scary stuff, you're not supposed to be an enjoyer, you're supposed
to be a victim.
Yeah.
And so that's what I do.
When I watch scary movies, when I watched Barbarian the other day, I was literally doing,
I had my hoodie all the way down over my eyes, I'm looking through my ... I'm a grown man.
I'm a quarter of a hundred years old.
And I'm covering my eyes with my hand, I'm looking through it and I'm eeping and wifey
has never been less attractive in her life.
But I don't care because I'm having a good time.
- It is my wifey, she does the cover eyes thing
and it makes me laugh so hard every time.
There's something, it's like a build up to a jump scare.
She holds her hand in front of her face
and I always, if I've seen the movie before,
I'll always pull her hand down right before the jump scare.
- Oh my god, you're gonna be a mean father.
- Yeah.
- You're gonna be one of those mean--
- It's so funny to do. - Scaring.
It's not funny.
- It's really funny to do.
- If you did that to me, I would break your arm.
- Okay, I'm not gonna do it to you.
- And I'd probably be really scared even worse.
I don't have a beautiful love connection with you that would allow me to do
something like that. As if, as if you don't. I have a different type.
I've known you for years. As if you don't have a beautiful fucking love connection.
There's a bug. Okay, hold that thought. There's a bug.
Do you love me? Okay, wait, hold on. The bug is gone, guys.
The bug could be anywhere. Why is that video?
I saw there's a quarter on the ground over there. Okay.
That's not important to me.
That video that Alex sent of Moe playing with a cockroach.
Do you guys let that happen?
Do you let your cat play with a cockroach?
No, he sent me that last night.
I wasn't home.
He sent me the video of that,
and I asked him about it this morning.
I was like, "Did you get up and kill the cockroach?"
He was like, "Yeah, but I just let it fight it
"for a little bit.
"I wanted to see what would happen."
(laughing)
He's letting my fucking cat just fight.
Like if it's a mouse, I've seen him like,
he came into the living room with a dead mouse
in his mouth before.
- Yeah, but you're not supposed to--
- That's his job, he's not supposed to fight a bug.
- Dude, him sending that video to us,
and he sent it with the text, "Mo fighting a cockroach,"
and I was like, "Oh, it's probably
"like a dead cockroach he found."
It's just a fully alive cockroach crawling around
and Mo's swatting it, trying to kill it.
- I guess, so Alex told me-- - Disgusting, dude.
He picked it up in his mouth.
- That's the one that picked,
that cat licks your face, licks your fingers, your ears,
and I don't know what else, God only knows.
- I notice, I wake up to him doing that
because he's like--
- And right after he's been--
- He had that stomach worm.
- He's been deep throating cockroaches for hours
while you've been asleep.
And then he comes and he just--
- He wakes me up.
- Burps it into your mouth.
- Wakes me up like he dragged my ear,
like he was like, "Come on, feed me."
- He's gonna drop a cockroach in your ear one day.
- Dude, he's gonna pull up in my bed
and with a dead mouse in his mouth.
- Yeah.
- And that's gonna be his prize.
- I need to get a mouse attacker.
- Dude, it's--
- Phil's too scared of the mice, man.
- We don't have, like, I mean, honestly,
he's doing his job. - Usually I just get them.
- You just get the mice?
- Yeah, I just bat them around a little bit.
- You're too slow.
- You dress up like a cat.
- I walk down on all fours, I bat them around,
I pick them up my mouth, put it down,
toy with it a little bit. - You don't do that.
- And then I usually will cut it open with my claws,
and I usually will bring it to someone I love
and leave it in front of them.
- What? - Usually.
- As a present?
- Or your sick idea of a present?
- It's basically my sick idea of what a gift would be
if I was a human.
- Yeah, it's also a mouse's sick idea.
- Yeah. - Mice's sick idea.
- Well, it's not 'cause the mouse is dead
and the mouse had no idea what was happening.
- That's a pretty, this is a serial killer mouse.
- I'm kind of like an Old Testament god
toying with this little creature
and I'm just kind of being cruel.
And it doesn't even know what I am.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- An animal, that's what I am.
- I think it knows what you are.
I think rats and mice are very aware of--
- The bug's back, guys.
- Oh my God.
(laughing)
mother of god. My god, he's fucking right. There is a bug. No, dude. That is too scary.
I am the bug correspondent. Yeah, yeah. And now to Cameron. Going to our bug correspondent.
He's outside speaking to a bug. The bug was here earlier. It landed on the wall. When
I looked over, it was gone. But folks, this just in, the bug is back. We've set up a bug
trap using apple cider vinegar and soap. I've set up a bug trap using my cup tan. And Cameron,
me this am I one of your best friends in the world?
Folks I'm getting an important news in my earpiece the bug is nowhere to be seen
and we have to all eyes must be open to the question. Cameron answer the question.
How about you just answer that question. It's dangerous for a bug to be loose and no one
to know where it is. Cameron if I need somewhere to stay will you let me stay
at your house? I'm seeing the bug in the distance it's about a mile away. Things
are not so good at home and I need someone to talk to. The bug is about two
miles away now and I have a clear sight on it with my eyes. How can you even see that bug? You're making that up.
The bug just flew 10 miles away and it's going in circles. You're fucking lying.
Cameron is there some sort of magnifying lens we can look at this bug in?
No Patrick, I'm using... And also are you best friends with Caleb or me? The bug is right here Patrick, it just went on the light.
And I've been drinking way too much. Folks the bug is about a hundred miles away at this time and I'm
looking at it with my naked eye. I don't believe you that'd be the fastest bug
ever made by God. By the way, do you love both of us? Do you love us? We're brothers.
The brothers you wish you always had. Folks, this is news I did not want to
have to break on this show but the bug is in China. Okay, you can't see the China, you need a TV.
It likes the light folks, the bug likes the light. I've been drinking
grain alcohol and Kool-Aid all day. Scientists are looking into whether bugs
like light and this could be crucial evidence for the case. I've been
I've been experimenting with pills and I just need someone with me.
Folks, I have horrible news. There's a hundred bugs in a tree in a forest.
I don't know that you can know something like that.
I just saw it with my naked eye 3,000 miles away.
Speaking of naked, will you rate my body out of five?
Folks, I just saw another bug. It's on the floor.
Oh my god, he killed the bug.
Wow. You are fucking Jackie Chan.
Dude, you said I wasn't fast enough to play with a mouse.
- Wow, with a mouse? - He just smacked that bug
out of the damn world.
- It's like the news anchor thing was a bug trap.
- It almost was, the bug was like,
huh, they're so distracted with this news anchor thing
that I'm gonna fly right next to his head.
- I just hurt my shoulder doing that.
- See, you're not built for that.
- That bug was too strong for you.
- Yeah, that was me trying to unlock my animalistic instinct
and that's what happens when an animal spirit
flows through a human frame, it can't handle it.
- Yeah. - You used brave bird on it
and you did some damage to yourself.
- Yeah, I was a Pokemon.
- I've been feeling like an animal.
- But that's why werewolves wake up
and they're covered in bruises.
- You do look like Blaziken.
- Oh, I don't.
- And don't say I look like the Doug one.
- Diglett?
- Don't say that.
(laughing)
I look like Diglett.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Doug Trio.
- Okay, there's two of them.
- Doug Duo.
- Well, there's a third guy.
- You look like--
- Oh, a couple of Dodos, though.
- Shut that bitch ass up.
- I don't look like Incineroar.
- Oh, a couple of Blaziken ass.
okay okay but i don't like it's in a roar blast always last or no wait it's
is in center was a strong
it's in a lot of stories and a lot of war
your guard of war but
how my guard of war
regard of what if anything i look like me too
i look like low plenty you're a little more like me or think
now you know i would do it i know who you are nine oh yeah i got a friend i
have a habit you know who you have my balls in your mouth
- Geodude. - He's Celebi.
- Oh. - Which one is Celebi?
- I do do this. - You're also the egg one, too.
- The egg one. - The egg fancy.
- Yeah. - All right.
- You know what? - Well, that,
but also the one that is eggs.
- I opened up a, I'll say it.
I opened up a can of worms, Pandora's box situation.
- Oh, is there a worm one?
That would actually, that would be really good.
- No, no. - Weedle, yeah.
- I don't look like Weedle?
- Well, I guess Weedle probably has more hair than you.
He's got a little spike.
- Okay, very funny. - Metapod.
- Metapod. - Metapod.
Yeah, you look like you look like unknown cuz Hank can't tell if you're a boy or a girl so
Got you bitch ass and you look you look like you used to look like snorlax
And I look like a skinny version of him asshole bitch. You look like four of the unknowns you look like no
No, be a L and D. No on a row. Yep. Yeah
Also, you look like every digimon not the cool ones only the girl ones
I don't think so you look like angel mon. No you look like I'm Edward and SpongeBob's house and Patrick's house combined
It's kind of true. The head shape of SpongeBob's house, the face of Squidward's, and the top
of... Yeah, you could make my face out of those, I think. Yeah.
Yeah.
Could look cool.
Meanwhile, over here, I look like Mr. Krabs.
I think you guys better be quiet because my testicles...
Because of the herbal supplements I've been taking, my testicles have actually like 1.5
X in size. So you might want to watch who you're talking to.
Really?
Yeah. They stopped fitting through when I do this with my hand. My ball won't fit through
that anymore because I got so many...
- I think that's good.
- No, it's good.
- It's called Tangat Ali.
- You always end up taking some kind of supplement
or something and then you start complaining
about what it is doing to your body.
- No, the side effects are good for this.
I like having big balls that hurt real bad
when they touch my leg.
- You would do so good in medieval times.
- You really think so?
- I think that you would eat so many plants
that people told you to eat.
- I would do anything, yeah.
- Whatever the apothecary was like,
yeah, I think today we need to,
- The only cure for your twisted ankles,
I think we need to cut off your hand at the wrist
because that will equalize your body.
And you're like,
"Actually, can you cut off both of my hands?"
- I want the symmetry.
- Yeah, I really want that.
- He would eat crimson nirnroot.
- I think both of you would probably die at four years old.
- I would be an incredible slave in medieval times.
- No, you don't work hard.
- No, I would be a scribe.
- I'd be an amazing olomon.
- You'd be an eunuch.
- Eunuch?
- E-nuch.
- I would not be a eunuch.
You would be way more of a eunuch than me.
No, when my balls are fucking you.
Imagine him as a eunuch in the little cloak
and he's doing the tented fingers.
He has a big falsetto.
Master.
I don't have a big falsetto and I can't say master.
Yeah, well, you just did.
Remember that, we saw that fucking--
Remember we saw that eunuch?
We saw that movie--
It's e-nuke.
--in North Carolina.
Movie idea, e-nuke.
The woman eunuch of the North.
E-nuke of--
We saw the woman king and there's a eunuch in that movie.
Is there really a eunuch in--
Oh, yeah, there was.
I forgot about the eunuch.
Yeah.
What do they do?
It's so funny that I saw that, and then immediately,
like, two days later, saw this video of someone being like--
yeah, that was one of the biggest slave trading groups.
Or one of the biggest slave trading--
We need Pat to talk about this.
Patrick, he came out of that movie, and he texted us.
He said, so, I have some thoughts.
And then he unloaded.
Yeah, I didn't know.
I was just like, all right, that was just a pretty--
it seems like an Oscar bait movie.
- Was it Oscar, was it good?
- It was, I mean--
- It was certainly long.
- We've definitely talked about this before,
but I really don't wanna discuss that movie
with someone who hasn't seen it,
'cause it's kind of an experience.
- Yeah, really. - And I mean,
you weren't there, you didn't see it,
so I feel like I don't even feel comfortable
talking about it. - That's true,
I was literally fucking driving as that.
- Yeah, well-- - I need to scrape
this goo off with this, give me that.
- No, you can keep the goo there.
- No, I don't want-- - Leave the goo.
- You're gonna dull the knife.
- Can I have this back?
- Yeah. - Thanks.
Can I have this nothing back?
- Yeah, you can have that nothing back.
- Thanks.
There's nothing all over our nothing.
- Oh no.
- Oh man.
- So what is your big plan for Halloween?
What are you guys going as?
- Apparently there's a big show we have to do.
- Well yeah, we're gonna do our stupid little show
at the bell house on Halloween.
- On Halloween night.
- And the day before.
- But the day, which hey, I just wanna clarify,
I know this is probably the last chance
for us to tell people to get tickets.
The show's at 7.30, so you're gonna still be able
to go to whatever fucking degenerate satanic shit
you wanna do afterwards.
So if you're still planning on doing a summoning,
like if you will go, the show's gonna be,
you know, you'll be out of there
in an hour, hour and a half or so,
and then you'll be back in your fucking shithole,
summoning suddenly, in Molok, right?
Watching scary, satanic, scary movies.
You are gonna go and see Baphomet.
- Also, realistically, if you listen to the show,
how fun is your Halloween normally?
What, you sit and you watch Halloween Town
with two people at home, right?
you make popcorn, you drink soda.
- And that would be cool to do the day before on Sunday
and maybe you guys should come to my house.
- How about you come to our show
and we make you do push-ups in front of us?
How's that sound?
- And also, I still can't stress this enough,
if you bring a pillowcase, you will get candy.
- We're literally giving out free candy.
- This is the only chance you will have in your adult life
to trick or treat without getting put on a list.
- There's no question, you will be leaving with candy.
- And with a signed copy of a new vinyl album
that we are releasing.
It is an R&B album.
- Yes.
- With 20 songs.
- 24 songs.
- 24.
- And it's called-- - 'Cause there's four
hidden tracks.
- It's called My Spooky Sexy Halloween.
- It is, and we'll give it a little taste of it right now.
- And it's $1.
- Yo, your face look like a pumpkin
and I wanna fuck it now.
And I wanna go and take you back to Halloween town.
- That is, see, that's,
we don't want to give away too much.
Yeah.
But here's another part that I don't want to give away too much.
Not too much.
Ghost.
Mm-hmm.
That's one word.
And we do a cover of Candy Girl by New Edition.
Obviously.
There's also--
Girl, when I'm in that pussy, I'm a monster.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna come into your--
Girl, your pussy smells like a zombie.
Your pussy smells like a fucking coffin.
You got bolts on either side like Frankenstein.
I'm bobbing for pussy.
That would be kind of hot if I'm bobbing for pussy.
And then there's a lyric where you have the pussy in your mouth and you're like
*mimics*
Because you got it.
Yeah.
Right?
And then there's one spoken word part where it's like we're doing all that sexy stuff and then
it goes like, "Girl that costume's really good, but it would look a lot better on the floor of my crypt."
Yes.
My abandoned crypt.
And there's a, the album cover is there's like a sexy girl Frankenstein and she has the bolts on her hips.
So that yeah, yeah doggy style. Yeah, you're holding on like she's a like she's a horse like she's a horse. Yeah, and there's
What is that called a horse?
What is the horse wheel that you ride on?
Your pussy feels like when I put my hand in the brain bucket
Yeah, side a is all Halloween stuff inside B is all horse stuff. Which ride is this?
What a carousel?
That's what I'm thinking of I got it. I got it. I wasn't that hard. I just had to mime it perfectly
I didn't do the movement
And
My shit what you wanted a buck on your shit isn't bucking like moving away like getting away from like yeah
Like trying to like get away away like trying to get you off you know girl to try to get away from your penis
I don't know you don't know what bucking me. I've never I've been on a horse once so they taught you but I saw a video on
I think I think I was on tick-tock that my girlfriend was watching of have you guys seen videos of people putting horseshoes on horses?
That shit is crazy. Oh wait where they put the hand they like fuck
They have like a knife, and they like scrape a bunch of a hoof off. Yeah, that's pretty cool. It's crazy
Well, I just looks like it. I mean I know it probably doesn't but looks like it hurts so bad
No, I was like their fingernail. I know yeah, but I even then I wouldn't want someone holding on to my finger
and scraping my fingernail with a knife
and then hammering nails into it.
- You could technically do that with a human fingernail.
- It's what an acrylic nail is.
- Technically, yeah.
- But they're--
- Same thing with an acrylic nail.
- So you could get like a metal nail.
- Yeah.
- A horse's legs are fingers.
- You could do some like Tony Iommi like--
- Horse has four fingers.
- Yeah, that's anatomically, it's walking on its fingers.
- It's a four fingered monster.
- Yeah.
- And it's head is a thumb.
- Horses are so scary, they should be a Halloween monster.
- It is crazy.
- Their teeth and eyes are so scary.
There's that one Bloodborne boss that's like a horse guy that's like the scariest thing I've ever seen in my life.
Based off of the size of horses, they should be in the top 10 scariest animals, but people are very comfortable around horses.
I'm afraid of horses specifically because I saw the, what's it called, the...
Oh, it's time to be real?
Don't come up with that.
You just like got a notification like something terrible just happened.
- Yeah, you did look at it.
- I was about to look up a picture of a scary horse
to show you guys and I saw that notification.
- You know what, I'm a pro,
so I'm gonna post late on B-roll.
- It's okay, I'm an amateur.
I don't mind being an amateur.
- You know who didn't do that?
- Yeah, Patrick.
Patrick didn't even care that it had to be real.
- Didn't even look at my phone.
- Well, you did look at your phone, actually.
- I looked at his phone once he did
because I thought that we all got a notification
in the Slack that Patches is sick.
- That would be so hor--
- We have to know about this immediately.
Patches has a cold.
Patches is sick with something bad.
Yeah, what do you think he would get?
He would get something that made him look like this.
Oh, I was talking about I saw the horse scene in The Godfather
too early.
Oh, the head?
Yeah.
I finally--
No, a horse can't do that by itself, though.
I didn't see the--
You'd have to be scared of a horse.
I don't know why.
You'd have to be scared of mobsters and gangsters.
But I just associated horses with scary because of that scene.
That scene isn't even scary.
It's funny.
It is fun now that I've seen The Godfather all the way through.
I think that's funny. I've never seen it before.
Yeah, The Godfather is actually a comedy.
Yeah.
I hate when people do that about movies.
And it's a Christmas movie.
Yeah. When people said that about Phantom Thread,
I said, "Suck my dick."
Yeah.
I never saw Phantom Thread. I don't care.
It was fucking boring as shit.
It was my brother's favorite movie.
Fuck him.
Stupid brother.
Yeah.
I don't think...
I think you better.
You think I care?
Do you honestly think I care?
Some of that guy's movies I like, but some of your guys...
My brother's movies?
The... No, fucking...
You know he's a famous movie maker, right?
Paul Thomas Anderson.
You can't make me care about the Phantom Thread.
That's what, "There Will Be Blood" that shit's awesome.
Yeah, exactly. You gotta put it in there.
The Phantom Thread.
You want me to watch, okay, should I watch "There Will Be Blood"
or "The Phantom Thread"?
Which, by the way,
they only added the Phantom part to make it seem cooler.
It could have been called "Thread".
The Thread.
"There Will Be Blood" you're like the whole time.
"Boogie Nights" I'm like, "Oh, I'm excited. Let's go."
Let's go.
OK, let's go.
OK.
Yeah, yeah.
Liquorice pizza, not a damn--
Punch drunk love?
No, no thank you.
No.
If it was just called Punch--
Yeah.
--I'm in the master of that seat.
Punch drunk.
Drunk punch.
Drunk.
Drunk?
Drunk love punch.
If it was called Bumfights--
Yeah.
--you could get me in the seat.
Then I'm paying a full 20 for that.
I'll watch it on iMax.
That would be so funny to rent out
like the MetroGraf or something and just
screen Bumfights the whole time.
and I see the master, that's another cool one.
- Cool name, cool name.
- Okay, could be a samurai.
- And then I'm like, Magnolia?
Okay, a flower?
No, no.
- No, no.
- No.
- Am I looking like a gardener?
- Yeah.
- No.
- And then it's like, yeah, what else do you direct?
Like, Fight Club, Finding Nemo,
it's like a similar situation.
It's like, I would rather watch Fight Club
than Finding Nemo, it's a cooler name.
- Exactly.
- Fighting Nemo, on the other hand.
- Did he do Fight Club?
- Yeah, and Finding Nemo.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Wow, this guy's the most talented guy.
- Whoa, Resident Evil 2?
- Not the first one though.
- That was Paul W.S. Anderson.
- Really?
- Whoa.
- Paul W. Sanderson?
- Yeah, Paul W.S. Anderson.
- Whoa.
- It is crazy that there's enough Paul Andersons.
- There's two Paul Andersons, it's so funny.
- Hey, even The Matrix too.
- Those are the absolute funniest two directors
to share a first and last name too.
- What else is Paul W.S. Anderson?
- Paul W.S. Anderson did Resident Evil
and like all the video game,
like all those video game movies he did fucking.
He did event horizon he did
He did the death race remake. He did that monster hunter movie that just came out in a bunch of Resident Evil
Yeah, no no he's great. I love him. Yeah, he's a real, but it's just so funny to have a confusion between the guy who directed
fucking
Yeah, that Resident Evil and the guy who did the master. Yeah, that is a very good
There's a big one. I'm blanking on that he did I just because we were talking about Paul
He did that three Musketeers too.
It's Paul W. Anderson, right?
Paul W. S. Anderson.
But then who's the... it's Paul...
Paul Thomas Anderson.
I straight up for a second...
I fully lived in a world in my brain
where they were both named Paul W. Anderson.
Oh, he did... of course, yeah, he did...
I knew I was forgetting the big ones.
He did AVP and he did Mortal Kombat.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, those are the ones that I couldn't think of.
The new Mortal Kombat or the old one?
The old one.
Okay, sick.
I watched that when I was a kid and I played army men.
Yeah.
And I ate my lunch that day too.
Out of my lunch box.
So any other questions about my life?
Nope.
Not a single one.
I think, do you ever think about like how many people write memoirs and you're like,
man, if I wrote a memoir, that'd be probably the worst book ever written.
I honestly, I feel like we're on a crazy wavelength because I genuinely have had the thought a
a few times in the like like probably three to four times in the past month or so of like
it is so funny who writes memoirs and what they call them. I've met people our age who
are like I'm working on a memoir. It's like is this a high school? A memoir? A diary of
a wimpy kid? Is that your fucking memoir? Memoirs are straight up. That's good. That's
right. That's right. That's good. A memoir is straight up money laundering I think. It
has to be. Who fucking cares? Every politician has like a memoir every two years. Yeah exactly
and even though, like even those the most,
the like objectively those are the most famous
or interesting people who could have memoirs
and nobody reads those.
- Yeah.
- Like what, yeah.
- You think anyone's read Pete Buttigieg's?
You think anyone's read Chastin's?
- I have a few times.
- And they're all, it's always the picture of them
looking right into the thing
and it's called Bravely Trying.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Bravely Trying, my fucking weird life
summed up in 120 pages. - The only ones
that are worse than politician ones or actor ones.
- Can you imagine? - Oh, it depends.
No, it's bad.
Tell me who's good.
It's fucking...
I like "Born Standing Up," the Steve Martin one.
That one's good.
All right, I don't have to tell you one then.
You tell me an actor.
That's a comedian and a magician.
I just, I'm against the premise of a memoir.
Of a memoir.
I don't care.
Well, I'd read yours though.
Really?
Yeah, let's write a memoir.
What was the first page of your memoir?
What is it saying, Pat?
I was born fucked up and trying to kill myself.
Wow. Continue.
Because of all the shit.
Okay.
And then I turned 13.
When then what happened?
And then my life got pretty much normal after that.
I have a really good first line from my memoir.
This first line, you open it, first page,
first line, first sentence.
And then everything changed.
Oh, oh shit.
I thought you were just going, and then.
Right, so you just kind of talked as I was talking
and we're just trying to interrupt my cool line
that I came up with.
- No.
- I said and then and you said it in the middle,
you said that's perfect in the middle of me saying then,
so it's almost like--
- Why is there so much static between you two?
- I can't get over his cop, he's a copier.
- Can you squash this cop,
will you let him copy your memoir at least?
- Okay.
- Can I copy your memoir?
- You can copy my memoir.
- Okay.
- But you have to change one thing.
- Okay, I'll change all the names to Cameron.
- Yeah, change all the names to Cameron.
- But none of the other names.
- No, all the other names can stay the same.
- I'll change every name to Cameron,
Even other people's names, even, yeah.
- I think the first line of my memoir would be,
I fucking loved being born.
Being slid out of my slimy mom was one of the best feelings
I've had thus far in my short life.
And then I was thrust into the arms of my father,
that fucking piece of shit.
And he held me tight, and then I realized
I'm okay with him too.
And then the rest of my life was pretty up and down
in certain different parts.
- The rest of my life was smooth sailing.
The rest of my life was not interesting.
- I fucking loved going--
Every single chapter starts with whatever it's about.
I fucking loved third grade.
I loved eating my lunch
and playing with my different recess friends.
- Every chapter also has to end with,
but little did I know.
- But little did I know.
I fucking loved fourth grade.
- But little did I know something big was on its way.
- I read-- - Or something like that.
- I read Tony Hawk's memoir when I was 10.
But it was the kids version.
- They should make memoirs about companies.
'Cause I'd like to read Sony's memoir.
- And I'd like to read Apple's memoir.
- You know whose memoir--
- Not some job, Nintendo.
- You know whose memoir I was forced to read
for my internship was with Bob Iger.
Is it Bob Iger, the Disney guy?
- Yeah, that was Bon Iver.
- And there's a whole part in his memoir--
- There's a hole in his head.
- Where there was a kid who got eaten by an alligator
at one of the Disney parks. - I remember that.
- Yeah, and there's like a whole chapter
devoted to him being like, how could I let this happen?
I was shattered, I couldn't believe this.
And then they have, in the middle,
they have, you know, like in books
that you get from the school library
and they have pictures on the like
different type of paper in the middle.
There was right at the end of that chapter,
there was pictures of him sitting in this like
huge fucking like ornate room on this like ornate bench
and just like doing like a clear photo op
of like his head and his hand.
- Oh my God.
- And it's like Bob Iger after he received the news
of the child being eaten by the alligator.
- Jesus.
- And then the rest of it after that was like,
and then I made fucking money
and we kept making fucking crazy money.
- And then we kept long rolling.
- And then we fucking bought Fox
- And it was fucking insane.
- Yeah, and then we made alligator adventure.
(laughing)
- That's so cool.
- You know where that's never happened
is fucking alligator adventure.
- That's right.
- Myrtle Beach, South Carolina.
- Shout out, Myrtle Beach.
- Buddy, there's a whole lot more alligators
and a whole lot more tasty little kitties walking around.
- Tasty little kitties, huh?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Children?
- I'm not sure you can--
- Well, they're looking for an alligator.
They'd eat that kid.
- Okay, okay.
I thought you were about to say
they were looking like a snack.
I thought that was the words--
- To an alligator, most likely.
Dude, what are you doing?
What?
What are you doing?
An alligator, a cartoon alligator would say,
oh, those tasty little kitties running around this adventure
park.
You can make a cartoon alligator say whatever--
I feel like the cartoon alligator was implied
when I started talking.
You could make a cartoon alligator
say whatever you want it to say.
Yeah, and I'm--
You could make it talk about its anxiety, its depression,
but you immediately made it a pedophile.
We're talking about how tasty the kids are.
But because he ate a kid at the Disney park,
You fucking assholes.
You guys fucking stupid.
Ohhhh.
Yeah, did you not, did you not miss, did you miss that connection?
Yeah.
If you, if I talked like that, you would have no choice but to fucking be my friend.
Cause you'd feel bad for me.
If I sounded like that.
Isn't that true?
Me and Pierce were laughing so hard last night, just do it, just, yeah, I would have loved
to hear that.
Thinking of the most annoying guy ever who just, just the guy who's always like, see,
- C, look, C, like when something they talked about
like a week ago happens, and then be like,
C, oh, oh, C, right?
- Pat does that. - That's me.
- Pat does that.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- We were just talking about him doing that a second ago.
- Oh, we were. - Before we recorded, yeah.
We were. - No, we weren't.
- So now we know that you were secretly
behind Patrick's back.
- Well, it was specifically--
- You were making fun of him saying C.
- The funny part was specifically the hand and voice,
which I don't think you do.
And it's specifically the word C, I think.
- You think he has no hands and no voice?
No, that makes no fucking sense.
Why are you trying to create beef right now?
You're trying to create beef where there ain't none.
Morningstar. Shut up.
Shut the fuck up. He got it in.
Shut the fuck up. He got the line in the show.
That's right. I knew it. I saw that coming from a mile away.
Have I not said it in the show before?
You've never said it on the show. I saw that coming from a mile away.
It's so good. That's gonna be the 50th time you've said that.
Saw it coming from a mile away. Bug.
(laughter)
We need to go back to doing punchlines, man.
(laughing)
- Coming from a mile away, bug.
- Makes, it's perfect.
- Yeah, it's perfect.
- That's a perfect line.
- Oh, just anything with the punchline being bug.
- Yeah.
- That is so, like, even something that made sense.
That would be so funny.
- I flew, then I died, bug.
- Bug.
(laughing)
- I lived for a day.
- I ate shit.
- Bug.
- I took a shit on your food, bug.
- Yeah, well it's like, now I wouldn't say this,
but if I was doing a diss track on Patrick,
I'd be like--
- See, you're creating a beef where there is some--
- No, I said I wouldn't say this.
- Hamburgers, patty.
Yeah, that's right.
(laughing)
- I could be like, Patrick is biting me, bug.
'Cause he's like biting my style,
was what a rapper might say.
But I wouldn't say that, I would say
Patrick is my friend, love.
- Love bug.
- My love bug.
- Patrick is my love bug.
(laughing)
bug. It's just starting a new sentence. It was love bug. Love bug was Herbie. Herbie the love bug.
Did he fuck Lindsay Lohan? No. Well it was like the love, it was called a love bug back in like
the 80s or the 60s. To get rid of the Nazi stuff? Get rid of the Nazi stuff and I think it's because
people would have, it's probably the easiest car to have sex in. Pretty genius way to get rid of
the Nazi stuff. Think about it, that's probably the easiest car to have sex in actually because
It has a elevated roof.
Hummer.
Oh, yeah.
Hummer, huge.
Yeah, Humper.
Yeah.
You can call it the Humper.
Humper.
Humper H2.
My buddy's dad had one of those and he died.
Yeah?
Yes.
Not in the Humper.
In the car?
I don't know.
He got shot.
By the car?
No.
There is a machine gun mounted.
Oh, yeah.
He had a military Hummer.
He was playing with it.
He thought it was a telescope.
He wanted to look at the night sky.
Blew his head off.
- As soon as Iraq started, the Iraq war started popping off,
they were like, we should just sell
all the military vehicles to people.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, it's also funny too that like--
- And put all of these new stuff on it.
- Yeah, as soon as like that war started popping off
on Cybertron, the Autobots were just like,
we're peacing out, we don't even care about the AllSpark.
- Yeah. - We're going to Earth.
- Yeah, we're going to Earth.
- We're gonna become Hummers.
- Yeah, yeah.
- To get inside of the mind of an alien species,
invading would be something else.
- Yeah.
- You know what else I was just thinking about?
I mentioned that guy dying.
I knew a kid, or didn't know a kid,
I knew his parents,
who they had an elevator in their house, right?
- Whoa.
- And he got decapitated by it.
- Oh, you've told this before.
- I'm so scared of that.
- Isn't that so scary?
- You've told that before, 'cause I know.
- I get scared of elevators every time I'm on them.
- Actually, I don't know if he got decapitated,
but I know that he got stuck in it and it killed him.
But I'd like to think--
- That was in final destination.
I'd like to think he got decapitated and his head flew off.
Well that's the number one.
And his head flew off into his mom's arms and she looked at it and went "Ahhhhhh!"
And then it went "Hey mom, I'm okay."
"Hey mom, wait, mom, I think I have a bug bite."
Bug.
I think I got bitten.
I know you told me that story before.
Yeah I definitely have.
Because I...
It just went back into my head.
Every time you mention it I'm like, "Oh yeah, my cousin had an elevator button in his closet
Really? My cousin James growing up had a... his dad was an elevator repairman.
Wait a second, was your cousin a fucking code name kid next door spy?
No, his dad just installed the elevator buttons on his door and we all thought that that was the coolest shit ever.
When I was a kid it was very cool.
And then I was like, okay, so when we press that, your closet's gonna go up and down?
And he's like, no, it's just the panel.
I remember when we moved at a cellar house when I was growing up,
I was grown up I was like I was honestly the one thing I was mad about I was like
But I was gonna basically build a fucking layer
Underneath the house and have a trunk that I click on and it may puts me into a giant tube and shoots me into it
But okay, I guess you guys got to get divorced. Yeah. Yeah, it's annoying as fuck. Yeah, that sucks. Yeah
Yeah, I don't my layer player. Yeah, my layer was like kind of small and shitty
Yeah, do you ever know anybody with a fire ass treehouse something insane? Yeah, actually
Really?
Yeah, they had a zip line.
What?
Yeah.
Damn.
Crazy, right?
What?
OK.
It's like a zip line from the--
They live in camp?
--from the tree house.
No, just from the tree house down to the ground.
We didn't have a tree house.
To the ground house?
Somebody did drill a piece of wood onto a tree
and put a ladder on it.
That's a tree house, man.
The people--
All right, that's a tree house.
We have a tree house.
The family that lived behind my mom's old house,
during COVID, they built an insane tree house.
Yeah, like giant. I would love to do that. It's so crazy. Like it was so loud all the time because they had the construction guys
Building this like huge thing that construction guys bill. It was it was crazy. It was a hired people. I think so
I mean, I don't I don't really I don't know that family
Yeah, it could have been maybe their friends or something, but it wasn't them
And the kids never use it. Oh, it's so funny. I always
Once it's done you're like, yeah. Yeah, they exactly it is. It's so funny
It's like buying a toy for a cat where they were in there for one week after they built it and then never again.
Have I told this before? I went to this...
I was hanging out with these kids that I don't usually hang out with.
And then they were like, "Yeah, we're gonna go smoke."
I was like, "14, we're gonna go smoke weed in this tree house."
By the way, it's like a 20-minute walk away from my house, and it's my friend's old house that got foreclosed on.
Whoa.
So nobody lives there.
Your friend lived in a tree?
Their friend lived in this house,
they got foreclosed on, and then they had this big,
it was like they took a tough shed
and just built a tree around it.
That's cool.
They built a tree around it?
Or they built the, they put the, you know what I mean.
They built it around the tree.
And then,
one of those kids holds up his phone
'cause he's like, "Dude, we should do the circle
"from That '70s Show."
Oh, that's genius.
And then he tried to film us
having a Mad 70s show conversation.
- What do you think they're talking about
in that circle, man?
- What he was talking about in this circle was--
♪ Down the street ♪
- You know what the craziest part about this story
is both of those kids were named Corey and Trevor.
- No.
- Wait, you had four people there?
- There was two kids.
- Two Corys, two Trevors?
- No, no, no, there was two kids
and they were named Corey and Trevor.
And I've told someone that story before.
- That's some of my favorite jokes in Trailer Park Boys
was Corey and Corey and Trevor and Trevor.
I don't know what Trailer Park Boys is.
- He doesn't know. - That's Corey and Trevor.
Where Corey and Trevor is from.
- Oh. - I don't know.
- It's characters, I only watched like three episodes
of that show. - Yeah.
- I think one of the guys-- - This show's a bit
too poverty stricken for someone.
- One of the-- (laughing)
- Hmm. - I'll stick to--
- I'll stick to-- - I'll stick to billions.
- I'll stick to House Boys.
- I don't know who, which one of 'em it is,
but one of the actors who plays Corey or Trevor
is named Michael Jackson.
- Whoa.
And it's just somebody who recently told me that a dog trainer named Michael Jackson.
Really? Yeah.
At a certain point, there's like some names that I think you just can't.
That has to. Yeah.
Michael Jackson is definitely one of them.
I was. You know what I thought of?
I always am trying to think of names like you can't use.
I mean, you kind of can make a Jordan.
You kind of can be named Jesus, but not really Jesus Christ.
Can't be named Adolf Hitler, obviously.
Yeah, I always am trying to think of these.
And I thought of a really good one the other day to add to the list of names.
You cannot give your child anymore because a famous person ruined it.
What is it? Quasimodo.
Yeah, that's pretty much over.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think that that's a pretty good life goal for anyone to have, is like,
"I want to make sure that my name is fucking ruined."
"No one else can have this name."
Yeah, whether good, whether I did too much good or too much bad,
I want to make sure that nobody ever can have this name again and have a normal life.
Yeah.
Michael Jackson is a specific--
Pinocchio.
I know somebody--
That's another one.
I know somebody named Richard Simmons.
Really?
Yeah.
That's--
See, that one, too--
Doesn't go by that, though.
That one, too, you can't even--
Doesn't go by that.
Yeah.
But that is he tell every meets people they go by like your middle name. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, I'd Richard Simmons
He's the he's the man
I know a guy who works this boring ass job and his name is he has shares a name with somebody I can't remember
Michael bolt yeah, yeah Michael Bolton. Yeah, it's another boring ass fucking job, but it's
Destroy the printer or a computer what the hell he loves gangster rap yeah
Ghetto boys, yeah, but that that sounds pretty fucking meanwhile one of his friends neighbors is funny as fuck
Says two girls at the same time like that's what he would do with 1 million 1 million. No, dude, put it in a bank
Barely watch the movie don't even say that
crypto put an index fund man what are you doing bro the fuck is wrong with you dog he's a fool
he's foolish for real put that money in the bank put it in a safe or vault at the very least but
you do want it in a bank forget about the money after that is interest it actually gains interest
every year you fucking it accrues interest yeah yeah yeah and then all of a sudden you
could have a million point one a million point two and do you know how much a million point one
1.2 is that's a lot a
Fraction of a million so much dude, and you want to have what two girls at the same time you realize you could probably do that
For free yeah, if you're a sexy ass guy with long hair, and you're an actor you're famous as actor
Yeah, and you were in this office space. You can definitely do two girls at the same yeah
I'll fucking find you two girls like you do
Like you're gonna do that with a million
So why don't you why don't you give it to me and also listen our good friend?
I'd hate to see what you do with five million.
'Cause I don't wanna see,
are you saying you're gonna do 10 girls in the same outfit?
Meanwhile, there's also this, there's this fuck--
Meanwhile in normalville,
I'll put my money in a bank, please.
Meanwhile, there's this fucking asshole too,
who is basically like,
you need to wear 30 or 40 pieces of flair on your outfit.
I'm like, what the fuck does that mean?
Do you realize this isn't even a real restaurant?
Yeah.
You realize this is a set, you asshole?
And you're Mike Judge.
Yeah.
This doesn't make any damn sense.
You don't work at a restaurant.
You're a millionaire. You made Beavis and Butt-head. Yeah, why are you talking like this asshole?
You're acting like a Butt-head, pal. You're acting like a Beavis.
You're acting like a Beavis. That's another name that's been ruined.
Beavis and Butt-head. You can't even name your kid Beavis anymore. You can do Butt-head but not Beavis.
Sullivan the Frog is over. You can't name your kid that anymore.
Elmer Fudd. Fudd is done. Elmer's okay.
But you could be a glue cow or a Fudd as an Elmer.
Yeah, I guess it's a glue cow. Don't bother me. A glue cow. A glue cow. Oh my god, if you could milk me for glue.
I milk every farm animal. Is that implied by the Elmer that they milk that cow and they give the glue?
Yeah, that's what I always thought the implication was, but I didn't realize it's because it's made out of farm, glue is made out of farm animals.
Where the hell does the super glue come from?
That comes from a chemical plant. That's not even horse stuff.
Let's see, what do we have? Pretty fun stuff coming up this week.
Oh, did you guys see that fucking giant fucking green laser?
Borealis, what's that thing called?
The auroral?
The auroral Borealis.
Northern Lights?
Yeah, I saw something like that, some kind of fucking giant green,
blue shit flying on the street the other day. Did you see that?
I did see that. I didn't see it in the photo.
I saw a picture of it. It was like a green flare almost with a little line.
weird shit. I saw the photo I did. I was asleep. Yeah. It's been a weird couple
days here. There's like, I mean, people are just been acting weird.
Something's up. A guy was throwing up a computer chip the other day on the
street. A computer chip? Yeah, like one of these. Like just a weird little like
thing. You know what I mean? Yeah. It's like a green. He choked it up. Right.
A green chip? Yeah, and he had some slime in his mouth as well. Anyway, I saw, I actually,
where was that? Was that, because I feel like in the same area I might have seen,
I did see something weird. I saw a guy with green eyes.
Green eyes? Not like colored contacts?
No, yeah.
Green eyes, like the wave song?
Yeah, I think it was the wave song he was doing a reference to.
See, all of this stuff, I was asleep through it.
You were asleep?
You were asleep.
Uh-huh.
Did you...
Oh.
Okay.
So I missed out on a lot of that, but I did have a dream.
What was your dream?
Just dark room, low rumbling.
Mm-hmm.
and then an explosion.
Oh, shit.
That I--
I had that dream, too.
I did also have that dream.
Really?
And I also-- I was doing--
I mean, it's Halloween and getting in the mood.
I was doing some tarot cards, and I did
flip over the explosion card.
Oh, shit.
All right.
Well, probably everything's going to be OK.
Yeah.
Come to the Halloween show.
Oh, and we're due--
Oh, we're about to film prank--
Yeah, Juby goes in town.
--and since Juby goes in town, we're
going to film prank guests, too.
We have some funny shit coming out,
and it's going to come out on November 1.
November 1.
Day after Halloween, PrankS2, go to the YouTube channel.
YouTube channel, youtube.com/podcastaboutlists.
Yeah, subscribe.
You gotta watch that video.
It's gonna be really, really good.
PrankS2, coming soon.
We have a plan, I think we're gonna do something
with like a church or something,
ask the guy to pray for it.
It might be pretty funny.
Yeah, priest of paper.
Priest of paper.
Pray, pray, pray.
Could you pray for this paper?
Pray for you.
Yeah, so that's a little spoiler,
but it's gonna be very funny.
That's it, that'll be the first bit.
See, there's a lot more.
And come to the Halloween show the day before.
And yeah, we're pretty excited to see you guys
and see what kind of slutty outfits you wear.
Yep.
All right.
Bye.