*outro music*
Clap if you want.
No you can't because the whole point is there's only one clap.
You can clap.
No you can't clap.
You said you can't clap, asshole.
You can't clap.
It's not me, I mean I'm just trying to be a friend to our poor friend.
I bet you're pissed off.
I'm not pissed off at all.
Oh I bet you're mad.
No the issue is you can't clap once at the beginning.
*imitates clapping*
You can do that all you want.
I can do that too.
(imitates a song)
- You're copying now.
You're completely copying.
- I've been copied before I did though.
- I'm the one who did it first.
- He clapped first.
- I clapped first and I also raised the roof first
and it's all on video now, so.
- Video proof.
- Every single person.
- Well now because you guys clapped,
the video's out of sync so it's impossible
to tell who did it first.
- But then we re-synced it with a (imitates a song)
- That's true.
That is what a lot of audio engineers use to sync.
- Audio engineers use the whoop whoop
to sync up every single song.
- I don't think that those people should be able
to call themselves engineers.
That's a little too--
- They should call themselves songgineers.
- A little too generous, I think, to call them engineers.
- Engineers, yeah, they're not really building anything.
- They're not doing much.
- Yeah.
- They're not building a rail road.
- Yeah, they're not building a rail road.
- Yeah.
- I was stretching in the middle of that.
- Somebody's mic is going nuts.
- Whose mic is going nuts?
- I don't know.
- Probably yours.
- It's probably not mine.
- It's probably yours.
- It's always Patrick's.
- It is always Patrick's.
- Patrick, is your mic close to your phone?
- My phone is in my pocket.
- My phone, don't know where it is.
- It's true, it's gone.
- Somewhere in the office.
- We lost Caleb's phone.
- Tried finding it, didn't do it.
It's also, it's this big, it's very old.
- It's not that big.
- It's this big.
- It's an iPod shuffle or a butterfly.
What's that thing called?
You know.
- Firefly.
- It's a firefly, I can only call my parents
in a Domino's pizza.
There's two buttons and that's it.
Hard to find it.
- It's not that big though.
- I tried to--
- It's huge.
We bought new storage units and then yesterday we found out we what it's hurt or the storage things
This is what nerds call shelves
storage unit
Parental unit, can you fix me a bedtime story from the storage unit that the lights went out yesterday?
You thought all I was the one who solved it. So I
On that wall you're doing a horrible job explaining this story, okay
The where I was going with this yeah, I I texted the super so you're just skipping the story completely
I texted the super to tell her like hey all of the lights went out. Yeah, and then she texted me. Let me
Read this text
Nope that's a different person don't have it pulled up in advance or anything no
Yeah, by all means don't have it pulled up in advance. Yeah, hi
did you get back lights? Read that textual unit Patrick. The Kirkit break to Ter is on
there. Wait, now I actually am interested. Hi did you get back lights? The Kirkit break
to Ter is on there. Just say no. Can I see this message? I said yes when we got them
back. But I realized. It really does say Kirkit. I texted her and then forgot that she has
a jitterbug. Oh she has a jitterbug? Yeah. That's like the old lady version of a firefly?
Oh, man with the big buttons. I want one of those I do too. Yeah, that would be Kirk it break is on to tour
It doesn't seem like that easy to text on one of those no because I bet you using t9
Yeah, what's t9 t9 the old one where you press the keys?
No, that's called t9. I think she's using she's using a system called t1000 where there's a thousand buttons and each has a word
Unfortunately, there was no button for circuit, but there's one there was for Kirk it
(laughing)
- You doing a stretching session?
- Yeah, stretching and--
- I went to town on myself with a Theragun this morning.
- You have a Theragun?
- Yeah, well it's a bootleg one.
It's like a $20 one.
- You went to town on yourself?
- Went to town on yourself with a Theragun?
- Yeah, dude, I sat--
- What kind of moves are you putting on yourself?
- Rose petals up to the bed.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
Does the Theragun approach you
or do you approach the Theragun?
- What do you mean?
Are you splayed out on the bed and a Theragun walks in,
or do you walk in and use the Theragun?
- I pick it up from my nightstand.
- Have you ever just beat the shit out of your balls with it?
- No.
(imitates gun firing)
Haven't yet.
- Do you think you might now?
- I gotta get the...
- The ball sucker attachment.
- Yeah, the ball attachment.
- Yeah.
- I don't have, it's like, it's not an official Theragun,
it's clearly like one of those $20 pneumatic massagers.
That's what you call it.
But I was just like
going crazy with it.
I still feel like shit.
I had it on the highest setting.
I was sitting there just like get
my knees.
Yeah. Taking them out.
I go into town.
My legs still feel like shit.
I haven't skated in two weeks
and then just started trying to like
skate again.
And I feel like an old man.
You know, we do that.
We do about one.
We do. We spend all this time.
We built all this set, knew this whole thing.
Oh my God, aliens have invaded.
You said that we didn't want to.
Two days later, it's just back to, yeah, I've been skating a lot.
I really like it. I really like that.
I think the set shouldn't limit us to talking about our lives with each other.
That's true, to reaching for higher and higher dizzying heights of creativity.
Trying to change the entire medium of podcasting.
Right.
Maybe some skating talk and, oh, I'm sore.
Yeah.
I'm tired, my stomach hurts, maybe we get back into that kind of trifecta that we have.
You're tired, your stomach hurts.
My stomach doesn't hurt today.
It feels completely fine.
That's a whole new combination that we may be discovering.
Yesterday, your stomach hurt a lot.
See, and now he's making us talk about a hurt stomach.
I did not have a stomachache at all yesterday.
Yeah, you did.
Did you hear that?
What is wrong with you?
That was my race.
I hate you.
Oh man.
(laughing)
- Oh man.
- I was watching, okay, what do you know,
what I was doing yesterday, I was watching a movie.
- Yeah.
- And you know how in every disaster movie,
or movie with a disaster in it--
- No, Cameron's watching a movie, what's new?
- They have a--
- I'll pound that out, that's pretty good.
- I actually haven't watched a movie in a while.
- Okay.
- So, it's actually crazy, but the movie's not the point.
You know how in every disaster movie,
or movie with a disaster in it,
they have the one scene where everybody in the city
is in like a big warehouse, or like a sports stadium,
or something, and they're all,
'cause their homes all got destroyed?
Yeah, they're all I really that looks so fun. It looks like the biggest slumber party ever
Yeah, when the light there's a blackout and the lights go and everyone goes
At the same time and they're all sitting there with their ever all your neighbors are there you all they have big boxes of food
They're soldiers. They're giving you food. That does look really doesn't that sound like
After tomorrow when they're in the library and they're like, oh no, we're in the fucking library
It's like the library has sells VHS movies and DVDs and video games now
Yeah, so the library is actually when you're when shit goes south. That's like the number one place you want to be yeah
It's literally like the it's like it's like your fantasy when you're a kid of all your friends living on the same street
Yeah, but they're all living in the same house and all yeah, you get a free food from a cool guy
Yeah, all your friends plus soldiers. Yeah, buddy wanted that when you were a kid exactly
What if all my friends plus soldiers what if soldiers people in hazmat suits? Yeah, right?
I would love to go through one of those hazmat cleaner things. Oh my god
Why is that was that always such a bad thing in the movies?
Yeah, they never show you it's always behind a it's always a silhouette. It's like I bet they're coming on the other end clean
Yeah, you know clean as a whistle. That's got to be fun
It has to be fun sometimes
I bet you it's like it's like when you go to the doctor and you're like they do a physical and you got a hot
Nurse I bet you sometimes get a hot person
Cleaning you and you know the hazmat the window on the hazmat suit, you know
Yeah, you're like and you know some of those hazmat suits the windows down here. They show a little mid riff
Why do they do that? I don't I think it's to make you more
Make you more well cuz you know why cuz if they're cleaning you
They don't want to have to reach between your foreskin or stuff and shit
So it's easier if you get a boner because I can just clean your penis with a single swipe. Mm-hmm. That's true. Yeah, that makes sense
Why are you putting Teletubbies on this maybe like I feel like maybe if I was in that situation
I saw a hot hazmat suited nurse with a bare midriff
It would be like, you know in Cloverfield where they have this sheet and the woman like explodes
I'll be putting a complete different kind of splatter onto the onto that she healed
You'd be putting I'd be putting come I would see a nurse and I would shoot
It would be a silhouette of me kind of like a if you can imagine Austin Powers. Yeah, okay
Yeah similar situation, but in Cloverfield a woman explodes so and me I'm throwing a bucket of oatmeal
Wait, I'm imagining Austin Powers
Jizzing on a woman not on the woman just on the sheet, and it looks like oatmeal. Yeah
Why would it look like oh do you oatmeal type?
Come well in silhouette and silhouette. Okay. Oh, oh, okay. Okay, so the Austin
Yeah, I lost the part. I lost the
The part there you're talking about the silhouette thing. Okay. I know I'm moving fast. Yeah. Yeah, it's some heady stuff
You shouldn't have even said mentioned Cloverfield. You should have just went immediately with Austin Powers. That's true Austin power
Yeah, that's the only they're all when they're all in the big stadium together because of the disaster. Yeah. Yeah, cuz this
That's a better movie. Austin Powers is better than Cloverfield. Oh by a long every single one of them
Hold your roll man that third one sucks. No the third what gold member that one's ass. That's a fine movie the worst one
Yeah, but Cloverfield's a good movie good is better than fine
Cloverfield that's a very compared to Austin Powers
You already said you haven't seen it. I don't even care. I already know the fuck you're being an asshole
Don't make a total weirdo in a dick wise fine
I don't I don't give a crap being a piece of shit take that back. No. Why would I take you?
Yes, you realize you're basically you're killing your killing knowledge and art right now
Yeah, judging art before you even have seen it before you even I don't give a shit read the cover
You're judging a book by its cover. You're judging a DVD by its case. Yeah, that's jewel case. That's right
Doesn't come in a jewel case does it okay? I thought that was you were you were talking okay? Hold up
Never mind. I thought it was like syncing up to your speech
The the plasma ball you thought it was syncing up to my speech like maybe like the Windows Media Player. Yeah, okay
Can we figure out how to do that?
Can we get a window start we're gonna start designing that yeah, we'll do that cuz we can put it right here
That would be way better for thing for right there than whatever is there. I don't even know what's there right now
piece of crap. I hate that thing. What is that thing? I think it might be a fly with a big
head. Oh my god, somebody kill the fly. A green ass bug. A fly just landed on that laptop.
Pat, hit the fly. Oh, it killed him. It killed him instantly. Wow. He's got the top ten movies
of 2022 up. Do you guys see... Do you guys remember Top Gun Maverick? Yeah. Because I
forgot completely that that came out. That ish was sick. Every single movie that's come
out this year I've immediately forgot except for Marcel the shell with shoes on.
That was fire. Do you guys uh you've been seeing what this fucking maniac Kanye West
has been doing? Oh my god yeah. This guy thinks he's designing crazy shoes. He
thinks it's it's okay to wear pink polo. Really? Yeah. Is that true? He thinks that
even guys can wear pink. But he's a gangster. That's what I said. He's doing
gangster rap. He's doing all this stuff where he's like it's okay to be a rapper
and be a nerd and be into technology and dance EDM music.
This guy's sick in the fucking head.
- You know what his biggest crime is?
- I think we should blackball him from the entire industry.
- Yeah, but here's the thing about Kanye West.
I'm gonna say it, he's so dumb,
his sunglasses are obstructing his view.
- That's true. - That's true.
- Lines across them. - That's right.
- Yeah. - He's seeing the wrong.
- His sunglasses have shutters built in.
- And let me tell you-- - Make it make sense.
He's wearing these shutter shades, he's looking out at the world, he's seeing these lines across
his vision, he's seeing, "Oh, there's a line, I think I'm gonna cross that."
Yep.
Holy shit.
That's what goes through his head.
Maybe the lines that he's seeing are obscuring the, because he's meeting all these Jewish
people, he's getting all mad at them.
Yeah.
Maybe the lines are obscuring all the good charitable parts of these people.
Yeah, the good qualities.
Yeah, they're being obscured by these lines in his glasses, and so he's getting the wrong
idea about an entire group of people.
Yeah.
And because other people...
That he's looking at.
people have their good parts in the places where he sees the empty thing you
know so this is a perfect sense what I'm saying yeah yeah I can see that I think
he needs to sit down I think he needs to to just to just read I think he should
I think he needs to close the shutters on those shutter shades yeah and be
completely blind that's right hey you know what I think he is blind he is
already blind you're thinking of Ray Charles racist no you're you think Kanye
West you're mixing up Ray Charles I'm not mixing up Kanye he's he's blind to the
truth so is Ray Charles he's he wasn't blind to the truth I don't think I think
he's still alive I think I think alive yeah he's still alive I think Kanye West
could start the healing by releasing a song called can tell me something
that he's ready to learn that'd be a good I'm ready to sit down and yeah yeah
you can tell me something right now and then the rest of the song is empty
because he's expecting you while you're in the car.
- Yeah, you fill it in.
- Oh, okay, well.
- What you're doing is really fucked up.
- Yeah, I really don't appreciate
how you're treating people in the Jewish community.
I think that you need to take a step back, Kanye West,
and the whole instrumental's playing underneath it.
♪ Ah ♪
That whole song.
- Yeah. - Pretty good idea.
- I thought Zach Galifianakis sang that song for so long.
- 'Cause of his music video.
- I thought that was Zach Galifianakis' song.
- Weird Al never touched that one, right?
Weird Al, Kanye's too--
- Weird Al, Weird Al, the only thing that Kanye--
Kanye. He didn't parody Kanye and that's why he's anti-semitic.
Kanye finds out that Weird Al parodies him and he's just like, "Fuck all you go Slavian people!"
Yeah, yeah. Could have been. Could be that. The only time that Weird Al has ever touched a Kanye
West song was in "Pokorama" on Straight Outta Linwood and he just sings "Gold Digger."
He did a version of Power.
He did.
Did he?
No, he didn't.
Where his head-
You're thinking of Rucka Rucka.
I don't think so.
And it was probably just as bad as what Kanye's saying now.
Kanye and Rucka Rucka doing the song!
They need to clap.
Oh my god, they should wake up.
That would be incredible.
That would be so fucking sick!
Kanye doing the Obama song?
That is so smart.
Oh wait, which Obama song? The Thrift Shop one?
Yeah. Kanye could slide in. Dude, Rucka Rucka Olly had some crazy,
crazy bars. Tell me why that guy hasn't been blackballed from Hollywood.
Yeah! No he hasn't. Yeah, what are you talking about?
He's everywhere these days. Well he put black on his face and sang
some songs. He got black faced from Hollywood. Yeah, he got black faced from YouTube.
YouTube land. Yeah. Which is like Hollywood land.
But I think that, did you see that thing where some guy is trying to, Kanye's fitness trainer
was like, "I'm going to put you in the Santa Sao."
I did see that.
Kanye's fitness trainer is also-
Yeah, the thing where it's like, "You have two options, buddy."
Yeah.
Either you-
How is that guy going to get, is he going to be like, "We're going to go for a run
into that building."
Well, that guy was also Whitney Murphy's fitness trainer.
Holy shit.
And someone else, right?
Mac Miller.
Holy shit.
I don't think he's a fitness trainer. I think he's a secret agent.
Yeah, I think he's fitting this soul into hell.
Yeah, yeah. I mean, and you know, Brittany Murphy, Mac Miller, these were
dangerous minds. Yeah. They were trying to upset the order of the world, the
political order in a huge way. Mac Miller wanted every single person to watch a
movie with the sound off. There are so many people who work on the
sound design and also the musicians who write the music for the score.
And Brittany Murphy, she was...
He hated John Williams so much.
Brittany Murphy, Mac Miller, both were on the verge of a Dr. Sebi documentary coming out.
And they got... they both got killed.
They got got...
This personal trainer.
Yeah, yeah.
And little Pete.
I did what... when I was looking at that, the thing I saw about that personal trainer,
and like there was like a Twitter thread about like how he was the personal trainer for all these celebrities who died.
Yeah.
By the way, not that good at training your people.
No, yeah.
You need to work harder.
But there's one of the top, like,
top of the list is like,
oh boy, this guy's gonna get suicided soon, isn't he?
It's the idea of like, the Clintons like killing
this personal trainer.
I feel like it's more likely
that Kanye gets suicided, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
But nobody would believe that.
That'd probably be the easiest,
most debunkable one of all time, right?
Yeah.
he would ever kill himself? Hell no. He would never kill himself. I don't know, maybe. I
think about it. If he did kill himself, that'd be the craziest concert ever. That would be
actually pretty cool. Because it would be at a concert, he would do what G.G. Allen
set out to do. What was that? G.G. Allen was going to kill himself on Halloween. That guy
was something else. Yeah, I know, he's scary. That guy was just something fucking else. What
kind of a brain thinks of an idea like that? I don't even, sorry, wait, wait, wait, sorry.
I like the shit eating, the racism, and the killing yourself.
Killing yourself is one thing, but what kind of fucking sick, twisted psycho
would do it on Halloween of all the nights in the world?
It's too far.
He couldn't do it because he overdosed on heroin.
Well, maybe somebody tried to stop his plan.
Yeah. Wait, wait, G.G.
Allen's personal trainer. Holy shit.
Yep. Same guy. No way. It was Kanye West.
This guy hates Halloween or loves Christmas and was like,
I can't, can't let that go through. Yeah.
We can't let this is this holiday is already so dark, you know, yeah
This is Halloween
Well, that was actually that same same guy who was trying to keep Halloween from getting too evil was actually
behind the scenes produced nightmare before Christmas because it's
Injecting Christmas into Halloween and bringing fun to Halloween and a happy holiday combining you can you disgusting movie?
Can you pull up a photo of what Kanye's personal trainer looks like?
I think his name is Harvey or Harley.
Kanye-us trainer.
Okay, this is, wait, pull this up right now.
He's a pair of shoes.
So pull, no, put this up.
This is, I guess, this is his trainer.
Can you show everybody the phrase that you Googled for us right now on Patrick Essac?
Can you just go to this other tab and show them?
Zoom in right here.
Kanye-us trainer.
I'm feeling this becoming a compilation pretty quickly of Juvio fucking up.
Okay, so this is a US trainer personal. Okay. Well, he's doing Spanish grammar. Okay. So
we're going this is barked barked.
Okay, you can you can fill this good. Yeah on this out off camera Juvio. You can do your
thing here. It doesn't matter.
If you guys ever get a personal trainer, I feel like that's a I mean, I guess I would
if I needed to if I was a famous celebrity get healthy and I was really rich. Yeah, I
wanted to do that. Or if I needed somebody to drug me and put me in an insane asylum,
I might look for this specific guy.
Yeah, I didn't realize that was part of the job description. You know, you ever in college
and stuff, like you meet people who are like, "Oh yeah." I feel like I would meet so many
people in college who would be like, "Yeah, I want to be like a sports scientist or like
a personal trainer or something."
That's the craziest. That's job.
That's like when you're, when it's the same as people going to school for nursing, I think,
but for guys. And I just can't imagine what is fun about that job until I realized, "Well,
Well, if you get to like fake people's deaths
and fucking kill celebrities.
- That's true, right?
- Yeah.
- With no regard for who you hurt.
- If you can be on the news.
- That's kind of awesome, right?
- Yeah.
Being on the news is kind of the ultimate goal.
- Is there any other reason to become a celebrity doctor?
Like why become a celebrity doctor if you're not?
- You have to look at their penises.
- Look at Dr. Drew.
- Did he kill anyone?
- Yeah.
- Who?
- A lot of people.
Dr. Drew has over prescribed fentanyl
to so many people, I think.
- So people are, so he's writing prescriptions
for normal fentanyl, but he's just given too much of it?
- I don't even know if that's true, what I said.
- I don't think-- - I don't even know
who Dr. Drew is. - I just made that up,
I made that up, and I'm gonna run with it.
- Okay, that's fine. - Yeah, that works for me.
- Dr. Drew is the one from "Love Line," though, right?
Is that the, okay, so Dr. Drew has--
- I love "Line." - He's actually just
given out so much real ass advice to struggling men.
- Yeah, that's not so wrong.
That isn't wrong at all.
He's the love doctor.
That's true.
Have you guys ever thought maybe we could do a love line
kind of thing?
Definitely.
That would be--
Actually, we will.
That's a good idea.
We should get a doctor in here.
(laughing)
We should get like a 103 year old
like Long Island Jewish doctor,
like an old, old man,
and just ask him, get questions about like,
who should text first?
(laughing)
I met my girlfriend on Roblox.
Hey, I have these are yeah, these are some questions that we have from people who sent
in things.
My girl hasn't posted her be real today.
Yesterday, I saw her be real with another guy.
What does this mean?
How do I tear the pussy up?
Just drooling.
He's just completely...
He's just asleep in a turkey sandwich.
What do you do when afterwards, the room stinks?
How do I get the stink out of my chest?
He would know how to do that.
Because you know, if you're living that long,
like the people who live in the 100s,
That's true, the stink gets worse.
They are so accustomed to the...
Like imagine when you beat it up so hard that the room stank,
but then plus you have the old person smell on top of that.
You have the old person smell because like the only thing your body can digest
is like cans of tuna.
Exactly.
cat food? Yeah, yeah. We should put, you know the
cat food? You know the cigarette hole? Is that a stoma? Is that what that's called?
They should put that in old people, all old people, and put one of those air
fresheners just in that hole all the time so whenever they breathe, they
breathe out the air freshener. It smells like chocolate. Yeah, well you could
switch them out. You could customize your grandpa or grandma. Oh my god, I would love to customize my grandpa when he was alive.
If I have to, if I absolutely have to come up with a theory on the old people
smell thing, here's my guess, is that it that is what the world
smelled like when they were coming up.
Okay.
Yeah, right?
Yeah.
They still wear all the same.
The same.
They're using the same ish.
They're using the same ish that they're spraying.
They're wearing the same ish, you know, and so I really
I yeah, this smells like some old ass ish.
Yeah, so I'm thinking, you know, by the time we get.
Jubia looked up, why do old people smell?
I don't want to actually know.
And the answer is too not at all.
Yeah, this is uninteresting.
- Yeah. - Two, not an all.
- I don't wanna hear it. - It's uninteresting.
- Turn it off. - Turn it off.
- Turn it off, it's too boring.
- I think that when we get older,
our grandkids will be like-- - We're gonna smell it, yeah.
- They're gonna walk in. - Why do you smell
like the cool mint vape pod?
- Yeah, exactly, why do you smell like a Juul?
- Yeah. - Why do you smell
like a phone battery? - Wait, pull that video up.
Pull that video up. (laughs)
- Don't pull the video. - No, we don't watch that.
- No, we don't. - Just watch it
on your own time, that's really cool.
- All right. - Yeah.
- There's people who listen to this.
- We have this video thing that we can pull up whenever now.
- Oh, speaking of the video, everyone can see now.
I mean, I know I mentioned the first episode,
I was gonna use my clothes reconstruction machine
to build you guys back your old wardrobes,
'cause we are living in a post-apocalyptic world,
and we're kind of making up stories to amuse ourselves
about our daily lives. - Playing imaginary.
- Yeah, for the past 20-ish minutes.
But how do you guys like, I do,
- You're talking about that ish?
- I like good-ish, but I hate bad-ish.
But how are you guys, did anything strange happen
- My shirt is inside out right now.
- It's inside out, so oh, printed on the inside?
- Yeah.
- That sucks, 'cause I actually, I had a big mishap.
- What happened with you?
- Well, there was, I guess, some kind of glitch
when I was trying to recreate my wardrobe.
And I mean, I'll just, this is all I have left now.
My only shirt. - Jesus Christ, what, are you okay?
Oh, God.
Come on.
- This is the only shirt that I own now.
There was some kind of, I think,
I think maybe a bug flew into the machine
when I was printing my shirts.
- How would a bug cause that to be printing on your shirt?
- Yeah, what kind of printer did you use?
- Well, it's a shirt creator,
kind of like a 3D, 4D printer.
So either a fly or a beetle might have crawled into the,
might have crawled into the printing.
- You know what it seems like,
based on what the shirt says,
it seems like Patrick maybe climbed into the printer.
- Oh, come on, that's not nice to Patrick.
I think it could have been a rat too,
I guess, went in there or something.
or a pervert who escaped from prison.
- Maybe somebody hacked my machine.
I really don't know what happened.
- Are you sure that wasn't just,
wait, do you do any kind of scanning?
Do you have to scan yourself in
for it to make your clothes or anything like that?
- No, I just wanna know how a mouse
getting into your printer would make your shirt
say pervert who escaped from prison.
- Well, I'm not really sure how it happened.
I'm not like an engineer or a tech expert
with these kinds of machines.
I think maybe a switch got flipped on on the back
that changed the-- - Oh, oh, oh.
That originally, I think this--
- Oh, you've got the prisoner printer.
Yeah, I think there was some kind of button I might have inadvertently pressed that made my shirt say this.
Wow.
What I'm really hoping is that, I think if I walk around wearing this shirt, people are going to think it's a band logo, right?
Yeah.
It'll probably be fine, right?
Yeah, well if you put some tour dates on the back.
Well, so you guys think this shirt is bad right now.
So that's why I would love to do that to maybe salvage this shirt, but what is on the back of this shirt is actually far worse.
Let me see what's on the back.
What's on the back?
No.
Tell me that's not.
Come on. Are you fucking serious?
That is disgusting.
Scoot into the middle here.
If you agree with that, you're worse than a pervert who escaped from prison.
If you think that the way Squidward treats Spongebob is A-OK,
that you, I, personally, I think you should go to prison.
- And I didn't even notice that that was on the back
of the shirt until I was wiping my butt
in the mirror this morning.
- Oh, no.
I think that, all right, if we could,
if there's any way that we could maybe tape over
that stuff on the back and make it say, you know,
'cause then it'll just say,
"Pervert who escaped from prison.
"People will assume that's a band."
- Yeah, or a company's logo, my favorite restaurant.
- Yeah, something like that.
And then you put tour dates on the back.
- Yeah.
- Maybe, but, you know.
- Maybe, yeah, like, it would say like--
- House shows only, so you can just,
people's addresses on the back.
- People's, yeah, yeah.
- Dates that you're gonna be there.
- Addresses and dates, that's a good idea.
- Yeah, it's not a bad idea.
I do like that shirt.
- Yeah, I think--
- It's kind of, I'm warming up to it a little bit.
- It's growing on you?
- Yeah, it's pretty good.
- Well, I'm gonna be wearing it every episode
for the rest of time, 'cause the only shirt I have now--
- The only shirt you have right now.
- That's, that's, that's fucked up.
- It's pretty sad.
- Yeah. - It is pretty sad.
- I wish I, I mean--
- I spent every last dollar I had printing this shirt.
Really? You lost all your money?
That's a billion dollar shirt. You can resell that.
Damn, that's a good idea.
Use Grailed. Oh my god.
You get on Grailed and sell that shit. Say Cardi
Playboy Cardi.
True!
Playboy Cardi inspired t-shirt.
(laughter)
Can you just list whatever you want on those websites?
Oh yeah, I have a
Bones Red sticker.
This is on Grailed for $5,000.
red sticker on grail for $300.
Playboy Cardi inspired t-shirt.
Yeah.
It's not a bad idea.
I saw somebody selling the cuffs of a pair of Polar Big Boys for $300.
Why?
It's a funny.
You ever sell anything on Depop?
No.
I think that website and app is da poop.
I think that thing sucks.
I agree.
Come on, pound that out.
That's a good close on there.
- Can we get a fist bump of Caleb?
We got a picture of Caleb fist bumping
somebody who's wearing the shirt?
- Well, joke's on you, 'cause you're fist bumping
somebody who has the word skater on their shirt,
which I would say is a lot more damning.
- There's no way that I can hide.
- Get a close up on me with my shirt.
I support Barack Obama.
(laughing)
- Holy shit, I like that, that was good.
Wait, wait, wait, we can get you to say other things.
- Yeah, I know, wait, wait.
- Let's see, we can destroy all of our enemies right now.
- Yeah, pervert who escaped from prison.
- Read a Brandon Wardell stand-up date right now.
(laughter)
- Pervert who escaped from prison says what?
What?
- Oh shit, you got, fuck!
Shit!
- Yeah, you're double, you got hit twice.
- Fuck, I don't need this right now.
I don't need this right now.
I only have one shirt and I loved all my shirts.
(laughter)
- Oh my god, wait, that is a sick--
- Wait, it stinks $300?
- Yep.
- Oh my god.
- Message this person right now.
Message them and say, "What the fuck is wrong with you?"
Do you think that's--
Continue with your Facebook, yeah.
No, don't click any of those buttons.
Don't click any of those buttons.
No, it's finding Senna for grilled with the business account.
Not a big deal.
We'll just start.
We'll move into that space.
We'll just start selling shirts for grilled.
It's not a bad idea.
Yeah, let's send this guy a message.
Pull up the--
What's your fucking deal?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't send that.
- Hold this up on screen.
- Yeah, we need this on screen.
- Put this up on screen.
- People need to see this.
Okay, so let's construct a message here.
- All right, just here, here's my pitch for a message.
- For the pervert jersey.
- Short and simple, easy message.
Just write.
- Do you really support what this shirt says?
- Write down just $10.
Just $10, nothing else.
- Can you support Barack Obama?
- Oh, that's where that's from.
Barack Obama was a walk-on at Harvard.
- Oh.
That was his jersey, I guess.
- $10, all you said was $10?
- Yeah.
- This is gonna get the conversation moving.
- The vintage Don.
- Let's go back to more of these pervert shirts here.
I think I saw, that is just a white shirt.
- Wait, there's a bunch of pervert.
- There's another vintage 90s pervert jersey for $2,000?
What the hell is this?
- What the hell was pervert?
There's so many of them.
- Pervert 69?
- Was pervert a brand in like Japan or something?
- I mean, it's this shit.
- Japanese brand, yeah, right there.
- Oh my God.
- You're a genius.
- You're a brand genius. - Spins a thing of all time.
- Freak pervert. (laughs)
- $1.34.
- Freak pervert.
- This is how a businessman gets deals moving.
- I would wear that shirt.
That was a cool shirt.
- I would wear any of these shirts
because I don't want to wear this one anymore.
- $900 for a pervert shirt.
Ask them for free.
(laughing)
- Man.
- We'll have to check that out.
- Yeah, wait, what's that red shirt down there?
- We'll have to all get some pervert jerseys.
That says--
- Pervert University, $333 angel number.
- I'm not gonna go to Pervert University.
- All right, I've had--
- Message them and say-- - Yeah, close it.
- Santa could wear this.
- No, 'cause it's red.
Yeah, actually, yeah, you should message.
Santa might be able to wear this.
- Santa might be able to wear this jersey for Christmas.
- Yeah, just write four.
Actually just send the number 4. Just do that. Yeah. Perfect. He does anything we say. He's
a robot. Artificial intelligence. He totally is. Vintage serial killer pervert. We're done.
Whoa, what the hell? Why are you on Trump? Trump3times.com? Do you guys think he's gonna
win? He's got to, right? Is he running again? I think he's definitely gonna run again. Oh,
he's running again. He's definitely gonna run, right? Why would you even run against
them. If you're the other guys on the thing, why would you even run?
Exactly. Here, I'll help him out too.
Who's running against him, Ron DeSantis?
Julio, give me a close up for a second. Donald Trump, I think you're unsavory.
Oh, that sounds about right.
Yeah, so then people can put that on their @ political ads.
I do kind of feel like the skater thing is also a bit, like I can have some sway as well.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Here, you do something.
Well, I don't want to say anything like that.
Say, "I want a skateboard."
All right, I'll say, oh yeah, this one. Yeah, I want to skate right about now.
Okay. All right now Pat you do one. I don't have anything. You have a camo shirt on.
Yeah. I'm a tree! What? You're... I'm a bunch... I'm the woods. That's shit. You're the woods?
That's not... I don't know! I don't have any words! Skater could be... Wait hold on. Okay. Yeah. Remember this is
You're reflecting with your clothes.
Whatever you endorse.
People are going to be like, "A tree said that."
Cut down more of me.
No.
Yeah, you could say that.
Completely wipe me out.
Turn me into toilet paper.
One fly.
I don't really get why we care all that much about the Amazon and shit.
Who gives a fuck?
It's because there's strange beasts that are there.
And if we cut down the trees, it drives them into civilization.
- That is not a nice thing to call those people
who've never seen the computer.
- I'm talking about dinosaurs,
I'm talking about demons and bat-winged apes.
- Bat-winged duck.
- There's apes with bat-wings?
- Yeah, orang-batty, Google, I don't know,
I think that's actually not in the Amazon,
but check this out, just orang, like orangutan,
O-R-A-N-G space B-A-T-I,
and go to Google Images or Bing Images.
- Orange-bati?
- Now go to the images, check this thing out.
Okay.
Holy shit.
Oh, I've seen that.
And this thing is real and I forget where it lives, but it's real.
Yeah, it lives on Searam Island.
It lives in Bushwick.
Indonesia.
I've seen this.
This is an Indonesian animal.
That is just abnormal bad buddy.
Well, that's a, yeah, don't click on that one.
Click on the, one of the actual ones.
This was in my neighborhood last week.
One of the real ones.
Yeah, like the one right to the right of it is one of the real ones.
Yeah, I saw this at Burger King.
You did not, because it lives in Indonesia.
It was visiting.
And so that's how, stuff like this is in the Amazon River basin.
It has wings.
It can go anywhere.
We're cutting down the trees.
they're gonna fly over to us. God knows what they do to us. Did you guys know that
you that in Singapore there's no there's almost no crime? I learned that this week.
Because they're not allowed to chew gum. That was yeah there's all these gum
chewing that makes people criminals. If you like trip if you don't tie your
shoelaces you go to jail for like 20 years. Yeah. So just everything people
just like we'll see money on the ground and be like nah. Yeah. You're not allowed to
pick up money off the ground in Singapore? No you'll go to jail for that.
of what your hands off in your head to pretty cool I'm looking at something
there is crime in Singapore and that is no three sources no there's this year
there have been a slew of ghastly crimes in Singapore I guess I mean I think
we're gonna gasp anyone no this doesn't make any sense I saw a YouTube video
said there's almost no crime there it makes sense there there would be a bunch
of if you weren't allowed to chew gum or eat lollipop that drive you to fucking
murder yeah yeah I said if I went to this country and they said you can't eat
candy yeah I gotta have my five gum gotta have my candy yeah yeah what else
have you what are you guys been up to trying to try to get my body back to
normal yeah even in the gym no come to the gym with me I would I have to I have
I have to start working on my arms because I saw a photo of myself skating and my arms
are so... no one told me my arms were this small.
Do you think you have small arms?
Do you see that?
Give me one of these.
Let me look on the camera.
That's a completely normal sized arm.
Look at my arm.
Look at this though.
Look at my little arm.
What do you mean look at this?
You see that?
You're a weird double jointed kid from school.
Oh fuck you.
- You can't claim you have small arms
and you sit next to me.
It doesn't, even if you do, I just have small arms.
- One time I saw a kid do this thing or whatever,
do like the, yeah, like that when I was in middle school
and I like vomited in my mouth.
It was like the most, I've never seen anyone do that.
- Sometimes the first time you see that it's really bad.
- Double jointed people are like, should be put down.
That is fucking disgusting.
- I'm double jointed.
- You are, I would say, the number one rule,
the number one proof that the rule is
you should be put down
'cause you have too many joints going on.
- I do, it hurts a lot.
I wish I had normal joints.
I wish I had that normal joint smoking on that normal pack.
I should get an opiates.
Have you ever done any kind of opioid?
I think.
You think?
I think you would know.
They're pretty strong.
Yeah.
I think maybe after a surgery when I was a kid.
I think someone put opium in my beer.
Somebody slipped some raw opium right into it.
Yeah, because I threw up when I drank too much of it.
I would love to do the opium tea thing.
Yeah.
We should open an opium den.
I don't think I could ever do a downer though.
I'm not a downers guy.
No?
No.
You hate alcohol.
Beer is not a downer, beer gets me up.
I guess you're right, yeah.
Yeah.
You see what I do on beer.
He does some fucked up shit on beer.
Yeah.
Some really bad stuff.
Yeah, not nice stuff.
Car wheels, he starts eating trash,
He's throwing things at, he's scaring people.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're a scary person on beer.
You are.
'Cause you have no control over yourself and your body.
And you'll fucking do whatever you want.
Yeah.
Yeah, I did--
Very scary on beer.
In Boston, I threw a thing of cheese balls at a cop car.
No.
No way, dude.
Cheese balls?
I took--
So did the cop car blow up?
It was on the 4th of July.
Did it burst into flames?
I took a thing of cheese balls--
How old were you?
Off the ground.
- I'll agree with you. - It's like 19.
- Oh my God. - Damn.
- 19? - And you're drinking?
- You wait, you were drinking as well?
- Yeah.
- Dude, this is one of the craziest
fucking stories I've ever heard.
Did you--
- Tell me you were not having a sleepover beforehand.
- And I was having a sleepover at night.
- Okay, but tell me this much, all right?
Tell me that you were--
- And you're not gonna like whatever this next answer is.
- Tell me you were home by 9 p.m.
- Buddy, it was 10.
- Dude, you were out that late at the witch's hour?
- And I threw a thing of Utz cheese balls--
- What?
A name brand one?
You're wasting money.
- Yep.
- You didn't even get the groceries--
- Tell me you picked them up and ate them afterwards.
- That I took from the ground.
- No.
They could have been somebody.
- They were fucking disgusting probably.
- And I was giving them out to people.
- God, and telling them that they were from the ground.
- For free?
- And for free.
- Charitableness?
Oh.
- Yep.
- And tell me that you weren't--
- And I only had one beer.
- But at least--
- And tell me you didn't murder anybody right after.
- I killed a cop.
Oh my god, that's crazy. But tell me that you weren't living in sin with a woman at the time.
I was.
I'm done.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, here's me with my skater shirt on. I think it's okay for people to move in together
even before they're married. Especially people who love each other. I think that's okay.
Yeah. Hey, okay, now me.
It's okay for...
Okay, now me.
Yeah.
I think it's okay for women to be loose.
Oh yeah, that's good.
I guess yeah, if a pervert who escaped from prison would probably love a loose woman.
I think that having...
Okay, so now the skater's saying this, the guy with the skater shirt, so people can cut
this out of context.
It's fine if you see a woman's belly button, and she shouldn't be in jail for that, honestly.
And then now me.
I should be in jail for what I did when I saw a woman's belly button.
Okay, now go to me.
They printed the Declaration of Independence on what I made.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, because you're the tree.
I don't think the tree thing sells that well because you have a human head.
And then maybe back to me. I wrote the Declaration of Independence.
That is honestly kind of fucking awesome. That is honestly a little bit fucking awesome that
you're a pervert who escaped from prison. Because a lot of those guys, people don't
get that. A lot of Tom Quincy Jones.
Do I look more like a tree now?
Quincy Jones. Oh, you actually do kind of blend in here.
Quincy Jones.
Let me say a tree thing.
Rashida Jones. Tom Adams.
Tom Adams.
Adams, Tom Atkins, these people were kind of perverts. A lot of them had sexual
escapades that they don't tell you about exactly in the fourth grade homework.
Cut to me real quick. I don't think this is the machinist's journal. And it's okay to
print cigarettes onto me. That's true. That's true too. Yeah, that's good to give
cigarettes to kids. Chuck Schumer I'm voting for your ass motherfucker. Chuck Schumer and
your sister Amy? Yeah. My favorite motherfuckas. Rashida Tlaib you're a you're based. I'll
say it. You're a based asshole. You know who's based as hell? Wait. I I I hey hey I support
High fructose corn syrup ism. You know, yeah based Paul Bunyan. Yeah cut down a bunch of my cousins
Okay, I think you're missing the point of this whole thing a little yeah, it's supposed to be political
You're trying to be a little political a little edgy. It's like hey we a
Nancy Pelosi years your fucking husband is straight as an arrow and he's never had any kind of
Homosexual prostitute in his house your big fake breasts. Give me wood
Why would a why would a tree have yet what it would already have wood the whole things would yeah, he would he would
See at least you could have maybe done some wordplay would
All right, you're going back I think as well as maybe yeah, maybe we leave the politics stuff
I'm gonna do something like this where it's like
like and I
Tree that comes before the bill. That's a prequel. Yeah
- Prequel song.
♪ I'm just a tree ♪
♪ Yes I'm only a tree ♪
♪ That turns into paper ♪
♪ And one day I will be a bill ♪
♪ In the ♪
♪ On TV ♪
♪ And then I'll sit in the forest ♪
♪ Where I ♪
♪ And then you can just do the normal song ♪
♪ And it's the same thing pretty much ♪
♪ From there once it's the bill ♪
♪ And then it's basically ♪
♪ It just has an extra verse at the beginning ♪
♪ I'm gonna be a bill someday ♪
And then you do that, yeah.
And maybe beforehand.
And now--
What's before a tree, like just carbon?
Yeah, dirt.
A seed.
♪ I'm just a seed ♪
yes i'm only a seed and i'm sitting in the ground with the weeds
and then what
but i'm gonna be a tree someday. A thread on the shirt got stuck to my hat
i'm sorry. That's sad
i think it's okay to wear hats
damn, hide your true head
i'll take my
i'll take my hat off, i'll show my damn
real head. I can't take my hat off because it's under my headphones. Speaking of Nancy Pelosi, I wish she'd do this
with her blouse. Take off her blouse. She is kind of hot for a really old lady.
She's gotta be in the top 2% for 80 something year olds.
Who else is even in that weight class? Helen Mirren, is she 80?
She's not 80. She's gotta be like 300. She's not 300. Nobody's 300.
Nobody's lived to be 300 except maybe Methuselah. What about
all the people born on Double Day. Double Day? I've never heard of that but I... It's like
Leap Day. It's like Leap Day but you double it. You double the leap or you double the
years that they were born? You double the leap. Well because Leap Day is... So it's
8 years? Yeah. Every 8 years? So you add 8 years to your age. So they would live to be
like 3. So this person is 8 times 300? No it's... Because they only turn... No it would
be divided by 8. They're 300 because it's 8 times... No but they only turn 1 year older
every 8 years. So you go, it's double day, it's just like getting the daily double in
jeopardy, right? So it's like, oh I'm 10 years old, 10 times 8, I'm 80. What? And what does
the day have to do with it? Because that's when they were born, on double day. Which
today is double day. June 20th. Okay, Google people born on June 20th. And it happens because
it's the day before the summer solstice. People born on. We should check our, you guys ever
check your, your, your birthday? Your, what's it called? Your, uh, Nicole Kidman, double
day birthday. Oh, so she's old. She's old. Double day birthday. That makes sense. Errol Flynn
makes sense. I don't even know who that is. I would have figured. Looks old. Brian Wilson.
John Goodman. Double day. See what I mean? All these people look like they could be 300
years old. Martin Lando definitely roots us as an old guy. Olympia Dukakis. That's a 300
year old if I've ever seen one. All right. Well, you've kind of-- Tika Sumter. Chad Atkins.
convinced me okay? Well Robert Rodriguez, Mike Berbiglia, holy shit. Yeah that guy is
not aging well. That is a 300 year old man. We should start doing some Mike
Berbiglia style one-man shows. I've always wanted a one-man show. We could
hit pause right now, move the desk, and then just have us stand in the
middle. If you did a one-man show what would you say it was about? What would
your one-man show be about? Probably just me saying I'm tired. I'm tired of all
of shit. Like what shit would you be tired about? That I have to be here. At the
one-man show? Yeah. You'd be pissed off. I don't want to do this! That's a good angle for a
one-man show. It would be called like, "So I have to do this bullshit."
Yeah. And it opens up. This shit sucks. So I guess I was fucking born on the 4th of July.
It would open like you're fully into it, and then there would be a
moment where all the lights turn on, and you go, "Do I really have to keep doing
this and then that's the audience would you also wouldn't market it like that
that's how you get the top reviews you market it as the fall of sir Doran yeah
and you're dressing in a knight costume yeah and you're doing that and then and
everyone's like I can't wait to see this fantasy one-man show one minute in you
take the night helmet off all the lights go up you say I'm tired I have a stomach
ache and I want to go home they go okay then leave somebody friend the crowd go
to this leave the show yeah don't get me a Red Bull and then come back bring the
green bitch from Wicked. I saw Wicked a couple months ago. Yeah. It was awesome.
That's a, your mom's in town, you got to do something. You gotta see Wicked with
mama. Mama loves Wicked. Yep. Wicked's the one about the witch from the
West. Yep, the West Coast witch. Uh-huh. Yeah. And she's cruising in a six-fo.
Wicked Moms Club. What is this movie? It's a broom I think. The Wicked Moms Club.
See in New England this would have a different meaning. Yeah he's got Wicked
Mom, Wicked Hot. Yeah. Pound that out. No Patrick come on.
Can I have a pound? All right I'll pound that out. Thank you. See in the other
parts of the world wicked does not mean the same thing. Yeah you go
into India and say wicked they're like that's not even a word in our language. Yeah we don't
know. Wicked is not. Wicked. It could be but it could mean something else. Is that your name?
I guess that's your name, Wicked.
Wicked.
Honestly, you're kind of just tricking them into giving you a cool nickname.
You going to China or any of those places?
Wicked would be a cool nickname.
Wicked?
Can my nickname be Wicked?
I don't know what that is.
He looks like Wicked Warwick.
I've never seen somebody miss a fist bump that bad.
You aligned it and then you just went right under it.
You moved your hand.
We have video evidence of you moving your hand.
that we're gonna do a slow motion we'll put in a slow motion right here like
wipeout I'm just an instant replay of you messing that up so bad. Oh we should build a wipeout course.
That's something I would love to do they brought back wipeout you know this?
They brought it back? They brought back wipeout and there's but there's way less
fat people yeah there's way what they were like okay the fat stuff is probably
a little bit too mean. Too much water splashing everywhere we have to hold the
costs a little tighter. Oh my god and there's mermaids on the show?
And Nicole Byer. I love Nicole Byer. Yeah. Nailed it. What a great show. Mm-hmm.
Some people might say that that show... Some people might say that show
ended right before something really good was gonna happen to that show and then
it was a pretty abruptly ended. You can probably talk about that, right? Yeah. I don't know.
I don't remember if I don't think I signed anything. Yeah, fuck 'em then.
Cameron was almost, he was pretty close to being unnailed at one point.
And he made me... I can't believe we've never talked about this.
Somebody reached out to him and was like, "I'm gonna put you unnailed it."
And he made me come over to his house and film him making, gotta be the worst cookies ever.
I think it was brownies.
Brownies. We have to release that.
I'll see if I find it.
We still have it. We have to release it.
It's embarrassing.
- Oh, you're the worst cook ever, dude.
It was crazy.
Or baker, I'm sure you can make a damn good pasta.
- Oh yeah.
- Yeah.
- You can make some pasta agio.
- And then you put icing on the brownies or something.
- Yeah, 'cause it needs to have more components.
It was like, it needs to, you need to show off
that you need to have.
(laughing)
- It was so crazy.
And we were like, yeah, it's a sure thing.
You're gonna be able to nail it.
- It was close.
- What happened, they, you did that, or they got canceled?
- They ghosted me, and then I found out
that they got canceled like immediately after.
pretty sad so but i did that i did the interviews that it was pretty close
that would be a little bit of the interview you did the interview and
because what you nailed it
that's right what was your i'm curious if you had gotten on the show what would
your thing it would have been like in that that we've been like
all that's the other thing uh... is that
uh...
i guess i could talk about it and i remember it
I forgot about that!
So the person who told me that...
*laughter*
Sucks that this never happened to you.
Oh dude, I want to see it.
Yeah, I wish that it's gonna happen someday.
I will be on a cooking show.
You know what'll suck?
They bring back Nailed It!
and then this is on the podcast now.
But it's behind a paywall.
It's fine, they're never...
No one is going to leak this.
The person who reached out to me
then said that I should audition for Nailed It, told me that they were doing a tie-in
for the next season with a bunch of Netflix shows that were coming out with new seasons
at the time of that new season. And one of them was Cobra Kai. And they said that they
have people locked down for a bunch of other times. They have like a The Witcher fan who
would like audition or whatever. And they're like, "But nobody who's auditioned is a fan
of Cobra Kai. So I just had to say in my audition that I'm a huge
fan of Cobra Kai.
And I watched I watched most of Cobra Kai just just in case dude
maybe that was never because that's a thing they would never
ask a question like I'd be like I'm a huge fan of Cobra Kai and
they'd be like, who's your favorite character and I can like
you know, pull up IMDb or whatever. But on the off like I
know there's no on the off universe where they ask like a
plot detail or something, but if it was between... if that was the
thing that stopped me from being on Nailed It, I would kill myself.
Yeah, well that would have been so funny because obviously nobody's a
fan of Cobra Kai. So when they say...
Well, hey, my aunt and uncle, huge, huge fans of Cobra Kai.
Oh my god.
Gigantic Cobra Kai fans.
I didn't even know anybody watched that show, but I think...
Well, I think they might be...
That was almost a year ago now.
If I'm a producer on Nailed It, I'm gonna be grilling the people who are
Cobra Kai specifically. If somebody's like, "Oh, I'm a Riverdale fan," I'll be like, "Yeah,
I'm sure you are." But if somebody's a Cobra Kai fan, I'm gonna be like, "So what's, uh,
so like when they built the new Dojo?" Yeah, yeah. You guys should check out Cobra Kai.
There's some interesting characters. Who do you think is the, who's the best character?
Hawk. Hawk is awesome. He has a mohawk and he turns evil. But he's a nerd at first, and
then they teach him karate, and he turns evil and he gets a giant red mohawk. Alright, well
save some of this for Nailed It, maybe. Yeah. You know, I don't need to know every detail
of Cobra Kai. Dude, Hawk is a complex character. Oh really? Because he gets bullied
because he's a nerd. But then once he gets power, he turns into a demon. I did just remember
something, which is that the last episode of Nailed It I watched was Cobra Kai
themed, or like they had the cast of Cobra Kai on or something. So that
would have been a second push. Maybe I didn't get it in. Maybe they canceled it. No, no, because they didn't
have any fans of Cobra Kai. Oh. Well, this is possible. There was a guy who...
Maybe I just didn't get it.
There was a lady who was hosting it,
and she was one of the people from Cobra Kai,
and then one of the people competing was from Cobra Kai.
And almost all they talked about the entire episode
was Cobra Kai.
So I'm thinking maybe now I just didn't get it,
and then that got canceled after.
When did that come out?
I probably just didn't get it.
I have no idea.
Just search Cobra Kai nailed it,
and you can see what this--
Man, I've been going, I mean, even though I know,
I've always known in my heart that I just didn't get it,
I have just forever been telling myself
that it was just 'cause it got canceled.
Let's see.
And I'm gonna continue believing that.
It came out in 2022.
Oh my god, dude, wait, you got passed up for,
wait, who's this guy?
Who's Gianni DiCenzo, that's the dude.
This is the fucker that, look,
they picked this guy instead of you.
Gianni DiCenzo, he was born in Los Angeles
and resides in the Santa Clarita Valley.
Wait, wait, wait, but he could also be--
No, this is the guy from Cobra Kai.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
He was on the show, he was on Nailed It.
Okay, and there were no other--
Wait, there was no other--
There was no like long-haired, funny guy
who was on it?
(laughing)
himself is on the autism spectrum that makes a lot of sense after watching that
episode I think that the the they wanted
make sure you don't mention Godzilla you got passed up for just a an autistic
guy is closer to the source damn that is so fucked man look at him he's a nerd and
wait wait make that make that face how you gonna pass up this for this fucking
guy well he's on the show yeah fuck him that's right he's on the show but then
they don't I never seen that show but I'll say this much this guy couldn't
make bake a damn cake to save his I don't think I would have been worse and
I would have been worse and funnier yeah you would have been mm-hmm yeah cuz
That's the whole point of the show,
is I'm gonna make the shittiest,
here's how you win that show,
every single cake you make like a realistic piece of shit.
- Yeah. - Right?
And you're like, oh, I'm sorry,
I thought I was making a karate fight.
- Yeah, yeah.
- But it's a giant lie. - I would have actually cried
if they let me on that show.
If the person who reached out to me before
is still listening, I will cry on command
for any cooking show you want.
- All right, let's do a test right now.
- I will make an incredible television--
- Here's your screen test right now, okay.
So cut to Cameron, I'll be one of the judges.
Here, cut to me first.
Cameron, dun dun.
After eating your cake and tasting the different flavors
and eating every single bite of it,
we have decided
to let you go.
Here's a picture of your cake also.
- This is the cake you made us.
- We've decided that you have lost the competition
and have nailed it.
- At first, I fully believed this was real poop.
Do we have this for my brother?
Okay.
- He's autistic.
- Oh, I thought you were the autistic one.
- We both are.
- Okay, both are.
- I just thought I was making something good.
- Okay, so if you thought you were making something good,
I'm not sure why you made a cat litter, cat shit cake.
- I like that kind of cake.
- You like this kind of cake.
This is the kind of cake that you order
when you go to Cold Stone Creamery for your birthday.
- And what kind of parties are you having with this cake?
- This is a housewarming party cake.
people walk in.
I thought it was a post-army party.
Oh, because you have to move a lot?
Yeah, because of the smell.
Because of the smell of the cat-shake cake.
The smell and your dad is in the army, as we've already discussed.
Okay.
And your dad died in the army?
Well, I'm going to have to kindly ask you to leave the kitchen.
And scene.
That's good.
Wow.
Can you imagine?
You have nailed it.
I would love to be on retainer for some television network to be the person who gets eliminated
first in every cooking show.
That would be my dream job.
Yeah, and then you always should stop touching things.
I will beat your ass.
I will beat you down.
I didn't get to touch it last episode.
Okay, that's fine.
That is true.
Stop, you don't need to touch it anymore though.
Cameron can touch it.
Patrick, stop touching it now.
Oh, Caleb can't stop me from doing this anymore.
I can stop you.
I stopped him.
- It was not me, it was very easy.
- I think a great, don't push the set, dude, come on.
Come on.
(laughing)
- I didn't think the whole set would--
- A great thing to do is always to say
that some family member died when you're getting kicked off.
You're like, this is a cake, this is a cake I used to make.
As they're leaving, they're like,
Derek, you have to leave, and he's like,
I was actually doing this for my brother who killed himself
and I'm raising money to stop people
from killing themselves and--
I'm raising money to put a net under the--
But I guess I'll just leave.
I'm raising money to put a net under the Golden Gate Bridge.
A big ass net.
It's so funny that every cooking show
has evolved into it's sob stories.
Nobody anymore does, I just wanna make a new restaurant.
You know what my favorite one that they do
is when they're like, they've been together,
this is a four hour shoot.
They've been together for four hours and they're like,
I'm just gonna miss all my friends that I made here.
And it's like, there's two other people here,
You all live in Los Angeles.
You can keep hanging out with these people.
It's really not a big deal.
- Yeah.
- I wonder if they ever have like a friend meet up
at a bar after the show.
- You think they go to a bar?
- No, definitely not.
They hate each other.
- Maybe the alligator lounge.
- They should make one.
I don't know what that is.
They should make one where they do--
- Oh, we got a message.
(laughing)
- Wait, they hit us back?
- Yeah, $1.5.
- Whoa! - Whoa!
- Okay, yeah, yeah.
Say reply, say deal.
Say deal.
We have to. Deal.
Say yes. Say deal right now.
Hurry. Deal right now.
One point five dollars.
One point five dollars. A great deal.
That's good.
For a freak pervert T-shirt.
Wow.
What was I talking about?
Oh yeah. The contestant thing.
Yeah. I think you have to say somebody
has cancer. Somebody died.
And then you win no matter what.
Yeah. Somebody is going to die
when I go home.
(laughing)
- That's just so sad because--
- After this, it's just so sad that both of my kids
and my wife have to die because I couldn't win.
- Wait, wait, wait, are you saying that they died
and that's why you're here?
- No. - They're going to die.
- I'm going and you know what?
I've never ever tried to kill someone with a car before.
So I guess I'm gonna have to try that out
when I go home on my wife and two kids.
- Okay, I think you're getting confused.
I think what you're saying is that your family has died
and you're doing it for them in support of them
to maybe raise money for their funerals or caskets.
- Hey, we're gonna have to raise a lot of money
after they die because there's gonna be
a lot of destruction of property.
- Yeah. - Is what I'm saying.
- And then they finally usher you off the set
and then the next person gets kicked off
and is like, it's just really sad
that that guy's family has to die
now that I'm getting kicked off the show.
(laughing)
You may have locked him up, but his family's still not safe.
I'm roaming free. - It's just really,
really sad, just loading bullets in a revolver right now.
It's just so sad.
It's so sad that I get to shoot the car that they're going to be in.
It's so sad.
I'm going to have to shoot it in the gas tank so it blows up.
I have a Tommy gun.
I have a Tommy gun like a gangster.
It's just so sad that they didn't run a background check on me at Walmart.
It's honestly just a real big tragedy.
I can't believe it.
I bought a Tommy gun at Walmart.
It just sucks that you guys gave me all these chef's tools.
All these giant fillet knives.
It's so, so, so sad that you can buy that much gunpowder on Amazon.
Just walking out, that would do this thing where they shoot you walking down the hallway
out of the thing.
You're like, "It's so sad," and you're just holding the blast freezer as you walk out.
It's so sad that this thing could fit a human head in it.
It's so sad that you can fit an entire human head in here.
And then it turns on with the door open.
It's so, so sad.
What an awful, awful world.
It's so sad that this is the last episode of this show ever because the hosts are both
going to die.
It's so sad that I studied what the hosts' cars look like and I'm going to follow them
around.
It's so sad that I have your license plates memorized.
I know exactly where you live.
It's so sad that every address has to be public.
It's just sad.
It's so sad that guns.com exists.
Do you guys just look at it?
Is that how much it costs?
And then this is, and then the guy who wins, they're like, what are you going to do now
that you win and he kills himself on TV.
- Oh yeah, yeah.
- And you just wanted the attention.
- Yeah.
- Yippee!
- Most of these people, that's the thing.
- They have a tight shot on his face.
- In his mouth.
(laughing)
- A lot of the people who try to become actors,
they just want attention, right?
- Yeah.
- That's pretty well established.
- The best way to get attention is to hurt yourself.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- The best way to get attention?
Holding your breath.
- If you hold your breath, if you scream,
if you scratch your eyes out and stuff.
People are gonna be like, whoa!
- Especially from your family.
- Yeah, so instead of trying to become an actor,
wasting all your family's money and resources, just walk up to them and start just like scratch
yourself, cut yourself, and like pull your hair out.
Yeah, it's yell.
Yeah.
Say there's a demon in here.
Make your hair look like Angelica's doll.
Maybe give yourself poison that gives you a new disease.
Yeah, stuff like that is a probably good idea.
Stuff like that's always a safe bet.
You could order one of those, you know, you can buy a piece of, I think you can buy a
piece of uranium on Amazon.
Really?
Yeah.
You know what else you can buy is a Home Depot 2x4.
Is that what Angelica's doll looked like on...
days maybe. Yeah. Alright. Regrets? You know what I'd regret having that fucking kid Chuckie
Finster. He's a sissy. He is a total sissy. Chuckie Finster's dad, Bernie Mac. He's a sissy!
I, hey guys, I have never seen, I've never seen the Rugrats. I've never watched the TV
show the Rugrats. You think that's a good idea? No, just because I'm wearing this shirt
I can't say that I will watch that show.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
But, hey guys, I'm a fan of podcasts about Liz.
(laughs)
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Get the fuck out of here.
Alright.
Wait, we can maybe end this one like Cribs.
Okay, we already had an ending for this one.
Oh, we do?
Oh yeah, we have an ad.
We have an ad and then, so like go...
Yeah, here, we'll just keep talking, we'll fade it out.
Subscribe to the YouTube subscribe to the twitch subscribe to everything
Okay, all right bye everybody goodbye today's episode has been sponsored by ABC mouse comm
ABC mouse is high quality curriculum as thousands of learning activities to support your child's education at home
Backed by research and designed in collaboration with nationally recognized childhood education experts,
ABCmouse's supplemental homeschool curriculum includes books, games, puzzles, learning videos, and much, much more.
Go to abcmouse.com today!
[BLANK_AUDIO]