(music)
Now the timer is running.
Oh my fucking god.
The clock is ticking.
Watch out. Uh oh.
Tick, tick, go.
One hour.
You have one hour to write the song of the century.
Write the song of the decade?
And we're going to sit back and listen.
- Song of the decade.
♪ You must have sung back in you long ago ♪
- This is my song I'm writing.
- Okay.
♪ A sentimental fool don't you know ♪
♪ You know, you know, you know ♪
- You know what song?
- No, you gotta work it.
- Was that part of it?
- You gotta have, you need lyrics that are intelligible.
- Yeah, I only know like half,
I only know half the lyrics to what--
- You only know half the song you wrote.
- Yeah, I only know half the lyrics
to what a fool believes the song that I wrote.
- Well, you gotta start at the beginning.
What makes a good, what makes a popular song?
What are the greatest songs?
Melody, lyrics, rhythm, and theming.
Okay, that's for sure true.
That's the number one thing.
Sensuality.
Sensuality is extremely important.
That's the theme though, is sensuality.
You can start with sensuality, and then you need to move into lyrics.
So maybe like, what's sensual?
Like licking and stuff?
Chocolate.
Licking a chocolate off a nipple.
Something dripping.
A Bananas Foster perhaps.
We could sing Bananas Foster all day.
We've got it on the brain.
Bananas Foster?
Bananas Foster.
Do you know what Bananas Foster is?
Bananas, right?
The dessert?
Yes, the dessert.
Bananas Foster.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, I guess I know that.
You'd be looking on a guy name.
We're talking about the famous guy.
I mean, I don't know if this is like, you know, some kind of drink.
Bananas Foster is the name of the R&B singer that's going to sing this song that we write.
Yes, that's correct.
Yes.
Well, they write.
I don't want any part of it, but it is about sensuality.
We're just working as like a Barry Gordy type.
We're involved in the marketing, the production, not the actual music production, but the general,
we're going to make sure that you guys make like no money on it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
streets yeah you got like you guys blackmail right yeah okay I'm gonna I'm
gonna go I'm gonna give it to you I'm gonna make your last I'm serving you
dessert I'm gonna make it last that should be the next and give it a
You gotta make the dessert last.
The dessert gotta last two meals.
I feel like we have a kind of a divide here.
You're almost being sexual.
You're just saying you love food.
I know.
You're saying my banana's faucet.
Yeah, I'm trying to make it, trying to tie it back in.
Well, that's the thing, you don't understand.
Those are, that's called an innuendo.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Also that you gotta make the dessert last two meals,
that would be kind of a hit sexual anthem
maybe in the Great Depression.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That could be really huge for families
that were torn apart by poverty.
Not too sexual in the Great Depression.
Yeah, I imagine it was hard. Yeah, they were very sexual. Yeah, they were nothing else to do
Yeah before the code came in they had Mae West being like why you'd mind you'd suck my titties hard, you know
Yeah, oh, yeah, yeah is the great I grew up in the Great Depression
Is that the one where they had to sell their kid like their yeah, it's meat. That's where that was the that was the Obama
Administration. Oh, I'm thinking of the recession 2009. That's right. Yeah, that's what's up
Have you ever seen that picture where people are like selling horrible photos?
It's like some... I think it's in Europe.
They're like some famine or something is happening and the guy is like
his kids entire body like butchered up on a table. What?
Pretty crazy photo. No. And I like that somebody was like
walking by and was like "huh, photo time, let's take a photo of that."
I did also see that picture on creepypasta.wikia.com.
I think it's real. I think it has to be real.
Why would you fake something like that?
It's too scary. It's way too scary.
The dab was Slenderman.
I guess, yeah. No, I'm not going to fake.
We have Nate and Will with us. What's up guys?
How are you? You're in New York for a little bit for the...
Girl Guide. Open it up for April and Grace.
I'm here for no reason.
- He's just here to hang the hell out.
- Here to chill.
- He's here to hang the hell out.
- Which is more honorable.
- I'm here to be laid back.
- And then we're doing that,
and then I guess we also have to write
the hit song in an hour.
- Yes.
- Or we're gonna--
- Well, the time ticket is 56 minutes.
- Well, the problem is we're now writing
two different songs.
- It's New York City, we're just gonna dump you out
on the streets of Bushwick,
one of these gangs will kill you.
- That's right.
- Oh, man.
- You'll get knockout gamed with a bullet.
Pretty fast around here.
- They're gonna have a famous dance about you.
- Yeah, exactly.
Harlem Shake. Yeah.
The way I die is going to be like a meme.
The white boy wiggles.
I'm going to be like, "Eee!"
It's going to be pretty famous.
I don't know if you guys have heard of Mr.
Freeze either, but he's been on the loose here.
Yeah.
Really?
Yeah, it's been huge.
Pretty bad.
I'm going to get my ice kicked.
Fuck, Slenderman's around, Mr.
Freeze.
Slenderman is not, he's not allowed in New York City, I don't think.
No.
Yeah.
No, he's like in the out...
Because he's too white.
Yeah, that's true.
Which is a crime in New York City now.
Patrick keeps talking about. What's that? Is that a picture of Mr. Freeze?
That's Mr. Freeze in New York.
That's good, yeah.
So, I mean, seriously, Los Angeles, New York, these are two completely different places.
Oh, oh, dude. You know the way they act, like, over there is, like, really different?
They honestly, yeah, they're always, um...
You ever tried to buy a salad in Los Angeles?
No, it's impossible.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here it's only $32.
I do I actually do I have a specific salad memory of Los Angeles was when I got to LA and Caleb was already there
We went to I think we went to a sweet green. Yeah, it was nearby and kills like I want a salad and
They wouldn't let him pay in cash
They make it they charge you double if you don't tell them your astrology
Astrology yeah, I was paying in pennies, but they're rolled at least
Bank with those they honor it yeah, they don't even accept goats over there. No. It's fucked up here
You could said that you could definitely trade a goat to our boy over there on the corner. Oh absolutely
Absolutely, bro. I think that uh you know places should start accepting dowries again
Mmm. I think yeah, I'll still accept like when if you get married you can still get a dowry
There should be like you know what a dowry is get married tomorrow
Okay, it should also be a dowry to like hang out and be roommates as well
Who traditionally gets the dowry
The guy gets the girls
Right. Yeah, you're a girl's husband. So yeah
Women used to be so ugly that they would have to pay the dads have to pay for women
to the woman's dad the woman's dad would pay his dad yeah and say your boy is
your boys laying it down good yeah you got a strong young little ox there mm-hmm
is laying the dick down so he'd say fuck my ugly here's an apple tree and his
daughter and here is yeah it usually was stuff like that it was it was something
that you would you could eat for a little it was it was part of Virginia
Yeah, I given you this parcel in Norfolk
Nano man, oh whatever they're calling it these days. It's an iPhone that still has flappy bird on it
Yeah, or a fucking wedding ring. Yeah
Registry
Fucking things that you get like a wedding ring
or a name in marriage or a hand in marriage.
Bro, I do not want to give away my last name.
That shit's funny.
I will take my wife's name if she's taller than me.
I want to take my wife's first name.
That's the rule?
Mm-hmm.
If she's taller than you, you take her name?
That's the rule.
What if she has a badass name like Stuart?
Or like Godzilla?
Last name Stuart.
If his name was Patrick Stewart, that'd be awesome.
Yeah, that's true.
Damn, Patrick Stewart.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, okay.
If the name--
If the name...
Yo, if you married Patrick Stewart, you'd both be named Patrick Stewart.
Whoa.
That's a mindfuck of a term.
That's a huge mindfuck.
That's wild.
My mind just got fucking hit.
I think if the name was funny enough, I might take it.
What's the...
If my future wife...
Give an example of a name you would take that's funny.
Poop.
Poop, yeah, okay.
Fair enough.
You wouldn't be Patrick Poop.
Cause then you're Patrick Poop and your initials are Pee-Pee.
That's the name Poop, initials Pee-Pee.
See, see, that's why I'd take it.
You can't do that.
Keeping your middle name being Patrick Edward Poop.
(laughter)
- And I've become Pep.
- Pep, Pep, Peepee.
- My name's Patrick Poop, and everyone calls me Pep.
- Yeah, my name, yeah, I'm Patrick.
- I don't know why.
- My full name's Patrick Poop.
Actually, it's Patrick Edward Poop,
but you can call me Pep or Peepee.
- You gotta have a kid, Peepee Junior.
- Or just Mr. Poop.
- I did, I had a guidance counselor in seventh grade
who would call me Peepee.
- That's awesome.
- She called me Peepee because--
- She called you Peepee?
- She called me Peepee because my brother
named Paul and she was she would call me Paul and she's like you both have P names
PP I'm gonna call you PP and she was my best friend
How often were you talking to the guidance counselor?
Well I mean come on
Pretty much every day
Yeah well you didn't log hours in the counselor room
I'd fucking was raised there dude
Yeah dude they let you uh
if you didn't have a belt she would give you suspenders
cause she didn't want kids sagging their pants
I wonder if that's still a problem, because they had like a t-shirt and a pair of pants
that they would make you wear if you sagged your pants.
Yeah.
And they were fucked up.
This just reminded me of an insane tangentially related thing that happened to me yesterday.
Okay.
I was sagging.
I was sagging my pants.
No, I was at my mom's house, and she's a teacher.
She teaches fifth grade, she teaches at a middle school, and she told me, she was like,
the seventh and eighth graders this year are out of control. I was like what do
you mean like what could that possibly mean and she said that at the seventh
and eighth grade dance this year, they they like they were booing the
principal. That's the first thing she said, which I was like, okay, sure,
and then she said they were
just wait. They were they were crowd surfing at the dance and they also they
were breaking windows and they're running around the school and trying to
go in all the locked
last. It's over. Booing is such an adult thing to do. It's like you're at a
Rams game. She even in a separate conversation, like hours later, she was
like, "Oh yeah, also I forgot to tell you, the police had to come to the
reservoir because there were... 'Cause some of the seventh and eighth graders
started a fight club." And I was like, "Oh, that's crazy." And she was like,
"Yeah, there were 70 to 80 of them at the reservoir." And I was like, "What
you talking about? That's bigger than the one in the movie. 70 to 80,
what are you... There's no plus one. She's like, "No, I'm telling you
the truth." She was insistent that it was 70 to 80 kids having a
fight club at the reservoir. The police had to go to the reservoir.
It just sounds like you grew up in the '50s. Yeah. It sounds like you
live in fucking Pleasantville.
70 to 80... Can you imagine 70 to 80 male schoolers doing anything together?
Oh my god, 40 separate kid fights happening at the same time.
They'll get to the reservoir.
She said that they brought furniture to sit on to watch each other fight.
That's so fucking sick, dude.
That's crazy.
That's incredible.
How long was it going on for?
I don't know any more details than what I just told you.
God damn.
I really would love to see video of that.
That has to be on the news, I think.
I know.
I didn't want to look it up because I didn't want it to be spoiled in case it was like,
"Oh, it's actually five kids."
Because I'm sure that's actually what happened.
That definitely is the truth.
If that wasn't a fight club, it was a--
I could see 20 kids.
- 20 kids.
- That would be on national,
if there was a 70 to 80 kid fight club.
- 70 to 80 kids in a fucking reservoir.
- 80 kids.
- How big is your middle school?
'Cause that's a significant portion of the middle school.
- Well, it's even, she said, oh my God,
she said it was--
- Was it boys and girls?
- No, she said, it wasn't even just like random kids.
It was like a subsection of like the chorus class.
Like there's a giant chorus class
and like half of the chorus kids left the class
and went to go have a fight club.
Holy fuck.
That's awesome.
The theater kids have discovered something.
That is so fucking cool.
It's so crazy, dude.
These kids are...
I need it to be real so bad.
Dude, the computer is making children crazy.
They really messed up when they said teachers can't hit kids anymore.
It really did mess up.
Oh, absolutely.
They need...
Is it for self-defense purposes at this point?
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
There's every day some video of a kid shoving paper in a teacher's ear.
why they should arm teachers. They always every time like every couple months
there's a video of like a substitute teacher like breaking down like like she
was the like the lead in like Jacob's Ladder. Yeah. She's like freaking the fuck out.
She's actually in hell. She's in hell because like a child called her like poop butt too many times.
No they're way meaner. They're way meaner. Kids genuinely are actually evil now.
Oh, I've heard some insane stories from my mom. The kids like they just actually
have turned evil because of phones. It's nuts. Like it's just a real life thing
that they're all villains. Yeah, but dude, their podcasts are gonna fuck
you.
So many good stories. Oh my God. Man, I remember we used to follow around our
teacher and just openly call him a pedophile all the time. We recorded him.
Well, that's normal. Kids are doing that forever. That's true. I stabbed my math
teacher in the leg. Yeah.
Yeah, they're telling stories on their podcast of like things they did when they were 12,
but they're being like, remember how awesome that was? Like how good we were at fucking
yeah, how good we were at killing that mailman.
Yeah, we mentally broke down Mrs. Peterson. It was awesome.
Dude, we tied so many women to train tracks. It was nuts.
You really do have to be like, like, it all is going towards like, we'll just have robot
teachers pretty soon. Oh yeah.
And it should be like that because there's no reason why these people who, they should
should have been nurses. I'll say that every single one of these teachers
should have been in nursing school and flunked out at the very least.
McDonald's. They don't need that. These teachers should work at McDonald's.
They should have from the from the first second. Everyone there should be like
like like in Israel like two years required McDonald's service. I'm pretty
impressed. Speaking of mass shootings, I'm pretty impressed that there's not any
mass shootings where the teacher is like snapping. Right. You would think that would happen all the time.
Well, they just teachers snap and like a more adult ways. They don't they don't that's true. They just like the type of
Yeah, mass shooters the type of person who decides to become a teacher their idea of snapping is like I
Called a kid stupid. I called the kid stupid or like I don't know
I just ate like I ate a whole cake in the car. I drove home at 60 miles per hour
Wow a teacher in a car just like putting out cigarettes into her wrist
Yeah, I had a teacher like that. She was pregnant and she was smoking while pregnant
She would always every I think that she was like
I think I would have been a pretty good grooming candidate for her because anytime I went on
Went on field trips all the kids would go on a bus
But me and one other kid would always ride with her in her car and she would yes
She would just like immediately start just like chain smoking. That's blowing it out the window while pregnant
I had a drunk teacher.
Like my first grade teacher was hammered.
All the time?
Yeah, my mom told me that recently.
They're like, yeah, because you didn't know when you were a kid?
I had no idea.
No, I just thought she was like sleepy.
Oh, yeah.
But no, my mom's like, yeah, she left halfway through the year.
It was like a Steve Blues clue situation.
Like, oh, she's actually going, you know, to go take care of her mom.
And it's like, no, she went to fucking rehab, you know?
So you realize that you drove her to that?
Oh, yeah.
I just want to make sure it's completely making fun of her cankles.
entirely your fault.
Oh my god.
Do you want to go to a special amusement park that only teachers can go to?
Wait, you made fun of her?
Isn't cankles like kind of a
side effect of being an alcoholic too?
Is it? Yeah. Maybe.
Like a big red nose too?
It's a pre-existing condition if you're an alcoholic.
That's why Rudolph's nose was so red.
You think he was hit with the sauce?
Fetal alcohol syndrome.
His mom smoked while he was in the womb.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
really snops yeah I remember schnapps was one of the first things I ever drank and
I was the peppermint one oh yeah that's shit is this is dr. right that's dr.
regular Cody we had cut oh yeah last week on on on set we brought through doing
overnight shoots and we brought somebody brought cutties to make cutties and
coffee - that's the little ones yeah yeah taste like mint are you doing England
Yeah, I'm from Rhode Island.
Oh, okay.
So you had the same kind of fucking disgusting...
The McGillicuddy's is what
like literally only the worst
alcoholics buy that comes in a 10 pack.
It's one of those medicines.
Dr. McGillicuddy's apple pie
is like the first time.
If somebody is buying that at the liquor store,
you know they have a problem.
Someone gave me one after a show in Boston, I think.
Oh yeah, someone gave you a shot of the
peppermint one.
peppermint. It's pretty brutal. It's all like the it's the most dangerous liquor
because it doesn't taste like anything but candy. Yeah I don't think it tastes
like candy at all. Well that's the peppermint one but the apple pie
McGillicuddy's, it tastes like liquid candy. I don't believe you. I really don't believe you.
No that's what an alcoholic says about it. I don't think that's true at all.
Also a guy who can who can draw into mind different flavors of
Yeah, somebody after our show in Boston a couple years ago was like, "Hey, try this."
And it took me, I think it took me an hour to work up the courage to drink like a stranger's
liquor.
It's a very Boston thing to do is to just to be randomly, like a water bottle full of
vodka.
It's like a given a villainous potion.
Yeah.
Like an evil elixir that gets passed, those get passed around a lot.
They acted like they were doing me a huge favor.
Yeah.
It's like a fucking 50 cent shot.
That's literally what happened on the movie.
We had somebody who's like, I got we got like we got nice whiskey for like the crew and stuff.
And then fucking this guy Pat from the North Shore came in.
He's like, and I brought Cuddy.
Oh, yeah, dude. Yeah.
Can you buy it outside of New England?
Yeah. Yeah. I miss drinking disgusting shit.
Oh, dude. You ever do like the like I'll have a four loco every six months.
Vodka from like a gas station.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Did you have a Zanka vodka?
Zanka? No, we had Ruby and we had Popov, obviously.
Mine was Popov, yeah.
Yeah, Zanka was a... I thought that it was like a widely New England thing. I knew that it was like...
You're a widely New England thing, come on.
I knew it was produced in New England and then I found out that Zanka is a vodka brand that only exists in my hometown.
What? That's not even possible.
It's made by some...
Is it also like a plastic thing?
It's in a plastic bag.
It's like a craft.
My town is known for artisanal craft
liquors.
Zanka.
Right in a grocery bag. That sounds not that bad.
I mean it is.
I've had, they had pink lemonade
Zanka. There was two Zanka flavors.
It was that one and pink lemonade. And they
taste like gasoline.
I think they only sell it in
or like all New Hampshire liquor stores?
Our regional thing was mostly fake LSD.
We didn't have a lot of regional liquor.
Really?
Yeah, there was a lot of fake LSD that you could buy.
And it was like hometown pride kind of thing.
It's like, "Well, you gotta do it."
It's like McGillicuddy's. It's like, "Well, come on, you gotta do this."
Yeah, we had one.
2-5-I, that's gonna be good for you.
We had a lot of K2.
Oh, yeah.
Floating around.
Oh, yeah. I've accidentally done that before.
Dude, I smoked, so the first time I ever smoked weed was K2.
And then for an entire summer, all me and my friends smoked was K2.
K2 thinking it was real weed. Yeah been there bud. Yeah and so at the end of the
summer finally one of us was like I'm in hell all the time yeah and then
everybody else is like okay yeah this does suck. Yeah yeah. Who even made why
would you make K2 man? It's an evil it's the most evil thing in the world.
It's an incense right? Is it? Or do they have to legally sell it as an
incense? Are they legally? Yeah because we were buying it on like a farmers market.
Yeah legally yeah they sell it as like potpourri. At a farmers market
I got kindly old lady yeah
Growing these potpourri
Put them on your mantle
Immediately just everybody just smoking
Jail
Dude's brain like this size of a fucking quarter. Yeah, it's literally pine cones with bleach on
You're going to like the wrong the wrong booth at the farmers market by accident you're like
you're doing dabs of just like honey I've been having a spoonful of honey every
day yeah yeah how does that change is it doesn't make it smile it's making me fat
yeah there's a bunch of sugar in the poo yeah goddamn bee I really thought I
thought that it was gonna like does it help you like your voice no it's all a
lie no everything about honey is the bees got to be behind all that cuz they
are fucking they're selling a hearty lobby it's like $17 for a thing of honey
now really it's not true if you get like nice honey instead of the like squirt
bear where you drink its body you get like 17 all right I guess that is true
my college roommate had a couple week phase where oh my god favorite snack was
is
- Oh man.
- What the fuck? - And the honey.
(laughing)
- Onion.
- He, so that's obviously a reverse engineered from the name.
- Yeah, that's what I was gonna say.
You have to have the name work backwards.
- You start with the onion, what could that be?
Honey and onion.
- Not even like an attempt to like caramelize it
or anything, just what--
- Not even an attempt to caramelize it.
(laughing)
- Also one of our last days living together,
he ate a tomato like it was an apple.
(laughing)
- That's okay. - I've seen that.
If you do that with a, old ladies like to do that.
My mom does that actually.
I've only seen that happen in Boondock Saints 2.
All Saints Day.
Their dad eats a--
he cuts like-- he scores it and then just puts salt in it
and just eats it straight up.
And I was like, I wonder what that's like.
Did you do it?
I ate it and I was just like, I'm not--
that's not for me.
It's not for me.
Also, the tomato wasn't ripe.
And my dad got really mad because he just put it--
Just wasted a tomato.
You put it back with a bite out of it?
Yeah.
- Oh my God. - That's like 12.
- What the hell's wrong with you?
- 12. - You gotta stop doing
the things that you saw in Boondock Saints 2 All Saints Day.
(laughing)
- I gotta, it's something I haven't grown out of.
- I got all the tattoos that they have.
(laughing)
- That movie makes being Catholic look so sick.
Is it really that cool?
- It's that cool. - It really is.
- Jesus Christ. - We're all like that.
- Yeah. - I need to do that, man.
- We all know the Shepherds We Shall Be speech.
We all have like a gay scene in prison.
Y'all have some cool ass movies, man.
Spotlight's cool, though.
Spotlight's badass, dude.
Is it that awesome to be Catholic?
It's always solving mysteries.
That's cool, man.
Catholicism is like 20% solving mysteries.
That's awesome, dude.
We don't even have a lot of
cool Protestant guys.
They're all like founding fathers who
had syphilis and died. Catholics really
they've been a
finger on the pulse for a long time now.
Yeah
We won the Crusades that's pretty fucking cool. That's it was there a winner declared. I think it was us right no
It's pretty bad what yeah, I think they got owned yeah
Make that clear the they got beat so bad in the Crusades that they said all right
We all of our adults didn't work. Let's send children
And they did it they didn't an army of like kids to go fight in the holy shit those fifth graders
Yeah, yeah kids are also taller now, yeah, yeah, yeah, but the Crusades they yeah, so the Christians lost
They of course yeah, cuz otherwise the they'd all all those countries would be like Catholic now, right?
I feel the first the first crusade
I believe what happened was because there's like six over the course of 200 years and the first crusade I think worked
because they didn't tell the Muslims they didn't tell the
Abbasid Empire or whatever that they were coming and then they just so imagine that you just are hanging out and then one day like
600 9/11 all at once in your in your country. You're like Jesus. What the hell are these guys?
I think we brought 4,000 boats and four of our kings
And they're like oh god so that one worked and then they got Saladin like a hundred years later to come and rally the troops in
He's the kingdom of heaven guy
How do you know all this stuff?
What point did Aragorn come into this?
I've got a beautiful mom
Are you a vlog brother?
Like you're one of those guys who does a crash course for me?
Yeah I do, I do
He does six hours about
You just crush it
a little bit about everything no I just watched Kingdom of Heaven yeah that's it
just the extended version. The salad Dean uh was that Paula Deen's nemesis?
Paula Deen's vegan nemesis. Her Wario yeah. Yeah it could be that. That works.
It's Paula Deen she's made out of salad yeah yeah yeah what would she say she
would say she wouldn't say hey y'all what would she say then she'd say don't eat
there'd be it yeah I have a heart and a brain I don't know why God created I
think she probably going oh she might be sad
I have my life and it's my birthday!
I was born today!
She'd be like, "Hey Morty, I'm Saladin."
No, she'd say, "I'm Saladin."
Not salad!
She might say that to Morty.
I guess if Morty was around, yeah.
You guy wouldn't...asshole.
She wouldn't just say that, but she would say it to Morty.
Is it true that she had a slave-themed wedding?
I think so.
Was she the one who said that?
Yeah, she said the N-word too, right?
Yeah, she did.
That's one thing, but having a slave-themed wedding is so...
I mean, that's definitely two things.
They're also, I think, kind of similar things.
What the hell?
Oh, man.
No, you just searched "slave-themed wedding" on Photoshoot.
We don't need... This is not... By the way, this is bad taste, I'll say.
This is crazy.
I'll be the first to say.
Yeah, this is not good.
This is definitely in bad taste.
I don't think this is glorious.
No, we want to see the Paula Deen slave thing.
Search "Paula Deen wedding."
Didn't Paula Deen, didn't like her... She did like a "I love Lucy" costume.
Oh, yeah, that's...
Oh, that was her wedding. Oh, my God.
Beautiful day there. I love Lucy costume and her like husband was in like brown face or so
Yeah, that's all Desi Arnaz wasn't even like yeah, that's like 10% breath. Yeah, he didn't have to do it
Paula Dean, okay, maybe I'm wrong. Yeah, that doesn't look very I mean, well, I got that can you be a butler?
That's a kind of slave. Yeah. Hey, hey, hey every every every wedding is a slave theme wedding, but it has a husband in it
Yes, sir. All right. Absolutely. I was thinking about at speed butlers and slaves
Alfred has to be a slave right?
No. Yes. He's gotta be a slave.
He just hangs out.
If you were a butler you would not be doing all that shit.
No he just hangs out in the house.
No he's in love with Bruce.
He's got an electric shock collar on or something.
He's just there to play his video games and stuff
and just hang out and eat his food.
They made a TV show about young Alfred.
Yeah. About him being hot and sexy
and a cool sunbite.
It's called Pennyworth.
It's called Pennyworth, the origin of Batman's Butler, and I keep getting ads for it.
And it's like, this is the funniest new show I've ever seen that they're making the show.
That makes no sense.
And it's on season four.
It was like the ad I saw was like season four premiere.
That'd be funny if every Michael Caine movie was a movie about Alfred.
Just had an awesome life, too.
That's got to be the number one Batman character to spin off.
Like, yeah, I want to learn more about Alfred.
right yeah no no cool no cool villains no cool like there are a million cooler gay
old men in Batman yes like Oh the Joker will whoa well okay you're not old are
you how old are you not that old how old are you I'm 50 say admit it admit how
old you are I am 53 I knew it I knew it and and I am gay man I knew it
And you're in Batman. And I'm in Batman. And you work for free. And I work for free.
Yeah. And I'm gonna clean this place spotless after this.
You're gonna figure out that mess over there. No one can see it.
That's some good radio, Pat. Yeah. My bad. We even have video now and you still
fuck it up somehow. You found the one thing in the point 2 that's not on camera. Point out of frame to nothing
interesting at all. I can't even make out what those items are. Yep.
We're just continuing to talk about it. Well, it is an interesting thing
to look at. And if you get items at home, yeah, look up.
Yeah, it's this.
And basically that.
This is what it looks like.
Looks good.
These are all of Cameron's drawings.
These are maybe a little too organized for what's over.
That's more like it.
That's definitely what it looks like.
That tube for sure.
That tube is awesome.
There is a tube right there.
We do have a couple of tubes over there.
This does look like those fucking like, like AI generated, like, mess images.
No, it doesn't. I can tell what everything is.
Yeah.
Well, let's do it.
It does say mess by.
That's a tube, that's a can, that's a mug, that's a bucket, that's crazy frog, that's
a Best Buy bag.
Okay, you know what this looks more like is I Spy.
Oh my god!
I love I Spy.
Yeah, I see a mug there, and you know what else I see?
What?
I see an ugly mug right there.
Oh, where?
Oh, the one on the table?
Where?
Oh, the one on the table.
It isn't pretty.
I don't think it's that ugly.
I mean, it's not that bad.
It has a bunch of coffee words on it.
It says, uh, shit, no, sure, it says cappuccino right there.
And it says mocha, okay coffee, it's a $2 mug we have a damn I take it back. That's a cool
so I
Mean how's the trip been so far? I guess it's been cool. Yeah. Yeah, I'm great. I made it made a Chinese connection
Yeah, that's good. Yeah
That's what I call having Chinese food for lunch. Oh calling him Chinese. Can did you go?
Yeah, mom I did when I went to we had to stop at an Old Navy so they could poop
I had a poop emergency. Yeah, the Old Navy's let you do do in there now?
Yeah, really did the lady is a really nice old they all log the bathroom for me. Yeah. Whoa, they let me then
Let me just baller status. Yeah
Let me in the back room
You're like a social engineer went behind the velvet rope thing. Jesus. Yeah, I got to see where the employees poop
I got a bottle service
Let me into this thing called the fitting room. Yeah
The weirdest bathroom I've ever seen.
One of these new...
Frisbee Fringe.
The mirrors is a little bit weird.
I don't want to watch myself poop on the floor.
They gave me a tag
that said number 2 because I was going to change.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know who the guy doing number 6 is, but he's having fun in there.
And the toilet paper
hook, there's a bunch of shirts.
Oh, well.
They say like a wipe with a shirt.
Well, yeah, it's an old name. They got so many shirts.
- I was on my ass with these guys, so many of them.
- And the window on the door wasn't working.
(laughing)
- So you shit there.
- I shit there and then I ate Chinese food
and then I went to three restaurants to try and get dinner
'cause I'm the most persecuted man in the world.
Bad things have ever happened to me.
- They just didn't have dinner?
- No, no, one of them was closed for--
- We're only doing breakfast right now.
- We're at a dinner, man.
- No, we only have clothes.
(laughing)
You want lunch maybe? Maybe I could get lunch for you, dude.
No, no, no. I have certain codes for each food item. A turkey can only be lunch.
You can't serve me turkey after 4pm. It can only be a lunch.
What do you do on Thanksgiving then?
Um, I don't eat.
That's an early dinner. Thanksgiving dinner is 2 or 3pm.
Late turkey, you're crazy.
We do 2.30 dinner.
You're courageous.
Are you calling the Senate family crazy?
I'm a 2.30 dinner fan.
I am.
Those might be the last words you ever say.
Might as well be the loony bin lock them up. I don't know how you guys cook that turkey with the straightjackets on you fucking crazy nuts
You're a nutcase your mom's a nutcase your dad's a three years old, dude. Oh you have
That is scary yeah old man strength is the scariest thing in the world you the guy they're so strong everywhere, but their back
Uh-huh yeah back. Yeah, pleated kill. Yeah, it's like the you know shadow of Colossus when you fight your dad as a kid
You fought your dad, that's weird man. Yeah, it's really weird. Yeah, you guys have such a great
I feel like most people who they're like I fought my dad. It's because like they have a really bad relationship
No, I have such a good relationship
No, I just like I've tried to fight him one day
But like in my brain of fight every fight I've ever been in the end goal has been like either I kill this guy or
This guy kills me. So when you're going in with your dad, you're not thinking like it wasn't respect kill my dad
And you and he's like he definitely lost respect for you. Yeah, you're sparring like the pink panther and the little guy
Yeah, it's like doing like tricks on each other
Jumping off his back like matrix
I'm like trying to walk walk up his back and fucking a prodigy smack my bitch
I think that's my problem is that I don't think you fought him. I think you wrestled your dad
You are we were we were mad at each other. No, I was very young why not
Probably I was four
Okay, something like that no my dad always was offering he's like, oh you want to fight you wanna fight right now
You know really that's a dad like I think every father
I'm gonna shit relationship with my dad if you try to try to your ass never one if your dad hasn't tried to fight you
you have
You have a bad relationship
Means he sees you as vermin. You're beneath his shoes. Not even worth his knuckles.
Because one day he knows, he knows one day this dude's gonna terrorize me.
Yeah. He's gonna take me down. Yeah. You gotta run up to score before he... I was nothing to him.
He's like why would I, you don't try to fight a mosquito. Yeah, yeah, yeah. You don't swerve out of the way of a bug on the highway.
Yeah, no. You just hit the windshield. You just go. Not too worried about it. Just goo up the fucking windshield, man.
You ever try to fight your dad?
I threw a lamp at him once.
Yeah.
Wow.
Okay.
That was a dare.
Yeah, it was.
It was.
Yeah.
And it didn't go far.
The lamp did not go far.
You had to unplug it first.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Quick to chase back.
Yeah, and I went to school and the next day I was like, "Hey guys, guess what I did?"
And they were like, "What the hell?"
I was one of those evil kids.
Yeah.
But not with the teachers?
Or just...
No, with the teachers.
I was getting like during during the period of my life when I was getting the most savagely bullied
I decided to get revenge on my school
I went to several classrooms that I had classes in
Took the computer mouses they have that little ball inside them you unhook the bottom and I just stole like nine of those
Sick.
Oh man.
And then they found it was me pretty quickly because they were like, "Who's the most insane
student that we have?"
Yeah.
Who's the guy whose pockets are filled with balls that'll clack in?
Who's the juggler?
Who's the one with the big puffy cheeks?
Wait a minute.
Imagine that.
This guy with the big puffy cheeks.
Chipped cheeks walking around.
How autistic do you have to be to be like, "I'm going to do that instead of just kill
everybody."
Yeah.
Thank God.
I'm going to destroy them with their most vulnerable claims.
They'll never think of this one.
They'll never see it coming.
Yeah.
The reason that now there are so many school shooters is they invented trackpads.
You can't do that anymore.
Every single one of them has been like, "I know what I'm gonna do."
"God damn it! This makes me want to shoot a mice!"
Oh, fuck.
Well, you can do the tape thing with laser mice.
What?
You can just put a piece of scotch tape over the laser.
Like a clear piece of tape.
It's not comparable, because you can just take the tape off.
Yeah, but you can take the tape off.
If you have the balls, you have them forever.
You have to order a replacement part.
- Mr. Piva from your cold dead aims.
- Mr. Piva called the IT guy.
I did that to him.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- He got fucking owned.
- We didn't have class for like 20 minutes
because he was like, don't know, my mouse is broken.
- Any way that you could like,
when somebody would like spill a drink in the middle,
like oh fuck, that was good dude.
Just huge delay.
Wait for somebody to come in, nobody's paying attention.
- We set a timer, he had like, it was the science room
and we set a timer on,
Like he had one of those timers. It's like, okay, the lab starts now.
And then like just sets the thing. That's a really loud buzzer.
And then we just set it to like 30 minutes and he didn't notice.
So in the middle of class, the buzzer went off and then he looked at all of us.
We all started laughing and he went, is that funny to you?
It's like, yeah, yeah, it obviously is. But like, that's not, I don't just,
it's just a buzzer. Just like go back to teaching.
It's always so shocking when a teacher for real yells.
My elementary school music teacher was the one who blew up the most.
Like he was like one of those guys that like from like the 1800s
who just didn't die like they just one of the last one of the last guy.
Yeah, he was one of those things was he was like one of those guys.
It was 200 year old.
He's never had like a teacher who's like a vampire. Yeah.
He's always doing those dastardly vampire things going like that.
Yeah, he can only have class at night.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But he would drop books, he would hold a really big textbook and drop it.
That is like a 200 year old.
And then he would scream and yell, and then get this, he was one of the last guys who
would make you stay after and write a sentence 150 times.
He did a Bart?
I had to do that in like 1999.
Oh fuck, you got Barted.
I will not disrupt the class.
Jock?
Or no I had to write it in pen like a hundred and fifty times
And like that you and he ran up a tab on people like like they would do it
He would there be like three of us like every class
Like three of us would do some kind of like infraction and get barred it like every fucking class for elementary school
Music Wow like this is a recorder that you don't know how to yeah, right they make a school shooter, right?
I will not shoot up
Yeah, that's what they do in Guantanamo Bay.
It is basically hypnosis that they're trying to put you under. I think it might work.
I think they're just trying to hurt your hand. Yeah, they just it hurts so bad your hand is like
Yeah, I think how Pablo Picasso felt doing all those paintings. Yeah, his hand was hurting pretty bad. Yeah, that's how Jackson
That's why Jackson Pollock. He just gave up. That's why his shit is so messed up.
Yeah, my brain hurts pretty bad looking at all this Pablo Picasso stuff. I'm like, that's right. Yeah, no thanks.
Make it make sense to me.
Put the eyes in the right place.
Make it a xenomorph.
Try a photo, fucking idiot.
How about a nice house with a flower
and a fence and a smiling dog with a
smile face. That's what I like.
What about an old man with a newspaper?
Art is not for you, Mr.
Picasso, because this bullshit looks like
a whole lot of nothing.
Back in my day, we didn't have these
fricking guys like Picasso.
We had Rothko doing
blue and purple. I love that one. And that was it. You didn't need any fancy expressions,
faces, or squares. I thought Rothko really went downhill when he did blue, purple, and
orange. Yeah, that was a little fruity to me. And white was just lazy. He didn't even
paint that shit. But his red, oh my god. That was fire. That was so swag. That was when he
is
home the entire time. It's just like a giant ramp.
I just feel like, I don't know what it is about a museum. Maybe I have to take an Adderall
before.
I don't think it's about a museum. I would say it's a view more than a museum.
Yeah, I think I have to take an Adderall to go to a museum.
Well, all that shit already happened, dude. You gotta be thinking about the future.
Exactly.
I'm not sucking the piss.
What about like a museum of stuff that's gonna happen?
They already have a museum of the future.
They have that.
Yeah.
Yeah?
Okay, well, I wanna go.
Apple Store.
That's the Apple Store.
That's the museum right there.
That's the museum of the future.
I remember when we were on tour, I skipped the CIA museum or whatever the fuck you guys
went to.
It was the natural history of Smithsonian.
Yeah, I skipped the CIA museum.
It's as tailored for a little kid, like a little boy as possible.
It literally is the little kid museum.
It's dinosaurs.
It's going to be so crazy boring.
You know that dinosaur?
Yeah, he was CIA the whole time.
Too academic for Pat.
So he went and he skated a fountain for about four hours.
We made friends with some cool eight year olds though.
I saw bones, so what'd you do, asshole?
I saw fucking bones.
I saw bones, bones wheels.
This guy was riding bones wheels.
Shut up, Joe.
Is that a skeleton?
No, it's a company.
But the National History Museum was sick.
Yeah.
Yeah, it was so tight.
It was so awesome.
Somebody told me that they were going to tear down Pulaski, so I went.
No.
How do you tear it?
It was flat.
You're going to build something on it?
Yes.
Good.
Well, they're tearing it down because of all that stuff he did in the '70s.
Yeah, I don't even think he skated.
I don't even think he skated. Why did they name it after him?
Guys, I got a skate park.
That space would be much better served by a McDonald's that was open one hour per month.
That would be an upgrade.
That's what Roman Polanski should do, because he wants to come back here.
No, he should just start like, every once in a while, you should be like sitting on a park bench
and be like, "Wow, this is so nice." Right on the plaque.
Yeah, yeah.
Paid for by Roman Polanski, right?
People start being like, "Whoa, that's a nice bench."
Or like you're in the office and it's like, hey, a bunch of free pizzas got delivered.
Yeah.
I'll never tell.
Everyone eating it and trying to put it must be like Robert Polanski or something.
Yeah, there's no way he was.
No way.
And it was a good pizza.
Yeah, just from Blaze.
He got his 20 just plain cheese pizzas from Blaze.
The most expensive way to do a pizza.
Made no sense at all.
TikTok, do you guys know who the new Blaze pizza spokesman is?
Well, he's got a bad past, OK?
Listen up.
The idea of going to Blaze and going through the whole line
and looking at everything, be like, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I think I'm allergic to that.
going all the way back to the weight yet she's a red sauce please no no
sauce no bread and see so they made my they had to make my pizza three times
because I kept putting it in the oven and then it would just explode and I
there for like 45 minutes were you getting TNT on it yes I was getting a
big black bomb yeah I thought it was an olive yeah can I have that olive with a
fuse. It was not good. That fizzing olive was delicious. That's so crazy. I've not been to
Blaze Pizza in probably four years. I've never been to a Blaze Pizza. You got to check it out.
Dude, LeBron is a stakeholder. Yeah. So you're supporting the go. Incredible. Yeah, I got to
support. Guess what? Unlimited toppings. Yeah. Really? And get this too, the pizza, it's not a
big pizza. No. It's a small one that only you can eat. It's a personal pizza. It's only for you.
That's good. I hate sharing. It's like a diet sex. Just you. Just you and that pizza.
That's good dining. It's a good dining alone experience. It is. There was a lot of
people at that Blaze, like a lot of old men in Pasadena eating Blaze pizza by themselves.
There's the Blaze in the in City Place in Boston. That was next to the Halal Guys.
And I, dude, I'm just, I want to go to Halal Guys. I had Halal Guys in Los Angeles when it opened.
horrific yeah it's a food snub yeah yeah I only like escargot okay so when you're
at the Chinese food place what are you ordering I got a cumin lamb spicy
- Isn't a lamb a child animal?
- Yeah. - Yes.
- Okay. - Yes.
- That's so fucked up. - Oh shit.
- Yeah, you wanna think about that one a little more?
- He said, "Give me the youngest one you have."
(laughing)
- What is the youngest food?
- Do you have any like, uh--
- Which food didn't wanna die the worst?
- I would like to have the youngest food,
the youngest meat that you have,
the flesh of the youngest animal,
and also the spice that sounds most like semen.
(laughing)
- What is the animal that had--
- What other combination you could whip up for me here?
- That had the most head up.
You want to--
Who's the most scared?
We don't have spermie duckling anymore,
so you're gonna have to settle for--
That's how I feel about it.
Veal is like a little freaky to me,
just because it's like, dude,
that cow would have made a great,
I mean, it could have been a great man.
That cow could have jumped over the moon.
Could have cured cow cancer.
Yeah, it could have gotten older,
it could have done a lot of stuff.
It is so--
I mean, what happened if they killed the fucking,
the cheese cow?
You know, the one with the little circular one?
Oh, the baby bell lady?
What if they killed her when she was a holly?
Exactly.
Everything would be different.
But then, you know, could have been a cow
sort of Hitler situation.
Maybe you're stopping by doing a veal.
Yeah, it's not that bad of an idea.
It's crazy that the-
I would cook and eat baby Hitler.
Yeah.
I mean, why not?
If you're going to kill him already, you
might as well eat him.
I would put white sauce on baby Hitler at the
Chinese place.
You might as well do whatever you want to the
baby.
You're turning him into poop.
Yeah.
That's mad disrespectful.
That's mad disrespectful to the ultimate hater.
Except his bones, he was kind of the ultimate hater.
I would digest his bones easily.
Yeah, he had very gelatinous bones.
Yeah.
He's germy.
And I just have a good bone stomach.
Okay, I didn't know that about you.
What is it, the Babybel cow lady,
and then there's also that purple one for lactate, I think?
Why are they making all these cows sexy?
Yeah.
They are, that's sexy.
I bet there's gotta be a lot of--
That's a good-ass point.
Yeah, and the male cow from back in the barnyard,
Why is he so sexy?
He's got a big gutters out, dude.
Does an Elmer's glue have a hot cow on it?
True.
An Elmer.
Whoa.
That was just a lady getting milked.
Okay, are you going to pull it up or no?
Oh, God.
Whoa.
See, is it Doja Cat's fault that all these women are dressing up like sexy cows?
I think she opened the Pandora's box.
Yeah.
I guess that makes sense.
Whoa.
That is just a...
Don't show that, but that is a woman just getting completely milked by...
Jesus Christ.
Wait, wait.
Whoa, there's a fucking...
- There's a lady fucking a horse on there.
- Wait, what?
- Bing is on some other stream.
- Yeah, Bing is on some other stream.
- Wait, scroll back up.
- Why are you, you know what it is.
- No, I barely saw it, yeah.
- Scroll up further.
- That is a horse.
- Oh my God.
- Lesbians grab a horse's cock.
No, that's not a horse's cock, that's a cow's udder.
- There's a woman squirting, she's squirting fresh milk
into her pussy.
- Onto.
- Look at the tag on this image, lesbian 3D cock sex.
This is some like German stuff. Yeah, why are Germans so weird about why are they so sexual?
I mean it all comes back to Hitler man. Yeah
Yeah, it's really you can't like the barn doors are gone I think
Before there were there was wearing all those helmets with the spikes on top
Is it because there's girls were sitting on those? Oh, yeah, because what is it cuz Germans are so punctual and they
They get there uptight they need to rely only the other star
There's two stereotypes about Germans and it's like German dungeon porn and like I will show up to your house so early
You have to you have to make your food so fast. I think they show there's one more stereotype about German
Talking about I do you know German in high school there so they the one thing that they taught us is that Germans are
And they're punctual. That's it. I've never heard of
sex dungeon German
That was like the biggest there's a huge running joke on like South Park is that carpet?
Yeah, like the Germans are Germans. Yeah, okay, so that's not so much a stereotype as it is a South Park joke
They look I think that makes sense because the Germans are uptight and there's I think the French are probably foolish shit
Oh, yeah, but they are fucking boring. We're all prudes and
Germans want to the Germans want to make French French people can't have sex with the second they take their clothes off they throw up
French people disgusting
When a when a French person farts it gives you heartburn you smell it
That's nasty who said that
Pat I don't think I've ever known a French person really I knew a French Canadian kid growing up and
He was so annoying that like you know when your mom Canadian
Yeah, but you know when your mom tries to like organize a playdate and then like it's so clear that
You don't like the kid that she has to end up hanging out with him for the whole duration
Yeah of the playdate yeah that happened to him and it kept happening because she kept having to watch wait
So she likes hanging out with the kids.
So your mom has to hang out with the kid.
I don't know that ever that ever happened to me.
Yeah, no, I actually I actually hung out with like the moms and dads like all the
time. That was just because like they we were like boys.
Like I was like chill with them. They didn't do that.
I was mature as a kid.
I remember going over to kids houses and they would think I was so annoying, get
pawned off on their parents and then I'd leave, be like, I'm so mature.
Yeah, I know. I understand what you mean.
I have no time for it.
I think I just took the scenic route explaining all of this.
frivolous I got in an argument with my friend's dad about 9/11 I was like
whoa I was like 11 or 12 years I was like it was an inside job and he was
like no it wasn't George Bush is a beast and then I left and I was like you're
right and then I ended up telling my mom I was like mom George Bush is fucking
awesome yeah for sure I talked to Ed and George Bush is a
is a beast now. His name is Ray. Ray? Ray. That was pretty close. Yeah. What's Ray? Ray Gunn.
Yeah, Ray Gunn. Oh my god. Oh, whoa. What the fuck? Ronald Reagan? Ronald. Fuck. Ron. I
think Ray is a, I think he does delivery for like DHL or something. He's a man. I love
a man in logistics. That's why he crunched the numbers in his head. He was like, it just
makes no sense for it to be an inside job. It's too much money involved and stuff. Logistically,
- It's impossible.
- Okay, I may not be an expert in aeronautics
or architecture or any of the many fields
that enter into this horrible disaster,
but on the logistics side, I can tell you.
- I know logistics, okay?
- Logistically.
- Logistically makes no fucking sense.
- Where'd they come from, Iraq?
It's gonna be like 50 bucks overnight.
Come on.
(laughing)
- It'd be way too expensive.
- Way too expensive.
- Ship 19 guys overnight, come on.
- He also showed me one of my favorite websites
'cause he was like, he was like,
look, let's look at the facts.
And he, that's when--
- It's albino black sheep.
(laughing)
- He pulled up a website called Conservopedia,
which was like, I think just one crazy guy
went and like redid Wikipedia basically,
but with like a conservative slant on every single article.
So you can just put anything in there.
Here it is. - Pull it up.
- You're on-- - Chocolate milk made
from a chocolate cow.
- It's a conservative, family-friendly,
wiki encyclopedia.
click the random button let's see yeah let's see what a random page what's good
on here
the evolution is an agnostic Richard Dawkins said in an interview what's to
prevent us from saying Hitler wasn't right I mean that is a genuinely
difficult question. That's so funny, the first random page. Well that's the only page on
there. Click random page. Click random every time. Let's see random again. Let's get another
random. Conservapedia the trustworthy encyclopedia. This place is so sick. It's right under new
pages. Fourth one down. Yeah. You guys lost. Yeah, now we're, now we're. Notch Germany right
there. Oh my god. Yeah. If you play, you know the Hitler game with Wikipedia where you like.
always just one with the yeah wait you hit random again in a brain there's only
a couple pages
over oh my god there's there's there's life is about two things
happening I think it just gets confused go back to the to the splash page I bet
you can do it from there. I bet it goes straight to Adolf Hitler here.
(laughter)
Okay, we're back to Yugoslavia. Anyway,
it's a great website. I highly recommend you guys check it out. There's some good 9/11 info.
We might have to do a deep dive. I think that, honestly, I don't...
we haven't done that website before? No, we've never talked about it. We're going to have to check out
Conservipedia. I guess I've never showed that before. Well, we already finished it.
- Oh yeah.
- Blew it all in one fucking thing.
- We went stem to stern on that website.
- It's sick dude, it was like one of those ground floor
like 2000s culture war things where it was like
the Bill O'Reilly had all the books that were like,
my grandma gave me one, it was called
like Little Culture Warrior or something.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- It was just telling you like when you go to school
just plug your ears for eight hours.
- I used to have two books that was called
How to Win an Argument Against a Democrat
and How to Win an Argument Against a Republican.
- Whoa, whoa.
Bill Maher like both these guys are sword for hire. I'm cutting through the BS
Yeah, you got to be like I'm your prime to be like a public figure
I should I was or a samurai I would tell people when I was a kid
It was like hey look I really wanted to right now
I if I'd set my life on it I could be the governor of Rhode Island
No, but I would tell people yeah, yeah, I think I could I could probably sure you probably still could I said
I think there's still can't be that hard. No. No. Yeah, you just have to get three people to vote for you
Yeah, you guys have that a governor who's like a mob boss or yeah
Buddy Cianci. Buddy Cianci. Buddy Cianci. Really? Tied. He was very mobbed up and he one time, he went to jail twice.
One time he was, he went to jail for regular like racketeering stuff. The other time he went to jail
because he got his wife's boyfriend that she was cheating on him with and
him and his boy tied him to a chair in his house, and he put out a cigarette on his arm. Damn.
I think he was mayor at the time. That's a people's champ.
thing we have to like a Rob Ford and no no I was gonna say it's the closest thing
we have to a Rob Ford I think America has like 50 we had Andrew Gillum yeah that
was the one who was the Trump recently just called a crackhead the one from
Florida that was found doing some DL behavior yeah he was like taking pictures
of like guys naked on his floor with them yeah he was he was naked on the
Oh right right right. He's a crime to be naked on your own fucking floor.
Yeah that's a really good point. Yeah is it a crime to do meth?
Yeah. I did meth and it was like film or
smoking crack I guess there's a difference here but the dad from ALF
Really? The dad from ALF on like the final season of ALF they had to like work
around him like
being addicted to doing crack and like
What do you mean work around? Like they cut like he couldn't go like one
Well he kept smoking crack with Alf.
We're breaking for crack lunch.
By the way that is like a dream
Pookie sesh is you and Alf.
I mean if you
are on a TV show with like a puppet
for, it's like one of the biggest shows
in the 80's, I think
you get the,
you are granted the right to
hit the Pookie every once in a while. No question.
I mean it's the same thing, I feel like anyone
on Family Matters was allowed
to do that too, once Stefan or Kel
jumped in I mean how do you think got so damn cool man yeah uh-huh that and then
the ones Joey Gladstone start put started pulling out that fucking woodchuck puppet
I think anyone on that set was allowed to just do whatever they like yeah shoot up
heroin in the middle of your scene pulled out though the woodchuck puppet you
remember that fucking thing he went full Mel Gibson beaver the beaver was that
part of me that was part of his act right he was like oh I don't know I lost star
search and he loses star search to Steve Oedekerk, the guy who created all the
thumb movies and like Kung Pao and I why do I remember this episode so well?
Full House. Yeah he loses star search and then like incorporates a woodchuck
puppet into his act. He's going into one of his little holes where he just starts
listing details and doing this. And he was on Dallas. He has every single date
perfectly in his head, but then he gets confused when he goes into a museum.
In his head, just a perfect like one of those like conspiracy pegboards. Yeah. It's
just Twizzlers connected. Yeah, they don't have that shit in museums. They don't have the shit that I know. That's a good idea.
Yeah, be a cool kind of you should open the Steve Otter Kirk
T-rex being like it doesn't clinger and radar
T-rex doesn't is it made out of a thumb? Yeah, I can't pay attention to it. This isn't a
Parody you've never been to a museum that you liked
I went to the I went to the Jim Henson exhibit in
It in the contemporary Jewish Museum
they didn't have a Skeksis anywhere. So you didn't like it? No, I liked it. I love
that you got it right back to puppets when we talked about museums. It was like, first museum, puppet museum.
No, it was the Jewish Museum and they had a puppet exhibit. You were disappointed by the Jewish Museum.
I don't think the Jews should be messing around with puppet imagery.
Caleb is asking, "Pat, are there any museums you liked?" and Pat was like, "Well, I really didn't like the Jewish Museum. Let me just bring that up right away."
I like you with some Nazi dudes protesting the museum, not realizing it's just an office
in Texas.
I like the museum.
I just wish that they had...
They had a big...
They had Agra there.
It's pretty sick.
Yeah, the original Agra.
It sounded very sick.
I think that exhibit sounds very cool.
It was really cool.
I did like it a lot.
He liked it.
Yeah.
You know what I didn't like as a kid was when my cousin refused to go up the escalator at
the Museum of Science.
Why?
because he got afraid of it for no reason.
My cousin was--
That's a scary escalator.
It's not.
He looked at it-- you know what the thing is?
His dad is an elevator repairman.
No.
So I assumed it was some kind of beef.
It was a beef that he had with escalators.
He was like, my dad said they suck.
They're definitely less efficient, I guess,
in an elevator.
I'm losing my shit at you.
I keep saying that's a scary escalator.
It's not that scary.
And then cutting yourself off to die.
Yeah, escalators did kind of Pepsi, elevators, Coca-Cola.
Yeah.
Big elevators came in really...
They had it figured out.
They got it and nailed it.
I like escalators better than elevators.
You're crazy.
I mean, obviously not for like a long...
They're more prone to breakdowns.
That would be cool for like a 40-floor escalator.
You're not stuck in an elevator.
You made it into Dmitri Martin.
You got fucking...
Fuck it. All right, wrap it up.
Well, guys, talk about a closer look.
Oh, yeah.
Nate, you want to do it?
Yes. A Closer Look is our parody investigative history podcast.
You can just say it's real.
It is real. Everyone, if you look, if you look, Closer Look
podcast, the top search result is real.
And then, yeah, it is a yep.
Rose Scott.
That's me.
Rose Scott, NPR.
Seth Meyers' podcast.
Yeah, yeah, we got all weird.
There it is, guys.
Everyone go check this out.
Everyone check this out.
Historically black medical colleges expanding
that's a genomic research.
That's an exciting. But so it's called a closer look, right?
Yeah, not just closer look. So maybe try that.
It's right there. It's right there.
There we go. There it is. Go check this out.
It's called a closer look. Everything in it is real.
The first season is about a world series between a team from lower
Manhattan run by the mob and a team from Nashville run by a Christian cult.
The second season is about the making of the most expensive unfinished movie
ever made a Kevin Costner sci-fi blockbuster called Cyber Cowboys.
We play almost every character all of these guys. These guys all did though, a wonderful.
Very significant roles so you like hearing their voices they're in it a lot.
Hugely significant. We over we got you guys too much that we that makes me
make you work too hard. I remember I recorded I was on vacation and I just
was like I told my cousins I was like guys I have to go into the next room I
have to scream for two hours. I have to do something that I cannot explain for the life of me what this is.
And I came out and they were like, "What the fuck was that?" I was like, "Ah, we'll see in a couple months."
We'll find out. You're gonna see that, you're gonna realize why I was in there throwing up.
And you know what I like is how scary you guys look on this drawing. Yeah, that's crazy.
Really, really scary looking. We're the demons and dark iconography. It's a little too weird for me, but I hope the
audience goes and checks it out. If you like nefarious stuff. I'm not really into weirdo
comedy but if you guys are into that go check out a closer look and it can be
found everywhere you get your podcast by that we mean specifically Apple and
Spotify. The only two where normal people get their podcast. Somebody in New
Orleans said that told me he's like I have this app called a podcast addict can
I get it on there and I'm like no you can get it on Apple podcast because I
I don't have that. What about Spotify? I don't have that either.
Can I listen to it on Listen Zone? Or Brain Fun?
Podcast Addict is the craziest name. I think that's what it was called.
It's called Podcast... Hey man, I can't find your podcast on Podcast Addict.
Dude, it's the number one Android, it says. Number one Android app.
Wow, number one Android app. If you don't tell me where I can get it on Podcast Addict,
I will have to kill you. We really should get on there because people with
uh
Addictions. Yeah, we're not on podcast
We're on a different a closer look I wonder are we on podcast addict let's yeah
Because if we are then you guys have to leave. Yeah
Yeah, why don't we ever plug the show at the end of the episode?
Yeah, go check out podcast about yeah, check it out on podcast addict. Yeah, it's uh, we don't know if it's on there yet
If you try to look up podcast about list on podcast.
If we get a fucking Yugoslavia page, I'll kill myself.
Oh, there we are.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, it's kind of nothing.
Yeah, we got to get on there.
This is an app for lunatics.
They'd be predisposed to like what we do.
All right, well, thank you guys for coming on.
Yeah, dude, thanks for having us.
[KISSING NOISES]
Mwah, mwah, mwah, mwah.
Love you.
Bye.
Mwah.
All right.