*snoring*
*spitting*
Oh, oh hi.
I didn't see you there.
You're looking well.
Hmm.
Would you like to hear a story?
A story about...
Well...
About Thanksgiving.
Let me just light my story candle.
*lighting candle*
Come on now, there you go.
*punch*
In the year number two, the fulgrum sailed the ocean yellow.
They discovered the pool world by accident.
It was a complete whoopsie.
When they got off the ship, there was nobody there.
This new land, which they dubbed Amerikaka, had nobody there at all.
Not even anyone except the pilgrims.
What they did find, though, was a feast most ex-squishy.
The table was set with hundreds of da squishest squishes.
Brown turkey, brown bread, brown mashed potatoes, brown gravy, squishy squashes, and corn.
and lots of corn. The pilgrims tucked in and they drank chocolate milk with fudgy chocolate
syrup and there was delicious brown chocolate ice cream topped with brown chocolate sauce,
brown chocolate sprinkles and brown cherries which were covered in brown stuff. And everything
was served in brown bowls. But then, the pilgrim's tummies started to rumble. You see, dear listener,
this food had been left out for 700 years, and that's why it was brown. The pilgrim started
to poop and pee due to the stomach sickness, yes, in their trousers. But they didn't want
to run to the toilet because they were enjoying the food so much, and also because the toilet
hadn't been invented at all.
Just then, while they were pooping and eating and in such despair, old Ben Stanklin ran over
holding a scrap of white cloth.
"Look at my toy!
Look at my toy!" he exclaimed.
A marigold in my pants was spoopy grabbed from him.
This is what I think of your toy."
And he wrapped it around his poopy ass.
But then, inspiration struck.
"Wait a second," Amerigovispoopyinmypants said.
"My poop is only touching my ass.
Not my knees, feet, or the person sitting next to me's feet."
Then the pilgrims realized that old Ben's toy could be used to hold poop and pee.
And they asked old Ben what his toy was called.
And old Ben accidentally said diaper.
So then all the pilgrims wore diapers while they ate so they could have diarrhea.
And all of this was really quite gross.
This day, November 19th, year number two, was called Stinksgiving.
And they never repeated this tradition, it only happened once.
And it didn't mean or represent anything when it happened, and nobody remembered it
because everybody cared way more about Jesus Christ, who was also called Pea Sauce Crust.
But that's a different story for Christmas.
And the pilgrims all died last year of complications from the COVID-19 vaccine.
But that's also a different story for Christmas.
And that's how diapers came to be.
Yup, and all that was true.
Happy Stinksgiving everyone!
Okay, gonna get up.
Oh no.
Bye bye.
I'm gonna crap right now I think.
Prairie doggin'.
Yeah.
I'm gonna crap right now I think. Prairie doggin'.
Welcome everybody.
Happy Stinksgiving!
Happy Stinksgiving to everybody.
It's so good to be here with you. It honestly does feel so good to be in my friend's company right now
Yeah, yeah with everything crazy. That's been going on in this world the
Democrats lost the house
Wolf mm-hmm. I don't pay attention to stuff like yeah, and it's not really a day for that either
Let's have a check that I'm sorry. I'm sorry that brought up politics. Yep. Thank you
I'm giving dinner because you know there's always that one family member who brings up politics
- 'Cause listen, we can get in a whole fight,
but I don't wanna tear--
- Let's wait 'til later for the poll.
- Let's not be fucking divisive as fuck today.
- That's right.
- I have an idea.
Can we just rub each other's shoulders again real quick?
- Yeah, we can do that really quick.
- And get that mood back.
- Oh man.
- Yeah.
- Oh yeah.
- That is good.
- It feels great.
- That is really good.
- Okay.
- Why don't we do this?
- I feel we should open every episode like this.
- Yeah, that's actually, that does give positive energy
when you do that.
- And my question--
- It's like zip zap zap.
- How many Stinksgivings have we had together
as friends at this point?
- Four.
- This is the fourth one?
- This is the fourth one.
And I also, I would really quick like to congratulate,
I kind of dropped a hint on the previous,
the free episode, I would like to congratulate
everybody who guessed that November 19th,
the world holiday I was referring to,
World Stinksgiving Day.
- And I tip my hat to thee.
- And it's difficult for me to get the hat back on
'cause it's a little too small.
- These are pretty tight, they were pretty expensive hats.
- Yeah, these are all made out of premium silk.
- Money's not a concern on a day like this.
- What is Thanksgiving Day?
- So here-- - I need to know!
- Yeah! - Here comes Little Pierce
asking about the true meaning of Thanksgiving.
- What could it be?
I don't even, this, you guys may have celebrated
four together, but this is my first.
- Well, we actually explained all that in the intro.
- Yeah, in the intro. - Oh.
- Yeah, so you don't-- - So you might--
- You should just go ahead and watch the intro.
- So when it comes out tomorrow, just watch the video.
- Okay. - Just watch it.
- All right, I'll probably catch up on the way here.
- We'll, don't worry, we'll show you the ropes as we go.
Thanksgiving is about a lot of stuff. It's about friends and family, but it's also
about some damn good down-country, low-country home cooking.
Yep. Right? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh wait, yeah, I prepared a whole dish and put it in a
diaper. Yeah. Of course I know it's Thanksgiving Day. Yeah, if we get, Jibrio,
can we get a shot of just our, basically the... The cornucopia here? Yeah, the corn, so there's a
cornucopia here. These are all of our meals that we're gonna be partaking in
today. I mean, I'm, I'm about, I'm famished. I'm famished. Let's dig in, no?
you know what and I'm breaking I'm breaking a 22-hour fast okay just to
just to have this okay this something that something green is already
hungry well so good I'm so excited to eat this. It looks so amazing. It really does look so good.
This one is, there's like a, this is like a, there's a yellowing. Oh this is the, I think this is Caleb's guacamole.
It is my guacamole, my famous guacamole. Okay well it's a perfect little appetizer I think, it's some chips.
Okay. Let's find the chips in here. Well here, first of all, open up the guacamole and show everybody.
Let's open that up. Yeah, let's open the guacamole. You can go ahead and show them, Pierce.
Can you get that thing open?
Once you put the Velcro on those things, it's
kind of hard to get them back open. Oh, no, it's opening up. Here we go.
Alright, let's see the undiapering.
Oh, yeah! That looks so good!
Guacamole. All we need with that is chips. Well, I got great news for you, then.
because right here I got some chips.
Oh wow!
(laughing)
So let's dig in!
This is great, yeah.
Someone pass me a chip.
I wish I wasn't allergic to avocado.
Because that looks
simply delectable.
That's going to be divine.
really divine some some chips and guacamole for me put the chips put the
chips from the chip diaper on to the guacamole diaper I'm just I'm gonna I'm
gonna have I'm gonna take a sip of this hell guacamole puts me in a little bit
of a modelo mood there's something about guacamole yeah it is borderline
Yeah, he was he was employing a pun
We employ so what's everybody's line favorite part of Stinksgiving is it me it has to be the food
Have you ever had I mean so obviously this is more of a friend stinking
But when you were growing up, and you were celebrating Stinksgiving with your family
What was like that one dish that just made you go?
Actually
I immediately had an answer to this.
Okay.
And it's actually the meal that I brought, or the part of the meal that I brought, for
me, it's the cranberry sauce.
The cranberry sauce.
Oh wow.
Uh huh.
Oh, so how about you pop open that cranberry sauce, show these lucky viewers what you have.
I didn't think I got to see this.
You didn't see the cranberry sauce?
Before it got taped up.
Nope.
Oh, just, you're in for a treat, buddy.
And you're gonna be in for a...
Alright, let's open that up.
Yep.
Real gourmet...
that up hold that up hold that oh and that's so good that oh no cranberry
sauce well that's not a problem because it's gonna it's not like we're gonna eat
the cranberry sauce by itself anyway right yeah so let's just let's let that
simmer not eat it yeah I don't know why we opened it so early I mean I feel like
Patrick opened it he's talking about how much he likes it he has to take a bite
of it. Yeah. Okay. And it tastes what? We should have brought your bib for us. I think it tastes amazing!
Wait, you just mentioned we should have brought bibs. It's funny that you say that
because I do have some bibs. Oh yeah? Give me a moment. Yeah. Here, hold on. While you're
away, I need to inquire further about why is it called Stinksgiving?
While you're getting those bibs, can you get me a damn napkin? Because I got some
I got some cranberry sauce all over my hand.
I think you don't know what a bib is for.
The smells that I'm experiencing right now are kind of pleasant.
I mean, it's mostly like...
Oh, just hey, listen, pal.
I know it's your first Thanksgiving, but what I will tell you is stinky things come to those
who wait.
Okay.
Classic Thanksgiving tradition.
Everybody eats this delicious, good smelling food and it's a celebration of how the body
can turn that into something so foul.
Something unbelievable.
- Okay, so it's sort of like a chrysalis, right?
- Much like a chrysalis.
- It's almost exactly like a chrysalis.
- No, that's a different holiday.
I'm just playing. - Oh, chrysalis.
Oh my goodness.
Okay, and then I'm noticing that diapers are a part of this.
What does this have to do with friendship?
- Well, who's surrounding you?
You're left and you're right, and you're more left.
- Oh, that's right.
You guys kind of catch all of my crap.
Crap yeah, exactly yeah, you guys take shit from me in a way
You know way yeah, but we also give food to you and speaking of food. I mean look at this. Oh the main event
This delicious bird umptuous
Lift that up lift that up show the camera Stinks giving turkey
prepared in the natural in its natural casing here and
Here show the head yeah here hold it
The head is right here. Can you go back to the... The head is in here. So the head used to be right there.
Right. Oh! Hey, hey, can you hold that over this way? I'm just... I mean, I can't help myself right now.
I want to get in there too.
Everyone take a bite.
Yeah, let me grab some of that.
Oh my god!
Oh! This is what it's all about.
It slides right out of the diaper!
Go ahead, guys.
Oh my god, look at that.
There's plenty enough for everybody.
The way seasoned food brings friends together.
Look at the brown on that.
God, the brown.
And what is this I detect here?
A spot of rosemary?
A hint of spice?
It's a little bit spicy for me.
I got it from a grocery store.
Mate, I like to eat this with a spoon.
I'm already almost full.
I'm more of a spoon guy.
I don't know if I can get another bite.
But, but Pierce, there's so many more dishes to dive into.
Well, so let's go, let's keep going, yeah?
I mean, if we're feeling a little stuffed, I think we can also take maybe a little break.
So let's think about...
And move on to some of the other dishes in a minute, because I know that...
This seasoning, I love seasoning, but when it gets on your fingers...
Oh, it's even better.
Stinksgiving.
It's not just, I mean, it's about friends, it's about food.
Here, you want to suck the seasoning off of my finger?
I mean I'd be an idiot not to.
(laughter)
What it's also about...
It's also about giving each other gifts.
That is true.
That's a big part of the Stinksgiving. I don't want to burn through all the food
you know, in the first few minutes of our Stinksgiving.
I think we have plenty of exciting reveals.
That's part of the pleasure of the meal.
That's true.
So I mean, if you guys will,
why don't we go ahead and have our first gift
given to us by one of our delightful friends.
one of our delightful friends.
How does that sound to us?
- Who wants to open up their first gift?
- Whose gift is first?
- Well, Patrick, because you're the youngest,
maybe you should open up your gift.
- Okay.
Okay, Julio.
You're gonna need to pull up the gifts now.
- Oh, there it is.
- All right, this is my Stinksgiving gift.
Now, what I found--
- I'll just tuck into this chicken if you don't mind.
- Yeah, I'll be reaching across
and helping myself to tidbits.
- I'm gonna need to read it off my phone
because I foolishly forgot my glasses.
- Well, I mean, in the spirit of Thanksgiving,
I can whisper to you what the things
you have to read might be.
- That would be delightful.
- What an amazing showing of friendship between you two.
- Wow.
- I think I'm starting to catch on to this.
- I feel like I'm almost seeing a bond grow
between Pierce and Patrick, my friend.
- I'm feeling a mass.
- Really?
- It's warming in the deep part of my body.
- That Stinksgiving chicken was a little dry.
I wish we had some of the famous Stinksgiving brown gravy
that I could have dunked it in.
But here is my first gift.
This is from--
- Your first gift?
- The first part of my gift.
- Your one gift is all of these things.
- Okay, well, it's not, you have to click
the other screen, Jubio.
Here it is.
This is a forum post from--
- You want me to whisper?
- No, that's all right.
- AD, what's that website?
Diaper Forum, the Diaper Talk Forums.
Here's what somebody asked.
- Oh, I love this website.
- Rusky asks, "Anyone in the military and a diaper lover
"did you ever wear while on duty?"
I'll start off, there were several instances
when I was able to wear on duty.
I was in the USAF Security Service
and stationed at the NSA at Fort Meade from 1972 to 1975,
Which, I fully thought that wearing diapers and doing all this kind of stuff was a thing
that happened exclusively in the last 10 years.
But it turns out, people have been doing it since the 70s.
Back in the groovy 70s, maybe.
People have been doing it all the way since the time of the pilgrims.
I'm not to get all technical on you guys as a kind of a Stinksgiving historian, but it's
actually been a tradition for longer than many have even been alive.
Well, can you imagine that big 70s bush in a diaper?
I guess I can. Yeah, I can. Yeah, totally.
Anyway, I had a desk job.
So wait, this is a gift? This is a gift.
Pierce, little Pierce, okay? You're along for the ride, okay?
I want you to let kind of the warm liquid of Stinksgiving flow over you and soak you
and just, I want you to take on this knowledge and the tradition around you.
Uh-oh! Hey, look around the wishbone!
And here's a bone just for you, little Pierce.
Pierce, blow on it and make a wish!
What do I do?
You have to blow on it.
You blow on the bone and you make a wish!
But don't tell your wish or else it wasn't come true.
Okay.
I had a desk job and was able to wear during the midnight shift.
It was a neat place to work and the job I had was to monitor Russian fighter jets.
I didn't really have much supervision.
It was easy to wear and not get caught.
Only real concern was random drug testing, but that happened while I served.
Looking back at the time, it was a nice job.
I spent nine months in Monterey learning Russian and the remainder of my enlistment at the
NSA.
Okay, so I'm curious, they are worried about random drug testing.
Is that because somebody has to watch you pee?
That's the point, right?
That's either because they have to maybe...
So because you'd have to...
Somebody has to come in, watch you pee.
The cotton of the diaper is in his meatus.
They're taking some kind of drug to increase their diaper pleasure.
Ah, that's possible.
Maybe a laxative or...
I don't think a...
that baby powder laced cocaine. That makes you poop. I guess you could if you were a
diaper lover you can just hand a used diaper to the drug tester right?
I also yeah I don't know if you can wring it out into a test tube. Also isn't it so easy I mean we've
talked a lot about the the ABDL community isn't it and so much of it is
about the shame of like hiding it and like isn't it so easy to explain it as
like oh yeah I'm incontinent I have like a slipped disc or something like that why
are they so they're so concerned with like somebody caught me and I had to tell
them the truth well I pretend I'm a baby what if we caught you wearing a diaper I
would just lie I'd lie well actually it might be tough I was thinking while we
were preparing this I was thinking about what maybe if one of you three not me
started thinking because we've had so much so much exposure to this community
started being like I'm starting to get a tiny tickle in my balls yeah thinking
about this maybe I want to try.
- Some of the stuff I was reading.
- Was tickling your balls?
- You think you might want it?
- I think maybe, I could be a messy baby.
- I guess like a hot woman in a diaper,
does the diaper kill it for you?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I mean there is something about a diaper
that is just underwear.
I mean I like a lady in underwear.
- I don't. - No?
- And that's where I draw the line.
- You.
- Yeah, I wouldn't like it if any of my friends
were wearing a diaper.
definitely tease them about it but you're right I mean they would hold me
yeah right yeah part of it yeah I probably put him in the timeout corner
I probably make the meat Brussels if I caught one of my friends wearing a
diaper I would probably send them to bed with no yeah
oh no I think that's also that is that's the answer to your question is like why
Why do these people who are obsessed with being demeaned and degraded and wearing diapers,
why do they spill their life story about loving diapers to people?
It's almost like they're always celebrating Thanksgiving.
That's next year.
Why would they tell an embarrassing thing to somebody?
Speaking of, this next slide here.
United States Marine Corps 2007-2010.
I was originally stationed in Okinawa.
While I was there, I didn't have much chance to get if,
didn't have much if a chance to get padding.
Once I was restationed in California,
I was in combat unit, so I didn't have much time to do it.
Once I knew I was getting out,
I started padding up more and more.
Also happens when I first tried ABDL padding.
- So you found a couple people
who were in the military served.
- I found a lot of people who were in the military.
Here's another one here. - Well, I would say
That's a huge part of Thanksgiving, right?
Is like respecting the people who have served.
Definitely.
Lay down their life for your country.
Here's another-- yeah, like this person here.
I was in the Navy '94 to '98.
I wore diapers when I did the balls.
Eight hanger watch on occasion.
Did the balls?
Did the balls, that's what they said.
I was also doing the cleaning.
So I just made sure my last diaper of the night
was in the trash bags piled up in the back door by then.
I was wearing the depends on diapers.
Once I got married and moved off base,
it was much easier to wear diapers.
Especially once I corrupted my wife.
- Now, in the ABDL community,
is corrupting someone when you finally expose yourself
as a diaper lover and they have to accept it, change you,
they have to be a part of your lifestyle,
or is corrupting is when you get someone
into wearing diapers?
- It's when you get someone into it,
and participating it in whatever way.
- Yeah.
- Well, I think there's a huge difference
between participating in it as in you accept me,
and maybe even you changed me versus you are now deriving
sexual pleasure from filling a diaper.
- We've thought about this more than us.
- I mean, if I was a diaper lover,
I don't know if I would want someone to also derive pleasure
from filling their own diaper.
- Well, but I think the point is you get your wife
into putting the diaper on you.
- A lot of the relationships that I've seen
looking at all this stuff is, yeah,
there's somebody who is,
that's why so much of it is the little thing of like,
"Oh, I pretend to be a baby.
They change my diaper when I wake up in the morning."
It's, uh, God, that chicken is so delicious.
I mean, it's hard to--
- I think you're good enough.
- It's hard to deny how good a man you are.
- Is that hunk chicken and guacamole, anybody?
- Yeah.
- Hey, I think Stink'sgiving is about talking now.
- Yeah, here, let me read this next one.
USMCE, United States Marine Corps, 2003 to present.
I do not wear at work, but all the time after work.
My wife will oftentimes just have one waiting out for me to put on right when the camis come off.
God, that is romantic.
That is so fucking romantic.
To be like, maybe it's not my thing, but for my husband I'm going to lay out a diaper for him.
Like as if she bought lingerie for him for her to wear.
Kind of just lay it out.
Like he knows exactly what it means.
I saw one that maybe I didn't put in my gift, but a husband was like,
"Yeah, my wife actually likes that I wear a diaper.
She says well at least no other women are gonna want to fuck you
Who would fuck a man who wears diapers and then he says it's weird, but it works for us check this out
This one is a different thing okay. I looked up some ABDL tattoo ideas. Oh, that's a great idea
That is really somebody wants to get the hug
On their hip I want to have this tattoo. Well. That's genius because it's covered by the diaper. No one sees it exactly
It's a private thing for you. Nobody knows you like diapers based on your tattoo
Imagine going to a tattoo artist and showing them this logo and being like
That's you know
You have an easy out with any time you have to or you want to get a tattoo and want to explain it you say that
You lost a fantasy football league, and then it's like oh the guy
You know what's harder to explain though is you say you want this tattoo and you're like yeah
I lost a fantasy football whatever and then they're like alright
and you get down on the table and you have to roll up your shorts and you have to pull your diaper back.
That was another part of the punishment for the Fantasy Football League.
I also have to have this pacifier in my mouth.
That's how you get out of it any time somebody catches you with a diaper on.
Yeah, you have to change me also, that's part of it. I lost the bet also
and part of it is that you have to change me right here on the table.
It was either the Waffle House thing or I do this.
and I don't want to read it. Okay. You are a pro. Yeah. But this next one here, this was on a
discussion about the Queen. Nice. Says, "Irish and British here. Sad time for the world at the
moment in history with the oldest monarch to ever lived. I've seen a lot of toxic comments about the
Queen's death, particularly coming from the country of Ireland." I'm gonna dip back into this guacamole. "About the six
counties. Whatever happened in the past is the past. She was someone's mother, grand, and friend.
That's what's more important
It's cool to see the the the members of the ABDL community. Just say whatever happened in the past in Ireland is in the
Think it's cool that these are full human beings that yeah, that's what I like to do - I mean once we get to my gift
I think I found some nice people like that - yeah, I think that's part of Stinks giving
I was more criticizing this person's of fucking asshole behavior
the Queen the Queen and this person who said that the whatever happened in
Ireland should not a big deal the power under the bridge it's not water under the
bridge under the ass never been to Ireland I'm gonna go next year the four
Irish people you know are your family
that's not true my cousin did oh that's awesome all right well that's the end of
your gift right well then let's I mean maybe yeah so I don't think that this is
on no it wasn't on very easily tell that it wasn't on by you pressing the button
and it not working yeah nice that you figured it out thank you for your your
- I thought it was so special.
- Thank you, that was really special.
- That was, I really can't say enough.
- Everyone just say thank you, Patrick.
- Thank you, Patrick.
- Thank you very much.
- See, he's already, he said it before you guys said it.
- Guys, I'm fucking starving after that long ass rant.
- Oh yeah.
- Can I open up something here?
- Yeah, open up one.
- Let's open up a present here.
- What's this one?
- Ooh.
- This one is in a diaper.
- Just dig into that.
- This one has a diaper around it.
- Who hasn't opened one yet?
- Oh, this is Patrick's.
Oh my gosh.
This was supposed to be the appetizer.
This is exciting.
Hey, don't say anything about it.
No spoilers.
Let Cameron open this bad boy.
And what could be hidden beneath that beautiful cotton layer but...
Oh, a shrimp cocktail!
Oh, that looks so...
Oh God.
And Patrick, I mean, you love shrimp cocktail.
You can't eat the guacamole, so...
That's gotta be your favorite food, right?
How about you enjoy some of that?
Mostly diaper, I tell you.
We reached for the same shrimp.
Get into that.
Oh no, I'm allergic to shrimp.
No, I'm allergic to seafood
Yeah, me too
Actually fed me the tail he ate the tail and all oh the tail is not good for you. It's a bone
No speaking of bone I got a why that shrimp is making me hungry
I got the shrimps making me hungry for chicken the shrimp of the air all of this food is making me real thirsty
Mm-hmm. Oh my god. So look at my tasty fingers
Everybody look at my fingers delicious
I know you want to lick that off
Mmm. I know you want to lick. I know you want to lick that seasoning off - get over there get get your get your chompers
On that seasoning oh he got it
There's another piece of shrimp for Pierce
He's so he's so
I've been to plenty of Thanksgiving's and no one comments on how much food the other people are eating oh
Oh, another piece of shrimp for Pierce.
- I'm just excited that you like my meal.
- Well, this is nothing like Thanksgiving.
- You're like my fucking mother.
Chill out.
- You chill.
- No, no, no. - Chill, chill.
- Oh, okay.
- Yum.
(laughing)
- All right.
Well, guys, I think I already, do you guys want a gift?
- I would love another gift.
- I want one so bad.
I gave my gift first, and now to receive three more.
That is just absolutely divine.
- That's the best feeling in the world.
- What's better than that?
First of all, giving a gift,
and then receiving three in return.
- And three come back.
- Oh my God.
- It's the best deal in the world.
- Thanksgiving is really beautiful.
All right, here's my gift for everybody.
- Okay.
- So let's start it off here.
Okay, so the animation isn't working.
I forgot that the animation wouldn't work in this.
- Wait, click presentation view.
- It's not gonna work.
So mine, yeah, see?
- Oh, now I can't see anything.
- Yeah, so this will make a list,
my gift might be a little scattered.
- Hey, hey! - And, Julio,
you might have to drag stuff around
'cause some stuff is covering other stuff.
- I'll say this, Cameron, stink you for trying.
- Oh, thanks, thank you. - That's what I really care about.
- But I really did kind of-- - And Cameron, Cameron?
- Thank you. - And I tip my hat for you.
- Guys, I kind of messed it up.
- Buddy, listen, look at me, look at me, it's okay.
- Stinksgiving is about learning from your mistakes.
- I know that we're here and we're eating food
out of our diapers, but I really want you to know,
I stink you very much,
you're one of my most stinkful friends.
I stink of you as a brother.
Hopefully you still stink of me that way,
after my terrible, stinky mistake.
Us three are like one in the stink
and two in the stink with you.
(laughing)
In terms of how much we stink for you.
Okay, does anyone conceal carry while diapered?
Bambino Baby says, "I carry regularly and am diapered,
"usually thickly regularly,
"and I am proud and not ashamed of both.
"To answer the original question,
"I think your concealed carry setup,
and of course weapon of choice makes a difference as far as diaper wearing go.
I used to have an inside the waistband holster and would wear it while diapered.
It was sometimes tricky depending on how many diapers I was wearing at the time,
but doable. I now primarily carry a full-size Glock 19 with an optic
concealed with an OWB holster. I find that diaper wearing doesn't
affect this type of carry at all.
Wow. A diaper and a Glock.
I mean that, wait, so this person...
So what is their setup with the diaper and the and the the holster? They don't
have the... No, the Glock is not in their diaper. The Glock is outside of the diaper. It's between the diaper and pants.
This person is just bragging that they... because of course you can conceal carry
with a diaper on. It means, I mean, it's... I feel like having two diapers. Yeah, it's like
concealed carry with a diaper. I feel like if you are wearing a diaper, you
should have to put the gun in the diaper. Yeah, I think you're right. I agree. I will
- I will say though, this question,
the tenor of this question,
this is I think the only thing I put in here from this,
but this is a lot more,
like there's a lot of people who are like,
how can you live with yourself carrying a gun around?
It's more like that than like, how do you wear it?
- So the ABDL community is not so kind of--
- It's split down the middle, I would say.
Some people who are like this,
I read another guy who didn't put in
who says he does halo jumps,
the high, he was in like the Marines or something,
and he did like jumps from like 20,000 feet in the air.
he used to skydive for the military
while he was wearing a diaper.
He said that it's normal to wear a diaper
while you do that.
- I'm curious.
- You're falling for hours.
You're falling for hours and hours.
- That's how he found out his true--
- You either do that or you piss out right in your face.
- What if he found out that's,
like he was doing a halo drop or whatever
and then found out like,
man, wearing a diaper is fucking awesome.
- I do wonder, you said it's like wearing two diapers.
I wonder if you wear the holster
and that's the first thing that awakens you.
- Oh, it could be.
- You're like, oh, this kind of feels good
to have something, and then you get like--
- That no one knows about.
- This is making me think of my childhood,
but I never wore a gun as a child.
- I don't think I had a gun when I was a baby.
- What else did I carry while conceiving?
- Oh, oh, a screwdriver.
It was Tommy Pickles.
(laughing)
- Okay, here's my next gift for you guys,
or my next part of my gift.
Do you consider yourself ridiculous wearing diapers?
And naughty boy Nathan will see--
- I found this exact same post.
- I did the exact same pose.
- You did?
Naughty Boy Nathan is responding to someone who said,
"Even though I love to wear diapers,
I've been wearing them 24/7 for over three years.
Sometimes I still feel kind of ridiculous
for wetting myself like a baby."
Somebody else?
And Naughty Boy Nathan says,
"Why?
It's totally awesome having warm pee
flowing over your nether regions."
And then a bunch of smiley faces,
and then a thumbs up,
and then a cool sunglasses face,
and then the awesome face.
- What is the awesome face from?
- It's a meme face.
- It's from the internet.
- What was the-- - Oh, damn!
- What was the search term that you found?
Did you look up nether regions?
- I do not remember.
I think this was just a recent post.
- I think nether regions is a good search term.
- This guy actually, again,
this is something else I didn't put in.
This guy has made several posts
with the phrase nether regions.
(laughing)
He's going over nether regions.
That's kind of his thing.
- I mean, you gotta get kinda tired at some point
of saying crotch or no-no zone or all that.
- My wet winky.
- Okay, so.
I did see a couple of people who talked about their diapers, a couple of women who talked
about their diapers and said, "Yeah, I pooped and it got all over my pussy."
And I really hate, I really was like, "Okay, no half step in here.
You can't be like talking about your diaper and then call it a pussy."
But of course it did, you know?
I mean, like, I look at a pussy and a butthole and I'm like, "No diaper in that area, please."
They're a lot closer.
Please don't cover all that good stuff.
For God's sake, yeah.
Don't get that all smushed together.
Don't do that.
- Julio, for this one you're gonna have to uncover it
'cause these are boxes that are supposed to animate out,
so you're gonna have to delete them one by one, okay?
So this is, what were your weirdest dreams,
including with diapers, either asleep
or recreationally speaking, that changed you
or you remember strongly?
- Here's a Stinksgiving rule. - Recreationally speaking
meaning a daydream?
- Stinksgiving rule,
no talking with a mouthful of food, please.
- I love my food, though.
- Okay, then that's his food.
- Then I'll make a special Stinksgiving exception for you.
- There are mainly five, so these are five dreams
that this person had.
So just delete, just delete that.
Just delete that box.
Yeah, there's one behind each of them.
No, stop!
What are you doing?
Stop!
Undo! - Oh my God.
- There's five boxes that cover them up.
- Well, it's hard to understand what the hell you're saying.
- Okay. - Don't shout at him.
- Yeah. - I'm shouting at him.
- That's not what Thanksgiving is about.
- Give a Thanksgiving apology right now.
- Look directly into your camera and give him an apology.
- Right here. - No, I feel like
that's not a good enough punishment.
I feel like someone should get a spanking
if they break a rule.
- I think you should have to wear a diaper.
I think you should have to put a diaper on right now the diaper listen guy. I Julio
I want to give you a really sincere
Stink apology that was not that was not very stinky of me, and I'm really sorry for what I did
I got caught up in my emotions because
Okay, no, I take it all back. That's
You have to do a stink apology you interrupted a stick down close it all look how sad he is look at him
He's crying. I apologized. It's not my problem. He looks like
He's crying up there. I'm sorry that you don't know you have to look into the camera. Okay wait give me that
Give me my camera, please
That's Cameron. That's Patrick Cameron. I'm sorry you keep looking at me
Asked for your camera
You know that is actually very customary they've been doing that for 2,000 years almost
That's completely. That's what you're supposed to do during
(laughing)
- Do not pull that up.
Wrong episode.
- Okay, here are five dreams that this person had.
First one, a cartoon character was suffocating by a gum.
I feared them when I was a child because of it.
Can we get the second one here, please?
Second one, a mystical dream where I was dying
and climbing a Mayan pyramid.
- That sounds cool.
- That's the second dream, yep.
Okay, now I'll have the third one.
Third one, Jesus appeared in my grandma's bedroom.
Then he hugged me and told me he took care of her.
She lived many years after that.
- Awesome.
- And now here we have a warning
in between the third and fourth one that says,
warning, things get sexually explicit from now on.
- I'm nervous.
- Oh, you should be.
Let's reveal the fourth dream for us here.
Fourth one, I had sexual relations with my own mom.
I didn't see the direct action though.
I was just laying with her after finishing doing it.
It seems that kind of dreams is common for some people,
but it was still disturbing.
- Okay.
- I love being an ABDL and having a dream
where you have sex with your mom,
being like, "What could this mean?"
(laughing)
- What the hell could this mean?
- I also love having that and being like,
"Well, everyone has that.
Everyone probably gets dreams like that."
- Yeah, that's normal.
- Yeah, that's a normal dream.
Okay, you guys ready?
- Yes. - Yes.
- Fifth dream.
Fifth one, a girl pooped her pants so much
she could even rise her turd as an erected penis.
(laughing)
- Oh my god.
- A girl pooped her pants so much
she could even rise her turd as an erected penis.
- So let me kind of lay out what my theory,
'cause that makes almost no sense.
But I guess, is he saying that she would sit down,
like in a chair, shit her pants,
and then maybe she has her zipper open,
and it fills up her pants so much
that it pops through her zipper.
- No, I think--
- Zipper absolutely has nothing to do with this at all.
- I think that rise is a typo.
And I think it's supposed to be ride.
- Oh, that does make more sense.
- I think it's rise.
I think that her turd was so solid and it was packed in.
I also think that--
- I know this is about to make no sense.
- You're thinking about this--
- It's a dream, uh-oh, sorry, it's a dream, dipshit.
I think--
- The zipper makes perfect sense.
- You fill up your pants, the hole is there,
and it's like a play-doh.
- Yeah, that would make sense if it was a real thing
that happened, Caleb, you're right.
That physically, mechanically makes sense.
- Okay, then tell me your theory!
- Using dream psychoanalysis, I will tell you
exactly what happened. - Okay, dream expert.
Okay.
- When he said that she pooped them so much,
he just means she pooped them so specially.
So, she pooped them in such a way
that her turd went up and down.
That's what happened.
- So like-- - It wasn't the quantity,
what? - She shit so much
that like, it like, she was like--
- She shit in such a way that her poop was a full turd
and it went up and down like a butter.
- She pooped her pants so much, though.
- She was in Super Mario Sunshine.
- Why would he add that detail if she's saying
that she goes up and down like a piston in her own ass?
- Otherwise it would fall out of her ass.
- No, otherwise it would come out of the zipper
like a fucking hard brown cock, you fucking idiot.
- So you're thinking it's like Super Mario--
- If you didn't poop her pants, it would fall out of her butt.
- I'm the third way here.
I think that it doesn't come out of the pants at all.
It's a print, it's a poop print.
- You think it's a print?
- I think it's a pooped-up print.
- You really think that?
- It's like an Instagram picture
that the game would post. - Yeah, I think it's
a gray sweatpants.
- Okay, all right, that makes sense.
- This actually happened to me in real life.
- No, it didn't.
(laughing)
No, it did not.
- You're thinking, you're like, it's like--
- Okay, it was a dream that someone else had.
Okay, I was a dream that someone had of the diaper. I do like that. We all just had our own psycho like analysis
We were all like no your theory is completely wrong. I'm not sure my my theory was what I would call psycho analysis
Yeah, that shit would come out like a cock out of the you approach like Adam Savage
Yes, which I actually I've been watching a lot of videos where Adam Savage explains kind of his process
- Does he ruin everything?
- He does.
- All right.
- Yeah.
- For this next one, Julio,
can you please drag the bottom one down just to uncover,
just can you uncover them?
- Oh my God.
- 'Cause they're all covered up each other.
So can you just drag them out of the way?
- Cameron.
- I thought I would be able to have the animation
have them fade in.
I'm very sorry.
I already apologized.
You guys said it was okay.
- Yeah, it was okay.
- I love, okay, interesting places to wear.
I love wearing at my local casino.
I can sit at a table for hours and just keep drinking
and never have to take a break.
And I love walking around in it thinking,
I wonder how many people are wearing.
- Okay, I, that is, I do, that's a great idea.
- Yeah. - What?
- 'Cause that does suck when you're at a slot machine,
oh it's hot, oh the roulette table is hot,
I'm making fucking $10 an hour.
And then you-- - Nature calls.
- And then you go, oh I have to use the little boys room,
excuse me dealer. - Yeah, yeah.
- That sucks. - I'm no longer
a roulette machine, I'm a piss machine.
- It's better to when they ask you for your bet,
just kind of stand there, just grit your teeth
you push up the piss for a full 30 seconds.
Yeah, talking to the dealer, be like, "Can you not look at me for a second?
I need to go and I need to get shot."
If you're a seasoned pro and you're shitting your pants and pissing your pants at the casino,
I think that it could help you with your poker face.
I think if you go to the poker table and you're just like, you know, you're sitting there shitting.
Oh yeah.
Oh my God, that's impossible to read.
Yeah, they look at you, and they're never thinking this guy's shitting his pants
But they're looking your face, and you're like he's looking at me like he's taking a fucking shit right in his pants right now
Yeah, what car does he have?
He has to have two keys
Hey, yeah, he's got a deuce. Yeah, you know and you know it's not gonna be a royal. I also think he's got a full house
Diaper he has a full
All right next
- I have to say one more thing, which is that--
- Yeah, he's not holding it.
- I think that might be good luck to wear a diaper,
because it is like, anything that I think is like,
impeding on a normal life, any kind of disability,
is very good luck at a casino.
- Yeah, I'm peeding in my pants and my diaper
at the casino.
- Once you get into the mindset of, I'm just secreting,
then you start secreting money.
- I'm plugged into the matrix, I'm sitting here,
I'm just a money machine.
- It's falling out of me, coins are falling out of my holes.
- I am a slot machine.
- And it's kind of effortless.
It's basically second nature.
A slot machine.
- I am a slot machine.
- A slime machine.
- Next interesting place is,
I love urbexing, that's urban exploration.
- I know.
- Padded with, I don't care what you know.
- That's okay.
- You don't know anything.
- Padded with a few beers.
If it's a place that's already cluttered with litter,
such as an abandoned hospital in the downtown of my hometown,
I've actually left used diapers there before.
Am I allowed to post pics?
Although when I've come back, they're never there.
It really makes me wonder how that is the only piece
of trash to go missing.
- It's a raccoon.
- Is there another part of this that's covered up
by any chance?
I can't remember.
- No, I don't think so.
- I think there might be.
- Oh yeah.
- Yep, yep, yep.
Depending on whether the locations
already have a good amount of graffiti,
I actually have left my A-disc username tagged before.
This person tags their adult diaper
full of Andy Hamming graffiti.
- That is so funny to be into graffiti
and also wearing a diaper.
- Yeah, they're not so far away.
- You think they get a paint pen
and write their fucking, write their name,
like their graffiti tag name on there.
- You think they do graffiti with their name?
- You think they, what, that's what it says.
- No, no, no, no, I mean, I was, oh fuck.
I've had three beers.
- Do you think that they poop on their finger
and wipe it and smear it?
- Is that what you're asking?
- No, do you think that they write their graffiti name
on the front of their diaper?
- I think it makes more sense,
and it's probably a funnier point
that they might write their name in their shit.
- Yeah, maybe they're spraying it.
It comes out exactly like spray paint.
- But that wouldn't make any sense
'cause it's too weird.
- Yeah, it's strange.
They did it in the in the graffiti style with poop.
That would be pretty impressive.
They might be one of the greatest artists who ever lived.
If somebody would have had that much control of their ass
and their penis.
I mean, that's how much they like Jackson Pollock.
You just throw you have a stencil on the wall and you just
explosive diarrhea.
I wasn't I wasn't going to say that I was going to say like
you you shit like in like block letters like you like you
- Oh, you put like a little cookie cutter on your anus.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- That's a good idea.
- And it writes out your tagging name.
- The only problem with that is that
you could only graffiti the floor.
- No, no, no, no.
- You would have to bend over and do it on the wall.
- But how does it stick?
- You eat a lot of--
- Sticky foods, right, it wouldn't pull down.
- You eat like a lot of garlic or like--
- You eat sticky foods.
- Something that makes you diarrhea.
- Yeah, you eat what you normally eat plus glue.
- Yeah.
- Okay, that might work.
- Simple.
- Okay.
- The last interesting place is obviously
on the last interesting places opera premier billionaire environment so
it's been a recent millionaire vibes
billionaire environment is so funny to me
this wearing a diaper in a billionaire environment
uh... i'm struggling being a diaper lover and i don't like it
i'm struggling with the fact that i can't stop wearing wanting diapers
i ride bulls and cowboy but i can't help the feelings of wanting to wear and use
diapers this is a problem to me because i feel we can baby is when i wear diapers
and it's the direct opposite of who i am when i'm writing polls
I feel like I have a split personality
and I really need helping coming to terms with who I am.
Is there anyone else in the Western lifestyle
who loves diapers?
How do y'all deal with it?
And how did you come to terms with it?
Slash stop binging and purging.
Any and all help would be great.
- Well do you guys know about binging and purging
in the community?
- In the diaper community? - No.
- Yeah, binging is when you wear a fuck ton of diapers
and shit and piss in them all the time and get off.
And purging is when you say,
I have to stop being into diapers
and you throw them all away.
(laughing)
- I just learned that.
- So it's not really a, it's more of just a choice here.
- It's nothing digestive, it's like you excess in diapers
and then you stop, yeah.
- Here's some more from this thread.
I felt the conflict when I was much younger.
In high school and college,
I loved sports and managed to play a few.
After I graduated from college,
I got into quarter mile drag racing
and had two cars I ran at the track.
At the same time, I dearly loved wearing and wetting diapers.
For years it was a conflict
and I had trouble as to how I saw myself.
But over the years, I began to realize
that as people were complicated
and sometimes were more than the sum of our parts,
so to speak.
I learn to make peace with myself, learning to accept my quirks along with my plusses
and successes.
Both are part of the same person and they can reside together in peace if you accept yourself
for all the wonderful things that you are.
So the reason I put this in here is this one.
I realized I've never wanted to see a movie more than a movie about a guy who's a drag
racer and he's trying to make peace with being a diaper lover also.
And he's like, he's drag racing and then he's going home and putting on diapers and he's
drinking and he's like, "Fuck.
Fuck, I need to quit."
Fuck I need to quit but somehow we would need to figure out a way for the diaper is like
Somehow also kind of making a metaphor. It's making it like better
It's well, it's making a better at drag racing because you can stay in the car. Oh, how the fuck does he do it?
He's in that damn car and his wife his wife or his new girlfriend or whatever is like like you never
It's you never want to get intimate with me. Yeah
Wouldn't that be perfect? I got something I need to show you and he pulls off his fucking like suit
Oh my god, nothing on but a diaper underneath holy diaper driver. That would be good
Yeah, just baby
That's genius
Any of mine, but there's I was looking up if anyone does psychedelics in the adult baby
Community and a ton of people are just like tripping on mushrooms and wearing a diaper is I will never go back
I was tripping with my friends for hours and I came home and I put on a diaper and I was able to go into
to my baby place immediately.
- When they say, "Well, they'll never go back,"
do they mean that they will--
- No, they'll always trip and--
- Right, but is it that they always took mushrooms
and now I can't take, like, now I'm adding diapers,
or is that I always wear diapers and I'm adding mushrooms?
Do you know what I'm saying?
- Oh, I think it might be a little bit of both.
- Is it like I used to love wearing diapers,
but now I have to take mushrooms when I do it,
or is it like I'm just like a stoner,
I always take shrooms, but I realize my best trips
are always when I'm wearing diapers.
- I could see myself, I could see--
- It was a psycho nut who tried on a diaper.
- Yeah, exactly.
- If you were on Mushrooms, I could see it feeling
really good to piss your pants.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I personally wouldn't want to, but I was curious.
I thought that maybe someone would say,
"Oh, I'm a disgusting freak," and they had a bad trip,
but all the trips were extremely good trips.
- So now you have an interest in it?
- You don't wanna knock it, you know,
the people who are asking the questions.
- Yeah, yeah.
- The next one here is, "I've been trying not to do this,
but the urge is too strong.
Do do do do do do do do do do do do.
- You don't know this song?
- I know this part of it,
I don't remember how the does go.
You sing it.
- Yeah, you go.
- Do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do.
- I knew that, I specifically put this in for Patrick.
- And then you sing the part.
- Some people call me the diaper cowboy.
- What? Wow.
(laughing)
- Some people call me the gangster of loves.
- Oh my God, wait, that is fire.
That is a fucking bar right there, dude.
- Woo, woo, wah, wah.
- Yeah, loves is a good little pun.
- The gangster of loves.
- I just love some people call me the diaper cowboy.
It just doesn't even fit.
- Some people call me the diaper cowboy.
- All right, paranormal happenings.
- No.
- I have seen ghosts before
and prophetic dreams and energy experiences.
And then the next one, I had a ghost poop once.
I really had to go one day, almost pooped myself at school
because toilets were full and a line outside of door.
I made it home after 10 more minutes
I have an absolute hell of a bus ride.
Every bump was torture.
Got home, ran to the toilet and squeezed out
what I thought was a log.
Looked in the bowl of whatever demon I spawned
into this world and nothing.
I apparently pooped out a ghost.
- This has happened to everyone here, right?
- Yeah. - A fart?
- I've pooped a ghost.
- No, no, no, like you feel it coming out of your ass
and then you look in the toilet and there's nothing.
- That's never happened to me.
- It's so heavy that it slips under the bowl, yeah.
- Let's go.
- Oh, okay, so you have an explanation for it.
You've cracked the case.
- Yeah, but you can't see it when you look down.
- You've never taken a ghost poop?
water they float directly to the surface like fish food my shit's like shaking a
pepper grinder they don't I don't have perfect logs that decide to flush
themselves because they know what is this a cartoon I don't shit turds out of my head
I really don't and some more paranormal happenings here I think these are my
last ones I've been recording the er the prompt for the yeah yeah I hope I go to
heaven if not I hope I'm running around in my diaper with a mommy ghost chasing
- I'm gonna need you to tell me to change me.
- That is so awesome.
- Can you imagine a ghost like that?
- Heaven should be someone chasing you.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Who would chase you?
- The candy man. - No.
No, heaven should be relaxing.
- No, it should be Gapool.
- Julio, can you uncover the middle one, please?
- Okay. - Thank you.
So I'm sitting on the couch in my room
with some buddies smoking Kush weed.
When my door creaks open a centimeter
and I say out loud, "Not now, I got company,"
and immediately the door creaked shut.
Later that evening, my guests have left
and I'm laying on my floor and I recall the door incident
and I say out loud, "All right, my friends are gone.
"You can come in now."
Immediately the door creaked open.
Yeah, that's my true story.
- Holy fuck.
- That's just backdraft.
I don't believe this person.
- I believe it. - Pretty scary though
if it's true. - Yeah.
- I'm now, this last paranormal experience
from Diaperman0723.
I have had a friend of mine that had the demon Beelzebub
attached to them. (laughing)
- Wow.
This is, what part of the forum were all these on?
I was just typing in "parents."
I typed in "ghost" I think and found this.
I have one last one to show you guys.
- I'm getting hungry!
- Okay, so there's one more for you to go through.
It's so short and simple.
And here's the final one.
Women have best butts, period.
(laughing)
- Deleted member!
- Come back, man.
We need you back.
Deleted member said that.
- Women do have the best butts.
- Period.
- Yeah, men's asses are too small.
- Yeah.
- They need to be big and concrete.
- I almost thought for a second you said
women's asses were too small.
- No, women's houses, thank God.
- And I thought, how much bigger could they get?
- Women's houses are the perfect giant size to me.
- Well, let's say we open up another piece of food.
- Okay, what is it?
- Okay, open it up.
- Oh dear.
- Well, who hasn't opened one on camera yet?
- We've all opened one.
- So why don't you do the honors?
You can do double duty.
- Oh, what's this?
What could this one be?
- Okay, so first layer.
Hey, oh, this is totally that pumpkin pie.
- Okay, open it.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Open it, open it, open it.
We're hungry.
nothing wrong with sneaking along my done with dinner hey now this I'll enjoy I
don't know if I've ever really had pumpkin pie I think I usually check this
out looks good right mm-hmm never had pumpkin pie I don't think I've had it
but I've definitely had it but it wasn't remarkable enough and I always go for
the apple pie instead apple pie is way worse than pumpkin pie hey I like that I
I like both of them.
This doesn't taste like pumpkin, though.
But you know what?
Now that I'm older, with my more refined palate,
I think maybe there's a secret ingredient that
is making this taste better.
Oh, yeah.
It's my diaper.
It's a diaper.
Oh, yeah.
It's my diaper.
Would you pass that?
Oh, that was good.
I can't stop.
Can we have another dish, or is that too much?
I feel like we have another.
Yeah, let's have one more.
We might as well.
This is, I think, mine.
OK, well then, open it up.
You can do triple duty.
- I'm excited to see this one.
- You can do triple duty.
- This is like a recipe that my mom taught me.
- This is a traditional Stinksgiving or no?
- No, this is a little bit--
- Kind of a new twist?
- This is a little bit outside of the tradition.
- And what's that?
- Well, you can see we have some rice here.
- Okay.
- Maybe this is some bok choy.
- Oh, this is like an Eastern inspired Stinksgiving meal.
- So what is that?
- Let me get my spoon out here
so I can get to the real main event.
- What would you--
- Oh, what is that?
- Imitation crab!
- Oh, wow, well--
- You're gonna find some imitation crab,
gonna find some of that sweet triangular egg that we love in our sushi dishes and
you're gonna have...
And don't forget the rice, Pierce!
Here, I'll help you out.
Oh, he's so hungry!
It looks so good! I'm so jealous you get to eat all of this!
You can have a bite if you like.
Oh yeah.
Have a bite.
It's a sushi bowl.
Oh god.
I love this.
Let me have some more of this imitation crab.
Oh it is exceptional.
I'm full. I already had some.
I think Cameron hasn't had a single bite.
This imitation crab is perfect room temperature.
You know I'm pretty full but I can't help myself.
I'm going to have one grain of rice.
That is good.
Oh, that's just the right portion for me.
That's delectable and we should store that right in the trash can right now.
Oh, that's good.
Oh yeah.
And he loves it!
Look at how much he loves it!
Complete sushi facial abuse on beers.
He's crying.
I can smell it coming out of my mouth.
(laughing)
- Oh fuck.
- Oh my god.
- It's the worst episode we've ever done
in a fucking Plasma Jam.
- Oh no.
- Oh man.
- So that was good.
- That was awesome.
- That was delicious.
- Yeah! - Give it up for Pierce!
- Thanks for bringing that, Pierce.
Happy Stinksgiving, buddy!
- Say stink you for your food.
- Stink you for your food!
- Mm, that was good.
- Oh, I can't wait to shit this all out.
- Well, let's get to the next gift.
I want another present.
- Oh, I thought you were reaching over to eat more of it.
(laughing)
Okay.
- Patrick, you made a mess.
- Oh, dear.
Oh my god, that really sticks in your mouth forever.
Yeah, I can't taste anything but sushi bowl.
God damn, dude.
OK, we can show my gift.
I actually brought a gift for you guys.
It's a little larger than the last two gifts.
But I would like to show you guys.
That doesn't really matter on Thanksgiving is the thing,
isn't it?
I just hope nobody gets hungry during the big gift, right?
It's probably going to make everyone--
I mean, Pierce is ready to eat again.
I can see it in his eyes.
Why don't you here?
Let's get you something to eat during the gift.
- Oh no, we only have one last thing
and I'd like to save it.
- No, we have, okay, we have more than one last thing.
But we'll save it, we'll save it.
- You're right.
- Can I get some more of that pumpkin pie?
- Yeah, help yourself.
- Where is it?
- It's over here.
- Okay. - Have some pumpkin pie.
- Here, how about you feed it to me, Pierce?
- No.
(laughing)
- I think Patrick learned a little too much
from the diaper forums.
- Yeah, I think so too.
- I think Patrick learned how to derive pleasure
from odd things.
- So here's my Thanksgiving gift, guys.
So let's take a look at this.
This is, I did not go to the ABDL forums.
I found some other, or I didn't go to the one
that everybody likes, the diaper talk one.
I went deep into the pages of searching ABDL forum
and I found this one on christianforums.com, diaper fetish.
MRA 22, hello, my real name is Matt.
So right off the bat, he tells his real name.
I'm in need of prayer and advice.
I'm not trying to do this for spam or anything
and I trust that I won't be judged,
but for pretty much my whole entire life,
I've struggled with something called a diaper fetish,
which falls in with something called ABDL.
Growing up, I had somewhat of a rough life.
I was abused when I was younger before,
and I was made fun of, and was called an egghead,
or a conehead, and it hurt.
But I would resort to wearing diapers,
and it took stress away.
The thing I know, wearing diapers in general is not a sin,
it is just another form of underwear.
It is just that I find myself becoming aroused by them,
and I even like to look at grown women wearing them
and I'm aroused by that.
I don't like the nudity stuff though
because I know nudity pics is wrong and sinful.
It just feels like I'm at a tug of war
because I love God with everything in me
and I just don't really understand my fascination
with this lifestyle and I'm going on 23.
It is something that can be embarrassing
and I would just appreciate prayers and advice, thank you.
- Oh my God.
- So there's plenty of people on this Christian forum.
- You can tell that this guy is truly
kind of a good-hearted Christian man
'cause he's not at war, he's at tug of war.
(laughing)
- I really wanna see--
- He said-- - Bug off, War.
- He said he was called an egghead or a conehead,
and I really wanna see that.
- I can't remember, but I do wanna see what he was.
- Hello, my name is Matt, and this is my real head.
(laughing)
This is my real head shape. - Wait, can we just look
at Patrick's plate real quick?
- Oh yeah, wait, let's show his plate real quick.
Oh God, that looks delicious.
Look at that, the cranberry sauce
mixed in with the sushi rice.
(laughing)
Oh!
Man down with the cranberry sauce.
- Cran down.
- So we have some people trying to help.
This person is Saltwater Heart,
a Christian furry and a Christian brony.
I'm familiar with the community because I'm an ABDL too.
Like you, I was abused and wearing diapers
helps me to decompress and cope with the trauma.
Drawing baby furs or ABDL furries is pretty fun as well.
I will say that I harbor no sexual interest
for any of it though.
That aside, I have run across some pages
that tackle ABDLism and Christianity.
perhaps they'll be of help to you.
And then he doesn't link them,
which seems kind of selfish.
- Yeah, find 'em yourself.
- Selfish to somebody who might need
looking for stuff for a podcast.
- Exactly, and then within a couple of days,
these two people make a pretty similar post.
I have the same feelings myself.
I like looking at pictures of women in diapers
and I feel aroused when I wear one.
It gives me a feeling of security, peace, and happiness.
And hey, I need help with this also,
says History Incognito.
And then so I found this other website,
which I don't think we've touched before.
This is a German diaper website called Diaper--
- It's about to get freaky as hell.
- Diaper.community, okay?
I didn't get all that much from Diaper.community
because it's not very active.
But I did find some things, like this post,
made big in the diaper.
This is from Helmet.
(both laughing)
And this is all translated by Google Chrome.
Hello everyone, I did it last night, finally,
and I would be interested in how you do it.
And there's some responses here.
Here's one from Wow, who says, "Hello."
(laughing)
Who says, "Hello, you shit pants."
For me, there is nothing more appealing
than doing big business in a mostly wet diaper.
This often happens in the morning
after waking up when the toilet is urgent.
If I plan to do that, I pack myself in the evening
with thick night diapers, pads, and rubber pants.
Always wear a pair of long-legged panties
so that everything stays in place,
then lie on my back, empty the bladder,
and then follow the AA.
I've learned AA, I don't really know what it means,
but for whatever reason, all these German people,
that is what they refer.
- Follow the AA.
- Follow the AA. - AA means basically
take a shit.
I think it's like BM, basically.
- Oh, okay.
- A very-- - Hausfacht.
- Yeah, I think something like that.
- Ausch, ausch.
- Ouch, ouch.
A very wonderful feeling.
Knead a little, distribute a little,
and then stand up slowly.
Sitting on the chair for breakfast, what a pleasure.
I can easily enjoy this unique condition for several hours
by applying a lot of lotion the night before.
It could well be afternoon.
Depending on the packaging,
I do that from time to time when I'm on the go.
That's even more fun.
But as I said, you should only allow yourself
the necessary packaging, rubber pants, air brakes.
I have good experience with it.
Greetings, Wally.
- Oh my God.
- And then I looked into Wow's profile some more
and he posted this on how often do you AA in your diapers?
Not everyone wants to admit that.
Of course, a pee diaper is easier to handle, but those who have become addicted to this
fetish are happy to accept the unpleasant side of feeling a really full diaper on your
bottom for the unique feeling.
For me personally, there is nothing more beautiful and lovely than doing AA in the always thick,
wet diapers and enjoying this wonderful state for as long as possible.
Of course, you can only do this when circumstances allow.
For me, it's at least 4 times a week.
I don't just do it at home, but also when I'm on the go.
but I have to say that I then wear very good
tailor-made Bermuda latex rubber pants,
which hardly let any unpleasant smell escape to the outside.
Who would like to be labeled as a pants shit?
(both laughing)
- Oh my God, it's a superhero.
- I know.
And then so there's also some groups on this website.
So there's like, they're basically complete copies
of like Facebook groups.
So this one, there's Pokemon Go,
there's Mac users,
and then there's geocaching in diapers.
Everyone with a hobby of geocaching is welcome.
- That's nice.
- So I looked up AA is ah ah ma shin, makin,
to do big jobs.
(laughing)
So it's like to do a number two.
- Okay, a big job.
- Yeah, to do a big job.
- Oh, that's why they say big business at another point.
Okay, that makes sense.
- I wonder if it's like an autonym from baby days,
like when German babies shit, they go ah, ah, ah.
(yells)
- I hate big business.
I think what big business is doing to this country
and to my pants is disgusting.
- It's very, very bad.
- It's nasty.
- All they're doing is eating schnitzel
and sausages over there.
- Okay.
- Of course their craps are gonna look crazy.
- I agree, they're eating shit.
- And then I found, so in addition to this,
so these couple forum posts,
I found while looking for other forums,
I found this website, let's see,
Life as a Diapered Mother.
Wearing diapers as a parent
who is a diaper lover and an adult baby.
And this is a blog spot that's been going on
for I think 10 years now.
And then she has an FAQ where she answers,
or sorry, sorry, about me.
My name is Beth and I have been happily married since 2009.
We both have two children together
and I am a 30-something year old woman
and my husband is a lot older than I am in his early 40s.
I've been wearing diapers off and on since I was 17
and have gone 24/7 a couple of times.
My husband, on the other hand,
has been into them for a while,
but he is more of an AB than a ABDL.
He also forces me to wear diapers
and I enjoy it more that way.
Plus, it is what I've always wanted.
I have always had a fantasy of a man forcing me into diapers
and I have to wear them and do everything in them.
Plus, I'm more calm in diapers
and more relaxed and happier.
So it's as if I mentally need them.
Plus, I seem to function better in the relationship.
I think it's more fun to be forced into them
than be wearing them on my own, under my own consent.
My hobbies are computer.
(laughing)
And I also like video games.
And I like to write and have return to it.
I also love to clean and it relaxes me.
This was written in English also.
I am also childlike and a kid at heart
and my emotions are a bit immature.
That is just the natural part of me
but I think it's very good for my AB role.
I also love cartoons and kid shows
but I don't watch very much TV.
My husband views me as innocent
despite that I am capable of being mean and rude and bad.
I am also an opinionated person.
So I have a lot of unpopular opinions and point of views,
so it makes me look like a jerk or judgmental
or come off as a troll.
My husband likes to describe me as having mean views.
In no way do we involve our kids in our fetish.
How old are they?
Well, they were born in 2010 and 2014.
- By the way, this is how I used to do
all of my writing prompts when I was in like fourth grade
is I would ask myself rhetorical questions
and then I would go, well.
- Well.
(laughing)
Warning, this blog contains off-topic posts and rants
and my ramblings and may contain irrelevant stuff.
It's my blog, so I don't try to be normal or anything,
and I am more than ABDL, so I may just blog
about other stuff as well,
which is why I had created another blog.
I hope you enjoy my blog.
- What do they mean by off topic?
I feel like the topic here is being a diapered mom
constantly, so it's just--
- No, there's a lot of-- - Interesting here is--
- I'll get into it, but there's a lot of other stuff
on this blog. - Yeah, okay, well.
- So the-- - I'm glad you have more--
- Really quickly, this has one like,
one blogger liked this. - Matt DeVito liked this.
No, it's not Matt DeVita, it's actually Gordon Shagin.
(laughter)
Who seems like a good guy.
- Oh, that's Gordon Shagina.
- Shagin.
- Shagina.
- He's Shagina in a diaper.
- So, uh.
These are some of the posts, these are some of the titles.
So I don't want to include the bodies of these
because a lot of them have pictures of her diapers
filled with shit or very--
- We're going for some more chicken right now, oh my god!
- We're very particular--
- Hungry as fuck, dude.
- God, dude.
- His skin just rubbed up the diaper.
- Very particular details about her life.
So I'll just stick to mostly titles for this.
I'm so full of shit, a huge load,
ouch my butt.
- These are all accompanying with photos of a full diaper?
- For the most part, yeah.
pooped my nappy, I felt like using a British word,
I'll include somebody.
And then yay, wifi is back.
(laughing)
It's not all about the diapers, yay, wifi is back.
Another stinky in one day.
I haven't used the toilet since last summer.
- Oh my God.
- Oh, Jesus Christ.
- And the PC police have struck again.
The PC police have struck again.
And then there's more stuff, there's a retarder.
- This was a new term I just learned.
(laughing)
Let's see.
Oh yeah, so she also has claimed
that she kind of invented her own religion.
She says, "I also think people do a religion
"because they need rules,
"but you don't need to pick a religion to do.
"Why not make up your own?
"My religion is no toilet usage, no underwear,
"no weighing above 125 pounds, no unemployment,
"no belief in God, no church,
"no Christmas before Thanksgiving."
- What does that mean?
- I have no idea.
- No Christmas before Thanksgiving?
Must shower when I see too much pubic hair growing in.
Must not judge people for things that they do
that are totally different, that are not harming others
no matter how gross it is.
Must, which seems a little bit like she's trying
to get you to kind of believe that.
Must exercise five times a week on weekdays.
- This lady's taking showers so hot
it scalds all her pubes off.
(laughing)
- It is, I don't really know why we're not shaving
instead of taking a shower.
Maybe it's because they're like, they're too fluffy.
- Yeah, the terrifying reality of this is,
is that her diaper is putting so much shit in her pubes.
- Oh. - Yeah.
- It's working like fertilizer
and making them grow at super speed.
- She's growing, it's like she's got like hydroponics
for her pubes. - That's awful.
- 'Cause of the piss and shit.
- But she doesn't take it that much.
- Like paint and a paintbrush.
- She doesn't take it that seriously.
She says, "Broke," oh whoops,
she says, "Broke my diaper religion again."
- Good. - Was I think the next one.
- She did Christmas before Thanksgiving.
- Yeah, that's the one thing.
- So here's where it gets kind of bad,
is that this is-- - No weighing above 125 pounds.
- Petite lady.
- Yeah, that's a small woman. - As long as,
that might be tough if you're including
the big puffy butt load of rape.
- Yeah, I wonder if she takes that off the way.
But so this was, after this, I looked at the tags,
and so here's some of the tags.
3DS, ABDL problems, and then the biggest one is abuse.
So from there, I kind of fell into
what has to be the worst things I've ever seen.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Is that, I need to ask before you go any further.
Did you investigate 3DS?
'Cause does that mean--
- She has a, this is--
- Like a Nintendo 3DS or is it the 3Ds?
- This is unrelated, she has a Twitter account
where she just posts her 3DS games
and how much she loves 3DS.
- Okay.
- The most diaper-friendly gaming system.
- Yeah, definitely.
- It's on the go.
So this is kind of the beginning of where I started to see
that this was maybe not gonna be all smiles.
So then, here's some more titles of some of her blog posts.
Got my kid taken.
- Oh.
(laughing)
Oh no.
- I got to see my son again, ready to have my son back.
I hurt my mother.
Yes, you read that right.
(laughing)
So I stalked my ex.
I sometimes wonder if my ex was a pedophile.
(laughing)
Showing signs of autism.
Looks like our son will be having autistic parents.
Search terms again.
I just read another blog by someone
about disturbing search terms she found
and I decided to look through mine again
to see if there are any interesting ones
or if I had gotten anything disturbing.
I've never gotten a search term yet that is about me.
The ones I found that stuck out for me were,
so this is, you can see what search terms
brought people to your blog spot.
So this is one that she found.
She is weirn and adult diapers.
The misspelling made sit look like I am reading
she is weirn and Adolf diaper.
And then I see Adolf Hitler in my mind
because of me being visual.
Then I'm seeing Adolf Hitler's diaper.
I know it's supposed to say she is wearing a adult diaper.
- I know now how you found this blog.
(laughing)
What search term you put into Google to find this.
- I've been caught.
- It became perfectly clear.
(laughing)
- Okay, so we only have a couple things left.
- Before my gift, and before we open the next one,
I do actually have to fill my diaper.
And by that I mean use the toilet,
just a little bit of a joke.
I'm going to use the toilet briefly.
- Oh yeah, you can go use the toilet.
- Okay.
- God, I feel so good now.
- I feel good after that. - Let's do this again.
- All right.
- Okay, Pierce is back. - Okay, guys.
Before Pierce's gift, I just have,
I mean, we have a really exciting one to open at the very end.
- That's gonna be a huge finale.
- But this one, this is our second to last,
kind of our penultimate diaper that I'm gonna open up here.
- Go ahead and open that bad boy up.
- A little snack that I brought for all of us.
- Good, 'cause I'm starting to get hungry again.
- All right, here we go. - Did you work up an appetite
in the bathroom there, Pierce?
- I did.
I'm so starving, you guys.
- Oh, I can't wait for this.
What is this?
- This looks like it's gonna be the best one.
- Or the second to best one.
What is that?
Oh, I can't even see it yet.
Oh, it's digestives.
- Get it?
- Oh, I get it.
- A side gag.
- That's a Stinksgiving marathon.
Did you guys go to the Stinksgiving marathon?
(laughing)
Oh, I'd love to have one.
- Oh yeah, the stinky trot.
I love any meal where half of the food is dessert.
[LAUGHTER]
I fed a whole person on my own.
Oh my god.
Cheers and happy Thanksgiving to everybody.
Digestives, a little chocolate to whet
the appetite for the lab.
These are really good.
That was a good--
that's by far the best thing we've eaten.
Why did they smush them up in there?
Where did you find these?
I want to bring these at home. I
Want to bring these home? Yeah, those are good. You have extras of those. Nope. I only bought four. Okay, okay
All right. Well Pierce, let's check out your gift, buddy
Can you help me do beer you change me
Okay, Pierce's Thanksgiving gift. Yeah, here we go
Okay, so there's a user I found that has a kangaroo
With the diaper on.
Just gonna read through all these that I found.
A few months ago I had a nightmare
where two people came in and took everything I had.
I had my games, my house, my dog, and my toys.
Treated me like complete trash.
And I was out on the street in minutes.
Over there crying and squeezing my bear.
Glad everything was still there.
This actually happened to me over nine years ago.
(laughing)
Jubio, shut the fuck up.
- Oh, shut the hell up, Jubio.
(laughing)
That was so loud.
- When I do mess my diaper,
- I first enjoy the farts before.
(laughing)
Sometimes I get a little pain in my stomach before crapping.
But feel great relief after messing.
I also like the clump on the back.
And then there's that cleaning
where the wipes feel a lot smoother than toilet paper.
The times that I mess are most often
in the wee hours of the morning
when everyone is still sleeping.
One thing I dislike about having to spray down my room
after clearing.
- Cleaning.
- The smell will reach all over the house.
I live in a small place with my bed
taking up one third of my room.
And then I also believe that this person has a child.
- Oh cool.
- And they posted on their own private--
- It's pretty common it seems.
- Yeah, on their own private account they just wrote,
I changed Barry's diaper yesterday.
He really needed a fresh diaper.
I don't know why that stuck out to me.
That must mean that he had a dirty diaper
for days and days.
- I like how much these people are willing,
like the diaper mother talks about her kids constantly.
- And it's like you would think that you would just be,
like I'm not sure you need to delve into that all that much.
- At a certain point, I feel like being a diapered mother
is just Munchausen's.
- Yeah.
I was almost about to say the exact same thing.
- Munchausen's by proxy.
- He also broke a record, this guy,
in one of these posts about how many diapers
have you worn at once, and he put everyone to shame.
He said, "I put on an entire pack of deep ends pull-ups
"at once, 18 pull-ups, and it was just as thick
as five diapers that I normally wear.
- Sounds like they were a thin pull up there.
- That's a very, I think that's a--
- But five diapers, that's crazy.
- But isn't a pull up thinner than a diaper?
- I guess, yeah.
- But he usually wears five diapers.
I think that's a lot. - Oh yeah.
Damn, I didn't even process that.
- I feel like you could fit,
I feel like that's a pretty easy record to break.
- Yeah, let's do it. - Very few people
attempting that. - Yeah, I'll do it.
- Here's a guy who just posted,
I basically-- - Can you imagine,
can you imagine how mad the diaper community would be
if somebody, a non-diaper lover,
broke the diaper wearing world record?
- That's our new record?
How dare you, you swoop in.
- You piece of shit.
- You wear 19 pull-ups?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
- I didn't even get hard.
- I actually didn't even like it.
- I fucking hated it the whole time.
- God, if only I could wear 19 pull-ups.
- The only person who got hard was the Guinness Book checker
who was in my room watching me.
Okay, this guy posted in the diaper lover,
he started a forum post that was basically,
he was like, "I shit my pants in my room,
"should I get up and change?"
He wrote, "I'm lying on my side watching football, soccer.
"I pooped in my nappy halfway through the first half
"and I still haven't changed.
"I can tell it's big and the room now smells really of poo.
"Even though it's now halftime,
"I think it would take too long to clean up
"before the start of the second half,
"so I'll probably have to wait until the end of the game."
And someone writes,
(laughing)
- Someone write, wrote, writes.
- Writes this, "Well, if you're in your own home
"and all alone, then why hurry to clean up?
"Just hope there isn't an unexpected knock on your door."
He just wrote, "Just didn't like the smell.
"I stunk out the whole room."
(laughing)
They say your own poop doesn't smell as bad to you
as other people's, and he just wrote, "Mine does."
(laughing)
- I do like how many of the posts that I've seen
are just like, "I love shitting my pants.
"I can't stop shitting my pants.
"I do it all the time, but the smell is just--"
- Yeah, the smell is crazy.
- What part of it do they like, I guess?
- I guess it's the feeling of a full diaper.
- It must be the pleasure.
I know that, well we've talked about it before,
a couple of, some people shove bananas up their ass
and they shit the banana out.
- Some people put oatmeal in their diaper
and they just have a mealy feeling.
- Yeah, we talked about that one, yeah.
- Oh my god.
- I have something to read from this book,
which is called, it's about smell,
and I found it on the ground and it's covered in crap,
but I'll read that at the end, sort of as a, all right.
- I thought you never did Stinksgiving before, Pierce.
- You're a damn Stinksgiving pro.
Catch this in your mouth.
Okay.
- That was not even close to right.
- It was so close.
- Okay, so there's a concept called keyhole incontinence.
Have you guys heard of this?
- No, I have not. - No.
- Someone wrote, "I have pissed and shit myself
"on my front porch fumbling with my keys
"more than I care to count."
And someone wrote, "I called it keyhole incontinence,
"because if you're having a good day,
"walking to the door and putting that key in,
"it can create a big problem, LOL.
"My incontinence has come and gone for years,
"and to be honest, when I was doing okay
"out of diapers during the day,
"then that darn door was my arch nemesis.
"Driving home and seeing that house, bam,
all of a sudden I kinda need a bathroom.
Parking it out, now I really need a bathroom.
Start walking to the door, and with every step,
the anger in my guts gets more extreme,
and my bladders start screaming louder.
Key in hand, running through the house to the bathroom,
you're extremely concerned you won't make it,
and you soak the carpet in a streak all the way through.
Basically, they're running to the,
as soon as they see their house,
they're shitting their pants.
- They're shitting their pants,
and then tracking like shit liquid, like a slug.
- Another key, like sort of atomic level operation
in their digestive system is happening
with each ritual of coming into their own living quarters.
Key in the hole, you're--
- I have that.
- I was gonna say, I will, I will say,
not for shit, but definitely,
if I like maybe left a bar
and I should have gone to the bathroom before I did
and I didn't, I walked home
and I gradually have to pee more and more.
The second I'm into my front door,
but not at the bathroom yet, it's the--
- When I get drunk.
- Can you imagine actually leaving shit streaks
on the carpet?
No, I can't imagine that.
I can imagine that.
Not me.
I don't like it, but I can.
I'm using my imagination.
I just have a strong imagination.
The other day I got into the bathroom and I was like, "Oh, I have to shit pretty bad."
And as soon as I locked the door, it was so bad.
I had to shit so fucking bad.
And I said out loud to myself, "Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no."
And it was the hardest I've ever had to shit.
Actually, I had a similar thing like that recently where I had to go...
It's probably one of the first times I had to tell my girlfriend, "You have to stop talking
to me.
- She was trying to tell me something,
and I was like, you can't talk to me right now.
- It's over.
- I have to go in the bathroom.
Like I literally did, I just had to close the door.
- I do that every single day with my girlfriend.
Diarrhea, okay.
This person, there's only one good thing in this post
that I'll just skip to.
I always have to wonder about people who talk about
how good it is to feel in a diaper full of poop.
When my ulcerative colitis is flaring,
doing that would cause an almost immediate
and very painful rash, not to mention that my poop
looks and smells like blood.
(laughing)
I end up with my backside so sore that I have trouble
cleaning up after a bowel movement,
which is often every 15 to 30 minutes.
Somehow the appeal is just lost on me.
A wet diaper, I'll change the first chance I get.
A soiled diaper, I'll drop everything to clean immediately
and shower if I probably can.
I would feel this way too.
My bowel movements are pretty evil, painful,
not necessarily like a fun, sexy time.
- Like you're pooping and then spinning up the poop.
- Like I'm spiraling upward?
Like I'm creating a, yeah.
- You create a poop so big in the toilet
that you're sitting on top of it.
- Like it's rocket fuel?
- Yeah, like you're sitting on top
of the Dr. Strangelove rocket.
- Right, you know that rocket was,
you know that was a bomb going down?
- It's going down, but from the perspective.
- Right, if you're looking at it,
if you're watching it, it would be upside down.
That's a good point, Pat.
- I don't have sex.
I'm too often in baby head space.
It's just alien to me.
I think this is a really good idea.
(laughing)
- Okay, elaborate.
- I think that if you are so,
I think if the reason that you don't wanna have sex
is because you think you're a baby,
that means you have the right idea about sex and babies.
- Yeah. - So I--
- Oh yeah.
- That's what you should be--
- If you're gonna be an ABDL,
you should be completely sexless.
- Yes. - Yeah, no, I agree with you.
- You should have no genitalia.
- You should just like the feeling of poop
just 'cause you like it.
- That's right.
- Not 'cause it gets you harder, makes you sperm.
- I'm sick of these fuckers shitting themselves
to just pick up chicks.
- Basically, every time we've done this,
I have broadened my understanding of how all this works.
And this time I really did see so many people
who were talking about how it is a comfort thing for them
and not sexual at all.
That was way more common than I realized.
- One split that I noticed, that I noticed a lot,
but I noticed this time,
is what another person put in uh... is there's something i find is very funny
is there some stuff we're like
half of the half of diaper lovers like
love it and the other half think it's
the worst thing it like you had a bunch of poster about like eating while
pooping like sitting at the dinner table and eating and also put your pants at
the same time
and a bunch people like that's the best feeling in the world something going in
something coming out it's incredible but then just as many people are in there
saying you are a degenerate human being you are disgusting i hate you you should
- You shit all you want in your bed, but at dinner?
- Yeah, I know, it's crazy, right?
- You're ruining-- - There's one thing that--
- Get your elbows off the table.
- Literally people are saying, "You are a degenerate."
And it's like they're on the diaper,
like how, that's the one thing?
- I think having both ends of your tube
that is your whole life essence going like this
must be the pinnacle. - What the fuck
are you talking about?
- Your anus going like this and your esophagus
going like this at the same time--
- That has to do something to the middle.
- No, I agree, I feel like--
- It's a sharper thing.
- How does rubbing your foreskin compare
to your whole soul vibrating like this?
- A single tract that both ends
are orgasming at the same time.
- Yeah.
- And then you just--
- That's the weirdest thing I've ever heard you say.
- You are officially wheeled.
- You are a wheel though.
Okay, this is called Stinksgiving
and we're reading diaper posts.
- Yeah, and Pat says, "You're being weird."
- Just to anyone who's sort of snapped
into a calm-- - And we've been eating
guacamole out of diapers.
- No, all this was normal up until he talked about--
- Okay, well you look like a leprechaun.
- I don't look like a-- - You do.
- You do look like a leprechaun.
- Thank you, Caleb, for coming to my rescue.
- Yes, I got you.
You look exactly like a leprechaun.
- There's a green hat, there's a green pilgrim hat
over there I could put on.
- Oh, this is from the same post that I think Caleb,
or maybe, who found the post about being ridiculous
in a diaper? - That was me.
- Okay, yeah, this is on the same one.
Yes, completely.
I love how they feel, but when I look in the mirror
or if I happen to be around my partner,
I can't help but think, who would love this?
I'm a complete joke.
(laughing)
And someone says, I tend to avoid mirrors when I'm wearing,
generally because I violate an unwritten rule,
you should never wear both a nappy
and a mustache at the same time.
And someone wrote, mirrors equals diapers,
or mirrors plus diapers are kind of like the old
don't look in the mirror on acid rule.
- Do you think that's the level of kind of euphoria
you get from wearing a diaper?
- I think 100%. - Is it comparable
to being on acid?
- This is my actual other weird thought that I had, Patrick,
so cover your ears, but I think that a diaper
is probably like the totem that takes a human being
back to the point of like pure, like unencumbered joy.
It's like tripping on acid 'cause you're going back
into a place where there's no right and wrong.
It's just shit and piss and it's all gravy.
- I think-- - That wasn't weird at all.
That's probably the most normal thing
you've ever thought of. - Gravy is gone.
(laughing)
I'm a little hungry.
- I would be more inclined to agree with that,
and that being, that beautifully put idea,
if the people who post about wearing diapers
weren't some of the, like, obviously the most,
like the stupidest people in the universe.
- Well, it's not as if geniuses love to trip on acid,
either, you know?
- That's a good point.
That is a very good point.
- Some, oh, here we go.
Same Tina Slip now been peed in four times.
- I think Tina is a brand, I found.
Same Tina slip now been peed in four times.
I decided to poop in the potty monster, but not wife,
and smushed my diaper between my bum cheeks.
One more pee, it will be okay.
Another after that, it will leak.
So been pissing and shitting the same diaper
maybe four or five times in a row.
And they're actually smushing it.
- I did see the diapered mother posted a picture
that was a--
- That's gonna make it better.
- No, it's just fun.
- I didn't include the pictures from the diapered mother,
but I did look at almost every single one.
and one of them was she was like,
I'm so proud of myself,
I pooped in the same diaper four times in a day.
It was just the entire diaper was completely black.
(laughing)
- Completely black.
- I searched smush,
I don't know if you guys have guessed this yet.
I like sitting on the toilet with a diaper on and messing.
Sometimes after I go, I will stand up,
put the lid down, and sit back down
to smush the mess against me.
- Oh my God.
- Oh man.
- Why even sit on the toilet?
Just do it in a chair.
- Yeah.
- Just do it in a rocking chair.
- That's too far, you are invoking,
you shouldn't be anyone to toil with.
- I think a lot of people here have gone too far.
- Yeah, okay, so this is like,
what foods put you in a little mode?
This wrote, if I'm in little mode,
then grilled cheese and tomato soup.
If I'm in grown up mode,
then a whole lobster stuffed with crab meat.
(laughing)
- Grilled cheese when in little mode.
- Stuffing a lobster with crab meat
makes fucking no sense to me at all.
- It's a crabster.
(laughing)
I don't know what you mean.
- It's a lab.
- Yeah.
"I don't soil but love to watch my diaper when I pee.
"Fill with pee.
"At times I pull the front of my diaper forward
"and watch my little guy let the pee flow into the diaper.
"This can be a little messy at a time, but I love it."
- Diaper dude, watching my little man.
(laughing)
- "I can't read this, but I found a guy on here
"he posts really, here I'll read one of these.
"We'll read the lucky one.
"Yeah, this one should be fine.
Okay, someone wrote, "We are a diaper lover couple
"and we both wear diapers regularly,
"so yes, she does know."
And this is basically a married man
who has a wife who's cool with it.
And maybe we should eat our final dish while we wait this?
- No, we're saving it for after.
- No, we'll save it for the very end, I think.
Okay, we just eat it raw, that's fine.
That got to be good.
Do you guys just lay there smoking cigarettes while going?
Or is it much more intimate?
You can lay there like you do when you spoon.
in bed, feeling her just pushing her mess out,
while you just hugging her
as you wet the front of your diaper.
Then flip and she can feel his tummy.
Just get hard as he's loading his diaper
as you wet yours.
That sound fun.
Then just squish around
and smush that bulge with your knees.
Oh, I can think of a hundred things to do
while you both wet and messy.
One smells, which one smells worse than the other?
Does either one get run out by the other?
I bet the both of you are a lot tighter,
closer to each other than normal couples.
And the big question,
do you change each other or shower together?
Washing each other up and nice and clean,
and then you are nice and dry,
and it feels like the perfect time,
as you know so much about each other,
to just have a heated, hot, and heavy session
with each other.
Do you change and powder each other before?
It's good night fun.
Good night, sweetie.
- Oh my god, that honestly is so romantic.
- Well, all of his posts are like this.
- I love playing which one smells worse than the other.
- That is so beautiful.
- Do you ever lay in bed and think
which one smells worse?
- It's me.
- Also, squishing the mess with your knees,
that's too, that's--
- Yeah. - How'd it get down there?
- You're gonna make poop wine.
- No, that's your behind, or you bring your knees--
- Squish it up, stomp it. - You bring your knees
up to squish it?
- Yeah. - Oh my god.
- Stomping on the diaper, making poopy wine.
- Yeah.
- Oh, this is a real quick one.
This guy is giving advice to a guy
whose wife doesn't know that he wears a diaper.
I'm only gonna read one part.
He just wrote, "Maybe you could go to a doctor,
comma, who deals in fetishes, comma,
but that's whole, comma, different problem, comma."
I mean, I went through a whole different problem
when I got put in a diaper.
It was not something I was looking for.
It was a sentence, a place I don't want to be.
But once I got there, I just had to sort of take it
one rotten day after another.
So that's what I can tell you.
What is the draw?
The diapers are using them both.
You have yourself a real fix.
All I can say is good luck.
- Oh my God. - Oh, that is a good book.
- This person is a poet.
- Yeah.
- Is that the end of your gift?
- That's the end of my gift.
I mean, I would read all of his posts all day,
but they're too small to read from here.
- Read the, can you read your book?
What is this book that you brought?
- This is a book about smell that I found on the grounds.
There's all kinds of awesome chapters.
- You found this on the ground?
- Yeah, all kinds of awesome chapters in here,
like the influence of Christianity
and the devaluation of the sense of smell and odors.
- Wow.
Have you thought maybe you could order
the full book at some point?
- It's very rare, it's a rare book.
- Really? - I can't find it online.
Okay, so this is from a chapter
called The Philosophical Nose,
and this is just a quick passage,
I think, from the writings of Freud.
The desire for cleanliness emerges
from the pressing need to get rid of excretia
that have become disagreeable to the sense of smell.
We know that this is not true in the case of infants
who are not repelled by them.
Education exerts special care to accelerating the passage
to the succeeding stage at which excretia lose any value
and become the object of disgust and repugnance
and are therefore rejected.
Such a depreciation would be impossible
if the strong odor of such matter drawn from the body
were not subjected to the same fate
as other olfactory impressions that were also foregone
as man began to walk upright.
Thus, anal eroticism is the first victim
of the organic repression that occurs
along the road to civilization.
Wow.
And that is what I'm stinkful for.
I'm stinkful that we don't have snouts and that our sense of smell is so muted
that we can actually be in this room with each other even though all this food is
clearly spoiled. Speaking of food, do you mind if I open this last one? Please open the last one.
I mean, okay guys, this is the very last meal that we have. Hold his mic up for him, Pat.
it this one is as you may know a thanksgiving this is probably the number
one tradition this is the of stanks can I have all for my this is the turkey of
Thanksgiving right the most important and we all met what we did all make it
together we all made this together
Traditionally you go no spoon here.
[LAUGHTER]
It's my turn.
Just go directly in on that.
Yeah.
OK, now Cameron, it's your turn.
Yeah, oh man, that's good stuff.
I mean, and that is creamy.
It's so creamy.
Patrick, it's Thanksgiving.
OK, you have to-- yep, all right.
Very quickly now, he's gonna drink himself.
- I'm a little bit dribbly.
- Oh, that's okay.
- You want me to get it from the microphone?
- Some of my...
(laughing)
There you go, Pat.
Dig in, buddy.
- That's so funny to have dessert.
(laughing)
- No, you gotta put it,
no, you gotta really get yourself in there.
Come on, come on.
There we go.
Oh man.
- And if I can get a closeup for a second.
If you guys are mad at us about what we just did,
I'm gonna get a real, my actual close-up.
If you're mad at us about what we just did...
Nobody can hear you.
If you're mad at us about what we just did,
I wanna show you the food item
for today that didn't make the cut.
That did not get put into a diaper.
Let's put it in a diaper for shits and giggles.
We saw that!
That is mashed potatoes.
And we said no.
Alright, alright.
Knock it off.
That is awful.
Sorry.
Oh, God.
But this is what you wanted.
What kind of potato could that possibly be?
[LAUGHTER]
Fuck.
This is--
Happy Stinksgiving, everybody.
Happy Stinksgiving.
And we'll see-- I mean, and we'll see you guys next year.
Yeah.
[KISSING NOISES]
Bye.
Caleb, get your kiss.
(laughing)