(upbeat music)
- Put it down.
- Put that thing down.
- Put the knight like that.
- Why are you holding it?
- You're gonna break it.
- That's supposed to be on the table.
- You were gonna break it.
- That doesn't make sense if you're, just put it down.
- I'm supposed to put that down.
- Put that down.
- Whatever.
- You guys are already ruining the sleepover?
- I am not ruining it at all.
- No, if anyone was ruining it,
it was just you holding that up in the air.
- If anyone was ruining it,
It was this guy who thinks that a mascot costume is pajamas.
It's not.
It's my pajamas.
Those look cozy.
And they are cozy.
Those look really--
It is a little hard to get up and pee in these
in the middle of the night.
Well, luckily for you, we're not
going to be having to get up and pee in the middle of the night
resting up all the way till motherfucking midnight tonight.
Motherfucking midnight o'clock.
The witching hour.
Julio, what time is it right now?
Can we get a time check really quick?
7 PM.
7 PM, baby.
That's right. We're staying all the way up till midnight tonight.
All night long. What do you guys want to do?
Living up to midnight.
Oh, that's good.
Sleeping after that.
Damn.
Living up to midnight with a cat.
Because you wear a cat outfit.
Is this going to be the latest that either of you have ever stayed up?
No, I stayed up till eight in the morning.
Yeah.
I stayed up till 2 a.m. at 3.
I was doing drugs.
What the hell, you're doing drugs at our age, man?
I was doing a lot of drugs.
Bro, we're in eighth grade.
I know, I'm the bad kid.
What the hell are you talking about?
Damn.
Uh-huh, I was doing drugs like sticky note.
No way, don't tell me you did toothpaste.
I did, you know what I did?
What?
I put a sticky note up here and then immediately after
'cause that, I mean, my tolerance is so high.
What?
What, dude, it's a slumber party.
Have you guys tried deodorant yet?
It's fucking awesome dude, check this out.
My mom said I have to wear that stuff?
I'm seriously gonna fucking get kissed now.
I don't fuck with it.
Try it dude, hit this.
No dude.
Oww!
You hurt our friend!
Jubio!
It's not that big of a deal.
You crip.
Jubio!
It's just a can of deodorant.
It's only 7pm and you're already like...
Oh my god, wait, wait, I just noticed these.
Cameron, show everybody your slippers.
Oh yeah, wait, we do have to have a little bit of a pajama check.
Yeah, my tolerance is so high though I smoked banana peels
to answer your question before I was interrupted.
- You actually did. - Holy crap.
- I smoked a banana peel and I got--
- So you got the Bruins PJs on.
- Bruins pajamas, but what I'm looking at here
are these amazing slippers.
- Kind of Chinese style slippers.
- They're Chinese.
- Now show us that T-shirt, boy.
- Yeah.
- I tested positive for Swag 19.
Where'd you get that?
- My mom bought it for me for school, back to school.
- Mad ass.
- I'm gonna smell like this all day.
- Smell like what?
Fucking adulthood? - I'm gonna smell like Agus.
where's my secrets by the end of the night
i have a what do you guys think girls like
uh... they select with the
like so i think we'll see what what what what what what what what what what what
what what what what what what what what what what what what what what what what
and they wait there put it in but with the same toilet paper you know you're
all the nice is that true
on
it's not a shot is that it not it i have a uh... to some of what can
gay ass shit that I don't even fucking agree with.
- Oh, I bet you jizz on that too.
- I jizz just to jizz it.
- He's having sex with it like, oh, oh, oh, oh.
- And I bet when you, 'cause you just learned to jack off,
I bet you jizz in your shirt and throw it under your bed.
- I do that outside of the world of the podcast.
I still jack, I'll jizz into a t-shirt.
Every once in a while.
- I think you're supposed to.
- If it's the end of the t-shirts,
kinda, you know, if I'm worn it 14, 15 times,
I'm not gonna wear it again before I wash it.
I'm jizzing into one of those.
Then I'll jizz into it and throw it in the hamper.
One of those APC white t-shirts that are over, like,
the really long ones.
I jizzed into the raw denim I just bought.
Yeah, that's how you break it in.
You get in the bathtub, you just jizz it in 5,000 times.
Just stretch it out.
But to answer your question, yeah,
I basically use this as a complete cum rag.
Do you want to smell it?
Actually, a hack that you can use when you're jizzing--
Oh, it's so crunchy.
--if you jizz straight into the washing machine,
it goes away.
- Then all your shirts will get jizzed up.
- No, no, it sucks it all out.
- Yeah, it just cleans it.
I mean, it's a cleaning machine.
- That's actually a good point.
If I jizz in all my shirts,
'cause I've done three jizzes in one shirt before.
(laughing)
If I jizz in my shirt a bunch of times,
then I take it to the laundromat I go to, which is public,
is there like people who are getting their clothes done
and they get tiny little speckles of my jizz in there?
- Oh yeah, you probably, somebody probably--
- No, so you know what it is?
Is these laundromats nowadays,
they have they have lint traps, but a lot of these places are advanced.
They have lint traps in the dryers, but in the washers, they have jizz traps,
which are these little, it's a little bucket that they pull out.
Do you know? And it's like you pull it out and it's like a drawer.
That's like a tray.
Oh, that's like a gray water?
Uh-huh. Yeah, and they pull that out. And what a lot of these, I mean,
I don't want to be the one to break this to you, but they're selling that.
They're selling the jizz?
Yeah, they sell it to like many places.
Well, it gets diluted.
They sell it to women's shelters for single women who want to have a baby,
But they can't cuz men can't be around I'm a Christian and that's fucking human trafficking
That is true as fuck
That is true as fuck dude. Can you imagine our eighth grade asses being getting to sneak into the women's shelters? Oh?
My god, I bet it's so hot in there. I what I was in seventh grade
I set up a GoPro in the women's shelter that is I bet it is so hot in there pillow fights every single night
pillow fights
(laughter)
- Oh my god dude, we should dress in all black
and wear our night vision goggles and go in there.
- Yes, and sneak in.
- Crawl through the vents.
- Be awesome dude.
- I saw they do that in movies.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I saw it at a Tom Cruise movie.
- That's my main thing.
- Patrick's tell me things is hot when girls cry.
He said that.
- I did not say that.
- Yeah, you said that in Mrs. Marfanee's class.
- Mrs. Marfan's class?
This is my fans.
Remember when the reason they have that syndrome.
She should have been a Hooper.
Remember you said.
Remember last year before he got a little more mature and he would chase the girls.
Yeah.
I was on my finger.
He said that he wants to show the girls again in a few years.
Yeah.
I think I'm going to have bigger.
That's why you don't have a way bigger boogers when I'm older.
You said that's why you want to get a learner's permit.
So you're better at chasing girls.
Yeah.
You said you your dad let you watch the movie duel.
It's about it's this movie no one knows about no
I'm an eighth grader, and I watched that movie on TV. You're essentially the nerdy movie kid right okay first of all
I'm not a nerd and second of all we're in a grade
We're in eighth grade and movies are cool back now Simon and a double Alvin mm-hmm - did you guys?
Golden compass fuck no that
That's why I think it's cool. No dude. No, that's fuck. I missed it now. I missed that DAP and now it's on camera
that I missed the DAP. Yep, you have been, you have been, and that's on
Cameron. Just a thing I've been saying. You are no longer an Alvin, you are now a
Timon. You're a Timon. It sucks because I have to do all these fucking singing things now. Yeah, you're a Timon. I gotta eat a bug.
You used to be, you used to be fully Pumba. When you were big, you were like,
honestly. You are a hundred percent. I'm glad we weren't doing video then.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm glad that we weren't doing it. We would have needed a bigger camera. Yeah.
Yeah, the file sizes would be too big no one to be able to download the show. Yep.
Yeah, I'm really glad that we weren't doing video back when I had that brown
birth marker on my mouth. Oh yeah. That was bad. Yeah. Yeah, I really like the show, but
This guy eat poop all the time. I know yeah, that would have been bad
That would have been horrible if we ate poop on camera. Yeah, luckily we never did that
You know and we got basically all the tools to stay up all night. We got some cherries seven up. Yeah
It's fucking caffeine free. Are you are you double fucking kidding me? Well mom is a slut she fucked up everything
I said get red Mountain Dew this bitch got seven up y'all put seven fingers up your ass you fucking old, baby
Yeah, you're gonna be excellent fingers up your mom's ass extra fucking fucking kidding me
Yeah, fuck you mom and honestly said he's gonna put seven fingers up his mom's ass. Can I get that can I get my camera?
Hey, dad dad you too dad
You up yeah, yeah, hey, can I get my camera?
Do I have a camera nope this is you have to I don't have a
Living with my uncle right now because of my behavior problems that makes sense
They kind of got you out of the house pretty fast, but luckily we got a lot of slumber party. Yeah
Two things I need to say before I mean I know we're not gonna sleep, but if we do fall asleep
Speak for yourself. I ain't sleeping. Yeah, no way if I all the way till midnight, okay?
I'm just well. Here's a warning I get very violent night terrors, okay
Combined with sleepwalking. What do you guys think the hardest penis could ever be?
probably a diamond penis
From it from from rock man or colossus from x-men's rock man, and he's gay, too
What do you guys want to do? I'm in eighth grade, and I don't understand that yet
Oh, yeah, well, I don't know anybody I was I was held back
I'm supposed to be a freshman a gay man held you know
I'm supposed to be a guy held your back. I'm supposed to be a freshman, and that's why I have a mustache
He held your back up. Yeah, and that's how you know about diamond penis. Yeah
I got fucked with a diamond penis.
- Oh my god.
- By a gay guy.
- If I guess if I had to get fucked with a penis,
I might as well be a diamond one.
- 'Cause you'd feel like a pretty princess.
- That's prestigious.
- Oh, hmm.
- Actually got fucked with a diamond penis.
- I would choose a big one.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, or no, a small one.
- Probably.
- I'd choose a middle of the road.
- Right, average.
- I would say about the end of my life.
- I'd choose one that was just right.
- I'd choose whatever one's nearby
so I don't have to wait.
- Yeah.
That'd be the piss me off.
Well, that's just like you're sitting there like,
"I know I'm gonna get fucked."
Yeah, yeah.
"When is this gonna happen?
"When are they gonna find a guy with a diamond penis?"
Could be years.
Probably not, not ever, yeah.
What time are we at?
What time is it right now?
Oh my God.
It's already 8 p.m.?
It's 8 o'clock.
It's going so fast, you guys.
I feel like we should get into some slumber party fare.
Okay, all right.
So obviously we have our chips,
which by the way, these are red spicy chips.
Everybody has to do a one chip challenge.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
'Cause I've been eating these the whole time.
Get a close up on Caleb doing his one chip challenge.
Oh my god.
How is it?
Oh, it's so salty!
Okay, can I do my chip challenge now?
Oh, it's so spicy!
Wait, you missed your face.
No, I ate it.
I can handle it.
Are these ketchup chips?
I don't know.
These taste like ketchup.
What slumber party games do you guys want to play?
guys want to do truth or dare? Okay dude I feel like that's kind of sixth grade but
okay. Okay well then what's your fucking idea? Sometimes you got to
appreciate the classics. Okay I have this app on my phone or my iPod touch that is
uh I don't have a phone yet that is um has all these kinds of truth or dares and
stuff and I was thinking maybe we could do some of these like so do you want
Easy, hard, or extreme and hot?
Extreme.
Well...
I...
Alright, Cameron, you're up first.
He was about to say something, so...
Easy, hard, extreme, and hot?
Um...
Let's start with easy.
Okay, we'll start with easy.
Truth or dare?
Pfft...
Truth.
Okay, truth.
If you have 10 hours to live, what do you do?
[Laughter]
That was easy!
That's easy as fuck!
I probably get a bit a million dollars and I'd spend all my money all my allowance that I saved I'd spend it and
I would get exactly what I wanted really yeah remote-control woolly mammoth whoa
With actual rubber skin damn articulating yeah partially wheels on the feet
Don't like Power Rangers
Fucking baby, and I don't like it either. Yeah, okay, so it's your okay, so truth or dare to somebody okay, Patrick
Well first of all I guess what do you see hard or extreme and hot extreme and hot like the chips extreme and hot
Okay, if you say so you can handle it truth or dare
Come on. I know you're a dare guy don't even trade Joe
- Dare, okay, let's see.
- Extremely hot dare.
- You give someone but not your partner
a sensual body massage, start at feet and work your way up.
(laughing)
- All right, put 'em on the table.
- Okay, who's it gonna be?
- Well, it's obviously the person who asked.
- I think it's gotta be the person who asked.
- It says not your partner, and we're kind of partners
'cause I asked, so it's kind of like a partner to work to.
- No, you have it at a sensual body massage.
- No, it's you.
- You told me, come on.
- How is it me?
- 'Cause we're partners, you're on the table.
- You have slippers on.
- Uh-uh, get those slippers.
take them off your feet. Get your slippers off and put your feet on the table. You don't
want to touch my feet. Put your feet on the table right now. You really don't want to
touch my feet. He wants to. You know what? He gets the daily double dare. You have the
daily double dare. Fuck. You fucking asshole. Yep, daily double dare for you. And it has
to be extreme and hot. Okay. You have an extremely hot dare coming your way because you wouldn't
get a sensual massage. Oh boohoo. It's against the rules of the game. It's not against the
fucking rules you asked that. It's against the rules. It's against the rules to not do
- Can I click it?
It doesn't, you have to send it.
- Okay, I'll do it.
- It's tech, this is mine, I guess, technically.
- An extreme and hot dare, okay?
Here it is.
- This is the dare.
What is your favorite sex position?
(laughing)
Click dare, that's what came up.
- Okay.
- Try to do another one, he's got a double.
- No, that, you can't get a, you can't, no, no, no, no, no.
You can't get two.
That's not fair. I already wasn't even supposed to have this.
It was your dare, first of all. You're the one who didn't do it.
Because you... No, I didn't refuse. You could do it right now. I'm right here.
Get your feet on the table. I'm sitting right here. He's the one not doing the dare.
I was about to answer that question, but now we're having a war.
Okay, war is over because I declared it and I'm God in the scenario.
Okay, more like I'm God and I declared it.
War is over. No, I already declared the war was over.
War is back.
No, we don't want the war back.
He's fighting it.
He started a war.
I'm completely...
He obeyed.
And now you know what?
I'm on his side.
Oh my god, Caleb just obeyed me.
Okay, I just became a Buddhist style not guy.
So I just say no to everything and crap like that.
Okay, what are we doing?
So you...
That's one of the Buddhist boosts invented, saying not.
They go, "Nah."
Yeah, I'm definitely going to do something.
Nah, I'm going to sit here and do nothing.
You have to answer the question, "What's your favorite sex position?"
Yeah, I bet you haven't even fucking had sex, you kid, because you're a little kid.
Uh, mine would probably be...
I'm gonna have soda and there's nothing you can do.
I like, I like...
It's too hard to open!
Um...
You cheated.
I'm trying to answer the question.
Sorry.
Mine's probably like, on the couch.
Okay.
On the couch or in the bed.
My two top, my top two.
You have to hold your mic up.
That's actually good as fuck.
Don't spit it out. No it didn't
Your voice is so deep for a child. It went up my nose
What's your favorite you said I said couch or bed
Okay, smart. That's not a position. Those are my top two that I've had doggy
doggie style
missionary, okay
I like both of those dirty Sanchez a
kid, yeah, I
Like I like oh no you know what I like what a girl flashes from her dress
Like from underneath or from above reaches up her pulls her dress over and shows you all of it
It's not so you like your favorite sex position is mooning when your girl shows pulls up her dress and shows it all
Every last piece of it every piece every it's as if she's completely naked under her dress. Yeah, I actually like that, too
Okay, can it be my turn to do a truth or dare? Yeah, I choose hard
Okay, oh, so my penis is and I choose truth
Okay hard maybe dare, that's I'd click truth
What if if you may name your job title? What wouldn't it be? Oh?
My god, and he has to say
Has to answer this oh my god. This shit is so fucked up at the slumber party recently
What is it again if you may name your job title? What wouldn't it be?
Gross
But cool that was actually cool. Yeah, fuck and that makes me want to drink even more soda
I would say that so my job title, so I don't have a job because I'm a child so maybe adult would be
Basically the opposite of what I actually should we do we all answer this now
Sure, if you want to answer you've done it. I guess my job went my job wouldn't it be yeah would be
Probably fucking cop
You want to be a cop cuz cops are actually like yeah, I want to be I like cops in eighth grade
Can you can we just see just for or a doctor or fireman?
I don't have to do it, but can we see what the day would have been Rex?
Can we see what the dare would have been yeah?
See what a hard dare would have been hard. He's not bumping in like
Chat with your crush in front of tow hers
HERS
You know it's in front of others tow her oh it says tow hers, so you read it as it's written can tow tow hers
Can you come here?
Tell hers I was towers in the studio. I don't think so
So the thing is the lucky for me is that first of all I don't have to do that because I already did my truth
But also I don't have a crush because I haven't started thinking about that kind of stuff really I have a crush
No, no, I can't tell you
For it I didn't get his turn
No, it's his turn. No you have to you know I know it's him a truth
So you asked him a truth, but then in the order. Oh, no he gets to pick whoever goes next
He gets to pick who is asking truth or dare I
Pass my thing on to Patrick so that you either dare
Dare, I dare you to tell us your crush. No, no, you can't do that. You can do that
that
Answer it right now
Amy Adams
She's fucking hot and I think she's poor. It's she's poor. It's wife. She's around our age man of steel
Yeah, or its wife. She could
I've well real-life borette
What really no that's I don't like her anymore very much
Why she's married Isla Fisher is Sasha Baron Cohen's wife right yeah, I get them confused
They are pretty easy to confuse who's that other bitch
So you get confused with Jessica Chastain all the time that was in Jurassic World
I stylus they look the exact same look the exact so scary man. They look exactly I have a crush on her, too
I have a crush on all the female ladies and celebrity Hollywood the ones with red hair. I love all starlets. Yeah
I love every freaking porn star because I'm nasty.
Yeah, my crush is basically every porn star
mixed together. Riley Reid and
Lana Roode. Scientists have finally made my crush.
Take the average of every porn star ever. This is what her body
would look like. It's just a piece of fudge.
Oh man.
What time is it?
What's the time right now?
Yeah, what time are we at?
Oh!
We're at 9,000.
Bro, it's about to get so fucking late.
Yeah.
Okay, real quick, what's your favorite fucking curse word?
Double fuck.
What's a double fuck?
It's a double the amount.
It's that double the badness of fuck.
F-F-U-U-C-C-K.
No, you say double fuck and it means it's twice as bad.
So your parents hurt you twice.
I'm just being weird over here.
My favorite curse word?
What?
one that I learned from watching British TV.
- What is it?
- It's twat.
(laughing)
- What does that even mean?
- That sounds like Dr. Seuss's book name.
- And you know what twat means?
- What?
- Vagina.
- Fucking crap.
- Wait, a vagina?
- Yeah.
- Fuck that.
- Uh huh.
- No thank you.
- Yeah, and I saw someone say twat waffle.
- Did you guys know I was looking--
- I saw somebody say cunned.
- Did you guys know if you look in the dictionary
for vagina under B, you can see a picture of it?
- For real?
- Can you, Jubio, can you pull up a picture of a--
- Can you go to the dictionary?
of a vagina you know a vagina you're spelling it right no no no no no wait
wait wait it's spelled vagina yeah no it's cuz in in Spanish B is V or V is B
oh that's why okay there we go vagina what's in the images okay so pull this
oh dude I have a crush on her she's actually bad as fuck oh my god Wow do
you think she would like want to hang out at our sleepover if we use a shirt
Here she'd be singh our DS and fucking one-second flash. He looks like such. What do you think?
What do you have tail in my boy? What do you think slutty is girl in our entire grade?
In our grades
Wow yeah look up your yearbook picture here it is I heard I heard the sluttiest girl at our school is mrs.
Mr. Raduchowski.
This is her.
Oh, Mrs. Raduchowski, honestly, for a teacher, pretty hot.
Yeah.
Yeah, she is a little bit hot.
The sluttiest person I know at the school is Janitor Rick.
Yeah.
Also, I don't want to brag, but the sluttiest person at school is actually me.
Damn!
That's why my mom hates when I fucking hang out with you, but I'll pound it because she's
not here.
Yeah.
Do we have any-- do you guys want to do anything else?
He's like a slut for guys.
As a guy.
He's a guy slut.
I'm a man slut.
A man-- Whoa.
- Have you guys seen Deuce Bigalow, Eurachia?
- They based that movie off my dad.
- You're friends with him on Facebook, me too.
He's, every week he's got a new relationship status.
He goes one week single, one week he's dating Jessica.
It's complicated with Jessica, single again.
Then married to Ashley, then married to Denise.
Married to, he gets married to all these women on Facebook.
And then they have to get a divorce.
And cousins with Sarah.
Do you guys wanna do--
One time he was dating his Facebook cousin.
Do you guys wanna do Would You Rather?
Yeah. Yeah.
All right.
Who wants to start?
Would you rather,
would you rather have,
would you rather eat poop made out of cream cheese?
Yes, I'd eat that.
(laughing)
- Yeah, uh-huh.
Keep going.
Poop made out of cream cheese or what?
- Poop made out of cream cheese
or pee made out of sour cream?
Oh my god, I didn't know you were gonna finish the sentence.
(laughing)
- I didn't know there was a second part
to the would you rather.
That was just the first part.
GBO, can you look up some would you rathers for us to play?
Nobody answered mine.
Okay, I would rather eat poop made out of cream cheese.
Of course, dude.
Would you rather question--
Wait, would it still--
Would you rather have sex with the most disgusting girl
on the planet or have $1 only?
Okay, I have some that I wrote myself.
Okay.
Okay, guys, these are pretty badass for a slumber party.
Okay, okay, okay, go, go, go.
Would you rather be a lion or a tiger?
Tiger.
Why?
I'm striped.
Oh yeah, that'd be cool.
I'd be a lion.
Would you rather have a playhouse or a trampoline?
Trampoline.
Bro!
I would rather have a playhouse.
We say bro in 8th grade.
I would rather have a playhouse so I could do girls inside my playhouse.
Oh, that's nasty but actually fucking sick.
Would you rather never use a dildo again or never use a vibrator again?
Probably never use a dildo again.
Yeah, I would choose that too. Yeah. Would you rather have it in the morning or late into the evening?
Well, what is that about? I think it's probably dinner.
Oh, I would have dinner in the morning.
I don't want dinner in the morning. Steak and eggs?
That's breakfast.
That's a good point. I've been eating that for dinner for so long.
Would you rather discover I was a sex offender or a drugs addict?
Drugs addict.
Sex offender? But a drug addict. You're a sex offender?
No, I can't be a sex offender.
I thought you just said you're a sex offender. He's a sex offender.
Fucking 13. How can you be a sex offender when you're 13? That's what I'm saying dude. Shut the fuck up and stop spreading rumors.
You're one of the five year olds? You're fucking a gossip and I bet you hang out at the lunch table with all the-
I was fucking a gossip at lunch one time. Damn! Gossiping girl. Shut the fuck up.
Would you rather sleep with someone you think is disgusting but the sex is off the charts or sleep with a person you're find extremely hot but the sex sucks?
I would want to do both.
I would love to have disgusting sex with a fucking ugly bitch.
(laughing)
- As an eighth grader, that is my dream.
- Sounds like onage.
- I also never want to do drugs or alcohol
'cause I think God has a purpose for me.
(laughing)
- There's no doubt in my mind that one day
God will make you a CEO or a fucking--
- Or maybe I'll have to go to war
and I'll turn the tide of the battle.
- And maybe you'll be like David Goliath.
- If I drink, I'll like fall, my body will be sick.
- I think that one day I'm gonna smoke one cigarette
and then never smoke a cigarette again.
And it'll be on the news.
- Yeah, when I'm 18, I'm gonna buy a pack of cigarettes.
I'm not gonna smoke them, but you just,
you get the privilege.
I'm gonna buy a pack of cigarettes,
I'm gonna give them to a hobo.
- I think when I'm 70, I'll probably start doing
like heroin and crack and shit.
- DMT.
- Yeah, DMT. - Bro, DMT.
- Because it's like, at that point,
it doesn't fucking matter about--
- Yeah, it's like, I might as well be fucking dead
when I'm 70.
- By the time you're 50 or 30?
- I'd be like, to all my kids and grandkids,
I'd be like this, fuck this, I'm out.
Yeah, I probably killed myself.
I'd slit my throat in the bathtub.
Here's a would you rather.
OK.
Would you rather have bad breath or smelly private parts?
Smelly private parts.
Look.
I smell--
Because my mom don't smell my private parts,
but she'll kick my ass if she smells my private parts.
Yo, your mom smells my private parts, though.
[EXPLOSION]
Holy cow.
All right.
That's OK, because you know that she's a fucking pediatrician,
so that's probably part of her job is when she has you--
Yeah, she does smell my private parts.
--in the appointment.
So it's not that big of a deal.
At the appointment.
I put her on the paper table.
Would you rather have a premature--
- A premature-- - When Caleb's mom
is working at the pediatrician's office,
I put her on the paper table that they have there,
and she gets so wet it turns to papier-mache.
- Would you rather have a premature climax
or never climax at all?
- What's that?
- I don't know, I'm just reading it.
- Oh, that's the thing-- - Premature is like what?
- Oh, premature is when-- - The climax is that thing
on top of the vagina that girls want you to lick.
- Oh. - Yeah.
- Wait, and a premature is like a baby
who's born early, right?
So it's asking, why would a website, why would you ask that?
That's fucking disgusting as shit.
I'm fucking, what's this?
Is this what Climax is?
Pull this open.
Yeah.
Oh, we found it.
Oh.
That's what it is.
It's like when you get really close to your friend's face.
That's not that crazy.
I can Climax with you right now.
I'll Climax with Patrick.
I wanna Climax with you now, Cameron.
That's not that bad.
That's normal.
I don't mind having that at all.
I don't like that premature.
I'm not matching with my friends.
Look, I'm still not, my body's not mature.
I'm still growing.
I'm not mature either.
Yeah.
So I guess we all just had a premature climax.
I have one curly, swirly pube.
Yeah.
It's half white, half black.
Are you guys uncut or cut?
What?
I got halfway.
What are you talking about?
Your penis is halfway cut.
Yeah, they interrupted the procedure.
Someone ran in like at a wedding.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
They said forever hold your peace.
Do you guys, does it stink when you pull it back?
- Mine doesn't pull back.
Mine's already professionally pulled back by a doctor.
- Oh, okay, so yours is cut off.
- Or they taped it or something.
- I have half stink.
- Okay, so when you pull back the half part--
- Spiders.
- You get a spider comes out.
- Yeah, I put a coin in there.
- When I was camping.
- I put a coin in there to,
I put a coin in my foreskin to stop the pee from coming out.
Do you guys like camping even?
I hate camping.
I don't like it.
I think it's fucking overrated.
Yeah, it's like get me back home where I can play Monopoly.
The computer's at home.
Wait, the clock just ticked again.
Oh my god.
Guys, it's 10.
Holy shit.
Now this is what I would call, we were in like pre, like normal night.
This is what I would call late night now.
Late night, yeah.
Let's get late night.
This is when TVs start turning off and stuff.
I mean, I actually have something that I wanted to share with you guys.
Really?
Yeah.
- Did you say that to me?
- You did not just say that.
- Wait, to me?
- I didn't mean that.
- To me?
- I meant whip out the thing that you wanna show me.
- Do you know that's when a baby has had a seed
goes into the woman's stomach and it grows.
- What are you talking about?
Just open up your thing.
- It's like a garden in there.
- What the fuck is on there?
- Apparently a woman has a pot inside her that grows.
- Are you like, did you like--
- It's like the mandrakes from Harry Potter.
- Do you like not even know anything about sex ed
from class, you fucking asshole?
That's why a woman can suck the thing,
'cause it gets dirt off of it and it goes into her stomach.
He said that when--
You guys literally don't know anything about sex.
The whole thing of sex that I learned in school
is you basically want the smallest pussy of all time
to make you cum faster so you can make
as many fucking kids as possible.
Make you fucking-- I thought I'd shoot it
all in the butt. Apparently,
if a pussy is really fucking small,
it'll make you fucking cum instantly.
(laughing)
If the pussy is like the size of a fucking molecule,
like guys love fucking coming what if there was a pussy the size of a
molecule there is a smile and what if my dick was the size of uh...
all the way around the planet i heard i was a hundred miles pussy was a big cave
i heard and and megan fox is a pussy the size of a fucking and i heard it looks
like this in their now
now it doesn't shows that you got hurt this was what how you this is how you
know what the city's open
This is my mom's pussy and this crap is your mom's pussy.
Who?
This stinky green shit.
That's your mom's pussy?
I've heard that.
This is how you tell what a pussy would look like.
Do that again.
This your mom's pussy?
There's probably something like that.
I haven't seen it.
Bro, you ripped it in half!
You fucking killed my mom!
You ripped her legs off!
Fuck.
You ripped my mom's legs off.
You ripped her clean down the middle.
That was fucking disgusting.
Okay, well, right.
Show us your 10pm surprise.
Okay, I have something, so.
I actually.
Soda check!
Alright, okay. Hold on.
I could drink the whole bottle if I had to.
Drink, oh, chugging contest!
Chugging contest.
Chug it!
Guys, I have to pee.
I'll have to, you put the diabetes shot in my stomach.
Guys, don't make me laugh anymore, because I'm going to pee in my bag.
Oh, we should make him pee with a tickle.
with a tickle. Don't! I actually have to pee. I think you guys are gonna make me climax!
Stop! I heard that's mommies and daddies do to make a baby. Damn. They tickle first and
it gets them in the mood. Woah, what the fuck is that? Don't look yet, don't look yet. What
the fuck is that? Okay, I'll show you. I fucking can't wait to climax with my wife when I'm
older. So, I went into my big sister's bedroom. Oh. Damn! And I stole her diary. Did you get
You're naked - no, that's my sister, so I don't want to see that
This is you would look at his sister. I'm fucking look at my own fucking
Realize she's fucking gross dude. She's so annoying and she's teenager is I would literally X teenager is sincerely
I would love to look at my sister's fucking naked body at just one time
Just because a curiousness
So the house of all brothers hold on what I have to I have to unlock
unlock. I have to unlock. I got I stole the key to check this out.
Damn. Did you hide that in your panties? No, this was actually
her thong.
Yeah, there's a thong she wore. Is that her underwear? That's a
G. I heard it's called a G string a key string guys. She's
like you wouldn't like her. She's so annoying. She drinks
And it stunts her that probably makes her fucking pussy stink. I would love to smell it probably smells like diet coke down there
Okay, you just open it up. Yeah, you just unlock it
You're a fucking tard open
Now okay, you know how to open it. You're just being a fucking bitch for no reason
How to check that
Check out that soda
Stop why is it so hard for you to drink?
Why? That makes no sense.
I keep squeezing the soda bottle.
Oh my god, you broke- she's gonna fucking know!
What are you doing?
She's gonna know!
I couldn't open it with the key!
You ripped the fucking cover off!
We have to get a new one. Guys, we have to get a new one.
I don't even know where to buy stuff.
Do you have any fucking money? I don't have shit.
I have five dollars.
Wait, we could sell the soda.
We could sell the soda.
We could sell what's in it to a journalist.
Tell us what's in that.
Read it to us.
Okay, let's see what the first one is here.
Oh boy.
Dear Diary, I have a huge crush on a cute boy.
Also Cameron shat his pants again.
We're not going to read this one.
What?
Wait, just go back.
No, go back to that.
We're going to move.
No, let's read it if that one wasn't.
Go back to that.
There's not much in that one.
Oh, here's one.
You didn't even finish it.
Wait, you guys are going to like this one.
Okay.
You guys are going to like this one.
I'm excited to hear this.
I'm having girly thoughts all the time.
Oh my god!
Also Cameron shat on the floor of his bedroom.
What the hell?
He left it there all night while he slept and we didn't find it until the morning.
I wonder if he just liked the smell or something.
Wait, no, keep, no, just keep reading that.
No, you know what, these are from a long time ago, so we're gonna go to the end.
I wanna read that.
It's probably from when I was a baby, it's probably from my diaper, so.
Wait, but she was having serious fucking crushes?
Let's know I'll just read whatever here. I'll just already did a hand job. Oh, dude. This was this was long okay here we go
This one. Oh yeah here get ready. Okay, okay, dear diary. There was a lot of drama today at school. I
Fucking love drama all my friends were talking about it
They announced over the loudspeaker that everybody had to stay in their classrooms because they were transferring this kid to the hospital
I didn't know who it was at first, but lunch was afterward and I noticed Cameron wasn't in the lunchroom
I don't remember this
I wonder what could have happened and if Cameron could have been sent to the hospital
Just then my friend Marcy tapped me on the shoulder
But they had a lesbian fucking scissor fest and asked if I heard what happened
I said no
And she said the kid who got sent to the hospital was this kid named Dustin who nobody knew and it was his first day
At school and he tried to do a backflip to impress everyone
But he landed on his neck and all his bones broke completely
Whoa she said that his bones broke so bad that they had to put him on a bowl shaped stretcher because his body became the
Consistency of a gummy worm left in a hot car
Just then Cameron came back from the bathroom, and he was leaving a trail of shit behind him like Splatoon 3 was just came out whoa
Wait Splatoon 3 just came out. This is probably from a long time ago. That game came out this year.
No, you left a trail of shit right behind you
By the way that fart was fucking rad as fuck high-five that yes, sir, okay?
But we actually have to replace this because I'm gonna get fucking grounded as shit. Yeah
I guess we do have to replace that I wonder and it's Caleb's fault. I ripped it open cuz he was
Needling me to open it faster. What the worst thing is that it's it's a what is it 10 o'clock now?
The diary store is definitely closed definitely. It's still 10 o'clock. Oh my god. It's a let. It's still no it's still
There's yeah, it's a 10 o'clock, okay
So what else do you leave the time checks to so to the people who can read a clock?
Learn how to read a digital clock yet. Yeah, I can only read an analog clock. What else could we do you guys?
Oh, do you guys want to do seven minutes in heaven?
Yeah, okay. Yeah
Okay, let's go. Okay. We all this. Okay. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go
Oh
Okay, so I guess I'm gonna be this close to your fucking butt. Oh get in what my
God, what is it going on in here dude? Are we gonna kiss each other?
We have to check off in here what do we have to jack each other off? Why would we jack it?
It's
Something touch my fucking feet dude what?
I
Have to go back for him. He's still in there
Patrick Pat fuck Pat are you in your Pat Pat?
(screams)
- Oh my god.
- Dude.
- That was crazy.
- That was some of the craziest ish we ever did.
- Talk about fucking awkward.
- Yeah.
- That was awkward.
- I think that we've changed the trajectory of our lives in a way that we won't understand until we go to therapy.
- We at least changed our friendships forever.
- Mm-hmm.
- Because that was seriously...
- I think the trajectory of our friendship has totally changed.
Totally changed.
Is it okay for a woman to ask a man to marry him?
I think like, probably in China.
Yeah.
Sorry.
But I don't know about in America.
Just trying to think of sleepover questions.
Do you guys want to have a deep conversation?
Yeah, let's do deep convo.
Okay.
Do you guys, so obviously my dad's a fucking pastor.
Yeah.
And that is fucking shit for me and shit.
that's been a serious struggle because
youth group is awesome when we watch movies
and fucking pirates who don't do anything and shit,
but once you get into the actual talking about stuff,
it can be seriously fucked up the way that they say
that the stuff that you actually can't do.
So what I'm asking is basically,
do you believe in God at all?
- Well, I think like, I believe in God,
but I don't think that he's necessarily,
I don't think he's like a big guy in the sky
with a beard or whatever.
I think he could be like anything, like he could be an alien or like an overlord or like
um he could be like a tornado like in Fantastic Four.
I think he could be like a big alien or like a robot overlord.
Recently I've been watching on the TV this guy Trevor Noah and he does not believe in
God.
He doesn't?
He's actually given me a lot of insightful um...
He doesn't believe in God.
What does he believe in?
He talks a lot about being a
liberal.
Does he believe in Allah?
No, he doesn't believe in Allah.
Are you sure?
What does he believe in?
I think he believes in there's
no God and that
actually religious rites
in this country are fucking up
stuff for good people.
He believes in Thor.
But he's like a like a fucking.
He's one of these atheistic Democrats,
and usually my mom says, "Do not watch that stuff."
But I've been watching a lot of it,
and honestly, I have to sneak watch it,
and I watch it, and honestly,
most of that shit makes more sense
than believing in some fucking guy in the sky.
- Sometimes I feel like I'm at that age
where I have to make a choice of whether I'm not gonna,
whether I will be an atheist,
and probably the way that I'll die is I'll probably get,
I'll probably be so depressed that I'll make some,
I'll like write an amazing book and then kill myself,
or if I'm gonna continue being a Christian
and wanna get married when I'm 19,
like this is a current plan.
- Yeah.
Well, I think of God, it's like,
if God is real, how could he let something exist like math?
- Yeah. - Or cancer.
- True.
- Well, no, that's a good point.
Like math, what is the fucking point of math?
- What's the reason?
Like when are you gonna use that?
- Yeah.
Like why do I have to do that?
- Like I'm not gonna do my taxes.
- They don't even teach us fucking taxes in school, right?
- And taxes, you don't even have to know math to do that.
That's letters.
And if it wasn't for math,
I would be a sophomore in high school like I should be.
- Do you guys wanna go to college one day?
- No, I wanna do a trade.
- I go to like a party college.
- Yeah.
- But I feel like to me,
like I know that I'm gonna be like a performer.
- I'm gonna go to school for,
I'm gonna go to a community college for video production
and then it's gonna ruin a lot of stuff for me.
- I really, really wanna go to full sail
like fucking cat and shit.
- Yeah, me too.
- I'm kinda mad as shit.
- 'Cause I do wanna become a vegan.
- You know what I wish I could go to, though?
- What?
- Hogwarts.
- Hogwarts is not--
- No, that's a fucking elementary school
for wizard-ass kids.
- Yeah, but imagine if I could get held back
and they're like, "You're being held back.
"You're going back to first grade."
And I'd be like, "Fuck, are you shitting me?"
- Bro said he wants to go to school in a dress every day.
(laughing)
- It's a robe.
It's a cowl.
It's a--
- That's what girls say, too.
- It's a tunic, actually.
- Mm, I bet it is.
I think it's definitely easily a dress.
- It's a tunic. - No.
- Okay, meanwhile you're wearing a skirt under the table.
- He wants to hang out with Harry P.
- Wait, I hear the time clock.
- Okay, show this though, show this though first.
- It's 11.
- It's not 11 yet.
- It is 11. - It is 11.
Show this though.
That's who goes to Hogwarts.
- Yeah, that's how you wanna dress.
- No dude, that's who I'll be in.
- You're gonna fuck that woman's bro.
- You're gonna be in her dress?
- Yeah, after I fuck her.
That's what, boyfriends and girlfriends
wear their clothes after they fuck.
That's why they show a woman in a flannel on TV.
Yeah, and they show a boy in a dress.
Yeah.
Did you guys ever--
I saw a boy in a dress get fucked.
A woman wears her boyfriend's hoodie, sweatshirt.
That happens to me basically every day
when I go to school.
And a boy wears the tights after.
I saw a boy in a dress get fucked.
Do you think if they have a dance at school
that we'll probably go and we can get blowjobs
in the bathroom?
We could be the blowjob crew.
Yeah.
We could probably get in serious trouble.
If we found three girls who would do that together.
I think I might want to hire a prostitute before I turn 18 to lose my virginity too.
Yeah, so you don't have to tell any girl that you're...
Yeah, it should be with a seasoned professional.
Mm-hmm, exactly.
Yeah.
I feel like I want to get it out of the way with a prostitute who, like, whose life doesn't
matter before I fuck, like, a real girl.
I'd probably hire, like, Timmy's mom.
Is she a prostitute or she just looks like a slut?
She's like, she just, she doesn't have a husband.
Yeah.
And she wears no bras on the list.
She, yeah, and she has no...
What I heard.
She always has, she looks pale.
Yeah.
But she dresses, I hear that...
She has a Subaru and I heard that lesbos drive those fucking cars.
Yeah, that's true. What I heard is that, you know Jason?
Yeah.
Momoa?
No.
Uh oh.
Well, Jason's mom and dad have these things called "key parties."
No fucking way.
And I know that because my mom came home with Jason's dad.
Holy shit.
Well, I know I kind of want to go to a party and I know exactly what could get us into one of those parties.
Whoa!
I got a pair of keys right here.
Wait, so this is basically two tickets to a wild adult party of sexual escapade.
You have to wear a mask there though.
Pat, here's a picture of Jason's dad with your mom.
I thought that COVID was over.
I didn't know you still had to wear masks to that shit.
Yeah, no, you have to wear a mask because of the smell.
Dude, I hate how all these adults nowadays are fucking liberal pussies.
They wear fucking masks to Starbucks and shit.
I actually like that because of a lot of stuff that Trevor Noah has been telling me.
You're always on and on about this Trevor Noah motherfucker.
What about fucking...
He's the funniest comic right now.
What about Logan Paul?
What about...
Okay, but that...
I chose to be...
He's actually fucking fire.
What's you guys' favorite brand of beer?
Probably fucking hops.
I like O'Doul's.
Or schlops.
Yeah.
I like vodka.
I like Smirnoff. It's good.
Yeah, vodka is best...
Smirnoff is really good.
...better than I drink blueberry vodka from the fridge
and I immediately threw up.
No, dude.
That's pussy.
I honestly...
I've only had a couple of sips.
Don't ever tell someone that.
- I won't do, we're in deep conversation mode here.
- I've only had a couple of sips, but I don't think--
- Dude, I'll, wait, all of us really quick.
- Definitely.
- This shit is all secret.
- For sure.
- We have to keep this under wraps.
- No one will ever know about what we say.
- Oh fuck no, dude.
Who's fucking got the biggest--
- I was fucked.
- By who?
- I don't even wanna say anymore.
- Damn.
- You don't even wanna say, why?
I wanna know who fucked you.
Who fucked you?
You were fucked?
- When did you get fucked?
You get fucked on purpose or an accidental fuck?
You're just lying for attention, aren't you?
- I got fucked.
- No you didn't, you're fucking lying for attention.
- No I didn't.
- This is the most, you keep doing this,
keep saying, oh I fucking got molested.
- Dude, I got fucked by Jamie Lee Curtis when I was seven.
- That's fucking a lie, dude.
- Damn, she was my babysitter.
- That's a fucking lie.
She's not a babysitter, she's an actress.
- Did you ever see the movie where she's a babysitter?
- Yeah.
- They hired her for that 'cause she really was a babysitter.
- That was like 65 years ago, asshat.
She's in a yogurt commercial.
Yeah, I bet you made yogurt on her.
That's how they got the inspiration
for that commercial too.
I had a whole lot of sex dreams about her
a long time ago when I was a kid.
Yeah? Yeah.
I wanted to fuck Jamie Lee Curtis
when I was a kid so bad off them yogurt commercials.
The yogurt commercials?
Not even Trading Spaces?
Trading Spaces.
She's in that.
Trading Spaces?
She shows her butt in that.
I've never seen that movie.
With Eddie Murphy and Dan Aykroyd?
Never seen it.
I just-- My dad and I would
watch that on Christmas a lot.
I honestly I saw Freaky Friday and the yogurt commercial. I was like 10 years old
I was like I have to fuck Jamie Lee Curtis
Yeah
I never saw any of the stuff when she was a young hot lady and then I saw
The one she did with Arnold where she does a sexy strip tease and I was like she looks too young
It's too young in those movies guys I something to admit yeah, I was lying when I said I got fuck yeah
We knew so I but when I was 10
Megan Fox called me and brought me to the set of Transformers and brought me to her trailer and fuck damn
Lying I was lying it was actually the girl in Transformers dark of the moon
They replaced her with the rose honey. Do we the British one? I fucking hated her. She's annoying as fuck well
She fucked me, and now we don't talk damn
Do you guys think that you guys could have casual sex one day or is it all
That's how I feel - I makes me throw up thinking that people have casual sex
Yeah, I really wish I could get on tinder though. I kind of want to check out all of the fucking sex apps and
I want to get I think it'll be so fucking hot if I could stay up all night looking at bumble
Yeah, dude, imagine what girls post on there. Probably they post their pussies on that
It's probably you're just swiping left and right on pictures of vaginas
I would swipe right on everything on hinge bumble and tinder
You guys ever gone chat roulette and show your underage penis get people sent to jail
We used to do that so much when I was a kid. We'd go on chatrelite and be like, if it was
an adult we'd immediately show our dick and balls.
That's funny. Yeah, I did that on Reddit.
No, you didn't, because I would get taken down. But chatrelite you can't get banned because
it's actually decentralized on the blockchain.
For real?
I don't know, something like that.
What do you guys think it will be like in 50 years?
Probably an unimaginable hellscape of fucking fire and flames. Do you guys think it will be go back to the moon?
I think probably the rapture will start by then yeah the rapper you think the Rapture is gonna start
No, it's actually because of some oil fucking company. I fucking hate the oil companies. Yeah, yeah
Wait, what's what's what Trevor Noah taught oil Michael Moore make Michael Moore movies? I like my mom fries vegetables in oil
What kind of vegetables? I did not just admit that what the fuck did you just say about vegetables?
You mean you mean vegetables like I mean eggs
Okay
I'm gonna do one more truth or dare
Cuz I just want I just want to do you guys want to do just do more truth or dare
Do you guys want to okay Pat? Do you want extreme and hot? Yes? Okay? Do you want truth or dare truth?
Okay, dare you already said it's truthful that I what is something that is absolutely off-limits in the bat
Beth in the bedroom not the bathroom the bath bath bedroom
Something that's off-limits in the bathroom is walking in on me jacking off mom
Enough guys everywhere in the house
Now for us what's that?
So we love to jack off in the bathroom or bedroom and we oh, yeah, and we hate when someone walks in
Oh, you know at the convenience store
they have a monitor where everyone can see what's happening at every part of the store.
No.
And they show a security camera footage.
They should have one of those on the outside of the bathroom so that someone can look on the outside
and if they see someone jacking off, they won't go in.
Yeah, or you could get a baby monitor.
Yeah, and then you do it like this.
And then you moan into the baby monitor.
That's what I do when I jack off.
And I jack off like this.
I rub the bottom like this.
Why? How does that do crap?
You're still learning, kiddo.
If you want jack off lessons, you should take them from the master.
It's like this when I do it. I go like...
You put the baby monitor under your mom's pillow.
Yeah.
And then you just scream and moan loud as fuck.
Also, sometimes I put a napkin around my junk and I go like this.
And I go like this.
I read an urban dictionary that's called the Rocketeer.
here. Yeah. What's your favorite urban? Wait, actually, I think the clock just
ticked. It's actually called a restaurant. Wait, I think we're one
minute away from midnight. Wait, are we actually? I think we are. I think it's
1159. Holy crap. Guys, I can't believe we almost did it. I know, but they know
you know how they say that time slows down the more they do. Yeah. Yeah. So I
don't know. Do you guys? I'm just joking. You guys want to play more truth or
dare, though, because I really like truth. Let's play more truth or dare.
Okay, wait. No, you, hey, hey. You asked Patrick one, so now it's Patrick's turn.
I'm the truth or master.
No, you are not.
I also can't press the button because it doesn't work on my phone.
Here, you can use my phone. I'm letting you. So you choose someone to ask. Who are you
going to ask?
Can I ask myself?
Okay.
What? Ask yourself. I've never heard of that, but I guess you can do that.
You can do it, but I don't like it though.
Okay, I dare myself to brush my spouse's teeth.
No, you can't ask yourself.
Okay, then I dare you to brush your spouse's teeth.
We're playing footsie under the table.
No, give me--
You guys are playing footsie?
Okay.
True.
Wait, what difficulty though?
Extreme and hot.
We only do extreme and hot.
Okay, okay, that's true 'cause it's late.
It's almost--
On your night.
Okay.
What would you like to wear,
an evening suit or a baby doll?
I would--
(laughing)
on your night what would you like to wear an evening suit or a baby doll
the baby
the
on your name
but what you like to wear
in the evening suit or a baby doll
i guess a baby doll
well that's an evening suit
uh... you know what i don't know look up the evening student urban dictionary
though
yeah and i don't know what i've said what are the dates of all of you look up our
names on Urban Dictionary. We did that before. We did that before in a different sleepover.
We had one of our 300 sleepovers. It just says a man's formal suit to be worn in the evening.
That's because that's dictionary, dude. Go to Urban Dictionary. Damn. Just click Urban
Dictionary and type in evening suit. Slang for businessman or any authority figure. What's
your favorite Urban Dictionary? What was that? Can you click, type in evening? Pimpin' suit.
A suit that is so nice it could even be considered pimpin',
but not a suit created for use by pimps or used while pimpin'.
- That's what I wanna do when I grow up.
I'll be a pimp.
- Wait, look up pimps.
Look up, click on the pimps thing.
- Look up evening, look up evening burger,
'cause that showed up.
I wanna see what that is.
- I do actually wanna see what a evening burger means.
- Yeah, pull up evening burger.
- On Urban Dictionary.
- Okay, pull up evening burger.
- Look up the word evening burger.
- So pull up evening burger.
- Evening hamburger.
okay evening hamburger it's a there it is
an ancient tradition derived from the earliest of civilizations it is normally
an act of solidarity but it can be used as a social function in a group of
close i'm this is boring i thought matter has a great score down there
might be more now that i have a p lit do you know you why did you make us do this
i thought that it was going to be okay okay okay okay i was somebody asked
somebody there may somebody there may start their way where i got a very
alarming out there for you all of that
on a fucking fire fucking there for you
ready? All right. Um,
shave one of your arms. Wait, I have a razor.
Wait, hold on. Let me see it. No,
no, no. Say you would do it. I said, give me a dare.
I didn't say I'd do it. Oh, here's the,
here's the evening burger I was thinking of.
Don't do that.
You have to shave your arm.
You have to shave one strip of your arm.
Dude, I don't know how to shave.
I don't know how to shave.
I'll shave it.
I'm gonna fucking--
You don't know how to shave?
I do.
No, you don't.
I do, I'll show you.
You never shave.
Pat, give me your hand or your arm.
You can tell.
I'll shave a little bit of your arm.
Shave the tip of your finger.
No, no, no, no.
Shave my knuckle right here.
I'll shave your hand.
Okay.
No, wait, don't shave my knuckle.
Wait, it's not my dare.
I'll shave my arm.
It doesn't even hurt and it doesn't look that weird.
That looks so painful.
See look at that.
Hold that up.
I just took some hair off my arm.
I guess you can't see it.
See that's why we need to use your hair because you have black cast hair.
You have no hair at all.
This would not affect you.
No I'm scared.
Let's shave your arm Pat.
Come on.
My arm right here, it'll look weird because I mean I have so much of it that
Shaved his costume
Nothing came off. Yeah, it's too thick. Actually we got a little bit
You got fucking owned. Okay. Your shit, your arm's been shaved into a square
You look awesome.
No!
Get away from me!
What are you doing?
My hands are already shaved!
Guys, don't fight.
Stop!
Get away from me!
Get that away and I'll fuck you up!
I'll fucking call the cops right now!
Call them, call them, call them!
I'm fucking serious, I'll shave the fucking cops' heads!
Don't you ever fucking try to shave me ever again!
That was bullshit, and you fucking know it.
You shaved me!
I did it as a part of his dare, you asshat.
Guys?
What?
Can we be friends again?
Yes, truth or dare?
Because you didn't even do your dare.
Okay, a new dare.
He has not done a single dare, so he gets a triple dare.
Just the triple dare.
I'm scared of dares.
Do something funny that only your spouse will understand.
You don't have a spouse or you know you're fucking forever alone.
Pour some sauce on your mobile screen and make a video call to someone.
After she lifts the call, lick the sauce.
Do you have any sauce?
Okay, hold on.
Maybe I can put a chip.
I can put some sauce.
You can put a chip but you gotta make a- Can I eat the chip off of the screen?
Yeah, sure.
We'll count that.
Okay, let me pull up- Let me pull up the FaceTime app here that I have on my iPod 10.
I love my I touch by the way doodle jump you know my job is fire jump poppy jump is fire
I love that stuff. Okay. I'm gonna go ahead and call somebody right now, okay?
Who you calling you accept the terms and conditions? I think that's how it works blockhead. Oh
It's making the wires go crazy
Guys, I just they just picked up. Holy crap. Okay wait
Hello, oh
My guys actually eating the fucking chip off the thing
Okay, you are officially the king of dares damn
He told okay that was a dare ignore that just pretend that did it happen
I do I don't do that stuff do normally
I think there's we really only have one more slumber party thing to do because it's getting close to being
1159 and 59 seconds really we should do spin the bottle okay, okay, okay?
Okay wait, let's use this bottle.
Because we don't have an empty one.
Holy shit this thing's a crap.
Okay wait, make sure it's really closed though.
Because I don't like spills.
My mom would fucking kill me.
Spill the bottle. Ready?
Okay, spin it.
Me? Okay wait, who's the next spin?
Jubio?
No, that's closest.
Okay, that was great. One more time.
goodness way as we have to do this okay seriously you know i fucking don't want
to
he spit out
oh
that's fucking disgusting dude yeah why don't we play that because it's about to
be midnight i need to wash up my mouth and crazy ass midnight and we're gonna
stay up
holy shit
That was some Mythbusters shit.
Arm hair all in my mouth.
Listen, guys, this has been the craziest...
Holy fuck.
There's gas coming out of it.
This has been the craziest fucking night of my life.
Yeah, absolutely.
I can say that much.
And I'll say this much, you two are like my fucking brothers at this point.
We are like bros.
That I kiss and that I go into the closet with sometimes.
And I fucking love you guys and I want to have a summer party for the rest of my life.
party for the rest of my life and the best part is it doesn't stop now once it
hits midnight we're gonna party all night we're not gonna be tired at all
but no oh my god wait guys coming up ten nine eight seven six five four three two
one midnight
(snoring)
I need a CPAP machine.
(slurping)
[BLANK_AUDIO]