(upbeat music)
- Ready in this bitch?
- Yeah, we're all ready.
We're going. - And let's go.
- And let's go.
- We're here live with Jack Frost.
He's been nipping at your nose.
Here comes winter, baby.
Jack, how's your day been?
- Oh, my day has been so good so far.
I've been making people feel the cold.
- And it's gotta be what, 53 degrees outside right now?
- I'm 53, but when you consider climate change,
it's supposed to be 103 today, but because of my doing.
- You lowered it?
- Has climate change affected your work?
- It's affected my work positively, yeah.
- Yeah, why?
- Because as the warm earth becomes more and more
in such a sense, in that regard,
to be such a way that I've then become into my,
people need me.
- So you can drop, so in the summer,
are you active in the summer all that much or no?
- Not really, that's when I like to go to school.
Nice.
People go to school not in the summer, but that's the best time to go to school.
Really?
Because there's no one there.
Everyone's there during the year.
The teachers don't pay attention to you, but you go in the summer.
It's you and three other kids.
Yeah, the teacher focuses on you.
You know those guys?
I know those guys.
Hell, I was one of them.
Curly Moe and Larry.
They belong in summer school.
They should have been in school all day long.
Why go to school for 18 years when you could stretch it out?
Why do they make stupider people go to school more?
I've said this all the time man, death lingers on every word.
I've been saying that a lot lately too.
Yes, you have been saying that a lot lately.
But they should, if you get the worst score, you need to go to a better school.
That's like, oh, that's like if you had a really bad injury, we got to send you to the
minute clinic.
Yeah, it makes no sense.
There's the, there's that.
They put the, the smart kids should be in the most shit fucking schools ever.
They should be so physically tough to learn.
All the institutions.
They should have like weights and stuff on them.
They should be in the school for Matilda.
- They should get sent to mistrunch school.
- Yeah, they should be locked up.
And I'm not gonna say who are the smartest people
in our society, because I don't want it to feel like
that type of thing.
- Wait, what are you alluding to?
The smartest?
- I don't know.
(laughing)
- The smartest people in our society?
- Well, it's just we're painting this image
of people being trapped for thinking a certain way.
- Oh, okay.
- So I don't wanna--
What are you guys talking about? I'm not interested in having any Will Smith slap type of discussion.
No, no, no. Jack Frost, Jack Frost don't play like that. He don't play that. Jack Frost got PR.
What's it like being a celebrity? One of the biggest celebrities I would say worldwide.
It's similar to, yeah, what? Your big celebrity world, everybody knows Jack Frost. Everybody, yeah.
What's it like? Yeah, what is it like?
Dude, it's fucking hectic. Yeah, I can imagine. You can't even go to the store without someone identifying you positively.
I mean, it makes, I mean, you know, you came in here, you're dressed in full gold right
now except for your gloves.
I came like this.
It's kind of interesting, I feel like Jack Frost, I guess maybe the images of you as
Jack Frost usually are kind of before you came up like that.
You didn't have the money to have an entire gold suit.
If you search Jack Frost 1993, you're not going to see me the same as I am now.
It's going to be completely different.
I can tell that you've kind of whited up the blue part of your body.
Yeah. A lot of that. Yeah. It seeps through a little bit, but not so much.
Yeah. But the gold is a good touch. I think.
You said people are recognizing you at the store too. Are they,
are they getting mad at you? Or are they like, why are you making a positive way?
Why are you making cold?
Well, they identify me positively.
Yeah. Like a suspect.
Like they know who you are.
Oh, okay. It depends on the store really.
And you're probably what?
So some stores people are mad. Some people are different stores.
Like the grill store.
I guess maybe a winter clothing store people might be mad because you're making them spend
money here.
A Burlington Co.
Factory.
Burlington Co.
Factory, they're saying, "Thank God, let me put this to the ticket for a test ride."
Why can't you take clothes for a test ride?
I agree.
You can.
Amazon Essentials, you get a seven-day try-on.
You're kidding me.
In my job, I just can't afford to be wasting money on clothes.
So this means a lot to me that that could be an opportunity.
You should be able to take...
you take like the manager of the Burlington Co. Factory with you and he
could walk around with you for a couple days? Well yeah it's just one
employee. When you walk down a fancy street and they have like a
Gucci store, Uniqlo, you should be able to wear those expensive clothes around the
city for a little bit. Right and because that's also...
I get what you're saying now. I didn't know you meant like an actual test drive with the manager.
but is like got binoculars. But imagine this scenario, okay?
You're walking down the street in this trendy area, okay? You're wearing full Gucci,
expensive clothes. You look stylish and fashionable. Everyone is looking at you, okay?
And they're going, "Oh my god, that's the most stylish guy on the planet. How can he afford those clothes?
That's incredible." And then they look slightly to the right and they see the manager of the store holding your hand. He's handcuffed to you.
Oh my god, he's test driving them. The way that you just presented that scenario made it feel like
SAT question like a comprehensions test. Yeah, I was like he's trying so hard to remember
This is also the thirstiest I've ever been around friends military age friends
I didn't go that well
It's Jack Frost! You're gonna freeze the water. I'm gonna freeze it. Imagine if you had the
Midas tongue and you're gonna make out with somebody. Oh my god. Turn their tongue
gold. That's it. That'd be uncomfortable as fuck. Mm-hmm. Gold teeth though.
Unsuckable. Gold teeth? You'd have gold teeth all the time. Yeah. It would
make biting into like walls and stuff a lot easier.
Oh my god, thank you.
Sure.
Have you had solid gold teeth?
Wait, show everybody our water bottle.
I'll bring it in for you.
Yeah, put it up on that table.
Fucking.
There you go, man.
So, wait, let me check the frame on it.
Yeah, sure.
Do you really think I'm going to go buy a water cooler?
They're $85.
You have to stay, you're going to freeze this.
- Yeah, you need to stay away from that right now.
- Put it over here.
- The benefit of ice is it melts again,
so as soon as I leave--
- Oh, you're fuckin' ass walking around.
- Ah, shit, I never really--
- There's a lot of benefits to ice.
- Listen, here's a question.
- You know, I--
- Hey, hey, hey.
(laughing)
Say that again.
- What'd you say?
- There is a lot of benefits to ice.
- Yep.
- That's rare.
- Yeah, that is rare.
Listen, if you could have a, what's your dream train?
- One that goes, what are the destinations?
every celebrity that could run a train on you
and like five to ten people.
- I thought you meant my dream, like an Amtrak train.
- Well that's Polar Express.
- That's gotta be the Polar Express.
- I guess that's the obvious answer.
- But if you, I'm saying like,
what are your five to ten guys that are like Jack Frost.
- To run a train on me?
- Put me in a room with these five
and we're gonna make magic.
We're gonna make a Kim K sex tape, we're going to the moon.
- And I only get five people?
- That was only one guy.
- You can get five to ten.
- There's only one guy in the Kim K sex tape.
- He had, Rezia has clones, but we can talk about that later.
- Vin Diesel, step one.
- Yeah.
- Step one.
- Step two.
- Oh yeah, in order too.
- Dead or alive?
- Dead. - Yeah.
- The Rock. - Only dead.
The Rock.
- Kill the Rock, get him in there.
- Okay.
- Sex tape.
So I want a lot of different body types.
- You want sizes difference, yeah.
- I guess a mummy.
- You kinda, I guess they could gauge,
they could kinda gauge you,
you know like people get their ears stretched,
kind of would want to do it in reverse order of size. Oh yeah. You could get a
gauge, you're saying like I put an earring gauge on someone's whole body?
So it starts small and then you get big. I don't mean to be crass but your asshole
would like be one size at the beginning and then a different size
at the end. You're kind of working your way up. Different shapes could be good too.
Yeah that's healthy. In the end it would be... What's the most interesting
asshole shape I wonder? Probably square. Yeah that might be square or star. Maybe a
letter if a letter a letter a or B put it fit hey if it was big enough you could
fit a lemon in there hey man not me that's what will Sasso was known for on
vine that's true he's shitting out lemon behind the lemon at first it was a curse
yeah yeah man those videos are funny as fuck five - that's not true yeah we'll
20 pounds I swear no no no no no no no see you check him out you saw him in
person yeah I saw him in this there's just no way this is by - this is fake
that's just a picture of him how's that fake that's yeah that's a man look five
- look how his collar goes only up to there on his neck oh that's true yeah
that's a good five - there's a good point he's a good-looking guy there's a
There's another the will Sasso cows calves cows. Oh
Thank you, oh my god
flexing calf muscles
And he's on shit. My dad says holy fucking God is that show a show?
Yeah, you never heard of the curse word in it. It was the world's change
There used to be a Twitter account that was shit. My dad said or maybe it was an Instagram. I don't remember
It was an Instagram.
But it was no, it was a Twitter.
It doesn't really matter.
But the guy would post his dad would
be saying stuff would be like, how
the fuck do I use my fucking goddamn
iPhone, you shit ass son?
And his son would say, instead of
helping my father, I'm going to post
this word for word transcript online
and have strangers laugh at it.
You know what's wrong with today's
society? An account called shit my
dad says it should all it should be
on there is I'm proud of you.
Yeah, that's right.
And then one late, late, late
into life, maybe a little bit of
confusion like some stuff like some kind of off weird questions and then just
kind of saying help kind of really yeah and then maybe like right right but as
the dad is dying maybe one that says like I see a gargoyle yeah or something
like that what or like something like it's watching me or grow my grandpa's
like my great-grandpa's last words I'm in prison I'm in a prison that's what
Was he in jail? No, he was in a hospital. So he was wrong. He's an idiot.
That's embarrassing. So embarrassing that he fucked himself.
Great guy by the name of Arnold. I got his shirt. Arnold. Back at the house.
You got his shirt? You got his shirt? Back in the day you could only wear one shirt your whole life.
He left me a grey polo that has his name in the back. It says Arnold.
I put it on every day. I'm like, "Ah man, I'm in prison."
It's awesome. We have something exciting that we're going to be doing through December.
through December. Oh yeah, it's December. You know what time that is. If you're Christian, pay attention.
Everybody else, take a break. Check this out. Don't, don't, okay, we'll put this, let me explain what
this is first, please. Circle. For God's sake! It's a circle. We're doing a circle every day. Yeah,
Will Sasso is a circle. That ain't Will Sasso. Someone, someone changed. We actually just got a
hold of some technology that allows us to track Santa Claus. Yeah. We put a GPS on Santa Claus's
outfit and we're not going to say our source of who got close enough to Santa Claus to do this or who
yeah you've had some run-ins with Santa I'm guessing. Yeah I've seen him at the tracks.
Yeah like the dog tracks? Gambling. Gambling on horses. He's got to make that money somehow. He's
got all those gifts to give out. That's a good point. I didn't even think about that. I always
thought just God kind of handed a check. God is Santa. God is Santa? That's something that is
sitting right in front of everybody that no one talks about. Santa is God. You think
Santa's just doing that? When I was in elementary school my friend told me,
"Did you know actually there's no such thing as Santa and Jesus brings the
presents?" Really? And then I told my mom, my friend told that, and my mom was like,
"Nobody thinks that. That's not even a thing that anybody says." Your friend
made that up. We had a... no that's... that's all I'm saying. That's what my mom said.
kind of people you got that going on. That Jesus brings the presents? Yeah and we just were like no.
No. Because if Jesus brings the presents that means Jesus is also sneaking into
your house taking your teeth at night. My mom told me that. What? No, that's the tooth fairy.
My mom told me that Santa brings three presents and then she brings the rest.
She brings the rest? She brings the rest of the presents. Did she make Santa bring the good
presents or the bad presents? See I never know. I never knew. You never knew? I
I never knew which ones were from Santa or which ones were from mom.
No, she just threw them all in a pile.
Oh man, we used to get the from Santa on the tag.
I think you just didn't read the labels.
No, they weren't wrapped.
They weren't wrapped?
My mom wouldn't wrap any of the presents.
Wow, sad.
That feels like it's not a present in that case, it's just an item.
Yeah.
It's kind of trash.
It's clutter.
It's an item.
- My parents are both Jewish and they tried to hide it
from me my whole life, so we did Christmas and all that.
- Jack Frost has Jewish parents.
- Yeah, and I'm not.
- Oh my God.
- I don't fuck with that.
- No, I can tell.
- Be careful now.
- I know, well, be careful about them.
Be careful of them.
- Whoa.
(laughing)
- Come on, man.
- No, that's not what we're saying, Jack Frost.
- Nuh-uh.
- No, no, no.
- What?
- No, we're kinda saying the opposite.
- You're putting words in our mouth.
- We love Jews.
- Jewish people.
- You love Jews.
we love Jewish people. To be... No, to be my friends, my neighbors. To be. To be. To be
around. We love Jewish people to be. Well, I just wish my parents had been honest about it. Yeah, that is
kind of... they hid it from you? They hid it from what age? Wait, they hid Christmas or
Judaism? They hid that they were Jewish from me. Okay. Because they knew how
disappointed I would be. That's a... that is a Jewish last name that I
think about it. Frost? Yeah. It's my cross to bear. Yeah. Well not your cross. Well yeah.
You're star of David to bear. I'm not Jewish. Your parents are. My parents are Jewish. I'm snow.
Okay. That makes sense. Two snowflakes met up at the 930 club in DC and 11 months later I
popped out. No we played DC9. I thought we played there. A lot of nines in DC.
so much like Michael Jackson when you cover your face. That's something you can't do
unless you're made out of snow, man.
Okay, we have a bit, we basically we have a, we have a, let's, we're gonna track, we're
gonna check where Santa is every day, every episode this month, so let's go ahead
Let's see where Santa is today.
People who are curious are all going to say that.
Oh my god.
Should we talk over this?
Yeah, you can.
Yeah, we're good.
There he is.
It looks like he's Mexico.
Where's that?
Oh!
He's at the Bellagio in Las Vegas, in LA's Vegas.
That's pretty cool.
I mean, I guess he's getting his gambling on.
What is Santa, can we see anything?
What is Santa doing?
Yeah, what's...
Oh!
Oh, that's good.
He's getting the coat.
He didn't have it?
It's kind of late.
It is kind of late.
Maybe it's up boosted.
It's kind of late in the game to be getting that.
So Jack Frost, I mean this mask stuff is getting ridiculous if you ask me, right?
I know, I can't hardly breathe because the mask I wear is so thick.
Yeah, what are you doing like inch, I mean you're a celebrity so you're probably doing
bulletproof kind of.
Yeah, Kevlar mask on your face.
Because if someone inside, I can't, the money maker, I can't have somebody shoot me in the
teeth.
Yeah, even though it would probably like, the hole would be there and then it would probably
fill back in with snow and then.
The mouth's already a hole for most.
Well, you know what I realized recently?
David Blaine said that?
Yeah.
That's a quote from David Blaine.
The mouth is a hole.
Yeah, he said that.
I was actually doing some philosophical thinking
recently.
I realized probably the reason COVID wasn't around back
in the day, way back when, is because of medieval knight
helmets.
That's the thickest mask of all.
And that's probably why it waited till now to show up.
That's a really new-- nobody's wearing helmets.
It probably popped out like the groundhog said, no thanks.
- And now it's like, now's my time.
- 'Cause you're seeing people who are in polycules
all kissing each other, coughing in each other's mouth.
- Exactly, and everybody wants to show their face.
It probably saw everyone posting their face on Instagram.
- He said, "I can attack that."
- Oh my God, that's so true.
- I'm gonna get up in that face.
- Yeah, I'd like to message you a disease.
- Yeah.
- COVID.
- COVID, 19 likes, that's what he was seeing
on the Instagram images.
- We got problems with these polyamorous molecules, man.
- I agree.
- Get out of here.
- Get out of here, get into a regular molecule.
You know, I feel like all those people who are polyamorous and have like 15 wives and
shit, they all live in like the Midwest.
It's all like Chicago down to like...
Well, it makes sense.
There's a lot more room out there.
That's true.
Detroit, that's a good place to have a polycule.
Get a whole fucking...
Oh, what, my studio?
Yeah, 12 bedroom apartment for $10 a month.
That's perfect for a polycule.
Siberia's got the big polycules.
Yeah, that's what the Midwest is like.
Yeah?
Yeah.
With the wolves.
Earth is essentially one polyamorous molecule.
- Is that true?
- If you think about it, it's the shape of a molecule.
Everybody here is procreating.
- That's true.
- We all do that.
- Yeah, do you have a--
- Jack Frost does that.
- Huh?
I don't do that 'cause I'm usually in orbit.
- Oh, you didn't, wait, you're in orbit?
You have to go up to shoot the cold in?
- That's why people like me like to chill.
- Outside.
- You notice that Santa, well,
Santa's on the floor right now.
There's Jesus in a Santa hat.
- Yeah, get that out of here.
Close that.
- Yeah, that's interesting.
And that looks like one of those things that you put up in the uterus.
Oh, an IUD?
Yeah.
Is that a conspiracy that the Mandalay Bay Casino is shaped like an IUD?
Could be now.
It's shaped like an IED.
Maybe it was supposed to blow up that night.
IED's nuts.
You said I eat D's nuts.
You eat D's?
That's what you said.
You tried to get us and you said I eat D's nuts.
Jack don't mess with Jack Frost. I'll fuck around and get and I'll uh...
Leave the gloves on.
Deez my own nuts.
Deez your own? Don't eat your own nuts.
I'm not... Jack Frost will deez, eat my own nuts.
Deez eat them.
Damn he's so crazy he'll eat his own fucking whole ass nuts.
You like CDs or cassettes?
Uh I like deez, CDs.
I like deez.
Well okay, alright.
Yeah.
Man, the air in here is just so fresh.
Yeah, it is.
It's our fun part.
What's your Spotify wrapped looking like?
Yeah.
2022.
Can we know yet?
No, that comes out.
But that's what you do. The fun part now is saying, "Oh, is my wrapped going to be..."
Oh, what's it? Yeah, what's going to be on there?
Yeah.
What's your guesstimate?
Is it going to be mainly classical or rock and roll headbangers?
Yeah, basically the two options.
I'm going to have a lot of that.
What's that?
Solamente una vez.
Amen a la vida.
Is that the Lady and the Tramp song?
You don't know Solamente Una Vez?
No.
What the fuck?
What the hell is that?
Everyone's got a different colored mics.
Who's it by?
A lot of different people.
Oh, it's one of these.
It's various artists.
Yeah, it's kind of like Jingle Bells.
A lot of people like it.
Everybody's got a Jingle Bell.
It's a Christmas song?
Yeah.
I don't know.
got a jiggle bell. It's a Christmas song? Nah, just love. I know the prayer. You know a prayer?
I know Celine Dion and the Italian guy with no eyes. That's good. Who's that? No eyes?
Or some shit. What's the point of being in Italy if you can't see? I almost said he's
deaf but there's no way he's deaf. The food. The food. Oh, the food. That's a good point.
Oh my god. The food in Italy is so remarkable. I would love to experience it someday for
myself. I mostly experience the food in Italy from Google Images. Yeah. HBO Max.
Did they ever do a Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles where they let them loose in Italy? I don't
think so. I don't think they could, it would allow them. Probably. They should let
them loose out there. Who knows where they'd go. They should make, I think almost every
character, they should make a movie about that character called that character's
name Unleashed. I agree. Sonic Unleashed. Yeah. Clifford Unleashed. That was a game. Clifford
unleashed would be fire, dude. An adult Clifford movie. Kind of a dark twist on
Clifford. Yeah, and you know why he's red. Yeah, he's mad. He's mad. He's angry.
His circulations, his heart rate is so high. He has a big vein on his head, too.
Yeah, it's popping out. He's got steam on his ears constantly. And he goes like
this... And he eats people. And he can only walk on certain ground 'cause his
paws are so hot it'll melt. Yes. He can only walk on metal. Yeah. My feet are
And if you walk on the metal after him it burns your feet if you step where he step and then everybody judges you
Life they did that one. That's the worst part of that. Yes, so she's a distraction. There's destruction, but then there's also judgment
Imagine if you're playing follow the leader with a guy like that his feet were so hot if you followed his steps you'd burn
You will I would just lose it's not that big of a deal to lose follow the leader
Maybe unless that's right. That's your value system being exposed right now. I just that's a moral judgment
Maybe I'm just not that competitive.
- Imagine playing follow the leader
where the person in front has a gun.
- Well, but are they aiming backwards?
- Yeah, they-- - I would.
- You would aim backwards or you would follow?
- What?
No, that's the whole point is that
you're trying to shake everyone off, right?
- Yeah. - Oh, got it.
- So they have a gun.
- Oh, true. - Good one.
- Or you could have a gun and maybe you shoot,
you do something illegal with the gun
and everyone else has to do it.
- Is that part of follow the leader?
You have to do also Simon Says?
Should we practice? Should we try? I think it can be part of it.
We could try that in here.
All right.
Jack Frost jokes LLC.
You have an LLC, Jack?
Yeah.
It is Jack Frost jokes?
Jack Frost jokes LLC.
You got to protect the...
Just for this. That's just for the jokes though.
You got like Jack Frost snow LLC.
Jack Frost jokes normal comments.
Jack Frost jokes compliments.
Jack Frost jokes...
Still Jack Frost jokes.
Where are you getting your money from, though?
somebody paying like what's your business model? I mean you make the world cold.
Well you're probably getting a paycheck from God. If it's climate change you're probably getting paid by maybe Soros or something.
True. Al Gore. I don't look man. I just open my bank account and I see green numbers
this week. I say thank you very much. I have no questions about who and what
type of people are outside my house. So you're saying that, who are you saying that to?
If you open your bank, are you talking into your phone when you open the bank
app. Thank you very much. It's a saying.
Also nowadays you can talk to you they have these voices.
There's a bank app that lets you talk to Drew Barrymore.
Chase Blue! Chase Blue!
Chase Blue Drew Barrymore. Are they of Blue Barrymore?
It might not come up yet because this is a business venture I'm not supposed to
talking about? You know what I would say? What's in the app store? You gotta go to the app
store. Why would it be in there? See I told you, look how many results there are. Drew
Barrymore Playboy Bunny. There's over a million point two nine results. That's just a blue
Drew Barrymore. That could be her in the Chase app and she's saying here's your fifty first
dollars. Right, welcome back. Maybe it's that she knows it. Is she an expert on banking?
banking it is so strong is superhuman I just made the wall call for you but it's
shivered is eternal where oh my god turtle of strength eternal straddles are
Jewish you're in a turn what they're like already Amica oh that's a video
earlier of a guy cooking a turtle cap no I can show you I said I think it's hell
cringe I'll show you right now I don't want to see that he does all right we
You don't have to look at the...
No, wait, wait, wait, hold on.
All right.
What were we talking about?
What about...
Oh, we were talking about Drew Barrymore.
Oh, yeah.
What you said...
But so my question was, is, was she like, I mean, I feel like...
This is...
Oh, this guy.
This is a clip.
This is...
Jack Frost watches cooking.
Okay.
okay actually starting to sound okay all right looks like soup can you dip soup
into another liquid can you turn soup into another yeah you can dip some I was
thinking about last night cuz you could dip a chicken finger in the ketchup but
you can't really dip a liquid into a liquid you take a you take I guess that
the soup is can a frozen motherfucker yeah that's true you freeze one dip that
you can make soup you're gonna do it like this I didn't even realize my
privilege. Yep, yep. Cold. That's why you're here. Yeah. What were you gonna say about
Julie Barrymore? Oh yeah. Well, because I think she doesn't know that much about
banking. I mean she probably knows enough about banking. But I don't think she's making
assumptions about her financial literacy. But what I'm asking I guess is when you
talk to her is it more just like she's like hi I'm Drew Barrymore do you have
any questions about my movies or is it specifically only about banking that
you're talking to her about? That's a good question. Like is it, I mean maybe she
Whether she's an expert or not, you know, is it like, oh, like, I'm, can I have an autograph?
Is it that type of conversation?
She's a human, man.
Is she, is live chat on the app?
She's really talking?
She's really talking.
How'd you search, did you Google, did you find this out, you Google search, I want to
chase Drew Barrymore?
I just met someone sitting on the floor at a mall and they were looking at this Aston
Martin magazine and I had to start chatting up.
And then they told you about this?
They put me on to the Drew Barrymore Chase app.
they're looking at an asset Martin magazine they're probably open up their
bank account millions of dollars yeah that's the point right so you got to pay
attention to people like that in society look at how they move and follow suit
magazine people the leader that would be it that should be a if you have like a
like a black like American Express black card type thing where you have like a
ton of money you should be able to get kind of whoever celebrity you want on
your GPS voice yeah they used to have that with ways right yeah Owen Wilson as
as Lightning McQueen, Morgan Freeman.
- I honestly do, an actual question I have is,
when they get a celebrity to do something like that,
or anybody for that matter,
how do they get them to say every word--
- They don't say every word. - In existence?
- They say every word.
They read the dictionary. - They say, "Turn right,"
and then it goes to the back to the robot voice.
It's kind of a let down. - You know what?
There are way less words than you think there are.
We've collectively, over this whole hour or so
it's been so far, have probably said about--
- 25 minutes. - 80 words.
- That's true. - Well, that is true.
And yet this is ouritarianism and that's another one ism. That's another that's a new word that wasn't said before
What you're gonna do you can I keep going you those kind of sound like you're going in there kind of five fingers of death
Yeah, you're gonna freestyle song
Talking is freestyling. That's true. That is true. Did you ever do sway in the morning as Jack? Yeah, I've been on
I've been on this way play. Yeah, you can search me. Yeah
Yeah, you ever you sound he ever should give you one of those huge beanies. He wears with the brim
No, he did not try to take it every time I see him, but he doesn't like me when I touch him
Maybe with a life has see three hats right now. They're looking pretty good. You want to snag these I do want to snag
I don't want this shit getting crunchy like one of those
Jack Nicholson in the frost yes, sir
Nicholson in the frost yeah, he doing Jack Nicholson
I think that his brain is being obliterated by like chicken nuggets at the Lakers games or yeah
He turned into a marshmallow man, yeah
He does yeah, he should he should try and monetize this somehow
It's a shame to see just something bad happen without me. We like do like a master class
Yeah, exactly you should just
How to eat chicken nuggets so long they died
He's always eating in the Lakers the front seat of the Laker car, and he's doing his thing. What's the Laker car?
Just the front seat
The front seat of what? Front row of the whole stadium. You have no judgment upon where a
chair is and what limits it to. No, no, no. You could be in the back seat right now. I'm
in the passenger side of this table. You are kind of in the, yeah. I want to get a side
car. What would be the front, who would be the driver of this table? Of earth. Of this
table? The driver of earth? That's a heavy question. Santa Claus. He's at the top. Yeah,
I guess that's true. Who is it? Santa Claus? I guess that's true. You don't drive a car
from the top. From the top? Maybe you don't. From inside. I do. Mr. Bean? Mr. Beast? Mr.
Bean drives the car from the top. Jack, do you know Mr. Beast? Jack Frost? Do I know Mr.
Beast? Of course we're in talks. He's always trying to make excellent content videos. Well
he would always, you'd be such a great resource for him. That's true. He's always trying to
freeze shit. I froze 30,000 Indonesian immigrants in a loose area. The least free area in the
The person who melts last gets to keep all the other donuts.
I remember that video where he was like, "I started winter."
And it at least didn't work out. It was a scrapped video.
Yeah, they threw it.
He couldn't make winter happen.
He tried to make winter, but he doesn't have any sort of frozen ability.
I feel like maybe we could get you two to link up.
I mean, I don't want to...
I've talked to Mr. B.
He's also a North Carolina native.
native. He bounces ideas off of us. That's right man. 75 South, Tribeboro, Cookout, Silas Creek Parkway.
What's your cookout order Jack Frost? Don't tell me you're getting five milkshakes for your tray.
No relax. Okay. I'm getting a barbecue pulled pork sandwich with hush puppies, coleslaw.
And what to drink? Yeah, cheer wine. Oh, with Nutella ice. Nutella ice. Nutella ice. That's not a bad idea.
I thought you, I didn't want to get caught like I'm not a North Carolina guy, which I'm not. You're
not. I'm from space. Yeah, it's cold up there in space. Yeah. So you're an alien? How's that work?
Are you snow? Okay. Well, what? Are you snow or are you an alien? Okay, I guess that answers my
I don't know. Do these hands lie?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I mean what else do you guys always wanted to ask Jack Frost? Yeah
I'm on TRT. I'm on HRT. You're doing
Yeah, you're doing on HRC
Hillary
Speaking of routines though, I do kind of want to know your skin care routine because you're
glowing blue and red.
You do look great.
I get one tub of moisturizer, I get one tub of sunscreen, mix them up and then I'll just
let it on my face every day.
You know what I always wanted to do for my skin?
Remember in Wanted where they make themselves into human candles?
No.
Wait, what?
In Wanted?
You don't remember that?
Is Wanted the Curve the Bullet movie?
They make themselves into human candles.
Oh dude, that reminds me.
That's like a mission impossible
and everybody turns themselves into a bunch of
teacups.
Talking about something like that, right?
I remember that. It's an action movie trope.
They always melt themselves into some 3D
printed object.
It's usually a
Beauty and the Beast reference.
It's a paying homage to one of the movies that came
before. Or a cabinet
Oh a cabinet could work line the witch in the wardrobe. Yeah, that's one of them cabinet
That's a cabinet movie for sure
Indian in the cover the original cabinet movie
Do the German expressionism is such a wonderful style that they brought it's gorgeous. Yeah. Oh, it's gorgeous
File I got a lot of time up there in the space. Yeah, what movies do you get up there?
Do you have do you get Wi-Fi or is it a theater situation? Yeah, mostly Wi-Fi movies. Yeah
Yeah. You see like money playing
anything internet related. Yeah.
Yeah. Money playing, snakes on a plane,
airplane, the smiley face killer.
Yeah. A lot of those horror movies.
What's it called? Geek School?
No.
The Geek School.
Bloom House.
Bloom House. Yeah.
They send those up to space?
Bloom House, Hill House.
Yeah. Well.
Yeah.
We need a little scare up there.
It's boring as hell.
It's boring in space?
Yeah.
Don't you have all the laser beams and shit flying by all the time?
planets? Whose laser beams are those? I don't know. You tell me. You're the one in space. I'm
just terrestrial. I'm not saying anything. Okay. I don't know whose is it. Yeah, not much goes on.
You just look around. Yeah. Anti-gravity. That's true. Anti-gravity? So yeah. So the way anti-
gravity works, gravity pulls you towards a heavy object, right? So anti-gravity is...
- It pushes you away.
- It pushes you, it pushes you away, yeah.
- Oh yeah.
- That's fascinating.
- You jump backward.
- So what, so yeah, running forward is running backwards.
- So everything's kind of opposite up there.
- That makes sense.
- It's backwards.
- It's backwards gravity.
- So do you make stuff hot up there and cold down here?
- Hot up there, cold down here.
Oh, you're talking about--
- Jack Frost.
- Jack Frost, having reverse temperature disorder.
(laughing)
- Yeah, that's what I was wondering.
- Is there a problem you have?
- With what?
Reverse temperature disorder.
Do you have any disorders?
No, I got no problem with that.
What disorders do you have?
Reverse temperature disorder, Spillman's curse, what did you ask me?
What disorders?
Oh, what disorders?
I got fucking attitude disorder.
Okay.
Damn.
Alright.
Do they still call it that?
I do.
That seems kind of an outdated term maybe.
What do you...
I just mean like is that, like are you, do you have any mental health issues Jack Frost?
Yeah, like do you struggle with anything?
Do you have an intermittent explosive disorder?
Nope.
of intermittent fasting?
Associative identity disorder?
Associative identity? Nah.
There's not really any mental health
problems for people who go to space.
That makes sense because it probably gives you a lot of perspective.
You get up there and you're like, "Oh, I'm
small as fuck. Nothing really matters all that much."
I'm the jewel at that point.
I have to imagine your IQ is probably pretty high
from being in space. I think that probably makes you smart.
Being in space, you have to
speak in front of the jewel. I bet LP's music
hits completely different in space.
that's not Linkin Park? No. I mean that's technically Linkin Park.
All of his beats are like... I don't know Run the Jewels as a band. Oh, you just know
them as a phrase. Yeah, like "Yo, run the jewels." The phrase is phrasic sense.
But Linkin Park probably hits different up there too. Linkin Park runs the jewels, I'll tell you that much.
I bet Linkin Park's Transformers songs hit different in space.
what I've done. What I've done, New Divide. Oh yeah! Yeah. I know I've talked about
this before. What is the Linkin Park song where the music video they're in a sink?
Oh, is that Breaking the Habit maybe? They're in a sink in them. I don't know.
They're in a sink in most of the videos. Okay. There's this guy at the at the park
I keep seeing. He walks around with this big speaker that has a big Puerto Rican
flag on it and all he plays is Linkin Park remixes. Sick. Yesterday he was
walking around he rolls it around he was playing the wah is a what's the wah?
The wah!
I'll be skating and I hear him just doing that and it hypes me up.
Do you ever think about dressing up in his exact outfit and doing exactly what he does?
That's a good idea.
I should get a big speaker with a Puerto Rican flag on it.
You think that as a joke, but the speakers, the larger speaker is, they can get into the
like $500 or $600 range.
Yeah I think that's a very expensive, it's like, it's not like the flag is hanging on
it.
Like when you see a guy who walks around the subway with a giant boombox, he's made like
a $1000 investment.
Yeah.
But it's not the boom box, it doesn't have a Puerto Rican flag draped over it. It's like
the grate on the meadow is Puerto Rican flag.
It's a big upgrade. He took that to an auto shop and painted it.
GTA speaker. He drove his speaker into a garage.
Well, it's got wheels on it.
True. Hey, if it's got wheels.
If it's got wheels, it can go to an auto shop.
Who's your celebrity crush?
That's embarrassing.
Sorry.
I have to know. Okay, but I have to know. But you can allude to it.
Okay, they're in a movie. Okay, okay.
Okay, let's guess. I think I know who this is. Okay, okay. I think I know.
They, uh... Will, do you want to guess?
No. Okay. Michelle Obama. Does it rhyme with Fousey Foo?
Who? Juicy J?
Lucy Liu? Oh. No, it's, um...
I can't remember her name, but she was in Chuck and Larry.
Chuck and Larry?
Jessica Biel.
Jessica Biel, man.
Woo-wee!
Jessica Biel is, you know who she is, Dave?
She's got to be from the US.
Justin Timberlake.
She's dating Justin Timberlake?
She's married.
No, she's not.
They're married?
Yeah, they're married.
They've been married a long time.
I think Jack Frost can change that.
Fuck Justin Timberlake.
Whoa.
You're doing--
Wait, get it, get it, get it, get Jax.
Yeah, get a punch in.
Get Jax a-- there you go, talk your shit.
Fuck Justin Timberlake.
You have stolen enough property from working class Americans and it's time to return it.
Your episode of whatever it's called, lost, or punked, sucked, um, what?
I think that's your camera.
No, that's not.
No, no, no, no.
I was picking your nose on the camera.
But you can zone too.
Fuck Justin Timberlake.
Whoa.
I didn't even say it again.
I think I heard you the first time.
I was so busy picking your nose.
I take it all back, whatever.
He was such an asshole on the social network.
Because of his hair?
Yeah.
He's a dickhead.
is his activity. He's playing a role guys, relax. Yeah, he's rolling over in his grave.
His roles are fine, but him as a guy is a dick. I think when he bends over he's probably got
some jelly rolls. That's what I'm saying. He's got some of the Don Vito's expresses
on him. He's got veal scallopini all over him. You need to stop eating sushi off of
Jessica Biel's body, you're putting on pounds. Oh my god. Justin, Justin, filter plate. Yep.
Okay, what celebrity do you want to put Ebby in their belly button and suck it out of them?
the fat guy from jackass. Preston Lacey? Or Zackass.
You can put both of their belly buttons together. Oh, Action Bronson. Oh my god. He'd be like a big gulp.
Because of his huge belly button. Yeah it's probably so deep. Yeah it works out.
What if he had a small belly button though? Like how big fat guys have little
nipples? Pretty big. You have a big one actually. Yeah that looks deep. I feel like I could see
your yeah I can touch my stomach through it you touch your stomach no I don't
that is your stomach you can touch my stomach that's foolish I can't even fit
my stomach I have like a I got a scar somewhere on this one you're just a
celebrity yeah which one it does looks like George Costanza that's true okay
there's a scar yeah there's a scar somewhere around there I had a umbilical
hernia yeah your belly looks like a celebrity a bigfoot what do you mean
hairy hairy oh yeah you hairy or does it all the frost kind of work like Bosley
or not the other one ice-cold that's crazy
Steve Hairless do you know I know he did the SNL a couple weeks ago but I didn't
fucking shit gone yeah just service
services no bars try picking it up moving it around holding it get the service can
I see you now yeah talking as an old in the corner in your ceiling can I can you
can I watch you now can I yeah yeah what's this
Oh, still Santa.
Still Santa smiling, yeah.
Yeah, can you just pull up maybe a hot picture of Jessica Biel?
We were talking about her and I was expecting to get kind of sexually aroused.
Oh, he already has a tab open with Jessica Biel.
That's been there.
Wow.
Sexual.
Okay.
Whoa!
This is gonna be not good to...
That is not her.
That is not Jessica Biel.
I know for a fact none of this is her.
That's Jessica.
That is not Jessica Biel.
Looks like it.
Jessica Biel, hardcore sex.
She did this?
didn't do any of this get this off my screen man that one said hashtag the
fappening that one might actually be here oh here were you a victim of the
fappening what's that Jack Frost is that like for every for one day everyone's
allowed to masturbate that'd be like the purge or the happening is splurge
There we go.
Oh, the splurge is good.
The jerge.
[LAUGHTER]
The jizz purge.
Hey, make that up.
Oh, that's the jerge right there.
That guy's jerging hard.
That's a jerging on.
That's a Christmas monster called the jerge.
We probably should have to walk down the--
[LAUGHTER]
God, I wish I looked like that so bad, man.
You don't.
No, it seems nice, but--
He's got sloth from the goonies eye,
because they put a watermark over it.
He looks scary.
That's OK.
Oh, yeah.
Kind of a spiral eye.
Yeah.
I know a guy who had sloth in the goonie eye and he passed.
That's sad.
He passed from sloth in the goonie eye, yeah.
Wow.
That's awful.
I know.
You know they're selling that house from the goonies?
Which one?
Yeah, there's a lot of houses.
The big house at the beginning.
I heard they're selling the ship too.
They're selling the shit out of that.
They're selling the cave.
The ship out of it.
I don't want no part of that cave.
They're selling the ship out of the cave.
Yeah, that's right.
Don't keep me as far away from that cave.
I know, it's scary.
How much would you pay for a cave?
When are they going to sell sloth?
are free. Why do celebrities have been buying all these islands and they're at
the point with private islands where they go to Saudi Arabia and they start
blowing sand into the fucking ocean to make an island that's shaped like a
square. It's so ridiculous. It's crazy right? It's not a real island. So do, but when are
they gonna start moving like okay now I'm trying to move like Batman and I'm
gonna have a cave. When are they gonna do it? I don't know. Should be coming up is all my
That is a good point. I actually just thought of a Jack Frost question you just
actually made me think of one. Have you ever considered, I mean, maybe going to
Hawaii and turning it into a tundra? Yeah, I've thought about it. I've thought
about it. I'm frozen. Apparently a volcano erupted there today. Really? Today? Yeah.
My god. Apparently it's really bad. Are you serious? Yeah, I guess it was a
tragedy. Look at volcano news. Yeah, a big one just blew everyone up and there was
ash. Don't look up sexual at the end of the news. That's interesting. News about did a
volcano erupt. Well it is inherently sexual when the earth busts. Oh it's not
my bad, it began erupting. That's the hottest nut on earth. Wait do people die? I think they
need you. A lot of people are... oh there's a smiley face. Look at this bull crap. I think
people in Hawaii maybe need you right now. There's fire and brimstone. It's an
interesting moral question. Sure. Because just because you have the power does that
mean you have to deny yourself the humanity of just living life? It's like,
"Oh, I was born with an ability to reverse volcano destruction."
Have you seen Hitch?
So you're kind of like Superman.
No, not Hitch.
Hancock.
Dude, that's crazy that you said that and I knew what you were talking about.
I've seen Hitch more than any other program on earth.
I can probably do every line of it.
Do it, go.
Do it, all right, from the top.
Establishing shot, New York City, we're coming in up top.
We got that song playing that I can't remember.
Fuck.
That's not part of the script.
Yeah, you can keep going.
Yeah, it is.
- Yeah, you can keep going.
- You can just say the word.
- Yeah, it is.
(laughing)
Oh, we come in, pull in, we get a close up,
insert shot on Kevin James.
Oh, whoa, I'm tossing the pizza today,
trying to learn how to dance.
And then Will Smith comes through,
he's got the allergic reaction,
and then Eva Mendez is like,
let me show you just what I like.
- And then they go on a see-do, right?
- And then they go on a see-do,
and then, I haven't seen in a while.
- If I see Eva Mendez, I would see her and do her.
- Oh my God, yeah.
Wow.
If I see her, I might do her.
That's a talented sentence.
Yep.
I'm going to patsy you, eat some pads.
I'm going to, I don't mind if I do eat some pads.
I would see, I would see Eva Mendez's pads and I would say ew.
I'd put on pads and eat some.
Those things are nasty.
What are, pads?
Just pads are nasty.
Eva Mendez's pads, I'd see them say ew and then eat them.
I don't know if anyone ever thought about this.
It's so hard to understand. Yeah, for some reason I thought you meant her butt.
Why? I'm talking about the neutral pads. If I see her pad and say "eww" I tie her pad.
I make a pad tie so she can't take it off. You wear her used pad as a tie.
Yeah. You have to be so good at language to have this conversation.
Very high level kind of stuff. Yeah. So that's good. But have you seen Hancock?
Because that's the whole moral dilemma of Hancock. I'd hand her my cock.
Huh? Saw it in theaters twice? Because the fire alarm went off the first time I had to run it back.
That happened to me once. You ran it back afterwards? Then you only saw it once. I saw it 1.5 times.
Okay, that's fine. Yeah. So what are you gonna say about it? Do you... Wow, this is a whole new look.
God damn. Damn. Badass Jack Frost. You look like Slim Shady. Whoa! You look just like Slim Shady.
Whoa! Come on, man. He doesn't even care. You're acting like Slim Shady too, disrespecting fucking
every so disrespectful dude.
- No, I don't.
- Whoa, what the fuck?
- Suck my eyeballs, man.
- Fuck you.
- I don't give a fuck.
- Why do you say that?
- Because it's abnormal, man.
I don't give a fuck.
- Whoa, behaving oddly, dude.
- You're acting ice cold to me, Wade.
- Yeah.
- Oh my God.
- I told you about this syndrome.
- Oh, this is part of the syndrome.
- Sleet snowy.
- Yep, sleet snowy.
- Is that like Slim Shady?
- Yeah, like Slim Shady, sleet snowy.
- Marshall Mathers, it's more like.
yeah what winters yeah weathers Marta Marsha are Mart for Arctic weathers
March Arctic weathers oh that's good Arctic weathers marginal matter in the
new Simpsons movie is there a new Simpsons movie coming out no blue Simpsons
movie dollar marginal matter one of the main characters of the show marginal
matter yeah got a Marge impression in you tell me really oh yeah do you want to
hear my Marge noise I came up with recently. It's if she never made this
noise, but I think she might, she maybe would if she something happened. So this
isn't an impression. This is like this is a what is. This is a speculative.
Hey, Mike acts like Homer. That's right. That's right. I respect you. Wait,
check this out.
Marge. Marge. Check this out.
Yeah. Okay. Okay. Okay. But here's a joke. Tell us.
Marge would never make that noise.
- Well, that's the whole point.
- Yeah, it's speculative.
She wouldn't make it in the show, but like--
- What if Marge made that noise
while she was snoring? - What if Marge made--
True.
- I'm in a disgusting mood,
but maybe that's the sound that her--
- Then don't say it.
- Don't, yeah, I don't even wanna hear it.
- You're in a disgusting mood?
- I'm just in a nasty sex kinda mood.
- Oh, I hear you saying, you're riled up.
- Yeah.
That made you, that riled you up?
- Little bit.
I was saying like, you know when something comes--
- See, you're perfect, you're good at it.
- I'm not good at it.
- You're not good at it.
- I wish I didn't do that.
- Do it again.
- I wish I didn't do it.
- You kind of have Bart hair.
No, he looks just like Eminem, dude.
What are you talking about?
- It's like a Bart in the shower.
- Here's a good question.
Speaking of Mark, I'll go Marin on you.
- Oh my God.
- Who are you guys in terms of coldness?
In terms of coldness and temperature?
- Low temperature.
- Who are my lowest temperature guys?
- Yeah.
- Or just guys that inspire you.
- Your cats.
Oh, I see. My influences?
Yeah, like who is the generation above you?
The class above you?
I mean, you gotta give it up for, like,
Lenny Bruce, man, just put truth on blast.
Yeah.
It revolutionized the comedy industry.
And then, like, you know, I'm an annoyance guy, so like,
I feel like Tim Robinson really made the Chicago comedy scene
what it is.
Yeah.
The annoyance was a Chicago theater?
That Jack Frost used to roll through?
Oh, Jack Frost?
Jack Frost.
I thought you were asking me, Jack Bensinger, what are your biggest comedic influences?
[laughter]
And you went Lenny Bruce and then Tim Robinson?
Those are your two?
I got the list tattooed on my back.
Lenny Bruce and Timmy.
You have a Tim Robinson tummy rocker in Old English?
Yeah.
Tim Robinson?
That'd be sick, dude.
Don't talk about this shit.
Hey, we got, well, Hitmonchan. That's Hitmonchan.
Yeah, I was saying Hitmonchan.
Did you play Pokemon growing up?
Yeah, I played Pokemon.
Which one? Ice Cold?
Blue Ice.
Blue Ice Crystals.
Yeah, man. I always thought that I had Pokemon in my attic.
Come to find, just squirrels and rats.
Squirrels and rats in your attic?
They lived together?
the most fucked up house that was unfortunately destroyed by a flood in
2019 growing up. For real? That's tragic. In Virginia?
Why didn't you freeze it? Refrigerator flood. What the hell are you talking about?
My refrigerator was running and nobody was home and the water from the fridge just
completely melted my house. Nobody even bothered to call? What? Nobody even bothered to call?
Call what? To ask? Oh because of the prank? Yeah. It's not funny man, my childhood home was destroyed by a
refrigerator running. Isn't that the most twisted sense of irony?
And my home was destroyed by it. Yeah. Damn. How does the entire home get
destroyed by that? Because we had a split-level house and so the fridge was
up top and my whole house is made out of wood. And so it just yeah really
ate through it. Wait so it like... because my fridge at home is broken and it
leaks water all the time. Mine was leaking brown fluid. Mine leaks a red fluid.
I think sticky brown fluid.
And then my dog walks up and eats it and I just go "Ahhh"
Is it cherry juice?
No I have no cherries anywhere near my house.
I touched my liquid with my finger.
Mine looks like chili oil.
It was sticky.
It could be chili oil.
It's gotta be syrup.
I cleaned it. You know what it was? It was rotten.
Oh wait, you already knew?
No I found it out later.
It was a sweet potato.
On the top of the fridge.
Isn't that horrible?
That never happens again.
I don't have sweet potato anymore.
You thought that was the problem?
What was that specific one?
Oh yeah, get rid of that thing.
You probably got your problem pretty much fixed.
Because they were brand new too.
So tell me, you're hitting up, you're a celebrity, you're rich, and you're all about ice.
Are you walking down Johnny Dang, icing you out, brand new chain, walking around Paul
Wall style?
Johnny Depp ice.
Oh yeah.
People see me walking down the street and they know that I have money based on my appearance.
I'm Jack Frost, man. I'm rich. Duh.
Yes, sir. Duh.
Put some music under that.
Yeah.
They sampled you for that.
Like they did Trinidad James in that one song.
Where they said, "Don't believe me, just watch."
They sampled the word "watch."
They gave him like $3 million for that.
He didn't even do vocals on it.
The guy who made the song just was friends with Trinidad James.
Who the fuck is that?
Had no money anymore.
the guy Trinidad James? No, Trinidad James. He's that song that's like "gold all in my
watch" "gold on my watch" "hello hello hello" yeah. I don't remember if that's the lyrics but probably close to that.
It was. Part of the song where he says hi to the audience. That was with a...
He waved to every single person. That was a scrapped take. He walks up and down.
I feel so good when Trinidad James does that. That was a scrapped recording take where his phone rang during
and when he was singing the song in the studio.
Yeah, and he went, "Hello, hello, hello."
You really do look so much like B-Rabbit to me these days.
You have more... Oh, you want more water?
If it's going around, I don't want to be weird about it.
Yeah, yeah, come on. There you go.
Alright. Alright, so...
Here, I'll pour it for you.
Here, go ahead and pour it.
B-Rabbit.
Should we do it more over the electronics?
Yeah, it's pretty good.
Thanks, man.
Wow.
I might hit that a little bit myself.
Stuff's good.
Why don't we just get like a cooler thing for it?
D-O. Are you made of fucking money?
No.
Because he's made of snow.
It's true.
I'm made of money.
Jack's drinking that whole thing.
Look at that.
Oh my god, you're going to have to pee so bad.
He's got ice to produce.
You know that I hold the record for the world's slowest chug?
Really?
You hold it?
You are going really slow.
I'm not seeing that cup move at all and somehow you're still gulping.
Oh, he's kind of tasting.
It's in the middle.
Okay.
put you through the whole thing. How long would it take you if you're at your
slowest to drink that? Competition or just practicing? Competition, Coney Island.
Coney Island slow chug competition? It's a smaller competition but they do it
kind of in the same part. They do it in the winter. Well so are you allowed to do
that? I mean I don't know if you guys ever had as a school child you ever
did a slow race you ever tried to do a race where you're at going slow but
people some people would be clowns they go backwards and can you do that in the
slow chug? Can you spit up water? Can you just not drink? I'm gonna get it. I don't know.
You have to have a clear regulation cup.
It says here that you're worth 1.2 million. That's a lot. That's your revenue in 2022.
That's not what it's worth.
I was gonna say, that's not even close. That's just my revenue last year. That's probably
not even including my streaming. That's probably not even including...
You stream?
Yeah, man.
You're on Twitch?
Hasan Abi. That's you? Yep. Whoa you do a zip up all the way up? That's me man. Oh my god.
I clean up good. You do yeah. I had no idea that was you. I didn't realize you were
so political. Super political. Damn. I'm like a super political guy. Yeah. What's your
what what's your politics? Well you know it depends on the issue. Uh-huh.
Abortion. Um clean it up man. Clean up the abortion? Yeah clean up your act. Okay.
Wait should we clean up the most of my opinions are 3,000 years in the future
Well you're in space developing these yeah, just like who'd you vote for
West election
Biden Biden yeah
Just the most sensible thing Trump is Trump was a wreck
He was the second he got into office his policies were you know all over the place
Where do you think, are you thinking in this next, you think he's gonna win the nomination
in this next cycle?
You know, it's not looking good for him after the midterms.
I do feel like it's hard to even imagine anymore a world where Trump doesn't win a primary,
but it's really starting to look like that.
I know that a year is a long time from now.
It's, you know, it's, we didn't, everybody got the midterms wrong this time.
So it's really, it's a weird place to even try and pretend to know how to predict these
elections at this point, yeah.
- Do you think DeSantis might win?
- Sure.
- DeSantis.
- It's certainly gonna, uh!
(laughing)
- Oh wow.
- I needed that.
- Who's your guy in 2024?
- My guy in 2024?
It's President Belly, man.
I'm trying to gain weight.
- Trying to gain weight.
- I'm trying to gain weight.
Yeah, big time.
- Are you saying you'd become President Belly?
I'm hoping President Belly maybe comes up
and he's like, "You're everybody."
is my belly. Oh, I get you. I listen to my belly, that's it. What's the country? It says
here President Belly is President Reagan. Can you put this up here? If you search President
Belly, President Reagan is... Your bro Reagan? You didn't know that? You're bringing him
back? Yeah, vote for him. You froze him? I ride him in. Yeah, wait, so what other things
can you Google that have something weird come up? What if you search President... Try it,
Space Invaders. It is so fun having Google, right? You can play Space Invaders. I would
I never sit at my house and just Google things and look at the results, but it is so fun
to do here.
Yeah.
Something about somebody else doing it for you, I'm like, "Oh my gosh, I'm blessed."
Maybe.
Space Invaders, doesn't play.
It's not your own Bing, that's the issue, I think.
No, it didn't work.
Yeah, I don't know why you use Bing so much, Jubio.
All right, so let's go ahead and play this, I guess, really quick.
I don't think we want to play Space Invaders.
Okay, let's just go ahead and play this really quick.
No, no, no, I don't think we'll play Space Invaders.
Hotline Bing.
Favorite video game, Jack Frost.
That's a tough one.
I don't know.
No, no, no, I don't think we'll post this.
Favorite video game, Jack Frost?
That's a tough one.
Maybe Bomberman.
I thought you'd say Ice Climbers.
I thought you were going to say Jack Frost Adventures.
Let me try again.
Cold War.
Wait, what's your favorite war?
My favorite war is the Ice War.
The Ice War?
When did that happen? Who was that between?
That was 1913 between East Timor and Papua New Guinea. East Timor? East Timor?
Right? What's Timor? Google it. East Timor. Search Ice Wars. No. Yeah. Okay. Oh I've never
even heard of this place. Yeah. All right. They got a nice flag. I guess you've seen
all the world because you're a famous celebrity. Yeah. How old are you? I can name every country
right now. Okay, try it. America, Canada, Mexico, Guatemala, Honduras, Belize,
Nicaragua, Salvador, Panama, yeah Venezuela, Colombia. You want me to keep going in this
order or should I? What is the order here? Top to bottom. The earth is a line. Okay.
and America to the top and then Canada and then Mexico? Yeah, the bottom is Tuvalu.
Tuvalu, which is another country I'm not so familiar with. Kiribati.
What? Kiribati. I don't know what that is. You guys really don't know every
single oceanic island? No. What do you do all day up there in space? I guess he
sees them all from space. What else am I gonna do? I got no internet and I got these, I'm
looking down at the earth and I just see the names of the countries on the
different colors. You can see the names. They don't tell you that about space.
Yeah. Whoa. All the names on top just so it makes it easier for a traveler. I
wouldn't be surprised. That makes sense for a space traveler. Yeah. You ever get hit
by any of that space junk? I get hit on by ladies with space junk. Oh my god.
Oh my god, holy shit. That was fucking crazy dude. Yeah bro. Oh my god, how did you do that?
Alright, yeah. Only got a couple minutes left. Okay. Yeah. What did you ask? Do I have to
get hit by a space junk? No, no, now I want to know about your love life. Where are you
fucking these women with space junk? Making love, making love. Oh, okay. When you say
Space junkie mean like those galaxy pants?
Maybe?
Yeah, like disco pants?
Yeah, kind of a...
What is disco pants?
Are they human?
Shiny?
Oh, okay.
Yeah, there's a fuckload of humans up there.
Okay.
Every one of us.
Do you ever hop at the ISS, maybe get a shot of every single liquor from every single country
because they're all up there?
Damn, that would be so fucking sick, dude.
Can you imagine doing a bar crawl in the ISS?
Holy shit.
You'd be drunk as a skunk.
Now in Korea, you would be.
From the Twinkling Star?
Yeah.
You'd start at the Twinkling Star and then you go to...
What is that?
you go to international space station that is the twinkling star ron's galaxy
it's all the bars and bars and the space station
the ron and then and then shea jupiter that's a restaurant that has a bar in it
exploded on her way up there the carissa mccullough rocket ship
exploded yeah it was not her that exploded and then the ship caught on
fire we don't know sorry was there a security
camera in there no there was a security guard in there he didn't do his job
trying to make sure no teachers explode on you i know you've been exploded on by
a couple teachers. I can just tell man. You've got a smile. There's a pain behind that.
There's pain behind it and romance in a sense. But I didn't know anything. I
thought when when everybody told me that story when I was a kid because I was too
young to know what was happening there or maybe I wasn't alive I don't remember
but that when it exploded. You were not alive when the Challenger exploded.
when was your parents died before you were born?
Oh yeah. I was not alive.
89?
88, 89, something like that.
I think it was in 1720.
I thought it was in 69.
That's probably why it was quite exploded.
No idea. I built a spaceship in 1720.
Who's sticks?
Krista McAuliffe was a teacher in New Hampshire.
Oh, that's why you know.
Yeah.
That's why it exploded.
We had to learn about that all the time.
Were you related?
No.
Was she bad?
She wasn't bad?
She was bad at flying a spaceship.
- They like to show us off.
- This is so wrong, this is so wrong, man.
- She was in like a cartoon UFO.
It's just her in like a glass dome.
- Can we just show respect, man?
Can we show respect to people who are dead?
- I used to have a poster of the Challenger.
- You were a weird, tortured child.
- I had a, jeez, I had this as a grownup.
- That's not right.
- I had a poster of all of them.
- I bet you had an action figure of the falling man
from 9/11. - It said America's Heroes
and it was just a photo of all the Challenger victims.
They're not heroes.
Yeah.
That's why I had it in my room.
Isn't that heroic?
I hung it up in my...
It's not heroic to die, dude.
Yeah.
I guess it's nice of them to not fall on a suit.
That was heroic of them.
Dude, let me say this.
Thank God everybody knows how the 9/11 planes flew into the Twin Towers.
You know some kind of secret?
Someone threw this?
All I'm going to say is this.
Stop doing Tee Hee.
Stop doing Tee what?
doing tea what? Tea heat. You know Michael Jackson. All I gotta say is thank God
they didn't throw the 9/11 planes into the whole earth instead of into the
buildings. That would have sucked. We're all on it at the time. Yeah. I need water.
You've been using so much water. Wait what were you saying? I don't think I was saying anything.
you froze me yeah you came in here and froze me up you did that's what I do
froze my frost jokes LLC Jack Frost jokes freezing people LLC Jack is there
anything that you want to you want to tell the people about Jack Frost tune in
to wildin out this week are you on wildin out here you would be such a good
wildin out. You would be incredible. The thing is I'm the most wild one because they
call it wildin out everyone's there sitting playing by the rules of these
here's a game here's the rules of the game you'd have no you know out go wild
Yeah, yeah, forget the games. Pull your hair out. Pull your hair out. Yeah, take your pants off. Twerk. Twerk.
Twerk. You can twerk on Wild 'N Out. Twerk. Is twerking cheating? Yes. On your wife?
Yeah, what kind of cheating? Is grinding cheating? Yes. Yeah. Definitely. If you get a boner, if you're not
doing funny grinding with your guy friends at different parties. Yeah, funny
grinding is good. Funny grinding is not cheating because it's funny. Actually, have
you ever have you ever gotten an audition for Wild 'N Out? No but I got cheated on
in college. By like a cast member or just? By my significant other. But why does that have to do with Wild 'N Out?
I asked about Wild 'N Out. We were talking about those two things directly weren't we?
I mean a little I guess earlier. I thought you meant cheating at the games in Wild 'N Out.
You can't cheat at those games they're fucking bulletproof. Yeah that's so true
the CIA needs to focus up on what Nick Cannon is doing over there. There's no way you can
get past those rules. You guys want to go see Wild 'N Out Live at Madison Square Garden?
I really do. Really? Yeah, it's happening. Hell yeah. It is happening. Are you down to
go? Let's do a vlog. Let's do a vlog. Alright. Let's cut to it right now. Alright, thank
you Jack for us. No problem guys. Watch your backs. Go check out... Watch your backs. What
Watch your back. He might nip at your nose.
Somebody nipped at my nose.
Yeah.
My nose looks like a nipple.
Yeah, a little bit.