(upbeat music)
(howling)
- Does that make you sad?
- That was less than a second.
I said a second after I clapped and that was--
- Does that make you sad?
- What, a go?
- A dog.
- Try it.
- A dog making a sound.
- See if this is what you actually--
(howling)
- That makes me happy.
- That's, yeah, that's not that bad to me.
You know what it sounds like?
Here's the thing, dog being sad, oh it's breaking my heart.
A wolf being sad, fuck you wolf.
Yeah.
Fuck you.
I trust a wolf more than a dog.
Fucking suck my dick you fucking wolf.
Suck your dick?
Not really man.
You want a wolf to suck you?
They got huge teeth, I don't want a wolf to suck my dick.
I don't think a wolf knows how to suck.
What do you mean?
I don't want a wolf to suck my dick.
You're stroking your beard.
Give me this one thing dude.
Just let me have this.
You can't grow a beard.
Not like me.
- Look at my shit right now.
- Oh man.
- Saying I can't grow a beard.
What's this then?
Don't touch it!
It's seriously, I'm allergic to you!
Stop.
- I just touched you.
I just touched you, you're gonna break out in hives, bitch.
- I'm gonna break you out in my hive.
- I'm gonna break your hive in.
- And me and my thousands of brothers.
- Break out of the hive would be a good movie
about being kidnapped by bees.
- Yep.
- Why would it be a good movie?
- Break out of the hive.
- Break out the hive, you bee.
- The hive is not that big.
Break out that damn hive, bee.
Godspeed, you black and yellow bee.
It's either either giant bees or tiny me's.
Yeah.
Giant bees versus tiny me.
[LAUGHTER]
Have you guys ever seen that video?
Giant bees versus tiny me.
That is an amazing title.
That's an amazing idea.
You came up with gold just there.
Just there.
That would be a good movie, though.
Yeah, tiny bees versus--
No.
No, sorry.
Giant bees versus tiny me.
Because tiny bees versus giant me is normal.
Yeah, that's not a movie.
Giant bees versus tiny me's is pretty good.
Yeah, and there's a lot of me.
Yeah.
So is it one, is it just a couple bees and a whole lot of me's?
It would be a lot of bees.
Who do you guys think would win?
100 duck-sized horses or one horse-sized horse?
No, let's get into this.
100 duck-sized horses versus one horse-sized horse.
No, let's attack this from all angles.
What do you think, Woodwin?
One duck-sized duck or 100 horse-sized horses?
This is the kind of question that we could go on for hours.
One duck-sized duck.
Okay.
You said one duck-sized duck.
One duck-sized duck or 100 horse-sized horses or 100 planet-sized destroyers.
I'm gonna go with the destroyers.
Which one would you rather fight, dude?
A horse-sized duck or a thousand duck-sized horses?
Let's get into this.
Okay, let's hit it.
Yeah.
If I was a grizzly bear, I would win against both.
Yeah, well, it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter?
No, no, no.
It's about who would win between the duck-sized duck.
size. Oh, he said, who would you rather? Which am I?
You're the dark Santa.
You're Santa. Actually, Santa wins Santa versus everybody like a Detroit versus
everybody shirt. Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
Everybody might be a pretty good.
I almost wrote Santa versus everybody.
I did.
I wrote it, but I did write a song.
I did write a Christmas rap.
Yeah, we're not going to save that.
I feel like maybe I did write a Christmas.
Would you want to do the right now?
At the right at the top. OK, I did.
Can we before me? Can we check in on Santa first?
Yeah, oh, yeah, yeah, can I just say yeah before we go any further I wrote a Christmas rap that does have
Themes of that are similar to what we were just talking about and it's crazy that that was that was brought up
It's almost as if you read my rap. I didn't read I'm not a rap read. It's also it is truly
I truly almost I wrote one line of Santa versus everybody and then I said I don't want to do this
It's too much work. I couldn't read your rap because a rap doesn't make any sense to me
I'm one of those people where people are rapping and I just don't know what they're talking about.
I typically don't listen to rap or read rap, I listen to it.
I don't even do that.
I feel it.
I don't do any of that.
I don't understand the words but I feel the emotion behind it.
I don't listen to it, I avoid it.
I understand the inflections.
I don't understand what they're saying but I can tell it means something.
Yeah, absolutely.
Alright, let's check in on Santa.
Yeah, let's see where Santa's at today.
Let's pull up the Santa tracker that we have, our software.
Oh, well he's still on Earth, guys.
Oh, that's good. Now. Where's this?
Near the North Hawaii. Yes, this is Hawaii. I think it looks like Hawaii. Oh, my shit
I'm Motel 6 in the Arctic. They have Arctic they have Motel 6. Why is he at a Motel 6?
Is he the hell could be staying there? Oh
It's December, why is it the
Bigger oh my god. He's getting bigger, but don't cry. Don't cry scary. Oh
Okay, don't wait bigger Santa get smaller there. We there you go, but what's he doing not at his house
He's at a motel. Fuck if I know dude something must be kind of off over it
What's the fuck did you do Santa white bitch is being an adulterer and he's fucking bald
Jesus it's a bald under the hat and he has oh my god. He is
He has mystical sigils behind him.
Look how scared he is.
Look how unhappy she looks.
I can't tell if that... Here's the thing though.
We don't know that he's cheating. That could be just a goth child.
Yeah.
That could be Mrs. Claus and that's his mom.
Yeah, we don't know.
We don't know. We don't have all the facts.
The only facts we have is that Motel 6 is sad and this happened.
You'd think that Santa would be able to afford something better than Motel 6.
6 all those sponsorship deals he's doing sprite commercials yeah yeah Santa's
doing Santa also has a residency is at the Christmas tree shop yeah exactly
yeah and they get Waltham I don't think there's a I don't think there's a
Christmas tree shop I bet there's a Christmas tree shop there and where
you're Waltham Waltham Waltham are you kidding me do all the Waltham how do you
say it's Waltham Waltham fake New Englander I know I genuinely I did I
I didn't understand what he was trying to say because I assumed he would know how to say
Waltham.
Fake New Englander.
Wow.
I thought it was called Waltham.
We caught him.
I've heard people say Waltham.
We finally got him.
Well, check this out.
Check this out.
He said, "Oh, I'm from Boston."
Fake, dude.
Haverhill.
Completely fake.
Oh my God.
Fuck you.
That one's Haverhill.
Haverhill.
You dumbass Haverhill.
Me dumbass?
Yeah, you dumbass?
I'm from North Carolina.
I don't give a fuck about...
You dumbass bitch.
We got a place.
Oh, you're from North Carolina, right?
Yeah.
No.
You're not even saying that right. It's Bolivia.
There's no O.
Bolivia. Shut up man. We should play a game where you guys have to pronounce normal words.
Yeah. Yeah. Worcestershire sauce.
No. That's not a normal word.
That's far from normal.
What's a...
Yeah so say the word we're supposed to pronounce and we'll pronounce it.
Western Central South America.
Let's just do our chants.
Or our cray-rolls.
We wrote some Christmas cray-rolls.
For today. I mean continuing the Christmas
Christmas coverage. Everyone knows December full Christmas. We're doing 360
degrees on Christmas. 360 days of Christmas. A Christmas perspective.
And a lot of you might be saying, Caleb you already wore this
Santa outfit. Yeah and I'm gonna wear it all. And why don't you show, why don't you,
you're very committed to wearing the Santa outfit. Why don't you show
everybody I'm exactly exactly what happened before the episode see right
here is completely look don't rip it more I'm not trying to rip it more I'm just
showing the how ripped it is it's okay to have ripped pants learn that from Bob
No, no learn that from
Shit out of me Lenny Kravitz
SpongeBob Square remember Lenny Kravitz split his huge dick dick flew out and he had a ring on it
Yeah, where's some fucking underwear thing pointed out of his pants like a finger yeah, dude
I won't even show it online not a big
on Bing. Look up Lenny Kravitz penis. That's how disturbing it was. You google Santa Claus
on Bing and it shows you a guy eating poop. You google Lenny Kravitz penis and it won't
show it to you. There it is. Pull that up. That is not Lenny Kravitz. I don't think either
of those two people are Lenny Kravitz. That's Merlin Gate. Dude. Alright. Wait, wait, there's
the gift right there. No, don't show this to Lenny Kravitz. Don't show that. You can show
this Fortnite guy. That's Lenny Kravitz nowadays. Yeah, that's what happened to him after all
that. He put on more clothes. Do you think his daughter saw his penis? His daughter definitely
saw his penis every day she was raised by him. Yeah. Do you think his daughter Zoe saw
that on the news and was like, "Damn, my dad's penis is out." Probably said, "Damn, my dad's
penis is huge. You think her penis is as big as her dad's? She's got a big clit that poked
through the Batgirl costume. Yeah. I'll say it, I will never ever meet her. That is just
not gonna happen. That's not the kind of life I plan on living. Yeah. I will never meet her
and she has a big, stinky, bright red Rudolph clit. It's nasty. Her pink hair is a little
emo in the movie. That's a pink hair in that movie? It's a pink, she puts pink
hair on in the movie I believe. Here's the thing about Batman. I believe. He was a
he was a tad emo. Yeah. It's like Batman is supposed to be. He was kind of like me in a way.
More like this guy in the costume. That's a terrible parody. Batman in the shirt.
I just thought of it right on the spot. You guys both shut up because this is the parody.
Jokers in the way.
Jokers not in that movie.
Well he's at the very end. He's not in the way though.
Jokers in the jail.
Yeah. That's okay.
The Riddlers in the way.
Yeah. He is in the way.
Penguin.
The penguins in the way.
That would be a perfect,
that movie would have been a perfect candidate
it for having a rock and roll or a rap song in the credits that says the events
of the movie.
True.
Bring it back.
Yeah, or just a remix of that.
The penguin was in the way.
That's another reason the Addams Family movie is so good.
That's a great parody.
The penguin's in the way, the Batgirl's in the movie, the Riddler's in the way,
the Joker's in jail.
Yeah, because that's also the that's that happens in the order.
That's the order.
Yeah, that's the order.
Speaking of singing, we have these beautiful carols.
Yep.
Who wants to go first?
I feel like you're usually Mr. First.
Yeah.
That's not my fault.
Yeah, I know.
There's nothing wrong with it.
It's good.
It's horrible.
First is the--
Why is that bad?
First is the burst.
I have to bare my soul for everybody.
And then--
Second is the--
See, you just said first is the burst.
You know what we call that in stand up?
Call it a bullet.
Exactly.
A bullet.
A bullet is scary.
Yeah.
And mine's not good.
Where did I put my phone?
Uh oh. Whoa. Mr. Unprepared.
No, it was right here. It blended in with a black wire.
Damn, that's gotta suck.
It's pretty embarrassing.
I can't even imagine what that's like.
So, mine...
You said "mime"?
Mine...
Why would I say "mime"?
A mime can't sing, dumbass.
Mine is...
First of all, it's called...
It's a satire for part of it.
It's called...
Part of it is satire, but the rest is true.
You'll just... You'll take it as it comes.
I'll say... I'll put it that way.
But it's called The Problem with Christmas Lists Nowadays.
And it... I took the tune...
I took the tune... And the tune might sound familiar,
but I changed everything about the lyrics and the message of the song.
I just took the tune... A classic Christmas tune.
Because I felt that would make it easier for me to sing it.
But I changed everything about it.
And it's about... It's called The Problem with Christmas Lists Nowadays.
What's that song it's the tune of I think you'll hear it when I sing it. That's a really fair point
Can you play the I think I'll sing the Christmas?
Why you first get on this shit? I first you make me go first second you ruin my life
That's a Christmas list right there. Yep. This is the problem with Christmas lists nowadays
and
It's where you going he hates your song
He hates your song so much
I just had to change the camera angle. What if that made it worse? Okay, okay here we go.
All right, okay. I'm gonna sing it now. This is my carol, so imagine being sang this at a door.
Your door. Well you gotta knock first buddy. You can't just sing it at my damn door.
Hello?
Fancy make a pack of beer, new air fryer, golfing gear,
candle fire selfie stick, MacBook laptop supreme brick, brand new car sedan or
coupe. Me, I want a hula hoop. Everyone else wants expensive gifts, but I like
hula hoops. Wow. That's a beautiful carol. People nowadays want expensive stuff.
Yeah. Whatever happened to a... Me, I want a hula hoop. Whatever happened to a
hula hoop right yeah that was used to be a good old-fashioned hula do you remember
that used to want that you remember that when you were a kid you'd walk down
there and you'd see some big ring that was wrapped up and he thought maybe
that's a hose or a pet snake that nowadays you know kids would see it that
and they'd be like oh my god what I'd exactly what I wanted a giant ring one
that's for my only fan that's right and I'm 12 yeah that's what actually what
could happen these days what happened to hula hoop the hula hoop craze swept the
world dying out in the 1980s except in China and Russia. Wow. Whoa where hula
hoop and hoop manipulation. Hoop manipulation. Whoa. That's what I bet China
and Russia are doing it right. I see this dude in the
park sometimes speaking of hoop manipulation. He is in a big ring. He
stands in the middle of the park, Maria Hernandez, and he spins, he spins, he
gyrates in this hoop like like he's in the center of the hoop and the hoop is
going like he's going upside down yeah I've never seen him if you go to the
center of Maria Hernandez all the time the center the scent like the way the
big might be powering the poor I think he is I think he's powered by the there's a
generator under there's a big magnet that's a magnet yeah human generator
yeah literally dr. Manhattan oh my god I really want I really want one of those
Pat one of those things that you put a piece of metal on it. He wants a Pat. Okay.
Alright well never mind then. I don't want okay. This kind of Pat. I thought he meant me.
I'm not gonna say I don't like getting Pat. I'll actually go by Patrick because I have a cousin who has the same name.
What about a Pat from Pat? Yeah that's fine. It's not really doing that much. Me I want a hula hoop.
I can get you a hula hoop. It's not that crazy. For real? Yeah probably a nice wooden artisan one too.
Made in Africa. A Brooklyn one? Yeah what? A Brooklyn style hula hoop? I can get you a Brooklyn style one.
A craft hula hoop?
Damn, an artisan hula hoop for my best friend.
I'll get you an artisan hula hoop.
The thing about me, I would love that, but I'd also be happy with any old thing that
costs one cent or less.
Yeah.
Nowadays people are like, "I want an iPad, I want an iPhone, I want an iPod."
Meanwhile, I'm like, "I paid."
Yeah.
I pay for all that stuff.
Damn.
With my taxes.
Yeah.
And you know what? I don't even care. If he's paying, I'm going to get whatever I want.
I got the most insulting question yesterday from my own fucking wife. She asked me, she was like,
for Christmas do you want us to get each other a vacuum I want to pay for half of
a vacuum and open it up ago Merry Christmas to me the hell it pissed me
off so bad dude I was like fuck no you better be buying me something from
brookstone dude what about a vacuum from brookstone okay I don't do that I want a
massage chair yeah right I want to something that circulates water on my
air gun I want to put a toilet no what's it called what's it called a bidet yeah
I want to what it don't know what this part of your body it cleans it clean
what you do to this and it goes right on your ass they should make a bidet with
artificial intelligence I can speak to you yeah yeah it says you're doing so
good yeah hey Ludwig good boy they had that on yeah they had that in invention
city really shut the fuck up they did shut the fuck up they had that in
invention city first of all you never been there second of all I'm not so sure
exists you fucking hula-hoop mother fucker stick to your hula hoops and let
me handle the artificial intelligence. They're making a square hoop. Whoa! In
Invention City. That's cool. Yeah for your square ass. Lose some weight you right-angled
motherfucker. Lose some weight? That wouldn't help me lose weight. If you lose weight you
become more right-angled. Don't tell Cameron to lose weight. You lose weight. I've been
trying. Both of you lose... I've been doing one meal a day. You've been doing OMAD? I've
been doing one meal a day. Nice dude. Everything you ate? Uh-huh. I document everything that
I eat. Really? Uh-huh. I would love for you to become a fitness YouTuber. I've been working
on I have this new weight loss method I've been using the the that crystal
machine from the dark crystal yeah suck the food out of me really deflate yeah
whoa I put myself in a chair and I go yeah I'm living off of modeling and
since it's it I only know it's not if you're trying to lose weight getting
into a James and the giant peach situation oh my god yeah that your way
pure sugar yeah peach we're being blown up mm-hmm
I'm dying dying would put a I said that being blown up by a balloon but it would
really suck to get blown up and explode in the middle of your weight loss
journey yeah I did think yes you lick your beard I just try to push my lips
out of it cuz it gets my lips get stuck behind it cuz I big fucking beautiful
lips cuz I could be Puerto Rican we haven't we don't know really we don't
know. Are you doing 23andMe for Christmas? No, I'll probably never do it. Are we still
gonna do the 23andMe off? 25andMe, December 25th. Oh! With the, what was it, the contest
you guys were gonna do? That's a really good amount to have. It was like a contest that
you and Cam were gonna have to see who was like the best. Yeah, and it was your idea
and you were like, and then you're gonna rank the races. Yeah. That was not my idea. You
did say that. You said we could. We were like, we wanna do it but we don't want it to be
racist and you're like you guys should rank the races from one to one thousand
and we're like Pat one thousand yeah there's a thousand races you think we're
gonna get one thousand races on our you got me pretty racist to think there's a
thousand races you're making some subdivisions that are yeah you're doing
some a-1 you're like dividing up like different types of Irish people yeah
- Yeah, that's bad. - That's unhealthy.
- Yeah, I would say there's four.
- There's four races.
- I don't know.
- I don't think there's any number you can say
that's not a bad number to say.
- There's zero.
- There's one race. - Besides one.
One is okay to say.
- There's one. - There's one race.
- White people.
- No.
- No, no, no, no.
- The other ones.
- Pangean.
- What? - We're all Pangean.
- I thought you said Indian.
- Nope.
(laughing)
- I was like, whoa.
- Okay, there's two races.
- That would be funny to--
- The human race and the Arcturans.
- It would be funny to do that,
like we're all one race, the Pangean race.
Or like, there's only two races,
Pangean and those friggin' Italians.
- Mm, that'd be awesome.
- Yeah, I don't like, I don't,
typically I find it funny to make fun of the Italians.
- You know what, speaking of fuckin'--
- It's funny to make fun of Italians for me again.
- Speaking of--
- I know, it's overdone. - I like the pizza.
It's overdone, but you know, it's funny to me again.
- Man, speaking of fucking awful.
- These are the races.
- These are the race, oh, this is a pretty,
this is a pretty comprehensive list.
- Yeah, this is all the races.
This is why I want you guys to do 23B.
- Kobold, Lougherin, Leprechaun, Miri Lanikode.
- I would say there's a strong possibility
that I'm part Sawakadam, Sawookadam.
- Or Skullsworn.
- Oh, I always thought I'd been Doomfallen or Bicknill.
I thought it said bikini.
- Me too. - Could be.
Listen up. - Bikini killers.
- Speaking of fucking awful racist awfulness,
and stop ranking them.
He ranked human as S tier.
- Yeah, for shit.
- Yeah.
Listen, I'm sure you guys have seen all this news
about Kanye West, right?
So I thought it was about high time.
I didn't do a Christmas carol, I'm gonna be real with you.
- You did a holiday carol?
- I did myself a holiday poem
that attacks violently Kanye West
for his horrible new beliefs.
And I thought it was about high time
that somebody takes him to task.
So I'd like to take him to task right here and right now.
And if you notice while I'm reading this,
I actually used pieces of what he's written
to attack himself like a mirror.
'Cause that's something that he should be looking at.
It's called Kanye Poem.
Kanye, you used to be a champion,
but I've become so appalled by your anti-Semitic remarks.
As an ally, now I see you in my nightmares.
I used to love your music, but now if I hear your music,
I run away from it.
When I saw your tweet, I thought about killing you.
(laughing)
Your music is gorgeous, but you are so heartless.
You're playing the blame game with the Jewish people,
you monster.
You used to be my amazing big brother.
(laughing)
But now I will throw you up until you touch the sky.
I will use my ultralight beam to destroy you
and I will take a shit on your white dress.
I want to kill you with waves
and if I see you in Paris, it's on sight
'cause I'm bound to kick your ass.
- Damn. - Wow.
- You saw something about Paris?
- I was like, I see you in Paris.
So what's like just if I see you in Paris, I don't know what was that a song name.
No. No, I was just talking about if I maybe see him around in Paris could be it.
Okay for him because I'm going to kill him on site.
I'm bound to do that.
Okay. Okay.
Well that wasn't really holiday.
That's more kind of way.
I guess your Santa costume kind of hold on.
No, no, no, no.
Hold on.
You have another and you're not invited to this Christmas in Harlem.
Okay.
Yeah, there we go.
Rounding it out with another Christmas.
Christmas
All of the
Pretty good and celebrate the eight nights or the eight lights
The eight crazy nights that he make a song called eight crazy nights
He's probably we got all the lights and all the lights in her. He needs to see we need to show me if he sees
If I think if Kanye sees Adam Sandler, he'll all that anti-semitism is gonna go probably doesn't realize it
He's probably never seen Adam Sandler.
Yeah.
That's probably his big thing.
He needs to see The Cobbler.
The Cobbler.
That could change the world.
Yeah, you know what?
If I see him turn into The Gobbler, I'll eat him.
You're going to eat Kanye West?
Yep.
Kanye needs to go to that Cobbler from that movie,
and he needs to try on a Jewish man's shoes.
That's true.
And say, Kanye, your shoes are ridiculous.
They look like foam blocks, these shoes you're making.
So maybe you do need to take a trip to The Cobbler.
Yep.
And if I see your shoes, I'm going to become The Gobbler.
What if I eat your shoes?
Stop eating stuff.
I'm gonna eat your toes!
Yeah, and if I see anybody else I might be the gobbler too.
Then you're not the gobbler, man.
Shut the fuck up.
I'm the gobbler.
You can't eat shoes and people, man.
Shut the hell up.
You can eat shoes.
Fuck you, you can eat shoes.
Shut the fuck up.
There's a man who ate a shoe.
Yeah, cut up the rubber.
No.
Yeah, exactly.
It was your mom and nine months later you popped out.
Yeah.
My mom ate a shoe and I thought that was funny.
You're a fucking shoe turd.
Yeah, my name is gonna be aglet the hell are you taught? I'll understand your fucking shoe jokes. He's doing he's doing shoe humor
Yeah, I understood it though cuz I know a lot about shoes cuz I'm getting ready to eat one
And now I'm going on the aglet then I will slurp the rest of the lace like it's a spaghetti string
I think that I'm David Lynch when I'm doing it. Mm-hmm. I'm eating my own shoe
- That was good. - Gordon, I'm eating my shoe!
- Yeah, I would say Kanye though,
'cause Kanye would be in my room when I was doing it.
- Why would he be in your room? - And it would be his shoe.
- 'Cause I'm eating his shoe.
- You're eating a Yeezy, you're eating a Yeezy One,
a Nike Yeezy. - One calorie.
- Yeah, Red October, you're eating a Red October.
- How many calories are in a shoe?
- One, I looked it up.
- That's a good question, man.
But yeah, that's my Christmas, or my Hanukkah.
- In a show. - In a show.
A person weighs 180 pounds.
He's cooking calories.
454.
Show it.
We're not going to read all that junk up top.
It depends on the shoe because some shoes have leather
and suede and some shoes have canvas.
Calories and sneaker. Right there.
170.
Sneaker chocolate fun size.
Ignore the second part.
That's about the color of this shoe.
It's a color way.
makes sense. I was really pissed off because I went to the store and I was
looking for a snack and I thought I bought chocolate covered pretzels. I
just bought chocolate colored pretzels.
I was actually really there's a Juvia had a reddit thing pulled up of like how
many calories were in a shoe or somebody asking the nutritional value of a shoe
and the only check this woman's book. Yeah. What is this woman's book? I want
to somebody wrote a book about eating a shoe. This is not a book. This is a
This is an onion video.
Oh, it's an onion video.
Oh, great.
Okay.
We fucking ate the onion.
And somebody said go to bed,
but it's better than starving.
There is absolutely no nutritional value in a shoe.
Yeah.
That's what I was thinking.
Go on Reddit.
If the upper is made entirely of leather or like leather suede, I
feel like that you could probably sustain, you could probably live
off that for like an hour.
So now go on Reddit and do TIL.
there is no nutritional value in a shoe.
And just post that while we're talking,
and you don't have to show up,
but just get that out there for everybody.
- And then a link to the post.
- We've seen it, it's a thing, you know,
people need information, the internet.
- And we're here to get it. - It's collapsing.
Have you heard about this?
Apparently Google search is totally ruined.
- What? - Really?
- What are you talking about?
- I guess AI has caused Google search
to become less useful, apparently.
- That's my reaction to that.
- Are you talking about that to me?
Yeah, but we don't have to talk about that because that's just depressing as fuck.
I hate depressing news.
Do you see how depressed I am?
Yeah, you're stroking hell.
You look hella fucking ugly.
You look so fucking ugly.
Holy shit.
You look ugly as a motherfucker.
How did you get your face to get that big?
Do you want to see a time I looked really pretty the other day?
Don't.
No.
I do.
I don't know.
I need to see it.
I looked so pretty when I was sitting in my room and I couldn't help but take a picture.
I said this to Patrick already.
Yeah.
I really wanted him to see that.
Oh my god, you look so beautiful.
Show the camera.
Put that up to the camera.
Holy, you're a fucking gorgeous guy.
You think I looked good?
You look like, uh, you seen Zoolander?
Did you just try to...
That's a handsome one as well.
Show that to the camera.
I didn't go camera left.
Wow.
I went, er...
See, yeah.
I stole a kiss.
Ohoho!
Santa should not steal, Santa should give.
I'll steal.
I gave a kiss to your bitch ass for Christmas.
What I was saying is, that's grounds for divorce if I get a vacuum for Christmas, I think.
That's gotta be fucked up, right?
I don't think so.
That's what happens, dude.
It's fucked.
I just don't want to become that kind of person.
That's why you have to leave America.
I do.
I need to go to Italy.
That's why people go to Canada.
I need to go to Italy and get, like, Godfather, get an Italian wife instead.
Doesn't speak any English, has an IQ of like 60.
All she knows how to do is wear a big white frilly shirt
and make you spaghetti.
Yep.
Pasta-gi-lio.
People in Italy, they live in castles.
Yeah.
They basically are in a painting world.
You can also, instead of going to Italy,
you could just move to New Jersey.
Yeah, it's the same shit.
It's the same thing.
They have castles there too.
South Jersey, maybe, or North Jersey.
All the same fat guys and women.
You could go to fucking--
Italy, though, does not have Atlantic City.
Yeah.
New Jersey does.
has no you can do you can move to cities though no can move to friggin hack and
sack or whatever I'm gonna hack your sack yeah yeah and then then every day you
can just go to the American Dream Mall it's just like Italy it has Nickelodeon
universe it has Uniqlo you know clo unique tunic clo yeah I hope to Nick
- Uniclose.
- Hope it doesn't have Unicron, the evil transformer.
- Oh my God, I just understood what Uniclo is short for.
- What?
- Unique clothes.
(laughing)
- Oh my God, you're right.
- That is so fucking true.
- I never realized that.
- They are pretty fucking unique.
- I thought it was a made up word.
- Long sleeve shirts, long sleeve pants.
- Heat tech.
- Yep.
- Uniclo heat tech.
- Wait, heat tech stands for--
- Heat technology.
- Yeah, heat technology.
It's for guys only.
Yeah, yeah, I gotta go to Uniqlo. That's a whole you never been to Uniqlo in my life really. Yeah, it's basically for
It's only for skinny minis, so I don't go there. No they got fat guy clothes there now for Rizzle
Uh-huh might have to check it out. Yeah, they have medium guy stuff. They got medium guy stuff
They have pretty much everything there. It's kind of like doesn't sound so unique. It's kind of like Primark, but if it was good
Okay, got him. Yeah, fuck you Primark. Fuck you Primark
Stop by stop let my mom buy my Christmas gifts wait
I just realized something what uniclo is like unicron and primark is like optimus prime
Because of the names my god because you transform when you put on a new pair of clothes into a new handsome dapper, man
Yeah, or a car put on a car costume
They might have car costumes a unit clothes
They got all the clothes. I don't know because I've been there is this the it's this the what's his name?
Oh, yeah, big sartorialist. I love this guy. Yeah, go. Oh, he's just not it just happens. Oh, wow good for him. Yeah
Damn, it's like the big the fat sartorialist. Okay. I have an idea
No, what do you think oh I can't read I didn't bring my glasses I
Have an idea for a thing that I was thinking about a few days ago that I think you guys could help me develop
Okay
So it will be a thing in a grocery store
Okay, I'm already so hang it up here
rotisserie candy
Holy shit, so here's my first pitch, and I want you guys to help me nut. Here's my
Made me come here's my early early
I need help developing so that we can maybe take it on shark tank or something, but you know a rotisserie chicken
It's hot in there rotisserie candy. It's chocolate bars, and it's cold oh
It's not melted whoa. It's true. It's a bar, and you can break you can take off a ball
So it's like the 7-Eleven rollers but they're cold.
Yeah, but it's not a road kissery. It's not rolling on, it's on a spit.
How would you do that with, I guess, you know, and then you could stack Reese's up and shave
them like it's like shawarma.
That's a really good idea. Holy shit. That is fucking genius. A bunch of giant, those
giant Reese's on a big stick.
Trust me, when it comes to candy, I have some great ideas.
What do you shave it onto?
Maybe, also, now I'm thinking.
Ice cream.
It's the idea is not rotisserie candy rolled ice cream dude rolled ice cream amazing
Maybe it's just a full rotisserie store and everything is on a rotisserie
And it's all fresh you call it spits spits is so good. Yeah, and the logo spins
Well, then you would call it spins. No because it spins spits it spits spinning spits
But it's a terrible spits with an apostrophe as if there's it's a belongs to a guy named spit. Yeah. Oh, that's good
When I think of food, I love to think of spits.
Yeah, saliva.
Spits foods.
Mouthwatering.
It can be called spits spinning foods.
Yeah.
What else would you eat at spits?
Cereal.
Shawarma.
Oh, there would be shawarma.
How is cereal?
Pickles.
It's spinning.
What did you say?
Pickles.
Pickles is a good idea.
You can slice off some deli cheese.
You know when you have the cereal at a hotel breakfast when it's in a big container?
It's like that, but it's spinning, so it separates out.
it's like a centrifuge. It separates out, say, the lucky charms from the
cardboard parts of it, the non marshmallows, and you could have it separate
'cause it's spinning. So it's like one...
Yeah, okay, I see what you're saying now. It spins really fast.
Okay. Danger. That's the other thing, you can control the speed that it's
spinning. Up to... It has a type of credit, like a touch toon credit,
where you can... Oh, and there's a touch toon in the store. You have an
app where you can control any item, you can speed up or slow down how it's spinning. So
if you see someone you don't like about to get some spinning food, you speed it up really
fast.
Yeah, then it's impossible pretty much.
You can pay to spin.
Pay to spin to win.
Here's what my counterpoint was to the vacuum. There's this place Jack--
He's on about this so much.
Listen, I had a-- okay, how much is a vacuum? Like a nice vacuum, like $150?
No.
Like a nice one?
A nice vacuum, like $300.
Okay, so even better.
$7,000.
I was saying for double for 300 bucks Jackson barbecue in Texas you can have
them ship you a brisket okay so that was
that's to get the barbecue place we went to no no no that's Tyler no Jackson
barbecue is like supposedly the best brisket in the world and it's $300
they'll ship you a brisket it's an entire hundred bucks yeah they got a
ship it and cook it and shit and then you come you reheat it in a pot so I
I don't feel like that's as good as a vacuum
Yeah, I think a vacuum spider. What are you guys on her side? Yeah, you guys love vacuums or no cleanliness or something
I've seen your house. You don't want her I need a new vacuum. I have two vacuums motherfucker. Yeah, you don't use them
Yeah, I do one of them. You can't vacuum shirts off. You know the other one is so bad
No, I'm the good one no
Mo keeps climbing up the he keeps climbing up the vacuum bag and where he's gonna break it. That's what I'm saying
I'll take it off your hands. You should vacuum up that little fucker. Yeah. Yeah, I
Need to teach him a lesson
And a vacuum is probably like a nuclear weapon to a shrinked guy
To a shrinker think about a dog when a dog
You know what he likes I thought that he would hate like loud noises, but I guess because he's a stray he grew up around them
Just like a little head. Yeah
Alive for like five days before you got him. No. Yeah. No he was he was yes
I found him at like a month old you don't know that there's no way to age a cat
He's obsessed with I have like a like a knockoff like Thera gun
Like one of those like $20 like Amazon ones
I was like using it before I went out to skate
and he loves the thing moving back and forth so much that he ran up and grabbed
the Thera-Gun like while I was on my knee and tried to like yank it away from me and
it's like as he's doing it it's going like so he's just... Do you ever get scared
owning a Thera-Gun that maybe you'll get pulled over by a police officer they'll
say license registration and you'll say oh I just want you to know I have a
Thera-Gun and they'll think you said there's a gun. I have I have a thousand
guns. Yeah, that is that kind of scary having someone with a gun in their house? No, cause
then... Just say no officer, I have a thousand guns in my house. Yeah, exactly, cause you'd
say you wouldn't have it in the car, you'd be like, I just say no, I have a Thera-gun
at home. Yeah. And it's thinking... I have a Thera-gun and then... I have a Very-gun.
Yeah, the worst part about that is the cop... Adio! The cop is gonna try to like bad lieutenant
me and make me give him a massage in the back of my car. Oh, true. Yeah. But then you, but
then he thinks you said Theragun, you said I have a thousand guns, he turns his back to
you and says "Well go ahead and give me a massage with that bad boy." And then I pull out my
one thousand gun and I turn him into Swiss cheese. And there's no way, there's not a
jury in the northern part of the United States that would ever convict you for that. Or he
thinks you said a flare gun and he's like "Now I need you to signal, because I'm completely
lost. I'm lost. This is not my jurisdiction at all. I'm in the wrong state. Yeah. I'm
Ohio. I'm really scared and I need people to find me. It says Ottawa police. I'm a
Mountie. I don't know what I'm doing. And then you're like, no, I mean I have this.
You take out the Thera gun. Bang! You're dead. He thinks it's a very gun.
Nowadays the Joker, the fitness Joker. The Joker nowadays. The Joker would be a
He would have a theragun that shoots out a thing that's all that bang no it says it says
Yep, that's right
Feels good my all my lower back the fitness Joker the
I need to become the fitness Joker. Yeah, you go to the gym in the in the joke
I really want to start walking. There's a bunch of like old Russian fat guys.
I don't speak any English at my gym. They're all like four feet tall.
And I want to make some videos where I go up to them. I'm like, be honest,
are you Natty or not? And just be like,
guys like shape like a gym, a guy like the Volus from Mass Effect.
Be honest, bro. Natty or not. Come on. Be real with me. You're on Anovar.
I know you're on trend, dude.
We're like you're shaped like a samovar. Whoa a sandbar. You should be in the ocean motherfucker. Yeah
Go in the ocean. Yeah, I'm sick of these lobsters walking around my fucking gym get back to the same
Revolutionary war Americans be like I'm sick of these lobsters, huh these lobster backs
They dress like a lobster back whoa if you can call me you can call me Santa Claus
You call me ho ho ho all you want don't you dare okay, red coat?
Well, what are you? What are you wearing?
Your penis is still wearing this fucking Nigel Houston
I went to the gym. That's okay to see my penis
How many times I've seen you wear these tights
They're not tights and I'm them if I wanted to become a dancer
I'd be honest with you guys and just fucking say that shit
I wouldn't just start dressing like a dancer slowly and slowly start wearing to do
Yeah, you're just like cancer aka the crab red. Yep, bro. I ripped my pants again. Yeah
I guess I'm looking at your penis, it's showing to me.
What the hell happened dude? Jesus Christ.
Oh boy, yeah.
So you still want to fuck me you motherfucker?
I know you're really sad right now because your pants ripped, but maybe to get you in the Christmas spirit I'll...
Smell these.
I'm not...
Actually, that smells good.
That actually smells really good.
Why is it blurry?
It smelled good. It smelled good. That was something that was on my penis and my ass.
And he said it smelled good. So all the ladies and guys out there.
It smelled like laundry.
It smelled like fucking small cock.
It smelled like Brian Laundry.
This is out on the ground. Smells like...
Well I have my Christmas wrap.
Nah, not today.
today. Yeah, Gabby, whatever his name is, and Brian fucking Laundrie, let's bring that back.
Yep.
GBO, is there any way you can play that beat I sent you?
It probably smells like a fish tank though right now.
Probably a little bit like a fish tank.
I sent you a beat.
It's so romantic they...
On the, over the phone.
Oh.
Don't just play it from your phone.
I'll just play it over my phone.
Why do you need a beat?
Holy shit.
That's a crutch.
Yo, what up, bitch?
My name is Santy Claus.
I got a gift right here for your fat ass meemaw.
I'm smoking weed and I'm drinking a 40.
Now I show my dick to a crazy ass shorty.
They turn my reindeer into ground beef.
I whip my dick out in front of the police chief.
You see me in your neighborhood, you know I got the present.
I lost my two kids in the War of the Pheasant.
That was a war in 1638.
It was between pheasant and ape, when then human joined and it caused a lot of drama.
It's the main cause of most of my trauma.
The war was long and the battles were scary.
Along with my kids I lost my best friend Harry.
I saw a man degloved by a pheasant.
Ah shit, that was so unpleasant.
Then man won, alongside the ape.
We took the pheasant king and squished him like a grape.
Back in those days pheasants were huge, about the same size as me and yous.
Then we ate the king and realized birds taste good.
That's how poultry was introduced as food.
During thousands of years we have eaten birds because of the war and laws and words.
We all turned birds into food like beasts.
Then apes unlearned how to speak.
And then humans ruled because of my power.
I'm Santa Claus and I live in a tower.
Is that it?
Holy shit dude.
Woah.
Oh wait no I still have more.
Anyways I'm Santa and I digress.
i go to your mama's house and i make a mess
on a sexual freak and i have no man is a month
dancing across your bad manager
and that was great that i was going on that crazy i can't know you had that
you're
what i want to do is is earlier when we're talking you said
that we were talking about what you're
you said it was a war between
apes and birds
to remember that i remember talking about that for you and what we talked about
- We talked about hypothetical situations
in which animals would--
- We talked about hypothetical situations?
- No, we were talking about ducks and fighting horses.
- Yeah, ducks and fighting horses.
- That's not pheasants and birds.
- Pheasants are birds.
- Or pheasants and apes.
Here's my question, man.
- That was really, I really liked that, though.
- Are you accusing Santa Claus of being a fucking monkey?
- No, no, humans, joint, do you want me to say it again?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it seems like you didn't retain the--
- Yeah, no, I'm gonna need you to run that back.
- And so apes could speak in 1638.
- Yeah, so back, okay. - Maybe do a rock version now?
All right. A rock version of this?
Let me look up Aerosmith Run DMC type beat.
Because that was just Run DMC type beat.
I was kind of hoping there would be more Run DMC type beat.
What kind of sad fucking kid is on Fruity Loops making Run DMC type beats?
I wanted to read the...
I wanted to read the comments to find freestyle.
That's an old soul.
The 12 year old. All his friends are rapping over Juice WRLD type beat.
He's the one kid doing Run DMC.
Free Traumatized Travis Barker x Aerosmith Type B C
Oh yeah play that!
I wanna hear that.
Alright then I'll-
Sounds lit.
Classic jeans for little boy.
These are fire.
These are not that Aerosmithy to me though.
These are just the intro.
Oh holy shit.
Okay.
Alright.
Now sing it.
Don't rap it but sing it.
Cause I can't understand that rap crap.
Wait until it-
It's got a YouTube premium. It's on the podcast YouTube. Oh.
Okay, that is gonna drop.
It's coming any day now. Damn.
Holy shit. Yo what up bitch my name is Santy Claus. You're rapping again.
Sing. Okay. Didn't even drop. Yo what up bitch my name is Santy Claus
I got a great gift right here for your fat ass me ma
I'm smoking weed and I'm drinking a 40
Now I'll show my dick to a crazy ass shorty
They turned my reindeer into ground beef
I whipped my dick out in front of the police chief
When you see me in your neighborhood you know I got the present
I lost my two kids in the war of the pheasant
That was a war in 1638, it was between pheasant and ape
Then humans joined and caused a lot of drama
It's the main cause of most of my trauma
The war was long and the battles were scary
Along with my kids, I lost my best friend Harry
I saw a man degloved by a pheasant
Aw shit, that was so unpleasant
Then a man won alongside the ape
We took the pheasant king and squashed him like a grape
Back in those days, pheasants were huge
About the same size as me and you
Then we ate the king and realized birds taste good
That's how poachers introduced as food
We have eaten birds because of the war and laws and words we turned all the birds into food like beasts and then apes
Unlearned how to speak then humans ruled because of my power. I'm Santa Claus and I live in a tower
Anyways, I'm Santa and I digress I go to your mama's house and I make a mess
I'm a sexual freak and I have no manners damn Santa Claus you a bad man my jamma
See it worked better as a rock song. Yeah, I honestly do believe that yeah
Wait the perhaps are the most important spots of the North Pole the clock tower is where Santa's sleigh departs for his Christmas Eve flight
Why would he not depart from like an airplane or a sleigh plane? I guess it makes more sense
Mm-hmm
Yeah, does Santa does Santa live in a tower because that's where the thing departs from so I don't know if he lives there
We'll get into it.
Listen, we have probably four or five or six more episodes
where we get to talk about Santa as much as we want.
I think we have four more Christmas episodes.
God damn it.
Would you guys be mad if I just wore a Santa suit
for the rest of the podcast for years and years?
I feel like that would be kind of complicated.
Why?
You wanna be the Santa Claus guy?
The guy who wears the Santa Claus suit?
For a couple years.
That's the kid with the rolling backpack status.
No, it's not don't say sad
Reddit guy who is a bear hat? Yeah, what are you talking?
I don't know what he's talking about, but I agree all that you guys saying this you guys are now
Humbugs and you are doubting me. I think that I may become a
365 Christmas style you pull this you pull this video up real quick. How is this me man?
Yeah, this is what you're gonna look like pull up that also rolling back
I never what are the hell's a rolling me a suitcase. No, you don't know what a rolling backpack
I'm older than you you didn't know rolling backpack. You were the rolling backpack kid. Yeah
I've never had a I never had a good backpack man. Have you seen what the backpack kid is doing now?
I've had I've had this backpack that I always have for probably eight years
I've never had a good backpack kid is now like a Christian youth minister. Yeah, real probably always did he?
He does all these he goes on live and he makes beats and then talks about I wish he would go on live. Holy shit
He looks so dope. He's a Nickelodeon
The kids choice or zoom out and show everyone the toys the rest of my god
Why does he look like that? Yeah, he looks badass
He looks like little people exactly damn look at his chain. What's on his chain?
My god, he's fucking dope damn
Gun Kelly dope it is the turtleneck though. I bet he has so many hickeys on his neck
True, that's where the turtle neck. He fucked Cardi B. He probably
dude
He probably fucked her
Wait, what happened back back?
Why is he got a black guy? He probably fucked grown-up Dora
it's makeup it's an emo makeup but he wasn't like that in the previous photo
it's just a it's a it's a photoshopped it's a photo show make him look cool man
what do you guys want for Christmas so cuz we do have to get each other
Christmas gift now I think I'm gonna get you this loop all right that's not
somebody wearing that yeah turn the computer that's enough computer for but I
did see somebody wearing the jacket from Guardians of the Galaxy on the trail
Oh, Jubio?
Oh, shit.
Yeah, it was Jubio.
Remember when Jubio was supposed to get that?
No, I didn't know that they were just straight up a cosplay jacket.
I didn't know they made that.
Yeah, dude, Jubio almost bought one.
Yeah, Jubio was supposed to get one.
How the hell did you recognize that jacket?
Because I've seen that movie.
Isn't it just a leather?
I wouldn't recognize that shit.
I would recognize it.
You know why?
It's a leather jacket, right?
What?
Because I wanted Jubio to wear it.
No, it's like a red leather jacket that has a bunch of layers.
It doesn't look like a normal.
You can also tell that it's not a normal leather jacket
I thought like just just not just just not by but just by the quality of the item because it is a cosplay thing it clearly
Looks like it's yeah something is wrong. You know you know what I mean you see like the like it looks like a Halloween costume
Yeah, like it's like the fake plastic leather that looks like if you like yeah
I was a word for that pleather. Oh
You might be a genius you should be buck
You should be I've been saying this for a long time that you should be if they reboot mythbusters you it should be you
You as one team and then me and the girl as the other team.
They should reboot the Manhattan Project and let you make the next atomic bomb.
Me?
Yeah.
I'd probably make it fart when it explodes.
That's what I'm saying, you'd save the world.
I'd probably make it fart when it explodes and then if the people who got disintegrated
heard it before they died, they'd laugh.
They'd die with a big smile.
If you guys had the nuclear launch codes, where are you dropping it?
I would probably accidentally make that code my password for everything and then I'd get
hacked one day.
I'd probably drop it on Japan again.
Yeah, I would probably I guess I would probably I'd be logging on to the nuclear launch code website on the library computer and accidentally
Click the button for show password. Yeah, and the old guy jack off next we would see it and I'd be like, okay
Well, fuck it if he knows that he sends a nuke to Lana Rhodes house because she won't answer his messages
She answers the messages
She's got like fucked over she's like
Or no she fucked over a bunch of people cuz it's some like crypto scam
We made an NFT of her asshole or something and people didn't it's had a smell effect
It had a smell effect a smell effect on her NFT. Yep on her NFT. It was a scratch-and-sniff
NFTs no fucking thanks. Yeah, those things thing is art. Yeah
- these NFTs are fucking
- Oh shit.
- I hate them.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, they're stupid.
They're not even artistic.
- It's like back in the day we had Mona Lisa
and now we got coronavirus.
(laughing)
- Damn, that took me a full second to understand that.
But that is a master class.
You should be teaching a master class.
- Is that camera blurry?
- You should be, just shut up.
- Yeah, just leave it alone.
Don't let it, why would it, why?
- The fans are gonna talk about it.
I don't think you're talking about it right now.
Someone's gonna say something. You're weird, man.
You are a weird guy. Someone's gonna say something.
Autofocus is on, more like the Autobots are on.
Can't wait for Rise of the Beasts.
Yeah, more like Autofarkus. Is that what they're doing?
Yeah.
That was my grandfather's name. We're doing Transformers.
My grandfather. We're doing Transformers right now.
Autofarkus Doran.
Optimus Primal. That's not your...
What are you talking about?
My grandfather, Autofarkus.
Are you crazy now? I'm going crazy.
Did you lose your fucking mind today?
Yeah, what's wrong with you?
- Marbles are at the door.
- You did the rap and then--
- He left his marbles at the door.
- And I didn't lose 'em.
- The rap really was uncharacteristic.
- Everything around the rap was just like,
you were so lucid for like a full 90 seconds
and you've just been crazy the rest of the episode.
- I've been crazy?
- You've been crazy, you've just been like babbling yourself
and going blah, blah, blah, blah.
- I didn't take my Adderall today, so maybe.
- So you maybe are crazy.
- Yeah, maybe.
- Yeah, did you take your anti-psychotic lunatic pills?
- No.
- Blah, blah, blah, blah.
- I did take--
- That didn't just happen.
I did take my anti-psychotics. I got a beet juice.
And I'm treating all of my mental illness with beet juice.
Okay. Is it working? Yes, look at me.
Yeah, I'm hoping that... Don't do that.
Speaking of beet juice, I fucking hate hipsters. I'm hoping the soda industry beats juice.
Yeah, that's right. Let's go soda! Woo!
And juice? Suck my dick, you fucking oaf.
Whoa, you did the fucking poem about Kanye and now you're saying that?
No, whoa!
Whoa, I'm talking about different vegetable and fruit juices.
That's messed up, man.
No, I didn't mean it like that, man.
You can't be saying that in that costume.
Saying that your holiday is better.
Better than what? You know what? I don't even know what you're talking about.
Okay.
That's right.
Juice day.
It's a good strategy.
Juice world.
Yeah.
There's definitely something anti-Semitic you can say about that.
I've become a businessman, I think, in my subconscious brain.
That has to be an amazing opening sentence for me.
That's going to be a 7-5.
Well, it's not really an opening sentence.
No, I'm just saying I like it and I'd like for you to continue.
In my sleep, I was talking about strategies.
What's the report?
What do you mean you were talking about? What did you say?
Let me hear some things you said.
All that I was told is that I said we need to use some new strategies
Man we really have gone so corporate, bro. I know having corporate dreams about strategies. Yeah
Synergistic stuff my girlfriend's I woke up like eight times in the night, and I wouldn't stop talking about strategy
Which I don't think I've ever talked about strategy in my life, I've heard you say it you've talked about maybe about video games
Yeah, yeah, you're talking you and patches are all talking all the time like oh, what's the best strategy for this dark souls boss?
Meanwhile well, it's usually dodged the attacks. Yeah
Okay, and Patrick talking about how much dark holes cost yeah
What 150 not that much 150?
There was women in Las Vegas who had sandwich signs on and I know you're thinking
Hungry different kind of sandwich sign on either side. There's a sign. Okay, just before you know what that is
Okay. Yeah, right now you do
There were women with signs on that said in your room 20 minutes or less
They were prostitutes who were wearing signs to sell their own fucking sex Wow
And then so I saw two women like that and then I saw a fat guy wearing the sign
Prostitutes, and here's my rhyme about that. Prostitutes, what's the cost of this?
Yeah, probably not that much.
Probably low.
In Las Vegas, yeah, if they're 20 minutes or less.
Even if it's a million dollars, I'll just win that money and it's not an object.
I definitely saw some prostitutes while I was there.
Yeah, you just said that.
I saw a lot of them.
Yeah.
All around. They're crawling.
Yeah, well that's why they call it Las Vegas. Moral code.
Uh-huh.
It's a it's a it's it's decrepit. Yeah, and all those all those damn prostitutes lost the elasticity in their vague vaginas
Something I think there's I think weird we got our second gas leak
Something's wrong
That's okay people like the gas leak stuff. Yeah, should I bring the gas leak detector to the office?
It's over there! It's just dead. It's dead, there's no batteries in it.
We'll be dead soon. There's no gas in here! How could there be a gas leak?
Here, I can give you a battery. What kind of batteries does it take?
Oh, fuck. A bunch of them. Triple A. Triple A?
Three of them. Three of them?
We only have two in that. Here's what we'll do. We'll open...
There's some in this, but I'll...
God, we just...
...some in the audio recorder.
Actually, you know what?
Actually, no, there are some--
Yeah, I bought AAA batteries like a week ago.
I did too, but they're old ones, and they're
in that direction.
Yeah, we definitely don't even need it on, dude.
There's something in the air.
There's something seriously bad in the air.
Yeah, it's Christmas spirit.
I hope it's just Christmas spirit.
We need to get a Christmas spirit detector.
Yule fumes.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
We can just put the word Christmas spirit right here.
OK.
Christmas spirit detector.
So there are dangerous levels of yuletide fumes in this room.
Should be I think this should be a permanent table ornament
Yeah, we should put that on the wall and just run it at the beginning of every episode just to do a quick check quick
Baseline why would it stick here a baseline?
Why would it just stick for no?
You thought it would stick by just thought it was holding it on the wall touched it no
Great you destroy that's my stocking and I don't want that for Christmas so meanwhile. This is my stocking
That's Patrick's and that's Caleb so Patrick can put that in his own stocking
He has the lowest stocking cuz he's the littlest brother. Yeah, he is the little brother
We probably have a tied stocking
There's that there it is
There it is. I don't know if that needed a punch in I'm gonna be real with you
It's pretty clear could have I would be so scared if I woke up on Christmas morning. I saw that poking
Whoa
Yeah, it's probably been blurry the whole episode huh it has been
It has been we got to get a camera that has work has bins. Yeah, we're washed up
I'm a complete wash up not me. I'm Santa Claus. I'm frozen. I'm dressed exactly like I'm Olaf from frozen
Yeah, that's right. I'm Josh Gad
You could be a gad type yeah
I was saved from doing a musical theater as a kid because my grandpa died.
Really? My grandpa died and the Peter Pan musical was the day of his funeral.
I was saved by what? I was pirate number two. I was saved by my own homophobia as a child.
I think I would have unlocked a lot more if I had done theater.
I was saved because my voice was too good. Oh yeah. I was like you show all the other kids.
I didn't make it. They were like, you listen, if you want to do musical theater, you have to go with the college kids.
I went out for Captain Hook. That would stunt my social growth.
True. So I went out for Captain Hook in the school play.
You went out with Captain Hook. I went out for Captain Hook.
I wanted to be. You went out with Peter Pan for Captain Hook.
I wanted to be Captain Hook and I made no, I made no choices.
No, no drastic choices. That is dangerous as a performer.
I went up. You have to make big choices. I tried to play Captain Hook raw and real.
I went up and I said, "Fuck Peter Pan!"
I did one musical.
"Little ass kid!"
You didn't say that.
"I'm gonna beat the shit out of him!"
That's a strong choice.
You did a Gritty, Captain Hook?
Yeah.
No you didn't, that's bullshit.
I played Gritty.
I actually was in a musical I just remembered, and I think I've talked about this maybe.
Maybe not.
I was in a musical for my church, and I was the secondary star, and I had to, and my guy,
my character had a broken leg, so I had to wear a cast, right?
You were Tiny Tim?
No, fuck no, I wasn't Tiny Tim.
I had a broken leg, right, and I had crutches, right?
- In real life.
- No, let me finish my musical story.
I had broken leg, I had crutches,
and in the thing, in the musical,
I pray to God, God heals my leg.
The musical ends, I ran around the entire church.
(laughing)
Ran around singing.
Ran around the whole church singing.
- Do you remember the song?
- It was like, ♪ God is a virgin ♪
- God is a virgin?
No.
(SINGING) God is a thug and a booby-de-doo.
It was something like that.
I know "God is a thug and a booby-de-doo."
But basically, my mom made me do it,
and I never ever forgave her.
Yeah.
Fucking hate her for that.
Really?
She made me cry in the rehearsal,
because I had to do push-ups.
Oh my god.
I had to do 30 push-ups.
What?
There's a red dot on your forehead.
I don't give a fuck. Kill me.
I don't even want to be alive anymore.
Wait, what happens? Can you switch to this camera?
I think it'll leave a mark on the lens.
I think it's a pretty good indicator that the episode is over if you start pointing around a red dot.
All right.
Check us out on YouTube.
And Patreon.
Upgrade your tier if you want to join the shareholder meeting, which will be...
which will either...
It will be on or has our...
It'll be on the 16th of December at 5pm, so join the discord to find out how you can get
access to that.
And it is business formal, it'll be sending out evites I've been told.
I do think you'll be getting an evite.
You have to wear a suit, or maybe a collared shirt under a sweater, or a Victorian dress.
You can wear a dress if you're inclined in that way.
If you're a girl you can wear a dress, or you can wear a powerful pant suit.
But that's about it.
- Yeah, if you show up in a fucking t-shirt,
if you show up in a t-shirt, I'm beating the fuck out of you.
- Whoa. - I'm going,
'cause we have your email address, I can trace that.
- We got your normal address too,
you credit card motherfucker.
- Exactly, and I'm traveling to your house.
I'm gonna get in your zone.
- And I'm bringing Julio, and he's bringing banditos.
- Uh-huh.
(laughing)
- We're bringing banditos to your house.
- And chihuahuas.
(laughing)
Yeah, so watch out motherfucker!
'Cause I'll fucking fuck you up, bitch!
And burrito!
We bringing the whole-
We bringing all of Mexico, and we bringing soccer balls
We gon' kill that.
Yeah, we're coming to your house and all of Mexico is coming with us.
You're gonna wish you were Chris Rock
'Cause we're gonna do more than slap.
That's right.
Yeah, you're gonna wish you was just a slapper.
Yeah, you're gonna wish you was just a Will Smith slapper.
I'm coming with 5 million Mexican guys,
banditos, we're chopping your head off.
You're gonna wish you were Idina Menzel.
Yeah.
'Cause we're not gonna say your name right when we fuck you up.
Nah.
We'll say Cuervo.
You're gonna wish you weren't mean to Denzel.
That's one of the Mexican guy's names.
And he's gonna chop your head off.
Yeah, and you're gonna wish, and you're gonna wish upon a star that our beating will stop and end.
I just got a second wind right as the episode's ending.
I know.
Let's keep going.
Holy God.
Let's do the two, this is it, the two hour episode.
And the whole second part, about how Mexico's coming down, we're gonna kick your ass.
Yep.
Me and all of my Mexican buddies.
Uh huh.
three or four of them. I have a Mexican hitman named Bubblegum. Yeah? Really? Yep. That's cool. You have him?
Yeah, I hired him for life. Whoa. He's a wafer. I wish I was a word for that. He's your good friend.
Bubblegum. You're number one best pal. That's a terrible name. Actually, that's a great name for a hitman. If you're a hitman,
you should be going by Bubblegum Marshmallow. Bubblegum in a dish. Marshmallow. His name is
bubble gum in a dish and how many pieces do you wish to remain on your body?
Yeah, that's his thing. He sings bubble gum, bubble gum, you know that song.
Bubble gum, bubble gum in a dish. We're coming to your hometown, we're
throwing grenades, we're throwing hella grenades.
Grenado! Grenado. That's actually about 50 of the guys. You're going to be made
into a flank steak. Yep, that's right. We're cannibals. Yep, human asada.
mm-hmm yeah yeah we're gonna make Ronald Ronald Asada yeah we're making fun
old Ronald yeah we're making a motherfucker Rachel Tinga yeah I know
Rachel Tinga making Tinga out of you Rachel I know Rachel Tinga and then
we'll throw that shit away cuz we hate you so much yeah wait what was the point
of all this carnitas are we killing our fans yeah I don't remember oh cuz if
they show up in a t-shirt oh yeah right oh you just made me angry again I'm
come with me, more Mexican guys and even some Spaniards.
Yeah, so dress in a suit or as they say in Mexico, a poncho.
That's not how they say it.
Bring your burro.
Yep.
Or I'm going to put you in a flauta, Jim.
Alright, until next time, motherfucker.
A vampiro, you're going to get bites on your neck.
I'm doing three, four a piece sign these days.
I'm doing four for this is what you do in Mexico.
This is how you do peace.
Whatever, man.
What's up, guys?