*intro music*
Well, well, well.
Andrew, Brandon, and Chuck.
It's been nigh a year.
Tell me.
It's been nine years.
What's been going on with you guys in the past year?
Like just my personal life?
No, no, no as a...
Or just in the news maybe.
Oh, that you thought--
We're working on our credit scores.
--that you liked a lot.
Let's see.
Biden did some stuff, right?
There was-- he gave us some money, I think, like less--
I think that was a year.
And then--
No, that was way before that.
Yeah.
No politics.
That was like two years ago.
Yeah.
No politics, nothing socially divisive.
He legalized it, I think.
That happened in the last year.
So yeah, this year we discovered a video
called the evolution of dance.
Oh.
Not familiar.
I want to see that.
It's pretty new I've been really into rolling Wingo lately
He's kind of been really cool to me
I've been like interested in like his stuff and his scene and kind of people he's been talking so rolling Wingo
He's kind of like a player. I mean you go on his Twitter
He's got like 70 80 girls responding to everything. He says every blurry Christmas tree. He posts
And some of these girls that are responding to him are also in like Andrews DMS honestly damn
Oh, he's kind of giving--
He's kind of like your OG.
Yeah.
Oh, for sure.
He's giving a-- he's like redistributing.
Oh my god.
I mean, these are the hottest women I've ever seen.
We're talking about Fleezer Sandy, Boo Boo--
Yeah, Burry Boo.
Silverton Kifty Jones.
That's three Os, but--
I mean, we're talking about these 10 out of 10 sport--
you know, maximum qualified women.
And they're-- he's--
oh, go ahead.
I'm gonna be going to Three Pumpkins, California to meet her.
But she got--
Whoa.
I don't really know how to get a hold of her.
Three Pumpkins?
That's where she lives?
Three Pumpkins, California is where she lives.
That's where I was sending all the money.
[LAUGHTER]
How much money did you send her?
I was taking it out of E1.
So it wasn't that much.
Because it's a write-off.
Yeah.
It was like $17,000.
That's not that bad.
The IRS--
Convince everyone she's part of our business
to get the write-off.
The IRS gives you like a tax break for getting pussy.
I heard that.
- She's not just some pussy to me, watch your mouth.
- Yeah, you heard that, you don't know that yourself,
you just heard it.
- Well, he hasn't had sex with her yet,
so he doesn't like saying stuff like that.
- Well, she tells me about it,
but she doesn't call her her pussy.
- She tells you about her pussy?
- I just think it's honestly really weird
that you're still into her when you know
she would eat dog food out of Roland Wingo's hand
if he asked her to.
I think you should just let her go, dude.
- I mean, who wouldn't though?
That's that's like what an American female wouldn't do that
and with Roland Wingo.
Roland is like the Paul Newman of for bots, you know.
I mean, we're on a we're on a podcast with some young people,
maybe not do Paul Newman.
Yeah, you I would say you guys are definitely of Paul Newman's time, though.
Yeah, sure. You know, I was in
a moment was really kind of hitting his peak for us young guys.
You should have said Paul F. Tompkins.
Yeah, we would understand that. Yeah.
You'd understand Blady better.
I don't know anything about Blady.
Old head just said Blady.
You know he's 28, he's not that young.
Yeah, that's how I know you guys are old and out of touch.
Okay, well it's not my fault that he can't fucking spell his own goddamn name.
Well maybe it's spelled different in Sweden or whatever.
I like to say it Blade, Blade, Blade, no it doesn't work, nevermind.
No, that's all the same word.
I had to confess something.
I'm kind of done riffing, I'm not riffing anymore.
Okay, Andrew, it's rich miss. What are you fucking on about? So we win?
That's cuz you got fleas or sandy on your brain damn
Yeah, I told you that you got it. Do you guys just want to have like a heavy conversation then?
No, I told you before that I was texting him right before this
He needs to go to the bathroom and he needs to take care of it before we record you guys
He's gonna be talking about
Sandy the whole time and burry boo and all of the money that he sent them
The blood if you just would have went yes if you just want to went to the bathroom beforehand and taking care of it like a
Grown man, yeah, I wouldn't have this problem. He wouldn't be all say for Riff Smith's. You're a grown man. You still jerk off in the bathroom
That was granted that put that out there
I hope no one sees me in my bathroom or my apartment alone
Yeah, what if the exterminator comes over yeah
I'm just gonna jack off in a chair and...
Sprays my dick and my balls like, "Oh, ow, ow."
I hate that.
"You're not supposed to be out here jacking off."
What are you doing?
I'm getting all your bugs out.
Don't you know war's going on?
You've got your bug out and you're rubbing it.
I'm trying to exterminate all the bugs.
When you're married, you do have to...
You jack off in the bathroom and you really ham it up too.
You light a match, you open up the door afterwards like, "Oh my God."
I think a batch to get.
Oh wow.
Turn on the shower.
I had to shower after that one.
Yeah.
Yep.
That was a huge shit baby.
What's for dinner?
Yeah.
And then I kept slipping on the bathroom tile back and forth.
So if you heard any noises, that's what was going on.
I learned how to do this cool thing with my cheeks in the bathroom.
I was kind of sliding around on the floor.
Check this out.
Just walking out of the bathroom, you're like, you're still super hard.
You're like, I just took the biggest shit.
Wow.
The whole time your phone's connected to Bluetooth, it's in the bedroom and is just playing everything
you're watching.
Dude, that's the big danger of jacking off in the bathroom is airplay, man.
God damn airplay.
I'm sorry I wanted to watch an NBA game last night.
Technology's gone too far.
I agree.
Andrew, keep this in mind when Fleece or Sandy moves in with you.
Yeah, we need to get rid of it.
Can we stop talking about her?
Can we move on?
This is not Fleece or Sandy hour.
You guys are talking about Roland Wingo.
I just remembered this other guy from Instagram.
my new he's my new my new bestie Jeff Houtman take a look through this guy's Instagram page
he's got a lot of here he's got 30 359 K followers and all of his pictures are him showing his
nipple and stuff dude this clouded poses in his face is damn he's a piece of ass you wouldn't
even know what to do with that oh yeah I would not hell I wouldn't know what to do with that
mother fucker loves Christmas trees too. Yeah, you put him on a big silver platter and put
him at the center of the table, I'd try to eat him right up. He's one of the most famous
people I've ever seen. There's something about Christmas trees that old horny guys love to
post pictures of Christmas trees. I don't know what it is. I do worry about that when
somebody's like, "I gotta get my phone charger, I gotta get my phone charger." I'm like, "I
I hope he's not doing some rolling wingo shit on there.
- Every time I find an old guy on Twitter
who's posting a picture of his groin
and it looks just like an upside down ziggurat,
like an Aztec pyramid,
I feel like I could,
literally I'd scroll two more pictures
and it's always a Christmas tree.
It's always.
- Yeah.
- They love Christmas.
- Or just a depressing family photo
in some shitty house
and then back to his weird marshmallow nipples.
- Those guys are cool because like,
they all love to do the tongue out thing
And you can do the thing where you flatten your tongue
and stick it out normal like that.
But the guys that do the little chode
that's barely peeking out with the mouth,
they're just like--
- I love the little tongue.
One inch tongue.
- It's a little cuter, I would say.
- It's a feeling cute might delete type of thing.
- Yeah, 65 year old men rarely get an opportunity
to feel cute.
- It's like a Pokemon face.
- There's this one guy that I found
in the replies of like a, I don't remember what,
but this guy is obsessed with genital piercing
and right-wing politics.
- Oh, interesting cross-section.
- Yeah.
- I've seen that guy, Patrick.
- He posts a lot of Christmas trees.
- It's the season, you know.
- He got the big--
- These guys gotta get some wholesome content.
- Is that the guy who's like German?
- His name is Matthew.
And just take a look at this one here.
Whoa, that's such a good Christmas.
Look at the caption.
Look at the caption here.
Gorgeous cleavage--
Can you read the caption?
Gorgeous cleavage and lips for pleasure.
He's going after that Sapphire Saint.
Sapphire Saint who asks, can I be owned?
Tatted plastic Barbie bimbo sex doll.
Double XL boobs, 2,200 and growing.
Still growing tits and ass no way so this guy's double XL booze. That's huge. He's into a few things
Dick piercings turning into an action figure and fucking people who are turning into action figures in Christmas trees. Yeah
This Sapphire Saint seems like a pretty nice young lady. Oh my god. She has an only fans never mind Jesus Christ
Look at her. She's naked sinful life
Oh yeah, she really is like, she's gonna hurt her titties.
I'm looking at her titties and she keeps talking about how she puts more of the plastic stuff
in them.
It looks like they're gonna pop.
Yeah, she's gonna be, you know, suckers are gonna go.
She can't get on an airplane without blowing them up.
They've popped before.
But if she does get on an airplane and it crashes, she's the only person surviving the
water landing.
- She's like an interesting case in that all of her pictures
are of her naked, but you really can't tell
what she looks like 'cause it's all so blurry.
So it's like a sexy cryptid.
- It's just like the Christmas tree photos though,
they're always blurry.
- This is the Owl Witch.
This is the Owl Witch from Mexico, the legend.
- This is La Llorona, what's her name?
- My Llorona.
- This is My Llorona from Mexico.
- On the first episode of the new season of The Witcher,
he's gonna fuck this bitch.
(laughing)
Grumbling at her titties.
- I wish it, can you get your balls this big?
- Yeah. - Or is that impossible?
- Oh, yeah.
Dude, you've seen BK Bulge, we've talked about him in 202.
- Oh yeah, that's Saline.
- You guys familiar with Hydro Seal?
- No.
Oh wait, is that the machine he uses?
- Is that the thing that you spray on the screen door
to make a boat?
- No, I had a friend in high school
who had a hydro seal.
And it was-- he literally had to get one of his balls
drained once a month.
Whoa.
The sack would just fill with fluid.
And he said they'd get pretty big.
I never saw them.
I wasn't that cool back then because--
I see it a lot.
I would have made sure to see it.
I see it a lot at work, especially people
with heart failure.
So their body just can't pump all the fluid around it.
So a lot of people just collect in the stroke.
[LAUGHTER]
(laughing)
But what you do is like their balls get so big
that you have to take like blankets or towels
and make like beds for their balls to sit on.
- Like a little bird's nest?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- I wish I had that.
- Otherwise they get like,
they're gonna collect all this gunk under there,
get like excoriations.
- Is that the medical term is gunk?
- Yeah.
- Your balls are covered in gunk 'cause it's so big.
- One of my favorite things about when you're charting
is you can't write pussy, you have to write like pure ruralent
that's like the same thing.
Yeah, you can't write pussy because it looks like pussy
Right like
like
Pussy got vaginal discharge. It's just like you can't write that like yeah, there's white stuff coming out of the vagina, but
You can't write pussy discharge
What is the medical in the med school right now anyone who's listening?
Yeah, I'm very interested
I'm learning a lot. Have you ever gotten have you ever seen just like the biggest cock ever on a real unsuspecting guy
At the bed. Yeah. Yeah, also there's guys like they'll have they have in ease
Any penises what yeah?
tell so I
That'd be terrible
An out invasive catheter is a urine collecting device one for women is called the
Pure wick and I don't even want to know that one
But I'm leaning it to it but to the dicks
So it's like a blue for the good stuff you put it in front of the vagina
And it goes to suction of the wall so when they pee it just sucks it and it goes up to the wall
So the guys that have the innings why we put it shouldn't leave it in the wall
The tube goes to the wall to the suction container
So it collects a pee okay, okay?
So we put those on those guys to have such tiny little wieners that go inside them that we use it for them, too
Where does the pee go after it's in the wall?
Yeah, my mouth. Why do you want to collect it you measure it and then you dump in the toilet?
To the next room there's a room
It's a scale that's on the floor, it's just a
Glass scales you get it like Walmart
How accurate yeah, there's like these tubes these suction tubes were here when we opened the hospital
We never we don't know where they go. We've never looked into it. We've just been using there's a guy who sits there
Just he has two cups one one that's filled with poop and one that's filled with pee and that's what he eats all day
Oh wait. Yeah, Andrew. How do you get their poop out?
Yeah
But there is so you know catheter a fully catheter is a tube that goes where your dick
That stays in so that's a long-term catheter and they can't get what we have something called a flex a seal
Where it's a tube that goes in the butt and then the poop goes out of the tube?
Caleb that's the thing that's the thing you spray on the boat
How big is the tube? Yeah?
Does it depend on the person it's a kind of around the size of a can like the width of like a month no way
Is it transparent please say
Yeah, you can see that
If you're having trouble pooping don't worry. We have a device here at the hospital. They'll take care of it
It'll well here's the thing you second can't get out as big as a Foster's beer can
It's the vacuum cleaner from
You put like a check in the thing and the vacuum tube
So the reason why we'll use those is if someone has like really bad diarrhea, and they're having like a GI bleed and shit
But also they have like a wound like on the bottom is a real commonplace for wounds
So you don't need all this shit going into their wound and making infections happen
Andrew do any of your patients ever get the crazy idea to go to the bank and shit into the tube after they've been in the
hospital
Well, actually Charles we have those tubes on all nurse floor every nurse station has those tube systems
That's why we get our meds and shit you
That binks use you ever put a diet coke can in there I wish yeah
There's something there's a lot of meds that you can't put on those because they get shook up or they'll get fucked up and people
have done it and it's like a monster energy drink. Yeah,
it's all fizzy. That's medicine. Yeah. Monster is
medicine cuz it has a lot of vitamin B. Have you ever kept
somebody's body part? Yeah, I ate a guy's uh amputated toe.
No. Oh my god. I can't keep anything. All my what if what
if what if the patient says I want you to keep this when I
die? Yeah. What if someone's last words are you get my brain
when I die? Would you be able to take the brain home? It'd have
to be in writing. I think a lot of paperwork. Yeah. All right. Well,
let's get it started. So like in the ICU, when the ICU,
when there's a donor, when someone's like, when there's brain death,
we keep them alive, their organs perfusing,
and then the Oregon nurses will come in and take over and they'll keep them
alive until they find recipients for all the organs. And then we pull the plug.
I just like to repeat that Andrew actually works in a Wendy's.
And this stuff is happening in every Wendy's franchise.
They'll get in contact with the surgeon and he'll be like, yeah,
I can take this heart out tonight
and they'll like send them out and go extract the heart.
- Damn.
- I got a buddy who is a psychiatrist
and he's got a patient that at the end,
at the very end of one session was like,
you know, when I die, you can do whatever you want with me.
(laughing)
- That's a huge compliment.
- Like just slipping it out there right before I leave.
You can do whatever you want with me when I die,
I don't care.
- I believe in your will,
like I leave my body to my psychiatrist and my will.
- Yeah, it's either science or--
- It's also funny to say it to your psychiatrist
as if they will have anything to do with your dead body.
Like, that guy like showing up to the funeral
and being like, just so you know,
before he died he said I could do whatever I wanted.
- He's my guy. - Who are you?
- Dude, I would do Weekend at Bernie's with him.
- Oh yeah. - I definitely did.
- I think he imagines, well the psychiatrist
obviously wants to fuck my dead body over and over again.
So, you know, I know he won't admit it.
Yeah, wait, what kind of vibe was this therapist putting out
where he was like, this guy probably wants my dead body
for sure?
Well--
Dr. Acula.
Come on.
You know, I don't know what vibe he was putting out,
but the guy has been trying to have sex with him
ever since he started working there.
That might be a clue.
All right.
So now I'm thinking about what we're
going to do with our bodies when we die.
Obviously, Branson's going to die first, because he
doesn't have much time left.
Big time.
So it's really up to me and Andrew
what we wanna do with Branson's body.
I think we could weekend at Branson's him.
- I'm gonna take it out to the desert and shoot it.
- You guys would be tired after 30 minutes
of hauling my big ass dead body.
- I wanna scrape a slut on him.
- I have honestly looked at Branson's body before
and thought he would make a good canoe.
So I'd probably burrow out a little hole in you.
- Yeah, well that's where you get the flex seal.
- Yeah, get his arms like-- - Give me fake eyes.
Just give me fake eyes and it's cool.
I realized oh man, it'd be awesome do some taxidermy but dress you up like a sasquatch
Some museum in Portland just has a big
Somebody to just put me in a cigar shop and dress me like
and yeah. You guys have you guys ever heard of the cryogenics
where people have their bodies frozen after oh yeah that's it's
cool there used to be in Michigan right by where I live
there is a facility that held those and I was like man there's
so many fucking rich motherfuckers that got fleece just
sitting there frozen but I was like thinking it might be kind of
fun to be a popsicle and then like one day you definitely
definitely yeah Futurama vibes yeah oh that does remind me of
Futurama vibe. For some reason. I think you might wake up as Bender. There's some kind of Futurama
vibes there. Yeah. I haven't understood how they do that because I've seen...
It's a load of shit. I mean, they freeze you after you die, right? Yeah. Okay, all right. So they just
are holding on to you. They think that there's gonna be some technology one day where we could
just like thaw you out. It's like a big rusty car. You turn yourself into a big rusty car that just
sits in your own yard. Mm but it's cold. When I die, I wanna
be a Pontiac.
Andrew, if all five of us got sick in Colorado, um would you
be our nurse? How sick would you be? Really, really, really
sick. Incredibly sick. The same thing. You guys are all in the
same room. Yeah, we all got it from like a ward like a
military ward. We all. Yeah. We had a party. Covered in
bandages we had a party sub that we were all sharing and we all got yeah I just
ate from it yeah well is that the good one into my eyes yeah you then you could
probably get like a ketamine drip oh that's yo
I mean hot now I don't remember ketamine being around when I was in college
ketamine is big now it was big in like the 70s and it came back like the hippies
loved it I love that Branson always acts like he's 50 we may do just good old
fashion cocaine just came always shows me a text from Branson that's like a
text him in the middle of dead it says do you remember Bugs Bunny he always
wants to test I think you've asked me if I know who you've asked me if I know who
Jiminy Glick is it?
Yeah, I was there.
I was there for the text because you asked everybody else in the car
if we know Jiminy Glick and I was the only one who knew.
Well, see, that's why I asked.
Well, we'll be writing jokes and Branson like he'll make a reference.
I'm like, holy fuck.
Like our audience a lot is a lot younger than you think.
You can't be talking about that all the time.
It's like, well, let me touch cameras, see if he knows what it is.
Damn, dude.
Did Cameron tell you guys about when Branson called him?
He calls him a lot.
I only called him once, it was on accident.
Oh really?
It was only one time.
I think we were there.
I was sitting on my phone.
I just looked down at my phone and I saw a missed call from Branson.
I was like, "What the fuck is going on?"
"He's calling me right now."
Is he okay?
Is there some kind of emergency?
Only Cameron can help me right now.
Yeah, like everybody else in his life died and I'm the only person he could call.
He calls you and he's talking in a low voice.
He's like, "Listen, Cam, I really fucked up.
I really fucked up."
"You gotta get over here, man."
"I can't tell if people know who Beavis and Butt-head is."
"Cam, you like dead bodies, you like zombies and stuff, right?"
"Well, I killed a guy."
"Cam, quick! Do you know who Alonzo Bowden is?"
"Cam, have you ever heard of Space Ghost?"
"Cam, have you ever seen Tough Crowd with Colin Quinn?"
(laughter)
- You're just like a--
- I would be so blessed to get a call like that every day.
Oh my god.
- So a picture in the mail of Brian Big Country Reeves.
It's just like, Cameron, I need you to study this.
- Tell me what the young folks think, Cameron.
- Well, actually, Cameron didn't know the Budweiser frogs
when I showed those to you.
- Cameron's gonna do a residency at Branson's house
for a year, just learning all the old Puma references.
Alright, we'll start with the Sid Caesar show.
The thing is, I'm not even...
Hunk of El Chihuahua.
I'm not even a good person to...
I'm not even a good person to ask those kinds of questions to
because I don't know anything.
I don't even know the stuff that I'm supposed to know.
You know about Blady?
I know... that's all I know.
You're talking about Brandon from beyond.
That's the only thing I know.
And I only know about him since like a month or two ago.
That's not true.
Well then why am I talking to you?
I gotta find a different young guy.
That's true.
[Laughter]
None of you guys are a good young guy.
Maybe a 17 year old would be really good for you to text.
text. I have an 11 year old brother. What can you tell me about the state?
The state? Yeah, I'll give you his number. What is the state? The state, uh, uh, it was a comedy show with Michael Ian Black
and it was, uh, they were all NYU kids and they, uh, one of them was really, really rich and that's how they got a show.
Which one was it? Was it David Wayne? I don't remember who. David Wayne's the best one.
It strikes me as the richest.
They're all good, but Michael in Black just kind of sucks.
Yeah, they suck now, but back in the day, they were fire.
David Wayne is so funny.
You say that, but you probably haven't
read his book with Meghan McCain.
You would think differently if you read it.
That's true.
True.
You'd probably be able to reach across the aisle.
Hey, the only book I want to see Meghan McCain is Playboy.
The only book I would trust her to write would be a recipe book.
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
Hey.
Do you guys want to know why?
Yeah, because she's a great big fat lady.
She is a bit too fat for me.
Yeah, the only movie I'd want to see her in is The Whale.
Yeah.
Or a bit of a Werner Fraser.
She's not in it.
Well, I'd want to see her as Brendan Fraser in the Brendan Fraser biopic.
Hey, any movie with her in it is IMAX.
Yeah, she was in Super-Sized Her.
Yep.
When she sits around the house.
She really sits around the house.
I heard that she has her own zip code.
Even James Cameron said, "A little bit too rich for my blood."
(laughing)
- She is big and fat.
- I heard that she went whale watching
and all the whales jumped out of the ocean
and said, "We are family, even though you're fatter than me."
- I heard a similar story.
That's very funny.
- I actually also heard that.
- I talked about that on the view.
- I heard that she did motion capture
for all the mech suits in the new Avatar movie.
- They got a regular guy to climb on her
for Shadows of the Colossus.
- Yeah, yeah, they strapped him to the front of her.
- She's gotta be one of the fattest women in the world.
hundred and forty 150 pounds push.
Yeah, this one's this one's not about her, but I heard that
her mom puts two quarters in her ears and thinks she's
listening to 50 cents. What a **** idiot. Her mom is really
stupid. Her dad's as dead as a doorknob. Yeah. Yeah. He can't
he can't raise the roof because he crashed a plane in Vietnam or
whatever. That's right, man. The big the worst punishment of
all. Imagine you go to Vietnam, you think you're fighting for your country, and then you come
home and you can't even raise the roof to celebrate how good of a job you did over there.
He actually broke his arms hugging her when he got back from Vietnam. He said, "Come here
Darling, she jumped into his arms.
- They fell off and had to get stable.
(laughing)
- Oh God, that is actually awfully disrespectful
of an American troop, so I'm gonna go ahead.
- That's completely terrible.
- I'm gonna curb my laughter right there.
- You think hell has any aisles for him to reach across,
or is everyone like politically the same in hell
'cause it's just like the devil, you know?
It's like the only game in town.
I think, well you think that John McCain is in hell.
That is very interesting.
Because I think pretty much he spent his entire life
trying to get into the kingdom of heaven.
So, I think you might be wrong on that one, bud.
- He went to heaven.
- Like the movie kingdom of heaven?
- No.
- He was trying to get in that movie?
- Yeah, they put his court,
they digitally edited his court.
- He was a big fan of Bradley's guy.
He's like, please, I have to be in this movie.
He's like, absolutely not, absolutely not.
- He could have been in that movie.
- He's like, what about my big time huge daughter?
is like he put she's in there you can look at the background.
She's yeah we got to project every person where.
Every person on earth should get one what they get to choose one
movie to be in and they get to be in it. No.
I think we should all get to know what I know I just mean that
when there's a movie is being made you should be able to say
I'm going to be in this movie and the director can't do
anything about it you just get to be in it.
Well we had the idea a while ago to have skins for movies so you
can watch your favorite old movies with skins in them and you
Change like George Clooney to Ronald McDonald
Like Brad
You're gonna spend like 500 bucks in your favorite movie to rewatch it. Yeah, like you change the Godfather to Stewie Griffin, that's cool
Yeah, and then the main thing though is now all movies when you watch them without the DLC
Everyone's just wearing a white t-shirt and jeans
It's like when you first get to Grove Street in San Andreas
That's smart. That's a money maker
It's an incredible idea. Yeah, well this AI art now. I want to watch taxi driver with Minecraft Steve. It's my dream
Did you see that uh there's supposed to be a taxi driver video game
Yeah, what are you doing that like? Oh, I'm gonna. I'm gonna kill a little politician. I it's like a
Prostitute I I read that they like tried to make it a sequel like how it was that that John Woo game
That's what that movie needs. There should be a Call of Duty where you play as John McCain
Video game it's a sequel to Paris, Texas. It's called Paris, Texas to the video game Paris, Texas to Paris France
Paris video game I agree. Oh, yeah
Pervert what's that fucker's name that little fucker leisure suit Larry? Yeah
Concord should get a picture of her as well. He should bite on her pussy with his buck teeth, and it should chatter them either
To chatter his teeth her pussy should
They don't explain it, but actually that's the mystery the entire game
Paris Hilton wouldn't know what to do with leisure suit Larry
You know what she'd probably do is put conquer in her purse and walk around like it's her tiny dog
Problem, you know what yeah
Crazy though is leisure suit Larry has like four kids now. He's been married for like ten years
Really? Yeah
He's doing cannabis company - really
- He's a stage advocate, yeah.
I think he lives in Three Pumpkins.
- Does he do like Delta-8 and stuff?
- No, just pure gas.
- What is Delta-8?
What is that?
- Delta-8 is--
- Is it a gas station drug?
- Yeah, no, it's weed with a removed chromosome or something.
They take something out of it
and then it makes it really scary.
But it's legal.
- It's weed without cum.
- Yeah.
- It doesn't have weed cum in it.
And it makes your friends back home want to join the military.
Oh, just like the movie Shooter with Mark Wahlberg?
It's pretty much the exact same thing.
That movie's badass.
My cousin said he was going to be a sniper because of that,
then he made up a lie about being flat-footed.
It's like, "Okay, you're 24."
Not flat-footed.
Can a sniper not be flat-footed?
I feel like being flat-footed would be a good thing as a sniper.
You can stand really still here, not wobbling back and forth on the balls of your feet all the time.
all the time. I hear you walking around like a penguin. I think snakes would make really good snipers.
You're like a mile away.
Because they just crawl around and slither.
All of us should join the military.
Why not?
I've been trying to, but I never make it past the psyche val.
Because I say I want to go over there and I want to make everyone ground beef.
And I don't care where.
I don't care where it is.
Killing machine at your service sir.
I
Want to be I say I'm really looking to cause a disaster
I want to do something disastrous a war crime in an area where you're still allowed to kind of do it a little bit
The thing about the full motherfucking military though is they'd like that shit. They'd be like you're in yeah, you're number one bastards
And here's my weapon
Yeah, I'm gonna go do that over there
Flip everyone off
Did you guys see the video of the the China and Indian armies fistfighting no
Whoa?
I need to see that
No, no
There's some like border dispute between China and India where they like have it guarded all the time
one of them overstepped the boundary a little bit and then instead of like
Like they don't have I guess they don't fight with guns at that particular border to like make it a little less
- Yes, uh, what's like crazy?
- Keep it real man!
We fight like real men in India, China.
- It's like a 60 person fight.
It looks exactly like an Instagram video.
(laughing)
Fighting outside of a nightclub.
- See, that's why we should join the military.
We should just join the Chinese military so we can do that.
- Oh my God, oh my God.
We go over there and we're like,
we go over to China or we do this in the US
and we're just like the street beefs team.
So we just teach people how to street fight.
How about Potabot List joins the Indian Army, E1 will join the Chinese Army, and then we'll meet at the border.
Yeah. Oh my god. I would love to fucking...
That is incredible.
I would love to ding Branson right here with a rock and a slingshot and kill him with one single hit.
I'd love to get hit in the middle of the forehead and instantly go cross-eyed and fall down.
That's David and Goliath shit right there.
Yeah, of course. That's what we're doing.
I want to make sure I fall and a lot of dust goes into the air.
- Rant's just speaking just like the most broken,
two week Chinese of all time.
(laughing)
- I think we should play soccer,
like the Christmas Armistice in World War I.
- That's after the--
- Look at this, and we'll go viral, and then we'll be rich.
- Is that like a boring Hallmark movie?
- No, it was really a big dumb asshole.
- The Christmas Armistice.
Okay, a Hallmark movie called The Christmas Armistice.
- Actually, you know how people go to like China
and other countries like Japan to teach English?
We should go there to teach podcasting to the Chinese.
That's actually a wondrous idea.
We should go over there to teach Chinese.
(laughing)
No, that doesn't make much sense.
So, "Ni hao" is "hello" and the rest of it is sounds.
I don't know the rest.
I just started this job.
I'm gonna learn as I go.
I'm just gonna, you can translate anything on your phone.
(laughing)
Yeah, and they're all teaching Chinese
to Chinese kids who speak Chinese already.
It'd just be like, "So, ni hao is 'hello.'
"Zai jian," that's "thank you."
That'd be like kind of a school of,
Oh, go down there, do School of Rock.
Oh my god.
That's an amazing idea.
School of Rock in China.
Charles can do that.
They need it.
Charles plays some music.
Rock and Roll might get rid of that internet policy they have.
Or we could teach them how to rap.
There's a lot of potential for some funny stuff happening.
Imagine if you taught Chinese kids how to riff.
Mm.
They're not allowed to celebrate Riffmas
because they put fucking riftians in camps
over there in China.
Oh, you can't riff in China is what I heard.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
I think you can in Hong Kong, though.
You can in Hong Kong.
You get so many shoes, and you open them up,
and there's a little one-liner written in there
that they're not allowed to do.
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah, I was taught growing up that China basically
put Christians into the male chicken meat grinder
thing every day.
Turns out it's really not that true.
I think it'd be more expensive.
I think chickens is one of the cheapest things there is.
Yeah, people--
- Getting people would be way more expensive.
- Yeah, like we'd probably eat people in some other thing,
but not just like chicken, you know?
- We should try to bring the price of people down
so we could eat people if we wanted to.
The only thing stopping me from eating people
is that they're too damn expensive.
- Yeah.
- People are, hey, people are priceless.
It's what I always say.
- Would you eat, Charles, would you eat--
- You do say that.
- Charles, would you eat-- - You say that a lot.
- Would you eat person in tikka masala?
- Dude, I wouldn't know what to do with that.
(laughing)
Would you eat Roland Wingo if he was rotisserie?
- No. - In a heartbeat.
- And 40 giant breasted women all got to eat him.
- I'd eat Fleezer Sanger. - Oh my God.
Dude, that lemon pepper, that lemon pepper Roland Wingo,
oh my God.
- Big apple in his mouth.
He'd be the Christmas goose.
- We're all doing the wishbone with his entire body.
Oh my God.
- Cracking every one of his ribs.
You would definitely need to cook him well done though.
Oh yeah, I don't trust that.
There's worms.
There's something dwelling in there.
He's beer battered for sure.
He's like the iceberg from The Thing.
I feel like if you heat him up, something's going to come out of there and end the world.
He's got a couple critters in him.
I don't know where.
We could roast him over in there.
You would thaw him and his tapeworm would escape.
Pinworms are spinning out all over the floor.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Guys, what are we doing here?
Like what are we doing?
- We're talking about eating a guy.
We're talking about--
- Yeah, we're talking about eating an old man.
- Oh God, this is fucked.
- An old man who gets--
- Hey, what do you guys do on here?
You do like a list thing or whatever?
- We're listing old men that we would eat.
- Oh, okay.
Well, I would like to eat,
oh man, if Regis was around, he'd be like beef jerky.
- I was just thinking Regis!
- Yeah.
- You guys don't--
- Cameron's never heard of Regis Philbin.
- Cameron, do you know Regis Philbin?
- No, Regis would taste like Peking duck.
to
people
- But by the end you gotta eat the whole torso.
- Yeah.
- It's not as much. - Yeah, it's too much.
- I need to-- - Now--
- You know, Kelly Ripa, she's so thin,
I always offered her a bite of me, but she never wanted it.
- I want you to put me into this stew pot!
(laughing)
- Breathe!
Breathe!
Slice up onions and carrots and dance around me!
Over a fire!
- That's like half Gilbert Gottfried, half Regis Gilbert.
- Most of it is the same enthusiasm.
- Regis Gottfried.
- They're both up in heaven bitchin'.
- That's true.
(laughing)
complainers those two. I want to phone a friend on the Who Wants to Eat Regis and I want to
call Cameron and I want to ask him if he's ever heard of Wait Wait Don't Tell Me. Yes.
How about Car Talk? Have you ever heard of Car Talk? Yes yes yes yes. Cameron have you
ever heard of Mr. Beast? Come on no Branson's never heard of Mr. Beast. What kind of old
ass shit is that? Oh I've heard of Mr. Beast. He's the most famous, he's got the most subscribers
on YouTube? No. He's the richest guy ever. He's the richest guy in the world. He'll get
like big, like a bunch of food for people and then give them like $10,000. Yeah. Why
would he give them food and $10,000? Dude, he's a hunter. He's huge on his YouTube. He
gets like 11 million viewers. That motherfucker's 100% gonna be like, "All right, we're doing
Hunger Games 3 on this island. The winner gets $5 million. Go." He's like, "I want people
to kill each other." I feel like he's already done that. He's pretty much already done that,
it was more of a tag. Didn't he do squid? No, I mean real straight up killing like he wants
to see people killing each other. Yeah, that's it. I mean, because like he's gonna run out
of brain juice, but that's all that's left. Like he's gonna eat a guy to he's like, I'm
gonna make you a Mr. Beast burger. Branson, do you want to be a Mr. Beast burger? Your
whole family and friends will be taken care of for the rest of their lives. But you got
to be eaten. God, that's so poignant. I would offer myself up. Oh, like, Christ, you do look
like Jesus. Fuck that, dude. My family and my family and friends can take care of themselves.
I don't want to be a burger.
- Yeah, I would be like, can you reverse that?
Can you just make all my family and friends into burgers?
'Cause then I have a lot of burgers.
- Can you cook Rolling Wingo for me?
- Mr. Beast Burger, he should open a Krusty Krab
under the ocean.
- That'd be such a good idea.
- That would be, that's a really, really good idea.
- Yeah.
- Oh my God.
- He could make a Rolling Wingo into a Krabby Patty.
- And Linus Tech, do you know who Binging with Babish is?
- It's me, Binging with Babish.
- I've heard of him.
today we're going to watch the videos
the
everybody should be able to get in one movie.
Game shows should just take,
every like fifth episode should have to be just a normal guy.
Like somebody like that, who nobody really--
- It should be like jury duty.
They should send a letter,
they should have a registry of everyone in the US.
They should just, yeah, and you have to do it.
- You get a rolling wingo,
you get maybe a Branson on there, who knows.
- You get a Burry Boone.
- No, I'd win over so many people on Hot Ones.
- You would eat the bones.
- Oh, yeah.
(laughing)
- Just go ahead.
- I do think Hot Ones would be easy,
I have had the hottest sauce before.
It's not that crazy.
Yeah, right. You've had the hottest sauce before.
Charles, Charles.
Also what you don't realize is that half of the challenge
is the crazy ass questions you get asked.
That is the most clear lie ever, by the way.
Is you saying, "Yeah, I've had it before."
And I call you and say, "No, you haven't." And you say, "Yeah, I actually had it twice."
[Laughter]
I don't mean the hottest sauce in the world. I mean like the
triple X last dab thing.
You fucking suck my... Shut up.
I put it on pizza once. This is Charles.
nothing to me that I put it on pizza.
Yeah, no, pizza is different from a wing,
because then you got the cheese to counteract the hot sauce.
He's right.
All right, we get to do a--
That is a--
--one in Palo Alto.
Patrick, that is an incredibly fat guy argument.
You're like, well, hold on, it's got the cheese, though.
When he's right, he's right, though.
And Branson immediately-- Branson goes, he's right.
[LAUGHTER]
When you're right, you're right.
You got to give it up.
That's what I always say.
It's a science.
You gotta break it down, you gotta think about this.
Speaking of science, I actually had the hottest sauce a hundred times.
Yeah, fucking fuck you, asshole.
No, you didn't!
Charles is a hundred feet tall, too, and he ate the hottest sauce in the world.
He went, "Yum, yum, yum. It's not even hot to me."
Yeah, and he's--
My dad's a spy.
And he's talking to us on a computer that was made by Mr. Bean.
Yeah, I'm talking to you-- yeah, I'm talking to you.
Also, my laptop is alienware.
Welcome to dealing with Charles. Welcome to dealing with Charles all the time.
I've told this story before, but one time we were staying at Joel's in Chicago.
in Chicago. Joel made us these really good breakfast bowls. And we're just sitting there,
I was like, "Man, this is pretty good." And Charles is like, "Yeah, it tastes so good,
that's why I have to eat it." I was like, "What the fuck?" Who the fuck says shit like
that? What the fuck is wrong with you? He watches too much anime, so he talks like an
anime character. Yeah, he just reads One Piece. Oh yeah, I forgot that you're more of a manga
I. Is a. You have to say
main get a piss all the all the nerds. Cares
a camera to be ever it's so good that I. I'm
not so much about main gum but I like a main
go. In the right season yeah. Too hard to cut
too hard I say annoying stuff. Yet you said that
before Britain fuck you it's like a. I don't have
a kind of you know me pussy. A man goes
too hard to eat it's wet I always eat it over
the sink it's so what it is and I said yeah
That's 'cause it's-- that's the trade that you make.
That's like good pussy.
'Cause how good it is.
You eat it over the sink.
[LAUGHTER]
Oh, I wouldn't be able to handle that mango.
Standing over the trash can eating pussy?
Man.
I wouldn't know what to say to that.
I'm so busy at work, I don't have time to take a break.
I'm just standing over the garbage can at the break room
just eating pussy.
I was wiping my mouth with my shirt.
[LAUGHTER]
Wiping up my sleeve.
Dress like you're about to eat, like, all you can eat crap.
It's got a pop--
It's got a hammer.
--on the bottom.
Yeah.
Plastic poncho on.
I actually put some-- when I have a mango,
I put some of the triple dab hot sauce on it.
I actually had that.
Oh, really?
I think you did that 100 times, actually.
It wasn't even that hot to me.
And I didn't have the cheese from the pizza.
If you guys saw the video that Tom and Charles
did of eating the six burgers--
what was it, the Wendy's burger?
Yeah.
We were so drunk.
We were when we filmed that.
When I watched it, I was like, damn, we're so drunk.
Charles takes the first bite, and he goes,
it's actually pretty good.
Basically, it tastes like food.
I was like, this motherfucker.
You gotta stop talking like that all the time.
He's right though.
It's hard to get a good bite, cause like,
there's six patties, so it's hard to get
the bun in there, so you're just eating pure meat.
And then your hands are getting
ultra greasy from this shitty bun.
It was terrible dude. Dude, it sucks you didn't live.
Food challenges suck.
I'm so glad that Charles lives
in a different city than me, man.
I would hate to be your
mailman or something. Just have to
have like weird interactions with you once a day.
today. Okay. So one time we were going to record the trail mix.
Yeah. The trail mix and Charles is like Charles is like well
Margie his wife is like her friends can be driving off this
trail mix and he's like he's acting like it's like a drug
deal like he's got like I'm gonna have to go get it. I
quit worrying about the show. It's like yeah, they might I
don't want to get started yet cuz I think she's gonna come by
with the trail mix and then he's eating it while we're like
of course like man. It's really good actually. It's like and
we're like what no I asked him what it tastes like and he goes
trail mix. Again, not wrong. You're right. I resend what I said. The most tedious man.
The most tedious man. Another thing is that you can never piss off Charles, which is also
very frustrating. I bet Charles does not care. Yeah, hey. Suck on that one, Charles. Actually,
you know what pisses him off? That just makes me sad. I'm not mad, I'm just sad. Actually,
the venue in Chicago fucked up our files. That really pissed him off. Oh yeah. He fucked
You can tell just by looking at him he's serious about it.
That's a lost episode.
That's one of the few lost episodes of you and I.
That one podcaster who don't play about his files.
This motherfucker don't play with those files.
He need his files now.
Charles he'll let you know.
If you don't send your file he lets you know.
Charles sent us a picture with a gun.
He says I'm going back there.
You're about to run me my damn files right now.
That is truly, that's the number one benefit of getting a producer for us, of getting Jubia
to be a producer is I don't have to be the files guy.
- Oh yeah.
- I don't have to say, can you send your files?
- Can you send your files?
- I just have to do a really shitty bit.
- I don't have to worry about it.
- That just like failed hard where he was like,
I'm gonna start sending my files to Andrew
so he can send them to me.
- I thought that was a good bit.
- It was terrible.
- I still think that's a good bit.
- It's not even a bit, you're just inconveniencing Andrew.
- I know, that's the whole bit.
- You know what I would do?
- That's the best.
- I would send them back to Branson.
- That is a good, that would have been a good bit.
I was is badass. I was really into the email bit for oh, yeah. Yeah, we should bring that back. Oh, yeah, that's true
I did also I got a lot of
I would be like at work and I'd get an email from Joel that he sent to all of us
It's like a woman's like big tits. You just have a great
The email bit though is that you email your friends
and
Yeah, basically, do you see someone's kid now? It sucks.
Yeah, it does suck.
Now old people started getting a bunch of a bunch of really good emails.
Oh, yeah, we just updated our website.
Now we get literally a hundred emails every day that say wow, your website is so beautiful.
Do you want me to to make it even more beautiful for you?
And they're all up to make swag.
We got one more beautiful. We got one from Salman Gupta.
Hello, your website is amazing. And so beautiful.
I would like to discuss a business opportunity with you.
Oh!
Wait, listen to this!
This is a, I just opened up our email.
This is from, this is from Jivica, whose email address is fannyyoung1999.
Good user, good name, good email.
Hi, hope you are doing well.
I was examining your website.
Your layout design is good, but your website ranking is not able to find on starting pages
on Google.
Isn't that funny, losers?
I have one here from Harry Ram.
Wow.
It says, "Hello there.
"Ready to start boosting websites rank
"on top page on Google and get visitors?
"If you like, I can send full plan."
- I wanna hear the full plan.
- I know, I want all of these people to send us full plan.
They also always ask, like,
can we schedule a 20 minute call to talk about this?
- Yes, we can.
- And I feel like we should, we have to.
- Oh, you've gotta do it.
- Just take up, just every single person
who sends an email is be like,
yeah, we'll talk to you.
- Let's get in there, let's talk business.
- You know what you should do?
Schedule them all at the same time
and put them all on a call together.
it. Yeah. No one owns the website used to what we used to do when we were younger. Michael
and I would go into Skype with our buddies and you can make two phones call each other.
So we just listen in and you hear people like some store calling other stores like hello
will you call me. Then they'd be like look motherfucker you called me. Yeah I don't get
I feel like you don't get the real people on the spam calls anymore that often you only
get the robots. Yeah, I think people don't pick up enough anymore, you know? Like, I'm not
gonna pick that shit up. The texts are really good. The texts are really good too, though.
They're like, "Hey, Kevin, let's go skydiving tomorrow." And I'm like, "Okay, not Kevin,
but where?" I got one the other day that I just, it was clearly my friend's mom calling
me. Like, it was him calling me from her phone, but because I instinctively didn't like, like,
He had the same last name and I think it was her first name, but I just denied it
And then I was like it probably was an important phone call
But I just if it's not somebody's in my contacts. I always just delete it
Was last time you got an important phone call though pretty much never
Yeah, but it's like Cameron talking about
Calling him being like what the fuck is going on. I get like my one of my brother's calls me like oh shit
Is he okay?
Phone I I screen my mother's phone calls so often that I think I could probably go six weeks without finding out that like somebody
Very close in my family died because I would just she just keep calling me be like fuck she wants to talk about Thanksgiving again
No
Yeah, I actually was gonna call someone I would probably text them first like yo, can I call you? Yeah
Yeah, I let it go to voicemail. Let them leave a voicemail. I'll call him back
But most the time like I have the excuse I'm like, oh, yeah, I work nights
I'm probably still sleep during the day and I'm not but they don't have to know that my brother called me
my brother called me while I was at the Nickelodeon universe in
The American Dream Mall in
That's a place in his imagination that I was by myself
My brother yeah
no, I my brother called me to tell tell me that we had to like put the dog like our family dog down and
He called me and then I was like dude. I just rode the Shellraiser
It's so sick, and he was like I'll just call you back then he called me like two hours later
Oh my fucking god, I just saw Dora. I swear to God.
- Guess what dude, I touched the real Agrocrack.
I'm not fucking with you, it's a real one.
It's not a replica.
It's the real one. - Oh my fucking god,
they got the guy from Legends of Hidden Temple.
Yeah.
- I feel so good right now, my dogs will never die.
(laughing)
- They do have the Legend of the Hidden Temple
thing though there.
You got that?
Can you climb to his mouth?
Patrick, if you never left that place, you would have never had to learn that your dog
died.
That's true, yeah.
If I just stay in the American Dream Mall, I would never know.
I'd meet Jimmy Neutron, Ren and Stimpy.
Dude, you wouldn't even know what to do with Ren and Stimpy.
What would you guys do if you saw a cat-dog in real life, though?
Oh, I'd throw up.
Fire on sight.
Wait, what if the dog half was already dead and the cat lived like four more years?
Eww.
It's so morbid.
Well, I'm taking that cat dog, putting two apples in its mouth, and I'm rotissering it
Roland Wingo style.
You gotta try this.
Dude, when you come to Detroit, you gotta try Roland Wingo style chicken.
It's the best chicken in the world.
I'm telling you.
I think if I saw a cat dog in real life, I probably would just instantly vomit.
Yeah.
I don't think I would have it.
would reflexively just puke. I don't think I would have a choice.
Yeah, because like, cat dog in real life...
Cat dog body horror?
Yeah, I was gonna say, it'll look like the dog in the fly 2.
Like, it won't look normal.
I would be scared.
It will look normal.
Where's the one that's just the...
I would be like, why is a cartoon running around?
I would throw up because toons should not be in real life.
That's true.
I would throw up because my brain would be so broken seeing a real toon, dude.
I agree, but like...
What's its dick?
I feel very comfortable around Eric Hartman. Yeah, oh yeah, he wouldn't cuz you you would get it blow your mind cuz you're that's his
Homie, you've always been like that's a fat kid. He's so fat, but then you T turns completely sideways and he's two-dimensional
No, and he turns
Anything yeah, he's even yeah, he's even
If you go to like Coachella with him he like takes care of everyone he makes sure like everyone is constantly hydrated
He has the best drugs
I have heard that sometimes you'd go out to eat with Eric and the end of the night comes and you say all right
Let's like how we're gonna do this bill like let's split the bill or whatever. He says oh, no. It's already
It's already taken care of what you didn't even see the bill
He paid for it before you even got to the restaurant
Are we sure that cartoons are 2d cuz what if they're using really thick paper back there that we can't see that's a good point
I don't think that's a good point. I don't think I just want to push back on that being a good point
That's a good point. I'm on Charles' side.
Eric should go on Hot Ones.
I think that we should get Pat and Branson on Crossfire and they can talk about things.
Oh yeah. That'd be good.
Isn't it a good point?
Welcome to Crossfire.
All right.
Branson, what is the most yummy food in the world?
Roll and Wingo.
Sandwich.
Prepared in which way? Prepared which way?
Oh, I mean, to me, it doesn't really improve the flavor, but anything where he has an apple
in his mouth, I would like, you know, braise them, do a red wine beef broth, and go for
like two hours on like 250.
Reverse sear?
You know what, I wouldn't even want to sear them.
I'm really into J. Kenji Lopez and Guga Foods style chefs, so to get like a sous vide Roll
and Wingo where you gotta put Roland Wingo in a vacuum sealed bag.
I think you cook him like a brisket. I think low and slow on the Traeger.
He's too fat. Like he's some short rib.
Yeah, you could literally whole hog him.
I'm whole hog where you just cut him up.
Definitely. This all sounds really delicious, but I'm a pretty lazy guy, so I think I'm just gonna air fry him.
He won't fit in no damn air fryer.
like 15 minutes in my air fryer.
Listen, an air fryer undeniably is going to give you a great crust on a guy like that.
The thought of microwaving a person is so fucked up to me.
Yeah.
I chop off his feet and hands too.
And I thought in my head, I thought in my head like, oh, I don't want to eat a microwave
guy.
Like I want to eat a guy in the first place.
Like, oh, don't microwave him.
Come on.
If you're going to eat a guy, you're going to ruin him.
He's going to be all soggy and still frozen in the middle.
too fatty. It can't fit in there. Well, you make like a man-sized microwave. I have a big
microwave. Make a big broth. I have a giant microwave because I'm a popcorn freak. Oh,
really? Well, you like movies. Yeah. So it's not a surprise. I go crazy for huge amounts
of popcorn. I buy popcorn bags that are the size of a room. I actually do. I have a whole
floor of my house that's a microwave. Well, when I worked at the movie theater, if you
wanted some of the popcorn in a big bag at the end of the night, I would have given it
to you.
Aw.
It was free.
It was free for us.
And now you get people in a colostomy bed.
I also fucking hated popcorn after working there.
What?
How do you hate popcorn?
What an amazing gift.
Oh, after working at the theater.
Yeah, but you, what?
That would make me love it even more.
You don't get anything to eat.
You just only have to eat popcorn.
You're just like, "Ugh, something I used to love I now hate."
That's why I hated working at the ice cream store.
And they said, "Your job here is to eat as much ice cream as you want all the time."
That sounds awful.
I had a desk
In the seating area
Families eating ice cream around
My desk end of day I'm calling my wife listen, honey, I gotta stay late I gotta finish this
Leftover military-grade ice cream from Iraq that they didn't get through and it's like it's part of the military
I don't remember what the I don't know what the brand is
They have it at Whole Foods though
But there's this one that has a Turkish coffee ice cream and they also make this one that has like bits of like Captain Crunch
In it and it's fucking easy. Okay, so he shops at Whole Foods hippie. How's that going for you?
More of a hipster. Okay. There's a whole
so, please
Educate me.
Basically, here's the thing.
I only wear my skinny jeans.
Ugh.
I love Taylor Swift.
Ugh, what the hell?
As a boy, a male--
As a guy, I'm disgusted.
And guess what?
I'm addicted to Starbucks.
So fuck you.
Well, I'm a hipster too, but I'm a different flavor of hipster.
I'm more of like a Zooey Deschanel style,
adorkable hipster.
He's been fucking with us for fucking 10 months.
First of all, I've never even heard of Starbucks.
What the hell is that?
Oh, you're a hipster now?
No, I've never heard of it.
It seems too underground.
Where do you buy your December CDs if you don't get them at the counter at Starbucks?
I buy them at a normal coffee shop like Dunkin Donuts.
Thank you very much.
Oh, you're more bro.
You're such a bro, dude.
You're indie.
Yeah, I'm a little bit of a jock slash bro.
Fucking sue me.
Yeah, and I'm more of a scientist.
Patrick is mostly an emo, I would say.
Yeah, I'm pretty emo.
He's like a J.I. Simpson.
I have really long bangs.
Me and Branson are jocks.
I think I'm a jock.
I'm a hipster Patrick are emo emo hipsters emo hipsters who would care about their clothes and cameras and scientists
Cameron and Charles are two scientists or astronaut a couple eggheads Einstein. Hey, what is point X equal?
stupid
Well, they would know that where you are. What is it? What is the equal? Why would you call it?
But they know they're on the spot. I'm on here. I just want to hear it. Carol
E equals.
- You guys, listen, you guys might think, you guys--
- This is more of like a Zoomer thing.
I think people my age don't know what E equals means.
- Zoomers don't know.
You're a Zoomer who doesn't know E equals MC squared.
(laughing)
- Yeah, they lost so much education--
- You guys might think I'm a nerd or a geek
or something like that,
but something that I have that you guys will never have
is an imagination, okay?
And I have a special machine that plugs into my TV
that can turn me into anything from Master Chief
to Mr. Chief to any video game character in the world.
So as a jock you probably don't even know that shit, so shut the fuck up. I didn't understand a single goddamn word
You just said
The files anymore, so how could he be a nerd and as an emo?
I don't even sir I washed my hands of the nerd stuff now now
I'm a president more worried about poetry and like yeah me and Patrick hang out in basements with wood paneled walls
We just sit there thinking about girls. We liked in high school and let me guess you guys are listening to fucking Mumford and sons
and no Nelly and Tim McGraw that one song it's all in my head oh the jock knows it
again whoa Patrick might be a song jock that's a new mix mm-hmm it's almost like
guys it's almost like you can't categorize people based on
That's the most you ever said
I think that actually Caleb is more of a prep. I'm a hipster in what world am I a bloody prep?
And I'm a wizard in point and I'm a wizard at Hogwarts
Yeah, you're back into sniffing. Oh
It's miss cuz I can smell you through the screen motherfucker. Oh
Damn, what's he smell like?
What's he smell like he smells like a fucking doo-doo? Oh
Jocks on top back back up top again. Yeah, I'm a motherfucking jock. I'm an I'm a hipster. So I wear like
Abercrombie and fridge or shut whatever shit that is JC penny
I only wear dracar noir. I go to JC Penney head straight to that's why you're like got shit. Yeah, exactly
I'm a cool water guy
I'm covered head to toe in cool water. Oh
Cameron do you know what cool water is?
We got really into crack this year, how about you guys yeah crack crack cocaine tell us what you've done in 2022
Oh, yeah, motherfucker. I played Xbox damn
Yeah, I was on the PlayStation for real I
Got the Wii for cam and it's got to be the Wii for my guy Patrick
Wait my 2022 wrapped wait pause let me get this straight you guys are gamers. Oh
Hello, you wouldn't expect it. Oh
He is a nerd look at that Star Trek. Oh
Oh, man.
Branson doesn't know anything about that.
I know.
To all the list heads at home.
V for Vendetta.
All the list heads, what video games did you play in 2022?
Sound off in the comments, like and subscribe,
podcast about list.
We love video games on this show.
As always, I'm Charles from podcast about list.
We just want to know what you think as the stupid and normal
man. Charles has played two games in his life, Final Fantasy 7
and Pokemon.
Are you forgetting Tony Hawk, Metal Gear Solid.
Oh, you're a jock.
Oh, he is a gamer too.
Damn.
All right, that's five games.
Make sure you go to our website.
You check it out.
Email us any suggestions you might have or business
opportunities.
Especially if you're like a Canadian guy.
If you want to email and ask about how
you can improve the website, just hit them up.
And we know there's a lot of improvements to be made.
We will schedule a 20-minute session with you.
No, it's actually pretty well done, the website,
if people want to go take a look at it.
The website actually came out pretty well.
The SEO part of this episode sucked,
but I know all the episodes suck because we're just
not good on this show.
Okay, so Charles is a complete dick sucker for his entire life.
(laughs)
What?
Well, there we have it. That's it.
Yep.
Maybe we should, uh...
Fuck you. I'm stopping recording right now.
I'm gonna wrap this up.