(upbeat music)
- I think that was a good clap.
- Ooh. - Did we get it going?
- I think we got a good clap.
- Do you guys remember--
♪ Where the route side is frightful ♪
- Okay, starting strong.
♪ But my friendship and my show is so delightful ♪
- And not spiteful.
- And not spiteful with our friendship.
♪ And when there is a thing to hold ♪
We will hold, we will hold, we will hold.
Wow.
This is awesome.
Can you fucking believe it?
Three weirdos on the same mental level.
Yeah.
And holding too.
And holding something.
We're holding a clapboard.
OK, on three, let's not hold.
OK.
One, two, three.
That was--
Wow.
That was crazy.
That was a fucking amazing episode of television.
Yeah.
It's the--
And that's the end.
Yep.
The end of the show forever.
How the hell has your holiday season been?
It's been--
Actually, not great.
No.
What's going on?
Well, you know, this time of year is when the in-laws come.
You know?
Damn.
The in-laws come to town.
Don't even get me started on those.
They should be--
If you ask me--
--Focker's family?
Yeah.
If you ask me, they should be outlaws.
Yeah, I agree.
They should have thrown in jail.
So--
No doubt.
--the in-laws show up.
And fucking Auntie--
I don't even know her name because she's such a bitch.
She's Auntie.
Auntie, yeah.
Auntie shows up.
Auntie, and you know I'm dropping a C.
And she's got that low cut shirt.
That low cut shirt.
So my auntie shows up.
Acting like a ho.
Not related to me, so I don't feel bad
about saying any of this.
Of course.
Shows up with his damn ass fruitcake.
Like her husband's?
Like her husband's a fruitcake?
No, but I'm gonna save that.
Give it to me.
I'm gonna save that for when I see him again.
Yeah, oh, the fruitcake.
He brought the fruitcake.
So much yeah, and then you could be like yeah
And now it's time for me to do the cake walk and you can walk all over him you brought the fruit cake
Oh and dessert
Yeah, and you're pointing to his cock. Yeah. Yeah, it's up fruit cake nice cock. Yeah, you gay wad yeah, whoa
So she brings the fruit cake right and it's hard as a brick. He's hard as a brick. Yeah
He's hard as a brick uncle Chuck's hard as a brick. He's harder than a mo me. Oh my we call him uncle brick
Yeah, true, and what does he do he knocks the fucking knocks all that shit off the counter with his hard cock
He's that tall
Yeah, Chuck Wadlow
Chuck Wadlow yeah
I was thinking about that guy Robert Wadlow
And I saw a picture a family photo of him
And it was like him and his dad and stuff and his dad's like 510 that was a man how fucking pissed off
Would you be if your son was not just taller than you, but he's the tallest guy who ever lived
He's 10 feet tall. Yeah, and you were like and you're like that. Yeah, you're like will you do your chores, please?
Your son is the number one tallest guy to ever live and you're the
152nd best bank teller. Yeah
He had a he was tall because of like a pituitary gland problem, too
So it's like I think he was just like that for no just like imagine being his father and it's like I remember reading that
In the in the Ripley's believe it or not
And he was this tall for absolutely no reason.
But imagine being like his dad.
And he reached this height for no reason.
His dad and just being like, you can't even claim like that, like when your dad gets proud
of how broad your shoulders are.
Yeah.
Your dad's like, "Oh, you're going to be a great linebacker when you get older."
When was he alive?
Last week.
2003.
Just finally died.
Because I think there's, he, I feel like, can you Google that?
I was I read this book about guys who are born with like just either really tall or really
small or with extra limbs and yeah, and joined twins and stuff like that.
And it was like freaks there.
It was their call.
Well, they're called they call them monsters in the book.
They're like scientifically when a when a man is is born and he's three feet tall.
That's a monster.
And it was all this stuff about like, yes, we call them monsters.
It's from was from it's from the UK.
And I was like, it's like an old book.
it has like old drawings of like... Click Robert Wadlow. Yeah, just go to Robert Wadlow.
It's down there. And just see when he lived. Yeah. Okay, now scroll past this,
please. Can you... Come on. You are... Okay, to 1940. Yeah. So yeah, I was
reading this book and I was like, "This is a pretty old book. Like, it's about these
people being born in the 1800s. Obviously not from the 1800s, but you know, it must
be pretty old because it's saying that if you're born with an extra arm, you are
scientifically a monster." And I looked at the... I looked in the inside the cover to
you and his friends from 1960. Oh my God. I think those guys were writing a book for like,
he was like a, and he was like, he was like a director of a museum. Like he was like an
academic. Well, if he was a director of a museum, he's trying to like get people to
go. He was like a part of like a, he was like a surgical, he was like a surgeon or something.
Like he was like, he was a real doctor. He was at the surgery museum. Yeah. It was the
surgery museum. The museum of surgery. Um, you, they were still doing like lobotomies
and stuff in the 60s. Yeah, they gave one to Rosemary Kennedy. Oh yeah. I think so. But
she got a street named after her in Boston, the worst street ever, the Big Dig Street.
So that's pretty cool. So that's worth it, I would say. They're also doing, still doing
lobotomies now, but through a different method. Nowadays, they do it through TV news. That's
true. They do it through TikTok and Fortnite. Yeah. And TV news. And this mumble rap. Yeah.
Yeah, I don't even want to say what rap is an acronym for hey who's coming to Christmas listen
Anybody's invited to my Christmas except for a fucking mumble rapper. Yeah, right
They're gonna walk out say hey there partner. I'm Caleb Pitts very nice to meet you welcome to my home. They go
Yeah, we don't be caroling and they're going like
Or they'll do ad-libs let it snow this mumble. No
Mumble rap should be called mumble crap. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, and it should actually be called mumble core
And I'll say every kind of movie and I know about back
And I celebrate their deaths when they die the mumbo rappers. I celebrate I'm dancing on a I'm dancing on a building in, New Jersey
I have you know in a movie. I know in a war movie when they have those guys
Which one who were the dancing guys and there was no head say go ahead. What do you think?
What do you think they were who do you think could have been dancers? Yeah, they were rock stars
Yeah, when I'm up there. It's a rocker day. It was the jabberwockies
You know and people said jabberwockies dancing on 9/11. It's like they dance every day. They're not gonna stop just because it's fucking 9/11
In a war movie when they have the like map and they have all the little figurines for the different
Oh, yeah, and they like push them around with a thing. I have that I have every mumble rapper
On a map of the US and I every time one does I push it off the edge. Yes
And I move my little piece to come up behind them a lot of the time. Yeah, it's cool that that was like a
Way to strategize they still do that. Yeah, they still do that. Yeah, it's just computer programs now. I guess that's true. They call
It's called Civ 6 yeah, it's basically that's all like the civilization games is is that fucking well
That's a little map that they had in dr.
It went from if you think about it
They went from you used to used to control your soldiers through several settlers of Catan and nowadays
It's like battlefield 2 yeah, they upgraded the technology flying these drones, and it's like you're playing
Titanfall - yeah, you're right. It's mostly two games. Yeah, you're a sequels. Yeah
Thinking about maybe asking Santa for
One of the Sims games for Christmas. I'm played a Sims game in a while. Yeah, yeah, but I do I do I
Am I remembering this that you when you on like the first Sims for a GameCube?
Could you burn people alive in the bathtub you do it with the oven or something? Yeah, they're like soup
So they open the bed. You know what I'm gonna say all these mumbo wrappers are probably asking Xanta for a gat
Okay, yeah, yeah, that's all right. Yeah, Xanthia asking Xanta Xanta fucking
claws
Dude cause a
Clause with a dollar sign yeah, yeah, yeah there. We thank you. Thank you for saving me from anyway
I wish the Sims was all guys and was called the Tim's I there's only one listen
I'm not much of a rap fan, but I do like that song that goes like a boss
That one is good. That is a good cuz you can you can understand what they're saying actually get it can hear the lyrics
It's not a mumbling
Like a boss you I listen to something like juice world or fucking Mac Miller gone
Yeah, like what are you doing casting a spell Severus Snape get the fuck out of my face you rapper
Yeah, hip hopper get no get lost get lost get take a hike. Yeah, here's what I'd like to do
Here's what I'd like to do
XXX XXX that kid if he hadn't died I would have liked to take him out to the country and show him
Fields and beauty and a tire swing. Yeah
Be careful cuz that's how you get little Nas X pick up a
Pick up a ukulele and we can sing and we can make real music and you can I can feed you till you're
50,000 pounds
Little ukulele and you sing over the rainbow
Let me bring you out there will find you a farmer's daughter big buck teeth and 80 IQ
Make you guys just completely fall in love. You're gonna show her the TV. She's gonna attack you
She thinks you're a wizard and I'm gonna teach you to make butter and I'm gonna make it
- Yeah, I'm gonna teach you to make--
- You're not gonna be making drugs or lean
or whatever the hell anymore.
You're gonna make butter now.
- 100%. - And butter has
just as much effect, if not more, than lean.
- Oh, way more! (laughing)
- The lipids?
- Yeah, and it affects your physiology.
- The fatty acids?
It's good for you.
- Yeah, butter is very good for you.
- And it tastes damn better than lean, too.
That purple crap, I hate the shit.
- Tell you what there, mumble rapper Juice WRLD,
if you were on a ketogenic diet, you could still be alive.
- Speaking of rap.
- I would like to move Juice WRLD to an orchard
so he could truly experience a juice world.
- Yeah, hey juice world, go home.
- Or maybe a Jamba Juice.
- Juice world, go home.
To juice world.
Get out of my world.
Earth.
- Speaking of rap, you guys remember when
they changed doing your mom
from doing your mom to stalking your mom
'cause there was a copyright dispute over doing your mom?
- These days, I think that Congress should make a song
called Doing the Nation
because of how much they're fucking us every day
with the legislative decision.
- The IRS is doing your taxes.
No, you're doing your taxes.
They're doing your bank account.
They did my bank account this morning.
They're trying to do mine, but I'm not letting them.
It's crazy that they can hack your shit.
It's a pretty dangerous way to live.
It's cool that if you try to do a payment plan, you cannot change it unless you call them and cry.
That's easy. You're an actor. Cry.
That's true.
I don't like talking to people on the phone, though.
I hate it. I have so much anxiety about it.
I just think they're nothing to me.
Yeah.
They can't hear me because I'm going like...
I think they're all trying to steal my stuff.
Yeah.
They can never hear me because I'm going like...
You know what I do?
You know what I do every time I pick up the phone?
I go home.
What?
I say, because I don't want them to steal my stuff, I say, "Send me an email."
Yes.
"If you know who I am and you're calling me, send me an email. I'll just go on your website and see it."
Come on.
And they go, "Okay," because they're never trying to steal my stuff.
Yeah, that's true.
But then I don't have to talk to them.
That's my email face.
That's it.
I really want to get into a...
Means I love it.
That's your email face?
That's your email face.
I don't know what that means.
That's your female face.
Oh yeah, true.
Cumshot face.
Cumshot, yeah.
O-face.
Receiving cumshot.
Email.
Electronic mail.
He is an electronic mail.
Receiving another mail.
Oh, a cumshot from an electronic mail.
Yeah, well no, to...
So a robotic mail.
No, you're an electronic mail and you're receiving a cumshot from a normal mail.
Receiving, downloading cumshot into throat.
Receiving cumshot.
Blast.
You'd be like this.
- You'd be like this, you'd be like,
downloading cock into throat,
uploading cock out of throat,
and you'd probably do that 100 to 200 times.
- And then make him cum.
- Yeah.
- And then you say, "Digesting semen."
- That's what I do.
- A little progress bar on his belly.
- Ding!
- And you can hear it going,
(imitates gurgling)
- And then maybe like an easy bake oven,
like baked good comes out.
- A baby comes out.
- Yeah.
- I need a coffee.
We have coffee in the pot.
- I'll make you a coffee, yeah.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna make you a coffee.
You you um
Will you get me a cup of water?
Yeah, anybody else want anything? What do you guys want? Do you want some ceviche or something? Yeah, that would be great
Well, you just stood up would love ceviche ceviche would actually be splendid would be busing right now. Oh you fucking offered it
Okay, he's being a total cock. I got a I think I'm gonna do like one of these uh
Things are you just die all of your clothes black? What's what do you mean one of those things?
There's like all these videos I've been seeing they'll show up on Instagram reels and it's like all their clothes
Yeah, it's like they get like one of those big sterilite tubs
Plays that like do you wanna are you gonna play music while you die your clothes? Yeah, I'm gonna do that
It's gonna be a video of me dying all my clothes black and then posting the results
Okay, there's I can guess what the results might be. I think they might be black clothes. I think it might be
These jeans I wash these jeans. I think I accidentally washed them in hot water
Man, I hate to interrupt what if you guys had your own podcast would definitely be probably the greatest podcast of all time
I was just filling time. I did not care about what I was saying the whole that's what a podcast is is filling time
No, everything that we've said up until this point has been
Beautiful sentences see I was sitting in there, and I was talking to myself like I'm such a machine
I couldn't even stop I was like you guys are saying ceviche I walked in there
I imagine putting ceviche in that sink and trying to make it in there. Yeah. Yeah, I'm the sink in the sink
Well, I was that's almost as interesting as dying your clothes black. It's way more interesting
You already have black clothes first of all dumbass your entire clothes are black look everything you have on is black
I know that he would he would he would accidentally fall into the tub of die
Yeah, I know and he would not die a single article of clothing. I would turn gray
He would fall in and his skin would absorb every last drop of the time.
And he'd be like, "Oh no, I can't do this. I can't tie my clothes anymore."
No, I ain't touching you. No. If you fall into a thing of black dye, I am not publicly wringing you out in front of everybody.
Why not?
Because I don't want to be associated with you in that way.
He's wringing me!
You wouldn't even do it for a good friend?
You wouldn't do it outside in front of everyone? You wouldn't wring him out by the neck?
No, you just, yeah, you take one side and you take the other and then you twist in opposite
ways to get all that dye out.
Patrick doing his racial color humor again.
What do you mean?
No, it's not racial at all.
This is not racial at all.
This is about an imagination.
You know what's not racial to cover yourself in black dye?
You know what Christmas is about for me?
It's different.
Christmas is about love, family, cookies, values, sag-nod, values, morals, ethics, logos, pathos,
Patrick it's Patrick it calendar he flips it over to December he says hmm I wonder
what kind of racist jokes I could do every single day of this month it's not
true one I don't have a calendar yes he probably has a bad you don't know how to
use a calendar no I know how to use a digital calendar I have one you can't
read one bro I have one waking up every morning and looking at it looking at the
wall next to his bed and going I can't understand what day it is at all cuz he
bought a colander actually you know what I do there is a calendar it's metal
There is a calendar in my kitchen, but it's from the former tenant and it's all in German
You should still be able to understand it. I do I understand well sequential months
I remember the I remember the German fucking I don't think you need to it's all numbers
And then you should be able to know if you are looking at the calendar to find out what month it is
I think there's you have a bigger problem. Yeah true donor stock. I know it's the 12th today, but what a month
Guys, we should do a calendar.
We should. Maybe with funny pictures on each month?
Funny ass photos of us for a calendar.
That's not so bad an idea.
I bet we could make a billion dollars.
Yeah, it's pretty much the same.
I forgot.
It's called calendar, well it's got a K.
January, February.
What months are these?
January, February, March, March.
Oktober, Dezember. They have a cooler, honestly this is just a cooler spelling.
Bro, March is called Mars.
Of course, wait, of course it's October.
August, October, I remember December as date-cember.
Oh, and I wouldn't even understand what I was looking at because it says calendar.
Yeah, and C, you see the two D's there.
No, not C, K.
No, no, no.
No, K.
Sontag, Montag, Donnerstag, Midwach.
Mid what? Oh my god, what's this? Pull this up.
up is a news article. Oh wow on CNN. Whoa. This is huge. Christmas will be tomorrow this year.
Official. Wow that's huge news. I didn't even realize. Barbara Starr the Pentagon reporter.
All that shit with Santa Claus must have been kinda. Leading up to this. Yeah. They changed
the Christmas date. Yeah. To tomorrow. Wait what's tomorrow? The 25th. Of Christmas month?
- Yeah, December, of Dezember.
- Oh, Dezember.
- Yeah.
- Dezember!
- Stop doing that, man.
- Yeah, you don't like that.
- But today's Christmas Eve,
and because it's Christmas Eve,
everyone knows the Christmas Eve tradition
is to open all of your presents and stockings.
- The ones from your friends, yes.
The ones from Santa, you save 'til the next day.
- Sure, okay.
- We can agree on that.
- But also, I'm gonna be real with y'all,
the Santa shit is a little bit more personal,
and I don't really wanna publicly be opening
- I'm really into sharing that.
- My standard Claus gifts.
- And I saw something this morning
when I came into the office that I don't know
if you guys saw.
- And what was that?
- I saw--
- You sound like Tiny Tim.
- No.
- I did see something pretty exciting.
- What'd you see?
- And this is huge.
- Okay, we'll just spit it out, maybe.
- It's actually rather small.
- All right, well just, can you talk please?
Tell me what it is.
- I saw an elf.
- No way.
- Yeah, right.
- And you will not guess what he was doing.
- Do we have a video of the elf?
- Nope.
- We have cameras all around the office.
Elves cannot be taken video of.
For real?
That's a fucking lie.
Well you shouldn't.
It's not nice.
Well yeah, that's true.
Wait, so what happened with the elf?
Who was the elf?
What was he doing?
The elf was an elf.
Yeah, but what was his name?
I didn't ask his name, I just saw him.
I didn't speak to him.
I was a little starstruck.
Any elf?
He's not even a famous elf and you're starstruck?
Every elf is famous.
What are you talking about?
Humanity is more famous than elves.
Humans are more famous than elves.
What are you talking about?
What kind of Christmas blasphemy bullshit is this?
Wait a minute, I saw...
Look, look, look, Jimmy, I'll pull up the security cam.
Oh wow.
That is right outside.
Is this the elf you saw?
Nope.
No, okay.
This is a different elf.
That's a weird elf that I don't like.
I'm not a fan of him.
But I will tell you what I saw the elf doing when I came in.
What's that?
He was putting toys in our stockings.
No fucking way.
I am deadly fucking serious.
Okay, stockings that have been here all of Christmas December.
Did you hear that noise when he put-
- Hold on, do that again. - Whoa.
Holy.
- There is something in there.
- All right, well let's check these out.
- Whoa, there's one in mine too.
- Okay, wait, maybe there's something in mine.
I really hope there is.
- Let's all pull it out at the same time.
- Mine is stuck.
- Well, I guess you don't get it.
- That was a very-- - It's a different noise.
- That was a weak-ass fuckin' drop.
All right, ready? - Okay.
- Three, two, one. - Two, one.
- Oh my God.
Wow. I got Max Pro Contact Cleaner.
And I got... Oh, we got Blow Off.
We got Blow Off Duster.
Oh my God. And look at that guy.
Look at this little guy. This is awesome.
I got a different one. I got Contact Cleaner for circuit boards,
power tools, batteries, and electric repair. He's spraying what anatomically should be his penis.
Or his lap. Yeah, you're right.
More his lap.
Wait, there's more shit in here.
There's something else. Let's go one by one on this one.
I mean, come on. Here, I'll go first.
You go first.
What did you get?
What is that?
- It's a paint your own wind chime.
- You got a paint your own wind chime?
- Of a unicorn.
- Wow.
- For ages three and up.
Unicorn paint brush and paint brush included.
- And check out what I got.
Smile factory.
- You got a smile factory?
- You know, you could be the foreman at the smile factory.
- You kind of are a smile factory for me.
- You have such a joyous fucking smile on you.
- Yeah, you're always making me smile.
You're kind of manufacturing smiles for me.
- And let's blow that away.
Oh, it got all wet.
Okay, let's see what I got here.
Oh my god.
Arthur Dinosaurs 20 pieces peel and stick watch and play.
Wow.
I have been wanting this for a hot minute.
What does this have to do with Arthur?
I wonder.
Arthur's on it.
Arthur is an animal and there's animals on it.
Oh here, I can tell you what it has to do with him.
Arthur and Buster found a dinosaur footprint.
Which dinosaur do you think made it?
That's what it says on the back.
Stop doing that. Did you do it?
No. I got scared.
Try it one time.
I got scared last minute.
Just try it one time. This is on Patreon. You can try it one time.
(laughter)
How does that feel?
I did not want it to get actually in my mouth, but I tasted that.
How did you feel though?
It doesn't feel good.
No?
No, it's like, leave it. It's left a bad taste in my mouth.
Mmm. I feel a little light you sound a little sick. Yeah, yeah
Open up your smile factory dude. I want to see what these do I want to see what the smile
Thank you save my wind chime for you're gonna save it. Yeah. Yeah, I'm gonna save my wind chime for home
What is that?
I guess it's yeah
Get a punch in on this here
Sponge and I guess this is supposed to be the ink. I don't know man. What I look like the fucking smile
Factory owner I am happy is be with you
At the bottom at the bottom here it says I am happy is be with you that's so cute
You know what I trust I trust what this I trust this ink
So what my body? Oh, it's stamps. Oh
And it's not very good
What's a smile factor you need employees yeah, you're gonna need to get a few this is terrific
Let's stamp it come on stamp yourself. It's not there. No it doesn't work. I think the ink is dry
Oh, that's okay, and you look amazing with that you do look amazing. Well Christmas guys. It is Christmas well guys
Miss Eve do you guys want to open our other gifts, maybe oh?
Yeah, yeah, how's that sound I'm excited for these who should we open first?
I
Don't know all right. We'll open mine first. Okay. Okay. This first one is to
Patrick oh my gosh, okay wait. I'm excited
Kind of see what this is through the bag just open up, baby from the fucking front then and I'll hold your mic for you
No, I'm not upset no upset today. It's Christmas Eve. I'm a complete smile factory
Okay, he unwrapped it, and he's doing it as slow as he possibly can.
Here he goes.
What is it, man?
Oh my god, I'm so excited.
What is it?
No way!
A clinic set.
Oh my god.
No fucking way.
Wow!
Hold that up.
Hold that up to the camera.
Tear into that thing, dude.
That is incredible.
It's got everything you need.
I'm jealous.
Oh yeah.
I'm jealous too.
I found it at the doctor's office.
And look, it even has a photo of me.
There you are.
That's you!
You look so sweet.
Alright, how about you put that stethoscope on there.
Okay.
And go ahead and start inspecting my body.
Come on!
Oh, it fits like a glove.
You wanna check my heart rate?
It does fit like a glove would fit on his head.
You need your glasses.
Every doctor has glasses.
yes replace your current glasses what else do you need you need to make sure
that you can you can charge people yeah cash register because this is something
that you should have it a doctor's kit is a cash register oh there's a syringe
there's scalpel yes you need to cut your wrists oh you broke the scissors my
surgical scissors wait is this a gas mask oh I think so what the hell is this
What's that supposed to be? That's a urinal cake.
This is a... Wait, what's this one? Oh, this is a heart rate monitor.
Wow! Hook me up to that. Okay. And I don't know what this is. You have a red line and a blue line.
Maybe this is calipers. Oh yeah, it does seem like maybe it is.
Some kind of calipers. Or a body fat percentage. Here, why don't you try these on? They look like they'll fit you.
you yeah this set is incredible I just want to inject stuff with this all day
you look amazing this gift is so cool Caleb yeah well listen I didn't just get
a gift for this fucking stupid piece of shit I got you one as well you're gonna
I'm a piece of shit what I got you one as well did you really yeah once you go
and check that out and you'll notice say who see who that says it's from this
This says from secret admirer to...
That's right, I mean...
And then a scribble.
And then Cameron.
Yeah, I accidentally put my own name on it first.
Because I'm so stupid.
Okay, I'm gonna untie this.
I can't wait to see what this is.
I caught my finger in it!
No, you asshole, shut up.
Wait, let me use my surgical scissors.
Tear into that bad boy.
Yeah, it's just cardboard.
Oh! What is it?
It's a pretty dress!
Oh my god!
Come on!
Oh, it's got a woman feeding a parrot on it!
Put that thing on right now.
Put that beautiful dress on.
And look so fucking lovely for me.
And look at this!
It's...
It's a nail and hair set!
It's got a perfect nail and hair set,
'cause I was thinking about you and I was like,
"There's hair chalk!"
Cameron likes to look good.
Cameron li- I mean, look, you're dressed to the nines today for Christmas.
Cameron likes looking fucking good.
Fucking good right look and so I was like I'm gonna swag camera now. He can color his hair. He can color his nails
And he can make sure that he's looking mighty
Chuck has a what does it say on the back here? It says it has titanium
Titanium dioxide
Titanium all in it's very strong titanium and the nail polish has aluminum and this comes with six hair chalk to glitter nail polish one
Toe separator one nail file and one rope go ahead
(laughing)
- What's the rope for?
- Go ahead and put some of that chalk in your hair.
I wanna see what colors that you can come up with.
- Oh, you should give yourself one colored bang.
- 'Cause Cameron, you're just so creative,
and I wanna see what you will do with something like this.
Oh my God, it looks so much fun.
Guys, I'm-- - I like how it's like
this kind of opaque plastic.
- Oh, look at that.
There's glitter everywhere.
Which hair color are you gonna put in?
Pink.
He's gonna put pink in his hair.
He's putting pink in his hair.
Real men wear pink in their hair.
As chalk from the nail and hair combination.
How do I use this? I think you just rub it in.
Do I just hold it with my hands?
Maybe there's something in here. What's this?
That is a kind of monkey.
Let's see, does it open?
Not for use in eyes area.
That's lip balm.
And it tastes like green apple
Really how does that feel?
Dry and waxy yeah, all right. We'll just apply all your fingers should
Apply the hair chalk with those those digits chalky. I would hope so it's damn chalk
Let's get now put on your bang. No no no we need it. Oh
Yeah, you could do that
Yes, oh yeah, oh, you're gonna need a lot more than that there Cameron. Yes. Oh, that's fucking lovely
lovely. Wow that looks amazing. It smells good. What does it smell like? Can you smell the
titanium dioxide in there? I can't smell it but I can feel it in my nose. Yeah.
You need more. You need much much more. You need a lot more. Yeah. And look you're getting it
everywhere. Well that I would hope so. It's chalk. There we go. Now you're getting
a nice pink strand. Oh my god you look fucking Christmasly lovely. You look
festive AF my friend. Yeah. Is this enough? That's maybe a little bit more, maybe a
little bit more. Oh yeah, oh yeah, that's good. Yes, you look good.
Oh my god. And look at these. Oh those are ribbons for the hair. Caleb you
shouldn't have. Yeah, probably not. Yeah, I probably shouldn't have gotten chalk and
Nail polish yeah, you're right. What's this last one here? Huh? Who's that -?
Look at my hand
Caleb to
Caleb
Okay, it appears. I got this for myself because I was so jealous of you guys having fucking awesome gifts from my mind
Because I guess your gifts are gonna be crap so I got myself a little something
Wow
playset. That's incredible. I need you to put on this mask right away. Trust me. That's why I got it.
There's so much badass crap in here. There's this mask, first of all, which doesn't have a way to go on your head.
Just hold it up. Looks good. Actually, we want this. That looks good. You could tuck it into the brim of your hat.
Oh, I could.
Here, now hold your mic.
Hold on, hold on. You hold my mic.
I got, um, let's see, a sheriff's badge that also has no...
There's nothing I can do with that.
I got a walkie-talkie.
Roger, Roger, you know?
A watch.
You should say Caleb, Caleb or Santa, Santa.
Put my watch on.
That's a cool watch, too.
Yeah, it doesn't look big enough.
Alright, I give up.
best part a gun working it says good good
good gun super world good gun super high
performance power do not shoot at any
human or animal let's see if I can get
the lens of the camera oh wait I'm gonna
get this I swear to God I don't know oh
oh you're coming close I know I'm coming
so close dude how fucking badass that
would be so fire okay go again
Oh, it won't stick it won't stick. I don't think you got it that basically good. Can I play with one?
I know maybe try playing with your fucking chalk you pussy
Which one you want to play with?
Yes, you can play with the knife see I've been I've been holding the pistol this whole time
so
But anyway, I hope you guys
I hope you guys like your gifts.
Oh wait, there's a hand grenade.
Oh wait, speaking--
There's a grenade too.
Guys, wait, this one doesn't go.
I gave myself one other thing.
You gave yourself two things?
Well, yeah, but it's kind of a one-two, they're related.
I got myself Power Perfume.
Power, ingredients, alcohol, made in China.
Keep out of the reach of children, do not put on skin.
So let's pop this open, I wanna see how this smells, right?
Okay.
Let's check it out. Power.
Oh my god, it's a fucking grenade!
Wow!
Let's pop the top.
*laughs*
Don't put it on your skin, you're not supposed to.
Oh, it smells of maze balls.
Can I smell it?
Don't, don't spray me.
Smells good.
It's...
It smells like bod body spray.
It smells like bod black.
But, it's a grenade.
It is a grenade that is pretty badass pretty cool. So that's the end of my gifts guys. I hope you enjoyed that
Anyone else got fuck me. There's a lot of crap over here. There's a lot of gifts all right
Okay, Pat. I think I think you should go next okay
Oh
My gifts you mean I thought you were going to give me another no
I think you should give your gifts next I know I know what you got Caleb
And I and I think yours needs to go before yeah for Caleb, okay?
I think I got two grenades
You're rich. Oh this watch out world. I got for Cameron watch out you know for me, and it's pretty it's in a big bag
I like a big bag. It's got our homeboy on it - Santa Claus is right there
Yeah, and someone hold my microphone for me. You look like a mumble rapper right now. Yeah, they you look like take Takashi 69
With those face tattoos
Oh my god now pull that out of the bag and show everybody
I know that Cameron is a cinephile Wow
Fucking
Shit, it says let's watch a movie. I am putting this above me and my girlfriend's bed
Yes, and you're gonna be fucking sometimes look. I will put I
Love this when you can't fucking come while you're fucking you'll
Look at that and look at that glitter on all over it, and I like the speckled eggs it has with tails
It's love that's not what those are these those are eggs with tails your movie. These are reels of movie film reels
What's a film reel? It's if you it's what a movie on the DVD. Oh, these are DVDs with multi-hole DVD
Yeah, pretty much. I know about this and then thank you so much Patrick. You're welcome so pretty
This is what I got for Caleb. This is looking like maybe that bag up
Yeah, hold up that bag up that bag. It was the only bag that I could find at the store
Okay, here's the bag. Oh, it looks so cute.
It looks big!
Yeah, it looks like a big gift for a big guy.
Okay, open that up.
I'm really nervous.
What does it say? What does it say? I can't read it.
I made you a self-portrait on a t-shirt that you can wear.
Oh my god.
Patrick, thank you so, so fucking much.
I've never had a friendship like ours, and you are my fucking best-ass friend.
Why don't you put that shirt on right now?
It's going on my ass right fucking now.
On your ass.
So everyone can see that it looks exactly like you.
Wow.
How did you make this?
With sharpie.
Wow.
And a shirt that I bought.
is his mic up for him or something, Pat?
Wow! I'm so lucky to have you as my friend.
Christmas is so nice this year.
It's such a lovely shirt of my face.
That's so pretty!
It's pretty, I would say it's pretty accurate.
You could also go to a punk rock show with that
and people would be like, "This guy is hardcore, he has a DIY shirt."
True.
And then you'd be like, "It's actually not hardcore, it's lovely."
Yeah.
Because my friend made it.
But I also keep it a little bit classy by bringing my collar out of it.
of yeah see that's nice thank you so much that's so sweet that's so pretty you
look what a lovely gift this is the loveliest Christmas ever so far yeah
I really do look like an extra in green room when I wear yeah I know what a
shotgun in my hand yeah it's pretty cool yeah that's pretty awesome now Cameron I
think you have some I do have some gifts that I got for my friends I'm gonna give
Patrick is first. Now, okay, Caleb, this is Patrick's time to open his gift.
Here, Patrick, this is your gift that I think you might like.
I can already, I'm holding it.
Now, I know that...
Wait, who am I? Wait, real quick.
Who are you?
A lot of people.
Alan?
Yeah, my friend.
Yeah.
My friend's dad, Alan.
Okay.
Patrick, I know that you like to wear a lot of different hats.
and i got you one that maybe can satisfy a lot
I'm not gonna look at what it is
I'm just gonna put it on
here let me do something before you put it on
ok just go ahead and put it on
and I'm gonna do something for you really quick
as you put it on
hold on here
oh I feel bad for the sad souls who aren't watching this video
ok now go ahead and put
go ahead and put your new hat on
pat
cause this is I think a new type of hat for you
Holy fucking shit.
What does it say?
It says magic
display
It says magic display
You can make it say whatever you want
There's an app you can download
to make it say whatever you like
Oh my god! This is incredible
I know you've always wanted a hat
that says magic display
So I got you one that not only says that
but it moves around on the hat
And you can make it say magic display in different colors
- Yeah.
- Well, I don't think that's possible.
- Look at this accessory on the back.
- I think it's only blue.
- Okay, well, it's a very cool gift regardless.
(laughing)
- And I thought you would like that
'cause I know you're a fan of hats.
And I thought maybe you'd like a--
- Yeah, I mean, you know I'm a fashion guy.
Look at this shirt that I made.
- And this is a fascist guy.
(laughing)
So, I do, there's one more gift to give out.
- Give it to me.
- I'm not gonna give it to you if you do that.
You are coding this hat. I think that's how you get the app.
Oh, okay. This is so much fun to hold a gun to people's heads.
So here, Caleb, here is a gift.
Check out this bag, everybody. The golden reindeer. Somebody mic me.
That is the most golden-est reindeer I've ever seen. Alright guys, this is the last gift, right?
The last gift. Yeah, I'm very excited. And I think you're going to like this one a lot, Caleb. I tailored it to your interests.
So go ahead and unfold that and hold it up.
Oh, it looks like it got glitter all over it.
Holy shit, what the hell is this?
I'm getting the coolest fucking outfit of all time today!
Oh my god, it's a badass fucking hoodie that says "Hip Hop" on it!
This thing's going on too!
Oh wow.
From a punker to a rapper.
Throw that thing on, dude.
And doesn't the texture feel incredible?
Oh my god, it's comfortable.
You look incredible.
And turn around and show the back of it, Caleb.
It's exactly the same.
[LAUGHTER]
Wow, dude.
Yeah, I thought you might really like that.
Thank you so much.
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas, guys.
This has got to be our best Christmas yet.
It has been so far.
Wait, this is a-- oh my god, I got a badge as well.
You come with a badge?
Whoa.
Swat police.
Wait, that came with a sweatshirt?
Yeah, Swat police.
says magic display would like to access your apple music your music and video
activity and oh yeah library i think i have to accept that for i gotta accept
it let me re spritz yeah
well i don't know
old got pop the top of the only way let it could what a christmas so far
this has been one of the greatest christmas ever smelling uh... but
you know we didn't just did you get yourself
we got him to my
deep mouth uh...
That's no good, pal.
No, no, no.
We're gonna have to go to the Christmas emergency room.
Definitely.
We didn't just get gifts for each other.
We actually got a gift for our listeners,
which is a podcast episode.
We did, yeah.
We just did about 20 minutes of opening gifts for ourselves.
Wait, can you get a punch in on this?
I think I changed my display.
What does it say?
S rocks.
It's supposed to, wait.
Oh, oh!
Oh, Chrisma!
Chrisma.
Chrisma?
S rocks.
(laughing)
Wow, I'm so glad you're having fun with your hat, Patrick.
Yeah.
So I actually have prepared, as some people
may remember, that we've done, we've looked at a website before that had some
interesting information about Santa Claus.
And what would that be?
And that website was Mystic Investigations.
Yes.
And it was when we learned about Santa Claus and the anti-claws and all this stuff.
I'll say it. One of the all time best.
One of the greatest websites I've ever loved.
Yes.
And I have prepared
a few just a few tidbits from this from mystic investigations that i want to
share with you guys uh...
and you know i uh... you guys have never seen the website for cousin we did it
before was all audio yes
well i'm mesmerized
not
right now i like that
the
- No, I think, you see Pat, I think,
I've been thinking that you should have,
- What? - Should wear your hat
in like a hip hop sideways style.
I've been thinking that lately for no reason, yeah.
- Or maybe wear it like this.
That's a cool way to wear a hat.
- That's a cool way to wear a hat.
(laughing)
- Wait, hold on.
Oh, I didn't, it didn't say the full thing.
I'm sorry, hold on, let me fix it real quick.
- Okay, what is it?
- No.
- Don't do that. - It should be fixed now.
- Don't do that to us.
Yep, it says the same thing.
(laughing)
- I guess it's not working.
- You hit the character limit.
You can't call both of us a pedo.
- Oh, something's happening.
- Now it's just point and hit.
(laughing)
- This is truly most the incredible hat ever.
- I'm gonna have to agree.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
So yeah, I have some stuff from the Mystic Christmas blog.
So let's take a look at what's going on here.
First of all, Disney's Frozen Queen Elsa is real
and she knows Jack Frost.
(laughter)
- It really startled you?
- Oh God, no!
China's grenade perfume is hitting me.
(laughter)
Oh my God.
- In fact though, she's not just real,
but when we go forward here,
Snow Queen Elsa has met Keanu Reeves.
On December 26th, 2015, Elsa appeared at the North Pole
and met fellow immortal, the actor Keanu Reeves.
He was visiting there for the first time
since the 21st century let him discover
the most enchanted avenues of the supernatural world.
Keanu really hit it off with Elsa.
Some think Santa invited Reeves to the North Pole
just to set him up with Elsa.
They began dating and are often considered
the premier couple of love when they visit.
Their relationship has endured despite them
often being apart.
Keanu travels to Arendelle between film projects
and his own supernatural slaying activities.
Elsa goes to his home in California
when her busy schedule allows for it.
- Oh my God.
- Did you guys know this?
I didn't realize Keanu Reeves is straight up clapping Elsa's fucking butt cheeks.
Yeah, in the North Pole too.
Yeah, and sometimes in California.
They must be doing it to keep warm.
Yeah, I guess so.
You think Keanu Reeves is like a real warm cock?
Yeah.
Oh, I didn't know that.
He does.
Yeah, and her pussy gets cold?
Her pussy is frozen.
Oh, wait, why does she want to keep warm?
She's a fucking snow-ass bitch.
Yeah, she likes the frozen, I mean the cold.
You're making shit up.
I'm making shit up.
They're doing it to keep cold
Yana Reeves is trying to keep cold my dick is way too hot my balls are on fucking fire
Elsa you need to cool them off with your complete icy hole yeah, it's true John wick more like hot dick
Yeah for yeah, or and no they were four inches. Okay. I think Keanu Reeves has a big cock whoa
What's happened to my hat?
Hacked by Jubio. Oh my god. It was hacked great. That's great. All right. Let's go next here
Elsa and Keanu Reeves update the happy couple was seen on Valentine's Day 2016 at Elsa's ice castle in northern Norway
Oh, there's I'm so that's Elsa by various members of the supernatural community. She's looking a bit on the elderly yeah
Yeah, kind of I mean listen, and this is one year from the last one Wow
Gilf status a little bit yeah
grandma I
Love frozen mm-hmm
That's me telling my grandma that I love bro. Dude that movie is fire. Should I say ice it is yeah ice cold movies ice
Ice ice cold. Yeah, okay. Let's go. Let's go forward here. What so here's something I found article
I found on mystic investigations that actually I did not expect this is not the way I expected this website to go, okay
What does Santa Claus look like is Santa Claus white and we have a picture of Santa Claus and let's go next here
Technically is not white if one is talking about having classically Nordic features Santa Claus is Greek and as an olive completion
Common among those of Mediterranean descent he actually lies somewhere in between white and black
at least
At least that's what his human half displays as he is half angel as well
He has emerald green eyes that glow a bright white when activating his various angelic powers if you look closely
You can actually see even brighter white specks flying about his eyes like that of a snow globe
This is not seen among other demi angels and is most likely the spirit of Christmas flowing through him
And this we can skip over the rest of this and go to the next one here
The whole impetus of this article is reading this article and that was a link and I clicked on that link and it was this
Well Santa Claus cannot be a white man anymore. It's time to give st. Nick his long overdue makeover. Oh, yeah, click right there
He's a black man. Yeah, so let's go forward here
The whole impetus of this article is reading this article which appears to be another politically correct fueled race obsessed
Diatribe against the traditions of Christmas the author of the article wants the white Santa to become a black penguin
Santa could indeed turn himself into a penguin, but why the hell would he however he loves penguins and adopted some from the South Pole
They waddle about the quaint cobblestone streets of North Pole village with glee at Christmas time
He actually does put little Santa hats on them. It's beyond adorable
It seems like Xavier kind of got off topic there by the end of that. Yeah. Yeah, I do really well
Yeah, but they want to turn Santa to a black penguin is one being like
Santa needs to be not a white guy, but a penguin.
- Yeah.
- That's what they think is like the, like...
- Man, I'm sick of these white Santas.
He should be a penguin.
- Yeah.
- And we go forward here, I think,
yeah, Xavier gets back on topic here.
Maybe the author of the black Santa penguin article
can't grasp that fake Santas are generally white
because the majority populace, at least in the US,
is white in appearance for now.
This is reflected in his image being used in various venues
in his portrayal in films.
If the majority was black, then most of the Santas
probably be black as well. Santa Claus loves people of all races and he approves of fake
Santas of all races. Fake Santas? Of all races. Who wish to spread the spirit of Christmas
since Saint Nick himself can't be in every mall in the world. Although he does make it
to some and if it's in a nation of mostly one race he has been known to change his appearance
to that race so as not to stand out in a crowd. Clearly he would look out of place in China
or Africa. If your kid has ever seemed totally enchanted and beyond happy after visiting
a mall Santa then odds are it was the real Santa Claus.
- Yeah, Santa does a great job blending in
with the big red outfit, the Santa hat,
the reindeer and the sleigh.
As long as he matches the race of the majority
of the people in whatever country he's in.
- He pulls up the statistics on his phone.
- Yeah, and he goes, "Oh, goddamn,
"looks like I'm fucking Dominican today."
(laughing)
- He has to choose before he goes out.
I'm so distracted by the fucking,
I'm making it say so much funny stuff.
- What did you make it say this time?
I think you have to pick one for the rest of it.
- Yeah, you have to stop. - And then we can stop.
- We'll take this, we'll take Santa Claus.
- Santa Claus. - We'll take Santa Claus.
- Yeah. - Okay.
- Let me make it snow.
- You can make it snow? - Watch.
- Wow, this is cool. - Wait, what?
- You suck. - Oh.
- There we go.
- It's still not snowing. - Okay, this is awesome.
- Oh, there it is. - There it goes, all right.
- Wow. - Santa Cole.
- Santa Cole. - And then it's gonna say
- And it's gonna say - Ows.
- Ows. - Yeah, all right,
I guess I'll just. - Okay, phone away.
- Okay. - Now this is an ad
that I saw at the bottom of this page
that really made me laugh.
(laughing)
It is a direct screenshot from the website.
It's cut off a little there, but it just says ad,
and it has a picture of a Christmas train.
- Did you click on the ad?
- I did click on it, and you go next.
It's a goosh lighted Christmas snow globe lantern,
four snowman families singing under a tree,
and musical decoration with battery operated
LED water glittering music playing
with six hour timer Christmas home decor.
- So you didn't get one for me?
- This was expensive.
- Oh, eh.
- And I only saw it today.
- Oh, eh, damn.
- Yeah.
I wish I had this. Maybe we can all go in on one for the office. I'm down. How much is it?
I don't remember, but I think it was 50 bucks. We'll pick one up next time we're at Goosh.
I'm always at Goosh. Goosh does make good-ass lighted Christmas snow globe lanterns. Good,
awesome, awesome Santa hat. Everybody knows Goosh's reputation. I cannot believe how good
our outfits are. I know. Our fits are cray. I have multiple layers, you look cray cray
- I'm Cray AF, and you look like a fly ass motherfucker.
- Yeah, you do.
- Sorry, oh, that's just my clothes talking.
(imitates a bird)
All right, let's continue now.
- I've been trying to bring back Cray,
just saying something is Cray.
- That shit Cray?
- No, not saying that shit Cray,
I'm saying like, yeah, that's Cray.
- That is pretty Cray.
- Yeah, that's a Cray ass thing you wanna do.
- There's nothing--
- What'd you say, that's a Cray ass thing you wanna do?
- You wanna do?
- Wanna do.
- Yeah, you wanna do.
- You are cray, bro, you are acting cray today.
- What?
- Stop acting sassy with your tag, please.
Continue the slideshow.
- Okay, next.
This is another section of the website that I discovered,
and this is called North Pole City.
♪ North Pole City, please go easy on me ♪
- And something that you will see on the next--
- That's good.
- Something you'll see on the next few screenshots
of North Pole City is it's very hard to get screenshots--
- Oh, okay, go back here for a second, please.
I'll tell you when to go to the next one.
(laughing)
It's very hard to get screenshots of this website
because these, you can see at the bottom,
see that present and that sleigh and stuff?
These are things that move across the screen constantly.
Those lights at the top, those are always there,
no matter where you scroll.
And also you'll see little snowflakes,
those are constantly falling across the screen.
So they have like three layers of stuff
that move around across the website.
And now we can go forward a slide here.
And this is Santa's elves.
- Wow.
- That's one of them right there.
- I gotta say, if elves are that small
and they have children motor skills,
they're not very effective probably.
- No.
- You probably need a lot of them.
- Well you'd think like, you know,
maybe that like some years you get a bad gift, right?
- It's probably one of the elves
fucking up their baby. - Oh this shit is probably
made by a terrible elf.
- A baby elf. - It really is a fucker.
- Whoa, don't point that at that elf.
- Stop.
- That's not right.
Don't do that.
Leave him alone.
And I put it sideways.
No, I put it sideways.
And I hold this straight.
Normal, not sideways.
And I got...
That's not computer duster.
That's liquid.
This is liquid.
This is like Windex you just spray it into your face.
What, spray it in your mouth?
I thought that was the duster.
It's contact cleaner.
This is like poison.
- Well, at the end of the episode,
we will call Poison Control.
(laughing)
- Okay, next slide here.
Here's a list of Santa's elves.
- Oh my God.
- So they have a roster right here.
- Herbert Elf.
- So yeah, we could just like kinda jump around here.
- Chief Elf, Elmer Elf, Assistant Chief Elf, Penny Elf.
- Hold on, what's the, what do they call that?
- Herbert Elf, North Pole Air Traffic Control Elf.
- Eggy Elf.
- Eggnog Elf, Chief Nogger of the Eggs.
- Chief what, Caleb?
He's the nogger of the eggs, he nogs all the eggs up.
Eggy Elf is involved in all egg-related endeavors.
Oh my gosh!
Look a few above Eggnog, or one above Eggnog Elf here.
Cameron Elf, in charge of dolls and toys that come to life
within the magical confines of NPC.
North Pole City!
Wait, you are honestly looking like you deal
with toys and dolls right now.
I'm an elf.
Yeah, I would believe you.
Foxy Elf.
Leah Elf.
Leah Elf, oh my god, Leah Elf,
involved in all strawberry-related endeavors.
(laughing)
- Wow.
- They also have Abe Elf, manages the North Pole Synagogue
and secret Hanukkah gift deliveries
to kids around the world.
- And Iggy Elf manages the Internet Cafe.
- Wait, Abe Elf?
- I like that they have, their thing is like,
okay, there can be a Jewish elf,
Hanukkah exists and people get presents,
but yeah, it's also Santa Claus and the elves.
- And it's secret.
- Yeah, it's secret and it's also our thing.
- There's Iggy Elf who manages the Internet Cafe,
but there's also Nettie Elf who runs
the free Wi-Fi internet at North Pole City.
You telling me they got fucking,
they got fiber over there in North Pole City?
- We don't have it in New York City, Dan.
- Well, so they have Gerbert Elf, second youngest elf,
aka the Peppermint Ice Cream Bandit, apprentice in training.
- Whoa. - Oh my God.
- And then they also have Baby Elf, the youngest elf.
Newborn elves are named Baby until eventually given a name.
- Oh, okay, that's kind of interesting.
Bonnie Elf, the lifeguard who watches the water.
(laughing)
- Okay. - Ernie Elf,
manager of Ernie Elf's Enchanted Emporium.
- I wanna go.
- This, there's, that's also fewer elves
I would expect yeah, it's really not that many for a whole city. There's not humans up there really yeah
I mean you really you really need to Wi-Fi elves yeah to internet elves and to egg elves
And I think maybe you could get rid of the peppermint ice cream bandit. He seems like a maybe a negative elf
Fraggle elf yeah known to run mystic investigations when the team is vacationing at North Pole City. His name is fraggle
Yeah, and is he is he part fraggle? I don't know what the hell you're on about fraggle like a
Rock I didn't watch that I didn't either I watch Code Lyoko yo
We I watched that I made time for both of them. No you didn't yes. I did okay
How is your was your media diet so fucking diverse? Oh my god, but my mom didn't wasn't home a lot true
I know what you guys are thinking. There's something missing from this list of elves and that is next slide
And it was not what I was thinking human elves whoa
next slide please
There is a non-supernatural adult human chosen every 12 years
So you can see the snowflakes are blocking up for the words here
Who has a hundred percent complete belief in Santa Claus along with a total infusion of Christmas spirit within them for those in the paranormal?
No, it is too easy to have such belief and mo
Of course most children believe as well
It is truly something special for an average adult to have the spirit of Christmas dwelled deeply within them all year round with an unshakable
Belief in Father Christmas when such a person is found Santa Claus reveals himself to the lucky individual and they are whisked away to North
Pole City to become a human elf in a special ceremony. Human elves are granted immortality
as long as they stay within the walls of North Pole City most of the time. They also gain
elfin powers. Whoa! So you can become a human elf if you believe in Santa enough. I wanna
do that. The last person chosen to become a human elf was, I don't know how to pronounce
the name, Caesar? Caesar. Caesar Jacobson in 2012 and that's a link and I actually put
the link on that right there so if you wanna go ahead and click this and check out their
website that it links you to. Whoa! Whoa! Caesar Jacobson dot com. And just live a crisis text
Let's just scroll through this website here because it's pretty business and randomness. This is the last human elf
Norwegian can Canadian human right civil and animal right maybe it's a czar
So we're gonna just say it's a czar just keep on scroll always just wants to fill out the fucking form
I remember when I was contacted for the opportunity to possibly rescue and rehabilitate an injured birdie a
very injured juvenile crow
I think Eddie image. There's like looks like a watermark, but it's also saying must be his R
Is known as the first deaf pageant winner to represent Canada and go on to internationals so scrolling down just keep scrolling
Yeah, there's a big website look at that scroll bar. Just keep going
Jesus gender equality forum 2017 the huffing and post CNN God bless you Cesar
Jake Jacob and this is a human elf who was seen in playboy energy drink. Holy shit. I'd like to see that wait
There's a playboy energy drink. I don't know that's what it says what else is over here on there is not one way
Just keep going breakfast television and researches for the deaf or hard of hearing shoes on cover girl
Wow, just keep going here like to cover this girl Norway, Norwegian, so this is the this is a human elf wow
She's very accomplished man
You got to be do a lot of extra credit kind of a nerd to become a human elf not
Exactly my kind of thing I would want to do and just go fast all the way to the bottom
and let's see if there's anything else besides.
- Is there any elf stuff?
- Movies with sign language.
- There's gotta be, just scroll the bar all the way down.
- Wow, some development goals.
Wow.
- Let's see.
- Okay, and there's, click below to discover
how I use my neosensory buzz.
- Wow.
- Wow, what a website. - That is amazing.
- And that is what a human elf is.
- Wow.
- That's what human elves do.
- I think I'd like to become one and become--
- Yeah, me too. - I would like to become
a human elf as well. - I don't think I would like
to become deaf all that badly.
- No, but there is something else that we could become,
and I'm not sure if it's the next slide,
but it's coming up, so keep that in your mind.
And let's go next, it is the next thing.
So we have an events calendar here.
- Oh shit.
- This is what's happening this December.
- Of course. - North Pole City.
- We have Christmas Eve, we have Christmas.
On the 23rd, you'll notice there's anti-clause repentance.
So that's the day you're supposed to repent
for the sins of anti-clause.
- So we were supposed to do that last night.
- So we should have done that yesterday.
- Wait, I have to repent for anti-clause's fucking bullshit,
or he's repenting for himself?
- It's unclear.
- I think you repent so that he doesn't get you.
- Hurt me. - Yeah.
- But the reason that I put this calendar here,
six days away, everybody, the Claws Awards.
- No way.
- The Claws Awards held in North Pole City.
- I want to be nominated, and not only that--
- I think that maybe we could have a chance
because of all this Christmas cheer we just spread today.
- Oh, 100 P.
- I spread contact cleaner to my chin.
- Exactly.
He spread that.
He spread hat all across his head.
Yeah, yeah, wait a minute. You spread the folds of your brain smooth and wide. I have an amazing idea for what I can put on this
Which um, which awards you think we would be we'd be eligible for?
Maybe most holly and most jolly. Most holly and most jolly. Dual awards. Most cheer spreading. Best three friends to give presents each other
Oh for sure. Yeah, that's an issue and greatest three friends is definitely up there. Yeah sure. Best picture?
His best hat that says Christmas cheer, but does it in a reverse? Chris just says Chris. Yeah
Chris. Chris. Chris.
Cheer. Chris. I think I could win a
Chris award too. Yeah? From Chris? From Chris. Wait a minute. I don't think there is a Chris award.
You can play music off of this thing? No, oh wait. Wait.
Oh my god. It does sound bars.
Whoa! Holy fucking shit. And this song is beautiful.
This is the best hat I've
ever seen in my fucking life. Was this $600? Yeah. Wow. How much was this? A gift giver
never tells. Oh my god. A gift giver never tells. Look at this one. At what? It's the
same. That just says "Krisma." Okay, wait. Oh, what is that? Who the fuck is that? I don't
know. I'm fucking terrified. What is that? Ow. Sorry. Dollars! Dollars! I like those.
I like those.
Dollars!
Woah.
Okay.
Alright, back to the sludge.
That's the last slide I believe, I think.
Oh my god.
Wait, wait, oh my god!
This is like a...
We are getting a fucking Claus award.
I'm smelling a Cla-
We are totally getting a Claus award.
I'm smelling a Claus-y right now.
I'm smelling computer duster.
Still?
Yeah.
♪ We're checking it twice ♪
♪ We're gonna find out who's naughty or nice ♪
♪ Santa Claus is coming ♪
- Continue.
(Christmas music)
- That's not a Christmas gift.
- All right, can we clear off the middle of this here?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, what's up?
Why do you need this clear?
- I have a special surprise.
- A special surprise, a Christmas surprise?
- Well, more of a Christmas Eve surprise.
And so, something that you guys may remember,
may or may not remember, long time fans.
The first episode ever of Podcasts Without Lists
came out on Christmas Eve, 2018.
Which I have no idea why we did that.
- Wow. - What reason?
- We have to be the biggest geniuses of all time.
There's not a better time to start a podcast.
- No, who wants to listen to a,
well there's no better time to listen
to a first episode of a podcast.
- 100%.
- On Christmas Eve.
- That means that this is canonically a Christmas podcast.
- It is. - There's no doubt.
- We are the diehard of podcasts.
- Here, I want you to hold my microphone for me,
for God's sake.
Please. - This is crap.
- Please hold it. - He's being a crap face.
- Because today, you're so bad at holding this.
Hold it up where I can talk, thank you.
Because today is, okay, all right, this is awesome.
Today is not only Christmas Eve, okay?
- That's not the only holiday.
- Oh my God, Baby Fud's birthday!
- Today is Baby Fud's fourth birthday.
- Wow. - Everybody.
- Oh my God, he's so cute.
- Look at him.
- And of course, I--
- I'll hold him up for you.
- What are you doing, Pat?
I was adjusting the mic. - I don't know what to do.
- You just hold it.
It's the same as holding it for yourself.
Please.
- No, I'll hold Fudd here.
And I actually got Fudd something special from all of us.
- Oh my God.
- Yup.
- What is it?
- I will give you the honor of opening it for him, Caleb.
- It says, "To Fudd, from PAL."
And you guys know what that stands for.
- Podcast about Liz.
- Caleb, yeah, okay.
- Fudd, you're getting a fourth birthday present.
- Oh.
- I thought he was finally mature enough to own one of these.
- He can finally be trusted with a power outlet.
His very first extension cord.
- Ah, all right.
- Guys, I really am so excited.
- Well, let's plug him in.
- Go ahead.
- This is gonna be awesome for him.
- Let me get it plugged in down here.
Okay.
All right, let's sing happy birthday real quick.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Happy birthday dear Fudd.
Happy fourth birthday to you.
And many more.
Let's plug it in you little pink bastard.
There he goes.
Well, it's been a nice Christmas-y this year.
And the--
And we got so many gifts.
And that's gonna be Christmas for us.
So good night and bye fuds ahead.
Bye bye.
[BLANK_AUDIO]