*intro music*
*ding*
*music stops*
Yeah, have you- is-
*silence*
What is this for?
What is-
*silence*
What's what for?
Your out- your outfit.
What is it outfit for?
The firefighters?
Not that outfit- no, the-
*silence*
What is that...
shit on your... what is this for? Why are you dressed like this?
My headphones?
Not your headphones.
No, he always wears the headphones.
That's so I can hear the episode while we're recording it.
I don't know.
I think that maybe you went a little too far.
With what?
What could I have gone too far with, possibly, that I'm doing right now that could be considered too far?
Just... why do you have the... the blue face is okay. We've done blue face before.
This...
Why do you have a braid?
Have you never seen Avatar?
I'm a Na'vi.
The braid is...
Don't touch! That's like my penis!
Bro, have you not seen Avatar?
You're lucky you...
He touched it.
No, you didn't.
You touched it and looked at us when you came in.
You were rubbing it.
I don't like you being a Na'vi.
Me neither.
It's giving you an attitude problem.
You're acting like a Hollywood superstar.
No I'm not.
And it's pissing me off.
And also I have a bunch of healthy and animals in my body.
You were a superstar before.
You were a superstar before you were a famous singer or dancer.
You haven't decided yet.
You didn't need to do this to your body to become an even bigger star.
This is bullshit.
It's just what I want.
Is this who you really are?
Yeah, I'm a Navi.
So you'll be like this probably forever?
Forever.
Mmm, likely story.
So this was your New Year's resolution?
Nope.
What about when you go to get a new driver's license or if your first driver's license?
They don't have skin on the driveway do they yeah, they have skin color. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, they put blue
Well, I don't understand. No for the photo you think they're gonna let you be dressed like this if they let freaks
Do do flying spaghetti monster. I think they have to let me be a Navi. It's true
I mean freaks do flying spaghetti monster or a colander on their head people do that
Yeah, you never saw that and they say it's funny as fucking funny
Religious freedom yeah, so this is your religion now. Yeah, I believe in a wah a
What a wah what is a was that the world yeah?
That the world is pandora spirit of Pandora
I think the only thing I honestly don't know that much about the only Pandora
I know I like to respect is tenacious D radio on Pandora thumbs up tribute
Yeah, thumbs up fucking cock pushing. Yeah thumbs up Liam Lynch United States or whatever
That's gonna come up on the show. Roots Bloody Roots by Sepultura, big
Pandora song for me. Thumbs down that. Thumbs up.
Bo Burnham, Inside. Some shit like that, thumbs up that. Comedy music only on my
Pandora. I used to fall asleep every night to comedy music radio on Pandora as a
child. Is that true? 100% true. Liam Lynch, what's that other guy?
Stephen Lynch. Stephen Lynch, that's who you're thinking of. Yeah, and Liam Lynch is the
other guy. Liam Lynch had United States of Whatever, I just said. Stephen Lynch
Oh peanuts crazy peanuts
But Stephen Lynch he also had a song about being a great Christ Craig
Fucking Craig
Dude 2004 he was a bastard blasphemy wise yeah, it's a fucking bastard. Yeah, that's on about special Olympics
He was a big blasphemer
I bet he would talk and if he was here right now
He roasts the shit out of you in this song. I'd like to see somebody try to roast me
It'd probably like a cure in myself a blue face. Yeah, what do you say that to a Navi blue face lazy?
That'd be you what like that guy blue face where he says blue face, baby, but you're late. Oh, why am I lazy?
Plus you ain't even naked they dress like Tarzan in the movie
They're dressed like we're loincloths. They barely wear a cloth you have ironic shirts a Navi would never run a good blue
It's a blue for the FDNY. It's a blue shirt or just and I can't support the fire department
They don't have a fire department so fire there. They haven't discovered that yeah, that's later on all they know is unobtainium
Yeah, I like unobtainium if you like unobtainium so much. Why don't you marry it? Yeah?
Well, I don't think Navi have marriage. I think they just fuck
With their hair sounding pretty
Like this now, holy god damn this lifestyle it was yeah, I don't agree with your lifestyle
This is a lifestyle choice that you're making you were not born like this
I know that for a fact because I was saw when you were born or shortly
That's thereafter. I actually saw a video of Cameron's birth earlier, and I showed him he showed me
I don't remember that you want to see it again. I don't think you
It's a premium
- That doesn't really, that's not really what I mean.
- No, no, I don't think that you should show that.
- I saw blue, it was like a surgery on a horse,
and they--
- It was like a giant blue sack of tumor.
- It was a giant blue sack coming out of a horse.
- Okay. - And he wanted to show that.
- Well, that was your birth.
- You guys wanna see my new tattoo?
- Yeah.
- Oh, yes. - Yes.
- There's more?
- Yeah, what's your new tattoo?
(laughing)
- It says avatar, and it has the avatars riding.
- How did you even get that?
- On my stomach.
- No, but like how did that even happen?
- It's a little like, it's peeling.
That's what happens when you get a new tattoo, you know?
- It's peeling, it's a little blurry.
- It's a dolphin or some kind of animal.
- Okay.
- That they have in Avatar.
It's probably in Avatar 2.
Which I haven't seen.
- This is bullshit.
- What's bullshit about this?
- You're looking pretty ripped.
You're looking pretty ripped. Yeah, yeah, you think so yeah, I got a Navi kind of looking pretty ripped for a Navi
You know Navi are stronger than humans. I will say of the three of us you would definitely I'm not saying you are a Navi
But you would be the closest to being a Navi. Well, yeah, cuz my blue face and my braid. He'd be one of the
He'd be one of the nerds on the computer dude if I could be like Norm Spellman. Yeah, he'd be like Norm Spellman
Oh my god dream come true one of the scientists in the avatar program this guy Norma the North
So you're Bill yeah like a snowman and I'm gonna be no man. It's your mr. Peanut. Oh, yeah
I'd like to see you prove that
How does he act?
British right very very British very regal. Would you like a proper peanut?
Proper peanut I don't know what he says. I does not say proper never fucking met the guy didn't die yeah
He died and then he became a little
Well, I'm not the little version. I think you are no one that's around right now. It doesn't make any sense
Do you guys grow up? Yeah, okay peanuts age differently than human that makes sense. Yeah
I think he's a teenager now wait if you're not V
How long do not be live because taller people usually live in years, okay? That's very is that true
That's like a possum only lives one year. Yeah, I should have like read the Avatar wiki
Or you've seen the movie
First one so the first one it's cool
spaceships
motor so no motor cycle dresses
Dress as a spaceship then why do you pick the you know at least be a little subversive any but any fucking Joe Schmoe off the
Street of walking to avatar be like I'm gonna dress up like the blue guy for work tomorrow. It's interesting
It's there's only I'm the only one here
I see doing that so I don't like you guys are below average if that's what you that's your point
- You know what would be really, really funny?
It would be really funny to be really, really into Avatar,
but instead of dressing up like the Na'vi,
dressing up like the guys who kill all the Na'vi.
- The evil, the general or the colonel.
- He looks exactly like small soldiers.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, and he has the claw marks on his face.
- Yeah, dressing up like those guys is like,
yeah, I love Avatar so much.
- Yeah.
- Do Na'vi get, can Na'vi get rabies?
- Probably.
That is scary. I think I think that they're gonna do all colors of Navi soon red yellow green
Purple but no white one, huh? There will be a white one in Avatar 5. Mmm. Yeah, is he still planning on making like 15?
Avatar movie. Yeah, it's pretty fun
He's been doing a bunch of interviews where he says like just so everybody knows an avatar 5 they're gonna go to earth
Yeah, just doing a full just like as crazy as somebody that we would find on like a forum thing
But he has 20 billion. I also I read a thing today that he apparently I don't know
I guess I don't know if they already shot avatar 3 or what but they said that he turned in a 9-hour cut of avatar 3
And was like you we're gonna do all the VFX for this before we cut it down. Oh my god. Isn't that crazy?
He's a genius. Yeah, he's a mastermind
He has to be one of I also the funniest part of this is that we're backlogging right now
So even though today the day we're recording is the day that avatar 2 comes out. It's gonna be
It's gonna people are already gonna not be it's already gonna be sitting at a 56 on rotten tomatoes
More like a 98 but yeah, no the rating will settle is the point. No, no, no
I don't think that uh, I don't think that it's probably gonna be that good
I think you're completely wrong. I still I I get up today. I still think it'll be good. I had to there's a
that thing with my tooth is still weird.
- Mm.
- That crown that they put in and then they didn't,
there's that one gap where all the food keeps getting in.
- I'm gonna take the crown off your head,
the podcasting crown.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause you're no longer the king.
- But every time I watch Avatar,
I get up to the point where he turns into the Na'vi.
- The Na'vi!
- And he plays basketball.
He plays basketball with Sigourney Weaver
and then I just, I lose all interest and I shut it off.
- Dude, wait, Sigourney Weaver as the blue alien?
- Bad AF.
And I'm not just saying that because I'm blue.
What if they went to the fuck,
what if the Terminator shows up?
That wouldn't happen.
So first of all, that wouldn't happen.
And second of all, the aliens are fucking sexy as shit.
He has no imagination.
But why not, wait, what other,
he did an alien movie, what if the aliens show up?
Yeah, the xenomorph.
I guess they could.
They'd probably fuck up all the Na'vi, man.
Yeah.
I guess so.
Probably fuck 'em to death.
You should dress as the xenomorph,
you should get some body paint and do that.
I could do that shit.
That'd be no problem or issue for me at all.
You kind of look like the...
H.R. Giger, a lot of his stuff...
You have the same type of head as the same...
You kind of look like the hybrid.
A lot of his stuff...
Like a newborn?
A lot of H.R. Giger's stuff.
Which I just watched.
Just saw it, re-saw all four of them.
Hate Joss.
Joss?
Joss.
That movie though, actually pretty good.
I like that one.
Do you guys feel like H.R. Giger,
a lot of his stuff was borderline sexual?
No.
Yeah, I think there's something about...
I feel like he maybe was drawing, you know like how artists have like, they have a light
table or something where they're like, I feel like maybe he accidentally had his dick behind
like he was, I think there's something, he was drawing an alien and he looked down and
he saw the silhouette of his penis and balls and he was like, holy crap.
The setup was he's sitting, he has a spinning chair right, and on one side he's blowing
a bunch of guys and like fucking sucking their balls and stuff and they have a light behind
And he's like, hold on guys. I have to draw something. I just got an idea and he turns around and now the shadows are cast all over
So he's outlining him. He's like man. These aliens look badass. These animals should attack a woman and then
Turn it around. It's fucking penises and cocks. Yeah, right
But also I guess one of them was holding like a cell phone or some piece of technology seen
It's the the album art for Frank and Christ by dead Kennedy's and it's an HR Geiger
Painting that is just dicks going into pussies. It's fire dude, but it doesn't look it
It only looks like that if you squint
Very close the way you know the HR Geiger was on some some sexual shit when he was drawing his designs
The alien has two mouths yeah, yes, and if that's not the most sexual thing you give an alien
I don't know besides blue tits and butt do we?
Do you ever see the undercarriage any of these aliens and the xenomorph where we go underneath that we're saying okay?
They got three buttholes they have two pussies. There's a I mean I've seen I've seen them in my research. It was two mouths
It's not unreasonable. Yeah, you have to deduce logically. I mean, I just logically
The deduction by reasoning of logic is that there's two assholes and two pussies if they got doubles of everything well
The the from what I've gathered hmm in my research on the xenomorphs. Yes. Yes. Yes is that the the mama?
The big queen the queen the queen xenomorph is just only all she can do
is lay eggs
All she does is she sits there and she might become a feminist gets beautiful. I think I'm finally ready to
Become a feminist we need to she lays a million
Bajillion eggs and then those eggs all come out and then they hug your face and they deep
Bury a baby deep down inside you a deep area man or a woman even a girl can get impregnated. Yeah. Oh fuck
It's gross. It's a disgusting Avi posited
It's not right up on the opposite or you'll go up avi posit or there's people who want that to happen to them
Yeah, people want eggs laid alien eggs laid inside of their butt nice, and they're funny. It's not a funny thing
It's an actual sexual thing okay, but it's kind of funny. That's funny. It's funny to a guy like me
Yeah, but to a guy... It's not funny to a sexual freak.
Mmm... To a sexual... A sexual freak, yeah. A sexual addict.
Egg addict. Egg addict.
Hey, there. Do you have a new Na'vi name, by the way, that has apostrophes in it?
Cam'ron. D'Shaun. Oh, Cam'ron. That's good.
Either one of those is good.
Okay, Cam'ron.
[laughter]
Um, is there any part of this Cam'ron that is sexual for you at all, or is this purely...
I mean well, I mean if I were to find my mate
I would I may fry I just watched his his his a ponytail
Yeah, that is fucked up you can't do that man excuse you touch your fucking hair to him, bro
That's fucking disgusting. That's your penis. He wanted to touch it earlier see if he wanted it
If he takes that blue makeup off, he's just a Jedi Padawan.
I agree, he's a fully an Anakin style guy.
Yeah, that's okay too.
You can't go around touching people with your hair, man.
Why not?
Because they're not, nobody wants that.
And don't say I'm asking for it because I don't have any hair, okay?
No, you didn't shave it.
I do wish that...
Turn around, show everybody.
I wish that you had a braid so I could link with you and ride you like one of the Nabi horses.
You should grow out nothing but that.
That's impossible to grow out nothing but one big square.
I think we should all get a braid.
I think we should all get one thing. It's cool. I know look I'm kidding
I'm you guys think I could rock this for the foreseeable future
Yeah, dude, you might be able to foresee the future with that fucking haircut. Holy
What do you think get a punch in on that here is you turn around completely?
and then I guess
People can see it's kind of thin well. Yeah, whoa back off man. That's his penis. It's okay. It'll grow
It will grow. It will grow. That is nice to know.
It'll get thicker. I think you could just shave like a square. I knew a kid who had a padawan braid in middle school.
Yeah, I did too. Yeah, he was pretty cool. Yeah. Yeah, it's funny cuz what I
The kid that I knew who had a, I guess it wasn't a padawan braid. It was just a rat tail.
It wasn't braided.
It was just a long rat tail and it's like you have to be growing that, to have that in middle school
and it's like down your back. You have to have that for like a while. Like that's a parent's
choice I feel like. That's something that your mom inflicted on you.
What was your conversation like when you got that red tail?
It was mostly about Avatar 2.
Yeah?
It was great clips.
I feel pretty bad for most service workers. Anytime that I have to hold a conversation
with someone, it's probably 10 minutes or less that I start talking about Avatar 2.
Really?
That's my go-to.
Well, I mean when you're getting tattooed I would hope that in 10 minutes if you're a full Navi and have a blue face
That you would bring up a blue face avatar before that haircut. Come on. Are you in an avatar t-shirt? No
You know, it's so funny is fucking deep pop resellers. You look up avatar
t-shirt
Like one from 2008 they will throw the word V
They'll throw the letters VTG on it vintage and then they will sell an avatar t-shirt
For $75 that makes sense. That's all that's funny old. It's not that old. That's decently old teen years
You know the quality on those shirts. It was like no I don't those paper thin like American apparel shirts
You know those shitty ones. No. I don't know anything about clothes, man
You're just talking about you know nonsense thing about getting this haircut though is I kind of was like oh
I'm gonna go it well so the way that I
Framed it was like I don't think I'm gonna keep this
"but can you give me this because I think it will be funny
"to go home to my girlfriend and I have this."
And I was kind of like, okay, which is true.
- Wait, so a professional, you didn't do this at home?
- No.
(laughing)
'Cause I wanted an actual haircut too.
I thought that your girlfriend did it for you.
She braided it.
- That's so crazy.
How much was this haircut?
Do you have to say that?
Where'd you go?
I went to this...
Please tell me you went to like a Dominican barbershop.
Well, that's what I was gonna say.
It's because I went to like a place in Bushwick.
They were just like, "Oh yeah, you should keep this. This looks great."
And I was like, "Oh yeah, I'll think about it."
Did you go to one of those ones that's in like East Williamsburg?
No, I said Bushwick.
You know it's Bushwick.
And it's called like chop it up. Yeah, basically
Tell me how much you paid well, okay, I paid it was a $90 haircut, but that is because my man
That's right. Treat yourself. Oh my that is the car. Let's go. It's not for this is for this. That's what I'm paying
That's a $10 haircut
No that man that you don't know dude. Yeah, you've never had long hair. I'm sorry, but you are
Not like me, sorry
I think it's hard. I'm saying it's expensive. I spent $60 on a haircut and I was like damn I'm doing too much
But him spending $90
No, I'm so good. I will get my haircut once every year and a half. I do not care how much it costs
Yeah, I know if you're getting like I get my haircut probably every six months or I'll do it myself
So if any like the 60 bucks on it, that's like think about it like a subscription service
And you pay that
It's like a loot box
Okay, now I'm starting to understand it. Yeah more nice thing a bit think about it like when you pay like like a gummy
That looks like boba
I don't have where you guys going. I will also say that it was so expensive because the
She took a really long time. She took longer than she
- She's an idiot.
- She's so stupid.
- No, she's smart.
She took longer so it cost me more.
- She's a genius. - She got more money.
- She did a real good job, I'll say.
- Thank you.
- See, when you don't have the blue skin on,
you will look like Squall from Final Fantasy.
- That's the picture I showed her?
- Yeah, if that's the picture you showed, then.
- I feel like you're gonna be very anakin,
especially we're gonna get rid of that mustache forcibly
when you're done being blue.
- Oh yeah?
a scar across your eye. We're gonna give you a scar. I would, I want a scar so fucking much.
Shut up. You talked about it. You love the scar. I want it. You can go to one of those. I talked about it because I want it. He wants a scar that goes like this.
Okay then walk into a stop sign. Nothing's stopping you. I've considered it. Yeah I bet.
Like it, it can't be that bad if you just cut yourself like that right? It, you know what
Nazis did what Nazis would get in fights no pretty tumble Nazis swastika style
Nazis would get into sword fights and they would duel when they were children
and then they thought that the scars are so cool they would pack the scars with
horsehair to like make sure they don't make it Wow all those Nazis have like
crazy fucked up scars on their face that's you yeah there were weird that
Listen those guys are fucking bizarre. Yeah, nothing. I mean they were kind of the Na'vi. I don't want to scar anymore now that I heard that story
Cars are actually not CAF. I heard that scars remind us that the past is real
Israel mm-hmm you want ours remind us that was a quote from Israel should be in the past
That's a quote from Jacoby Shaddix. Not me. Oh
He is such a cool name. It's crazy. I've never heard of this fuck. He's the guy from Papa Roach. Yeah
Papa Roach. You never watched Scarred on MTV?
Papa Roach was the...
Scarred? You never saw Scarred?
No. I never watched MTV once in my life.
It was a show that was just entirely like skateboard, BMX, like rollerblade bales.
Oh, I do remember that.
And it's like, yeah, I popped a bone out of my arm and Jacoby Shaddix going like, "Oh, shit!"
Sounds badass.
It was so sick.
- I think if your name is Jacoby Shaddix,
you have a God-given destiny
to start a band called Papa Rouge.
- Yeah. - Definitely.
- Or be an energy drink mascot.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Or just a video game character.
They have to download you into Crysis 3 or whatever.
- Yeah, a human keyboard.
- Yeah. - Jacoby Shaddix.
- He's like the goth hacker on a Mass Effect ship.
- Jacoby Shaddix is like a Magic the Gathering
Planeswalker name. (laughs)
- He definitely sits to the side
of the rest of the playing field.
he should not be involved. He floats above everything, Jacobi. That's a cool-ass name.
- Jacobi Shadix.
- Shadix.
- That was my fake Facebook account that I used for Spotify.
- Shadix, Jacobi Pimento.
- Jacobi Pimento. I used that for my Spotify. Jacobi Pimento. Badass name, dude. Thirteen
years old. Making sure my mom didn't hear me listen to... I thought that was the last
name.
- It's not.
- What is it? It's like a type of pepper?
- Pimento.
It's a thing.
You guys never had pimento cheese?
No.
Mayonnaise, pimentos, and cheese.
You ever had Aunt Myrna's party cheese salad?
It's fucking really good, man.
Aunt Myrna's party cheese salad?
No, it's pimentos and that.
Do you remember that video?
Have you guys ever had peanut butter toast?
Is that like a Navi thing?
Peanut butter jelly time?
It is.
What do Navi eat?
Do they eat animals or are they vegetarians?
They're vegetarians.
Oh, God.
Don't even, all right.
They, they, I don't remember.
- Can we at least trick them into eating some meat?
- I think they at least kill animals, but for fun.
They kill animals, they shoot it with a bow and arrow,
and then they go like, they put their hand on it,
and they're like, they speak their language.
(speaking in foreign language)
But they're like, you have been killed
for a purpose or something.
So I think that maybe they eat them based on that.
- I think I might start doing that.
- Yeah, doing some blessings over here.
anytime I eat meat. You can get your meat pre-blessed, you know that?
Is that true? For real? For how? For how much? It's from a guy in a cart. Can you get any
meat pre-blessed or just his meat? Just any meat. So I can walk up with like a big
pack of bacon and say, "Will you bless this?" Yeah. And pork chops.
and yeah good why don't they eat pork I will say there's there is something
about pork that is disgusting the salt the salinity what it's too salty it's
probably the mud I think you add salt to it I don't think there's salt no pork is
pretty salty on its own I don't think so I think you're making this up but there
is any time I'm eating a lot of poor anytime I eat this guy never ate steak
before I and now that is not now I've probably eaten more steak than either of
Not true. I eat about three or four steaks a week. Not true. That is true. Uh-uh. I ate one this morning
You did not. I swear to God I this morning. That's why it was so surprising to me that you never ate one
Because you talk about eating them four times a week. I had a steak and a glass of milk for breakfast
You're are you becoming one of these fucking carnivore guys? No, I just like steak.
I just try not to eat carbs before 5 p.m.
Cuz it'll slow me down. See how fast I am?
Just cuz no carbs. Oh my god, you are fast
(laughing)
(imitating gun noises)
- What are you doing with your hand?
Whoa!
(imitating gun noises)
- Move the chair over.
- And that was full of energy drink.
- Really?
- Yeah, yeah, it's called C4.
I thought, you know, before I go to my job
where I talk into my microphone,
I think I need to--
- You should take pre-workout.
- I think I need to have some pre-workout.
Have my entire body just fucking jazzed up.
I do feel tingling.
- Dude, that's the, I had C4 for that video I did
and Jenkum and I-- - It's got some shit in it.
- My head, the top of my head was tingling
during that video. - Yeah, you did.
Yeah, yeah. - And I thought
that I was going to throw up on camera.
- I like the tingling.
- I did throw up though.
I threw up 'cause I ate a worm, but that's different.
- Okay, well, I guess this guy's already promoting--
- Braggart. - Still promoting his video
from two years ago where he eats a worm.
- Check out the Dakota Jenkum magazine.
- Nice. - And watch that video.
- Check out my video. - There's a lot of people
mad at me in the comments.
- Check out this video I made,
guess who got kicked out of Starbucks.
I don't think you'll guess the answer.
- It's actually rather funny.
- And check out this other video.
- Oh, and check out this video that I've been working on.
I've been actually a part of it.
I didn't, I actually, this is a surprise for you guys.
Avatar 2 post-credits sketch.
- Yeah, one night and Cameron more like it.
- The post-credits sketch is by and starring me.
- I would love to see a sex tape with you.
I would love to see that.
Like a Ray J, Kim K style sex tape
where like a big guy's like recording it
and you're laying down on the bed.
- A big guy?
- A big guy, like a big strong guy.
And you're like laying on the bed.
Am I blue or just me?
You're whatever color.
And your ass is out and you look back.
I like, like, all right, you can record me, but I have to be blue.
There's no way I'm doing this where I'm not a Nazi.
There's an outline of your blue body on the bed.
And then that you look back like at the phone camera and you're, you're
like, kind of like that, right?
You're like a little bit coy.
He leans back up and just to perfect imprint of his face, his blue
face is in the pillow.
- Yeah.
- I'm kinda, I'm like.
- Yeah, well you're dropping the recorder.
- That's all right.
- But you do look like that.
Yeah, you're like looking back.
- I'll do it the other direction.
- Yeah, yeah, do it the other direction
'cause I do wanna see this to get something out of it.
Yeah, you're looking at, right,
and this guy's like,
like baby, you know what I'm gonna do to you?
And you're like,
yeah, you're like that, right?
And your ass cheeks are out.
And you have a perfect ass, by the way.
You got a BBL for this.
- Really?
- Yup.
Yup, you did.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
And Na'vi, Napoleon Dynamite, I like it. Na'vi, Napoleon Dynamite, this could be an entire
new...
Oh my god.
This could be an entire new SNL cast member.
This is a robot chicken sketch.
It is.
Na'vi, Napoleon Dynamite.
You should try to get on SNL as a Na'vi.
That's not a bad idea.
First Na'vi cast member.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah. And you could be the first booger picker.
No.
Do you know, do you guys want to ban me?
Pick your no-one.
I'm ready to booger picker.
I'm good for you for my packet, but I don't know if you I assume you guys haven't seen my avatar 2 post-credit sketch yet
You talk about packet. I'm still thinking about you laying on that bed saying I'm a packet. Yeah pack it in there
Can we can we pull up? Well? I can just explain it to you because it's not it's in theater
So it won't be well. No. It's it's you can't show it. That's piracy true. Okay. We're not taking that money away from
Fucking avatar the way of water, okay, but it's basically that I'll just I don't want to spoil too much so the premise
is that
White people be bonding with and riding their Banshee like this
And then do it and then do how do they do it show me yeah, they're they're like they're like giddy up
Be bonding and riding their Banshee like this. Oh, that's good
They say Yahoo I do it's a comedy sketch
(laughing)
I guess that makes some sense
that if you're trying to be funny,
you would say yahoo.
Yeah.
No, I guess that white people would be riding their banshee
and connecting with the mother tree by being like,
I'm okay, so I guess this is a thing.
Yeah, all right.
Oh, let me squeeze by you real quick.
Yes, oop.
Yep, oop, oop.
And I, oop, oop, oop.
Excuse me.
I do that, man.
And they'd be like,
do you guys have Taylor Swift on this planet?
Yeah.
If their banshee got hurt, they'd say, ah shucks.
What?
Shut up.
And if their music came on in the band cheat,
they'd be like, oh, I love this song.
(SINGING) It's got tissue that I wish you saw.
Step outside, but not to brawl.
And with the birds of shade.
Be annoying as fuck.
It's like Red Hot Chili Peppers aren't even a good band,
you asshole.
I don't like whites.
No, I fucking hate whites.
They should all die.
Yeah, I don't like them.
And end scene.
[LAUGHTER]
No.
No, we don't.
That's not true.
We don't like whites.
Nope.
It's true.
Yeah.
Except for...
Who's white?
Philip Seymour Hoffman. Jake Sully.
Jake Sully.
Noam Spellman.
Sigourney Weaver's character.
When I heard--
Dr. Sigourney Weaver.
That's her name in the movie?
Yep.
No, that's not true.
You're fucking assholing me.
It's true.
Liar.
You know there's a, what was it?
You're assholing me.
(laughing)
Acting like an asshole.
It's, yeah, Dishonored.
She agreed to be in Dishonored because there was an,
like, she was like, well, you know,
like technically you can't,
they were like technically you don't have to murder
to like move along in the story.
She was like oh then it's not a violent game,
but you can also still murder.
- I want to murder.
- Yeah.
- I have the urge.
- I have a serious, somebody--
- The sinister urge.
- The sinster urge.
- Somebody has to fucking stop me
'cause I will fucking murder.
- Yeah.
- I need to kill.
- I'm a beacon of sin.
- How is it that people,
do you guys ever think about--
- A blue beacon.
- How some people like killing?
I know this guy who used to be Noah's weightlifting coach,
who's a complete psycho,
and he was in the army for a long time,
or the CIA or some shit.
- Yeah, and plus steroids.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Plus steroids are gonna make--
- Yeah, plus the steroids.
- The steroids are gonna make you crazy.
- But he'd always talk,
they would ask him all about his time in the military,
like, was it scary?
And he was like, "Nah, man, it was awesome.
"I get to kill people all the time."
- I hate the fucking Earth military.
- Yeah, but what--
- But you love your tribe. - But the Na'vi is cool.
What?
But the Navi is cool?
Yeah, so I was just thinking out loud.
What's the Navi word for military?
Group of Navi.
All right.
Group of Navi is--
That's what we call groups of Navi.
Wait, do they have their own language?
I thought they speak English in the movie.
They go like Mahalo and stuff like that.
Mahalo.
Yeah, like this.
All right.
I think you're making--
I think you're mixing up a bunch of different indigenous people.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think they do that.
What was this again?
Live long and prosper, nerd.
got you easiest trick in the book easiest trick in the book you know one
second I'm going live long and prosper directly into the camera it wasn't
cameras you got fucking on the Vulcan nerve pinch - yeah I'm gonna do a fucking
Okay, do a Volcom and nerd pinch on you
Stop you from ever fucking touching a pencil as long as you live yeah, you're a pencil pusher
I use pens actually and I have a pocket protector for him. Yeah, we know you're a dork man. You can shut up now
Oh my god, and you see this tape between my glasses. It's very clear, but yeah, yeah
I have tape on the middle because I get my ass kicked so many times by jocks. I fucking would love to meet your jock or your
There really is something there though
You have a bunch of crap right here though.
(laughing)
You do have stuff.
There really is stuff here though.
Oh yeah, what is that?
(laughing)
Oh, I guess that's my,
I gotta get a new windscreen.
I actually did have shit on me.
I can't believe it.
Wow, you are a nerd, man.
I guess I never thought about it that much,
but you are a nerd.
You have--
It's cool to be a nerd.
Nowadays it isn't. That's fucked.
Because I'm a jock.
Yes, obviously.
Yeah.
Think about what it is to be a nerd nowadays.
Now it's cool to be a nerd.
I'm a jock because I mostly do long jump.
I wish I knew. I've got to fucking, I've got to memorize that Nick Cannon nerd speech.
Oh yeah.
Nowadays it's actually cool to be a nerd.
You should dress like that.
When you see me there's always nerds in my vicinity.
That's true.
There's nerds in the vicinity.
Yeah, I pull up at the function and I've got hella nerds on me.
I forgot that they exist outside of Halloween.
Nerds?
Yeah.
I thought that like nerds...
I think most people, to most people, candy does not exist outside of Halloween.
Yeah.
But I thought nerds were like a Halloween, like in my head, it's like that is a Halloween
specific candy.
You can only get that at a certain time of year, like the Reese's egg.
Like the Reese's pumpkin.
Yeah, or the pumpkin or the Christmas tree.
For other things, egg is for Halloween.
In a way, a pumpkin's an egg.
And Avi Positor, bringing us back to the Xenomorph conversation.
Let's go back to Xenomorphs.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
I was liking this where we were going.
If you got a face hugger on your face, right, and you knew there was an alien inside of your
body, what would you do?
Give birth.
Yeah, I remember.
Capitulate.
What would you do before the thing pops out of your head?
I'd be eating pickles and ice cream for real.
So you're saying if-
I'd be having those cravings.
Yeah.
You're saying, like, what would I do if it was like that movie Bucket List or some shit,
but-
- A bucket list, but there's a Xenom work inside you
at any point in time. - At any point in time,
if something's gonna jump out of my belly.
One hour?
- Yeah, 'cause that's what it--
- Probably watch about an hour of Avatar.
- Yeah, all right, makes sense.
It's like in--
- No, I would drink bleach or something.
- Yeah, or Pepsi.
- I bet it hates Pepsi.
Oh, true, 'cause Coke will dissolve a penny.
So that guy's probably made out of something like pennies.
- He's made out of plastic.
- He's made out of pennies.
- His blood is acid, though, that's the problem.
so I need the opposite of acid.
Oh, what's that movie?
- Base.
- Yeah.
- You need a base.
- Yeah, I need head and shoulders.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, what's that movie called?
With David Duchovny.
- Evolution?
- Evolution.
- The X-Files movie?
- Remember that?
- That's the only, I never seen it.
I was guessing.
- At the end of Evolution,
it's like the worst product placement ever.
They're like, how do we defeat the aliens?
And they're like, we have to use head and shoulders shampoo
and spray it all over the earth.
So that's what they do.
- Yeah.
That's cool.
That is kind of a cool plot device, I think.
You're a girl.
Yeah.
You like shampoo.
You are blue.
Whoa.
You like shampoo.
Would you say that you're good, yeah, you're feeling all right,
and baby, you're going to have the best freaking night
of my life?
Yeah.
I would also say dabba-dee.
No.
Dabba-die.
That's not an avatar Navi slang word.
What color is your girlfriend?
My girlfriend?
Well, if we're talking about my human girlfriend,
that's one thing.
Well, what is her emotion?
I'm looking I'm on the market for a Navi mate.
Not a girlfriend. A mate.
They don't have...
Do you wait so I've seen the movie.
And I'm...
What color is your hair?
If you're watching this, Neytiri, I know you seem pretty happy with Jake Sully, but take a chance on a guy like me.
Why do they not have nipples?
I don't know, but it's mostly so they can show their boobs the whole movie.
- What if the blue-- - It's so crazy,
they do a thousand boob shots of every Navi
a thousand times in life hack.
- What if the blue skin is actually shirt material?
- Shirt material, what do you mean?
- What if they have shirt material for clothes?
- You mean fabric? - Or for skin?
- Shirt material for clothes.
- Shirt material for skin.
- Right.
- So you're saying, what if that's not their skin,
what if they have clothes on?
- Yeah, what if that whole blue thing is clothes?
- What would be underneath it?
- Fucking another shirt.
It kind of is Jake Sully's clothes because he's an actual got no legs guy.
Yes. And he's inside of that muscle. A wheelchair. And how did they... He's a wheelchair. How did they grow
his blue man? In a tank. So basically his brother was a scientist and... Hats off to
him. Yes and shoes off for Jake Sully because he has no use for them. Nope.
His brother was a genius and they created an avatar, a Na'vi avatar for him.
- Oh.
- And then his brother died for some reason
that I can't remember.
- They don't even say.
- I can't remember.
- Blast it.
- And they actually let Jake Sully, despite his form,
into the Avatar program and he was also, he's stupid.
- So even with his mangled body and useless brain,
they still let him into the program.
- He's like an empty shell.
- Okay.
- And they let him be blue.
- Wow.
- It's actually an inspiring story.
and he gets so happy that he can walk that he runs around.
- So even if you're-- - And he plays basketball.
- He does, and he jumps over a garden.
- And I've seen up to that part of the movie.
- You should keep going because after that,
actually what happens is they have--
- Oh, they go down a waterfall.
- They go to an alien, they're on an alien world.
- I will say that's a bit of an oversight
by the people in charge of the program
that they would think that that guy
wouldn't wanna stay in Avatar
and marry all those people and chill with them.
It's like, he has no fucking legs.
It's so funny, the whole thing is he's like,
because he was a Marine before his legs got mistaked,
he's working with the Marines who wanna,
they hate the scientists,
and he's reporting to the lead Marine guy.
- It's a jock versus nerd movie.
- And they keep being like--
- That's the whole--
- The movie literally is jocks versus nerds
versus blue aliens.
- Yeah, it is.
- And he keeps reporting the Marines,
and the Marine guy's like,
"We're gonna blow up the whole tree."
And Jake Sully's like,
"No, I need more time to figure out how to blow up the tree."
And the guy's like, "Okay."
(laughing)
- Man.
- And there's just three hours of that.
- That's so funny.
- It's so sick, dude.
- I'm gonna have to do a rewatch now.
- It's really good.
- Maybe I'll show up next episode.
- I did, I, dude.
- Full blue.
- Oh my God, all three of us in our avatar forms?
- Little bit.
- I'd be the Marine.
- No you wouldn't.
- You would not be the Marine.
- I'd be a Marine.
- No, you wouldn't.
- You'd be stuck on Earth.
They would not send you to Pandora.
- I would never, ever, ever.
ever betray the USA. I would be probably if they had a real-life Pandora program
I would probably be the first guy they sent over there. No, because of your
knowledge. Because of my knowledge about Pandora. I don't think you're the number
one Avatar fan. Okay, let's ask him some trivia about Avatar.
All right, I got this. What color is the Na'vi's skin? Blue and some different
shades of blue at times. What color is the Na'vi's hair? Dark.
- God.
- What is the name of the Na'vi's race?
- Race.
- Na'vi.
- God, he's good.
Where on Earth do the humans live?
- The continents.
- Damn, he's fucking good.
In the second one, which biome do they go into?
- The Way of Water.
- Fucking shit.
In the first one, what is it a,
is the first avatar, would you say it's more of a
television show or a film television film. We almost got him there. Okay. What is
the color of the Navi's feet?
Blue.
I don't know that one. I actually don't know that one. Why don't, why don't
- Why don't the Navi show their bits and pieces?
- They do.
I truly cannot stress this enough, guys.
If you, they showed, Navi's entire naked body
is literally hundreds of times.
- But they don't have holes.
- But that's 'cause their holes are their hair.
They show that a ton too.
- But why even give Zoe Saldana perfect buxom bust?
- Because you get to look at it the whole time.
If she had nipples there, they wouldn't show it to you.
They show it to you literally 10,000 times.
James Cameron, I'm thinking, this is so crazy.
James Cameron, with how much he's thought about Navi and shit
and how much he's spent designing this
and animating it and all this shit,
he's definitely, probably, honestly,
in the hundreds of times, masturbated thinking about Navi.
Yeah.
Of course, no, right?
He's definitely had sex with his wife
and been like, "I wish she was blue."
He's definitely put on an Oculus headset
and had an entire three-dimensional realm
that he went into.
- It's a movie about a guy going into a virtual world
where he can fuck a blue alien.
- You're 100% right.
- That's literally what it's about.
- He developed all this technology so that he can--
- Is he becoming a blue alien
so he can fuck another blue alien?
- Man, but he's definitely also gotten
custom designs sent to him.
- Oh yeah.
- Had people sign NDAs. - Well, they made
a Na'vi fleshlight.
- Not, he didn't make one.
- He designed it.
- Really? - Yeah.
- Wait, isn't it, isn't that you have pussy hair?
There's no hair on it, but you can glue it if you have glue.
- That's true, I guess the Navi fleshlight
should be like a long braid that you stick your dick in.
Well that's this fucked up part about the Navi hair
is you're like, oh, the hair is like their dick or whatever.
And they're like, okay, that's kind of gross and weird,
but whatever, I can handle it, I guess.
And then they do so many close-ups where it's like
a Navi is like holding the hair in their hand,
and it's like, first of all, it's a close-up of them
holding the hair in their hand.
and it's like close up and there's little like
flesh tendrils inside it that are going like this
and then they touch it to a horse's, a horse's.
- What?
I don't remember this.
- And then they ride the horse around.
- They got motherfucking horses?
- That's how they ride animals.
When they have horses and the banshees that they fly,
they connect their hair to the animal's hair
and they go like, ah.
And then they like fly.
They just literally are fucking the animals.
- They try to like, they try to say that it's kind of
just like a universal tool that they use.
- It's like USB-C.
- Yeah, and it's like at first you're like, oh, okay.
- Power and data.
- That's literally what it is.
- Oh, this is USB-C that we use with our horses
and our birds and stuff.
And then they have this scene where Nateeri and Jake
are under the tree and they're like, oh.
- Yeah.
- And they're touching there and you're like, oh.
- Man.
- James Cameron loves to put in a scene
where the two people are,
two people who just met just immediately start fucking.
- I will say that scene,
Okay, they also didn't just meet so yeah fake avatar fan. They don't really
Avatar, but I know they were completely in love by that fuck
I know the term and also that scene was hot as fuck and I was beat red in the IMAX theater you
It's hard to get beat red through this exactly you would not be able to I looked purple
Yeah, what if you were listen if you were Navi right and you had a Navi
Boyfriend girlfriend situation or boyfriend only for some people in the look up a sneaky link a sneaky link
If you had a sneaky ass link with a Navi...
That's also my Navi's name.
Listen...
Her name is Sneaky Link.
I'm on the Navi DL.
Are you...
Here's a question.
There's nothing DL about this.
Are you...
You're trying to sneak around?
Sneaking out of the house.
Hey, I gotta go to the...
Are you trying to go to the movies?
I have to go to Pinto...
The gym.
I get my steps in. Do you are you here's a big question though. Yeah. Are you pitching you catch it? Oh, oh
I don't know. There's such a thing. Hey, hey a hair is a hair
It's a hair. That's what I said
That's right a hair is a hair cuz if catching hurts as much as it does in real life
Then I'm not doing that but it does sound kind of fun. I
Wonder how it feels probably hurts really bad like in real life. I wonder if they squirt you don't oh, that's a good one
Na'vi squirt. Yeah, they can. They squirt. They completely squirt. Do their hair squirts?
My hair squirts. If I run. Do you think that if we introduce hip hop to the Na'vi that
they'd be music videos or they'd shake their hair? That's what the third one's gonna be.
Like that? The third one is called The Pillars. No. Could be introduced to the song Cherry
Pie. Pillars. Hip hop rappers are pillars because they keep dying from fucking pills.
- That's true. - What'd you say?
- Could introduce cherry pie by Warrant.
- Hairy guy.
♪ She's my hairy guy ♪
♪ See my hair in her ♪ - ♪ Blue skin and stuff ♪
♪ With that hair ♪
- No, it's kinda rotten.
- No. - It's not gonna be a song.
- Look, I'm trying my best. - Fucking asshole.
- Just steamrolled my thing
where I was gonna say-- - ♪ She's my hairy guy ♪
♪ Blue skin and hair ♪
♪ Until I die ♪
- Uh-huh. - That's good.
- Or I get taken out of the Avatar program.
♪ She's my hairy guy ♪
- That's pretty good. - Yeah, that's good.
- I really like how that sounds.
- If we introduce rock to the Na'vi,
there's gonna be all sorts of fucking awesome songs.
- There is a giant rock on Pandora.
- There is the climate.
- They float, the rocks float on Pandora.
- Dude, oh my God, I just realized something, bro.
Imagine you're riding that Banshee, right?
And you turn that music up, "Fortunate Son."
- The Banshee's shaking.
You have an old Banshee and the wings are going like,
burn, burn, burn.
I would love 50 inch so my all the all the all the quarters in my banshees cup
holder are rattling around yeah we that's the other thing man if I was if
they were like guys Pandora's 100% real we're bringing people over I'm
volunteering not to be a Navi but to go be a mass murderer because they don't
matter because they're blue yeah that's I'd be I'd be I'd go over there to learn
how to do audio installations on the Banshee.
- You would not be putting tweeters.
- I'd be putting tweeters on.
- You would not be putting--
- I'd be putting those things,
those like the whistles on the exhaust.
- You would not be putting tweeters on a Banshee.
You would not be--
- That's the--
- You can't roll coal with a Banshee, motherfucker.
- That's the Navi version of, you know when you get,
when you have like a Bluetooth speaker and you connect it
and it says in like a Chinese accent,
it says Bluetooth connected.
That's for the Navi.
They connect their phone to their Banshee
and it's Patrick's voice.
Yeah.
That's the equivalent.
Your Bluetooth device is connected.
Like they're laughing at the accent.
Yeah.
I bought this Bluetooth speaker and I turned it on and
it made like, it went like, do do do do.
And then it played that fucking, you know that when you get like the phone call in
GTA 5?
No, make it worse.
Did, did Nico pick up?
It does that until you connect.
Did the cousin pick up?
No.
I saw a Bluetooth speaker.
But I think if I leave it on, it'll probably do that.
I saw a Bluetooth speaker for $4 at a store.
Yeah.
I was curious about it.
There's a store that's closing in my neighborhood.
I had another fucking weird dream, man.
I'm so sorry.
$10.
I had another weird, weird dream.
It sucks.
It sucks really bad.
I had a dream.
What's the name of the bald guy from GTA V?
Trevor.
I had a dream that I was in a movie with Trevor.
He was also in Better Call Saul.
But in the act, yeah, he wasn't in Better Call Saul.
I've been watching Better Call Saul.
I got to finish the sixth season.
Do not.
You're gonna show up fully Mexican next week, then.
What?
You can show up fully Mexican like this.
They have Navi.
You can show up as Nacho.
They don't have Navi in the fuck, all right, asshole.
Trevor was in my movie, Dream,
and we were acting alongside each other,
and the director said,
"How about you walk like Trevor for a minute?"
And then he walked around,
and he looked just like the video game.
Yeah.
Oh.
Pretty badass, Dream.
Way better.
So you weren't a movie set.
No te te, though.
You weren't like a movie.
No, no, I was an actor.
Yeah.
actor I had done a Willy Wonka relaunch in the mood in the you were Augustus
gloop fuck no I'm always an aglostic gloop would just Augustus I got a lot of
water in my mouth because that energy drink it's been stimulating my nerves in
my mouth is the top of your head tingling the top of my head is always
tingling I know hair there you see that there's that like non-binary like
defense person who got arrested for stealing luggage at the airport. Yeah I
don't have any thoughts on that. Yeah you can go ahead and say your thoughts. I guess you know
what I have no thoughts that start like this person be like this like I got
nothing like that. I don't have anything. I was just gonna say that's pretty funny
crime. Stealing luggage. Stealing luggage really funny crime. I feel like I always
funny I guess yeah what are you hoping to get like yeah I could I'm either
getting I'm getting somebody's musty sweaty clothes or I'm getting a snow
globe. Well I saw a picture of that person. The thing is the way they got caught definitely was that they
picked up a briefcase and a police officer was like there's no way that's
that person. That person does not work like that. You know what sucks is I forgot we're
backlogging so this is gonna be like. Oh if we're talking. It's not gonna be relevant. If we're just talking about news that
happened that's interesting. Okay. Today bro or maybe yesterday four chimpanzees
Shot today I saw this where escaped is in escape didn't even escape from the zoo escape from their enclosure
And they were fucking gun. They were yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, where was it was it what country was it in?
Some European bullshit. I was in Europe. I feel the Louvre a curse. Um shit. Yeah, it's something like that
Yeah
But whatever yeah, yeah, they were shot
Because they said they ran out of tranquilizer darts. They did not run out of train. Oh, bro. I also see banana
If we're talking about animal news, let's do some animal news.
All right.
Directly to camera.
I wish we had a graphic to camera.
So there was an aquarium in Germany.
Did you guys see this?
I saw this too.
It's 50--
Animal news.
They're trying to escape.
Did you see this?
I guess I'm the audience for the animal news.
In Germany, it was in a hotel.
It was a cylindrical aquarium 15 meters tall.
A million gallons of water.
And it exploded.
A million gallons.
and two were injured, but all the fish were okay.
(laughing)
- Wow.
- Yeah, it's a miracle.
They just started flipping and flopping.
- Yeah, they went into the bathtub of somebody's hotel room.
- They all ran into the, they all fell into the toilets.
- They ran, they ran outside and they ran into the ocean.
- Yep.
- And they were completely fine.
- It was all a happy ending.
- But apparently it was the biggest aquarium cylindrical.
- Wow.
- It honestly did make me, I was like, okay, great.
- I'm never going to an aquarium again.
- Yeah, that's another fear I had to have.
- That's crazy.
that they can explode yeah I thought that you could shoot a bullet in the bullet
would jump back into your head I did not know that that could chatter I wonder
sure if the aquarium breaks right like the glass in the aquarium breaks you're
fine you know how much time I've been you're fine do you know how much shark
fault like a shark it's not there's no water it's not that you think that we're
scared of an aquarium exploding because a shark is gonna eat a little bit I am
scared of that yeah I know he's afraid I know that's what it's shards of glass
- The glass being launched with a tidal wave.
- I don't care about the glass.
- Why is the shark what you hoped?
- Well, 'cause think about how--
- The sharks are scarier than glass.
- Think about the entire point of an aquarium
is to sit and look directly at the shark and go.
- That's true, and follow it.
- Yeah, well, no, that's what I do.
- Put slices of bread on either side of me.
(laughing)
- You can't get me.
- I'm dangling on a giant hook, swinging back and forth.
- You're just like looking back at the shark like, ooh.
(laughing)
- Paint my ass red.
- Yeah. - Like a baboon,
just like spanking it. - Pachum over my body.
- I bet you want this so bad.
- You will never get this, you will never get this.
(laughing)
Yeah, but then if the aquarium fucking breaks,
what if the shark, what if we walk out and we're like,
oh well, thank God we escaped the aquarium and all the water
and you say, Caleb, there's a shark on your fucking head.
- Dude, do you know what's so funny?
When you're saying that, so you're trapped in an aquarium,
the shark tank broke, there's water on the floor,
there's a shark swimming around, it's trying to get you,
and you have to get out.
That would be an incredible movie, right?
- That would be.
- And I was thinking about, that would be such a good movie.
And you know how stupid horror movie makers are?
- They've already done it.
- No, I was thinking they should make a movie like that.
And I realized, there is a movie like that,
but it's not set in an aquarium,
it's set in a grocery store.
- What movie?
- Why did they make a grocery store?
- Wait, what is it?
- It's called Bait.
- Oh man, yeah, why would you not make an aquarium one?
Aquarium is the most obvious place
to set any kind of fish thing.
- I watched that movie so long ago.
- Is that the one with the crocodile?
- No, it's with a shark.
- That's called Basement or some shit.
- Crawl.
- Bait is Australian and it's in a grocery store
and there's a flood.
It's the same as Crawl, but in a grocery store.
- Huh?
- They eat sharks down there.
- That's true.
- This shark eats them.
- Australians, they all eat sharks.
- But how stupid are Australians to think
we're gonna make a movie where a shark gets into a place
and it's not an aquarium.
You know what, I saw this has nothing to do,
this actually kind of has something to do with sharks.
It has a lot to do with sharks.
I almost bought shark jerky.
- No, that can't be legal.
That can't be legal, man.
- I almost bought it, it was at a mall in New Jersey.
I almost bought it, but it was like 20 bucks.
- Oh, you went to an exotic jerky store?
- Yeah, there's an exotic jerky store
in the American Dream Mall.
- There's one in--
- It's right next to the Nickelodeon Universe.
- There's one in Morro Bay, California.
I think I had a snake jerky there.
- They had all these different jerkies.
- I had beef jerky.
- And a guy was offering samples.
- True, beef is in a completely other place.
Do you think a shark bite might operate
kind of like a sniper wound where it doesn't really,
like until you notice it, it's like not a big deal.
- I think so, 'cause you go in,
I genuinely think you go into shock when you get bit by a shark.
- Yeah, so you could go for a while
with a shark flipping around
and everybody who you look at is horrified.
They're going, "Ah!"
They're covering their kid's eyes.
But as long as you don't notice, you're fine.
Yeah, you're good.
Yeah.
You good.
I think that's most things.
Huh?
Most things.
If you don't notice it--
Shark bites and snipers.
What about a beast thing?
A beast?
A beast thing?
A beast thing eating you.
I heard apparently that it's very dangerous.
I guess there's these things called killer beasts that
can sting you.
Yes.
It's very scary.
I can't believe that--
I mean, I feel like this would be bigger news.
Can I ask an honest question?
No.
- What the fuck makes a bee Africanized?
- I think it's--
- What the fuck is that?
Why, who--
- Thank God you got two experts in the room.
- I think what it is, I think it's a type of bee
that they, like an invasive, like I think
they brought a species from Africa.
- But that's just an African bee,
what makes it Africanized?
- Yeah.
- Somebody put some lever that one half was off
and the other half was Africa and they turn it on?
- I think maybe they breed them.
I think it's like a type of bee that they like mix,
They crossbreed it.
- You think they got that good honey though?
- No. - No, they don't have,
it's like a wasp.
- What the mother fuck happened to murder hornets?
I thought these were gonna be cray.
- Talk on that.
Yeah, and you know they said that there was--
- Oh, there's one.
There's one right there.
- There was a bug flying.
- Really?
- Yeah, we both saw it.
You're blind.
- Oh my God.
Wait, you were so ready.
- Am I closing my eyes or no?
- I can't even tell. - I can't even tell.
- Completely blind.
have an amazing auditory. Yeah I thought that I thought that murder hornets are
gonna be just as big as friggin Carole Baskin and yeah and Karen's. Karen's.
Whatever happened to Karen's? We still have Karen's around. Whatever happened to those?
We still have Karen's. You know the ultimate. What happened to them? The ultimate
imagine if Carole Baskin was a Karen. She is dude no need to imagine. They passed a
law. You're still doing this? They passed a law that bans the it's like going or I don't
remember exactly what it was. I wish that you were like late night Johnny Carson
telling that story. They passed a law. No no you come over to the couch, Patrick why don't you
come over here. You sit down you say they passed a law and I don't really remember
what it is. I guess they're finally cracking down on like people owning like tigers and
shit. Oh okay that's probably good. Yeah it's for the best but like. Unless you're a
I fucking hey they can do whatever they want as long as they don't take my banshee
That's right, and I hear they shut down if they come for alligators. They shut down alligator adventure
I will literally I will be so fine if people start protesting alligator adventure
I will do protests. I will drive a van through the crowd. I fucking I will do this
Just let the alligators out when people protest
Pussies cry yeah, Oh
Alligators aren't even they don't they aren't dangerous like that man. Yeah, they don't bite. No they don't have teeth
You know what I didn't like it
I didn't like about the the the crocodiles that we did see the crocodiles and the alligators what I?
Just did this to come for you because you said you didn't like something. I just like this nice moment, okay
You play six pence none the richer
Put play that six pence
- Zoom in. - No.
- It's kind of a stupid name. - None the Richer.
- None the Richer.
- Yeah, but it's kind of like--
- I'm None the Richer. - Doing all the heavy lifting
in that name.
- But I thought that the whole point was like,
oh yeah, it's Sixpence None the Richer
because even if we had Sixpence, we wouldn't really care
'cause it would be None the Richer because--
- But the thing I didn't like,
you guys playing, what was that game?
- Finger Hold. - No, the--
- Don't try to snivel out of this.
You did it.
- Your hand is so sweaty. - Look at his--
- That was so easy. - Look at his red tip.
look at his red hand. It's not sweaty at all. It's oil.
And I think it's because he let go. I was trying to show off how good your grip
was and you sabotaged it. I do have awful grip strength. Yeah, really?
Yeah. Oh, but the alligators had their mouths open and they would sit there and
just go. Yeah, that's how they release heat, I think. Yeah.
That's weird. I think that's like their version of sweating. It's like a dog panting, I think.
And you couldn't see a hole. Oh, yeah, that is weird.
Yeah, I agree with that being weird.
They'd had no hole in their mouth.
I wish alligators had a hole.
They do have a hole.
I do think that eating...
I wish alligators had hair.
I want to put something in there.
I'm covering my mouth so he doesn't see me saying this.
We had alligator in Texas.
We had alligator.
And it's good.
It tasted like food.
Yeah, but I do think now,
after different connections that I've had with alligators,
connections that I've had with alligators, I do think that it is immoral to eat an alligator.
I think it's more immoral to eat an alligator. I think you can tell that it's immoral to eat
an alligator if you watch a video of someone preparing an alligator. When they leave the
head skin on. When they inflate it to get the skin off, do you know what I'm talking
about? Yeah, it's awful, dude. It's crazy. We watched that video of the guy making a
turtle soup, right? Yeah. Yeah, I don't like that video much. Turtles, uh... Yeah, you
ever saw Cannibal Holocaust? Turtles are good. Built-in bowl, they make sense for a special
I think I've seen the scene from Cannibal Holocaust. Yeah full movie, but they just go to town on a turtle
Yeah, they just take his shell off, and they're just that's just his gut I just yeah
It's really gross you know like they also they kill some
You know yeah like this yeah, just remembering that in my brain just I went I
Was like this have you guys ever seen that super smash brothers video wombo combo? Oh my god that a falco
Yeah, that is a funny ass fucking video. I don't know
Yeah, I would love to see them do to falco what they did to that turtle you guys ever seen will it blend. Yes
He puts a PlayStation
What was the one with the microwave do you guys watch the one?
Is it a good idea to microwave this with Jordan? Yes?
That was a fucking microwave the microwave. Do you remember the one where they did the airbag and it blew up?
Have you guys seen too many cooks? That's the same. Yeah, I think about it and I'm ready to dry comedy level
100,000 million is it a good idea to microwave this they stopped that - I'm the Navi adult swim fan
Wow have you guys seen unedited footage of a bear? Yeah, it's fire. I love that. He likes the bumpers this guy's a bug
I'm mostly a bumper. It's a bumper
Big bumpers guy. Yeah, I like them a fully Navi comedy show
Good at my work. That is a good idea. Yeah, what time are we at?
Time for you to get a watch. Yep pound that out. I guess we have a stopwatch and we never did it
Well, the remote is lost. Thanks to you. Oh
Is it thanks to me or is it? Yeah, it's your it's Patrick's fault moving all this stuff
No, you toys are you you put it somewhere less you put it somewhere fucking you said I'm moving this and you put it somewhere
somewhere fucking weird. I did not do that. You did. You literally did. When you were
cleaning off the table last night. I don't remember that. I mean it's not a big deal
but it was your fault. It's probably over here. I just saw a bug on the ground. Oh no.
Oh not a bug. We got bugs now. Patrick it wasn't your fault I was lying. I know you
were lying. No you weren't. It was your fault. Who do you believe? I believe nobody. Oh well
can't believe nobody we're saying up that is an extra nobody but but but he's
making the plasma ball go back back with audio because you can't see it at all
yeah we're over an hour but I'm having fun yeah keep going for a minute okay
avatar - I enough your food tie-in is there a fast food tie-in with oh yeah
yeah what is there I would the only times that there's a makeup palette tie-in and
and there's a The Weeknd song
where he puts Navi chanting into it.
- Wait, The Weeknd did a--
- He's in the movie.
- He did a song for--
- Did a Worth It for Avatar?
- Yeah.
- Damn.
- Can we, is there a Fazlutayan?
I really--
- I don't know, I was just thinking
about a Taco Bell blue taco.
- Oh my God.
Bro.
- I was thinking about an IHOP blue waffle.
- Okay, don't say that shit.
Don't say that motherfucking shit to me.
- Man.
- Avatar food.
I'll just search avatar food.
That was definitely done, right?
Somebody fucking, somebody tried to make it look like
there was a blue waffle in promotion for Avatar.
Oh, well they have it at the,
they have it at Disney World or whatever.
Yeah, but that's different.
Yeah, I know.
That's a different area.
Disney released this new blue menu at Animal Kingdom.
What's on it?
It's just all blue animals.
It's just a blue menu.
Blue J.
It's the same food, but the menu's blue.
It's just like Blue J Burger.
Yeah.
(laughing)
- There's not a lot of blue mammals.
- Discover healthful dishes and familiar flavors
from another world.
Wholesome grains, fresh vegetables, and hearty proteins.
Featuring international inspired cuisine.
- Interworldly almost.
Interstellar. - International inspired
cuisine is so funny to say.
- I'm just looking at a--
- Just inspired by food.
- We got a text from Alex.
Just wanna show, maybe you can see this.
- Blue noodles!
- You can punch in on that.
- They have blue noodles?
know if you can't is Jubio even there yeah you can't read that man you can't
read it well it's a photo Alex just sent all of us that says you may never meet
your Holly if you never move past your chin oh and it's got Michael Scott I
think I'm on my Jan right now I think I gotta get a Holly all right bye guys bye
Avatar Nutrition. Happy New Year! Oh yeah it's happy 10 9 8 7 6 5 4 3 2 1
Happy New Year! So if you watch this at 11 p.m.
Yep okay bye