(upbeat music)
- Wow.
- Are you gonna include that clap in the thing?
I really hope not.
- We're back from our break.
- 'Cause I fucked it up.
- You didn't fuck it up, you did it fine.
- I said, podclabalabalabalist.
- Yeah, but the words don't matter at all.
- It doesn't matter what is said.
- Tell that to fucking every,
tell that to the Slater's union.
- That's correct.
- Oh, the words don't matter.
Actually, they would probably like that,
'cause they like to sit, it's a union,
they like to sit around and get a paycheck.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Fuck 'em, get an insurance.
- It really doesn't matter.
They just wanna,
they wanna be forced to do more work
so they can complain.
- They can complain more, yeah.
- Oh, I had to work a full work week.
- Oh no, I'm in a union.
- They fed me all this free food all day.
- I had to sit around,
I had to sit with a pickup truck where the bed was down.
I had to sit there and eat a sandwich.
- And I got to meet a celebrity.
- Yeah, they're in a union, an unholy union.
that sex with us incubus and succubus at the same time
what the union people and holy union
three so there are some people working union on that show probably not fuck no
it and only union you remember that that was a well as a punk rocker show they're
not going to use and i think i can
you know i am i think we should be using union now i'm not what i said would be
like that and that's a little bit you need to remember that you know
no course not it was the show it was a a six part series
uh... was it about him getting married? Yeah, Bam getting married to Missy Rothstein.
I don't know who that is. His wife.
Oh, that makes sense.
His ex-wife. That makes sense, that's who he was getting married to.
She did a Playboy shoot, Missy Rothstein, on the show.
If we were in the podcaster union, they'd make us fucking wear hard hats right now.
I wish I had a hard hat. We'd have to be clipped into this wall. And they would only let us do five minute episodes.
You have to do five minutes of talking and then take 55 minutes of break.
Wouldn't you guys hate that?
You have to take a 55 minutes smokers break
because you're in the union.
Five minutes of podcasting, medium hard,
and then 55 minutes just sitting around.
Oh, it's so hard to work.
Oh, working is so hard.
I should have a raise.
You know what? Let's cut out that five minutes
and stop working entirely
for an entire month.
And let's shut down all the trains
cash registers there's a cash register there's a cash register on the pod there's
a cash right over there we should get a square reader so we can steal your money
charge I would just I would do other for stuff we just use Apple request on the
iPhone no no no no no it has to be because then we can also tip each other
yeah you can tip me I'm a cash only business no no no no you're out of this
plan yeah you know we're gonna use a square reader between the cameras are
gonna get two square readers each and then you get lunch with your friends
everyone's like alright so who should I Venmo you're like oh we have one of the
like fucked up old ones where it's yeah it attaches to like one of the audio yeah
yeah yeah click okay yeah okay and that's gonna charge you that's gonna
charge you. Why do they always do that? It's gonna ask you for a tip and then they look away. It softens the blow when they click no.
And there's a 12% convenience fee because it does have that goes through the
square so you're gonna have to pay a little more. Yeah, you're just taxing your
friends for no reason. I would do that to you guys. I don't like you that much. Well you just said you
wouldn't. I just decided. Don't even say that as a joke. I don't like you guys
that much. Don't even say it as a joke. That is the rudest thing you've ever said.
That felt really fucking bad coming out of my little mouth. Yeah, I bet it did.
Oh, I want to look cool to everyone who's watching. Alright guys, I admit it. Give me
this camera. Punch in on him. I was just trying to look cool. I really do care about
these two guys. They're some of my closest friends and it's a pleasure to
work with them. So I'm sorry that I tried to look cool. Yeah, try to look cool to
some some fucker we don't even know yeah there was a guy with more hair than you
I was imagine seeing that that's also rude now now you have to do an apology
oh I have more hair than Caleb yeah now and that's an eye line across my forehead
that's an iron hair wearing this hat oh my god
that hat you high or down on your head yep doesn't give me hives it just gives
me you might be allergic to right through all over this yes you did and then you
got it back at that I remember at that place at that place that we were on New
Year's Day I saw fire that reached to the sky and then a day or two ago I
suffocated in my sleep three times are you okay I don't know are you where you
got bad to say so how was your new year yeah mine is okay yeah mine's pretty
uneventful I don't have really anything to say about that we say suffocated isn't
suffocated like electrocuted like it's you die from it yeah yeah I what do you
mean you suffocated three times I don't believe my sleep I don't believe that
one was in the middle of the night one was also in the middle that and the
other one was in the morning how do you suffocate three times in your sleep and
know about it I was dreaming it oh so you dreamed that you suffocated yeah but
I woke up and I was suffocating on what my throat I've like acid reflux no I have
sleep apnea how did you have sleep apnea cuz you're skinny mini yes that's why
that's the dangerous kind the skinny mini yeah really you know I just made that up
Oh
I told Patrick yesterday I told Patrick yesterday
You got so mad. You got so mad that I was like I don't need one.
Because you're a fucking idiot. I'm not an idiot. You're gonna die in your sleep.
I'm not gonna die in my sleep I'm gonna die doing something way stupider.
stupider sleeping no there's nothing stupid and dying in your sleep that's
not true bitch-ass way to go out there's not a bitch bitch-ass way no cuz you're
probably having a dream that you got stabbed or something and then you die in
real life prove that okay you can't prove that all right that somebody was
happy you can't prove that when somebody dies in their sleep I'll fall asleep
right now you will not try to die no you won't and you won't like when I die
I've had plenty of dreams where I thought I was falling or I thought I was
that
That is a crazy fire.
Is that an omen if you see that on New Year's Day?
Here, I'll play it again.
Is that...
Wait, it won't...
Let's see here.
Is this an omen?
Put it behind Juvia so it looks like
Wizard of Oz.
Oh wow, whoa.
I don't even...
It's too hard.
Wizard of Oz vibe.
But do you think that's an omen to see a fire
there is just a skylights one of those things where it's like if a bird shits
on you it's good luck
there was ash falling from the first shits on you it's good luck and that's a
thing that that's like no no so whoever came up with that came up with that
because the right your bird shit on your head is a are you know a lot yeah
no that's why you have a lot of that's like when a parent tells the kid that
the ice cream truck plays music when it's only out of ice cream
they're like when i get a really cool i got shit on by a bird
no you know actually that's good what actually really actually do that we're
going to get ice cream. I think that seeing a bunch of burning trees at the beginning of
the new year is actually good luck. Yeah, if you're Bob Marley. Yeah. Yeah, the firefighters
didn't even care. They probably didn't. Okay, so I walked out of... You know arson, most
arsons are done by a firefighter. Is that true? Yeah. Well, listen to this. Firefighters...
They get all horny when they see a fire. A lot of times you'll walk by a fire or something
and you think a firefighter is like... A lot of times. Oh, we're battling a fire. Yeah,
I walk by a fire often. Three or four or five times in my life I've walked by a fire where
there was firefighters there.
And you always think it's gonna be like a--
- Have you walked by, well, when you like walk by a fire
and there's no firefighters there?
- Well, that's never happened to me.
But when you walk by a fire,
you expect it to be like a painting
of the Revolutionary War,
and they're like charging in or whatever.
A lot of these firefighters are in a union.
- They don't care. - They're standing there.
- They're standing up there,
they're using the fire to light
their fucking marijuana cigarette.
- I even took a video of them not,
I tried, I was like, okay,
so the fire was going for a while.
- Yeah, I can imagine. - And then the fire truck came,
a bunch of fire trucks came and I was like, "Oh, I want to take a video of these firefighters
putting out the fire." And this video is like a few minutes long and they just walk around.
They just wait for the fire to get small.
Dude, that's the crazy thing about firefighters. They're like, "Oh yeah, well the best course
of action is we got to let it burn down a while before we can fight." It's like, how
fucking convenient is that for you? Like, "Oh, you have to wait two or three hours and
sit around."
Yeah.
And also-
They blocked my view.
an EMS worker run? No. Fuck no dude. They pull up, your grandma's having a heart attack,
they're like checking their Apple watch for their steps as they come up your fucking stairs.
They got that Pokemon Go thing, like the Pokeball that you can click and then it catches the
Pokemon for you. EMS workers have to be bottom of the barrel, right? Because they're all trying
to get into nursing school. They're 19. Well I think they're the people that get out of
nursing school. I think they're the like, "Ah shit, I became a nurse, but now I want
to be a thrill seeker. Yeah, I think it's the nursing school people, but then there's also
there's a subset of people who are just like, "I'm just going to do something crazy." It's
like the lamer version of being like, "I'm going to go join the army because I don't know
what to do." The army's cool, man. That's why I said the EMS is the lamer version of
joining the army for no reason. My uncle was an Air Force medic in Afghanistan. He did the
combination the you're a little plane no I didn't he flew an ambulance he was just
a he didn't even learn out of both of my uncles are in the Air Force neither of
them know how to fly a fucking plane well next time you see him tell him to suck
my balls mm-hmm I will okay I'll say suck Caleb's balls and they'll say what
no they know yeah they know who I am they know and they've seen my balls
before yeah see you hear that uncle Bobby and uncle Paul you never use your
- Are your balls like a scrub daddy
to get stuff out of your fingernails?
- No. - Nope.
- Me neither.
- Wait, how?
- You just like, 'cause it's kinda putty,
you kinda like slide it in there.
- What, your balls? - How big is the space
in your fingernails?
- No, no, my balls are just really like putty-ish.
- They get really thin?
- At the ends, yeah.
At the ends of the sharp-- - Like a bristle?
- Corners.
Yeah, in a way, yeah.
- Bristle? - I mean, I don't know.
- You got like a brillo pad down there?
- No, no, no, no, no, it's like a--
- It's covered in glue soap.
- How do I explain this?
It's really like... You can just show us.
I guess I could. I've showed you guys my balls before.
Oh, I've seen your balls many times.
And you said, "Those are huge."
Yeah.
I remember that.
That was a little feather in my cap compliment.
That was like when an old lady cat cheers
because you're handsome.
They were...
They looked big and like you had a tumor on them.
You're backpedaling.
It was like I was concerned.
He's backpedaling.
Yeah.
No, you were embarrassed.
You were embarrassed.
He said oh my god Becky look at that. Look at those. Yeah, that's what you were saying Patrick. Do you know dof?
I mean bofa
Dofa I mean bofa
Do if I mean bofa you ever heard yeah, I mean fucking job of the hood over here. I mean both all fought me bofa
Oh, oh, oh
What was this?
It's not gonna work on us this time. You're not getting you know, I mean, I don't know dofa
Dofa, oh wait, Dofa Bees.
- Dofa Bees. - Both of these.
- That sounds like a chain restaurant.
- Dofa Bees. - Dofa Bees.
- I'm a Dofa Bees.
- Or a producer.
- Dofa Bees, a producer?
Oh yeah. - Dofa Bees.
Japanese guy.
- Japanese guy? - Why is he Japanese?
- 'Cause New Jobbies was Japanese.
Actually, I don't know.
He might, maybe he was Korean maybe.
- All right.
- Dofa Bees is Japanese though.
(laughing)
- Dofa Bees is for sure.
- Dofa Bees nuts.
- What was the funniest Christmas gift
that you guys got this year?
- Dan Flash's shirt.
- No way.
- You got a Dan Flash's shirt?
That's funny.
- My brother got me that.
- What?
- My brother Eric.
- What do you mean?
- My brother Eric got me and my brother Paul
matching Dan Flash's shirts.
- Does Dan Flash's a real brand?
- No, just the one from the show.
- That's some funny shit.
- That's crazy.
- My mom got me this.
- It fits perfect.
- I bet you look amazing.
- It fits perfect, but I could never wear it
anywhere with anyone saying,
"Hey, that guy's wearing the Dan Flash's shirt."
really hang out a lot of sketch comedy fan do you get it can go anywhere could you
go on the bus now i was there is an ocean
well i got a look at the fucking guy who did it by sixty five-year-old bus driver
looking at me saying something like this and then he's like i hope my steering
wheel doesn't fly you know what it was as you know what
yet because i guess if you want to finish it
doesn't dot dot dot i'd i'd really hate how much i like that show
why it's a great chance to really good as i think that what you feel she just
just because of the memes and stuff.
You suck.
I suck so bad.
You're the worst ever.
My mom got me a book that she found at a used bookstore that was a, it's like a dinosaur,
it's like a book of like paintings of dinosaurs, but it's like self-published by a guy who
like thinks he's like a, like a paleo artist or whatever, but he's a really bad artist
and it's really funny.
Oh man.
Did she get it because she thought it was funny?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll show it to you guys, I think you'll, it's very funny.
What a sweet gift from a mom.
all they're all like they're all like really fucked up and fat and like from
the wrong like they're like all like the perspective doesn't make sense like what
a babe what a kid draws a horse you should not kill the number there's three
dollars left oh okay thank you that's nice of you that's pretty cool I don't
have one for you so you're gonna have to share that I got a trader Joe's gift card
that's huge yeah I'm probably gonna go in there by some some kind of fudgy fudge
Fudge mostly. Or some kind of maybe one of those food activities. What I did buy with that
was that South Park game Stick of Truth and then I spent three days just not
doing anything but play that. Yeah yeah man I was just you know I mean I... No
replay value on that game. I hate to say it but I'm back on my golf shit. Yeah.
Seriously I'm back. This always happens at the new year. Every time I go to Christmas I come
back and I'm a golfer again. Yeah. So it happened again I got the bug. I pretty
much was playing some of my best golf ever. My grandpa Pete out there who's been
sending some pretty racial stuff out there on the golf course.
And at that point you just you just got to ignore that. You know he's at that age
where you just gotta go yep. What stays on the court stays on the court.
Yeah. I mean the course. He's calling the golf course the court. Yeah. I'm not a golfer.
I never claimed to be a golfer. Okay. The thing that is different though I'm his
grandson so it's all gravy for me I just don't care right he's only got a couple
years left god bless him but this other fucking guy this young younger guy like
college kid joins our grandpa's friend you know no he just joins because he's
playing behind us he joins our now get this you guys are gonna laugh at this
he joins our threesome it becomes a foursome that's what it's called when you
I'm not even gonna go there I know I know I know and grant great-granddad
immediately starts talking to him about yeah what's your school like is there we
got black guys on the fucking basketball team and that dude that dude put up with
it like he was his grandson and it's like no you guy you don't know him you got to
put it into that but he was you're not supposed to you're supposed to let every
old person do that no I don't think so I think if you're not related to them
also if you're joining their golf group you can't you can't come into someone's
golf group yeah and it was way better at golf than maybe you know what the place
that the place that you should is if you guys are like boxing each other or
something that's okay to be like
fuck you yeah that shit but i don't
really want to store the golf course
might be the last possible sport that
you want to be challenging also
everybody who plays golf is going to
talk about that's all gone there off
is probably I resent that accusation
what why that all golfers talk about
black guys who said you're talking about
black guys with your grip no I wasn't
talking like yeah yeah yeah I was a
I was saying, I was like, I was completely okay with it.
I was saying, yep, yep, yep, yes, yes, yes.
No, no, no.
I was basically zoning out way off into the distance.
I was looking, I was thinking about my golf game and he's just telling me about Tiger
Woods all the shit.
I'm going, yeah, for sure.
You're saying, yeah, for sure.
I'm not actively engaging in a conversation.
I'm not, it's not like, oh, what's next on the list today?
Like we're going through the fucking around the horn and it says black guys.
If I was there and I heard someone say something about black guys and that was offensive, I
I would be like, I'm gonna stare at you
until you realize what was wrong about what you said.
- Yeah, or you could like--
- Or I'd box him, or get a hole in one.
- Yeah, this just became boxing, Pete.
- Uh-huh.
- Oh no.
But yeah, he, but that guy who played with us,
that guy Nick, pretty good golfer Nick,
if you're listening, put me to shame.
Me and my brother kept saying nasty shit to him
just trying to get him to crack, he wouldn't do anything.
- Oh, crack what?
- Crack up?
- What did you say?
- Crack like, you know what, screw you guys,
going home South Park reference. We were just sitting there talking about we wanted to
like eat his cum and shit trying to fucking throwing off his game and he was
hitting just fucking cherry drives right down the fairway. Yeah. Your first thought
when you like a guy joins your golf foursome is say I'm gonna make you eat my
cum. I didn't, no no I said I'll eat your, we were just slipping it in. Oh so you're gonna eat
his cum. Yeah we were saying like I'll eat your cum if you want and then he would hit the
most amazing shot ever and he would just like, he'd go, "Oh!" and then just hit a beautiful
shot.
You're probably making him stronger.
I think so, yeah.
Yeah.
But that's a fun game.
I would get better at golf if someone told me that they would eat my cone.
Yeah, that's huge because that's beyond saying like, "Hey, I like your shorts."
That's about as big as they get on the golf course, right?
Being like, "Buddy, I'll eat your cum any day."
Are you allowed to wear shorts on golf?
Yeah.
Interesting.
You know what they make is, they make like Jordans.
sport of all time. On weekdays you can wear shorts. They make Jordans with golf cleats
in them. Yeah I have some golf shoes. Do you have to wear golf Jordans? I have New Balances.
Oh ok. Why do you have to wear cleats to play golf? Because it keeps you stable. You run
around a lot? But some courses you can't even wear the cleats. I run around a lot. Barefoot?
No. I'm doing my new type of golf game. I invented it called fast golf. You're kidding
but I literally... I carry the ball, I pick up the ball and I run with it to the hole and I put it in and I smile and I look at everyone and I wave like I'm four years old.
You are hitting but when I am done with a hole, if I'm playing with people who are decent at golf, I'm like
completely out of breath and I've ran the entire way because I'm hitting my ball and then you're ten yards at a time running to it
hitting again. I hit it 13 times in a hole. Everybody else has hit it four. Like mini golf. Yeah, and I'm sprinting. Just like mini golf.
Yeah. Golf is a lot like mini golf.
Yeah, no, it's I'm pretty terrible. I had one good around it seems like it's really hard to be good
It's the hardest game of it. Yeah, it draws me. I suck at mini golf
It's got my golf is no humans
What I said, I suck at mini golf and golf is way bigger golf is a massive version of me
Yeah, it's maxi golf and there's no fun part. I hate there's no fun. There's no fun toys that bar built-in
I hate golf because all that land could be used to actually to do what house the houseless. Would you buy this?
Would you build those houses?
Oh no!
That's right!
We have the wrong set on to tickle him today.
Yeah.
Okay, scoot your chair back in.
Alright, gotta scoot that back out.
Woo!
Oh my god.
That was a close one.
We almost had a catastrophic fit.
We should, we need to be in the video.
We both died!
Oh my god.
That would have been a full Buster Keaton, I could have gone and...
Yeah, yeah.
And I did a real bad job doing that, there's a ton of nails in the back.
There's nails and look this is just a piece of tape. Yeah. Don't touch it you fucking asshole. Don't slap me.
Speaking of this thing, what is it? It's the Dungeons & Dragons set. Oh yeah this is
set from the Dungeons & Dragons episodes. Go check out those. Go look at that.
We're already on the Patreon, it's basically just one little click. I don't
even think it even charges you any extra money. I don't think it even does
anything. So you might as well just press the button. And you know what? And the
- The smarter thing to do is just make yourself
an executive producer, 'cause you get that,
and you get this episode, and you get that,
and you get to go on a meeting with us.
- And it's all the same price.
- And it's all the same increments of five.
- Price.
- What are you opening up the mail account for?
- Yeah, close the email.
- Juvio, what the hell are you doing, man?
- He's acting weird.
- Wait, show us the big Juvio cam.
- Yeah.
- I wanna see the big Juvio cam again.
- Why are you laughing?
- Why are you so ashamed?
(laughing)
Why are you so ashamed?
Oh, he's gone.
He's so ashamed. He tried to open up some mail thing and he
He was trying to prank us and he fucked it up.
Fucking idiot.
Yeah, we got you. He's embarrassed.
Yeah, we got you.
I don't think I'm ever going to be embarrassed again.
Whoa, that's a big New Year's resolution.
Yep. I think mine is to save more money.
I shouldn't have said that in front of everybody.
You're so embarrassed aren't you? Nope.
I think I'm going to do a hundred
backflips a day.
a day. Yeah, that will be good for you. Yeah. Actually, I think I maybe... I might copy that.
Maybe that's what I'll try to do this year. I might do 101 a day. Maybe I'll do one backflip.
A flat ground backflip. Yeah. I think I could do it. I think it's a mental thing for me.
It's... I'm a 48-inch vertical jump. You can look up how to do a backflip. Can you pull
up how to do a backflip on YouTube, do you know? I can do one on a trampoline all day.
I mean, we could just turn the cameras around and you could attempt it. I'm not gonna attempt
it live right now. Why not? 'Cause I'll hurt myself, man. You won't hurt yourself. I will
I'll hurt myself hardly.
You won't hurt yourself.
Wow, there's some great fucking podcast clips up here.
Backflipping 30, hey, I know that guy.
Who is that guy?
Wanna learn a backflip in just 30 days?
(laughing)
Wait, it takes 30 days to learn a backflip?
Holy shit.
Whoa.
You know, I don't care.
I'll learn myself on my own time.
It looks like this guy can already backflip.
This is company time, right?
Why am I wasting company time on my New Year's resolution?
Oh, hey, your time is more important
than company time. Why was that shot
in the Dutch angle?
Union.
he makes a bunch of videos. He makes videos where he's like, "I only ate fucking corn
for 30 days."
He's like a dolphin on land.
Yeah, he is. He does have a fucked up kind of look to him.
Yeah.
He's one of those guys whose square head disappears into his body. You know what I mean?
He's doing a macaque.
I can do a macaque and I can do an arm swing technique.
I can't do that.
That's easy.
I don't know how to do an arm swing technique. I can't do this either. I can't do any of
this stuff.
- No problem. - You're gonna learn to--
- So are these the building blocks of a backflip?
Is this like when you watch like a
how to do a kickflip tutorial and it's like,
to learn that, you have to learn how to do an ollie first.
- I wanna learn how to do an ollie pretty badly.
- Yeah. - Maybe that'll be
my New Year's resolution. - I could teach you.
- No you couldn't, I'm unteachable.
I'm one of those unteachable, I'm an unteachable maverick.
- It's literally, doing an ollie is like
one of the easiest things in the world.
- Not for an unteachable maverick.
- Yeah. - Good luck finding me a master.
I'm self-taught on everything. - Most stuff is difficult
for
perfect age and the perfect religion Aaron Cairo Cairo Islam nope Scientology
Oh Cairo though I was a pretty good guess by Caleb mm-hmm no because it's KYRO so
you three he's spelled he's spell it spells it like it's like a Star Wars guy
maybe his name is if his name was Cairo Aaron he would be like a perfect
Star Wars character but he's the one who's making all these fucking videos
for like him yeah he's looking he's gangster - he does look like a thug I'll
say it but he makes I want to learn from this guy probably robbed me he's such a
fucking thug he makes all these videos like how to do an ollie and stuff he
looks like how did he do that oh my god like these videos where it's like we
skated a 100% glass skateboard oh he's like the mr. oh this is the guy who does
the sharpest kitchen knife in the world yeah oh this is him he looks like he
might be able to be one of those guys who pulls his bottom lip.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What is he with there?
That's some...
The skateboard hero and the anti-semite.
Is Aaron Cairo an anti-semite?
I mean, maybe. I don't know.
He's a Scientologist, really.
Look at that foot.
He looks cool, man.
Yeah.
But yeah, I do want to learn how to ollie.
I feel like that'd be a good, you know,
teach my...
everything about my life yeah this year mm-hmm like starting with what just every
detail so maybe I'll start with can we give you a makeover yeah I would love to
give him a make well here he gave himself a makeover look at his hair
changed his hair up this year what if we gave you like a complete style makeover
new remove all the tattoos okay we could put you on Queer Eye I think yeah yeah
- No? - Yeah.
- I wouldn't listen to them.
(laughing)
- Even the food guy?
- I'd be like, no.
- No, no.
- That's all I would say.
They would say, so what you're gonna wanna do
is do this, put this painting up in your house.
I'd go, no.
- No, no, no.
- I'd move my head like I was gonna go like, no.
But I would go, no.
(laughing)
- That would, I saw one the other day.
- What's the food guy's name, Antony?
Anthony and Karamo. Karamo. Karamo. I would listen to Karamo. Karamo is cool.
Anthony though, Anthony's like not good at making food. Karamo just dresses normal.
Yeah, what does he teach them to do? Avocado toast? He literally does. He teaches them avocado toast.
And then what did I what did I say? I think like four years ago they partnered with Whole Foods
and it was like Anthony's like awesome summer recipes and he made grilled romaine lettuce.
I've eaten that.
It's the funniest thing I've ever seen.
It's just him putting lettuce on a grill.
I think I have a thing.
I think I could have a thing.
I've had a grilled salad.
I feel like if I was on Queer Eye, I could maybe have a thing or two to teach them.
Especially about the food.
I bet they don't know how to eat a PB&J sandwich over the sink.
I bet they've never done that before.
I do that three times a day.
- Hey, we are gonna put some seasoning in your food,
my friend. - Yeah, yeah.
- You white man. - This is how to eat a pretzel.
(laughing)
- Yep, yep. - You go like this.
- That's what's so important about that show
is that everyone learns from each other.
- Yeah, exactly. - It creates some kind
of mind meld in the end.
I saw one the other day, they do an entire high school.
They go into a high school. - They clear out a high school.
- They clear out all the kids in the high school,
or all the prom kids or some shit.
I don't remember.
I wasn't really watching it.
But they did a makeover with all the kids.
- You know what?
That sounds like you watched some propaganda shit.
- It kind of was, yeah, it was.
They made all these kids wear tuxedos.
- Oh my God. - Oh, what the fuck?
- Yeah, that's purely sexualizing.
- That's sexualizing, that's leftist ass propaganda.
- Who else wears a tuxedo?
- James Bond.
- Justin Timberlake, suit and tie.
♪ As long as I got my suit and tie ♪
Gay men.
Justin Timberlake.
I'm gonna have sex with Jessica Biel, my wife.
She was foin.
Chuck and Larry.
You know, I saw today in a very, very...
Suit and tie, two male guys.
As long as I have my suit and tie, I can have sex with two male guys.
Show me their poop thing.
Their butts.
- Dang.
- Their butts.
- Actually, if I was on Queer Eye,
I would take all the advice,
but every time I would do, I would say,
you know I'm just gonna stop doing this
once you guys leave, right?
- Doesn't it feel like Queer Eye?
(laughing)
- And then they'd dress me up,
and I'd be like, this is great,
but you realize I'm gonna throw this all away.
- Yeah, I really love these shorts from Target.
- Man, I used to love Queer Eye,
but now it just feels like they've gone so woke.
(laughing)
- Ah, I hate it.
They fucking go woke, go broke.
- Yeah, GVN used to be so funny,
but then they started doing all that fucking.
- They've just gone so woke on queer, I hate that bullshit.
I watched a video today,
2022 top five times Hollywood went woke and went broke.
- Turned broke by being woke?
- Turns out G4 went woke, and then they went broke afterwards.
Can you, G4.
- What's G4?
- G4, the.
I'm taking your straight card my friend.
You know G4?
I don't know say what it is. Olivia Munn. He has no idea who Olivia Munn is.
The TV channel about video games? Oh I don't know any TV channels.
Attack of the Show.
Oh Attack of the Show, yeah yeah yeah. Oh he's pretending now. No I've heard of Attack of the Show.
I'm not gonna pretend I watched it and know exactly what it is but I've heard of
Attack of the Show. She was fine. What was the other one's name?
Olivia Munn. No that's Olivia Munn.
Megan.
something beggin fox not the yeah
no
the idea is a way
they basically went uh... they went well can they will remember that role face
that's a troll face you're looking at a story seem like four fine fellows
similar on the right it's a troll for every last one of them is a girl
yet the your four girls
that's a literal totally expect this is so
pocketed
and always share
look at that. Jesus Christ. What the hell? What is it? Olivia Munn has a child with
John Lennie now? Have you ever looked up who the like, who your like state
representative is? It always looks exactly like this. This is this is like one of
the guys they get that they get to mocap every monster in every movie. Yeah, yeah
exactly. They just choose the guy with the longest teeth because they're like it'll be
easy to put fangs on him. Yeah but they have G4 apparently. They tried to bring G4 back
and then they tried to go completely woke. Can you believe that? Yeah.
John Mulaney had a kid with Olivia Munn and then that like made everyone
was like "Oh he's not actually a wife guy because he cheated on his wife" and then
it was like yeah he's fun. John Mulaney, what do you think that was a good guy?
Remember that? There was a big John Mulaney meltdown? You got a hairball.
sorry I feel like probably once a day you you tell me something like it's like
it's World War two history that everybody should know and I just what are you
talking about that is huge I heard about it but it was a it was not huge it was a
twit was Twitter and like what is the are you trying to make a point about it
remember that you're doing a remember remember that crap you doing you play too
much South Park game you're doing member berries yeah yeah shit you're right who
- Who did he get to instead?
- Huh?
- Get to?
- Who did he--
(laughing)
- Who did he get to?
I don't know.
Who did he get to instead of Olivia Munn?
- Olivia Munn, he got to Olivia Munn instead of his wife.
- He got to have a kid with her.
- He got her, but he was married to another.
- Yeah.
- Right, okay.
(laughing)
- Married to another.
That's sad.
- Okay, I couldn't remember.
First I thought maybe she and him was already.
- No.
- No, I don't think.
- She and him was on the side.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- She and him, what's that?
Zooey Deschanel and that fucking other guy
did sing Christmas songs?
- That's a sucked ass. - The Property Brother.
- She's married to one of the Property Brothers.
- Zooey is?
- Yeah, I watched, I--
- What?
- Oh yeah, I did know that actually.
- No shit.
- Yeah.
- That's awesome.
- The one who does the handyman stuff.
- They both do the handyman stuff.
- They're both the same, they're not interchangeable.
- One of them is so much Property Brothers
and they're not interchangeable.
One of them wears a vest and the other one wears a flannel.
They are interchangeable.
Yes, they are.
No, I'm a Property Brothers expert and there's no difference.
It's Drew and Michael, right?
Yeah, right, you're a Property Brothers expert.
No.
Drew Michael's a comedian.
No, no, Drew and Michael Property.
They're not named Michael.
It's Jay and Pharaoh.
I don't remember their names, but they're not that...
I'm pretty sure one of them is named Drew.
I think that's right, maybe, but there's definitely not one named Michael.
You might be the Property Brothers expert, but I'm a Chip and Joanna Gaines expert.
You might be a Property Brother.
Oh, yeah.
I'm a fixer-upper.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll watch that all day.
That's pretty good.
One time, he ate a cockroach.
Yeah, yeah.
Right off the ground.
Crazy son of a bitch.
I was about to say something that I love about the Property Brothers, but we already talked
about it.
We did?
Yeah.
It's a long time ago.
They always make women touch dirt.
Oh, yeah.
I've heard you mention this before.
Yeah, you should.
They go, "Look how gross this is."
and they are nasty there's a lot of how it meant so we did you know
to the leadership
you know i what i was quirky i watched l for the first time in years and i was
home to christmas it's good
what's really funny that i could we forgot about is how it it just ends
there's no real at like their ends that that they like to go to park at central
park they just sing the song and it ends no no no no no he does not
the they
they have a little and they have an epilogue yes like during the credits
but it is a house
yeah it doesn't just and it goes
now because i have to bob newhart on your tells a story and he ends the story and
then it buddy sits on the other side of this kid
minutes to the movie turns off
after the credits he's fucking in
this uh... you know you're talking about you know that you'd often do you know i
really dvd
you're a lot here yeah i did watch a baby a pop and i had a you know they're
really wrong setting i was looking at that but i have a very busy
i really want to find games on their own i tried to do it on the dvd player it
was like you have to put in the computer my grandma had a dvd player you could
play those games on that's yes fun as fuck we did with santa claus you can
make your own uh... you could make your own elf
you know what the worst special features
stills gallery yeah and always the worst
you really patent i hate i hate seeing stills gallery they used to have so much stuff
packed into those dvds
they have more now they have more now
no they don't
they have more way more than they have more now everyone wants to collect
dvds and and blu-ray so and everyone looks for special features
all right i guess i mean i don't know the unfortunately i was going out i think i
guess i'm just buying too many bare-bones dvds yeah you have to buy
that's
that's what's fucked now they they have the special editions and it's like
owed this you can either get this for two dollars that at uh... at like savers
yes somebody threw it away
or you can get it for a hundred dollars and it's in a really big case and i don't
- They don't have a-- - Interview that we made
this year that doesn't have anyone from the movie in it.
- Yeah, that stinks. - They don't have any
of the DVD-ROM stuff anymore.
- Yeah, that's true.
That shit is fucked. - You don't get to put your,
you don't get to put your copy of like Alien.
- Does Blu-ray ROM?
Did Blu-ray ever have ROM?
- I don't know. - You don't get to put that
in your mom's laptop and then play a game.
And that's what we need again.
- Yeah. - We need a combo movie.
- Games on every movie.
- Yeah, I agree. - Was that the great
Portrait of a Lady on Fire?
- Yeah. - Put that,
should a game on that
yet
tar
for a at like a split yet for july dot my gosh every every movie for girls
stop every movie for girls who have a needs to have a do you know i i i i
like a fucking bitch from barbarian movie for girls is ever do mode for guys
where you go through the whole movie and you can tell i don't know people
so that you can talk about the plot after with your girlfriend it's like a
I love when the alien jumped out of Olivia Colman's chest.
Yeah.
No, you should play, but you shouldn't.
She's in that movie, right?
It gets dicey for you.
I don't remember.
I saw that movie in the movie theater.
And it was a really quiet, it was a very quiet movie.
It's a lot of women looking at each other and not talking.
Portrait of a Lady on Fire.
It's a movie for sapphics.
It's a sapphic movie.
And I saw it in a movie theater.
it was so it was so quiet that just the entire movie you could just hear the
theater next door so we were just watching like these two women just like
looking at you like and then just like there were just like all these others
like it was really making me enjoy it shouldn't be like a wide release it
should be played at like a movie theater that has 15 seats that's not at the
Coolidge Corner Theater. Oh, that's a good theater. I miss that theater.
Every DVD should have... it shouldn't be... the Doom setting shouldn't be like
you're playing a character in the movie though. It should be literally like it
should open and it should say "epilogue" and then it should fade into first
person Doom guy at whatever the scene was and then you can kill whoever you want from the movie.
It's like Sex and the City. It's as soon as the...
there what movie is coming out next okay so they got what movies are coming to
DVDs what movie's coming you know Avatar got a come to DVDs I don't know what
TAR is about our is a TAR counts as a girl movie because the guys who like it
are girly okay what is TAR about it's about a composer that gets me to eat
Blanchette I mean that's a win for the guys yeah it's a movie where the fellas
for sure it's all about music and I read I was like I was like should I go see
this it's really fucking beautiful yeah it's actually not beautiful at all
but I watch I read the whole Wikipedia when she is 13 then I read it I read at
the end of the movie that... Don't spoil the end of the movie. Go ahead, just spoil it.
Why would you do that? It's a really good ending. But what's the point? It's just a
movie ending. The song that she plays at the end is from a video game. Yeah,
that's just... Why are you saying this? Still Alive from Portal? Yes. It's just part of
the movie. She composes Still Alive. Oh my god. You're just saying a joke from a movie that you
read on Wikipedia. It's a joke from the movie? It's a funny thing that happens at
the end of the movie.
Oh shit, well I didn't see it.
But if it's still alive, that is pretty funny.
I didn't see it and then I was like, well it's from that, I kind of want to see it.
It's a good movie.
Yeah.
It's from Monster Hunter.
He's been bending TAR so hard.
I don't even like it that much, it's just a good movie.
I don't know.
I'm pretty sure everyone who listens to this show has already seen TAR.
Probably.
I don't know.
You hope not?
I hope everyone sees Avatar.
That's two TARs.
I'm going to see it again tomorrow.
I have a funny ass display name for you.
Oh, I thought of this one already.
What?
I don't even want to say it.
Avatared?
No.
Close.
Okay.
Avata-er.
With a tilde.
Isn't that what they do in the Navi language anyway?
No, that's an apostrophe.
Oh, wait.
Do they do a different...
The tar...
The tar has this.
Oh, I don't know.
Did Mad Magazine make a spoof that was avatar-ed?
Probably.
Either that or I did.
I think that I had that one.
Yeah, what's this? Yeah, it's Tar. It's not Tar.
That's Tar right there. Who's that bitch? Who is this? She looks like fucking poop.
Oh my god, wait, he just made Avatar.
Holy crap. Is that even Tar? Yeah, that's Tar.
That's Tar from Tar. Oh yeah, that is Tar. Is her name Tar? Yeah, Lydia Tar.
I'm sick of talking about this movie. I don't know why we're talking about it.
- Did you talk about anything else with this fucking movie?
- I didn't see it.
I haven't seen any movies this year.
- I have--
- Well this year--
- I haven't seen anything in the theater.
- It didn't come out this year.
- It came out last year, pal.
- My brother tried to make me watch Everywhere Everywhere.
- All at once?
- Yeah, and I was like, it's too long.
- I saw a scene from that movie where they're both rocks
and I was like, this looks like fucking shit.
- Why did you say you didn't wanna talk about Tartan
and we're talking about just other movies?
- Why are you being a crybaby?
We can just talk.
- Okay.
I just put--
- This is the movie episode.
- Look, we have two big,
Jubio, I want you to just look up--
- It's basically movie scenes.
- Just look up the word full movie on YouTube
and then just play it behind us.
This is the movie episode.
Yeah, anything full movie.
- Full movie.
Full movie.
- Yeah, press enter.
Home alone 2 full movie.
All right, there we go.
Hit full screen.
- And just put it to the middle.
- Yeah.
- I don't think that works.
(laughter)
- Anyway. - There we go.
- What else did you guys do around--
- Directed by Christopher Columbus.
- No way. - Yep.
- Who's that? - Fuller.
Oh, no, that's...
(laughter)
I thought you were asking who was on the screen.
- You thought I was asking who the one character
out of the 12 on the fucking screen were?
And you knew it? - Fuller.
- Fuller, that's Fuller?
(laughter)
- That's Fuller.
(laughing)
- I've been watching a lot of old...
I've been watching a lot of old Johnny Carson.
I didn't realize he did that shit into the 90s.
I always thought it stopped in the 80s.
He had like Drew Carey on there.
- For real?
- Yeah, Drew Carey was on there.
- As he was like the standup guest.
- Yeah, yeah, he was the standup guest.
He can barely talk.
- Yeah, dude, Fuller got me.
- Do you think we could do a Whose Line Is It Anyway reboot?
Do you think that we might be able to do it?
Tried to do that, but they did they weren't they weren't us. Yeah, cuz we have you can do anything you can be drew
What he's the best part he's not the best part no he's the best part the best one
Everybody loved look I care if you said you could be chip. I would have taken it
They give me a who's on a few episodes. You should be the audience
You can be what's that's the best part you get to?
You can be this guy. What's his name?
The guy who sounds like this!
What's his name? I don't know. From whose line? Later Seasons.
I don't know.
That guy. Oh, Greg Proops? Greg Proops. He could be Greg Proops. He's a K-Hive guy. Do you know that about him?
He's a big Kamala Harris supporter. Oh me oh my. I think his- Great. Yeah.
So great. There goes my fucking fanship with Greg Proops. But he was also in
Phantom Menace, I think. Great, so it's back now.
Great
He was Greg groups, right
Greg Bruch and Phantom in his I went back to fear factor. Yeah, that's it. That's a home
That's I got a I got a I have a really good thing to share for that. I saw in fear factor
What'd you see so there were did they did they did there?
You know how they do themed ones with themed contestants and everyone it was two pairs of contestants that were dressed the same
And we're like is this twins?
And it was it was fear factor best friends, okay, but then there were two who were twins and they said we're twins
We're twins and then they got they got to the very end and this episode nobody won
Everybody I didn't know that it was possible. I know I didn't either but then it got they got to one of the you know
How they always do car challenges?
Yeah
They got to the car challenge and the twins one of the twins they were like like Joe Rogan was eyes like asking her like
like so are you like nervous about this and she was like yeah one time when I
was driving to work I fell asleep behind the wheel and caused a 12 car pile
he has to be the best host of all time yeah cuz he's sitting there and he's
like so clearly completely checked out yeah they're about to eat a hundred like
African cockroaches and he's like "so do you like cockroaches or do you hate them?"
I don't like them. He's like "okay three two one" he's also great because he's mean to
the people who need to be mean to him. Yeah he's pretty good at that.
There's that one clip where he gets in a... I've been distracted by all of them.
Yeah you gotta turn this off. I forgot he like gets in his
brothers fucking with him and then he gets in trouble for retaliating and that
pissed me off so much when I was a kid. Sorry but Joe Rogan's good at fear factor.
don't act like I'm saying the uninteresting no no I go ahead but Joe
Rogan's on fear factor sorry I was just watching home alone in the middle of the
podcast why you got a photo of me up now now you're gonna look at this like it's
a movie - that's probably that's like one of the fattest I've ever been mm-hmm
yeah remember that photo I remember that photo I remember taking it mm-hmm when
so have a nice life
good times that episode of fear factor was it wasn't there
he wasn't there
was an all-time retail for and every time i was here for a job every single time
that no matter what i always
make the same joke every time it's to get to get to me every time is
who's fears this is a great of doing this and that was the three-fifth
three-fifth and that work
going underwater to turn up a metal handle
sticking ahead in animal walkers to pick up a a cow's tongue i fear and
yeah i think it's hard for a couple of people to another car
the way i was there
here there those are the three fears of driving a car that everybody's
so nobody won
so the end is like
i guess everyone's to a friend
that is so funny when you do doing stuntman work
and they're like well you clearly missed messed up because you were too afraid
for
truck while you're driving on a highway. Yeah I've never driven a car. I haven't either.
But you at least have some logical... I've driven a car. You can understand... I guess I have to see what this looks like.
Because you're not doing a good job explaining it. How can it be more clear?
There's two cars one has a ramp on the back and you have to drive on to the
ramp car. It's actually a little more complicated than that. Well so the car...
Let's start with the base explanation and then we'll introduce more complicated stuff. So the car is going off of a ramp that is on
another car yes to just sit on top of it to just sit on that's just parking while
they're driving everything's driving on a highway driving there's like there's a
flatbed truck that you have to get on the way you get on it is you drive up a ramp
that is all on top of a car that is also moving and you're you're just true you're
just you're just I could do this I could do this fear no you could not even pass
the Lord fear I could pass the Lord fear then the Lord fear you want a Mazda they
one two cars
was the best episode of the put my head with the best episode ever is it's
smelly animal art
yeah you look at the candle after you get in it waits so what you're going to
hold on a large is a business was it's also more complicated it's it's there's
a lot and then there was uh...
was a big part of it was some other disgusting substance and their it was
used as tongues
that's that was in the reboot
um they made him drink jizz donkey jizz oh yeah that's why they got canceled like a
dust boot of it too yeah and then and they made girls do it and the girls went
oh and then they they were watching it love drinking they were watching going
like oh yeah you like that dude it was so i think rogan talked about it on some
episode where he talked about that specific incident and i don't remember
who the guest was but the guest was like yeah did you think it was hot donkey come
at while I'm at work and then they kept cutting to the donkey.
She would be drinking the jizz and going like "fwaaarrr" and they would just cut to its face.
The donkey had like, they went in the like liquify and photoshop and made its eyebrows
like "fwaaarrr" You know that thing where they do, they like
cut to an animal and they like, the ADR and the animal noise, like the dog going like
"fwaaarrr" They were like doing that but with the donkey.
I would have gone all out, I would have the donkey like looking back and just like, I'd
fart in a ways it was shit.
They basically, they went as far as they could, then they got cancelled.
they ruined everything. Speaking of animal jizz. We need to do a fear factor episode.
That's a great fucking idea. This is, I mean, the caution tape, I mean, we can even reuse
the set and do a cash cab one as well. Red and, or, red, white and, no, yellow and black.
Hey, nowadays a cab can be any color, thanks to Uber.
Whoa, that is true. But we could do a cash cab slash fear factor, we could divide it right
the middle yeah you can be on this side you could be the guy from cash cab and
Joe Rogan you can be Joe Rogan and I'll be the contestant because I look the most like the contestant
you yeah you don't look like Joe Rogan or anything no or the other guy from cash
cab I think I have a lot of facts and trivia I can ask you for cash cab yeah
go ahead ask me anything I'm a trivia god my dad does trivia every single week
at a pub? I was for a little bit I think I went twice in a week. So go ahead and ask
me your trivia. At the Clam? Yeah the Clam. Go ahead and ask me the trivia. Which 1999
movie featured the Titanic? The Titanic that's so easy. Can you give me a real...
Was this called Titanic? He's right you know. Can you give me...
well I actually saw the movie in Europe so I saw the European release
well that was called El Titanic. Spain also speaks Spanish. Go ahead and ask me another
question go ahead and ask me a trivia question. Which 1999 which two that which early aughts
movie featured the Blair Witch? Blair Witch Project this is so easy. Okay wait let me
Let me ask one.
You suck at trivia.
I don't suck at trivia.
I'm awesome at it.
I think you're just doing very well.
Can I ask a trivia question?
Yeah.
How about you whisper it to me?
No, I want to ask it.
Then I can ask.
I'm going to ask it.
Well, I'm the host.
Well, you just said I could ask it already, so I'm going to ask it.
Okay, I said it.
Alright.
Have you ever heard of MoFa?
I mean, BoFa.
No, I have not.
Both of these nuts.
That's not...
They would never ask that in a trivia game.
That makes no sense.
Okay.
I messed up the question. Next question. Which country does Fondalma come from?
Popular cheese in what country does Fondalma come from? It's not a bad
question. Yeah what celebrity suffered famously from the condition my big? My
big - this is the guy from from fucking back to the future yeah what's his name
if you can't ask the host what the answer is you two are confusing me who the host
is so they may not give it to you but they don't disqualify you just for
asking oh fucking yeah what's his name the guy with Sam no not Sam Michael
Michael J Richards yeah this guy from Back to the Future you guys don't
remember famous guy ever yeah that guy is pretty famous yeah he was as famous
as fucking God at one point where the Sun you know son of God son of God was not
that famous at first but he literally even changed it up look at old classic
Jesus Christ say a saviorship damn you know on religion a cult classic that's
some fire-ass shit no you're thinking of a classic cult
okay atheistic thinking mm-hmm listen I'll say this I left to be agnostic
atheist I left being a little to gate the is for Christmas I came back and I saw
many a multitude of miracles yeah I would say here's I did you just gave me a
really good idea to convert atheists okay I'll be going door-to-door as a
missionary knock on the door say so pretend you're an atheist yes hello sir
hello sir have you ever have you ever heard of Jesus's Jesus is your Savior oh
Oh that's good. So it weaponizes the bofa technique. Man, whatever happened to
magicianaries? You would go and they'd say, "Is this your Bible?" Remember they had a
they would have like a guy come to the school and shoot three-pointers to teach
you that like bullying is wrong but then he would be like, "I also got a show
tomorrow night at church." And it was just like, "Oh yeah." You think everybody's had this guy?
They always had a guy come to the school. I had guys come to my school but
not that guy to shoot they would they would have a guy going to church I was
they would have a guy come to the school and they he would do like be a you would
jump over something on a BMX bike in the gym now you're doing a different you
said there was three four different things that happened they had
motivational speakers like constantly at my school we didn't need motivation
because we were already self-motivated you were home skills not you guys always
say I was home to a buddy I went to fucking through sixth grade okay so I
think I got pretty much the entire school experience some might say yeah pretty
much they I used to go just hang out at my friend's school in high school cuz I
nothing they hired a guy to come to our middle school who was just his whole
thing was just being good at three-pointers he was like 46 or
something he was telling us about like don't give up blah blah blah but somebody
zeroed in on his penis while he was doing that and they thought it looked like he
had a boner so then everyone just kept calling him boner Bob boner Bob the
three-point shooter yeah I see a boners there was this uh we had a porn stars
come to our school every day yeah yeah there was this 19 year old guy who like
attacked cops with a machete in Times Square this past week oh you know what
Mike he was in the Taliban. Believe it or not my granddad told me about this.
Yeah and nobody heard about it. It's one of those things where like you he says
one of those I'm like he made this up. No nobody told nobody didn't tell anybody.
The guy in the Taliban. He wanted to be in the Taliban. He was a wannabe. He was a wanksta.
He said I read the I read the article. He was he was a wannabe gangster. He was a
complete wanksta. I read the article and it said it said according to the according to
the
Yeah, that's good. According to the perpetrator before he attacked the police officers with the machete
He took a sip of water and he shouted al-hu Akbar
But I didn't know why they said that he took a sip of water cuz water
Probably it was probably holy water. Oh
I don't know
We should do so he did he kill anybody? No, but he hurt some fractured. Well, so yeah, I fractured
You know, we should know we should go blow up the entire Middle East now
know. Let's go do that.
You know what else is funny about that article? It said at the very beginning of it, they said
we caught him and we think it's just a lone individual. There's nothing to be worried
about. And this was at 10pm on New Year's Eve.
Wow.
When this happened. They shot him in the shoulder and they took him away.
They're popping shots in Times Square?
Yeah.
At New Year's?
At 10pm.
Holy shit.
And people didn't even know he was there.
And on New Year's they were like, guys this is a lone, don't worry about it, it's completely
you can still party for new year's eve don't worry about it and they didn't
tell it they'd and then at the bottom of the article it says and this attack
lines up with uh... with a lot of police officers that believe that there's going
to be an attack on the
from the telepathic
and there's like you know and
persistent mileage new year's let's go to miami
uh... damn
that's mark they probably got the uh... that's probably why i was there
there's a buzz that mileage new year's but it's a plan is where this whole
article as reading this whole thing so like this is crazy how did i hear about
this
is all these details what is this
kid who bought a machete any like donated all his money and he came from maine on
on the amtrak is a false evidence like
yeah they think that there's going to be a huge it
well yeah from a guy in maine but i also i can't believe that people that you're
still out of by a machete
yes apparently i want to get a car to rush it was rested in blunt all god and
that's why the police officers weren't worsely injured
yeah he broke somebody's arm with a machete he fractured their skull oh shit
hit him on the head I think I got fred we believe that the suspect was named bam
bam rubble you'd probably be in a Taliban yeah where did Fred Flintstone
live in the man really yeah Bar Harbor Pangea there wasn't any places back then
but there was all bar here's fucking places no there's no there's one place
there's one fucking place you're a dickhead you're a you're addicted to
being a dickhead no I'm not no I'm not yeah you're Pangea was still like if it
never separated right do you think that vacation would be easier yeah okay like
just no water you don't fly you can walk we would do you think we would have a
train running through everywhere do you think you would just be you'd be a train
run through you I got a train right you'd never need a plane you have to go over
water we've sure him full of fucking Molly on New Year's fuck yeah me and
50,000 people fucked him for real no world's largest gangbang I'm one world's
largest that lady did the world largest world's largest gangbang what ten years
ago I don't know it's like ten years ago nobody's gone for that record probably
imagine the smell though there you know it's more you know it's more depressing
probably a bunch of people gone for that record
and nobody can do it
imagine going for that record and then tapping out
tapping out after like three
or it's worse if you tap out after 410
well i just fucking fucked 410 guys for no reason
yeah alright see you guys next week
you win that world record on like a technicality
right it's just like well she had like five hundred guys like it put their
penis in her
so i can tell you that making love the
it's not exactly
it's not a
no it's like i don't know do they have to listen to take what i would have
loaded there is a yes that the correct now it's obviously not yet i can't now
sexy is still having sex as a result of a pop it in pop it out
okay
i think i have a hard time and i'm a good at the end of five hundred got yet
that's as you say you're so nervous you're going soft you're like I'm sorry
I'm trying I'm trying I'm trying you don't even need to have a boner though
like I think you just gotta stick it in but you're going so soft you can't even
get it in yeah you gotta put it like go go we're gonna get the record we're one
away go like when you're put and you're like why don't why don't you just let
him go like I wanted to say he already went he can't go go go everyone's
standing or everyone else is already gone to you so there's everyone's just
watching you and this fucking oh yeah your things limp yeah go go put it's like
putting silly putty in a film canister. Yeah, oh my god your hairs are standing on
end. And I don't like to say this often but this that lady she's pretty loose
that's pretty... She's probably a hoe. Kind of a hoe slut. Yeah. Yeah that's a bit of a loose thing.
Hey, don't you dare call that woman a slut. Listen I know that that's rude to say that about
somebody but that is just a little bit... What the hell? You think that that woman who...
500 guys in eight hours.
The lady who fucked 500 guys, you think that lady's a slut?
She's just a little--
She's a human being.
OK, I'll say this.
She seems a little promiscuous.
OK.
She gets around.
I could give you that.
I've heard.
Is that OK to say?
What the hell are you saying?
But she's the best slut in the world.
Yeah.
World record holding slut.
I guess if you are the world record--
Or the sluttiest slut, at least.
True.
You get the sash that says, world's biggest hoe.
You get that gash.
You know what my mama--
World's biggest gash.
You know what my mama said? Whatever you do, be the best at it.
And if you decide, I'm gonna be a fucking no good dirty whore.
I'm gonna be the best there is at that.
I just like, I guess like, the prospect of having like a world record is fun in a way.
It's so exciting.
I think it's exciting.
It costs like $2000 basically.
The smell of that room, after a while your legs are gonna hurt.
Like what you're not getting fucked. All right. No, no
Lady's perspective. It's just like why
You probably wanted to do it. She liked it
Maybe why did she want to do it? She got famous. That's true. It's so awesome. She got 506. Yeah
I'm happy with one. Yeah, I get half of one. I'm happy. So if I fuck imagine how many babies she had after that though
the group is a sort of the like or or or
there's so many babies in here
many many abortion she got all the news reports are
she which is a porn star
i think so
i was just a little while
that's
that this is not a good i thought it was a normal girl yet she was not a
citizen
he did
you're just a point one issue like i thought it was a little more
the
this is outrageous
I thought you were just like a normal girl who lives in an apartment building.
She's a porn star?
Isn't that awful?
What the fuck?
You know what?
And even then, what?
Oh, oh, you don't give, like, okay, she's a porn star, she's getting fucked by 500 guys.
You don't give a record to a fucking McDonald's employee for flipping 500 burgers in a day?
That's the thing.
That's so funny, I really, when you said she's a porn star, I really was like, what?
She's a porn star.
You know, when I first saw that video of her fucking 500 guys, I said, oh my god, I'm in
love.
on
fifty guys on any given day. I don't know how it works.
It's five hundred...
It should be disqualified from the record!
It should be Olympics!
Biggest gangbang for a normal girl!
That's a great idea. It should be like the Olympics. You can't be professional in
the sport to go for the gold.
What are you talking about?
That's how it was for a very long time.
well they have a very long time ago okay until until
the uh... the dream team the basketball dream to you know
okay that i think i set the world record for most pleasure derived from sex
i like it
how do you measure that uh...
measure the pleasure of a man
you can i don't think i think men don't have a lot of pleasure and said no
not at all not anymore it's exactly like it's exactly like moving a couch rolls
come in like this guys come out like this
yeah that would be
a good cartoon that's kinda my new bill hicks and canister working on
yeah girls going like
all out it's pinching
and guys be like a little reverse pitching a pitching it out now i'm from
flowing free
yes free flying
i'm free
free alright uh...
uh...
i love you
uh... what day is the thing
of the meeting boy twenty seven on the twenty seven oh yeah
on the twenty seventh we will be our january shareholders meeting if you
subscribe to the completely free
if you pay a fifty dollars it's completely free you'll see your name
at the end of this episode at the end of episodes yeah and
uh...
i have to uh...
cancerous this enough
business casual attire
yes and so you need to be wearing some kind of collar maybe attack
is in our issue it's the next time
Bye.
[BLANK_AUDIO]