(upbeat music)
- There it goes.
- I should tie up my head like a--
- You need the bandage that goes all the way around.
- We could go get one right now.
- And you need a, the ball, this wet bean bag.
- You should put him in traction.
- We need to put you in a tiny little thin bed
and we need to have a old, old lady.
I'm doing it right now with this hoodie,
but I'm putting a little bit of pressure on the,
here right there.
But yeah, I'm gonna have a real fat face
this whole episode here.
Do a punch in, look how fat my fucking face is.
- Yeah, take it.
- See right here, how bloated that is?
- Now blow up your cheeks like a chipmunk.
- Yeah. - Oh my God,
you just got so fat.
Oh, you're, wow, you look--
- It seems like the swelling's gone down.
- Remember that?
Salt peanuts, Dizzy Gillespie?
Have you seen that video?
Oh, I guess you weren't in, no.
What class did we have together?
We didn't have any classes together.
- What is going on?
- Are you attacking him with a psychic attack?
- No, yeah.
- Psychic boarding him?
- Those too many questions in a row.
- That was scary.
You were like confusing yourself too.
- No, we never had a, we never had,
I took like five music classes at Emerson
because I thought that I could just fill up
my courses with electives.
- Do you think that the biotic infection
is, it can reach your brain?
- Yes.
- From your wisdom teeth?
has wisdom teeth, he has wisdom teeth infection. I was supposed to get them out.
They're not impacted though, right? No, they're both impacted. They're impacted. The bottom of it are
impacted and then the top are fine. They're impacted and infected. This one's infected. Okay. And I'm
getting them out. Well, once this, like the day that this episode comes out, I will be
getting, I was supposed to get it Friday, and I wanted to do, I was gonna call you
guys if it was that day. I wanted to get them out and then come here and record.
that would have been well but you'd still do that yeah we do that yeah great idea
yeah that's a really good I'm down to come in on Saturday to do that yeah okay
all right well you go under yeah and you're gonna have like cotton in your
mouth and you're not gonna want to do it but we could make you do it yeah I know
yeah no no I want to do I think you want you won't when it comes around you won't
want to bad yeah it's so fucking bad no I know I gotta get this fucking shit out
though it's it's I went well yeah you're going I went yesterday I went yesterday I
I was supposed to do it and then the lady was like,
yeah, so like, we're gonna schedule,
like, yeah, probably get them out in the next couple days.
And I was like, I'm going on tour to do comedy.
And I fucking, I flexed that thing and then never went,
and never went back after I, we came back from tour.
- Oh, nice.
- You tried to flex on the dentist?
- Yes, I did.
- You know dentists make like $500,000 a year,
dentists doesn't give a fuck.
- Dude, I fucking, I flexed on that dentist so hard.
on tour you lost 800 bucks in three weeks and you gained 20 pounds and you were like yeah
it took me so long to lose all that weight.
I guess though a dentist might be jealous of just being on the road.
Yeah true.
They're like a dentist doesn't get to go to you know Texas.
Unless you're a Glenn Martin DDS.
A traveling dentist does.
Unless you're Glenn Martin DDS.
Remember that show Claymation show on Nickelodeon?
No.
A dentist will never see.
A traveling dentist.
A New York City dentist will never see Shreveport.
Never.
A New York City dentist will never see heaven.
That is true too.
I hate dentists.
Are dentists still number one?
That's the most British part about my body.
Are dentists still number one suicide rates?
Mm-hmm.
Still?
Yeah, because I'm going in there and I'm putting subliminal messages to my teeth.
They're number two right behind men.
Yeah.
I hate when men kill themselves.
I know.
It's disappointing is what it is.
men that could have been anything, could have been in the military.
If you let me in a room with a guy who's about to kill himself and I slap him around a little
bit, he's either going to kill himself anyway or I change his mind.
So you might as well let me in a room with a guy who's going to kill himself.
You got a 50/50 shot of saving.
It really is like if you're going to kill yourself you should just join the military.
Because maybe-
You can just do a hurt locker thing.
I've never seen that.
I saw it when I got my elbow tattoo.
Jeremy Renner actually hurt his locker.
- Yeah, so his-- - Pull up that article.
- No, don't pull up anything.
- He might have to, Jubio's been showing us this article
all week, every time, before we forgot.
- It's still here! - Oh no!
Does Jeremy Renner's leg need to be amputated?
- That would be awful, dude.
- Story by promypool.com.
- They just start shooting every movie
just like they shoot the Tom Cruise movies
where they try to make a post the same height.
- Dude, they do the exact same thing that they did
for the Wakanda Forever movie,
where they show Chadwick Boseman's picture
and have people drumming and stuff.
- It's a picture of Jeremy Renner's leg.
(laughing)
It's like Captain America, he's being like,
our Hawkeye lost his leg.
How do we reckon with that?
And it's a really emotional moment.
- Can you imagine, if he loses his leg,
can you imagine the fucking album he's gonna drop?
- Oh my God.
♪ Heaven don't have no legs ♪
- It's gonna be so good.
It's gonna be so good.
- Dude, that fucking video, that music video,
"Heaven Don't Have a Name."
He's an unbelievable artist.
Have we talked about his music on here, right?
I don't know.
Probably not.
Yeah, we--
It's no surprise.
Pretty good.
You sound just like him.
You do sound just like him.
You could be a Renner.
You could be at--
I might drop an album.
You know that?
You should do a cover album of just Jeremy Renner songs.
I might write 10 to 12 songs.
I will write my own songs.
We definitely talked about his music on here.
We can still talk about it.
There's a place in Myrtle Beach called Legends.
- Yeah.
- Where you go there and they have like a
Michael Jackson guy and they have an Elvis guy.
- Oh my God.
- And you should go and you should be like
I could be a Jeremy Renner,
kind of look alike, sing alike.
- Well it's gonna be a problem if they amputate his leg.
I won't be a very good look alike.
- No it won't.
Have you ever seen--
- You'll just get in a wheelchair.
- Have you ever seen the fucking
Monty Python and the Holy Grail?
You think he actually lost all those limbs that night?
- Yeah he did.
- Bloody hell you're wrong.
- I'm completely right.
- You're a complete buffoon.
- You lot are--
- If you're believing.
That was that scene was what invented the word bloody for the British because they were like that's a muddy
That's bloody and brilliant. Yes, the scene is bloody. It's brilliant. Did you just say bloody brilliant?
Say this forever. Yeah, the
Celebrity I really love celebrities who do music. Yeah
Who else is good John Travolta never heard it. Oh my god that music dude. I'm
I've been watching it over and over.
You're so funny.
He did this music video for the movie Old Dogs where he does a cover of Every Little Step by Bobby Brown.
We need to do a phone recreation.
And he's singing it to his daughter.
It's the funniest music video I've ever seen.
Is it dope?
It's so dope.
It starts out, it's like him talking to his daughter, Ella Blue Travolta.
is John. I should have I should state the song is John Travolta
featuring Ella Blue Travolta.
Yeah. Wow.
And but her only in and they mix in clips from old dogs.
Yeah. Her only featuring part, though, is at the beginning where
she says, like, I want to live in a world that is full of cotton
candy and music.
And then the end is at the end of the music video where he looks
at her and goes, I wish I was part of your world.
Yeah. He says, I think we should be part of each other's worlds
forever.
He's also he like, yeah,
- How old is his daughter?
- His daughter's like eight.
- Yeah.
- Oh, okay.
- In the music video?
- Yeah, but the whole music video is him dancing around.
You can clearly tell his daughter's not fully into it.
And he's like dancing his heart out.
- Dude, he's going insane.
- There's a whole like 30 to 45 second part
where instead of dancing, they're on the computer.
And like, you can't see what's on the computer screen,
but it's like a computer in,
it's like this like white computer in a blank white space.
And it's just like John Travolta,
like pointing to the screen and going like,
like nodding and smiling and his daughter's like typing on the key.
Yeah.
And that's just like part of it.
That's adorable.
It's incredible.
She's watching like Barney on the computer too.
No, she's watching old dogs, right?
I thought there was one Barney.
She was going to be allowed to watch old dogs?
Yeah.
But there's a, the, I think it's supposed to be an homage to the, to the
original Bobby Brown, Every Little Step music video, but it's him like dancing
in between a big thing that says Travolta.
and he's but he's like doing like
like that that's it is a little blue there's what it is a little like that
like he's jumping through zone media
every that is also i think you like any does he does a lot of like around us
like these type of things
and then you know we don't think i watch the whole thing does the same when at the
end they like skip away and he like is skipping and shaking his hips and put it
at hands up in the air like this
do you say so it's probably the best video i'm not going to be taking that's
- Is that the number one celebrity music video?
- I think that is the--
- Music video, yeah.
- The top five celebrity music videos.
- It's really, really good.
- I think that's probably number three.
- How about Blame It by Jamie Foxx?
- That, no, no, no, no.
- Katherine Hagel is in that.
- That's a different subclass.
- And she acts like a hoe even though she's Mormon.
She shakes her butt.
- That's a fire ass song.
- A Mormon hoe?
- She shakes her butt in the fucking music video.
- Okay, I'm gonna have to see this.
- And she acts like a hoe to Jamie Foxx.
- What the mother fuck?
- And he's saying blame it on the juice.
She's drinking juice.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- She's drinking juice.
- Blame it on the coffee.
- She's a Mormon, what else is she drinking?
- Blame it on the soda.
- Blame it on the die, die, die, die.
- Blame it on the cussing.
- Blame it on the die and coke.
Blame it on the die, die, die, die.
- Yeah.
- Or, or, or, or, or, or, or, or, or, or, or, or, or, or.
- Yeah, they should have done a Mormon version of that song.
- She was in there, you know?
- But they should have done four Mormon.
man than Jamie Foxx. That's a hell of a man. Oh yeah dude. He's got a V taper. Have you
seen that um that video it's like Jamie Foxx somebody's like he's at a roast and
then somebody is up on the panel and they stole one of his jokes. And he
starts pretending to laugh and then doing the guy's conscience yeah. Yeah.
Yeah that's a great that's a classic video. He's a man. Jamie Foxx is unbeatable.
But I think that's a different subclass of celebrity music video though because
It's like that's genuine like talent like genuine like like a song you could play at the club
But like we're talking to every little step. We're talking we're talking
Rebecca Black Friday style music video exactly
I used to have I used to have a fantasy when I was a kid about
Meeting Rebecca Black and telling her that I didn't think the song was that bad and maybe we'd fall in love yeah
Yeah, she's a little Walmart. What I think she's a lesbian
I used to have a recurring dream where it was like all the celebrities everybody hated Rebecca Black Justin Bieber
I would be meeting them in a Walmart and I would tell them like hey, man
I actually think you're all right, and then we become like very good friends. Yeah, yeah, I
Had that with probably three or four different celebrities including Rebecca Rebecca Black Justin Bieber a couple other remember
There is Rebecca Black like it's all done by the FAO guys. Yeah, which they weren't my age
So that would have been a weird friendship. I think there were like 40. Redfoo and Blue. Blue. Blue.
Redfoo. Blue's close. Redfoo's white!
No he's not.
I don't know.
There was Rebecca Black Friday, but then there was also this other girl.
I think she's some kind of Hispanic.
Great. I'm failing today on race.
Yeah. There's the other one. I don't remember her name, but it's this song "My Jeans." Do you remember that?
They're all produced by the same guy.
Yeah, that's like the really little kid.
Yeah.
Ashley Tisdale is wearing my jeans.
That was a good one, yeah.
Kiki Palmer is wearing my jeans.
And it's the guy who raps in the Friday video.
He like pops up in the window and is like...
Yeah, the guy who's going down the highway.
We'd be on fire.
That guy, the guy who's driving the car, there's like a 20 second rap verse in Friday.
He produced all the music, all those music videos.
videos yeah what's his name is a pierre pierre from he's the pierre from playboy
cardi
I think that they had to pay him like $10,000 and the thing is those music
videos are pretty well produced you know I'm sorry your kid doesn't have talent
but that guy is not the issue
yeah Rebecca Black is not talented you just say that she's a lesbo that's why
saying that. Yep. You're just trying to get in her genes. I'm big in the lesbian community.
In what way? In what world? How are you big in the lesbian community? You don't know how
many fan letters I get from lesbians. Do you get letters from lesbians? I get letters from
lesbians. They all say, "I wish my girlfriend was as femme as you." That is sweet. "I wish
My girlfriend is a wimp like you.
My girlfriend is too tough.
My girlfriend is too fucking bush.
Why can't you be like this guy?
Just look at him. Just a wimp.
Look at this fucking wimp.
Yeah, you are kind of like...
I got told a lot by my ex's
friends that I was a male lesbian.
That's awful dude.
That's fucking awful.
I don't even understand that.
I would never ever let somebody say that to me.
I'd probably hit those girls.
hit him. Yeah. I wouldn't. I go like this.
And they're lesbians so they'd fall for it.
And then they'd hit their head on the wall.
Yeah. You must be a lesbian.
Lesbians are the only people that works on.
It's very, they're very easily hypnotized.
Yeah. Yeah.
They all got hypnotized by Daria when they were kids.
And then Drake stole my whole swag.
By saying.
He copied my whole flow.
He really did.
Bar for bar.
He really fucking did.
I don't want that many lesbians these days. Yeah, I think they don't
Lesbians love me
Actually, maybe not
Gay guys like me gay guys love you. I'm pretty much a gay guy
Superstar yeah, you are we got both ends of the spectrum, and I don't know what Cameron's got here Cameron is
Huge with animals yeah
In the animal community Cameron
Is a hit I
Got gay guys only some time
Gay, I gotta say gay guys are probably the number one kind of thing that I would like to be like surrounded by oh
number
Being like a like a d-list celeb and gay guys love you that is the list celeb
That is the thing cool if I ever if I ever decide to
I mean okay listen some people may construe may some people may construe this as homophobic
But I'd rather have a trillion dollars than be surrounded by gay guys
Hmm a trillion it's and if somebody will take those somebody takes that the wrong way not my problem
Okay, I want to be surrounded by a trillion gay guys like a movie scene in India where there's just like a
More like people even you were in the fucking world yeah, but I'm right in the middle
Just they're dancing a Caroline Polachek with you. Yep. That's right. So hot you're hurting my feelings and I'm doing all the
Yeah, I'm doing all the dance moves and shit and they're like, they're like, okay, you know, but it is good
Yep play that Caroline Polachek straight
But play that Caroline Polajek till you die
That honestly I remember hearing that song for the first time for that funky white white music
Play a lot of funky music every time I go to the touch tunes dude. I'm playing little baby as real as it gets
that's what I'm playing right and I'm looking around like somebody come on
give me some props for this somebody dap me up yeah come on please dab me I just
some so like as soon as the song comes on I'm standing in the middle of the bar
like this yep mm-hmm yeah yep I say I go to the touch tunes I
somebody all the little baby I head to the bar and I said let me get ten shots
of Hennessy I'm only gonna take one but any if anybody wants one somebody's
Williamsburg.
Yeah.
Some Williamsburg bar.
It's like, "Sir, we're --"
"We don't have Hennessy."
"We don't have Hennessy. We only do cocktails."
"Let me do Bacardi 151." That was discontinued 10 years ago.
Do you have any LSA?
Do you have any liquor that comes in a tiny bottle? We get 10 of those now.
Yeah.
You know, I was talking to somebody about it the other day. It was Dr. McGillicuddy's.
I want to have some Dr. McGillicuddy's again. It's been a very long time.
Yeah, dude. We've had a lot of them.
Yeah.
I want to have some Dr. McGillicuddy's again. It's been a very long time.
We get 10 of those now.
Yeah, you know I wanted I was talking about somebody about the other day was dr. McGirr. Yeah, dr. McGillicuddy's
Yeah, I want to do dr. I don't have some dr. McGillicuddy's again. It's been a very long time
Yeah, we should go to we should go to Boston. Can you not get it anywhere else? No, it's just where you should
It's not like Malort. You can't get Malort anywhere. You can you saw Malort? There's a bar on
There's a bar down the street and today's globalist world you can get anything anywhere
Yeah, there's a bar down the street that used to bootleg it until like three months. Okay. Yeah, literally anything
I go ahead try to find me a Faberge egg right now
Jubio you do that and no not on the web in physical reality. I'll go I have mine over here. Yeah, it's right there
That's a Cosby surprise egg. That is not a Faberge. All right fine thing
Oh, I like this one. I like this Faberge egg.
See, this is perfect. Giant egg in a brown egg cup mascot costume.
What is an egg cup? I remember seeing the fucking nerd from Jimmy Neutron
eating one in one of those movies.
It's like a soft-boiled egg in a cup and then you dip the bread.
It's a British thing.
I don't care for that much at all.
Speaking of mascots, I had the...
What's the best baseball mascot in your opinion?
- Nobody can read this by the way.
- Well, just go close up on it.
- It's gotta be the Philadelphia crazy guy.
- The Phanatic? - He's too scary.
- I don't know.
I was like, I looked up every single mascot
and I seen something that I'm like.
- The Philly Phanatic has the energy of a dog
that tries to fuck you.
It gets too excited and he gets like,
he's not humping your leg, he tries to fuck you.
The Philly Fanatic had the zoomies.
They would be like, oh yeah.
They gotta lock them in the stadium until he calms down,
tuckers himself out.
I was reading because I was like, oh like
what teams don't have
mascots and it's just the Dodgers and the Yankees
which I think that's disgraceful.
I'm gonna be the Yankees mascot.
Dodgers have a mascot. No they don't.
Me. Oh, okay. I'm being the Yankees
mascot and my mascot name is Cameron Jr.
The Yankees had a mascot
in 70 something
something called Dandy and they had to,
George Steinbrenner did not let,
I guess the Dodgers have a mascot, okay.
But the Yankees still don't have one.
- It looks exactly like Juvio.
- Yeah, I know.
(laughing)
- That is exactly what Juvio looks like.
- But the Yankees mascot,
the Yankees had this mascot named Dandy
and George Steinbrenner kept it in like the top row
of like the stadium or some shit,
like he kept it in like a box,
in box seats because he thought that somebody would go and beat the shit out of him.
You deserve it.
Dude, yeah, if you've seen this thing, Dandy, I would beat the, I would shoot that thing
with a shotgun.
Oh, Yankee Doodle Dandy, yeah.
I would shoot Dandy with a shotgun for sure.
That thing is scary.
You see Dandy come at you, you see Wally the green monster walking towards you, he looks
like Elmo.
He looks like green Elmo.
Why'd you search, you're just searching Yankee Doodle Dandy.
You're not looking up the mascot.
That's not gonna get you the mascot, buddy.
That's a movie.
Got at all.
James Cagney man that guy's funny.
Yeah.
Fuck me he's talented.
Oh but the the Astros
have an alien.
That's cool. That makes sense.
Yeah that is fucking cool.
Astros have the coolest everything
pretty much.
Yeah.
Dude those old Astros jerseys from
like the 70s those are fire.
Guy on the team named Bill Doran I
could get like the douchiest move
ever get like an Astros jersey with
my last name on it.
I want you to trow ass.
Yeah.
Trow that ass on me.
You know what team has a really cool logo?
Is the Fetter City Gangstas.
What's their logo?
It's just an F.
Speaking of gangstas, last night, okay, I forgot about this.
Last night, me and Cameron went to a barcade and they had a game that is the most fun arcade
game I've ever played in my life.
The best game I've ever played in my life.
I've never played a more fun arcade game.
What game is it?
It was called Namco Quick 'n Crash.
Or Quick 'n Shoot.
Quick Drive.
- No, it was Quick and Crash.
- Oh, the one, I know this.
- Namco Quick and Crash, that's what it was called.
- I know this is Barcade.
- Yeah, Namco Quick and Crash.
- Oh, this isn't the one I played.
- No, maybe it wasn't Crash.
- Yeah. - Oh, it was.
Yeah, yeah, that was it, no, not that.
- It's Nicktoons Nitro Racing.
- Yeah, that one.
So it's a shooting game.
No, we wanna see the actual one.
- It's that one right there.
- It's the one...
- It is a target shooting game.
- Yeah, I've played this.
- Where you quick draw.
Dude, we could not believe how fun it was.
- We spent so much money on this game.
- It was the most fun game I've ever played in my life.
- Caleb had it, so it scores you out of 100, right?
Like it says you're in the top whatever out of 100.
And Caleb had an insane round, and he got eight out of 100.
- I did.
- And I was like-- - Eight, eight.
- I had a really good round.
- And I was like, and this is what I was,
'cause I had one round right before that
that was really good, but I choked on the last part of it.
- You're a sharpshooter.
and I and I was like I know I can do better I can't I was saying I can't
leave this
barcade this hella fun barcade until
I get top 10 and Akil was like he just wants to beat my score
and I was like no I just wanna get top 10 I know I there's no way I can beat
top 8 but I'm gonna get top 10 Akil was like
you're gonna get you're gonna get 9 no way that you have a mental block
you're acting strange
oh wait wait wait and then I got exactly I got 9
I got top 10 but I didn't beat a score I predicted what I did exactly
one because you did what you were trying to do when you objectively lost.
So wait, you mean eight out of a list of 100, right? Not eight targets out of 100?
No, no, no.
In my head, I thought that you guys were saying...
No, that's what I said.
I thought you were saying Caleb had a good round. He shot eight out of 100.
No, I got every last one. By the way, you would stink at this game.
Yeah, no, I'm terrible at it.
No, no, you would lose the first one and then you would start doing 20 something.
I objectively lost, but I had incredible knowledge of my skill and Caleb didn't believe me.
I had a I had a decent round where I did my hat sideways, and I held the gun sideways
It wasn't decent it was pretty bad, and no I had a bad one where I shot behind my back
You also had a bad one where you shot sideways well
You didn't shoot side with a single time so your thug card you said nobody else could do it
Hand your thug card over, hand it over. Hold on. I'm waiting. I'm getting it Jesus fucking Christ. Please hand it over
I'm getting it hand that hand that that's gonna be early card. I bet
No, well what other card do I have?
I'm gonna do looks like I thought you had more cards in there. Okay here hold on wait
California driver's license
license number why so Eaton Lee
Curly Howard five to nine North Highland, Hollywood, California
Well wait to ten you don't strike me as 210. What's this one? This is class of 2015 London Derry Middle School
Patrick Doran you look like you were a cute little kid. I'd pinch your cheeks
Mm-hmm. I would have pinched your peep the peep the Boston Boston Red Sox
Zip up hoodie and the Star Wars shirt. Well. I was a fucking baller. Did you chew on the edges of this?
No, you did I didn't chew on the I gave it took a bite out of your chapstick last night
I'm not talking monster. You're an animal man. My photos like going so it's like almost gone
Oh, no, your middle school photos almost gone. They're gonna stop letting you into the middle school pretty soon. I
I already told you guys this, but yesterday I went to- I can't stop thinking about this.
Yesterday I got my blood drawn at the doctor, and they had the thing in me, and they were
pulling my blood out with the cable, and in the middle of it, the guy-
I wish my head had my thing in you.
The guy- and I was looking away, because I was like, I don't want to see the blood coming
out of me, because I don't like it.
And I was looking away, and I just heard the guy go, "Uh oh!"
And then he said- and I said, "What's wrong?
What?"
and he was like, "You're drying up.
"You don't have enough blood."
- That's crazy.
- And then he, there was like four vials.
- How much did they take, really?
- Well, it was like, they probably was like,
probably like eight vials or something.
- That's a lot.
- It was a ton, it was too much.
- Did you feel tired afterward and woozy?
- Yeah, I felt pretty dizzy.
And I was also saying to you, I really was hoping,
well yeah, so when he finished,
it started going really slow and hurting more,
and like each vial was only getting
like two drops of blood in it.
- Yeah, then like here at the end I was like,
is this like, am I all set?
Like what you said, I was like, I had no blood left,
am I okay, do I, do you need to do anything else
or do I just leave?
And he was like, nope, you just leave.
And I wanted so badly to stand up
and just faint onto the ground.
And then be able to come to him and be like,
look what you did to me.
- Yeah.
- Look what you've done.
- What have you done?
- You must have real chunks of blood.
- Fainting instantly and just being like stuck
on the ground.
- Yeah, he'd be like, look, look what you did.
- Why did you do that?
- Why did you do this to me?
- Why did you take my blood?
It really hurt!
I want my blood back!
Put my blood back in me right now!
It's scary dude.
But anyway, I got my blood test results and there were some exclamation points that said abnormal.
What's your blood type?
Oh you got your results already?
Yeah but just the chart or whatever
so it doesn't explain what anything is
it just says "this is abnormal"
and I don't want to google it.
What's your blood type?
I can read it.
I know mine. Actually I have my donor card.
I got a donor card. I just forget which one I am. I'm going to show this card on camera.
Okay, here we go. No, actually don't show it because then somebody could get my information.
Okay? If you take your wallet out, I'm allowed to show your card. Here, you can show it.
Caleb, get the cards in your fucking wallet. Holy shit. That's my dad's cards. You know
what we need to get, man? We need to get some Ridge wallets. We should share a wallet. We
We should have Ridge Wallet sponsor us, give us $60,000 a day.
Oh, I'm A+.
You're A+.
I got an A on my blood test.
What's this one?
A+.
Donor ID.
And then it went through the wash, so it has--
all of my dates are gone.
It's right next to Steven Vega, the pit bull.
Pit bull impersonator.
Yeah.
I'm glad you keep that in your wallet.
That's very sweet of you.
I think one day we'll need him.
Yeah.
What's going on in the world, man?
I feel like-- is there--
Is it just me or has there been like two weeks
where there's no news?
- Yeah, they're getting ready for something.
- What's the news?
- What's the news that there's been?
- There's some shit going on in Congress.
Matt Gaetz is, yeah, no, don't give a fuck.
- Renner.
- I mean cool shit like, brah, brah, brah, brah, brah, brah.
- Yeah, I think that will happen soon.
- Tatiana Patits.
- Patits?
- Come on, that's a crazy name.
- Supermodel of the '80s and '90s dies at 56.
- Wait, that's her?
I recognize that bitch.
- Oh yeah, she's from the Freedom 90 video.
- I don't know what that is.
George Michael?
Nah, no.
Freedom!
I'll say this.
I won't let you down, freedom!
I'm not usually one to enjoy the looks of supermodels, but that's a pretty decent looking
woman.
Yeah, I prefer girls next door.
Yeah.
Yeah, I just don't really like that Hollywood kind of thing.
I like kind of like milfy...
Yeah.
I'm imagining kind of the paradox where my brain explodes because I live next door to
Megan Fox.
And I'm like...
That would be crazy.
airbrushed and you're completely beauty standards,
but you're literally a girl next door.
So what do I do?
- We need a girl next door.
- Do I fuck you or not?
(laughing)
- Do I fuck you or do I?
- I'm knocking on our door, what do I do?
- Do I have sex with you now?
- Are you too supermodely or are you a girl next door?
- I really can't tell.
So should I just fuck you now?
- You're gonna love this movie.
- What?
- The Girl Next Door.
- What movie is this?
guess what the plot is tell them pray tell do am I in it no oh Paul Dan I
don't really know you kind of all Dan a type of a no thing and Paul Dan oh it's
a mean thing to see you not famous main character that's what you say yeah
that's the that's the thing you say yeah you realize you compared somebody to
someone someone really yeah yeah yeah you're a playboy yeah yeah anyway no
like funny funny and timeless yeah like Danny DeVito yeah a celebrity yeah
- Yeah.
- That's what I meant.
- A Playboy model moves in next door.
- Bro.
- To me?
- To a boy.
- Oh, I'm not in, I forgot I'm not in this movie.
- To a bro, to a bro.
Playboy model moves in next door.
- You're telling me Paul Dano plays a bro?
- Wait, it's just a bro and a Playboy?
I don't wanna see that.
- It's actually, no, it's actually a nerd.
- I wanna see a neighbor and a neighbor.
- It's a nerd.
- A nerd.
- A nerd, and I'm pretty sure it's a meal...
Hirsch.
- Oh.
- Meal likey, this idea.
- Yeah.
- I'm pretty sure.
anyone like he did in real life.
He hushed a lot of people.
He did?
Especially when he played Jay Adams
in Lords of Dogtown.
Who did he hush?
Jay Adams hushed a lot of gay people.
I don't know who that is.
I never heard of that guy.
I hushed that he hushed people.
That's why he's not in movies anymore.
Allegedly hushed people.
I read that on his Wikipedia.
I read it in an email.
- I read it.
- Could you email that to me so I can hear about it?
- Yeah, sure.
- Thank you.
(laughing)
- I read on his Wikipedia, it was like personal life.
- Personal life.
(laughing)
I read it on his Wikipedia, it was like,
Hirsch was like arrested for like assaulting someone,
and then said like, right under it said like,
Emil Hirsch is also a collector of fun socks.
- I did Hirsch that he Hirsched a female was the problem.
- Oh, he was hershing females.
- Yeah.
- Wow, that's awful.
- And you can't do that as a meal in today's society.
- That's a good point, that's a good point.
- That's good.
(laughing)
- Society's good.
- Yeah.
Oh, no, but ultimate nerd and girl next door dynamic
is Sam Witwicky and Megan Fox.
- I really thought you were gonna say Bumblebee
and then I would've agreed with you.
- Bumblebee is kind of the third wheel.
- Is Bumblebee, is Bumblebee like,
- Is he like a dog level intelligence?
Or is he--
- Well he doesn't have-- - He can't talk?
- He just can't speak.
- Yeah, he only speaks through the radio?
- He's lassie, basically though.
- He speaks at one time though.
- But they definitely--
- He says, "I wish to stay with the boy."
- I'll say that in this movie.
- They definitely--
(laughing)
Yeah, that guy, that's definitely an animal.
- They definitely treat him like less than the other bots.
- Oh yeah.
- He's treated as--
- Well he's also-- - Not even Bumblebee was--
I don't know much about Transformers lore.
So Bumblebee was made for that movie?
What?
Was he made for the Transformers movies?
No, I don't think so.
What?
I thought that he was like a Michael Bay OC.
No.
Oh, I don't know. I'm 90% sure that's not true.
Well, you are the Transformers expert.
I don't know. I've only watched the Michael Bay movies. I don't know anything about him.
You are going to become my Transformer. I'm going to transform you into a girl.
But he's the stupid one because he wants to hang out with the humans.
All the other guys, all the other Autobots
are like, they do their thing
and they're killing the Decepticons,
but Bumblebee's like, I wanna drive around with this guy.
I wanna watch him have sex in my backseat.
- I want this high schooler sitting in me.
- Yeah.
- Farting on me.
- This looks like-- - You think he farts in him?
- Definitely.
- He definitely, wait, he definitely fucks Megan Fox
in Bumblebee. - That's what I'm saying,
in the backseat. - Oh my God.
- That's cool, the coolest part about that movie
is Megan Fox opens up his guts and shows him her boobs.
- That is true.
Yeah, that is true.
That is true, yeah.
He's doing the pose, yeah.
She's leaning over what is probably like his heart and his lungs and stuff.
Not his eyes, for God's sake.
Imagine that.
Where is his head?
Imagine the hottest woman in the world flaying you open.
That would, if that was doctors, I'd be getting surgery every day.
You made a good point.
I'd be getting a damn prostate exam.
She showed her boobs to the wrong part of his body.
Do you imagine a girl, Megan Fox shows her boobs to your butt.
Yeah.
Oh, what a waste.
I know, complete waste.
Imagine a boob going into your butt.
That's a waste.
Might as well be a fucking balloon.
Hey, I don't know if it hits the right spot.
What kind of boob would hit your G-spot?
How shallow is your G-spot?
Probably real shallow.
Your prostate's like poking out of your asshole.
It's so swollen.
It's a big red point.
It's a big rock.
It's a big risen and evil boss weak point.
Yeah, yeah. One of those 50s cone boobs.
What happened to those? Why did that?
Why did that go out of vogue?
No, what? Why did they exist?
Was it chemicals or was it the shape of the bras?
It was chemicals.
The torpedo thing, the puffy nipples.
Pretty crazy, man.
You go back and you like look at old Playboys and shit and all the girls have
the their boobs are like 15 inches in front of their body.
Scary.
Yeah, I don't really like Playboy.
It looks like a librarian's weekly.
The slope is like a double black diamond.
It's like, could be dangerous to ski that.
The K-12.
You know why?
Because Dan Schneider hates it.
That's a better off dead joke.
Remember that movie?
Have you guys seen it?
No?
All right.
No.
OK, Dan Schneider, John Cusack.
John Cusack tries to kill himself because his girlfriend left him.
And then he meets his French girl next door.
I'm sensing a theme.
I'm sensing a theme in my pants.
And then the hamburgers come to life.
I'm sensing a cream.
The hamburgers come to life and they sing Van Halen.
Friend, you've lost the plot.
I've not lost the plot, mate.
No.
Mate, I have not lost the plot.
Bruh, let's change subjects.
You lot are afraid.
Us lot are not bloody afraid.
Yep.
My two mates right now are pretty much--
they've cacked their trousers.
Hey.
You better watch it.
Watch it.
You better watch your tone.
You guys are being bloody ignorant.
I'm not.
You're acting like a Tory.
I'll rip you.
I'm not acting-- hey!
Don't ever say I'm acting like a you're acting like a fucking Tory not gonna rip your Todger off
He's gonna take your Todger with me hands put it in your mouth. You're not gonna touch me Todger
I'll touch her and your arse. I'll touch you Todger and your arse all day. You're not gonna put my Todger in my arse
I'm gonna drop your I'll drop your Todger in the loo. I will say better not
You better not you better take that back. I refuse to make it back mate
I'm a serious your Todger's in the loo mate you better
I have anything to say about that.
Your Todger's going in the loo.
It's going directly into the loo.
Speaking of Todger, did you guys hear that Prince Harry audiobook thing where he says
like...
I think it was fake.
Was that fake?
Of course it's fake.
Crap.
What was fake?
It's like a thing where like...
Wait, the meme lord?
The meme god is telling us a meme?
No, I think I just fell for some shit, but it was like a guy saying like in Prince Harry's
voice, "They told me that I should put me mom's lipstick on me Todger."
He thought it was real. Yeah. You thought it was real?
Speaking of funny Twitter stuff, actually something funny I saw.
Oh shit. Was that fake?
You're blowing my fucking mind right now.
What, you think that was real?
I don't know, he's a weird guy. There's no way that's real.
Do you think that's how you would have felt?
Do you think that was in the audio book and there was no article about,
they've been posting articles about him,
what he said in that book or whatever for weeks.
Yeah, you're right. I think they didn't do that one.
Apparently there was some... I fell for it.
I've got egg on my face.
- There was some comic book--
- This motherfucker ate the onion.
- Yep.
- There was a comic book recently
where the Joker got pregnant.
- I seen that.
- And I saw on Reddit,
there was somebody on the comic book subreddit
posted a clip of Fox News talking about this comic
where the Joker is pregnant.
And I didn't watch the clip,
but everyone in the comments is like,
I can't believe they're talking shit about this comic
like the Joker's pregnant.
And one of the top comments was,
Yeah, it's like they don't even know that the reason the Joker is pregnant is because he's under a spell.
[laughter]
I was--
You'd think they could at least do the research before they talk shit about this comic.
I did see the pregnant Joker thing. That was the first thing I've seen in a while where I was like--
I didn't see it. I wanna see it.
Yeah, that's pretty stupid, man.
Well, he's under a spell.
There's already so much--
But the spell thing makes me--
It was so funny.
There was like--
They're literally not--
They're not--
You found it?
conscious lambs biden's box check yeah i'd i'd love to see what the slam some concha
i'd like to have a check out a box i'm gonna be checking some boxes and slamming concha
if you scroll down i bet you can see the comment where they say it's under a spell
let's see here
this is going to be this is getting a grander the fucking legend i love it i like how he
acknowledges the joker was a victim the victim of a spell realizes this would contradict
his rant and decides to brush it all away to complain about nothing.
Ingenuity positive 123, that is an awesome Reddit username. Yeah, the Pregnant Joker,
it did turn me on a little bit.
Yeah.
Just like to know.
I mean, I haven't seen what he looks like, but the idea of it.
He looks good.
The idea of it is making my, it's making the front of my pants pants.
It's one of the comic books they do nowadays where it looks like children's book art.
Yeah.
I want to see it.
It looks pretty bad show me pregnant. You know what I want. You know I want them to bring back
What was like the the badass DC comics called? Oh?
Image no not a new 52. No they're like oh
This is the fuck you versions with the oh sickos like Sandman and shit
Watchman no the one day was like a different whole lot there. It is there's the pregnant Joker. That's the Joker is now pregnant
Oh my god. Yeah, well. I think a spell y'all. I think you're pregnant. I think you're right
No, but you guys know what I mean, I'm not sure Lee field drawings. It was just like the
DC have like a vertigo vertigo. That's what it is. Yeah. Yeah, I think so. Yeah, it was like the
That's where like Constantine is bad-ass crap. Yeah, I want them this
How I want to all the badass comics are the best they need to do a pregnant Constantine. Yeah. Yeah, that's a great idea
They should just do pregnant all of them. Yeah, there's a Rorschach would be you know
They always do like a gender flip or whatever to me. Yeah, they need to do a pregnant
I'm trying to get my foot this fucking baby out of me with my grappling hook gun. Yeah, that'd be pregnant Rorschach
But you don't want to see his gender reveal party
Be like yeah, what is this gender look like you say I don't fucking crap yeah
Yeah, just this baby is made out of crap. It's my crap
Completely out of crap what a Wonder Woman got pregnant. Oh my god. I hope it would be my kid
What would her pussy even look like if she got pregnant probably like us like a not not woman gal gado
What would her pussy look like?
Changes once you turn it into a real woman
Why look at all these is this the Joker got these women pregnant Joker got starfire power girl
Why is he standing there? Why does he stand there looking like fucking Prince?
You know all these women. I knew all the women tell you what would would would not because her heads backwards and would
That's my
Well Joker's that obvious yes, okay, I got to see if the car one night with the drapes
Anybody would take one night with it. No I'm seeing
Yeah, that's right. I'm gonna have him fall
Yo, you know Joker Joker has to be laying the bomb-ass dick of Harley Quinn staying with him after all these years
Harley Quinn is a bad B. Yeah, I'll fucking say it. She's a badie
I want to watch
Harley Quinn dance to a Cardi B song yeah in the club
Oh, my dance to her own song by Chief Keef Harley Quinn Chief Keef Harley Quinn that song
She could dance to that she didn't make that song though. She could dance to it though. She could shake
Circus music working
That's a thing and you know you know because crazy women got the best pussy
Her pussying would be so fucking tight and wet on your shit, bro
Oh my god, and she probably would touch your balls. She wear high heels to dinner. Oh, she's a freak
Oh, she'll really she be literally a free to be two inches
She's a circus freak mm-hmm as you brought wrong as fuck pick you up ponytails. Uh-huh all I'm saying yep
Yep, damn. She's funny. I thought about bra only yeah
Bralette hair fetishes. Yep hair fetishes
You just thwomped
Did a full thwomp just clear my throat. I think how you clear throat. I've known you for 40 14 years. Yeah
I've been clear if you you just haven't paying attention. That's how I've been clear
I've always been paying attention to you. You're not enough to know that my throat clearing you the main attraction throat pying
They're up. Oh, I'd like to throw pie Harley Quinn. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, or with win Harley some random fucking guy in college
Quinn Harley I do remember when Harley remember that blonde bastard with that curly hair
He would go surfing and motorcycle back and I'd look at him. I say if your name was backwards
I'd be throw pine you pretty soon
Oh, you're right, yeah, that's a thing you cream pie in the face
Oh, and then she and then it blows up cuz she's a fucking evil clown. Yeah, I'd have a gun
I'd have a gun and then I pull the trigger and a flag comes out the yeah
I'm gonna bang you I was gonna say do you think when Harley Quinn gives birth like before like you know and you
They push out the placenta first. Oh
Do you think it'd be what the hell that says bang?
No, when you come on to her face the flag comes out and it says salty sperm
- She takes a flag out.
- A bunch of tiny flags.
(laughing)
It all says slurp.
- Flags all, like the fake Skittles commercial.
- It's all flags.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- It's all flag based.
- She's got a lot of red flags there,
but it'd be so worth it.
- I don't even care.
- Be so worth it to feel her pussy.
- Oh my God.
- Oh crap.
- I just wanna see what her clothes look like
when she's not wearing them.
- I bet she's got a big clit.
I bet she does.
- If she was in my bedroom,
and we were gonna get it on,
I would arrange her clothes on the ground to be shaped like her.
I want to be stuck in an elevator with her.
Because you know shit's going down in the DM.
It go down, it go down.
She's probably going to let out a noxious, gaseous fart.
Hello, Harley Quinn.
In the envelope.
Might I please go down on you?
And you could fart in my face?
I was trying to say elevator, it said envelope-inator.
[LAUGHTER]
That's the thing, you wouldn't want to be--
you wouldn't want to have your-- that's a bad time
to not get a boner.
She's gonna roast you Jeff Ross style.
Shit.
Until you cry.
Imagine if Jeff Ross roasted your boner.
Imagine if Jeff Ross' brain was a hot ass girl.
Jeff Ross.
Wait a second, Liza Lampanelli.
Holy shit, she's fine.
Jeff Ross is doing cock ratings on OnlyFans.
Cock roastings on OnlyFans.
That would be awesome.
Do you see some guy, he like did a...
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah. He accidentally got a guy on death row.
Yeah, because the guy was like in jail or something.
did like a jailhouse roast thing. He was like awaiting trial. And I guess part of the roast
was like he was doing crowd work with the guy and the guy was like, "Yeah, plus I murdered
my wife!" And now, and then in the jury, or in the trial, they were like, "We have video
of this guy saying that he murdered his wife at a comedy show."
It's like an outtake that's on like the DVD where he's like talking to him one-on-one,
I think.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
I just invented the middle part, but yeah, I think he gave it up.
hair you probably would want a middle part. You probably want some more hair.
You got Jeff Ross on the brain, I'm trying to do the roasts.
What's that about man? That's hurting me. Yeah?
That's fucking hurtful, yeah. That's hirschful. You're hurting my femelings.
Is emeal pattern balding? I'm emeal... Come on man.
I'm sorry that I hirsched your feelings. You hirsched my femeelings pretty bad.
I'm sorry that I hearst your familings.
Thank you.
Bastard.
You're one of the lords of Dogtown.
You're a bastard.
The lords.
I think that you could get it in with the girl next door.
You think I could bang a girl next door?
Girls next door don't want anything to do with me.
I don't want to harp on this,
but if I live next to four or five girls ...
Girls next door ...
I don't even want to finish.
Girls next door stereotype me because of how I look.
Really? Yeah, they say I should be a gardener.
You're not so much a boy next door type.
I'm not, no. Yeah, you're not made for that.
People say I'm a gardener or some crap like that.
You know that Drake and Josh episode where they had that song
about the girl next door? No.
Kind of puts all the Dan Schneider stuff into ...
You're like, "Oh, why are these kids talking about this?"
Not the 50 girls that were like,
"Yeah, I used to lick my feet in the craft services room."
It's just like one that's getting glossed over.
It's like, "Why the fuck is Drake Bell
singing about fucking the girl next door.
- 'Cause he's supposed to be a kid in the show.
He is a kid in the show.
- It's weird that they were talking about,
they were singing about fucking a kid.
- I don't think that they even fuck.
- A lot of nice girls don't like me
'cause they think I look too much like a motorcycle.
- Here's the worst part about the girls next door
is they don't suck cock.
- They don't?
- No, 'cause they're too good.
- Okay, I'm done with these.
- Nah, they're too good.
- I'm going online to buy a wife.
- Sometimes I'll let you do anal, though.
- Are you dead?
I'm dead serious. Yeah. They'll let you do anal sometimes.
You're daft. You're cray. Sorry am I being crass?
You're being daft as well. Am I working a bit blue today?
You are bloody daft. You're wearing blue.
I worked. You're wearing blue.
I did anal with a girl next door. For real?
No. But doesn't that,
but wouldn't that give me some serious points
on the crack.com forums? That would get you cred.
That would get you cred for sure.
That would get me cred in a major way.
Yeah. Yeah.
Damn. Imagine if you lived in a cul-de-sac
It's like you know like 10 or 20 girls next door or if you're gonna go to a football game
Cheerleader oh my god in the middle of the field yeah, maybe underneath the tackle pile so no one can see it
What if the girl was a scientist and she wanted to do an experiment on your butt?
I'm like first of all take those glasses off second of all take that lab coat off third of all take my pants off and
Fourth of all take all my sperms out of my balls
Extract yep you need an emergency extraction on my sperms that would be so hot to date a surgeon
I would give her a numbered list.
I'd give her instructions.
How hot would it be to date a surgeon and she could literally open up your nut sack, take
your balls out, put them in her mouth, and spit them back?
I've never seen that.
Really?
Yeah, basically.
Wait, thanks for spoiling the movie for me, you fucker.
I like to spoil a woman's boobies.
I completely spoiled the movie.
I'm really fucking horny all this talk.
It made me horny.
I have to pee so bad.
We just haven't fapped in a while.
We all need to fuck something and fap on it.
Wait, does that say 69th annual?
Yeah, bro that actually that has fucking fire. Oh, maybe you want ever got it never noticed that it's a 69th annual
Why are you wearing a your hat that says you put the stickers on video you put this sticker on my hat
I don't know what you're talking about you did that and I had nothing to do it because I don't I'm not a
Schemer a schemer. I'm not a schemer. You're a schemer, so we're gonna put that over there now moving on
Okay, two different girls that I want to do anal with yeah
The librarian the scientist the mathematician fucking biologist and anatomy expert rogue
Rogan not someone who was on Rogan who's got a connection. He had a got the connect
He had a hottie on really of the fear factor keeper on babes of fear factor get a babe be be keeper
Okay, yeah, I'm officially hard as fuck a baby keeper. No a beekeeper, and I was I don't want a baby keeper
I want one who will get an abortion bees. I don't want my baby keeper when I
Keepers you know I don't want her to keep a BB. She doesn't want to keep the BB. She was I don't want her good
I don't want her she doesn't she wants to stop her shing the bees I want her to be meals. Do you meet it from her?
body
Buddy Neil an abortion
That's what I want
After I cream you hire her baby
Baby, I don't think I think I need you to get an abortion. I'm not ready for a feeling
I'm sorry. I cream meal pie. I sorry. I cream meal pie you I'm not ready for a family and you have to get an aversion
And I don't want to hurt your feelings about this whole thing
But I know that I know that females like you I know I get it. I'm the meal you're the female
It should be your discussion, but no
But no no no
Here's what I want to meet. I want to meet a hot meek. I want to meet. Here's who I want to meet.
A hot girl beer keeper. A beer keeper. Yeah, St. Pauly girl.
Why did you sound exactly like fucking Larry King right then? St. Pau-
You did- you can't do it again. I will not be able to do it again. You sounded exactly like Larry King.
Yeah. Yeah, it really scared me. I wish I sounded more like Don King.
What does he sound like? I don't know. Mmm, Don King Kong. Don King Kong. Mm-hmm.
Which is a versions a Lee Miguel
What
That one didn't even work. You have to go do it in a back alley meal. Yeah
Now that's we completely lost it. It's done. We lost the plot mate. Yeah, you've lost a bloody plot
Lee meal
Not making any sense anymore
meal Gil and
Me what is his name? I forgot what his name is email Hirsch
No, it's not working at all even that sounds wrong just saying his name. I just illy meal gill
No, it's not are you saying illegal? Are you trying to say legal? No, that doesn't sound right. You know meal goal
Emil goal sounds better. Oh, no meal goal. No meal goal. Yeah, we'll meal meal meal
You're hurshing my fucking brain right now. My brain is hirsch. Okay. Sorry. It should be a meal goals for you to hursh
My brain like this, okay
Okay, we're done
We're done anything another movie where he's in spiel
racer speed meal
Stop guys stop
Off this is terrible don't go to spiel meal glaze richer
You're saying nothing
You're saying fucking nothing
We're not nothing right now eat meal racers
Turning off the microphones this makes no sense
What do we do we're not gonna turn minutes where the mics are completely off that's no I don't actually want to do
One minute where the mics are off
That would be experimental that would be we'd be breaking new grounds. I'm so glad you didn't say experimentally
No, we're not gonna turn yep, we're fuck me we were leeling them on no
We're you need to stop doing this right right now not turning them you need to stop doing this right now because this is not
This is not okay. We're not gonna turn the mics osh
that
Hirsch osh
You are you suck what else happened? Who's his wife wait? Who's a meal Hersh's wife?
Hmm looks like aria Ariana Grande was a Jameela Jameel. Oh, no way her name is
*laughter*
No man, no!
No!
Jamila Emeal
Jamila Emeal calls out
Emeal Hirsch for
Oh no, ok, so Jamila Emeal
calls out Emeal
for his Hirschful babe
*laughter*
No!
I can't believe it's Jamila Emeal
That is so fucked up!
Jamila Emeal calls out
the
So
A meal her meal her I literally don't even know this fucking guy is that's the worst part
I've never seen Lord's a dog town and speed racers
No
Not from speed racer. Yes. He is he plays speed racers
He plays speed meal ratio in the Wachowski sisters speed. Oh, he was he played into the wild guy that guy
Did he get eaten by a bear is that a different dude? That's a different?
Grizzly man, you know the wild guy just like went into a van and was like I'm just gonna die here
Yeah, right what an idiot what his middle name is Davenport. Let's work that in okay?
Is Emil from Halo reach black
What?
No, Emil is actually white
says
somebody on the
Is Emile Hirsch related to Leonardo DiCaprio?
What ethnicity?
How old is Emily Hirsch?
Is Emile from Halo Reach black?
Who is the tallest Spartan in Halo?
Why did Emile have a scratch in his visor?
What race is Cortana?
Why was Cortana blue than purple?
Cortana's original design was based on the Egyptian Queen Nefertiti.
Does Cortana have a crush on Chief?
What's the answer to that?
It's a romance.
It should be called Halo A Love Story.
- Bartana and Master Chief are in love.
- Master Chief. - Master Chief.
- No!
No.
Oh, fuck me, man.
- That's horrible.
- This is the worst day of my life.
- That's worship.
- Stop!
This is the worst day of my life.
- The worst day of my life.
- Man.
No, no, no, no.
- No, it's done, it's done.
- It's over.
It is over.
- No.
I said just said it's over it's over no we're not doing any more yeah it's over
it's over we're not doing any more you're saying it like you're about to
throw an sh in there but I did it uh no you didn't see ch-pounder reef how old
is Cortana human ears three four three believes Cortana's eight years old at
the beginning of a four holy shit is that true that's not cool they're in love
of
well how old is master chief this your burn
he's more than eight he's more than double
that we don't know he's
he's always wearing a suit we don't know
49 years old and okay 560 but that's just
physically it says how old is master
chief physically oh yeah so mentally he's
eight did you guys ever read fall of
reach the the no dan uh i ain't read that
was like one of the first that's the book
that people don't read it's so sick dude
i wish i'd read the so bad read it he got
No, we have like two minutes. We're almost done.
We're hushing my bladder.
You just want to, you don't even have to pee.
I do have to pee so bad.
Hushing my bladder is weak sauce too. Hushing was the first one.
Yeah, that's right.
And we're, it's over. It's over.
That book's good though. He gets kidnapped.
He gets kidnapped.
Master Chief does? Yeah, he gets kidnapped.
I didn't think that could happen. Yeah. Well, that's where he gets started.
The beginning of the book is like
a woman's walking around different planets
and she sees his ass. Is it a prequel?
It is a prequel. Yes. And Master Chief is basically selected for the Spartan program because he's
a bald little white kid.
Oh, hey, good news. Emile Hirsch was in The Mudge Boy.
I want to hear about Fall of Reach.
It's a really, really good book. I highly recommend anybody read it.
Yeah, maybe I'll read it.
Especially if you're a Halo fan like myself.
I don't really know anything about Halo.
I haven't played the last, I think they kinda started doing some stupid shit.
I think, honestly, I can't remember but I think Halo might have gone woke.
I think, uh, for real?
Yeah.
To me, I just feel like if I'm gonna play Halo I'd rather play some horrible indie game arena
shooter that's two times faster.
Halo goes woke.
You're on a circle jerk subreddit, Jubio.
Everybody is welcome except gamers.
Another TV show ruined by identity politics.
Oh, yeah, I forgot they did the TV show and everybody but the real complaint was that there's no master chief in it
Yeah, there is it no
I don't think so I think it's like remember when they used it when they said that Peter Jackson was gonna do like a halo
Yeah, whatever. It's a little bit fucking insane. That would have been so fucking I was just making what Beatles the movie
No, thanks. We already have that. Help. He's not even making any across the universe. It's called help
No help me away from watching this movie. Sorry. You'll have a lonely Hearts Club, man. Yeah, and the yellow submarine
Oh, just naming yeah
No, they're not there's a Beatles movie hard day's night. Yeah, no
hurt oh
Hard day's night. Oh, okay a hard day's night. Yep. Just a hard day's night with no words switched into
Yeah, nothing switched even a little bit not even a that
Even the easiest I listen. I'm just glad the Beatles aren't alive to see what the Tories have done to this country
Yeah, there's one or two Beatles that are alive one or two. Yeah, not for long disputed on whether or not that's really Paul
That's one of the greatest documentaries ever made. Mm-hmm, and I I haven't watched it in probably ten years
I need to rewatch it Paul. I watched it when I was 10 years old and I think
Like you know, it's like that part in the documentary where it gets really serious and like the screen
It's like whatever and then I think my dad opened the door and I went like
So scared you got scared. I thought that I was I thought that I was a scary documentary
It's it's shot in the same way that those are edited the same way that those like
Scientology documentaries are on YouTube where like they use like red words all the time right? Yeah
Music X-Files theme. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Do you think this Church of Scientology may come for us over for what we said about the disappearance of Shelly misc of it?
I we did a whole episode where you audited me. Oh, yeah
That's it that was pro Scientology. Yeah, I say I'm
Slightly pro I'm leaning towards it. Yeah, they have a beautiful Lee was in it. I'm willing to hear
I'm willing to hear them out. That's the thing Leah Remini is you're like
You're going there in the coal mine. Hey, she was a bitch on King of Queens exactly yeah
Also, you could get a hotter girl
Then Leah Remini yeah, right there's some fi-ass
Fiat celebrities and if they can get me doing stunts like Tom Cruise it isn't even on a smaller scale
I don't need to do the job. We can loop back to that
To play us out and watch the whole no we won't every
Scientologist video every Scientologist has a pretty good life
Yeah, you know Aaron Cairo and every other person has a pretty shit life. I'd say Aaron Cairo professional skateboarder from the
San Francisco Bay Area. He's teaching everyone how to do kickflips and skate
in glass skateboards. We already talked about this guy. He's in the Scientology DVDs.
Do Scientologists have heaven? Yeah. Yeah, yeah, okay. They do. I don't really know what they mean.
It's a volcano though. Oh no, no, no, no, no. The volcano. You're thinking of bionicles.
No. They live in a volcano. There's so many parallels to bionicles in Scientology.
Mask of Light.
Dianetics.
Bionicolonics.
Yup.
The Piraka.
We have to put these two together.
Piraka Obama is a Scientologist.
We put these two things, two religions together.
Bionicology.
Piraka and Dianetics, or Bionicles and Dianetics.
Science, Scienceicles.
If we get them together.
Bionicology.
I said that first.
You did?
I didn't hear it.
I was lost in my thought.
But, we get that together.
We get together like this you went like this and you're tickling you will have the greatest cult in the world
It's not a cult neither as a culture
Yeah, no no no they aren't cults we will make a cult all right
I'm starting to dislike your attitude, so I'm ending the episode now, okay
Yeah, the way that you're talking is play play that John Travolta song train. Don't try that play song tray that John Travolta song
Don't wait. What is this don't do it. Don't worry about it. Bye bye
Berserking
(laughing)