(Woo! by the Beatles)
That was such a weak fucking woo.
He said slate again? Slate it again!
(No)
Oh he said no.
He said no we're starting.
That was a weak woo. Woo again.
(Woo!)
It's loud but it doesn't have energy behind it.
It just it sounds like you're really tired. I am a little tired
Like that you know it has to have like some some punch hurting my fucking ears. Yeah, well you do one
I think I should scream as much
Rip this stitches out. Yeah, you think you can rip your stitches. I can feel them dissolving right now, which is a dissolving kind
Yeah, water soluble. They didn't just glue it now. I wish they glued my head clothes when I was a child
Yeah, that popped it over my head. Here you can actually see the scar now. Holy shit this one. Yeah, whoa
Yeah, I told you
Yeah, my brother threw that big Millennium Falcon at my head
And you went to the hospital for that. Yeah, I got to get had to get staples. Oh my god. They stapled a patch of
Something on in my head listen. This is because you had a you have had so many head injuries in your life
I think you're perfect for this conversation. Uh-huh. We were talking about on the way over here
And can't really kind of candy
Not best probably even worse probably even stupider than that. Yeah, what when so a whale? Oh, yeah
This is your question, yeah, so well, this is my yeah, well, this is it's just a fun story brain to decode
It's a thinker of like what you have to there. Okay. Well, it's just a thing I said, okay
Which is that when you think about it right so whales they're mammals right they have lungs they're not fishes
Which means that because of that because of how evolution works they they were fish first
Because everything was fish first, and then they came out on land, and they got lungs and then they were like nah
And then they went back now this sucks
Why do they didn't even have gills
We're way worse
We can't breathe this water but we want to be in here really bad.
The whales literally were like, "Fuck this man, I'm going back in the fucking ocean."
I'm sitting in the water until I evolve to be in here.
Yeah, that's right.
I'm going to sit in this water until these legs come off.
I'm going to sit in the water and I'm going to die, and my son's going to die, and his
son's going to die.
We're going to keep dying until we figure this shit out.
But in about 40,000 years, it's going to pay off.
We're going to get a little hole on top.
(laughing)
- We're just gonna keep fucking 'til someone gets a hole
in the top of their head.
How fucking awful is that?
- I'm gonna fuck a whole new hole into my wife
so that she can breathe underwater.
- Dude, and then I was saying,
they probably, millions of years passed, right?
They probably feel so good 'cause humans are on land,
they're enslaving wolves, they're slaughtering cows.
All these mammals who stay on land,
the whales are like, get fucked.
You guys are getting owned.
And then the 1800s come around, Captain Ahab,
He's out there.
They almost extincted the whales.
They never did that to cows.
- Captain Ate Crap.
Yeah, he's a piece of crap.
- But also, whales had been getting their blubber
munched on for hundreds of years
on the north side of the world.
- That's true.
- But that was just like a bad neighborhood.
- But that doesn't count.
- They were like, we gotta stay away from them.
- Which whale is it?
- It's just so funny, for millions of years,
they were like, yeah, that's right.
We go underwater.
You can't get us.
And then we came up with a sharp thing on a string.
- There's two whales that have been--
- That pretty much defeated them.
It's like a whale, it's...
Okay, there's one type of whale--
- This was important to interrupt with.
- You are remembering Avatar.
- There's a whale that hates orcas so much
that they will like purposefully get in front of them
when they're trying to eat seals.
- Just to block 'em?
- Yeah, just to like, fuck you.
You fucking stupid. - Is that true?
What whale is it, which whale?
- I think it's, I don't know.
- Was it Moby Dick?
- I think it's sperm whales.
- That's the only whale I know.
Come on, man. - And get, yeah, get this.
- Shut the fuck up. - They called the whole whale
a sperm.
- No, it was the stuff inside their head was a sperm.
They had sperm inside their brains.
- Can you not be a nerd for one second?
- It's called spermaceti.
- Can you take one fucking second?
By the way, spermaceti--
- Literally they named it that because it looked like sperm.
- That's what you were named. - Looked like sperm
and vermicelli.
- They killed a sperm whale and they cut open its head
and it was filled with sperm and they went,
"Whoa, this is a sperm whale!"
- And they ate it like spaghetti.
- And that was-- - And it was spermaceti.
- That's where the term thick ropes comes from.
Mm-hmm you busted and utter looks like spaghetti. Yeah, what yeah, but I have never had a nut that looked like fucking spaghetti
Yeah, well you didn't change your diet. Yeah, no
You eat spaghetti you you come spaghetti, I don't think so
I think so everyone saw I'll have an alarmingly big jizz and I'll go ah
Yeah, yeah
That's cuz that would probably would have been the one that had a that made a kid if I didn't shoot it inside of a fucking
some old underwear mm-hmm
With a sleeve of a shirt you ever do
Well, I don't want to do sleeve of shirt, I'm afraid what if it goes out the other sleeve it goes all over the wall
Yeah, or the ceiling okay fucking Superman. How powerful is your fucking come there's like goes into the other room
How fast does it come out again? It's like I think it's a hundred million miles per hour
At 60 miles an hour not my shit
There is some statistic or something or some fact that like like it's a manser's fact for sure
60 who did they measure?
60 it's maybe 50 Barry Bonds. I don't
Know don't search
This jizz of all time there we go you needed the of all time is there a world record okay fastest ejaculate is
42.7 miles per hour, okay, whoa
Whoa
42.7 that is a way faster than I thought was even possible mine. Honestly is probably probably not even
Mine is like a candle melting yeah
But dude even even like like think about a car that's going well
Yeah, I that's what I would love if you could get a really fast one off
And you could cut you could prank a speed trial like a guy cop with a radar gun
You stand really close to him and you come right in front of his radar and he starts chasing heels. Oh, yeah
Oh, no, mine looks like when you're like done with a slurpee and there's that little bit left. You got just pour it out
Yeah, that would but the cop pulls over your cum though. You just come what I was thinking
It's like maybe there's like an old lady driving by really slow you come in front of the gun
So he thinks the old lady's going like well for me, it'd be like
320 miles per hour you're going to jail for jizzing next to an old lady. I'm not that close
I'm close to the radar gun the road is far away
I'm going to go in it if I'm going to tell for anything is for jizzing on a car the fact that you were even jizzing in
The vicinity of either way you're an old lady can be an old man. Why did you say okay?
There's a solution. There's a solution to this also this takes place in Saudi Arabia and the old lady gets arrested for driving
Anyway, there's a solution to this but it involves forced perspective
Yeah, so what you do is you got to paint your penis up like a car Lamborghini
Uh-huh. Again, mine not being a Lambo. Golf cart. Yeah. Golf cart, I don't know, sedan.
Yeah, Fiat. Camry. Yeah, none of those either. Yeah. Smart car. I don't know. Yeah, smart
car. I don't know. One of those red and yellow cars, you drive with your feet. Unicycle.
You're on the side of the highway, your penis is painted up like a bird
scooter. The exact shape of a bird scooter, L-shape. You have to, then you nut while the cop has a radar gun on you.
Uh-huh, and then that's how you that's how you yeah, and he's like oh my god that radio flyer wagon is going 70 miles an hour
Who put this little tykes on the highway, but if you have a scooter shaped penis you're come shooting directly into the air
That's a good point
You know I would be worried about
Not if okay not if the first part the L part the tall part of the L is flush
Okay with your with your your thighs it goes down straight down
Like halfway to your knees. It's really long straight down. Who are you messaging?
Just he's messaging some
California
California will wallen and here is a crime to masturbate your own home
It can't be a crime to masturbate in your own home, and yes, how fast I need to pull this for it to be illegal
So you ask Stephanie on the engage live can you put this onto the onto the screen?
(laughing)
- This needs to be solved.
- I don't think he can.
(laughing)
- He can't.
- No, he can't.
- Oh.
- Yeah, is it, if somebody, okay.
- How fast do I need to come for it to be illegal?
- There's a dangerous speed.
There's a speed at which it's basically a gun.
- It is a, you're a menace to society.
- Well, it said, what was it, like 42 miles an hour?
That's like, that's as fast as like maybe--
- That's as fast as a bullet.
- Yeah, like a pitching machine.
- Search fastest--
- Like a really bad pitching machine,
but a pitching machine, no less.
- Search how fast is a bullet.
- A bullet, if I had to guess,
is about 40 to 45 miles an hour.
- In MP, yes.
How fast is a bullet?
- 20,000-- - 1800 miles per hour.
- I was pretty close.
- Yeah, you were very close.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, still 1800 miles per hour.
- So how many, just do the math.
How many wads do you have to shoot for it to be,
if you're that guy?
- 1800 for it to be-- - I guess.
- Yeah. (laughs)
Yeah, I guess for me, yeah, about 1800.
I guess the closest example is maybe like that dart shotgun we have over there.
Wouldn't that hurt if you were a girl and a 40 mile per hour...
Yeah, you'd go, you'd fly backwards.
Yeah, like in Evil Dead 2.
Yeah, it'd be like cable work, you'd get pulled against the wall.
Yeah, it'd be like the beginning of fucking Back to the Future.
You'd just be fucking shooting directly at a wall.
Like a Jackie Chan movie.
Ejaculate-y Chan.
Ejaculate-chan? There we go.
- Ejaculete. - Ejaculete.
- Why didn't you just say ejaculate, Chan?
Why'd you--
- 'Cause there's an E at the end of the name.
- Ejaculete. - Ejaculete, Chan.
- Ejaculete.
- Did you ever arrive on an answer on if it's illegal
to come in your own home if you live in a completely
glass house with a bunch of big arrows
that point directly to it?
(laughing)
- Yeah, 'cause you know people are getting right up
to the edge of the law.
They're doing it with the door open,
They're standing facing outside.
- This is a building in that place Storm King,
is the Jismin's Hut.
- Well you used to live next to a school.
- Yeah.
- And your room faced the school.
- So not just my room, it was also my roommate's room.
- No, it was your room and you picked the room also
when you got to the apartment.
- I picked the room because I would get the cheapest rent
because I wouldn't have a balcony.
- Yeah, but the balcony.
- And it was kind of a, yeah, it was like cheapest rent
and also some upsides.
- No.
were there doing rear window, would you ever, like every time you masturbated you had to
make sure that every window was closed.
My bed was away from the wall.
So you didn't close the windows.
So you left the shades open.
No, the curtains in that room were always closed.
He just said he had clurtons.
He did.
He admitted he had clurtons.
Closed curtains.
Clurtons are clear curtains.
I had to shower.
He just said he had clurtons.
Clear curtains.
So yeah, his bed was away from the window, but there was also his entire wall.
Yeah, but where was your penis?
His entire wall facing the window was a mirror.
Oh, my penis was on a magnifying glass.
(laughter)
My penis was on a magnifying glass being projected into the sky.
He lived in like a hall of mirrors where it's a bunch of angled mirrors,
so if you look in the window, just the entire, there's just a hundred images of him jacking up.
It looks like, in the reflection of a spider's eye.
It's like a fly's eye.
Yeah.
Scary.
Yeah, a fly.
I said spider.
Yeah, he lived in the kaleidoscope building, too.
Really?
That's why the windows look like it's an expensive place to live yeah
But did you ever get nervous that maybe like a little kid would I was nervous that like I would forget to shut the blinds
After I'd get out of the shower because that just ruins a kid's life especially like you were a magic Harry
Bye, yeah, I know that would ruin a kid's life. Oh, yeah
I mean I got like I think I saw the light version of that like all the time like all the fucking Quebec
Wah people at Hampton Beach all these like fat old guys who look exactly like I do now mm-hmm in speedos walking around
I mean there is only there's a thin piece of fabric between yeah seeing his whole stick and berries. That's not right
It's not right to be like that. It's not right to be extremely European in America
I hate Europe, and I want to see it fucking destroyed. Yeah, there's no doubt. There's no reason for a European style bathing suit
I'm a little bit interested in going to a nudist beach though. Yeah, and being as long as it's girls only yeah
Except for me. Yeah, I go as long as I'm completely alone. Yep, you go alone. Yeah completely alone. You guys walk around the house naked
depends underwear
Yeah, I do. I have but the yeah the thing is that I mean I have I have a street-level apartment
So I feel like even if my curtain is even a little crack open that I don't realize that's trouble. Yeah, yeah somebody
Yeah, my roommate had a like a girl over one time
and I didn't know and I was just fully just in my underwear in the living room.
Oh okay I thought you're gonna say fully nude. Yeah underwear is okay. If you're at
somebody's house it's fine to see their roommate in their underwear. Yeah I guess
that's true it's just you like in from your perspective you're just like
shit I just like there's like a level of like. No you're like I might fuck. I guess.
I might fucking get laid. Yeah yeah I just I'm glad I don't have an in-unit dryer.
Yeah, you know that she's into people who are in live at that apartment. That's true
Yeah, so then you're like yeah, I live here too. Yeah, here's my nuts in my ass check this out. It's a dumbbell
Yeah the worst curling yeah, she walks in the dumbbells on your stomach you're trapped under it you're going
I'm trying to impress you
- Arched back up, like the dumbbells on the back.
You're like, "Ahh!"
- "Help, help, I can't get up!"
- Pink underwear on.
- And then she's like, just anxious
that it's gonna roll off of you.
You go, "No, it'll clunk."
(laughing)
- It'll fall through the floor.
- "It's gonna clunk."
- My downstairs neighbors are already so fucking mad at me.
They can't clunk.
- "You gotta pick me up.
"You have to pick me up from underneath this."
- Or at least build a ramp for the dumbbell to roll down.
- "Please."
(laughing)
It's pretty hard to seduce women.
Yeah, I discovered a new Riz strategy.
Really?
Oh yeah.
Do you have Riz?
We talked about this on stream last night.
I have a few Riz strategies.
What's your Riz?
Well, okay, first of all, I'll tell you my first Riz strategy.
Okay.
It's just you walk up to a girl, you say, "Hey girl, check my Riz."
And you say, "Hey, what's up?"
Damn.
Or you say, a reverse direction, you go up, you say, "Hey, what's up girl?
That's my Riz, y'all."
That's W Riz.
Yeah.
That's W S Riz.
This is the real Riz secret.
Okay.
Okay, that this one, this one you can't steal because this is
gonna be, this is 2023.
This is the year of, wait for it, the bell hop.
What's the bell hop?
You dress up like a bell hop.
And say, may I take your bags to your room, ma'am?
You hang out at a-
And you take them to your room.
And you have the hat.
Uh-huh.
And then if it's stuff, and then I was saying if stuff gets
like hot and heavy, stuff you're like chatting.
It's known to as bell hop.
Chatting her up.
and you like chatting her up and you can be like
man can i help you with your boobs
all fuck
will get what you get small for a couple of your can i see can i help
man mom can i have to do it you can age
yeah i mean i think i would have a show our own pussy hotel in a note that
second one there were still here is the hand on the hip
yet the one reason and on the hip yep show this one
on screen
this is how this is how it's going to be a lot of money for it
this is
year of bill hopper
That guy has a 60 miles per hour cum shot.
Oh, for show.
Yeah.
But I think I'm going to get that complete outfit soon.
We were saying last night--
How pissed are you if you're the fucking Guinness World Record
person and they call you out to measure a guy's cum shot?
There's so many--
I mean, there's a radar gun.
I'm thinking about it.
There's so many sexual-- yeah, but somebody
has to be there to verify it.
There's so many sexual things for like Guinness Book
of World Records and stuff, like the biggest orgy and shit.
They have one guy and his name is Peter the Perv,
and he's really fat and he has a comb over
and he comes down and he does the breathing thing
where he's like.
- They get fax machines all day.
- He has waking sleep apnea.
- Yeah, I was gonna say he has a wake apnea.
- Another one on the line for Peter.
Peter, you go tackle this one.
We'll wait for a fishing thing.
- Yeah.
(grunting)
- He can't talk.
- He pretends he hates it too.
- Yeah.
(grunting)
- Peter, listen, I know you're not one for sex stuff
but you gotta go measure a guy's cum shot.
claims it's 45 miles per hour. And he's doing the thing, he's measuring it with,
he's holding his finger like this and he's just timing it with his eyes, seeing how
long does it take to go from my thumb to my index finger. They call me the human
radar. And he gets going, can you go again? Try it again. I missed that one. You're gonna have to
wait like 20 minutes man. That's the thing, if it was, my fastest cum shot would
probably be my first one ever, because I've only gotten slower since then. Yeah, because it's
been building up. Yeah, so maybe when I was like a baby, I probably had a really
fast come yeah yeah yeah that's probably why you had to wear a diaper yeah it's
true yeah I wore steel diaper my entire life
completely steel you're saying last night about the bellhop thing though it's not
like impersonating any other I guess I guess Bell impersonating a bellhop is
the same amount of bad as impersonating a cop I feel like yeah and you get in
trouble well yeah because you will you wouldn't cuz normally I mean I think
I think it's fine to go into any business and pretend you work there and help people out.
I think that's, you can't get in trouble if you go into say, a Target, you're wearing a
Target outfit and you go, "Okay, here's..."
But if you're tricking a woman and having sex with you...
Well, okay, that's not what a bellhop does, okay?
That's bringing disrepute to the profession.
That's not what we mean.
But if I go, for example, because I was thinking I would really like to dress up as a bellhop
and go into a hotel and just be a bellhop for the day.
Yeah.
Just for an hour.
But that's a profession where you're picking up people's bags and you're going to people's
rooms.
So I think you could maybe get in big trouble for that.
What do you think? No. I don't think you'd get into that much trouble. No, because there's
an element of serial killer vibes to it. It's like, "Oh yeah, this guy was pretending to
be a bellhop so he could follow people to their room and kill them." I just think people
would be scared I was going to take their iPad. Yeah. Well, that's worse than a serial
killer. In today's day and age. Yeah. Well, usually their heaviest bag is the one with
the most crap in it. Yeah. But you could sling that bag over your back. But don't they walk
up with you if you're the bellhop?
Sometimes. Sometimes not. Sometimes you just go straight up and they just bring your stuff
up and leave it there.
That's a pretty profitable impersonation. You're going to make more money doing that
on a day.
I'm not going to make any money. I do it for the love of the game.
And if you're a cop. Because what's the point of having, if you pretend to be a cop
for a day, which people do that, people pretend to be cops and they pull people over and shit.
Are you trying to just convince somebody to bribe you or something, like instantly?
I guess.
Because you can't really write a ticket.
Oh my god, yeah, because then people think you're being a bellhop for the tips.
can pretend to write a ticket though that's really easy you just write it
down but you have to be on that official paper yeah that's true you can't print
that out yeah shit and I don't have a printer in my car yeah computer but I
don't even have a car it's easy it's easy you just you get you get a ticket
so you have to get a ticket okay oh and then yeah oh yeah I see where you're
going I was gonna say whiteout what do you
have a where you have an what do you have a stupid name yeah well I say why don't
you write out your name Bob Featherbottom yeah why'd you say my uncle's name what
if you're Bob Featherbottom and they're like my name isn't Bob Featherbottom
and you say no that's my name like a officer Featherbottom or you say no it's
like a John Hancock thing yeah it's the name of the person who really had
John's this year yeah it's like wouldn't like the elevator inspector we'd have a
very different world if instead of John Bob Featherbottom
Yeah
And John Hancock John I didn't go to a morgue and seeing all those fucking feather bottoms in there
That it wasn't John Doe. They've all they would all be laughing all the time. Yeah, the coroners great
They'd be corners already have six senses of humor. They eat sandwiches next to the body from what I know about them
Yeah, they love eating sandwiches over the body. Oh my god. Are you kidding me? They're eating and you know what sandwiches
They're eating double roast beef. It's always no cheese and with the one job. I couldn't do I could do I get the one job
I think I do I honestly think I could probably do every other job, but I couldn't do that. It's too too crazy
Yeah, cuz what if some guy comes in and he's?
blasted to bits
No, just like imagine you're a coroner right and then the funniest body comes in you can't even take a picture of it
Yeah, that's the other thing yeah
Yeah. Well, no, I think being a coroner would be fun because nobody else wants to look at
the body. So you can say whatever into that tape recorder. Yeah. It'd be like, "Subject
had a tiny crotch area." True. And then the penis. "And his head's gone and a butt crack!"
It's like that guy, remember that guy who dressed up like he pretended to be a gynecologist
Yeah, I like that for a for a corner, but it's going and say everybody had
70 years in jail
Yeah, they don't play with that. They don't play with that. Oh, yeah, that's worse than a bellhop
impersonation on one hand the biggest form of flattery on the other hand one of the worst crimes to commit
I don't give a fuck one on once. I'm dead just let somebody fuck my body you said that before I think that's fine
Yeah, like if it stops people from fucking real bodies, then they can fuck mine
Yeah
In that way and science is the name of I don't my donate my body to my neighbor
Yeah, really. Yeah, what do you think? I'll do with it probably throw it away, but you have to try
I want to get my dead body one last act. Yeah
You want to do what be a lit-ass statue? Oh a statue?
No, but not as I just want to get it dipped in bronze to just and then get turned into a fucking
Bar of bronze I want to be it's not even body shape. Yeah, I'm done exactly like that monk
I want to be turned into the Buddha. Yeah
Yeah, I'm gonna be turning into a statue of the Buddha and then they'll find me in many many years
It'd be cool if they used my skeleton to
Scare a dog. No just like eat a dog
Like turn my head into like a mug my skull. Oh, you'd be a bloody brilliant mug be more of a tankard
Yeah, yeah, let's go. You have a form of a flag in I think
You'd be a propane tank
Click click click on the tree. Yeah, my my skull is the propane tank at the goth grill
Yeah, it's just like just a big tube coming out of my skull. Mm-hmm
donating my skeleton to the inevitable reboot of fear factor and what's going to happen is
they're eating something gross, they're eating bug eyeballs with poop sauce or whatever, Joe
Rogan is going to be Joe Rogan again, is making them do and then right as they finish the challenge
Joe Rogan's like alright well looks like everybody finished the challenge then a door's going to fly
open, my skeleton's going to fly out and grab them and they're going to go ah and it doesn't even
affect anything. It just happens in one episode. I want to be a soccer ball in Brazil.
Dude, that's so crazy that they like that video where they're like playing with
soccer with the beheaded guy. I don't know that. I don't know it either. Maybe it's a movie I saw.
That is, you're literally thinking of apocalypto. Yeah, they used to do that in like lion times.
Dude, that's so crazy that that's what Brazil is like all the time. There's two things down there
that I know about. They had a sport, but they didn't actually play with the head.
You don't know that, you weren't around back then.
You are right.
Didn't they say it was like, they also said that was true for lacrosse.
They said that like they would play lacrosse with people's skulls.
Or that's what the lax kids at my school would say.
Crackers in high school playing fucking lacrosse with people's heads?
They were saying that it was an ancient Mayan...
The fuck are you talking about?
They would say like, yeah, lacrosse is like, they used to like play it with people's skulls.
The sport they did actually is to play with human heads was field hockey.
That's what it fucking was.
Yep, hungry hungry hippo. Yeah, the original game the original with the real one
It was based on when they had real and real hip that happened one time
It was so you know it's so fucked up what what they they go like well
I don't care if it's true now where they go like you know hippos are actually the most dangerous
Animal they actually kill more people than sharks. Yeah, like shut the fuck up. That's a it's a fat hippo
Yeah, if you're a white ball
If you're a white ball, they're dangerous you're a watermelon yeah
Humans oh yeah, who took this survey that took this fucking survey that's like all these white ball
Yeah, five or six white balls
Such a fucked up animal to be the most dangerous
Yeah, I agree cuz also that's the bad way to go. They don't even have they don't have anything they just
Does their fat guys that sit in the water yeah, they're trying to be whales yeah, they do trying to be
Well, I do move in fucking silence you ever seen those videos of them. Just like floating through the water. Yeah
They're basically alligators. Yeah, like a piece of shit floating
Your shit's gray. Yeah, you have giant shits. Yeah giant gray giant gray shit with watermelons
Yeah, yeah
Look I drink half a bottle of pepto every morning so that I don't get stomach quakes
You have a pure black right angle shit. Yeah a fucking log
It's literally my my shit is more bismuth than it is human excrement
It's exactly it's crystalline. It's got all those it's pretty in rainbow. Yeah, I saw my I saw my shit to a jeweler
Yeah
They are they're shaving my poop down and they're turning it into like the like there's an Etsy store that sells all my poop
And they mold it into skulls and stuff with like a Dremel. It's pretty cool
I'm imagining now you bring you you make it you take your poop
Mm-hmm you make my business poop you put it on a you put it in a ring like a gemstone
And you take it to an appraiser, you say, please appraise this.
Well, the ring is worth maybe $10.
The gemstone is poop.
It's not worth anything.
I don't know about that thing.
Poop is funny pretty much every--
I mean, every variation of bringing any kind of poop
into somebody's--
Well, this is poop.
Yeah.
You know what I saw?
Bringing in a pond star?
It's the jeweler's loop.
You know what I saw the other day?
There's a website.
It was on a Facebook Marketplace ad
or you can sell--
- No, you ate the website.
- I ate it.
- 'Cause it was--
- Nope.
You can send people poop,
and it's called like poopsenders.com.
You can just send--
- What do you mean you send people the poop?
- It's literally, the ad is a picture of a man holding shit,
and it says poopsenders.com.
- Do you send--
Do you send poop--
- Go to poopsenders.com.
- Yeah, I need to see poopsenders.com right now.
- It's real, it's a real thing.
- This is about to be--
- See, first result.
- This has gotta be the ultimate,
Oh, okay. Ultimate gag gift, sweet revenge at its finest, guaranteed anonymous.
$50? Oh, with hearts, okay.
It's not real poop. Oh, it is. Oh, okay.
Soft and stinky patty of poop.
It's animal poop that you send to people.
Well, let's keep scrolling. Let's see what kinds they have.
Yeah, okay. Gorilla poop.
That's got to be a hard hit.
Ooh, the combo pack. I don't want the combo pack.
That's a good deal, though.
The family pack.
The ad is literally a photo of a man's hand.
No paper trail.
Wait, go up. Go up a little bit.
So it says under it says soft and stinky patty of poo serving up the zookeepers finest
That's elephant crap gorilla poop is now we're getting really gross and the combo pack is all three in one big nasty mess. Yeah
The mega pack you've been pooped on want to know by whom over what does that mean?
They don't you don't really you don't get this kind of website that often anymore like this and then the glitter one. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, I think that um wait top ten reason there's a list here. We got to read it top ten reasons to send someone poop
Oh, okay number one for your ex number two neighbors pet crapping on your lawn, okay?
Especially if it's a gorilla for you
I know
Hey, my name is elephant for a salesperson or mechanic that ripped you off five a last-minute gift for someone who has everything a
Gag true. I guess this is the perfect gift for somebody who has it all for that rich gloating friend knock them down a peg
Like, yeah, that's a good point. If you sent this to Scrooge, right?
Yeah.
Those are Scrooge.
He'd open it and go, "Oh, God, I've seen the error of my ways."
Yeah.
I don't even think it would be an error of your ways thing. I think if you sell this right, like, it's like...
Well...
If the person who... Okay, imagine this. Scrooge is the person in this example.
Yeah.
Where he has it all.
He... And...
So, yeah, he doesn't have animal poop.
Yeah, I think Scrooge is so...
Well, yeah, I guess if he has it all...
- Scrooge is so damn greedy, he's gonna open,
he's opening the package, he's like,
oh I hope this is a gold coin,
I'm gonna put it in my room of gold coins,
and then he sees it and he's like,
oh it's gorilla poop, I'll just put this
in my room of poops.
My poop collection.
- But you'd have to get the combo pack.
- He's so greedy, he just wants it all.
- You would specifically have to get the combo pack
because it's like, oh, I have all of these poops
in individual jars.
- He wants the box set.
- I think you guys are missing a point.
- Here's all of the poops mashed together.
- Scrooge would want poop.
- That's all we're saying.
- No, Scrooge would open it and he'd say,
"Oh my bloody stars."
- Then at least we can agree that at least,
- "Oh my stars, I've been rude."
- Maybe we can agree that at the beginning of the story,
he wouldn't want the poop,
but after he's been changed by the ghost,
he might want it because he's realized
he doesn't like gold or nice things anymore.
- He'd say, "I guess I'll get it."
- He'll say, "I'll take this poop
"so nobody else has to have it."
- He's not a trash can.
- He's nice though.
He learns about tiny Tims.
I guess Scrooge, they don't talk about epilogue Scrooge at all.
Where it's like, yeah, he's a completely nice guy after, and he takes everyone's shit.
You imagine how easy it would be to walk all over Scrooge after Christmas day?
Yeah.
I would be abusing that.
Oh, I'd beat the fuck...
I'd be abusing that old man.
Dude, I'd be...
I'd be going Stan Lee on his ass.
Yeah, I'd be making him like, give me like doubloons and shit.
I don't know what shillings...
I'd make him give me doubloons.
Yeah.
I've make him give me a computer so I can play the balloons game
Addicting games you get calm you get Scrooge after he sees all those ghosts, right?
You just ask him like every single day like can I have five dollars put that into savings?
Uh-huh your Scrooge account screw dollars every day. That's gonna compound. I just paint my ass blue and fucking ask for his whole house
Yeah, whoo. I'm the ghost of your
Blue
Yeah, the ghost of blueness present ghosts are blue yeah, I would I would be like I would become me
I would disguise myself as a ghost of tiny Tim
And I'd be like whoo I died because you turned nice and I make him turn back. Oh, that's a good point
Yeah, ruin it and then the three ghosts would get pissed off. Yeah there
- Yeah, I guess there would have to be a ghost
that would say, the ghost of keeping a level head.
- Yeah.
- I'm the ghost of keeping it real.
- I would be so pissed off if I was Scrooge.
- Definitely a ghost nowadays.
- I got through the three Christmas ghosts
and I was like, thank God, I'm nice now, everything's fine.
And then I hear a knock on my door
and it's the ghost of New Year past.
- Yeah.
- It's like, seriously?
- There's still gonna be three more of these?
- Yeah, well.
- And the ghost of Valentine's Day after that.
- You need to throw a rocking party, Mr. Scrooge.
Okay.
Alright.
The ghost of New Year's future would be like,
"It's going to be the year 2000."
And that's all he would say.
And the glasses will go like this.
We will have the best glasses.
Miley Cyrus will have her beach party on New Year's Eve.
And there will be years where the glasses don't make very much sense
because they have ones in them.
Kenan Thompson.
It's gonna be scary.
Scary. I'm the ghost of the Super Bowl future.
It's the ghost of Don Pardo.
Oh!
That's epilogue screw, just every single day there's a new set of ghosts.
Yeah.
Yeah, the ones that are, yeah, I'm the ghost of January 8th.
What happens on January 8th? It's two days after January 6th.
I, I...
The country needs to heal.
He's gonna be, the thing is, it's all, every single like day,
He's gonna be like oh, I fucking he always has a start with him being like I fucking hate
And he's like I fucking hate for the July this sucks, and then anytime he doesn't like a holiday BAM three
Yeah, sure out of the cut. Yeah, say I'm the ghost of
Martin Luther King jr. Day
future
Wouldn't it wouldn't it just be Martin Luther King though
three. The Christmas ghosts aren't just Santa. Yeah, that's true. Yeah, but the Christmas
ghosts are just... The ghosts are gonna play the Raptors today in an overtime thriller.
I'm the ghost of your birthday past. He's like, I already like my birthday. You don't need to...
Okay, I'll tell the other two guys not to come. The other two guys are coming with your present.
Yeah, but I saw the four hour shift, so I have to stay.
The ghost of your birthday future is like, "Next year you're gonna get a gift card!"
It's like, "I don't want to know that."
And it sucks!
That would suck if the ghost of birthday future is just telling you like,
"Next year your friends are going to be too busy!"
That would be scary.
"You're gonna have to plan to have it on the weekend instead!"
Damn.
That's sad. When you don't get to have it on your actual birthday,
and you actually have to fucking have it on the Saturday or the Sunday, the Lord's Day.
You just killed the vibe.
You killed the fucking vibe.
Well, guess who this happened to last year?
Who?
Motherfucking you.
Mm-hmm.
Nobody you know has a job.
Why do you need that?
You guys weren't in town.
Oh, yeah.
That's true.
No one was in town.
Yeah.
And then I tried to-
I missed your birthday two years in a row.
Yeah.
Then I tried to-
And I'm going to miss it again.
We tried to go to a bar, and then we went into the building, and the whole- I was like, "Oh,
Yeah, it'll be nice. There's like a little back like patio. You can go all go hang out there
Hold back patio whole bar shut down wedding reception
Just go to whatever bar I did, but I was like shit. I told all these people if I can go here
Yeah, they had to text everybody individually and just say like you strike me as the type that would have a lit-ass birthday party sex
with fucking drugs and
Birthday
Dave and Buster's I would love I would go to them, but I've been in a long time
I do want to go to Dave and Buster's I do want to do something for my birthday this year because I am losing my health
Insurance, yeah, you should start planning now. I want to do a stunts birthday because I'm losing my health insurance
But that's the day no do it because that's the two days before
I'm having my birthday two days before finna get hurt. Uh-huh July 21st. I'm gonna be jumping off
How does that work if you lose your health insurance halfway through a hospital stay like if you break your neck and no no two days
before yeah I know but okay three days before but if you go into the hospital I
do like your neck no I then you lose your health insurance on the fourth day
they're gonna pull the plug on you no yeah no no no I'm getting like I'm gonna
break all my bones dumbass wait is can you do that to get over the health it
because they have to probably cover you for your stay if you go in before you
lose your insurance yeah so could you do like Tom Hanks the terminal and just
spend the rest of your life in the hospital because you've been like
Admitted once and then you have insurance forever. Maybe there's a grandfather clause for insurance. Yeah, there is a good idea
I cause and he's old. Yeah, he's old as hell. Mm-hmm, and he lives in the South Pole. Mm-hmm for real
Yeah, I think you think he does Christmas stuff. No, he just does he just gives people like pretty shitty deductibles
He just tells people they're at the wrong pole when they pull up. Mm-hmm
When they pull up yeah at the South Pole at the pole, why is the South Pole so uninteresting to me
What are you talking about? They have all these cool jeans and sweatshirts.
Which one's on land and which one's in water? Is the North Pole in the water and the South Pole is on land?
Do I look like a genius?
North Pole is on land because where would Santa's workshop be?
No, I think the South Pole...
I think that... well, I just distinctly remember... you know, I think the North Pole is in the water because I remember being a kid and looking at a globe and being like...
No.
Yeah.
Where is it?
No.
No, I think the South Pole is...
There has to be an island.
That's because Antarctica is ginormous.
You can even see it from the back.
- Look at this picture of the North Pole.
- Oh, there it is. - Oh, crap.
Yeah, it doesn't look all that much
like there's land there.
- Huh.
- The Arctic Circle. - Then where the fuck
is Santa?
- He has an underwater base, like in a movie.
- Santa is an Atlantean.
Santalantean.
- Santalantean.
- This, wait, the North Pole looks like fucking shit.
- Yeah.
- This is the North Pole, bro? - This looks like a fucking
blue water.
- This is Santa Claus's whole hood?
- I guess.
That looks terrible, man.
Yeah, it looks boring.
Yeah.
At least.
They don't even show fucking Google Maps.
They don't even show boobs on Google Maps.
Google Maps is fucking up, not even putting a little tiny--
just a little blip that you can click on,
and then it's a 3D like--
oh my god, that is a perfect idea.
You click on the North Pole, click on Street View,
and then you can just see Santa's workshop.
I bet that they should do that.
I think they probably do.
Do that for the Christmas season.
Yeah, that would be a good thing for the Christmas season.
- They should do that for all the holidays.
- Yeah, like 4th of July town?
- Yeah, 4th of July town at the North Pole.
- Oh, that's a good idea.
- They should just all be at the North Pole.
- Bastille Dayville.
- Yeah.
- What's the point of it, Bastille Day?
- French independence.
- I wish that never happened.
- Yeah. - Yeah, it is.
- I wish that the French would be in--
- I wish they were dependent on me.
- Yeah, that's right.
- I wish I was their king.
- Because I would let them all starve.
- They all wear them damn pins over there.
- I think-- - Stank.
I've been thinking recently that actually France
would probably be, of all cultures in the world,
the one I would fit in with the most.
- Yeah.
- Tiny mustache, very rude, fuck you.
- And I like to smoke cigarettes.
- That's true.
- And drink all day.
- I think, yeah, I think all you need to do
is just wear the most heinous track jacket in the world.
- Fuck you.
- I think I'd probably fit in with the high elves,
'cause I'm proper.
- I would do so well.
- You would not fit in with the high elves.
You'd be way too short.
- I'm elegant.
I could just go to Canada and I feel like I'd fit in you think you'd fit in in Canada
Yeah, someone told me that I am I'm a quintessential Montreal guy
What yeah, who told you that Michael?
Who Michael Hirsch?
Michael Hirsch fuck him
fucking idiot
Quintessentially, I don't know I trust him. I don't trust him. I would fit in in space. He wears rings
Don't trust the guy wears rings
(laughter)
- He's behind a paywall, he's not gonna see this.
- Oh yeah.
(laughter)
No, I like Michael.
Even though he wears rings all day.
Would you guys ever wear rings if you weren't married?
- I have one that I bought as a joke.
I'd wear a neck ring.
- That is a necklace.
- And then it didn't even fit.
It's a Harley Davidson ring that has a big skull on it.
- It would look exactly like a normal ring,
but around my neck.
I'd have a gemstone like this.
Decides up would it be unlock would you unlock it unlock? How do I ring if it all our powers?
I put it on my head as a baby. I don't think you're wearing a ring. It's not wedding related
Yeah, I'm giving you some power. I guess I would wear a green lantern ring probably about a clatter ring
What was that a ring a cool?
Rings next to the heart. It's like a thing that Irish guys wear. I don't know that
I don't know it my dad wears one
I would honestly if I could wipe one single country off the map
I wouldn't even choose evil Stan or fucking North Korea. I would choose Ireland
No, you would I would go if I had a power and go like yeah, then the entire Irish
Diaspora, I would just obliterate with a single fucking snap. I
Hate Irish people you know what I was laughing about
Kind of a TV reference here you guys watch better call Saul right now. I've been watching
Watching nope
Me neither. I've been watching through better call Saul and you know Chuck how he's he's scared. He's scared of electricity
Oh, yeah, I was laughing so hard. I would love to be in that in his world in that show
And I'd love to be in Chuck's house and have a little ray gun. I'm just going
It's like a like a 50s ray gun that has like a visible like lightning
- Green.
- Yeah, yeah.
(laughing)
- It's got a little Vandegraaff generator on it.
(grunting)
- Stop it, you're murdering me.
- That's really good, Michael McKee.
(laughing)
- That would be good.
- He, I think he's got a point in that show.
- What?
- That electricity probably does kill you.
- Well you fuckin'--
- Yeah.
Don't, I know the spoiler about it,
but don't say it anyway.
- I'm sorry, I'm not gonna say it though.
- But I still haven't seen the sixth season,
'cause it's a--
I watched a YouTube video the other day, this guy sleeps on duct tape because he has a wire
that runs all the way from his house into the ground and he sleeps on duct tape every night
so he keeps himself grounded.
Wow.
And I was like, "Man, I should get some duct tape and do that."
Dude, I really, I wish I had like some, because the thing that's missing from my life is like
conviction, you know?
Like something like a...
Ah, you should be convicted.
- I did.
- Nuts, I knew as soon as I said that.
As soon as I said that I knew.
No, but like the thing is, it's like something that,
I guess like discipline is the word I'm looking for.
- You need to be disciplined in prison.
(laughing)
Sent to a work camp.
- No, I don't do that.
- So like, like.
- Like you feel like you just do.
I was talking to somebody about this the other day,
like the reason why people like,
like Andrew Tate or like Jordan Peterson
is because it's the first person,
the first time a lot of people have ever heard
that you can't just like eat candy all day.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- You need one of these guys. - It's willpower.
- It's just so hard 'cause like all the guys
who tell you to do that stuff,
you see them and they're like the biggest dorks in the world.
Like why would I listen to a dork?
- Yeah. - I would, dude,
are you kidding me?
I could bully the shit out of Jordan Peterson.
He could try to-- - No, no.
- He would try to-- - No, I mean this,
he would destroy you.
- Dude, he could try to mentally like--
- Your wit is dim.
Your wit is dim. - He would completely--
You sound like the pedophile neighbor and family guy not like Jordan Peterson
You you would get destroyed in a debate by Jordan Pete, I don't know it's not a debate in a debate
It's it's a it's it's a wedgie competition his steely
Are you doing the thing where you see so where somebody sees someone they don't like online?
They say I would give you my swirly. No, you're doing right now that guy eats 64 ounces of prime rib every fucking day
He would dominate you. Yeah, he would dominate you. I don't know. I don't think
I don't think I would listen, I think I could just say
shut up nerd to anything that he says.
- No, he would talk over you.
- Andrew Tate though, that's a different story.
- That guy-- - That's Mr. Plenty.
- That guy would-- - Check the leather
on the Bentley, yeah. - Pop your head off
on his legs. - Yeah.
There's a different route you gotta take with that guy.
- Yeah, what do you gotta do with him?
How do you take down, how would you take down Andrew Tate?
- I think that guy would probably Google
where his pizza came from and then snitch on him to the FBI.
- That would be fucking awesome.
- He's already been taken down.
- Did you see the only, he's like,
I have visitation rights for five people.
I'm giving four-- - Please some of their
bad bitches. - Four to my family
and friends, and the fifth one is Aiden Ross.
- Really? - Yeah.
(laughing)
- That is so awesome, bro.
- That's so funny, he just has like a little--
- God bless that kid.
- He has like a little fucking, like a little brother
that he, like-- - Yeah, I think it's sweet.
- Yeah, I don't know much about Aiden Ross.
- How are you gonna stop eating candy all day?
Oh, I've already stopped. I think this is a wake-up call in itself.
Oh yeah, the tooth. That's what you need. You need a medical emergency.
No, I literally, that's like the only way to stop me from smoking and stuff too.
If I fully just like, yeah, you have a little bit of cancer.
Oh yeah. Yeah, that always gets me to stop smoking is when I like.
I've been doing, what's it called? I've been drinking only sugar-free stuff.
Stopped like soda.
Wow. That's great. Look at you.
Soda is this the year what soda is sugar-free soda is this is this the year you get it all together
I'm completely different. I don't know. Oh my god. Wait. There's gonna be something crazy
GBO just did something fucking incredible on the video is this can people see this this I
Don't know how it's taking us this long to figure out we can do this Wow
You got a little and we have a little dancing Andrew Tate right here
Don't tickle him man. He's gonna grab his ankles. He's a badass. This is what they're making him do in prison right now
Yep, he's at Guantanamo Bay, and they're fucking making him dances a little hard out
Yeah, that would be the ultimate punishment for an alpha like him is being forced to do ballet
Do that fucking it looks so bad in a ballet outfit that rap song he made is so fucking I never heard it
What did he say and he's got a bar in it or he's like they call me mr. Plenty
Check the Ben check the leather on the Bentley. That's a good line. Call me. Mr. Plenty. Mr. Plenty interior crocodile
Dude, mr. Plenty is like he wears a top hat and a monocle and he goes around the town giving kids candy
Yeah, he's a gentleman with a British accent. What the fuck are you talking about? Mr. Plenty?
You know, I do I I'm plenty. I I don't
He's driving around the I don't like Andrew Tate because I think he's a fop. Yeah
Dandy yeah, the thing is I didn't know you think an alpha can do this. He says those are moves of a dandy
He's small AF. That's the other thing. I don't like too much. Yeah, he's tiny. I don't like that. He's right here
He's so annoying. Yeah, he is he's here. Wait. Can I flick away? We both had the same idea at the same time
Yeah, there goes
Awesome that was so funny. It was cool. Oh my
But yeah, maybe now that he's gone and
All JB peas in fucking meat jail or whatever. Maybe I will bellhopper is mindset
Mindset yeah, I think we need to sell bellhopper is Academy
What is it he's not Jordan Peterson isn't considered the lobster that's David Foster Wallace
What is Jordan Peterson say about lobsters? He says that lobsters are a good example
It's like the title of like the thing because we're trying trying to fit bellhop into it 12 rules for life, okay?
Well no rules for hops. Yes shit. Thank fucking God you were there
Yeah, I can be all day to figure out a bellhop o sphere. Yes. Oh
coming in strong
Dozens of bellhop YouTube I'm so sick of these bellhop youtubers coming up on my record
Just slow-motion videos of bellhops
It's important
You always want to push the cart you never want to pull it into the elevator push it and then pull it out
That's right in pull it out one of the most that's the one thing
I always do one of the most famous bellhops in the world Sisyphus
He was constantly
Pushing the pushing a car hops at the fucking Tower of Terror. Those are fakes. Yep. They're actors. You don't look up to them
It's true. They're fucking frauds. They're not real you stay away. They're bellhop for pay. Yeah
Yeah, you don't be a bellhop because you want money. You don't do a B
You don't do a bellhop thing for tips. No you do it because you need to move things
Mm-hmm. You need to move a point a minute. I do life you are you're gonna be moved
You're going to be moving bags from point A to point B, but you're going to be moving
from point beta to point alpha.
Shit.
Fuck, dude.
I think this is the next thing.
I think bellhop movement 2023.
The bellhoposphere.
Bellhoposphere.
2023.
I don't think that it's going to be the next thing.
Shut up.
I think auto-tune rap music is going to be the next thing.
No, that already had its day.
That's already in the heyday.
What?
That already-
It's sundowning, honestly.
Have you heard of T-Pain?
Yeah.
No.
That is a sundowning industry.
Wait, that Twitch streamer?
That's right. That's what I think he is.
But yeah, rap music, maybe where they're like, "Blah blah blah blah blah."
I think that'll be real.
Alcohol? That type of stuff?
Hmm, we should get you in a studio.
Yeah? You mean it?
I do mean that. You know who's in that music video?
Katherine Heigl.
We've already talked about this.
That's one of my favorite rap facts.
We're repeating shit from one week ago.
That's one of my favorite rap facts, is that she's in that music video.
She was already at the height of her, like, she was in 27 dresses.
- You ruined her career.
- No I didn't.
- Yeah I did.
- Her behavior ruined her career.
- Is that true?
- Is what I read, yeah.
- Did she have bad behavior?
- I read that she was an actorzilla, or what's the diva?
- Actorzilla?
- Actorzilla.
- There was a movie shooting near my house recently
and I felt so cool, man.
I walked by the trailers.
- Katie Huyck's there?
- No, there's a bunch of people sitting there like,
oh, look, and I walked by and I didn't even care.
I love doing that, not caring.
Like you know when you fly into New York City
and there's people are like looking out of the window
to look at the city and you're like,
I don't care, I've seen it a million times before.
And you feel so badass.
- Yeah, I know exactly what you mean.
- I saw a big trailer in front of a bodega one time
and it was like a, clearly a movie trailer,
but it had the Wu-Tang logo on it.
- Oh, probably for the Wu-Tang show that they made.
- It's either that or--
- Peter Jackson's Wu-Tang show.
- It's either that or there's a new karate movie coming out.
- Really?
I haven't either but I know they made it on Hulu Hulu. Yeah, they got a white guy to play old
That's awesome
I'm the old dirty beasted
Yeah, oh shimmy shimmy. Oh yeah. He was always saying shit like that. Yeah, Matt Barry. Yeah, they should get a
plate old dirty bastard they should get
What's his name the the guy from Top Gun Maverick the the bed
The guy with a little smile from Top Gun Maverick, you know, I'm not a teller
No, the bad the evil the evil guy from time to wager a thousand wonderland, bro
I don't remember his name James Gordon Asia Schmokey
The at the Allison Winterland cat Asia Schmokey is that his name is a smoker he smokes
Just he's a smoker doesn't smokes
To a punk like saying in real life your cat is just a blink-182 album fucking shit, man. If for real mm-hmm. That is awesome
then Buddha
That's also just a blink-182 album and or that green shit that I smoke you call that Buddha
Mm-hmm. I call it doodoo. I love us
You know that one yeah
You know it my you know my dad's a big bone thugs man. Yeah, he likes that one song they made with a con
Yeah, I tried so hard
My dad thinks that is one of the most powerful songs ever written up there with I was gonna ask
- I was gonna ask, I was gonna ask.
- Margaritaville.
- Did your dad think that that's Ja Rule,
but that's your mom?
- No, my mom thinks everybody's Ja Rule.
- You know what I think is the most powerful song ever written?
- My dad's favorite song is, my dad loves Akon.
- Yeah.
- I think the most powerful song ever played
was in the one in Back to the Future,
where it flies backwards.
- That is true, really.
- Oh yeah, that one.
- Second place the one from Mad Max Fury Road,
where the guy's jumping around on the car.
- Third most powerful song, P.O.D. by Tenacious D.
- Yep.
My dad had, the other day I was with my dad,
Christmas I mean, and a T.I. song came on
and he started singing along to it and I was like,
what the hell? - Which one?
- You can have whatever you like.
- Yeah, I figured.
- And I was like, what the hell is up with my dad, dude?
He's some fucking rapper now.
And he wasn't saying the N word when it came up
and I was pretty impressed.
I honestly was like-- - Good move, dad.
- Hi, dad.
Not that I've ever heard him say it,
but I guess I'd never heard him sing along to a rap song.
- Yeah, there's a certain--
As soon as he started singing along, I was like,
I'm in big trouble.
- Yeah, uh-oh.
- I'm in big fucking trouble.
- Did he conspicuously not say it?
Did he look at you or do like,
raise his eyebrows or anything?
- And he just went fully blank, dude.
He did the radio edit.
- Damn.
- Yeah.
- Good for him.
- He didn't even like, say it backwards or anything.
- Did he say shit or ish?
(laughing)
- I love this, ish?
Yeah, but he didn't do that.
Yeah, he just fucking said nothing. He gave it gave it a quick pause. It was his time to take a breath
Yeah, he's an old man. So it takes him. Yeah, it's hard to sing as an old man. Yeah, I remember the radio
Of Boulevard of Broken Dreams always used to be on the radio and when I said what's fucked up
It always sound like say what's nuffed up? What's up?
It was all it goes what's left up and it always made me laugh
What was that one fallout boy song where he said this ain't a scene. It's a
a god damn arms race. Yeah and my mom one time got mad at me because I didn't know
that he sang god damn in the song. Yeah you know what else is a funny one?
I've been so mad about this. Another funny radio edit was was don't trust uh yeah never trust uh don't. I like bad bad that's my problem.
Yeah that was really good. That was one of the all time ones. And yeah like to like to that's my that's my problem.
- That's the problem.
Just don't even make the song.
- Repeating the word that came before
is the funniest way to do it.
- I would so much rather have David Guetta,
Baby Rexha, I'm gonna have the best
freaking night of my life.
That is better.
- The best one is obviously the bedrock one.
I've said it before, but the one where
Nicki Minaj says, "Boingus, let me put this
"boingus on your sideburns."
- Wait, I don't know that one.
- Yeah, I've definitely talked about it.
- I think it's time to put this boingus
on your sideburns.
He say I'm bad.
- Radio edit of Bedrock, yeah.
- Boingus?
(laughing)
You have to be mishearing that.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- It can't be Boingus, man.
- I totally--
- I think it's time to put this Boingus on your sideburn.
- We can't look it up,
'cause we've looked this up on the podcast before.
- No, Boinga?
- We just looked up Boinga.
- Wait, this is what you--
(laughing)
This is what she's putting on your sideburns, man?
This is Boingus from Backyardigans?
- Whoa!
- Oh shit, he's green.
The green got green screened out.
He's green so he's transparent.
I think it's time to put this boingus on your sideburns.
Boingus.
There he is.
That's a boingus.
I hope this is the clean version.
The one thing-- I'm still mad about this to this day,
and I've brought this up a million times,
but there was a kid I got into an argument with because he
was trying to tell me--
he was trying to tell me that the song "Beep"
by the Pussycat Dolls, he's like, yeah,
you know it doesn't actually swear,
they just say beep instead.
actually pretty good song for that reason. I was like, well no, like I didn't know
what the word euphemism was and I kept trying to explain to him like, no, like
it's like, like that's the joke and he just kept going, no it's like a clean
song. No, it's actually way dirtier because they're making you think of the
words. Whoa! Reminds me of a certain Louis CK bit. Is this it? Here it is. You got to get to
the Nicki part. And she knows she bad. Grocery bag.
(Music)
(Laughter)
Okay, alright. She says put this boingus on your sideburns.
Now that I've heard it, it's, it's, it's, she says on this, on this.
Yeah.
I think it's time to put this on this, on this.
All right, but it's on you.
Way to just destroy the whole, the best part of the song.
But she says "this on" and so they just took that.
This on this on your side.
It's boingus.
But it does sound like boingus.
It's boingus. She fucking said boingus.
Would you do Nicki Minaj's boingus?
Imagine after a show, she picks you out of the crowd.
She picks you out of the crowd and she says
"You wanna see my fucking boingus?"
You want to see my fucking boy?
Also, also well the thing is it going on the sideburns
I don't want to see your boingus cuz it's probably been ravaged by plastic surgery true
Well that that's why first of all she doesn't have a pussy. She has a boingus. It's
Her boingus is big enough that goes on both your sideburns wait a boingus is not a boingus is a cock
No, that's a boingus right there a boingus is not a fucking vagina
There's no world where you would call a vagina boingus. She has a penis dude
She has to
That's what she said. She's saying that you could she could put her boingus or on your sideburns
But even then just like putting the boingus on the sideburns is like that thing's got to be
ginormous
Maybe she's got a big one a big boingus big boingus. Yeah, I mean yeah, she probably does I got lost in the boingus
- Swam to her butt. - Swam to her flip.
(laughing)
- Drown in the boingus so I swam to her flip.
To her rear.
(laughing)
- Her tub.
- I would like to get down on Nicki Minaj
and it's all just, it's all bop it stuff.
It's like swirly pigtails that you pull
and fucking flashing red lights that you have to slam.
- And then there's one part where all the lights
in the room flashing goes, "Uh-oh, Boingus time!"
- Boingus, get as many bonus coins as possible.
- Boingus coins.
- Get as many Boingus coins as you can in one minute.
- Three, two, one. - There he is, folks.
It's Boingus!
- It's Boingus.
- You gotta pull Boingus in. - There should be more
mini games in women's bodies.
- Yeah. (laughing)
- I honestly think that.
It would make stuff a lot more fun.
I'd be able to pay attention more.
- Yeah.
- If there was a Boingus that was flashing at me
and I had to get as many coins as possible.
- Catch the boingus.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Boingus is running around the room.
- Yeah, the boingus pops out.
- I have a boingus net.
- Dude, oh, imagine that,
you're about to go down on Nicki Minaj
and then the boingus pops out of her house.
Starts running around your house.
- The boingus fell out.
- Starts running around like that
motherfucking funny ass video of the Shrek
doing the dog run.
And you have to chase it around
and catch him and put him back.
- It looks like the--
- And Nicki Minaj's looking at you,
she's like, "Catch the boingus!"
It looks like the worm aliens from Men in Black.
Yeah, exactly.
It's running around, just jumping around, doing mischief.
Boinging.
Thing one, thing two.
Yeah, it's throwing flour across the room.
It's going in your cabinets.
Catch him where he multiplies and then he splits in half.
Banging pots and pans.
Yeah, he jumps in water and like a gremlin, like a magui, he starts to multiply.
Then you got a hundred boinguses.
There's nothing to do but take out a flamethrower.
That's going to hurt Nikki.
Yeah, anytime when you get to that point the boingis is need to go and then she's one gets out of the room
Yeah, that's world domination. They're crying from phantom pain
Because you
My boingis this is a great idea for a movie yeah, Nicki Minaj Nicki Minaj is boingis revenge
Yeah, it's called the boingis challenge, dude. I need to see your boingis all right
I'm gonna go home and look up pictures of Nicki Minaj is boingis
videos Danish yeah boingis all right bye boingis make him as big as humanly
possible boingis make Andrew Tate as big as there oh yeah oh yeah watch this to
play us out oh wait hit him what get him one good hit yeah give me give me a hit
*laughter*