(upbeat music)
- Why does he clap into your microphone?
I never understood that.
- Why does he clap into your microphone, man?
- What do you mean?
(laughing)
- So that the sound picks up.
- Why does he clap into your microphone?
- We all have microphones, he could do it in his own.
- How is he gonna hold his microphone and clap?
- He's holding it like this.
(claps)
He could do that.
- But the sound picks up better
from the front of the microphone.
- All right.
Also, do you maybe consider that maybe me and him just have a chemistry and a teamwork that we like to...
Yeah, it's a teamwork vibe. Teamwork makes the dream work, jerk.
I made that up.
I made up the last part.
That sounds beautiful as fuck.
Teamwork makes the dream work, weird jerk.
Damn, your rhyme is crazy.
They put 200 milligrams of caffeine into these...
The Dunkin' Ice Coffee Girl Scout Thin Mints?
have it's like 225 yeah and I bought that because the the the bodega that we
always go to has fallen off they've lost the bodega the bodega the bodega yeah
the it also has 260 calories per bottle man shit you gotta watch out for that
man yeah oh I failed groggless January you did fail groggless January I was
like, "Oh, I'm like two weeks in," and then immediately failed.
How was, now that you're on the other end of it, grogless versus grogging? Which one is
better?
Well, I mean, I was grogless for six months, and the whole time all I wanted to do was drink
one beer.
But not this one grog.
Six months.
Yeah.
Well, this is two weeks.
Two weeks, no grog, trip report.
Trip report. Well, the first week, I only stopped drinking because I was on antibiotics for my
wisdom tooth infection.
Yeah, it's a good thing good and then
The doctor said I would die
Poison and then I stopped for another week after that I was doing soda and bitters at the bar and then why
They give you that for free fuck that man. No, it's free. You know what? I like if I'm not drinking diet coke
Why am I getting a soda and bitters?
I'm at the bar. I'm not drinking. I'm just licking my lips in the inside of my mouth. Yeah, not
No, you're not I've seen you have a water see I got a hole now
I have a hole I've never got my wisdom tooth used to be and now I'm just doing this
That's nothing I'm putting my tongue in the hole oh
That was weird you look like a pirate you like the guy with no tongue for parts of the Caribbean
Stop it's my new style of speaking. You'll be a pretty good old mouth because you will in the next
I'm gonna look old dentures pretty yeah
No, I mean I have taken I brush my teeth after drinking that I think I'm doing a teeth healing journey
I think that your teeth might even be that's the one part of me
That's it might even be bad to brush them because you're like get your past the protective coat
And you're getting you're just like scraping away all the good stuff my teeth
I actually that is what happened my teeth have right after Pat's teeth problems. I've been having teeth problems, too
Like cuz we were kissing. Yeah, it's just they hurt and it just goes into my it goes up into my brain. Yeah. Oh my
That literally sounded like diarrhea
That sounded so fucking gross.
What? What?
It was in my mouth. It only was ever in the
can and then in my mouth. That is not gross.
That is not gross. That was pig energy? Yeah. You thought it was water?
I pour the
I pour the bang in the coffee cup so that nobody
So people think I'm drinking coffee, but actually I'm drinking fucking bang energy.
Because I don't want anyone to know that I drink.
That's true.
Well yeah, that's the perfect...
I thought that was water!
That's the perfect cup to pretend as though it was coffee.
What else could this be?
What are you drinking?
Oh yeah, what do you think?
See, I want one of these cups where it says like,
G-Fuel, Bang, Ghost Energy, Monster, White Monster.
All that kind of stuff yeah, I'm gonna drink the rest and it has bubbles from my mouth, but I don't really care yucky
You don't think that's yucky man. I think people in the military drink bang is that true. Yeah
I don't think I know it's not it's not the bang. That's gross here. It's you
Regurgitating it and I didn't ever I didn't regurgitate you
But you just brundle fly that never went you go. It never went down my you are a brundle fly
Don't know what you're talking is that what is that Dungeons and Dragons? What is that from the don't tell him from the fly
God the movie fuck
But I thought sex shit. I thought that was a mild-mannered
Nebbish nerd yeah named Brundle mm-hmm. I'm gonna go God. He's gonna start going cheeseburger cheeseburger
As we does in the movie says that in the movie. I've seen the movie in a minute
I don't remember that line. He says like he says the Gina Davis. He's like two words
cheeseburger. You know, I've been reading a lot about, or not reading, I've been
listening to a lot of interesting stuff about ADHD and autism, and one of the
biggest, one of the biggest like things that people use to diagnose ADHD and
autism in adults is like hyper specific memory about movies and television. And I keep
hearing that and being like oh man, man, that's crazy.
That's so crazy.
Yeah, it's pretty interesting.
Who's telling you all this stuff?
Why are you reading them?
I'm not reading them.
I'm listening to a--
Yeah, why are you doing that?
I don't know, just fucking any four hour YouTube video,
I'll just press play on it while I'm at the dog park.
You know?
Well, hey, to prove that theory more,
I've been doing that with the New Vegas lore.
Oh yeah, those are bad, dude.
Once you run out of the good years of Opie and Anthony on YouTube,
and you just want something that is a low hum that you don't listen to at all.
I was talking to you about this yesterday.
I will listen to lectures because it's just a guy with a pretty decent voice talking for a little bit.
Yeah.
I've been watching this one video. It was an hour of New Vegas.
It was like, "Here's some things that you might have missed."
and the guy just keeps mispronouncing
like every like food that comes up.
- Men dots.
- What I do, I watch six hour video,
I watch like six hour like stream vods
of people playing like Dark Souls or something,
which is a game that I'm not that good at.
And I watch it and these are like people
who are like setting world records
for like beating every boss.
And I watch it and I see them die and I go,
fucking idiot.
- That guy sucks.
- I'm gonna watch a different guy.
- Yeah.
I turn on one video and I see him die halfway through and I'm like, "God fuck, I'm never
watching this again.
He's the worst player of all time."
You know what, I can't even do that.
I've been doing it with New Vegas because you can't do that with Skate 3 or whatever.
You can't do that with skate video games because it's all people trying to like, "I'm going
to do triple backflip Christ Air."
It's like you are not treating it like a simulation game.
You are fucking up so bad.
You treat it like a simulation game?
You put it on hardcore mode and then you try to do like actual cool shit not triple backflip
Yeah, it doesn't sound cool. No trickliners
That's my message to you. I skate for comes out your day will come
That's a good thing. No your day will you will rue the day that?
When you play skate, do you what do you have like a storyline for your guy when you're around you don't do that
No, it's just like, I wish I could do this in real life.
You don't do it like...
I always do. I always have a...
You have to.
What?
My mic stopped working for a second.
My storyline's like, my guy has a polyp in his stomach, he's gonna die.
Yeah.
It's becoming cancerous, he doesn't know it.
Yeah, and you're playing Mario Odyssey.
Yeah.
That's my storyline for every video game.
'Cause then that's a perfect, kind of like, in-canon explanation
for when I get bored and I never play the game again.
Yeah.
Like, oh, my guy got to the dinosaur kingdom and he died.
I do, I do, uh, yeah.
- He doesn't exist anymore, I can't play the game anymore.
- He played Mario Odyssey in the same way
that people play Grand Theft Auto,
where you just play it like a normal guy.
- Yeah, yeah.
- But I'm walking around.
Yeah, my story is that it's a make-a-wish kid
who wished he could do Mario for a day.
And then I made an entire plan for him.
- He never gets past the first level.
- No, he dies so fast, he dies so fast.
- And I play about 50 or 60 of those runs per day.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
Just die instantly.
- I give them a full name, a full backstory.
- Yeah.
I hold a funeral for them in my apartment.
My girlfriend's like, "What are you doing?"
And I'm like, "Gregor died."
You're flushing a piece of paper down the toilet.
Like it's a fish funeral.
Yeah.
Man, I've been playing so much fucking New Vegas, though.
I don't know, like...
We should go to current Vegas.
We really should. I really would like to.
I was doing...
Exactly.
The Wisdom Tooth Recovery got me into New Vegas,
and I have not...
Nah, I think I have like 24 hours logged in.
I started like a week ago.
- By God, that's a day.
- Yeah, that's a whole day lost.
- In a week? - Fuck me, man.
A day in a week?
- That's almost three or four hours per day.
- That's bloody long.
- No, dude, it's like eight hours a day now.
- That math doesn't add up.
- I'm putting in the work in on my hot day ways.
- And you have way more than 24 hours.
- Yeah, I haven't checked in a while.
- Yeah.
- I don't wanna look at the number
of how much I've been playing it because--
- 'Cause you'll smile too much.
- It'll make me upset.
I just got my virtual reality goggles back.
You got them back?
They got refurbished and I'm going to be--
They refurbished?
And I'll be entering a completely different reality
shortly after we finish this episode.
Yeah.
I will be bye bye.
I will be gone.
Yeah.
I've been getting lost in my--
Mr. Gumdrop, my character.
I play a game where I'm God.
Yeah.
Yeah, I play a game where I'm God
and you can pick people up and just throw them off
the fucking world.
I'm the messiah of the wasteland.
No, you're not.
That's what it says in the game.
Fuck you, man.
I was talking to him yesterday.
You've played it.
You know what it says.
I've never played it.
- I was talking to Cameron yesterday about,
I have been doing some Grand Theft Auto playing.
- Yeah.
- GTA V and GTA IV.
- Do you play as Trevor?
Do you play as only Trevor?
- No, the online.
- Oh.
- Doing the online.
- And I had, but I do also do the thing
where I think it's fun to pretend
that I'm just a normal guy and walk around.
And I had one of the--
- You're playing free guy.
(laughing)
By the way, I love that movie.
I know you do.
That's why you love that movie.
I fucking love that movie.
You love that movie because you get on GTA Online.
100%.
Yeah, you just figured it out.
That is why I love that movie.
I've done that since I was a kid.
Play Grand Theft Auto, like you're just walking around,
doing your thing.
You never run.
Because what am I running in my real life, right?
I just want to go--
You have the phone open.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just calling my cousin, talking to my cousin,
fucking hitting guys up.
But I had one of the stupidest thoughts
I've ever had in my entire life the other day playing that game.
where I was at a red light,
and you know you stop at the red lights
when you play like that,
and I was sitting at the red light,
and I was like, at some point I was like,
man, this red light's taking forever.
(laughing)
And I was like, why is this light taking so long?
Thinking that for whatever reason,
the people who make the game would be like
trying to make them a convenient time
between the red and the green lights,
and I couldn't believe that I--
takes place in Los Angeles and that traffic is bad as hell.
- Yeah, that is a really good point.
But like, of course the red lights take two minutes.
They don't, when they were programming it,
they were never like, well people are gonna stop
at the red lights.
- They want, people who play that game normal
want the red lights so you can run it.
- Yeah. - They're criminals.
- There's a big GTA online RP community, I've learned.
- That makes sense. - Oh yeah, there's huge ones.
That's like the biggest fucking thing.
- It's like 13 year olds pretending to be gang members
and shit.
Even better is the roblox one. Oh, we're the roblox servers that are called Chicago. Yeah, just walk around
I love the videos that they make of so funny, man
Shot up my ops party
It's just like I do people are like just cuz you know voice comm so people are just typing in the the roblox chat like oh
Shit, oh shit run. It's so funny when people like take that like RP so serious like we used to go into like the fucking
Star Wars Star Wars our servers on
I'm down. I love that shit, man. Yeah, I all I will say
The reason why I love it is because I always go into it thinking like oh
Man, it might actually be fun to do this and then once I get in and it's not fun. It's not
- You literally start walking around with your open mic
going (imitates buzzing)
- The thing about RP servers on Gmod and stuff
is that is the societal release valve
where if those didn't exist,
we would have the Nazi party again.
(laughing)
Those are the people who you log in and they're like,
okay, do this, do this, do this, do this, do this,
and you have to stand in this room for 72 hours
before you can play the game.
- The rules that they make,
or it's so like, if you get hit with the fail RP in that,
you're getting reprimanded by like an ultra-neuro.
- It goes all the way up.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, they have a system.
- They have to get their super box in.
- They're literally building a virtual Reich
on a Star Wars TIE fighter or whatever.
- And they're not even, they're playing as the clones.
- Yeah, and they're playing as the clones.
- This shit is making me laugh.
- They're not even playing as the damn Empire.
- Yeah.
- It's fucked up.
I feel like the 501st Legion was a little bit chill,
from what I remember on the show.
- I don't, yeah, I'm just laughing.
- Clone Wars.
(laughter)
- Okay, all right.
Clone Wars was one of those shows where people were like,
man, this is a good show.
- Yeah, that's what I was thinking.
- And then I would watch it and I was like, this is a tune.
- Well, that's what, I never cared about Star Wars.
- He's doing his head shake.
He's like, wow.
- Yeah.
- I'm like, that's what I'm saying.
- Well, that's the thing.
- He's like, forget if you like the lore.
- That show, that show, that show Primal.
- Yeah.
- With the samurai jack guy.
It's the, so Clone Wars was--
- Jendi Tardadasti.
- Yeah, that guy, he did the,
I didn't know he did Clone Wars.
And I like watched Prime and I was like, oh, this is sick.
And I was like, I wonder what else this guy did.
And even loving Prime, I saw, oh, Clone Wars.
Oh, no.
Yeah, no.
I didn't like the 30 minute,
like the 30 minute long, like Clone Wars,
the Tardowoski ones.
Didn't watch them.
Oh, you didn't watch?
I have the DVD if you want it.
See, I remember buying, when I like first got,
my dad got a Blu-ray player.
I bought like the first season of the Clone Wars on Blu-ray.
You're talking about the 3D one or the...
Dude, I don't know.
The Tardivash one.
The TV show.
Yeah, there's two.
Fuck you.
The one that the Samurai Jack got made.
Shut up! Shut up!
I don't know what you're talking about.
There, we were talking about...
We were talking about two different things.
No, we're talking...
There's this TV show.
There was a Cartoon Network show.
There's two TV shows of the Clone Wars.
Whatever was the best...
The good one that people liked.
The cartoon one or the 3D one?
It's a 3D one.
Okay.
That's all you had to say.
Okay, 3D one.
You didn't have to tell me to shut up.
I'm really sorry.
I'm really fucking sorry. I got way too into my RP Ray then. I'm sorry.
You're doing jerk RP.
I was doing jerk RP.
But I bought the Blu-ray and I think I watched half of one episode and I was
like, Oh yeah, I'm not 10 years old. I don't need to watch this video.
I thought it was a video. These videos are not good. Is the 2D one better?
The 2D one is better.
But the 3D one is the one that people like, right?
- The 2D one is the one that the cool animator guy made.
But I never watched either of them.
- I don't give a fuck about Samurai Jack either, man.
- Yeah, me neither.
- I watched both of them.
(laughing)
- The only Star Wars--
- I always thought the name of the show Samurai Jack
was so lame.
I was like, fuck, I wanna watch something
that sounds cool like Naruto.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Or Bobobo.
- If I'm looking, listen, I'll say this much.
If I'm looking at a samurai,
I don't want a white guy named Jack.
- No.
- Well, I don't think it's a white guy.
- He's white.
- I thought he was-- - His name's Jack.
- Jackie Chan.
- Jackie, you think Jackie Chan was born
and they said, "Your name is Jackie."
- Yes. - No.
I'm not gonna say what his real name was.
- What was his real name?
- I'm not gonna say it.
- All right. (laughs)
Okay.
- I'm not gonna say it. - You know Jackie Chan
hates America?
- He hates America and he hates his son.
- He loves Chinese communism. - He loves China
and he hates America. - He loves,
Chan Kong Sang, that's what I thought,
but I just didn't say it.
That's his real name.
- There's like a headline. - By the way,
Juvio isn't pulling this up,
but it says that on the screen.
It says, "Ten Kong," there we go.
Thank you so much.
I did not just say, "Ten Kong song," just guessing.
That's his real name. - There's like some headline
where it was like Jackie Chan saying how disappointed he was
in his son. - That's 'cause his son,
which I get this, his son was smoking reefer.
- Oh, yeah. - And reefer in China
is as bad as fucking freedom to them.
It represents freeing your mind
and being free from communistic,
basically the same thing as,
They're basically the same as Nazi Germany.
Exactly.
And so they were like, we have, there's a son.
That is not Jackie Chan, man.
That is not him, bro.
But they were like, okay, we're gonna put your son in total,
in a, that's not Jackie Chan.
That's a bald guy.
That is a bald guy, Jubio.
They were like, we're gonna put your son in a labor camp.
And Jackie Chan said, fuck it, I don't give a fuck.
Damn.
Yeah.
And then they killed his son.
It's just kind of a shame 'cause Jackie Chan,
you know, Jackie Chan, how often,
How often can you be the number one movie star
in both a communist and a free country?
- Yeah. - Not that often.
- At the same time.
And he was just like, he saw, he was like,
"I'm double number one, I'm top of the charts,
"music, movies, comics." - Double number one.
- That makes him number 11. - Double number one,
China, America. - Found you a pretty good
Chinese restaurant too. (laughs)
- China, America.
We could have, he could have created a new country.
- He could have, he definitely could have.
- He could have created China, America.
- He could have bridged the gap.
- And instead he's like, "I hate America."
- Yeah.
- Double number one, that does sound like a good restaurant.
(laughing)
Yeah, no he is a piece of crap though.
- Yeah, 'cause he's the reason nowadays
that all this nuclear stuff's going down.
90 seconds to midnight, did you see this?
- No, what's that?
- The doomsday clock, Patrick.
- Oh yeah, I saw that.
- 90 seconds to midnight.
- That's not my problem.
- So I saw this doomsday clock 90 seconds to midnight,
I'm watching this time lapse of the doomsday clock
since its creation.
It's a horrible clock.
That's right.
It's completely broken.
That clock started at four minutes.
Is it rush hour or Shanghai noon where they get on top of the doomsday clock?
Shanghai nights.
Shanghai noon.
Nights.
No, it's Jackie Chan and Owen Wilson.
There's a different movie I'm thinking of then.
Is it Owen Wilson?
Jackie Chan and Owen Wilson?
Yeah.
Around the World in 80 Days?
No, fuck you, man.
That's a balloon movie.
Yeah, but that's Jackie Chan and Owen Wilson.
He's in a balloon the whole time or some shit.
That's like James and the Giant Peach.
It is not.
Yeah, it is.
James and the Giant Peach.
- It is. - 'Cause there's
a giant peach. - But the doomsday clock
is basically, we're doomed, is the day.
- It's 90 seconds away.
- Thanks for explaining it.
(laughing)
- Basically, we're completely doomed,
so there's not even a point in even looking at the clock.
- Well, hey, I've been prepared.
I've been playing New Vegas all day.
- True. - I know exactly what to do.
- What's your, you know what, I just watched a video.
- I just have to get some power armor and some pinyon nuts.
- I just watched a video that doesn't, don't exist yet.
I just watched a video that was a--
- What are you on about?
- They don't have it.
Dude, that's a great thing about the apocalypse.
You can just start speaking.
Well, that's literally because
You play False Jubilee, because half the fucking
people in the burned down America
have British accents for some reason.
Because everybody went to a
theater and watched Mad Max Fury Road,
now when America is bombed
and it becomes a full desert, everyone will just
start acting like Mad Max.
Oh, this is... I saw that movie. This is what it's
going to be. Definitely the coolest version.
- There, I, exactly, everyone's just gonna start
immediately like, like burning shit down,
like stabbing people.
Why don't we just make a movie about the apocalypse
where it's like, it's actually chill.
- It's actually rather chill.
- I wanna see-- - It's actually chill as fuck
and we can just start like a new type of barter system.
- Calm, calm Cameron, yeah. - I wanna see,
calm as fuck.
- Kind of like a chill, what if instead of
everybody goes crazy, everybody just gets depressed
during the apocalypse?
- Damn. - Damn.
- Right, and it's you walking down the street.
Something in the way.
- Yeah. - Right, you're throwing,
you're, Pete, you're about to drop--
- Boomsday.
- You're about to drop a bottle of something into--
- Absinthe.
- Into recycling.
- Yeah, absinthe.
- And then you're like, fuck it's the end of the world,
fuck it, throw it right on the ground.
(imitates explosion)
- Shatters.
- Jump in and away.
- Yeah, true.
- A dollar blows down the street and you just watch it.
- You almost go to pick it up and say--
- You just watch it.
- Oh shit, money doesn't mean fucking anything anymore.
- Do you think money would still be--
- Guess I needed this a whole lot a year ago,
but now it just seems like nothing.
Seems like a green piece of paper.
- What do you think the new money would be after?
- There wouldn't be any.
- No, 'cause they're, they clean their plates.
- Honestly, with bottle caps for water.
- It's so funny, it's like,
this, dollars, they don't mean anything anymore.
We need a new money.
- Yeah, bottle caps. - We need to come up
with something new. - Bottle caps.
- Honestly, dude, I hate to say it, women.
Women's bodies is what would probably become,
it's the truth, it's so sad.
- And that's, in "Fury Road" it was like,
oh, like women have not been pregnant in a million years.
- Water, I believe. - Yeah, it was water
was money but women are not pregnant ever again.
Wow.
Is that what it was?
Because they're lesbian.
Yeah, only pregnant women would come to the big guy.
Yeah, you're only allowed to get pregnant by him.
Only the big guy had pregnant women.
Charlize Theron, she had a short hair.
So a pregnant woman--
Well, so a pregnant woman maybe in that world
is not like money, but more like a peloton.
Or maybe someone who's really rich has one.
Yeah.
has a bunch. Yes, yes. Who has a bunch? You don't need more than one. If you're that fat,
like that big guy. Home Gym. Home Gym. That was his name, right? No. I thought you were
saying the guy named Home Gym. It was his name Joe. No, his name was Awesome. Oh, Home
Joe. Home Joe. Home Joe, yeah. I thought, I literally, I was thinking, who's Home Gym?
I know it was a Morton Joe, but I did think for a second it was a Morton Jim.
I do like the idea of a Morton Jim being like his twin brother.
His twin brother in calm mass.
Gets no fucking hoes.
And he's making a face.
No pregnant women.
Anytime now.
No water.
He's skinny as fuck.
Skinny as hell, no hair.
No long hair.
He's making that face to the camera, but he's got silver all over his mouth.
He's got, he still has the fucking crazy gas mask thing, but he also has to wear
these thick glasses and his eyes look fucked up and big.
Here's the thing.
And he doesn't look cool with the mask.
First date with a more tan Joe. I'm making them fucking take a swim in the swimming pool. Yep, right take that makeup off
That's right. Yeah, nasty ass wash that shit off. I want to see the real you a more
God, you're covered in boils. I got a skeleton now
Put that mask back on you got acne under there. You got acne around your lip
You know cuz I that mask bro, but imagine imagine fucking him in the back of his car though
Me. Oh my god. You got that guy for you. He's playing birthday
Yeah, yeah, I'm birthday sex
No the guitar guy he had like no mouth he has no eyes no eyes yeah, well yeah, then he can't see you fucking
That's just the perfect. He'll smell me and we're more tango
Afterwards I go from like smell my tube so my bro guess I stood
Huh, are you asking me what you just did no that's what you just did it's a smell my dad
Oh smell your - guess what I just did. Oh, this is still in this scenario. Yeah
You know would be the worst part of the apocalypse is all the graffiti. Yeah, it'd be disgusting
I saw some graffiti putting up Monty Python references. Have you read this happen? I saw some graffiti
Today I walked here walk to the office. I don't usually walk but I saw about 10 minutes in my walk
I saw a graffiti that just said vagina. Oh, it's like I was like my tag. Well, I will that I was like, oh
That's funny. Some kid decided to write vagina on this. That's funny. And then ten minutes later
I saw in a different color somebody wrote vagina like it's the guy's name. That's my tag your name. Your tag is not vagina
I've been throwing that up all around town. You've been throwing that vagina up all around town throwing up my vagina
Everywhere in town why look on the wall you'll see my I've been very prolific with my graffiti lately
I've been throwing up a lot of tags my tag is deli right, but it's just a normal font and I put it above stores damn
My I'm seeing you're like one of the most prolific writers. I guess believe in the smiley face killer no
It's about killers. There's a theory bye-bye man. There's it shut up
Don't say that man. Is that don't don't think it don't say it. I'm moving on there's
(laughing)
There's a theory, a real world theory.
- A theory.
- A theory about different serial killers,
or that there's a murdering ring of psycho crazies.
- Congress.
- That there's apparently, there's an epidemic
in this country of young men who walk home from bars
- Oh, and they get thrown in the river.
- They fall into the river banks.
- Yeah, yeah.
and they die. One of them was at the Charles River. Yeah, yeah. And at almost all of these...
I remember that. My mom thought it was me and called me. Really? She's not so smart.
She called me and was like, "Are you okay?" I was like, "Yeah, fucking...
I'm gonna go in the river." At almost all of the scenes of these crimes, or not crimes as Patrick would
have you believe, there are smiley face drawings.
Shoot. I feel like that's just a coincidence. What'd I tell you?
Yep. What did I tell you? Running interference. I knew that he would
be so terrified that he would ignore it. He's on the government payroll. He's on the government
payroll. He would ignore it. No, no, no. He's scared that it's going to happen to him and
so he decides I'm going to push that out. Yeah, are you kidding? I'm the perfect candidate
for that. Don't say that publicly. Why? Because now you're going to die. I'm not going to
die. You're going to die. You'll easily be literally die. I'll never die. Stay away from
rivers. I'm so healthy I'll stay alive forever. Stay away from rivers, swimming pools, bathtubs,
oceans, lakes, ponds. I don't even. Rain puddles that are too deep. I live in a river desert.
You could definitely, I could definitely see you. Like a pool desert? I live in a river
desert. That's just a desert. There's no rivers around me. You go over the river every day.
I could definitely see... I don't mean to be rude, I could definitely see you drowning
in a puddle on the side of the street. Nah. I could see myself falling asleep in the snow
and not knowing. You would see yourself in a puddle, reflection right before you fell
into it and drowned. Yes. Your last thought would be, this guy's getting too close to
me. Caravan of Courage, the Ewoks movie? Nope. Oh. What the fuck is that, man? You watched
a whole movie about Ewoks? I'm gonna start, I think to start positivity and start positivity
between males, I'm going to start the frowny face helper.
- Ah!
- The opposite of the smiley face killer.
I see a man walking home alone, drunk at night.
I walk up to him, I say,
"Hey buddy, let me help you get home."
And then I draw a frowny face on the ground.
- See, I like that, but you're engaging in the same
kind of horrific irony that the killer himself is doing.
- No, because it's the frowny face helper,
because why are they walking home alone?
They're probably depressed.
- But you're, the frowny face is for the killer.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- It's like, "Oh, you better be sad."
- He can't put his tag up, 'cause you've already tagged it
and that'd be some toy shit.
- The scariest part about this whole serial killer thing,
the smiley face killer, it's organized on 4chan.
- Ew. - No.
- Yeah, so you know they're-- - That's incel vibes.
- You know they're right wing dirtbags.
- That's literally fucking incel mashup vibes.
- Yeah, that's the website that cultivated
and created the meme of Pedo Bear.
- Yep. - Yes, yes.
- And they think that things like that is enjoyable.
- You know what else they made?
- What else did they make?
- Freaking Pepe the frog.
I heard they made a Pokemon ROM hack.
- Fuck me.
- They hacked a game that was not their property.
- Say psych.
- Say less.
- Please say psych.
- I heard they made an 8x8 image with a bunch of different
album covers of different underground artists on it.
- I heard that they did that and they made a chart
that was meant to lead youths, preppy youths,
down the path of emo, goth, sulking, mopey,
aggressive, violent, electronic, distorted.
Maybe that's how-- - You know what?
I heard that they-- - Oh my God.
- I heard they were responsible for--
- Music with those adjectives. - For getting people,
people getting into friggin' the money store
and the deep web. - Wait, I think I'm realizing
how this happened. - I think that's true.
- I think the smiley face serial killers,
the way that they get young men to join
into their ring of murderers,
is that they make these starter packs.
They get 'em listening to Pink Floyd.
- Oh my God. - They get 'em listening
to Swans. - Fuck.
- Oh, ew! - All this psychotic bullshit.
- Yeah. - Right?
They get-- - And what, and what--
- Bad melody. - And what swims in a river?
Officious swans. Oh fuck and especially in the Charles River. All right, you're right. They got swan boats there
So then these guys are those are big swans. These guys are running around
Those are those are real fucking animals are big animals. Somebody should call PETA about that. Yeah. Yeah, fucking Christ
Who's PETA PETA who yeah PETA in the child Griffin? Yeah, exactly. All right moving on. Yeah, we've already done
No, I was I'd yep
You I said PETA and I laughed so I had to finish it out even though I knew it was nothing
I think it was something. I really don't think it was I think it was something Cameron. I
Think that I will be joining the military
Nope
Wanted to announce this publicly I'm joining the military they wouldn't want you
First of all they would accept me and I'm they would see the height requirement
They would see all the footage of you playing jerk RP.
And they'd say, "That guy."
There's only one single clip of me playing jerk RP.
No, there's a lot of you playing jerk RP.
No, there's not.
I'm not a jerk.
There's probably 300 clips of you playing jerk RP.
That's a fucking lie.
Probably 300 hours.
I was being a jerk for one instance where I told you to shut up because you were talking
nonsense.
I was not talking nonsense.
I was talking about- You were talking about Star Wars.
I was talking about real shit.
No, you weren't.
Real shit that happened.
You actually were not talking about real shit.
Caravan of Courage, I was talking about that.
- No you weren't, that was a different time.
- Yep, he puts his, oh yeah, I didn't even,
he touches the pond and then he gets trapped under it.
He gets trapped under the pond, yeah.
Mace, Sindel's brother.
- Mace Wundu?
- No, it's a white guy.
- Mace Wundu, is it white?
- Something, Mace, he's a boy,
and they're looking for their parents and their Ewoks.
- Your eyes have nothing behind them anymore.
I'm looking into them, there's nothing.
What are you on, Jubio?
What was that?
Why was there a Reddit 18+ page that you had to click?
'Cause he's just doing his thing, man.
What are you looking up, man?
Stop looking at fucking nasty sex, man.
DM if you want a jerk.
You're distracting Patrick.
Yeah, dude, I want a jerk.
I will say, this is cool.
If they did a real life Simpsons, it would have to be PG.
Yeah.
PG.
Paul Giamatti.
It would have to be PG-13, maybe.
It would have to be PG-13 because the jokes
would be a little inappropriate.
Wait, was the Simpsons movie PG-13?
Well, I think if they, yeah,
because they showed Bart's doodle finger.
I would hope that if they did a live action
Homer Simpson movie, that they would,
I mean, so it could be PG, Paul Giamatti,
but I would love for them to do kind of like
a worldwide talent search and find the most,
'cause you know, he looks like Homer,
but there's gotta be someone in some country
that looks even more like Homer.
- Looks and acts like Homer.
- Yeah, could even be in the US,
but I want them to search all around the world.
- Could even be in this room.
I'm not so, I don't, I see, you don't look like Homer at all.
- You don't look like Homer.
You look like, you look like Krusty's monkey.
- A little bit like Homer.
- You look more like the evil monkey from Family Guy.
- Look at the white shirt.
- Do that again, do that again.
You look a little more like--
- You legit, you look like Curious George.
(laughing)
You look like Curious George
and Cameron should be the yellow guy.
- The man in the yellow hat, the yellow guy.
You know every fucking name of every Ewok
that's ever been drawn.
- Not true, I only know Wicked and Lowbring.
You don't know the man with the yellow hat. No. The human from Curious What? I was talking about this yellow guy. That's Homer.
You don't look like Homer. You don't look anything like Homer. Stop doing that. You don't look like Homer.
You don't you don't. Do you think Marge would confuse us? No. No. As twin brothers? With that white shirt and
this face you're doing
you look like Greg Heffley.
Now you're playing jerk RP
Camera does look a little bit like time to play jerk her pee not your time you fucker
I got I'm playing jerk RP. I'm playing you're a jerk RP. I saw it go back in time to 2010
I get really good at jerking
I saw video a dolly parton and I think that I would still I would still beat that beat the monkey
She looks like paper now. I know and I think that I would she looks like legit do summer
I would do some origami with Dolly Parton
With her body older I would fold her you I'll fold her now
Yeah, that's heavy. Yeah, it's like you literally you could have told me
Anything else I'm sweating. Mm-hmm
You better be making me sweat you better be
You and Dolly
Imagining you two in a room together. Oh, man, I wouldn't even want to be in that room
Imagine this your brother and Dolly Parton
On the doorknob
Get this they're coming they're coming in for Thanksgiving right and your parents were a little iffy about them staying in the same bedroom
Right he comes out of the room. He's really drunker stinks. Oh
Yep, he took his finally took his ring off. Yeah, and it's there's a there's been a culture of fungus
Green beneath and you know why it's not more. It's putting his thing in her thing our green thing
- Bang, right back. - You know, here's what I would be,
he comes out, he's been with Dolly Parton this whole time,
he comes out, he's got a complete,
like an exploded dynamite, a giant just like soot face,
right, and then she pops out,
and both of her boobs have banana peeled over
because they completely exploded.
- Oh my, fucking god. - Bang.
- They filled them up with dynamite.
- They did. - Back in the day.
- They didn't know how big they did.
- They didn't know what silicon was.
- They started throwing whatever in there.
- Silicone or silicon?
- Silicon is the valley, silicon is the--
Human creation well, it's not a human creation, but yeah, it's an inhuman creation it is in human creation station burning it
Wait, okay. Why is not a human creation? Well rubber is is
Is like a plant yeah, but is silicone growth the plant don't do they make silicone rubber is from a tree
They probably size it yeah
synthetic rubber
What huh?
That we were talking about no we've devolved into talking about on this show synthetic rubber rubber
Yeah, we used to talk about real evolved into talking about real shit. You just want to talk about you walk. Yes
I want to talk about low-grade nobody gives a fuck
People literally there are hundreds of people who care about synthetic rubber, and there's not a single person on earth who cares about you walk
I'm gonna
Get back to talk about synthetic rubber guess what hey here's the least here's the thing you walk mask
- Guess what it's made out of?
- What?
- Synthetic rubber.
- So I saw this video actually yesterday
of their rolling silicone, like this.
- What do you mean they're rolling it?
- They had big bunches of it
and they're putting it onto a roller
and it was flattening out and squeezing.
- That's so awesome.
- It was cool and I asked my girlfriend,
is that, I said is that Airheads?
And she said, no!
I said why?
And she said 'cause it's giant.
- Where were you watching it?
- Facebook Watch.
- Just on the TV?
- The phone.
I was spying on my girlfriend's phone.
- I do that a lot.
- I said, "Is that Airheads?"
And she said, "No, it's, look it, it's so big."
And I was like, "Well, I don't know, they could cut it up."
- Yeah.
- And then I said, "Well, what is it then?"
She was like, "I don't know."
- Here's what I like to do.
- I just, I really like--
- Turns out it was silicone on a big roller.
- Like, peering over someone's shoulder
and it's just like a video, just factory stuff,
just going on, that's so funny.
- You don't, that doesn't happen to you?
- No.
all the time. Is that airheads?
Here's what...
Are they making airheads?
You're watching somebody on live.
Somebody on live on the train.
I'm like, oh.
Here's what I love doing.
If my wife is sitting on the couch
and she's on her phone, I love walking up and being like
who the fuck are you talking to?
And then she's playing like Poppy Jump or Talking Ben
or looking at a photo of her mom.
She's playing Talking Ben?
Yeah, you know, past the time. Sunday afternoon.
She's learning. She's learning colors and shapes. It's cool.
We're talking Tom, or one of the more adult versions.
Who the fuck are you talking to?
Who the fuck is that?
Oh, now he's making fun of me. Awesome, you asshole. Now you're making fun of me, you asshole.
Luger says what?
(laughing)
- Got your ass!
- Who says what?
- What?
Oh, fuck!
(laughing)
- Those games are actually so much fun.
- Remember that video?
It's like the neighbor's fighting,
and the guy says,
I don't know, I can't find it,
I don't remember it that well.
He says like, "Dumbass says what?"
And then his wife immediately goes, "What?"
- Yeah, I do remember that.
Crazy irate neighbors.
- Yeah.
- That's the name of the video.
I need to watch more.
It's a really good video.
Oh dude, I've been looking at, because I've been making the thumbnails for the YouTube,
I've been looking at other YouTube thumbnails to see how to play the game, you know?
Yeah.
And Judge Judy has the best ones.
You should just start stealing those.
That's what I did.
The last episode that we did, the picture of the lady is from a Judge Judy clip.
That is awesome.
It's literally called Judge Judy Destroys Karen.
Judy destroys she is a Karen that's she's the final boss of Karen she's the
only Karen almost her and she is so rude her and Nancy Grace those are the big
Karen's of the grace love to call - there it is judge Judy destroyed this Karen
that's the oh yeah that is the same yeah that's awesome yeah she is the best
thumbnails do yeah she is ugly and fat - Nancy Grace
Nancy Grace addicted to calling kids tots every time that like I would say
- She's addicted. - She's addicted.
- No, she's completely addicted to that.
- Are you addicted to talking about Ewoks?
'Cause you do that shit way too much.
- Yes, 'cause they're a little cute and cuddly.
(laughing)
- Shut up.
I hate, how often do you--
- Ewoks is an animal that if it was a real animal,
I would be one of those guys who lives in India
and watches YouTube videos of like,
Ewok gets fucking eviscerated in Mousetrap.
- Yeah.
- Orangutan crushes Ewok skull.
Good torture Ewok, hate Ewok pests.
- Yeah.
- Commenting like-- - Little Ewok brain crushed out.
- Can you have a dog attack the Ewok next?
- Yeah.
- Making requests for a new, for a Mongoose.
- Little Ewok scream.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Meow!
(laughing)
- I know, wait, that's R2's scream.
- They can't, they don't have higher reasoning skills,
do they? - Ewoks?
I've seen one eat a cracker.
Are they intelligent?
Do they have intelligence?
Yeah.
Or are they animals?
Have you seen Return of the Jedi?
Do they have an academic culture?
Oh yeah, they fight with spears.
Yeah, they fight with spears and they have a bunch of traps and loads.
Yes, very intelligent.
They can make hang gliders.
Oh wow.
I can't make a hang glider.
They say like, "chuta!"
Oh.
They say that.
Isn't that what Borat calls a pussy?
I think so, yeah.
It is.
Oh my god.
Ewoks are fucking disgusting.
Oh my god, they're horny as hell.
Ewoks are horny as hell.
Fucking disgusting. Oh my god. They're horny as hell. That makes a lot of sense now
So I wicked was like humping Bleya's leg in that movie wickets a little one with the orange hat
I thought that was a wicked work or a cricket thing. I'm cricket a
Wicked space a cricket spacer hold holder through her that's got to be the worst sport ever made
Yeah, who the fuck invented cricket man cricket the British tell you who invented cricket somebody who was heavily invested in the wood world
Yeah, hey, you know what I know I can make fucking
No, don't don't laugh when I say this, but it was probably created by big wood and don't laugh at big wood
But it was probably created by the wood industry big. Okay. I can't even hide my smirk. Don't laugh. Okay
So I don't want you to and don't laugh at this either big cricket. Okay, here's a here's the thing
Big cricket is scary
You know why they call it cricket because it's a damn thing that's making the making noise when that games happening
Yeah, cricket cricket
Boring well no I think that's like a rule is you're not supposed to make any noise when they can make no I've seen videos
Of people playing are you signing up for a phone on cricket?
Why are you shut up the cricket is?
Got to be the best worst sport of all time best worst sport not early
Curling is cool curling is okay any sport that has ice in it is good
Yeah, yeah, what about ice cricket? What if that that would that's a that would be cool if that exists ice field hockey
I haven't seen that I
I'm standing by any sport that has ice in it is cool period
What it's just cool to be on ice. I'm trying to miss a bad one. There isn't one
Ice assault yeah, yeah, how about ice assault? I guess ice assault sucks. Yeah, I never considered that
There's no rules to the game and that you can't even watch it anywhere, so it's really boring
But there's a winner and a loser for sure yeah
Kind of it's kind of funny though because they're all slipping and sliding
You're saying if I'm if someone tried to assault somebody on a ice rink
Yeah, I'm not sure I understand if they don't both of them don't have ice skates is what I'm saying
So it's kind of like a Charlie Chaplin
Kind of like yeah, I remember all those episodes of Charlie Chaplin where the guy
Where you bringing rape into it as you said assault is not it doesn't always mean that when you know
On ice it does actually you know what I think if there was like a gladiator style thing on ice
That would be a very cool sport. That's a fight
Also, that's ice fight. They just do that on hockey. Yeah. Yeah, that's like 10%
But also the cool part of that is is that it's a glove. I think you could do a gladiator fight
I don't have to be on ice. As long as it's not Christians getting fucking murdered because
that is the craziest shit. It has to be one Christian versus one Jewish. Is that what
you're saying? That's what you're saying should be the rules of ice assault, yeah. No. A Christian
I'm not saying that's what the rules should be. Patrick made a game called ice assault
that is a gladiatorial style ice thing. As he says a Christian versus a Jewish on ice.
No, tell you what I don't listen gladiatorial. I love I love my I love my okay
Well, usually in glad there's a but in gladiator in gladiatorial games. It's a guy versus an animal. So what are you saying?
buddy or the Christians
glaciating
Glaciators glaciators listen it could be called. I don't God this is the best the Coliseum. Oh my god good in
Cold guys were not on board at first
but now I was on board for anything where people fight and kill each other.
Okay, so Cameron was on board the whole time. I don't know about you.
If I was a millionaire billionaire, I would fund a blood sport.
No, you wouldn't.
I would. I would want to. If they tried to stop me, I'd do it anyway and go to jail.
If you think if like Elon Musk or like JF Bezos, you think those two motherfuckers were like,
"Yeah, we're gonna have like, we've been training these
"warriors for like three years secretly,
"and we're gonna have like a big duel."
- Nobody can stop them.
- Yeah, but imagine that. - If I'm Elon Musk,
I fund Gladiator Games, they try to stop me.
Do you know what I'm doing?
I'm getting horns installed on my head,
I'm changing my name to Demon Musk,
and I'm taking over the world.
- That's true.
I guess it is true that like,
if you go make a private island or something,
you can do that shit as long as you don't like
find oil accidentally while you're like fucking...
(laughter)
There's somebody throwing a spear at a guy
and like a baby's head and misses and hits
fucking the ground.
Just right then you and choppers come in,
everybody's dead. But until that point
you're fine, like you can just do that. There's no
law above you until you have some
until you have some kind of iPhone ingredient.
Yeah, that's true.
Imagine they're building like...
They're building this big
coliseum because they've been training
warriors for like months and then out of nowhere they just stumble upon like the
biggest lithium deposit. You're pretty much instantly there's gonna be
5,000 UFO sightings yeah and people are gonna be like oh whoa UFOs and really
yeah while you guys are looking at UFOs we had to go and stop that gladiator
the glaciators yeah we had to destroy the glaciators. We had to wipe the entire thing out.
I feel like I feel like every single person in the country
would change their opinion on Elon and Jeff Bezos if they were like, "Yeah, we've brought
back the Coliseum."
Oh my God, every rich guy should have a few warriors that they train and then they all
go in a tournament.
Yeah.
All the warriors go.
And the two rich guys get to sit in the big thrones.
Oh my God.
Like the emperor and do the thumbs up, thumbs down.
But it would be a like button and a dislike button.
Probably these days.
Can you imagine the comments on that live?
Yeah, they would be-
They'd be funny as hell.
They would be really funny.
Mine would probably be-
String they call the guy string bean or something. Yeah, he would like keep winning and they're like damn string beans on a tear
That's true. Imagine the F's that they would send when someone got their head you
String bean finally gets snapped get it all imagine the ruskies reaction of that. Oh
my god, Drew ski and Jack Harlow or
commentators for glaciators their BFS and that would be
Fucking sick here comes string bean. He looks like she is this that's Jack Harlow. Okay
(laughing)
- What's the impression of?
- Basically, Stringbee's one of my favorite players
in the whole game.
And he basically, oh, he just got his head
completely ripped off.
Damn.
- No, I don't think, Cameron, do you wanna be Drewski?
- One of you, listen, I already grabbed Jack Harlow,
so one of you two has to be Drewski.
- I actually, okay, it'll be Jack Harlow and Pee Wee Herman.
- No, no, you already said Drewski, go ahead.
- I've been working with Drewski lately.
- No, you haven't. - Really?
- We've been cooking, yeah.
- Bull fucking shit.
- We've been cooking somebody else.
- You've been cooking and he's been eating.
We've been cooking some videos together.
He's fat.
- Fat guy.
- But he said I'm next up after him.
- Yeah, next up on his plate.
- Yeah, I'm just not gonna eat me.
When he dies, I'm gonna be the next Drewski.
- Really?
- Yeah, he said that.
- You could, I guess you are similar.
You're Drewski's protege?
- Yeah, I'm his apprentice.
- Holy fucking shit.
- Officially.
- Huh.
- What do you mean by that?
Remember that?
- Yeah, he's actually trained me doing that.
- Really?
- I can't debut it yet, no.
- Come on, give us a taste.
- I'll do this.
Yeah, that's all I can do. That's all I can do. It's a copyright thing, okay? It's an issue.
Where did Drewski get his start? Did he come out of Chicago? Pete Holmes?
Yeah, he's a Second City guy.
He's from that class?
He could be.
I don't know, man. Who knows?
That'd be so funny to be a guy that hates guys like Drewski, because it's like, "Well, they didn't do..."
- They did not cut their teeth at the Second City or the UCB.
(laughing)
It's like a comedy nerd about that.
- Yeah, Drewsky didn't, he didn't pay his dues ever.
- Yeah, they were only funny on like Instagram Live.
They don't know what it's like to be at an improv show.
- They're right, man.
- Yeah.
- They've never done Who's Line or on a cruise.
- We should do an improv show together.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- You think we could?
- Yeah. - Just the three of us?
- Let's try it.
- Yeah.
- Right now?
welcome to the store sir welcome what can i get to you are all going on a little
bit of a service that i messed up i restarted that's not like that
what was the source of i've got a way to start sort of a messed up
what are the source of what i get for you today i will be driving through your
store
and i have a gun with a million bullets superman here comes my right turn signal
but i exist in a cartoon world that
uh... so basically i'm doing the act of using my mind powers to destroy him
- Oh, well I'm kinda like Mr. Game and Watch,
so I'd like to play it back into the G.
- Would you like to say check please?
- I just did a back flip.
- And scene.
- I can't say check please 'cause I'm the guy.
Okay, we're starting a new scene now.
- Okay, what's the new scene?
- Let's do scenes from ahead.
- I'm in love with, oh.
I'm in love with you too, baby,
but I can't love you because I hate you.
I hate you.
- Musical improv.
(laughing)
- Improv is so easy, man.
What are these fucking tall guys complaining about?
- And I'm Michael Jackson, hee hee.
- Why is everybody who does improv always big-tongued guy?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
We're sorry, we step out to the audience.
We're sorry guys, we're gonna have to cancel
the show tonight.
Somebody made an inappropriate choice.
They decided to be Michael Jackson.
- Yes. - Hee hee!
- And they didn't specify which year.
- And they, despite knowing things that we know about him,
and they didn't, and it was a wrong choice and we're sorry,
and the theater will be shutting down.
- Yep, and also, our boss did,
I fingered 150 million women.
- He had a fingering machine that he invented
that looks like a Dr. Seuss drawing.
- Oh, here's something.
- Caleb and Drewski exercise together.
That's the random scenario.
All right, I'm Caleb, here's Drewski.
Go, just try it, Pat.
- Yeah, just be Drewski.
- All right.
Caleb, do you wanna start?
- I knew he was just gonna do white voice, man.
- It doesn't have to, it could be anybody named Drewski.
It doesn't have his last name on there.
- You better black out that voice right now.
(laughing)
- Black it up or I fucking walk, right now,
'cause I'm being myself, and you're being Drewski.
- Okay, well I guess-- - Right now.
- I guess the scene has changed.
- Yep, and-- - Here, I guess--
- Patrick and Black Caleb at a company holiday party.
I have no problem with that.
- Okay.
I'm so fucking drunk as shit.
- Man, me too.
I'm not. - End scene.
you know i gave it three percent yeah
yeah
a random scene generators not it's not uh... it's not really good and good no
good enough
now i don't know when i get enough
you're not running off for improve
now i'm proud to bow down to the
the day that a i get involved with improves the death of people much at
g_p_t_ fuck that man
from chatty p_t_ is putting so many fucking improvised a lot of the
uh...
knows putting audience members that work the suggestions are coming from a
- It's a fucking thing.
- Yeah.
- It's fucked up.
- Do you think that there's--
- Write me a screenplay where a crazy character
goes into a restaurant.
They can write 500 of those per minute.
- There's definitely, that's a thing.
Like there's like an improv, an AI improv show, right?
- Well one thing that AI can never take away
from professional improvisers is having sex
with a 15 year olds.
- That is true.
- There's no way an AI can do that.
- An AI will never be able to do that.
- Professional improvisers, that's basically
their bread and butter.
- Yeah.
So all you...
That's the name of their troop too.
Improv Hounds.
Improv Hounds out there, you don't have to worry about it.
Yeah.
Bread and butter age.
Bread.
Yeah, girls are all butter age.
Butter age.
That's rude.
God, dude.
That is disgusting.
Man.
Yeah, it is.
It is disgusting.
Yeah, that's not right.
You think I'm gross like a pig?
That's right.
You're gross like a pig.
Why'd you look at my body when you said that?
I'm gross like a pig.
look at my body that is so fucking rude
shirts all wrinkled bitch my shirt is
wrinkled a thriftage t-shirt your dog poop
but he's not even a down my body and
look at this what you got a stain on
that you have a stain a lot you got to
get some dish soap and some club soda on
there you know if if a therapist patient
was here right now they'd be like what
is this a picture my father that is an
awful that is an awful part of knowing people who go to fucking therapy yeah
that you spill the table I'm seeing my future I'm seeing yeah yeah tell me what
yeah my mom on the fucking naked picture my grandma with your coffee yeah cuz you
wanted to prank me so bad really sorry man yeah invite me over to do this
this
parents divorce I hate people in therapy I think if you go to therapy you're a
fucking idiot you're weak yeah you are weak right you don't go to therapy what
you don't go to you don't go to therapy lady who gives me Adderall yeah that's
not the same thing yeah I've sat in on those you have yeah I have it's cuz my
computers here yeah Pat always asked us to sit down on his therapy appointments
just to make sure that everything goes smoothly.
- I tell her.
- He's afraid that she's gonna come on to him
in the video.
- We have to go, "Ma'am, no slutting."
- Yep.
- Stop acting like a hoe.
Listen, I know the webcam's on,
your female instincts are turning on.
- She doesn't know you guys are in the room
and I keep doing this, I keep looking over.
- She just thinks you're crazy.
- I keep looking to my left.
- Yeah, you say, "No, sorry, my friend's here."
- Yeah, sorry, my two friends are here.
- She's like, "Do you wanna open up
"about that a little bit?
"Like, why don't we unpack that?"
I'm just going.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Do you talk about us in your psychiatry appointments?
- No.
- Yeah, you do, don't you?
- You say?
- I did, there was the one time I had to talk about you
because you were walking by with a camera.
- So?
- I was doing it over Zoom.
- That's so funny.
- Doing it over Zoom, therapy appointment,
walking by, just standing in the background filming.
(laughing)
Filming Patrick from the back.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm at my office,
my friends are making a video in a little bit
and she was like, "Oh, what do you do for work?"
- Oh, that's the worst, man.
- Explain to a doctor what you do for work.
- A medical professional, I have to be like,
"Yeah, I just do this podcast with my friends."
- Yeah.
I do the only thing with a higher fucking suicide rate
than you do.
(laughing)
It's really bad.
- My life sucks shit.
- Yeah, I just say I'm a famous performer.
- Yeah.
- A famous touring performer. - I'm a famous singer
and dancer.
- Yeah.
- But I haven't decided yet.
When when comedian every every comedian is in therapy, you know what sucks about
Like as a professional comedian having a therapist is they're all in squiggle vision. That's true
I'm trying sitting there. I'm trying to like tell her my problem funny story. Yeah, it's like oh, yeah
The funniest thing happened to me, but it's you know, it's because of my anxiety and she's sitting there like this
It's all fucked up. It's like, you know, I know you're only doing that good
I know there's only two frames of you right now.
And I'm looking at her, I'm like,
you remind me a little of my soccer coach.
I don't know why, something about you.
The style you're drawn in.
- Yeah, something about this,
it's just reminding me of my childhood.
I don't know why.
This reminds me of a movie.
- Yeah, let me tell you about my childhood.
So basically I used to make movies with my friends,
my two friends.
One time we made a musical.
- Oh my God, and there was this kid named Fenton
and he sucked so bad.
- And my mom.
- Made me sleep over and I saw his mommy nude.
- Yeah, my baby little sister was like this.
- Oh God.
- I miss that show, I gotta re-watch that.
- It's a good show.
- I love that show.
- Funny.
- Season three, episode one.
- Season one, episode one, the pilot.
The first episode ever made.
- That's the best place to start.
- Yep.
- That's gotta be it.
- Introduces the characters, introduces the premise,
introduces the style of humor, the art, the theme song,
music, the credits.
- Paula Poundstone as the mom.
- I'd like to pound her stone.
- Brendan Small as the small character.
not like to pound Paula Poundstone. I don't remember who that is but it sounds
like a girl? Yeah. I think she's a woman who loves women.
Look up who that is. Unless she's got a husband. Paula Poundstone. She's a female
comedian. Oh man she's a fox. Yep I stand by it.
She's a humorist actually. Did you guys consider yourselves more comics,
comedians or humorists? I am maybe I'm a look at this picture I'm more of a
scroll back up she's given herself the bunny ears holy shit she's fine I would
definitely consider myself more of an artiste really yeah you're an artistic
one yeah artiste look at this photo of Paula Poundstone yeah she looks good man
she looks good yeah that's the mom from home movies yeah but yeah the I'm trying
to become a humorist. I don't want belly laughs anymore. I just want hmm.
Anymore. You've been getting so many belly laughs. I've been getting a few out of you today.
Yeah, if I can't lie. Stop it! Tickling is not... If someone was an amazing... Imagine being the tickling humorist.
Yeah, tickling humorist is a good title. If you went on stage... Wait, wait, ready, ready, ready. Stop it, stop it. Don't go hmm.
This is something... I'm being Al Franken right now. I usually can only... You are being Al Franken right now.
That is a lot more like Al Franken than you realize. Yeah. Yeah, touching me when I
don't want to be touched. Very Al Franken-esque. If somebody could go on stage and just
massively tickle an entire comedy club, do you think that that would work? I guess that's what
humorists do. Is that good? It's just a laugh that you don't want to have. When a
humorist? When a humorist goes up and they're telling me this fucking
story about like like their AP bio teacher or some bullshit or the TV show
AP bio yeah that is a that is a humorist show it really is yeah you're a favorite
humorists favorite show yeah I heard Mo Rocca gave that rave reviews really
that's a country the country nope he's gonna say the company famous is lucky
you said the country before me I'd love to say the co-worker has a lot of of
fashionable frames, loves his glasses, different colors, same shape though.
What are you on about? Mo Rocca, the humorist. I've never heard of Mo Rocca.
Mo Rocca was on I Love the 80s. I don't think I saw that one. You didn't see I Love the 80s.
I Love the 70s or 90s. I saw 90s. I used to watch I Love the 1920s. Yeah.
- Yeah.
- What was that about?
- It was like, the factories are churning out
- What?
- Products.
- Who can forget, who can forget the Charleston?
- Yeah, I actually used to watch, I love the 10,000 BCs.
- Yeah.
- And they'd be like, oot, doot, doot.
- Paul Shearer sitting there.
- Paul F. Tompkins, ooga booga, hoobo.
- And I said, oot booga.
(laughing)
- That fucking, that story about Weird Al
that Paul F. Tompkins tells you, you heard that one?
- No.
- I think I showed my ex that when we first started dating,
'cause I was like, "This is so funny."
- For some reason I left it as an ex over Weird Al.
- That story did not happen.
- What was the story?
- It's the one where he meets Weird Al.
- What does Weird Al say?
- And he's like, "And I said weird!"
He says it's like, he tells this story about like,
he thought that he knew Weird Al,
and then realized, "I don't know Weird Al at all."
And she was like, "Yeah, that did not happen, he's lying."
You're doing a pretty poor job of recounting PFT's story.
I know.
I'm gonna have to stick with PFT.
PFT, 'cause when I hear his story, I go, "Pft."
Yeah.
No way, that didn't happen.
Not me, I believe him.
Yeah.
I believe in him.
You believe in him?
Yeah, I believe in him.
Maybe it's a surprise, "Pft," you know,
like kinda like what a humorist is going.
Guys, I found this thing, I found this YouTube.
The gall.
I'm always looking for new YouTube.
I know we've been talking about this,
but I've ran out of YouTube videos.
Sorry, I just had an idea.
Oh, you did?
I just had a remembrance.
- I found this YouTube channel,
the funniest shit I've ever heard.
It's called The Funny Channel.
- Oh wow. - Right?
And I know you're thinking,
"Wait, that's gotta be the worst name
"I've ever seen in my life."
- Put this on screen, wait, put this on screen.
Go back to the top and put this on screen.
- See, so it's one of these.
So if you search The Funny Channel.
- It will come up, it's gonna--
- It'll come up eventually.
- They've been clipping us here.
- Oh wait, they clipped something from this podcast,
The Funny Channel.
- I got bullied?
- Wait, this has gotta be our fucking funny ass video,
I'm sure. - Did you guys bully me?
It doesn't sound like us.
So what is this channel?
The Funny Channel 2646.
It's got to be--
it's one of these new ones where they post all the funniest clips
from all the funny podcasts.
So they started posting our stuff.
So let's--
Wow, I like their header and profile picture.
Yeah, The Funny Channel 2646.
So guys, go check out The Funny Channel 2646.
There's a lot of funny clips from all sorts of podcasts on there.
Wow.
It seems like Keely Ours.
There's a lot of clips from here.
So if you watch one of these, if you--
- Who's this?
- If you've listened to one of these episodes
and you said, "Man, that was funny,
"but I can't remember a fucking goddamn thing
"that happened in that episode."
- And I wanna send my friend a clip.
- And I need to send my friend a clip.
Oh, that clip was so funny.
- Oh, and some longer form clips too.
Beyond shorts.
- Pal's old YouTube sketches.
Nicki Minaj boingus challenge.
- And I don't even know who these people are in the video.
- They seem very, very smart though.
That guy in the middle looks hungover.
Yeah, and the guy on the right looks like he has some kind of autoimmune disorder.
What's wrong with this yellow guy's cheek?
Wait, this guy's cheeks are yellow.
His cheek is kind of swollen.
His cheek is swollen as fuck AF.
It looks like to me, like, the Funny Channel is a great channel, but it's sorely in need of more likes, comments, views, and sharing to friends.
I agree. So if you like funny humor, go on to the Funny Channel 2646, give them a complete follow.
Alright guys, we'll catch you next time and this has been podcast about lists episode 100 and we're out
Ice cream.
Bow.
Okay.
Sorry.
Bye.
Bow.
(laughs)