(upbeat music)
- New type of vibes.
- Okay, so it's basically a completely different
type of episode because I can actually hear my own voice now.
- You know what, it is, this is kind of like
putting horse blinders on us.
- This is actually, I would say, the opposite.
I would say normally I have horse blinders on
and right now I am a horse that is completely aware
of his peripheral vision.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, and I don't like it at all.
I hate these because I thought for a long time,
I thought for a long, long time,
I don't mean this in an offensive way,
I thought until right now that I sounded like a black guy.
And I'm realizing that I do not,
at all, 'cause I can hear my own voice.
- 'Cause you were listening to that Lou Reed song earlier.
- Yeah, well a little bit that.
But I always thought that I had like a lower,
not that black guys have lower voices.
- Yeah, what are you,
what are you getting up to right now?
What are you saying?
I'm not getting up to anything.
See, this is fucking me up.
The headphones are making me crazy.
Yep, in the world of the blind,
the smeller is the teller.
Are you the smeller in this scenario?
I guess I'm the smeller.
But I'm not, that's what I'm saying.
In the world of the blind,
the hearing are endearing.
I wish that I was blind right now.
These are my glasses.
Well, blind people can hear.
Barely.
- Well it's not, the,
(laughing)
the world of everyone's still a hearer
in the world of the blind.
- The world of the deaf.
- It's just gonna take some getting used to
to be hearing my voice. - The world of the deaf,
in the world of the deaf,
you can sometimes pick up on people's breath.
- I always thought I had maybe a Howard Stern kind of thing
and I'm realizing that I don't at all.
I really don't.
- Well that's what, that's what the,
now with the kind of the advent of this internet
that's been going on over the past several years.
- Don't even say advent to me, you atheist.
- Now people, you know, it's like,
now radio people can have high voices.
- You think I have a high voice?
- True that!
- Yeah.
- True that, camera!
- Well, I mean, compared to Howard Stern
and some of these other people, these pre-internet.
- Is Howard Stern the girl or the boy on that show?
- He's the black girl.
- That's Howard?
- Yeah.
- She is not as hot as her voice is.
I remember listening to her voice as a kid being like,
I bet she is so fucking hot,
and then I would see the videos and it'd be like,
you know, remember when Howard Stern would make a mom
and a daughter get naked and kiss?
- On the Sibian?
- Yeah, and they'd kiss and they'd finger each other.
And I thought that when they first saw the mom,
I was like, that's gotta be her, that's gotta be Robin.
But then you see Robin and you're like,
ah yeah, that's not as hot as I thought she'd be.
- That's crazy that he was making ladies ride the Sibian.
- Yeah, he had an interesting--
- In hindsight, once he became
the America's Got Talent guy for a lot of people instead of like the radio host.
It's like, "Oh yeah, this is..." Remember that guy that passed along your
favorite singer right now? Yeah, that guy used to make ladies get naked and jack
off on the radio. He didn't jack off. What are you talking about? The Sibbian is jacking off.
Today's topic. No, the Sibbian isn't jacking off. Today's debate. Fuck no. Is a massage chair for a
woman? Is that jacking off? Exactly. If you sit on the... Okay, here's a
scenario. Is the sibyan jacking off or is it some different third type of thing? If
somebody's getting a massage in a massage chair and you decide, "Well,
I'm gonna go visit my friend," and you sit on the armrest and you have a clitoris
and it starts going and stinging your clit, is that masturbating or is
that not? Yeah, I don't know. I don't know. That's why I'm asking the questions. I'm
I think that hard-hitting questions. I mean, if it's on the radio, it's,
it's probably all made up anyway. It probably wasn't even one.
Cause they filmed it. Also girls can't feel anything if they're not in love.
So they don't give a, they sit on that and they just,
it's basically just making a noise. So they were acting anyway.
It's basically,
so I guess the Sibian or massage chair is a rollercoaster.
Yeah. That's what that is. It's a rollercoaster.
It's not jacking off.
It's not anything else other than--
I think it's a chair.
As a roller coaster moves around.
What does a roller coaster have?
Well, I will say--
It goes up and down in loops.
--if you put me on one of those--
What do you--
--you put a--
--you would get in it, though.
--if you put a 3D video, an iPhoto booth
background of the roller coaster going--
which, by the way, that photo booth background never
made any sense because it goes reverse.
Right?
I think if you position yourself backwards, so say like your laptop's right here and then
you sit, you turn around, it'll work.
That makes a little more sense.
Yeah, it makes way more sense.
But nobody thinks to do that because they want to see themselves.
Actually, what you guys are missing here is that when you watch the video file, it's backwards,
right?
But what's actually going on is you're riding a roller coaster forwards and there's also
a clone of you sitting in front of you looking at you.
Oh, that's scary.
And that's actually what the experience is.
Because your couch or wherever you're sitting on while you look at your laptop, that's the
roller coaster seat.
And there just happens to be, there's a guy in front of you who turned around and he looks
just like you.
And you're like, "Please turn back."
I don't like that.
That's going to keep me up for a couple nights.
Last night I got kept up.
I got kept up because I thought, you remember last night we were here and you were like,
I felt a spirit on me.
Yeah, I did.
I went home and I felt probably 30 or 40 spirits in my bedroom and I started
freaking out and I went to go lay on the couch and there was a
dress that was hanging up on a door in my house. It was my
dress that I was gonna wear to my quinceanera and I was sitting in the
door and it was completely dark so not only did I think that it was a
woman, I thought it was a woman in a black dress. Wow. So it was pretty scary
because it's too dark to see that is really I did probably charm her and
woohoo would cry instantly if you felt if you felt the presence that I felt last
night or if you saw I guess the woman that Caleb saw you would sob I would woo
I got really really I get really scared ghost that's what the ghost I get really
scared of ghosts maybe once a month I'll get really scared of a ghost if I stay
up past midnight, the witching hour. But then there's always a moment about 90 minutes into
my fear where I realize, "What the fuck is a ghost going to do to me?" And I start walking
around my house like a gorilla.
Well, stop your heart. Is that what they do?
No.
If they get you good, yeah.
Well, some people have died from ghost attacks. Mac Miller, Whitney Houston, these people
have where they were haunted.
Well, I thought those were demons that they had.
I mean, it could be.
That's what a lot of the news stories said.
Yeah.
That their demons finally caught up with them.
And I went, "Ahh!"
Haunted by their demons.
"Ahh! That's scary!"
Kurt Cobain killed by his demons, they said.
Yeah.
Here's what I'm saying.
When you even, it doesn't matter what industry you're into.
If you're a musician, if you're a comedian, if you're a chef,
as soon as those demons pop up, run the other direction.
You know what sucks about being a chef that has to work with your demons?
You gotta eat all the food.
You gotta eat all the food they make, and it's always so fricking spicy.
spicy. That's right. Yeah. It's always so spicy. And it's also,
it's also always when demons are preparing food, it's always like,
oh, if this, like, I, this is my favorite food, but I have to,
I have to eat 100 servings of it in a row. Yeah. And I'm like,
I don't even like it anymore. Yeah. Like Bourdain. Yeah. Homer.
He was running all around the world from his demon. Demon?
He was running away from his demon.
A lot of people said his pedophile girlfriend was a demon, but I don't think.
Which is a different entity than a demon. Yeah. That's a sucky bi. Yeah.
Yeah, demoned a complete different entity.
Then the blue, blue, like, like, you know what the hottest part of the flame is or
the hottest. Oh, the hottest hockey blue blue.
Demoned blue. It's a palindrome to
demon. Demon. Do you write D M O E
and D D M O E.
D M O. That's how you decided to spell that.
DMO. I spelled it perfectly correct. You're just cracking yourself up with DMO-ed.
I'm, today, I'm on one, I guess.
I had, you know what I had? What'd you have? I had a, um, I went to that grocery store by your house.
Thanks? Mm-hmm. Thanks. Why are you thanking me?
It just stimulates the local economy. Yeah. This block is gonna be bumbling.
That's gonna trickle down.
Thank you so much. Uh-huh, it's gonna trickle down back to you.
I don't know why is it. You know they have that bakery there?
They got a you were calling me out turnovers and stuff now you're letting everyone know where he lives guava turnover
I had come on pretty good. Okay, so now they know that I live in a fucking Mexico neighborhood. Uh-huh great guava Danish
You had one of those no no I honestly have no idea. I didn't know there was a bakery in there
Yeah, there's a bread aisle that I don't go to cuz I'm straight ketosis. I would never eat
Oh, you're on that shit in my life. I've been on you wouldn't eat. No. It's really good
I would maybe eat one at a doctor's office if they had it on a turnover. Yeah, there is certain okay
- Okay, that's actually such a good point.
There are certain foods that I would never ever eat in my life
but if it's somewhere where it's sitting on a table,
then I'm gonna be like, I guess I'll fucking eat it for sock.
- Pretty much every entonoment.
- I'm gonna go buy a scone.
I'm gonna go buy 10 scones.
- Fuck no, I'll never eat a scone.
- No, a scone is something your girlfriend buys you.
- What? - No, it's something
a doctor--
- Yeah, she thinks you're a fucking tubby piece of shit.
- Your girlfriend buys you a scone?
- My girlfriend buys me tomahawk steak.
(laughing)
- A scone.
- Brobrain gets a scone.
- That's like, mayo flowers.
- She gets you a scone, 'cause she may work at--
- No, she gets me a PlayStation game.
- She may work at a bakery, a nice coffee shop.
- Nobody gets anybody a scone.
Scones exist so you can eat them from the table.
- I agree, that's not true.
- There's no such thing.
- I've never seen anybody buy a scone in my life.
- What if you know somebody who's a baker?
They would get you a scone.
- Scones are fucking shit, man.
- Scones suck, I'm not saying they're good.
- They would make you cookies, brownies, or a cake.
- I'm not saying they're good, I'm just saying,
It's something that somebody who cares about you gets,
even though you hate it.
- Is it a scone?
Is it a saccone?
It has an apostrophe between the S and the C.
- Yeah, like a s'more.
- Like a s'more?
- That's a saccone.
- Oh.
- Saccone.
- I actually--
- Yorma saccone.
- Let's do something with that.
- Yorma saccone from Lonely Island.
When I was 16, he liked a reply that I had on Twitter,
and I told five or six people in my real life.
(laughing)
I was like, "Yorma from the Lonely Island liked that I said,
'fucking whatever, hot raw rules.'"
- Yeah, he said, "@yormatacone, you're the best, I love you."
- It was essentially that, I think.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, but I remember I told probably four or five people.
I was like, "That was pretty awesome."
I basically touched a celebrity's arm.
- Yeah, damn, I would like to do that.
Speaking of comedy.
- Do tell.
- That's what we should have called it, the fucking show.
- Yeah.
- I had a dream last night,
and I had made up a joke in the dream.
- Holy shit.
- And I wrote it down when I woke up.
Do you want to hear the, and I forgot about it.
I remembered it when I was at the gym
and I had to take a break 'cause I started laughing.
- Okay.
- And I looked like a crazy person.
- You bragged that you went to the gym.
- You called me fruity pretty recently on the Twitch stream
for writing down my dreams.
- Yeah, but writing out a joke from a dream
is very different from writing down your dream
every single day. That's how Louis does it. Louis writes, he dreams, he's
also, I also to be fair, I called you for you for having a dream journal, which is
a hundred percent correct. It's not a journal, it's a diary. It's a notes app on my phone.
It has a little heart-shaped lock on it. Yeah, it has a heart-shaped lock with a heart-shaped key. It is the notes app on my phone. This is how a man writes down his dream.
That's right. He makes a separate note that says, "Joke I came up with in my dream." What's wrong with that?
Here's my joke. Okay. This is a stand-up comedy joke. All right. So, well by God, get
Get out of your damn chair!
Get up.
I'm all cabled in.
That's fine, fuck you.
Why is a machine gun called a machine gun?
What's the machine part?
Making a bullet go really fast?
All guns do that.
Damn.
That's pretty good.
That is actually funny as fuck.
Here's my dream.
stand-up read your dream had a dream that the Hard Rock Hotel had Indian Hitler as
their manager and he was helping me do stand-up that's a you guys both had
stand-up he had that weeks ago I know that's how I know yet it weeks ago that
mine was last night my no I'm telling you that was mine it's just funny that
we both had stand-up dreams that yours was a long time ago though well I don't
think about Indian Hitler you know enough to dream about yeah like you know that's
supposed to be well he manages the Hard Rock Hotel dreams are a reflection of
your subconscious. So all day you're walking around, you're walking down the
street, you're getting the bus and stuff, and people don't know that one of these
thought bubbles floating above your head is Indian Hitler. Sitting right next to lunch
of the Hard Rock Hotel. And movies, Indian Hitler. And he's on the phone with me in
my room. That is some fucking epic shit. Because I was calling for room service I think.
That would be a real... Talk about a wake-up call. Yeah. Right? You see this guy...
yeah this guy you walk into a hard rock hotel you see this guy behind the desk I
would say hello sir I must be dreaming yeah this is a dream come true dream do
you have any advice for me in my career honestly I would kill him you would kill
him yeah well the people you know that question people always say yeah if you
go back in time would you kill Indian Hitler yeah to India and kill yeah if
If you had a plane, would you go kill Indian Hitler?
Fuck it, yeah, of course.
If I saw him, yeah.
- How many businesses in India are named after Hitler?
- We talked about this, maybe not on the podcast,
but we-- - A million times.
We have talked about this one billion times.
- Not on the podcast, though, I don't think.
We just, we used to, we kept finding new ones,
new stores called like-- - Like Super Hitler Clothing.
- Yeah, Super Hitler Clothing.
- Hitler 100. - My Hitler Store.
Yeah.
Build a Hitler, Builder, Bearler, Blitler, Hilder, Builder.
You just looked up,
Juvia just looked up maps on Google Maps.
- He looked up India.
(laughing)
- Okay, now look up Hitler.
Let's see what we got in here.
- Wolf's Lair.
- Ruins of Hitler's wartime command base.
That is not in India, my friend.
- Wait, who's DJ Hitler?
- DJ Hitler, Eleonora Kassiev, DJ in, whoa!
This is in fucking New York?
There's a guy named DJ Hitler?
- Holy shit!
- Whoa!
- DJ, get a quote, get a quote!
- I am hosting a party for 100 to 120 people on August 24th.
(laughing)
- Whoa, okay, so we know who is DJing my wedding.
- Yeah.
- It's gonna be DJ Hitler, Alinora Kaseev.
- Huh? - When is that?
- It's tomorrow.
- Is it really tomorrow?
- Yep, it's completely tomorrow.
- Whoa, look at the mask that DJ Hitler wears.
- He can't have a what's his name,
Salvador Dali mask on.
- Yeah, that is.
- And a Shutterstock picture.
- That is confusing branding, Mr. Hitler.
With all due respect, open 24 hours.
- 24 hours every day of the week.
- We can call him.
- No, we won't call.
We don't wanna bother DJ Hitler, he's busy.
- Yeah, got a lot of events.
- He's very, very busy.
- Two pictures in the gallery.
- But yeah, there was a lot of good clothing stores
called Hitler. And then for whatever reason, there was like, you know,
every single one of them had some news story written about it, I guess,
because when you look it up,
there was always a picture of the owner in front of it,
like smugly crossing his arms, like, yep, I named my store Hitler.
Do you think that's like a shock value thing?
Like do you think maybe Nathan for you went over there?
Well, that's the Nathan for you over there, his every episode is like,
so we're going to change the name of the business to Hitler. Yeah.
There has to be stuff that they scrap
that is like when the US military
would like lose a nuclear bomb somewhere
and it's just like sitting in the middle of Ohio.
There's gotta be tons of stories called Hitler
that have no explanation
because the episode never came out.
- Yeah. - You know?
- That's definitely it.
There's no other explanation for it.
- You know, you saw that, the news story
where they lost some radioactive stuff
in Australia recently, right?
Like in the past week or whatever?
- Yeah, it's called the--
- What, they put it in a kangaroo's pouch and it hopped away?
- Yeah, they put it in a kangaroo's pouch
and it copped away, come on. - That is some funny shit.
but the funny thing about that's history to me it was that they like the like
headliner never was
the government has lost a cylinder
uh...
israel thinks so hard nobody clicks on the head of the israeli
what do you have to put this together and his story but i don't give a shit
about a cylinder of those of the cylinder i would like to know and that
was
thousands of those a week so that you have to take care of foster is right
right
Yeah, well no they don't know anything else. Yeah, they don't like fosters. Yeah, hope it's not fucking
Peanut butter do they like peanut butter?
Marmite is that an animal? Yeah. Oh shit. Marmite is a cylinder animal in Australia called a marmite. Yeah
Completely furry tube as no just had legs and one tail bloody. Yeah one tail to hell
There's a marmite right there. That's a marmite put this up. Yeah, that is scary man. It's got billions of seeds
I want and it's got one tail. Yeah. Yeah, I'm actually seeing two or three tails. Holy shit
There's spikes those got to be the same part of the tail right is Australia really all that scary
Isn't all the get this guy out of here. Yeah, I'm sick of seeing this guy. What is it get Matt Doren out of here?
Isn't um get this guy out of here. It's just you know keep this guy around is in
Is it true that Australia is full of giant Spidey's and creepy? I've heard that it's it's a it's a myth. I know Bruce paradise
I've heard it makes you say kill it with fire. Really
Yeah, I heard there was there was they the the settlers did do some horrible things when I got there
I heard in Australia all the toilets flush a different way, too
and that is one of the things they do.
- Yeah, they flush out onto people's faces.
(laughing)
- That's one of the things that the settlers did.
They were like, "We're gonna make these toilets go crazy."
- "We're gonna make 'em shake heads up."
- "It's gonna spin the other way.
"It's gonna come right back out, hit you in the nose."
- That is honestly a great idea for an opposite device.
(laughing)
Like if you're gonna make one thing that is--
- One opposite device.
- It's gotta be the number one device
that you want it to do the right way
and not the opposite way.
- Yeah.
- Which is a tullet.
Because if a tullet shoots the opposite way into your face,
you have poop on your face.
- Yeah. - Or gunk.
- Awful.
That is awful, man.
- Could be diarrhea, too.
- Oh, speaking of diarrhea, dude, I have--
- Diarrhea dude, was that your YouTube name?
- Shit, man.
I mean, I have to give it up for that.
That was fucking incredible.
But speaking of diarrhea,
- I've completely fixed my butt.
- Really?
(laughing)
- I fixed my butt.
- I thought you were having issues.
- I had a breakthrough moment when I was in Chicago.
I was walking down the street and--
- Would you just constipate yourself
with all that Italian beef?
- No, no, no, the complete opposite.
I was walking down the street
and I was walking between restaurants
and I was eating at two different restaurants.
I shit myself.
- Sounds like you're in paradise.
I let out a fart and it was very cold outside.
And I let out a fart and there was poop in it.
And I was like, "Hey, I'll catch up with you later."
I was like, "Oh, I need a cup of coffee badly."
So I went into a coffee shop and I bought a sparkling water.
And before I, with the water in my hand,
three people back in line, I asked if they had a bathroom
so they know what's going on.
Yeah.
Right, I'm not even up there.
And I'm like, "Do you guys have a bathroom?"
With the water in my hand.
She's like, "Yeah, it's over there."
But I get my water and then I go back there
and I think everybody must have heard me say,
I like ask if they had a bathroom,
'cause I was in there a really, really long time.
I threw away my underwear because they had poop on them
and I didn't wanna have to wash.
- How often do you shit your pants?
- Once every six months.
I threw away my underwear and then I walked out
and pretty much the entire, it was like a walk of shame.
Like pretty much the entire restaurant or coffee shop
looked at me and could like completely tell
that I just shit my pants
and that I'd just thrown away my underwear
because my fly was down and my penis was out.
- Is that true?
- No. - That part's true?
- No, that part is not true.
- Well, maybe they had-- - But then I got home,
on the way to the restaurant--
- You had to shame your poop in shape.
- On the way to the,
it literally was like rock bottom for me.
And so on the way to the restaurant,
I went on Amazon and I ordered 90 billion
probiotic organisms in a pill capsule,
and I've been taking those,
and it has completely healed my life.
- It helps.
- You know what you can also do?
- 90 billion.
- Sauerkraut, I've learned.
- Any fermented food is very good for your ass.
- It's crazy that the food that smells,
you're supposed to eat a bunch of stuff
that smells terrible.
- There's a bunch of guggy little bugs
sitting in your belly.
- Yeah.
- Eating up and farting.
- They have a world.
- And they shit in there.
- Osmosis Jones was a documentary.
- It was.
- There's a Jurassic world in your body.
- Yeah, your ass-ic world.
- I have a velastic world.
- Your ass is sick.
- Because of how many pickles I've been eating
because they're fermented.
Velasic world.
- Yeah.
- But yeah, so it's been--
- And the stork made you.
- It's been pretty awesome though.
So I have been feeling--
- It's fixed.
- Amazing.
I was pretty much right on the edge of schizophrenia
and I think it completely saved me from that.
I've been looking up, apparently that's a,
I've been looking at this,
like all the forums for people who are like
trying to heal their gut microbiome.
Half the people are like,
"Yeah, I used to be fucking schizophrenic
"until I started eating kimchi and now I'm completely fine."
- Wow.
I've been eating so much fermented stuff too. Really? Yeah. It's sauerkraut, kimchi,
it makes your breath smell bad, it makes your butt smell bad. Luckily I also just
switched to a completely natural fluoride free charcoal toothpaste that
doesn't do anything. So that's great. Perfect timing. That's huge. Yeah. You
telling that story made my stomach hurt. Really? Do you want me to... can I massage it?
No. Really? Yeah. You know it's also I guess maybe good for gut health if you're
talking just you know taking solid craps you're drinking an energy drink every
single day it's really bad for you I don't know how this works all of the I
don't know how this works but if you drink Celsius every morning no it's
super you take one really long solid poop clears out every single thing in
your body you have poop in your body every single thing it's kind of a lot of
a lot of my body how come when you don't drink enough water your poop turns more
watery sometimes. You sound like Jordan Peterson right now.
You heard him say that on Rogan this past week. You heard him say that.
I only watched the Rob Zombie episode of Joe Rogan.
He said like, "You need to drink, there's too much. You don't drink enough
water, your poop's gonna be water." You think I learned about diarrhea
- Is that diarrhea from Joe Rogan?
Is that what you were saying?
- It's feeling wet and runny,
but it sounds a little funny.
- No, that's Joe Rogan's voice that he's doing.
- I can't remember which guy's which.
That's Joe Rogan's voice.
Eating all that health.
- That's Jordan Peterson.
That's a quote from him.
- What is it?
- He says, "It's really wet and runny,
but it sounds kind of funny."
- I wanted you to make the noise again.
- These days, PC culture, you can't even say,
you can't even say you're gonna go--
Nowadays means poop and crap culture you can't even say you're gonna go drop the Cosby kids off to the off at the pool
These days now you have to say I'm going to take the Browns
He's awesome
He changed my life
He said clean your damn room and poop in that damn damn toilet bitch
That's it
He doesn't swear
He'll say bloody and fuck I just had a bloody fuck
With a turd I fucked a bloody turd he says that
Yeah, he says shit like that
Barely an impression
And the Board of Psychologists in Canada they wiped my butt
When you make a bloody turd you have to wipe your butt I said no I said I won't
I was taken off of campus because I walked in I said milk milk lemonade around the corner fudge is made
He actually would defend that yeah
milk is
around the corner
He did do
Milk is around the corner now.
Yeah.
*laughing*
You walk into any college campus, they're saying
Fudge, fudge, milk
around the corner, lemonade.
It's completely backwards.
*laughing*
These institutions are not being respected.
Milk is around the corner.
It's rum and lemonade
around the corner, milk is made.
These people are growing up
growing up thinking you can make milk from the back? That doesn't make any sense.
But if you don't drink enough water sometimes you can't make milk from the
back. That is true. No you make sign up pilk. Nah don't even get me started on
pilk. Poop milk? What's poop milk? Pepsi milk from the Lindsay Lohan show.
The Lindsay Lohan show? The commercial that she did where she went "ahhh Pepsi and milk." I don't care too much about milk. You don't care too much about it? I saw a new
video about it where the guy, the guy in the video of Lindsay Lohan
demonstrating pilk, she has a glass of Pepsi, she pours a little bit of milk in there.
That sucks that like it's like Lindsay Lohan is like making like a comeback
through pilk. Yeah, that sucks. Yeah. It sucks for her. She's like, I don't think she deserves what's coming to her.
Will you do this jackass style stunt for our commercial?
I I I think that Oh pickle milk that does not sound very good. No that does not
sound very fucking good. I'll be real with you yeah it also doesn't look very real
to me but I think I need to cut out all food I think I need to stop drinking milk
cuz I drink a lot of milk why do you drink a lot of milk cuz I just like the
cream no you were doing you I know your ass you're doing some kind of fucking
and you're trying to do some carnivore, yeah.
Carnivore diet. - I don't have a bone plan.
- He's doing, he's got a bone plan, this motherfucker.
- I know he's on a bone plan from YouTube.
- The carnivore diet, they--
- God damn it, dude, it keeps getting me.
- They, no, the carnivore diet--
- No more, no more!
- Yeah, you need to stop, you need to stop.
You need to close your eyes. - I just put a spell
on you, by the way.
- I saw a guy, wait, now that,
or since I have headphones on,
I saw a guy the other day who was doing a bench press
at the gym and he had this kind of headphone on,
and every time he would get up and hype himself up,
he's a big fat guy, and then as soon as he would go down
to do the bench press, he would do this.
(laughing)
He just wore his headphones like this, blocked his vision.
- You look like Jordy LaPorche.
- Star Wars, I mean Star Trek.
- But I didn't know what, I wanted to ask him,
what is this doing for you, man?
But this is kind of what Patrick needs to start doing.
He needs to block his vision so that he can't see
all the distractions, 'cause right now,
I'm in perfect radio podcast mode, ask me any question.
- Okay.
what is on the screen right now.
- What's behind you?
- What's behind me?
- And can you see it?
- The world, the entire rest of the world?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, in a way.
- In a way, yeah, I guess that's a good point.
- See, I'm so much more philosophical
when I don't have my eyes.
- Yeah, and that's what you want on something like this.
- See, it's like I said at the top of the episode.
- I don't even know which side is the top.
- In the world of the blind, the mice.
- No, the mice will not play.
- The mice are--
- There's three blind mice.
- The mice are three guys. - Three blind mice.
- Three blind mice. - You guys ever hear
that other, the Christian parody,
"Three blind guys, three blind guys,
"deny God's love, deny God's love."
You never heard that? - No.
- We learned that. - That's really good.
- In school. - I know three blind mice
from the theme song of the Stooges.
- I know it from-- - Which Stooges?
- Shrek. - Shrek 2.
- Well, I knew it before Shrek,
but Shrek, that's the touchstone.
- You know the one, you know the three Stooges,
They got that...
They got the theme song.
I've never seen...
Yeah, I did.
I never...
Yeah, me and the wife are doing three stooges.
I just had a mind blown moment.
Wow.
Yep. Those stooges are just as good.
They're just as intelligent as three blind mice.
Yeah.
You didn't think I was going to come for you, huh?
Were the stooges blind?
Curly.
They might as well have been.
Curly Joe.
Remember they kept replacing all those guys?
Yeah.
Shemp.
- No, I don't remember it.
I have never seen the Three Stooges.
- You've never watched the Three Stooges?
- I think I've maybe seen a clip
of the Will Sasso Three Stooges.
- They've got Shemp, Curly Joe,
- Curly.
- Curly, Moe, Larry.
- They have Curly Joe and Curly?
- Yeah.
- And then there was another guy.
- That's five Stooges!
- Well, they keep switching them out.
- That's bullshit!
- That's what we were just talking about.
- Shemp.
- And you're all like, I never even heard of a Stooge before.
- They replaced Curly with Shemp.
- The only Shemp I recognize is Sean Kemp,
Seattle Supersonics Dunk Master. Deadlift shrimp. Deadlift shrimp. Mm-hmm. Deadlift shrimp.
Yeah. That's what you and your deadlift so much that you get scoliosis. Yeah, yeah.
You look like a shrimp. Yeah. That's perfect form on a deadlift. You have a back like a
shrimp. Yeah. It's like downward dog. You make the back like a shrimp. Yeah, you make the back like a shrimp.
And you pick up the weight. Well, I'm sorry. We looked at the x-rays of your spine and you have a back like a complete shrimp.
have deadlift shrimp. You have deadlift shrimp back. I'm a basketball player? No,
no, no. You have deadlift shrimp. Your back is this big. Yep. I'm really, really
sorry. You know what people don't talk about enough? The Three Stooges, Curly, Moe,
and Shemp, all brothers. Larry, just their friend. He was not part of it. Uh-huh.
Now here's something. They could have had Curly, Moe, and Shemp, and it could
have been called three stooges three brothers these days they were this is a
very rude Photoshop that that uh GBO has just done on photo p.com photo p.com it's
a bad photo P yeah these days if they tried to do three stooges oh probably
don't even look like that probably called the three fucking sluts or something
right and it'd probably be Amy Schumer Nancy Pelosi and yeah it would be like
it would probably be like...
Or some other girl.
They'd bring Terri Schiavo back.
Nowadays they'd probably make a show that would be like
5 to 7 politically
approved and diverse archetypes.
That's probably the name of the comedy show.
You actually can't say stooge anymore.
Yeah.
It's a disability.
Diminishing to the mentally disabled.
You have to say...
Being a stooge nowadays is a disability.
Follicularly challenged.
three of these fools are.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, one of them got a damn bowl for a haircut.
- Calling him curly is just mean-spirited.
It wouldn't fly now.
- Oh no, it's 'cause he would do curl-ups.
- Yeah, curling a shrimp.
- Yeah.
His name was originally gonna be Shemp.
- And then he became Shrimp.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it was one of those--
- Shemp became Shrimp, then Shrimp became Shemp back again.
- But it probably would be called
the three or four only fans sluts.
- Yeah.
- Who fall onto dildos and that's--
So if they were going to create a situation where they were seen as lesser than or they
were silly or stupid characters, it would probably be called the 100-200 Republican voters.
That's true.
They would probably, yeah exactly, they would say, "No, you can't make three stooges anymore,"
unless they are living...
What the fuck is this?
Stop!
This sucks.
This is the three little stooges.
They would say, they would, uh...
GBO's just railroading everything with fucking photos.
You're ruining this episode!
You need to fucking stop.
You're literally ruining it.
I'm docking your pay.
Um, nobody can see these, you suck at, you're so bad at your job.
If you're gonna do that, you at least have to put them on screen.
You're actually so fucking bad at your job, it's unreal.
You show up to work in a hoodie.
Yeah, at least dress nicely.
Look at this fucking piece of shit.
You're dressed up like some kind of graffiti artist.
You made me lose my thread on Republican Stooges.
Which was gonna be probably an all time part of one of the smartest things we've ever done.
In the podcast.
It was gonna be on some Mort Sahl shit.
This was gonna be the one that pops us.
We're about to pop.
This was gonna be like fuckin, I don't know, what's another?
Matrix PowerPoint.
This was gonna be our Matrix PowerPoint.
It was gonna be Republican Stooges.
fuck it it got completely ruined by you yeah you are a piece of shit stop
touching the computer go back to your face you only use a computer when I ask
you to specifically and I say please go to addicting games comm and show me the
spread which real quick yeah you could do that you know it sucks all the games
on there now they're still flash enabled so you can't can't if you go to addicting
games right now you try to play balloons uh-huh it says this plug-in is not
supported now they got all these HTML 5 games Oh good game Empire that sounds fun
that doesn't sound as good good game Empire well arm good game big farm good
game big farm dude far did you guys play Farmville when you were kids no I love
it I love it and I was like what are you what are you are you a mom are you
that's what I would that's was my you were mad when a motherfucking got no
carrots that's you I didn't have anything you didn't I know that's what
I'm saying you didn't I played Tetris you had no carrots at all yeah all right
I had, I played Mafia Wars and then also there was a Facebook app called Flare.
You played a game called Flare?
Wasn't a game.
It was a light that you looked into?
No, it was a virtual cork board.
It was a virtual cork board that you could play?
My mom showed me it and she was like, "Look at how much flare I have."
I was like, "Okay."
What?
I guess it used to show on your profile.
Like OfficeSpace Flare?
Yeah. It used to show on your profile that you had this little cork board with buttons.
But then that only worked for maybe a year. So then you had to open up the Flare in a
completely different app. And it was like you could put a picture.
They ruined Flare.
That sucks, man.
That's why MySpace was sick because you could put those HTML things in your page. Like you
go to playlist.com put up your own playlist you didn't have to just have
one song you can have dude did you guys do you guys remember I just remembered
this do you guys remember that fucking Facebook game that Halloween game where
you would put in your information that would be a clip of a creepy old guy
looking at your profile and then he would be like I'm gonna fuck this little
kid and then jump in his car I'm serious and they jump in his car and I don't I
I seriously doubt that the thing that I don't remember he said that was I'm
going to do that. That's what I felt threatened. I thought that was
the kind of context, the subtext of the video. The threat was like he's gonna
come fuck me. There's like this scary old guy. Remember, remember, remember LMS for a truth is?
You guys don't remember that? Yeah. Now it's NGL. LMS for a truth is. You put it on your Instagram story.
Wait, can we do a real life LMS right now for a truth is? First of all, you got to LMS. Truth is, okay, wait.
Like this. I'm gonna do a silly one. Okay, but it's not, whoever likes it.
I'm not gonna like anything. I don't want to. I do want to truth is desperately. I'm gonna like Cameron's post.
Truth is you seem hella chill. We should hang out sometime. I don't know you that well, but you did make a funny joke in English one time.
Then rate. In English? Yeah, class. English class.
Rate and then I do want the emoji and it's like the emoji code.
Or like it's like it's like I do like the color the cut it's like it's like red
You're hot and I do I do blue which is IDK
Yeah
Okay, one time one time. I liked like just a truth is when I was in middle school someone that I kind of knew
They rated me a six
That is cold. That's I mean that's above you have to you also you have to expect if you if it's someone you don't know if
It's someone you don't know that well
I'm gonna get a Mariah you have to assume that they're gonna give you the you seem chill
Yeah, and the end at six to seven that's that's okay because you're violent said I was funny af though all right Wow
I'm liking Patrick. Oh shit. Okay. I like your status
Truth is Cameron. What can I say?
(laughter)
- Damn.
- We've basically...
(laughter)
We've basically been best friends since...
Since elementary school,
and we've pretty much been in every single class together,
except for fifth grade.
(laughter)
Bad face.
It's so cool that we have been friends for this long,
And honestly, we have so many inside jokes
that I can't even type this
without thinking about cracking up.
I would rate you a 10 out of 10.
And for the Sharpie color,
I'm giving you silver,
which means you're my bestie.
- Okay, I'm gonna comment on that.
And I'm saying, "Indian Hitler, LOL."
To everyone else, that's an inside joke.
And it's okay for me to comment that 'cause it's 2009.
I'm gonna comment it and say I get it too.
(laughing)
- I'm reporting your comments.
- Okay.
(laughing)
Okay, so what do you guys wanna like mine?
Saw my status.
- What status?
You didn't post a status.
- I just posted one that says LMS for a rating.
Like it, come on.
- I just posted--
- Come on, like it guys.
- 24 hours have passed.
- Yeah, 24 hours have passed, no likes.
- So somebody like it though.
- Yeah, you posted another one.
- I just posted on camera as well.
- Yo, LMS, LMS for a double true status.
- Bro, I think I'm shadow banned.
LMS for a triple rating.
- I just posted on Cameron's wall,
I just posted on Cameron's wall,
GMC for show, I'm da best.
And I said, check this shit out, LMFAO.
- I'm liking it and I comment, damn.
- Listening to Firefly's Owl City.
Somebody please like this status and I can rate you.
Mom, don't like this.
Wait, oh, wait, here's what I'm gonna do.
I posted a stencil cutout picture of Edward Norton and the caption says, "With insomnia,
everything is a copy of a copy of a copy."
I posted it at 1231 AM.
I liked that and I commented a fire emoji.
I just posted a new status, "Can someone drop a little bit of knowledge?
Tell Roth I didn't love college."
- End quote, dash chitty bang.
(laughing)
- I just commented on that,
a YouTube link to opposite of adults,
the one that samples kids.
- I like the comment, I say, "Damn, bro."
- Okay, you guys both just got a text from me, right?
And it says, "Yo, check my recent FB status."
And then my signature is, "Life is my,
"what should I scream for?
"This is my theme park, Little Wayne, forever."
Okay, you go on Facebook, you see my status,
- LMS for a triple X rated rating.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- Tell me that in a sentence.
- Okay, I don't like, but I comment, and I say--
- Or comment.
(laughing)
- No, you can't-- - I add after you comment.
- I comment, I say, "Damn, I don't know if I should XD."
- I post a status--
- I little X big--
- Okay, I reply.
- I post a status, I say, "Like for an anonymous truth is."
- I also-- - And I will post it
as my status. - I also after,
after I comment that, I make my own status,
and it says, "Some guys at our school seem hella gay, lol."
(laughing)
- Okay, I comment, I reply to your comment,
and I say, X-rated time, "Yo, motherfucker!"
(laughing)
I honestly don't know you that well,
but we had one of the craziest fuckin' dodgeball games
of my life, and I still have hella bruises from that ish.
You and me, we love rapping along to T.I.,
whatever you like, even the explicit version,
which you had on your iPod video, right?
remember that one time that you stayed over my house and you haven't come back?
What the fuck is that about? I'll give you a red for red hot.
10 out of 10.
But also I just posted another status that says,
can't wait for Kevin Rudolph album too.
I'm going to like Patrick's status about the anonymous truth is. Okay.
Come on. TBH. Honestly, bro.
It's kinda sad how desperate you are.
(laughter)
I'm not saying this to be mean.
But, some people just can't read a room.
My bedroom, that is.
You slept over my house and left super early
and I know it's 'cause you wet the bed.
- I comment LOL would hate to be this guy.
(laughter)
rating rating six colon there's room for some improvement though okay I'm going
on I'm going on Urban Dictionary and I'm getting a definition for Caleb nice the
most awkward motherfucker and bed wet in the whole school I'm hanging out with my
girl cousins and we're all looking up our names on our we look up Cynthia and
it says it says the most awesome best friend you can have we look up Courtney
the best friend you can have in the world. We look up Caleb and it says that and I
say it's got to be a mistake but then we keep scrolling and pretty much every
definition is the exact same. So we decided to go on chat roulette.
Uh-huh. Yep. Pull up chat roulette right now. No, don't do that. No, no, no. Stop. Dude, there's
gonna be a fucking hot ass girl that's gonna want to make love to us. Someone's gonna whip their
cock out. Yeah, yeah, we used to whip our cock. We've talked about that, right?
We saw you did that you you just say we we remember guys the royal
Way he's getting all those weird truths is yeah, no what dude
I was the fun ass kid at every party who whipped his dick out on chat roulette and tried to get the adult arrested
Yeah, that was funny
That's the funniest thing you can do
It's a you're is whip your dick out when as soon as you get an adult guy and say you're a pedophile
That's the funniest thing you can do. Yeah. Until you get a little bit older and
you realize that probably most of those people were pedophiles. And I gave them exactly what
they wanted. Yeah, and that's on their computer still. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
I thought when I was a kid that I couldn't take any nude photos of myself because I would go to jail.
Yeah. Because my body was such a perfect...
It was so perfect. Well, you don't ever, you never know who's gonna get in because like, you know,
Like say your your mom lets you upgrade your phone. Yeah going from the flip phone to the other flip the cooler flip phone
Yeah, and it's like they refurbish that shit, but you know they could probably recover some of the data or whatever
That's the text you sent to you know
Text I send to my what you know my girlfriend not my boyfriend
Sending text, you know my fucking uncle that is fucked up
You are
General not you well you looked at me and then away
No, I looked at Patrick
But you were talking to me and then you looked at Patrick when you said your uncle like yeah like cuz I was secret
I feel like you two
Honestly, I feel like you two gang up on me and make me feel like I'm this weird-ass kid all the time
Even though I'm the fucking completely normal one and you two will probably never get even jobs or go to college
Not true. We all went to college together. That's an offer God. I'm gonna go. I mean I
It's right we're just kids are we we're just kids where what where are we?
Where are we we're at my uncle's house?
He invited all three of us over
listen, I just feel like you two could be nicer in class because
You guys honestly are hella excluding me all the fucking time. It's bullshit
That is not dude don't laugh at that little Lego helmet, that's mine
- He thought it was a Lego helmet.
- Bro, stop making me feel like this.
This is honestly gonna lead to some
developmental issues for me.
- No, for real though?
- Yeah.
- I think I need to go home.
- No you don't.
- Yeah, I just remembered I have to do homework.
- You don't do homework, bro.
It's the middle of the summer.
- Do you ever know--
- I mean, I have to get into my summer reading.
- We're talking about Omegle and Chat Relay.
Do you ever know somebody who made a good friend off of there?
- I one time fell in love with a girl
and then my little brother turned off the computer
and I beat his ass for like an hour.
- What up with the girl?
- I fell completely in love and she was like literally
two digits into giving me her phone number
so that we could continue texting
and we could maybe fall in love
and actually have a marriage.
- Yeah.
- And now I'm with this other fucking bitch you guys.
(laughing)
So obviously it didn't work out.
Sucks.
I think about her every day.
- I knew a few people who were like
friends with people for like life.
That they met off of--
- Off of Omegle?
Oh, they died? Yeah, they weren't friends for life then, you fucking asshole.
They still have time to break the friendship.
You're such a no-it-all.
In what world?
You're just a no-it-all just now.
You're mad that I skipped grades.
Yeah, skipped grades backwards.
You skipped backwards.
That's called being held back, actually.
And don't say that I'm a no-it-all for knowing that.
I need someone to hold me back right now.
I almost got held back twice.
Where are you actually?
First time, first time, kindergarten.
I almost got held back.
- You didn't get held back in kindergarten, dude.
- So you didn't get held, you almost got held back.
- They were like, "We're thinking maybe."
- Your mom didn't say that 'cause you were in the way.
- And then my mom was like, "No."
- She said, "Let him through."
- Yeah, and then fifth grade, we had a meeting.
- That ruins you forever.
- I didn't wanna skip a grade because I didn't.
- Fifth grade, we had a meeting with the principal
because they were like, "He doesn't do any of his homework,
"so we have to keep him back."
And then my mom was like, "Yeah, he doesn't want
"to do his homework, he's a kid."
- That's like evil to hold a kid, but that's like, I mean--
- Of course he's not gonna do it.
- That's the biggest like stupid mom excuse.
Of like, "Uh, he's a kid,
"no he's not gonna do his homework."
- But I just remember how people would treat
kids who got held back.
- No, I know.
- Yeah.
- I think that's why--
- That's Frankenstein's monster.
- That's why my mom didn't want me to get held back.
But I think--
- You can't hold a kid.
- In hindsight, Bob--
- I remember Bob got held back.
- In hindsight, I probably should have.
- Probably shit-hoof.
- Probably should have.
(laughing)
- Well your life would be completely different.
I wouldn't know you, he wouldn't know you.
He might know you, but you would have been too young for me.
- Yeah.
- But I could have explained, oh I'm the same age.
- I only hung out with kids my own grade.
- Yeah.
- Pretty much my entire life.
- I'm younger grade than you.
- You are not a gunger grade.
- I'm a gunger grade than you.
- See, that doesn't even make sense.
Well you and me had a job together.
- That's true, yeah.
You are one grade below.
- I just proved you wrong.
You are a grade below.
Yeah.
That is embarrassing.
Damn.
No.
Yes, you're a grade below us.
He's a little kid.
No, I'm not.
You are literally a fucking junior.
I'm actually, I'm like two grades above him.
That's bullshit.
That's true, yeah.
That's true.
I was, when I transferred into college none of my credits transferred over.
Yeah, so he was still in fucking, yeah, he's a 13th grade.
I was a, I just became a junior when.
So you're a junior for life.
When I was in.
Do you ever think about going back?
out I like jet like my credits finally rolled over some shit I can't believe
that I'm asking you this would you ever think about going back to college? No. That would be so crazy. Everyone else that I know like dropped out of college would be like like mostly
like yeah maybe one day I would go back to college you're the only person I know
for a fact you will never go to college. I'm not doing school work ever again. Yeah fuck that man.
Yeah homework yeah you knew it's a tough homework that last year in college art
art history.
I'm trapped out of art history.
Too hard.
You know what, to get some kind of credit, I think it was like if I took this class I
would get a double credit and I took East Asian art history and it was so hard.
You have to memorize pictures.
Yeah, I had to memorize the whole artist from the entire gloria period and she would sing
them all in little songs.
You have to look at all these pictures that are confusing because they're art.
not just a picture of a thing, it's a crazy picture in a weird way. And you have to remember,
okay, what's the name? And it's going to be an Asian name, if it's Asian art history.
Like what's an example?
Oh, I didn't take Asian art history. So Patrick would have to give an example of this one.
Yeah.
Patrick, give me.
And then you have to remember, and then you also have to remember the year it was made
and also the name of the artist, which is going to be Patrick, an Asian name.
So what's the name?
it's it's hard trying to remember that's not even English there's that painting
with the waves I didn't take the class you know that one I know that there was
the Goryeo period and then you had a period around the same time I really do
not remember a single thing from that well cuz I took I took um I took an art
history class that was uh like Polynesian art yeah you remember I don't
- I don't remember any of it.
- Lilo and Stitch, mother fucker.
- Yeah, okay.
(laughing)
- Oh yeah.
- I'm trying, I can't.
- The picture of the white shirt.
(laughing)
- Lilo and Stitch.
No, that is actually fucking rude.
I took history of--
- Well no, you know what actually is nice about that
now that I'm thinking about it,
is a lot of it, you don't have to know the artist
'cause it's from like the 14th century or something.
You know, it would just be like, they made it.
- Yeah.
- It wasn't a person who would just be like,
yeah, they made this one.
- Yeah, yeah, the entire group got credit for it.
- They did this.
I took a history of women in America
and I kicked open the door, I said,
what up hoes?
This is the history of bitches and hoes.
And I got kicked out.
Yeah, that's a shame.
This is the history of fine ass women.
And it wasn't, a lot of these women were ugly.
Because it covered two credits
and I was trying to speed my way through.
I was trying to like only do two years there.
Yeah.
I took Latinx literature.
Yep.
I think everybody took that.
I got to watch that movie.
I took that too.
Yeah, I got to watch that movie.
Not me, but not me, because I didn't want to.
or what el norte I didn't watch that el norte good man or tape by el norte West
uh-huh el norte and then we read some play about pretty fucking sure we
listened to zoot suit riot by the cherry poppin I don't know what that is
what that is either but it's making me laugh that you're laughing we read some
play we read this play about this called the cherry poppin that's pretty nasty
that'd be a good name for a horse we read this play about a girl was only a head
and this guy fucked her whoa that can't be true
oh yes I don't know I don't know that's who I had to learn about he got head and
he fucked her and he got into a lot of trouble for that actually yeah do you
Diaz yeah. Bruno Bliaz. Juni Cortez. That's what I'd rather see. Latinx literature. The
Cortez family. Juni! Juni! I can run. I love that movie. Oh my god the best part of that
movie. The best part of the grandpa thing is when they they do like when he
gets his legs back there like they're scanning him into the game and they do
like a scan that's like a 3D wireframe of him in his wheelchair and it's like
rotating and it has like the little lines that are labeling parts of his body
and it says like "Grandpa useless"
that's fucked up man. That's awesome. That's crazy. That's a good movie. Dude all those movies are so sick.
I wanted to be teleported into their Hispanic family so bad. I re-watched
them recently I re-watched because they're on Pluto TV I was watching like
the second half of all of them. Dude, the microwave that makes the food. The McDonald's thing.
Oh gosh. You put the aluminum foil in the microwave and then it blows up and it's a whole Big Mac
meal. That's definitely giving you some kind of permanent bone cancer. Remember the little
bug bot? Oh yeah. The bug bot was amazing. I got this Spy Kids toy as a kid. It was like
the metal briefcase that they have. He gets handcuffed to it in Spy Kids 2. Had the bug
And then a bunch of other gadgets
Animals that were also big do you know what I realized this is
The fucking that whole movie the second one is all like Ray Harry how like it's all like yeah
Skeletons and then animals and stuff. I never realized that what are you talking about?
Oh all the like old stuff. It's all reference old stop-motion stuff
Oh like that old movie where they fight the skeleton Jason and the Argonauts
I never really processed as a kid and I grew up and I was like that's actually a hell of a
That's nerd service. Wait, there's a spider monkey in Jason and the Argonauts? Yeah. Well, no, that's from the just
Spider half monkey. Yeah, he makes monsters. I saw a play in seventh grade. That was like two guys doing Jason and the Argonauts
Comedic as hell. I remember I think maybe the theater can be funny. Hmm. Yeah, I remember the first play I ever saw Don Quixote
Whoa, and I was like they got a new show for kids called Don Quixote and he's a puppet donkey
- Isn't his whole thing that he gets
that he wants to fuck as many bitches as possible on planet Earth?
- He wants to throw a javelin at a windmill.
- But he also is like fucking hoes.
- Is that the... that's all I know, is that he fights windmills.
- Yeah, that's all I know too. - Oh man.
- I didn't read it yet. - Yeah.
- They took us to a play, a field trip,
and we saw The Monkey's Paw as a play,
and I was kind of scared.
- That's scary as shit. - Hey, it was because
the only thing I want to see... - It was because they had
thunder crashes and stuff. - The only time I want to see
- I'd rather see a monkey's paws at the zoo.
- That's right.
- Take me on a trip to the zoo.
- I'd rather see its hand than its paw.
- What?
- Are you for real right now?
- Are you fucking serious?
- Are you shitting me?
- I think the first--
- I wish I had a button here that had a hand,
a big hand comes out of here.
- I remember the first stage production I ever saw,
my mom was in a community theater thing
for some play that was essentially--
- You think Bad Mom's the play?
- No.
(laughing)
- That's not funny.
That's actually not funny.
- The movie Bad Moms.
- You're saying that I had a bad mom?
- No, I'm saying-- - That is not fucking funny.
- I'm saying that your mom was in Bad Moms the play.
- Is that like horrible bosses?
- Yeah.
- Bad moms and bad Santa, moms that like to drink wine--
- You're actually gonna piss me off.
You're actually gonna fucking piss me off.
- If I was in a play, I would not let my kids see me
in a play. - I'm saying that it was
Bad Moms the play.
- It wasn't though.
It was some stinky cheese-- - What was it then?
- It was like basically stinky cheese man.
- Your mom was in the Stinky Cheese play?
- It was basically the Stinky Cheese Man
where it was like a bunch of different like,
like the shit.
- Come on little Caleb,
come watch me in the Stinky Cheese play.
- Hey Caleb, I'm the Stinky Cheese.
- She didn't play the Stinky Cheese,
she played Rapunzel.
- I'm so excited.
- She played Rapunzel, okay?
She had to wear a giant hair extension
and then we got out and my mom said,
"How'd you think of it?"
And I said, "They should make the Matrix a play."
- How old were you?
- 17.
- No, I was probably nine or 10.
- Yeah.
Come on, this is gonna, come on little Caleb,
this is gonna shape your perception of me forever.
I want you to come watch me perform
in the Stinky Cheese Man.
- If you guys, if you guys, if my mom--
- My mom was in the Stinky Cheese Man.
- Okay, first of all, the Stinky Cheese Man
is one of my favorite films.
- I know.
- Like how you say, like when you say your dad
is in a movie or something.
- It'd be terrible, it'd be terrible if somebody
made fun of somebody's mom on this podcast.
- I agree, because I don't make fun of your mom.
- I'm not making fun of--
- I make love to your mom.
- Anybody's mom would make fun of the Stinky Cheese Clay.
- But if my mom--
He got so upset because I said his mom was in Bad Moms the play.
Yeah because his mom was in a worse play.
His mom's in a way worse play.
She could have been on some one woman show where she's drinking wine and stuff.
Okay, LMS for a rating.
Patrick? Nope. LMS for a rating.
I'm not gonna like that. Okay, I'm posting on your wall.
So...
dot dot dot.
You said that my mom was in Bad Moms the play
when I was trying to clarify that she was in a
play that was not the Stinky Cheese Man
not the stinky cheese man as at Cameron Fetter as at camera at my name my name
is Cameron Cuddy as at Cameron Cuddy said he was she was not in stinky cheese man
she was in a play that was akin to stinky cheese man and before you call me
and know it all for knowing what a kin means when we're only three years old I
learned that from the play because it was also educational it wasn't the stinky
It was a kind of you remember in the sticky cheese
Fine she was in bad mom. She was in bad fucking slut mom. Yeah, that's what she was in she played Katherine
Rip off this smelly butter guy
Such thing as smelly butter
When we were when we were kids in my family we got like us like this spider-man VHS camcorder
And we made it we tried to make a TV show and are my older brother my
My older brother we made him play a character called fat baloney
That's rude
You know it was just making you imagine fat baloney guy the play if either of you two came to my house
I'm opening the door and speaking of Spider-Man, I'm doing this silly string right in your face.
Okay, well we're never coming to your house. Here's what happens, you hear the knock, you
open the door, you spray out, you spray into nothing, we ding-dong ditched you.
Yep.
I have silly string that reaches hundreds of feet.
And we have flaming poop on the doorstep too.
And we have spy glasses that let us see through things.
You would do that because you're stealing from a movie and you're the kid who's walking
around saying, "Oh dear sweet baby Jesus,
you're ripping off Talladega Nights."
- Yeah, I'm putting it on my Facebook status.
I'm making Ron Burgundy quotes my Facebook status.
- You rip off Talladega Nights at school all the time.
- You've never seen Talladega Nights.
- All the fucking time.
- You're not allowed to watch it.
- I'm allowed to see every--
- You're only allowed to see the Stinky Cheese movie.
- My entire house, my DVD collection is all R-rated.
The entire thing is DVDs that are R.
- You have VeggieTales tapes that you wrote R on.
Open it, watch this, you're my boy, Blue.
- I have the unrated version of A of E.
is another movie that's from i have the under a diversion of a lot of money
ricky bobby
i have the under a diversion of a on flux and there's boobs are human torches
denied a bank loan
what is it we i've seen the movie is a referencing i've seen it
i've seen the movie that you are liberty kids
united
uh... it's a paper i've seen the movie references
you every day
every day you're like
you watch
you watch liberty kids and your favorite
character is benjamin franklin
no i didn't
i wish the kids weren't in this
i wish it was just the founding fathers
i've never even heard of this show
i've never seen it
this liberty kids is a new england thing
i don't know
liberty kids is the funniest
I watch... It's a show they make you watch in fifth grade when you're learning about the Declaration of Independence.
I didn't watch that, I watched the John Stossel program.
You look up and you pull up a picture of Liberty Kids for Caleb.
I watched the John Stossel program and I made my family computer's home page the US debt clock.
Okay? This is Caleb's favorite show.
No, I hated this show. I've never even heard of this bullshit.
No, I was doing... This is Caleb's favorite show.
No, that's just wrong. It was not Liberty Kids. My favorite show was Adventures in Odyssey.
You know what, actually maybe it was my favorite show. Now that I've seen that.
Oh my god, we should watch Liberty Kids. Yeah, just put that on YouTube. We're gonna, the
rest of the episode we're just gonna watch that.
You guys have been such dickhead assholes to me. And I honestly-
I'm telling your mom what you just said. I'm telling my mom that you two double bullied
We didn't double bully. I can't imagine it feels like
That must be so
So terrible. No
Back on this side there we go Caleb boy and Patrick gay guy yeah, you're in numb nuts
You're a cotton-headed ninny muggins. You're in numb nuts. I love that movie. You're a cotton-headed ninny muggins
I love that movie at Christmas, and I saw the unrated version of that movie - like five times
Well you are cotton-headed ninny muggins
No, I'm not and if you say that again the principal's gonna overhear you cuz I'm gonna get him. It's not even a cuss
It's literally not even a fucking cuss. I will be to the principal. Why cuz he's a Christmas elf cuz he's short
You're saying mr. Wolf is short. Yeah
Cuz he is short. He's not I'm taller than him. Yeah, that's cuz you hit puberty earlier than us - okay
So that doesn't mean fucking bullshit. I don't even care that you have pubes anymore
It's not even impressive that you have yeah, it's not impressive that you have pews my uncle has
stuff. It doesn't matter that me and Patrick are shorter than all the girls
in the class. Whatever, I don't care, I don't care, I don't care. I'm gonna go watch my Transformers DVD
with the slipcover that I got for my birthday. Patrick, we did karaoke at the last music
class of the year. None of the girls thought it was embarrassing that I picked
the "Who" as my song. Patrick, LMS for a YouTube video. I need to see a YouTube
video. I liked it. It's called, it's called "How to Be Awesome," right? You click it.
(Humming)
You don't like it?
You Rickrolled me and that's a type of...
That's blocked.
I'm blocking you right now, bitch.
Blocked on all platforms.
Facebook, Gmail, your cell phone.
You're not even going to see me on Sparktop.org.
I'm hitting you up on my...
I see you in class, I put my folder across my face like this.
I'm gonna hit you up on RuneScape.
I don't play RuneScape, I play Adventure Quest.
We just drew a funny ass photo of you
and Microsoft Paint in the computer.
My friend, Peter F., actually gave me his Guardian account.
Peter Fetter.
Guess what I'm doing?
You guys have set me off a very, very bad, bad, bad track,
and now I'm gonna start drawing swastikas
into all of the bathroom stalls,
and I'm gonna eventually get suspended.
(laughing)
And my mom is gonna start making me eat
natural peanut butter instead of the stuff with sugar in it.
(laughing)
'Cause it hypes me up too much.
Yeah, that's right.
Fuck you guys, I'm outta here.
- Fuck you.
- I guess this is the end.
- You're a piece of shit.
Fucking shit, man.
- He's dropped his C4.
He made it.
- I'm gonna put some C4 in the classroom
and blow you up.
I'm gonna blow you up.
- You're not, you wouldn't dare.