(upbeat music)
- Man, I burped into my hands.
- That was a Jurassic Park.
- Yeah, that sounded like a dragon.
- That was a quiet place.
- Hold my hand.
Now he'll do it.
Now he'll hold my hand.
Very funny, very fucking funny.
With the cameras are on, you'll hold my hand.
But a couple of nights ago, he once again,
- You were jilted. - Shoot me away.
- I'm very jilted. - He denied me.
He denied me, yet again the other night.
- Whoa. - What?
- That door just opened.
- That is the scariest thing. - What the fuck is going,
now it's closing.
- It's because Caleb smoked a cigarette earlier.
- What just happened, is there someone out there?
- I don't know.
You want me to go see?
- Yeah, can you go look?
- There's no one out there.
- It just opened and closed.
It opened and I said, "Whoa, it opened,"
and then it closed.
- It's backdraft and Caleb left the door open
after smoking in the building. - That was scary.
Literally told you guys there was a presence in here the other day. That was fun. It was it was that was a ghost from outside
That was coming in to haunt is just a great
Insane serial killer
You think that's more important than yeah ghost of a serial killer that
Killer it's not a ghost is a real. There's probably a ghost and a serial because there was a ghost in your operation
I raised my glass, and he's just you honestly you couldn't wait two minutes
Mountain Dew. You didn't even pour glasses for us.
I did. You decided to just start tasting.
You're a bitch.
I really, oh man, I missed it so much. I used to drink six cans of this a day.
Okay, you carry the next 10 minutes.
All right, I will. So, Burt Bacharach has passed away.
Burt Bacharach, you may remember him from such movies as Austin Powers and such
songs as Always Something There to Remind Me.
literally I'm carrying the next 10 minutes.
And you, if you want to--
- What's with all this dead air?
- If you want to hop in--
- I think you're floundering as well.
- I'm not floundering.
- I think that you're floundering.
- You're a flounder.
- But go ahead.
- You're a flounder for the little mermaid.
- But go ahead, I'm gonna put my mic back down, buddy,
and you can go give it, and see how hard it is.
- Burt Bacharach, legendary music, singer-songwriter,
has passed away.
He sang songs as "What the World Needs Now,"
and also The Way to San Jose.
But he had one song called Wives and Lovers,
which was sung by Andy Williams.
And the whole song is about how
to train your wife to be a dog.
- You want to check for that, Caleb?
- Yeah, we can do it.
- And...
(laughing)
It's a good song, pretty good.
but the lyrics could not be written today.
And I hope that people don't remember
Bert Peckereck for this song.
I hope that they remember him for
all of his other beautiful, beautiful songs.
What else is happening in the world today in the news?
- Are you done?
- I'm done, okay?
- Okay. - I'm done.
I couldn't handle it.
You we're not gonna get this you're the wrong address what address they ordered to ordered it to one two three poop lane
And for apartment you put do me I?
Made a but dookie, but I do me do me
Okay, that's my bad
Man I don't even I'm not even in love with you anymore Patrick. I decided this is such a you've had such a disgusting display today
Yeah, yeah, we can't restart the episode you're just drinking sody
We already had the most terrifying event of the entire year have caught on you want to restart the episode
Why wouldn't you fall in love with me the other night when we were the other night?
We went we went out to we went out to the soda
We went out to the stomach is shooting slob probably because the other night we went out to the pub
Yeah, mom. I hope you're not listening. Yeah, I had a couple pints. I had a few a few points a few
"Then fucking sue me, mom. I don't care, mom. It's not your business."
But I tried to come on to Patrick pretty heavily, and he basically took it as a complete joke.
And I was saying, "Let's go to the bathroom. Let's seal this deal." And he was going, "Ha ha ha."
And he said, "I'm jolting you."
Yeah.
And I was also eating wings while he was trying to do this.
So you saved me because you would have gotten buffalo sauce on my butt.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, which would have been this doesn't take this tape is grape juice. This is shit. Yeah, but you didn't drink it as a kid
So you don't get it
No, I wasn't allowed to drink soda. Yeah, you imagine how much worse I drink
When I was younger
That like I bought it just cuz I saw it in the store and then once I got here I read mighty refreshing
I looked at the the nutritional facts
75 grams of sugar. Oh, yeah, that is crazy. Yeah
It is like a miracle that I do not have type 2 diabetes.
Imagine how much fruit you'd have to eat
to eat 75 grams of sugar.
You'd have to eat like fucking 40 watermelons.
This, for me, this is like, you know when your mom
sees like, oh my god, they brought Frankenberry back
for the holiday season.
And then it gets excited and buys like three boxes of it.
Your mom gets excited to see Frankenberry?
He was my crush growing up.
- Frankenberry, ooh.
- No, you know, like, oh, when like, no, no, no,
when like, when millennials see that they brought back
like Dunkaroos.
- Well, this is unique to your families
that all of you are just like,
snacks, like, tooth-rotting, crazy shit.
- That's true.
- Yeah, that's not an experience I've ever had.
- There's a few people who get excited
when they see stuff is back.
- Yeah, I think your entire ancestral line
came from from wherever the Oompa Loompas are from.
India.
They like candy.
In the new movie.
India?
Yeah.
Remember you were saying I took that test, I am not, he's Indian.
I'm not Indian.
Oh, Native American.
You can't say that.
Oh!
Jesus Christ.
You can still say Indian.
I did a racial.
No, I'm putting my foot down.
You guys can't say that.
I've never said that.
I've always said Native American.
So speaking of that, I have some really exciting news.
Okay.
For people who didn't listen to the last episode, we found out that Cameron is 5% Native American
and about 3% Somali.
And among some other...
Interesting.
I don't want any more, man.
Because you know I'm going to drink that.
I was talking about my great-grandfather, that episode, right?
I remembered that when he died, he left me a small parcel of land.
What?
What are you talking about?
left me half an acre. Whoa! And it is in, I'm not gonna say where exactly, I'm not
gonna say where it is because that you can look up my dad's address from it if
you go to like the thing, but it's in the desert. Don't tell me. It's
next to, it's okay, no it's not, it's not reservation land. I was like, oh my god bro, we're opening a casino.
but even better than a reservation. I am going to travel there. You guys are welcome to come
with me if you'd like.
We should. We should open up.
I am opening, this is my official announcement, I am opening Fetter World, an amusement park.
No, no, no.
Whoa.
No, no.
Cam-de-land.
Nope, it's called Fetter World.
Fetter World?
There's no candy or soda there at all. It's healthy foods.
Cammy Land.
It's called Fetter World.
It's all celery.
It's a love letter to my family.
Okay.
Wow, like an album.
And it's also this land is next to an abandoned mine.
- Can you tell us what state it's in?
- It's in New Mexico.
- Whoa, you're a land owner?
- Yeah, so I'm landed gentry.
- That is so fucking sick, dude.
- Isn't that crazy?
And I was talking to my dad,
'cause I had completely forgotten about this,
and I was like, I just remember,
and he was like, yeah, I've been paying
the property taxes on it every year.
And I was like, oh my God, you didn't have to do that.
I'm sorry.
And he's like, no, don't worry, it's $5 a year.
(laughing)
- So it's worth nothing.
- Yeah, it's literally, it's undeveloped,
like a half a football field of desert.
- I think property tax is like half a percent
of the property value a year, so it's worth $1,000.
(laughing)
- But that's why we're gonna increase the value
by building Federworld.
- And also what that's gonna lead to
is that's gonna lead to some development around Federworld,
'cause there's gonna be people traveling,
you're gonna need somewhere to stay, somewhere to eat,
other stuff to do. - Exactly.
We can buy up the parcels around it.
- Maybe me and Patrick can finally open our comedy club.
- That would be perfect.
- Giggling chuckles.
- Giggling chuckles would be really good.
And this is also, there's not a road
that goes to this land. (laughs)
- So I can also open my own business.
- You can't get there.
- Or we could do Uber helicopter.
- I mean, it sucks that we can't look it up right now.
- I'll show you guys after.
But yeah, I don't wanna show it on here
'cause you can find out everything about my family.
- Yeah. - Okay.
- But then once you open Fetter World--
- Once you open Fetter World,
it's gonna be the Hall of Fetters,
and we're gonna see the entire family history
leading up to you.
And it'll start, it's gonna be all Native American.
- Yeah. (laughs)
- Just Native American history,
just normal out of a textbook Native American history,
and then your dad and you. (laughs)
- I mean, we should start a pop-up shop there
and sell T-shirts.
- You can sell T-shirts inside Fetter World.
I'm gonna pop out. I'm gonna pop off. Yeah. At Fetter World. Mm-hmm.
'Cause we're gonna do... I'm so excited to go to Fetter World. We're gonna have the...
And I'm... We're gonna have... You're gonna have a big version of your head that's like...
Yeah, you walk in... You walk in the tongue. To get into the tongue. Yeah. Yeah.
Tunnel of Love with me and Patrick. Yep. Could be Tunnel of Love.
You have a cherubic... And now here... Now, here's the thing about it, too. I'm excited...
The other... The other exciting thing about Fetter World... What's that? Is because...
So, this is half an acre of land. Yeah. And if you've ever been to an amusement park,
they're usually, I think, a little maybe bigger than half an acre.
- But in feet, how big is an acre?
- Half an acre is half a football field, roughly.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
- It's not that big.
- Yeah, it's pretty small.
And so I'm excited to announce a solution to this issue,
to the small amusement park issue
that a lot of people are running into these days.
I own land, it's too small for an amusement park.
Federworld is going to be the first vertical amusement park
that's inside a skyscraper.
- Wow!
- Yep.
roller coasters go up and down instead of side to side.
Do you think maybe...
You should get Tyson Krupp to design a lot of this.
There's going to be elevators up and water slides down.
Wow.
Do you think maybe...
And ladders too.
...that an up and coming recording artist could perform?
I think you could do a residency, yeah.
I think, but you're going to have to do, you're going to have to be some kind of impersonator
because that's the type of show...
But I have a music career now.
But you're not famous for music.
Yeah, but that's not what they do.
Yeah, but you're gonna have to impersonate Michael Jackson or maybe Tupac or someone like that.
So I have to do impersonations before I can do...
No, it's an amusement park so you just have to do impersonations, period.
We could dress you up in a really, really hot suit to look like a beekeeper.
Or to be a... just a beekeeper suit, I guess.
And then you could walk around and you could get heatstroke.
And I'm the Beatles.
No, no, no, no, no.
No.
We should dress him up like a mascot but just a beekeeper outfit.
Or a beekeeper.
of those keeper or one of those ones with the where would you want to be keeper
yeah that's the or just really football field but what if you put a half of a
football field there we could put anything we can do we can basically put
anything there because we can just go up into the skybox how far up do you think
you're going to build dig down to another think about maybe hit some oil
Yeah, New Mexico. Oh my God. There's a mine next to it. You build it. You build a
crater right inside of the crater whole amusement park. We should go there. I
really want to go there. We should go there and we should dig up and the
entire thing and see if we strike oil. Yeah. Yeah. We should just ruin the
entire thing because that's like the only that's yeah, that's a ticket.
That's how we have to if we do find oil there worth it. We fund we build and
- If we don't find oil there, we just pave over it,
what we dug, and it's like we never dug at all,
and then we don't Federal World.
- Either way, we're gonna have to dig
to build a foundation anyway.
So we might as well dig down,
if we find oil, the entire thing's paid for.
Federal World, we break ground on it tomorrow.
- If we don't, we just dig out some loans or something.
- It's not that big of a deal, man.
We have a business, we have a business.
It could be a subsidiary of Federal World.
- Oh my God, you could set up a PO box there.
(laughing)
We set up a PO box right there.
- In New Mexico?
middle of the desert, nothing's there, one road that leads to it. We paid a
pave a road to it, just one lone PO box and you can send us mail. We could go do...
We could go pick it up once every ten years. I think maybe we start with like maybe a
music festival or something. Yeah. Yeah. I think Fetter Fest. Fetter Fest is a good
idea. Fetter Fest is a great idea. And then you won't have to be an impersonator. You can be
You can be yourself.
I can debut.
I've already got a single coming out.
And half acre, we could probably fit 150 people, 200 people on a half acre.
More for vertical.
Yeah, it's a vertical music festival.
Oh my God.
And there's stages on every floor.
Yeah, exactly.
Every floor is a new stage.
That's amazing.
Oh my God.
Wow.
We have a hundred acts.
They all play simultaneously.
Holy shit.
And you can choose which one you want to listen to.
Wow.
And you use the roller coasters to get up and down.
Yeah.
Better World sounds incredible.
Right?
I mean, I texted my dad that I was gonna build it.
- I was a little bit skeptical at first,
just because of--
- We could get Skepta there.
- But then I realized that we could get Skepta there,
and that eased all my pain.
- There's gonna be a restaurant in there too.
- Dude, I can't believe you're Orlando.
I need to get land.
- You do need to get some land.
You should buy one of those.
You guys should buy one of those next to it.
- Pitsworld and Doranworld.
(laughing)
All three right next to each other.
- I bet you could.
- I would call it Doranvillage.
- It would be really cheap.
- Mine would be modest.
it would be Doran Village.
You would have like a--
Old Doran Village.
Yours would be like Colonial Williamsburg type of part,
but about the Civil War.
No, it'll be the old Colonial Williamsburg,
but about like two years ago.
Yeah.
It's just like, man.
He'd probably do Williamsburg, Brooklyn, 2009.
That's what you'd do.
Oh my god, yeah.
He'd fuck off.
I know why you're saying 2009 Williamsburg.
That's what you would do.
You went to a bar in Pittsburgh, and you
kept saying it's 2009 Williamsburg vibes in here.
I kept saying that?
- Oh, Adam said it.
- Yeah.
- Dork.
(laughing)
- Old dork.
- Old head.
- But yeah, that's what you would do,
is you would go there,
you would build an entire kind of Starbucks baby--
- Oh my God, it would be 2009 Williamsburg bars.
- You would have like a Colonial Williamsburg
and you'd have all the like old house and everything,
you'd go inside and be like,
"Wow, I wonder how they lived."
And it would just be monster energy cans on every surface,
on all the houses inside.
- That's it, you would fall asleep
while you were trying to build your park.
- Yeah.
- We're grinders.
- We're grinders, diligent hard workers.
- I literally, if I had land--
- And you're a never-minder.
- If I had land and I made my own village,
I wouldn't give a shit.
- Have you ever built a building before?
- Yeah.
- Have you ever like honestly,
have you ever like mowed a lawn or anything like that?
- Really?
- Yeah, actually I have.
- I forgot that I did.
I used to ride around, I would drink.
- Ride on mower.
- Riding mower, yeah.
- Did you ever have to do the manual weed whacker thing
where it's like a long pole and it has the thing
that goes like that and you swing it like a golf club.
- Yeah, a scythe.
- No, it's not a scythe, it's different from a scythe.
- Sorry, that was off.
- Huh?
- Planzaball was off.
- Oh, okay.
- Planzaball.
- I had a shoveled--
- My grandpa had a scythe,
that's how he would fucking cut his big trotter.
- I think it's different from a scythe,
what I'm thinking of, 'cause it didn't look like a scythe.
- No, you could cut grass with a scythe.
- But I think the thing I had wasn't a scythe.
I had a push mower that was not electric.
I had a manual.
Me too.
Those things fucking sucked, dude.
It drove me crazy, bro.
Yeah, this thing.
Yeah, mine was not...
Wait, he's doing this because his lawnmower got stolen.
I would...
A video...
Wait, did it say that?
Yeah.
But yeah.
I mean, it's a pretty good way...
This is better than a push mower.
That's way cooler, yeah.
This is way better than those fucking manual push mowers.
Dude, I would sit on that thing.
When I lived with my parents, I fucking would sit...
- That's a go-kart, bro.
- Yeah, I know.
- That's a fun.
- I would sit there and I drank polar hard seltzers on it,
and I would just like whip it around.
- How awesome was your life?
- Yeah, it was this.
Oh, it's called a grass whip.
This is what I used to get weeds out of the yard.
- I've never seen that.
- You swing it like a golf club and hit the weeds.
- Oh yeah.
- And it has like a serrated edge.
- I used to have a job where I worked at a paintball field
and I had to mow the fucking side of a mountain.
and it was so bad. That was the hardest job I ever had in my life. And then it burned
down.
Nice.
Probably because you didn't clear the brush.
Common Caleb W.
I think maybe it burned down.
No, no, no.
Because you weren't clearing out the tiny sticks.
No, the job was mostly there. I would try to start the mower, I'd give up and I'd drink
lemonade for about four hours. And you'd use a hair dryer on everything until it was brown.
- I shoveled for like, I think I got up at like,
five in the morning, I did like a whole,
it was a snow day and I spent my whole snow day
shoveling like, in old folks' home and then like,
certain people's houses. - A whole snow day?
- And I made 60 people's houses.
- Certain people's houses? (laughs)
- I know I said certain. - Certain people's houses.
- So I shoveled, people who paid this company,
I show up from probably like five in the morning.
I worked like a full shift.
I got 60 bucks.
You got 60 bucks?
Yeah, how old were you?
I was 14.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
That's normal.
Yeah, that's a lot.
And then they never asked for me back.
I can imagine that you were pretty bad
at a manual labor job.
Yeah, what about me says that?
Just I feel like you'd get halfway through
and be like, it's just bullshit that I'd so hard.
No, you know what the thing was
is that I was like 14, I was probably,
I was like a twig back then.
I couldn't lift, I could not--
- A mental twig.
- I couldn't even pick shit up.
I was like so weak and feeble.
- You were a wig, like the political party.
- That's right, you were somewhere in between
the Democrats and the Republicans of the time.
- Yeah.
- You were--
- Thanks for playing that.
Yeah, I was a little boy back then.
- For whatever reason, everybody around me
when I was a kid was getting like,
they would get like retail jobs and shit
and make like pretty good money
working at a coffee shop and stuff,
you know, when they were like 15.
And I just refused to do that.
So I would just work the worst possible,
hardest manual labor jobs for like my mom's friend
and they always hired me
because they knew that they could pay me nothing.
- Yeah.
- They'd pay me like, they have 30 bucks
for like an eight hour day of moving gravel.
- But yeah, just knowing you and just like, yeah.
- I thought I was cool.
You wanted, when you were younger, you wanted to work construction and shit like that so
bad so that you could like, you would have like a grizzled look to you.
Definitely.
You wanted to like come home covered in like shit.
I saw my dad and my dad is like, you guys have never met my dad, right?
He looks like a piece of coal.
And I was like, this is what I'm gonna...
Hey, not based on those 23andMe results.
Well, that's what's so impressive about it.
He worked so hard, he worked himself coal black.
I would go do roofing, and I'd be out in the hot sun all day,
and I never wore sunscreen.
You were making you do roofing at 14?
No, when I was 17.
I did roofing for a year.
And that is a hard job, and it's the hottest job
in the entire universe.
But man, if you want to get some sunburn,
that's a great place to go.
Get some big red skin.
No, the best place to get sunburned is Cabo.
I would say space, probably, because you
don't have the protective layer of the atmosphere.
I never even considered it.
It's a really, really, really bad spitting.
Comment Caleb Tubby.
You are spitting.
That was a dub.
Yeah, I'm basically full of fucking dubs today.
That was a science dub.
Yeah, I mean, I read, you know, and I know that there's an atmosphere for a fact.
Yeah, you have the two science things down there.
What are my--
Space and atmosphere.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, the thing is, you're looking at my shirt and you're thinking, "This guy's into independent
independent hip hop, he might be thinking of a different atmosphere, right?
Yeah, I understand.
God loves ugly style atmosphere.
Uh-huh.
You know what I'm saying?
When you say ace opera and this guy, he's not thinking soap.
No, I'm not thinking soap.
I'm thinking...
That's what that guy sounds like.
Jedi Mind Tricks was...
Cool.
Dance with the Devil?
No.
Immortal Technique.
Yeah.
Jedi Mind Tricks has a line where they say, "Don't mess with me.
fly planes into towers. Yeah. And all their songs are about how they're like, there are
just guys from Philadelphia and all their songs are like, we got to go back to Iraq and do
arithmetic with a fucking, with a beetle. Yeah. I showed you guys this already, but I've been
obsessed with this one Lincoln Park song for the past like week. That's just a, just Mike
Shinoda one where Chester's not on it at all. He just sings like, yeah, every once in a while
on the chorus. But there's one line in it that I just keep thinking about where Mike
It says verbally break bones with sticks and stones tactics. That is so sick
The other that the other really good one is I twist mic cords and double helixes and show them what I'm made of that is sick
That is honestly
No, it's so awesome
Hey, also, he said he was rocking the mic before monkeys had human traits
That's so twisting twisting a mic cable twisting a mic cable your you'll damage the thing. Yeah, okay sound engineer
That's punk though.
But for normal guys, it's punk.
No, that's not punk.
It's actually more punk.
It's way more punk to treat audio equipment with respect.
But then also as a scientist and genome specialist, I hear Double Helix and I'm like, "Oh my
fucking God."
That's awesome, because I don't give a fuck about sound engineering.
I'm into, I'm into, uh...
You couldn't last...
No, this is literally the best song of all time.
You couldn't last one day without sound engineering.
Yeah, right.
You literally could not last one day without sound engineering.
Every sound engineer on fucking planet Earth killed themselves like the happening, throw
themselves into a wood chipper.
I wouldn't shed a single fucking tear.
I'm not a sound engineer.
He's not a sound engineer.
He's on the ones and twos right now.
I'm not a sound engineer.
Respect his ass.
This is not, no.
He's pulling up-
I'm a hobbyist.
He's pulling up a sound right now.
I respect everything Cameron does, but I have to say what he does is barely anything.
He does almost nothing.
He sits there and he presses the button.
What are you talking about?
He's doing, look, he's about to pull up a sound-
I'm the guy in Slipknot who just dances on the stage.
I don't do anything.
thing Jamie Baz from Happy Monday same vibes but he just bought them drugs what
are you talking about the guy at Bez or Baz or something I've been digging into
grace ever since I was living in space before the rat race before monkeys had
human traits I mastered numerology and Big Bang theology performed lobotomies
with telekinetic psychology dude that is so awesome invented the mic so I could
start blessing it chin-checking kids to make my point like an impressionist many
Many men have tried to shake us, but I twist my chords to double helixes and show 'em what I'm made of.
This is how powerful rap can be.
Isn't this incredible?
If you're a rapper who can't say the N-word, this is the kind of stuff that you do.
It's so awesome.
I buckle knees like leg braces, cast a spell of instrumentalness on all you MCs who hate us.
Wow. Amazing.
A spell of instrumentalness.
Amazing. Incredible.
Yeah, it is funny seeing the filler words that they'd use instead of the N-word, though.
MCs, cousin.
I put a kick in the back bones of clones with microphones
Yeah, cousin rappers. It's just so funny man rappers. Yeah, Vinny Paz definitely says rappers
That's his that's his one. Okay the last one
I'm gonna read meant to put you away with a pencil pistol official 16 line the rhyme missile
Shit the rhyme missile
The rhyme missile the run I am kind of terrified of what's gonna happen with the rhyme missile. I think that we all this Russian
Stuff I think that we try to rhyme one of their fucking words
What is that that was more kind of Swedish, oh yeah, yeah, you did Swedish chef, right?
You said yeah the Russians go heat up organoid
You did I did not do that you did
We should start a rap trio of consciousness lyrical hip-hop and then all transcendental meditation base
I would all the chef
It's amazing is when a rapper like that samples something like very
Cerebral like Beethoven's fifth. Yeah, that's when you know you're like, oh wait
We could say you know that we're like or like a garage band loop cuz you know that when they sample Beethoven
You know they were sitting around just fucking
That was was that like oh
three to like
2008 we should do a
This guy's this guy knows I told you the eras. No I told you
- Era?
- No, 'cause it's different types of sound engineering.
- Yeah, you're into eras.
- Sound engineering stuff.
- I don't give a fuck about eras.
I don't know what time anything happened.
All I know is that Logic is the greatest rapper ever.
- We should make, okay, we're gonna make a rap group
and we'll do conscious hip hop,
but we'll tell the entire Bible.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- We'll tell the Bible. - That's a good idea.
- And we'll sample Bittersweet Symphony.
- And then it'll be, but people--
- Be careful.
- Why? - Why?
- Careful with that sample.
- Could get sued.
- We won't get sued 'cause we're conscious.
sued for anything these days.
The verb does not see a single penny.
If they tried to sue us, we'd be like, "You want to sue someone who's trying to spread
conscious messages about the Bible?"
You know who loves conscious rap in the Bible is the Rolling Stones.
They love that.
If they try to sue us for Bittersweet Symphony, they'll step back.
How does Bittersweet Symphony go?
(humming)
- Oh, that's Rolling Stones.
- That is, so the sample is,
it's not even Rolling Stones,
it's an orchestrated version of one of their song
the last time, I think.
- Oh, I-- - And then because
it was like their melody. - I thought that was
the Kumon Learning Center commercial song.
(laughing)
I really did.
- Well, that might be, I don't know.
What is this?
Jubio is just trying to distract you.
I know. Fuck. He's trying to distract you again. He got you again.
It sucks that he's my manager now.
Yeah. As a musician.
You think, should we let him manage our new supergroup?
He's gonna be like...
No. No. Because of what he's doing to me right now.
I gotta pay for my own glitter and my own makeup.
Really?
He's making me... That's fucked!
So what Jubio thinks...
This is his prediction.
That in
Glamrock is gonna be a big he's gonna come back. So you're trying to he's trying to yeah
He's trying to make me dress up like a glam rock star like Motley Crue. Well, Tommy Lee's on Twitter now
He's good walls and stuff. Yeah, so like yeah, everyone's like, okay. This is the glam rock lifestyle. I can get behind this
This is funny. I looked up some pictures of Tommy Lee's fucking penis the other day
Yeah, that guy was packing a fucking serious burrito down there. Why'd you look up his penis just see it? Okay
All right, yeah, that's
Yet another comic
No nuts, I don't follow him his wife took a photo of his nuts
His wife is a stand-up comedian if she does jokes about my fucking husband's cock is so big it destroys my pussy
Does she his wife is that vine star remember Jenna Marley Furlan? No, really?
Yeah, he married Brittany Furlan and she makes a bunch of videos about how Pamela Anderson must hate her
Pamela Anderson probably just doesn't think about anything. No
She reacts to stimulus like an amoeba yeah, yeah, like yeah, the light the light changes in the room and she and she moves a little bit
I'm gonna do this. I spots you're gonna defend her. I'm gonna defend her and say that she doesn't you're not gonna be able to
defend her from me. Yeah, I will.
(laughter)
What the hell?
I'd run through armies to just rip her apart
and destroy her. Oh, alright.
That's the vibes you guys give off.
I would be doing a Mortal Kombat create your own fatality.
Like, not even one of the cool ones, one of the really
lame ones where they did the system where it's like, if you
press circle, you rip off his arm. If you press
X, you rip off his leg. And the thing is,
she's so fake, she probably has fake arms too.
Yeah, I wouldn't hurt her at all. She probably got fake, yeah, she would
use ripped stuff on her. She probably doesn't even exist.
Material range philosophically she probably isn't anything basically a fucking ship that one ship that
We don't know about yeah the ghost ship
No
That one freaky ship the thesis the ship of the chalice is shit
Just like I said this ship of crazy ship of theseus the ship of craziness
Ship of thesaurus you got to get think of a different ship bitch. Yeah, I'm saying the same thing
That's the ship that he's talking about the ship
Did you just do this that wasn't he did chatterbox and and you didn't even do this is what you're doing this yeah
I know you didn't even reference it. Yeah, so this was an original thought that he had was that this is you oh my god
You move your lips and you move your lips or your tongue tongue
Yeah, my teeth. I'm gonna say lips you move your teeth more than anything in your body is that true?
That's most of the words in your mouth come out of your teeth. What do you say? That's kind of you're sounding poetic
So I'd like to continue this this strand
You know you're most and you got venomous fangs like a snake. Oh things you say I
Yeah, my all your words and poison. I mean and
Venomous you think he's mean and venomous. No. I just think he has snake trick trick characteristics tricks snake trick characteristics
Character tricks character. I think that the realization that the pitch-black had 91 milligrams. Yeah too much pitch-black
I think I've had too much diarrhea
Caffeine before the episode and now it was it was sand I've been pretty loopy this whole time
I was having wet dryness coming out of me. Yeah, that's the work when your shit feels like sand. Yeah
It was full sand. I like to kneeling your shit
No, and it comes out feel it on your butt you feel it on your body when it comes out
I can not tell what my poop is going to look like when I poop it out, usually.
So you are not in tune with your body.
I like to look at it afterwards and today it looked like sand.
I would say around the age of 10 or 11 I realized.
It looked like sand in space.
I like to look at my poop after I go.
It looks like the beginning of Uncut Gems.
It looks like they could have used it to make 2001 A Space Odyssey.
- Those Pepto-Bismol shits are something else.
- Yeah, no, it's pretty nuts, yeah.
- They come out-- - It looks like nuts too.
- Yeah. (laughing)
Tommy Lee's nuts.
- It looks like anything you could say pretty much.
- It was a Rorschach.
- I took a shit that looked like anything.
- Yeah. (laughing)
It did look like a nebula.
- Yeah.
- Like if you inverted a photo of a nebula.
- I need to get you on my probiotic blend.
- I am going to get some.
I'm gonna get some pepyr on my walk home.
- I have some at home.
When I was on-- - You need yours.
- When I got my wisdom teeth out
and I was on the antibiotics,
my girlfriend got me probiotics.
- Your girlfriend got you pregnant?
- Yeah.
You're not even touching your mic.
You can't even, no one's gonna hear you.
- So?
- Okay, so we just found out what Patrick thinks
of both of us at once.
- My girlfriend got me probiotics while I was on antibiotics.
- Patrick literally doesn't wanna have both of us at once.
- How fucked is that?
Do you ever think about how insulting--
I would I would if I said any two guys I wanted to have sex with me at the same
time can you imagine let alone some of your best friends in the world I know
close your same damn time that's like most guys dream I know in our
friendship to at the same time I think so I think it would only make it better
no you could ruin our friendship if you had if one of us had one of us yes but
if all two of us went against all one of him then that might actually work out
- Yeah. - Went against.
- Yeah. - Yeah, it's like,
you know, I mean like-- - Like we go, we versus you.
- Yeah, we would verse you in the bedroom.
- Like we would tag team you-- - Can you imagine?
- Like we go after you. - Dude, can you imagine,
you and me, we get ready at our his and his sinks
in our mansion that's in Federal World.
- And then we turn to each other and we go,
hoo, hoo, hoo! - Yeah.
And then we open the door from the bathroom, right?
And you have one of those,
we have one of those beds that has the railings,
it has the like sheer sheet around it,
what is that called? - Yes, yeah.
- Whatever that is. - The four poster bed.
bed. And so we see just kind of a 60% silhouette of Patrick behind it wearing
lingerie. A negligee. Right yeah and he's turned the other way and he's kind of
like dancing whatever music we have on we have on some D'Angelo and he's kind of
enjoying it. It's like yeah it's swaying to the beat. It's fluid. We're like it looks like
smoke. Yeah. It's like smoke flowing through the room. And then he peeks his
fingers from one of the from the seam in the in the curtain. I see his fingers I come.
I see the tips of his fingers I can't help it I come and I leave.
And I push you out of the way, and then I do a full Olympic dive into your ass.
Or with my ass into your face.
A backwards dive.
That's not a thing.
A backwards dive would not be able to--
This guy knows what things are with sex. You're gay.
Backwards dive?
Shut up.
Patrick will be putting a trail of rose petals to the bed,
but he'd be trying to stall, so he'd be doing a really wiggly, long S-shape.
Yeah.
- It goes all the way around the room.
- You lead a bunch of rose petals,
and I follow them, and they lead straight to the bathroom,
and I walk in, you're taking a big, stinky, loud shit.
(laughing)
You're going, "Ow!"
And then you go flush.
- Yeah, it hurts 'cause I ate Burger King
or something around the day.
- How come it makes you hurt?
- Burger King.
- Burger King, it's because of the ingredients.
- It must be the ingredients.
- Chick-fil-A is introducing a plant-based--
- Cauliflower plant-based chicken at some locations.
- Yeah. - I do wanna try it.
- Yeah, where, San Francisco?
I didn't mean to say that. - They don't have
a Chick-fil-A in San Francisco.
- Yeah.
- You know, every time that they talk about the big one,
dude, I gotta watch a video today about the big one.
- About the big one?
The big one, what's the big one?
- The big one. - The Cascadia earthquake
that's coming.
- The big earthquake.
- There's like an earthquake that is literally going
to destroy the entire West Coast of America
and kill millions and millions of people.
- It'll get rid of LA? - And they know for a fact,
maybe, they know for a, a 200 foot tsunami wave
will hit the coast, and they know for a fact
that it's coming, they just don't know when.
So it could be in, could be today.
Could be when this episode comes out.
- I don't like thinking about stuff like that.
- See, that's why, luckily in New York City--
- There's also apparently a galactus
that will come and devour-- - No!
- Yeah. - A lot of the earth too.
And they know it's coming, but they don't know it.
- A big guy with a purple helmet?
- Yeah, and the antenna thing stays on the side.
- Fuck me! - So he can feel.
- Yeah. - That's gonna happen soon.
- Can't feel any emotion.
- We don't know if the silver surfer is involved as well.
Do you know what the-- - That fucking prick.
- The lamest thing about me is as a kid,
I thought the silver surfer was so fucking cool.
I was obsessed with him. - That's not lame.
That's far from the lamest thing about you.
- No, that's the lamest thing.
- That's a cool one to get into,
'cause no one knows anything about him.
- That's the worst thing you can be into
if you're a kid who's into comic books.
You're like, I wanna get the giant collection
of the Silver Surfer guys.
- I don't think that's the worst.
- He's the trophy guy.
He has no, it looks like shit.
- He's a Silver Surfer.
- Silver Surfer's like cool.
- I was like, Hulk is gay, Spider-Man sucks.
I wanna read about the Silver Surfer.
- Hulk actually has some pretty good storylines
that I think you would actually like to read.
- Hulk is so fucking gay.
- I'm gonna be real, man.
I just can't do--
- What about Planet Hulk?
- Gay.
- I just can't do comic books, man.
- Yeah, you didn't have like any like,
you didn't have like a childhood full of wonder.
- I liked Bone.
- Bone is the gayest comic book you can have.
- Yeah, that's the one.
- That's like by far the least.
- That is less cool than Silver Server.
- Yeah, that is the least cool comic book you can like.
- I liked Sandman Mysteries or whatever.
- What?
- Sandman Mysteries.
- I don't know.
- What was that?
- The only comic book I liked as a kid was--
- The Sandman?
The Neil Gaiman Sandman?
- No, not that one, it was a different one.
- Justice League.
- Justice League's gay.
All comic books are gay except the ones I like.
No, I didn't.
No, X-Men.
I liked Teen Titans and X-Men.
I pretty much hated nerds my entire life.
But I liked--
Me too.
But I did play a lot of Super Mario Galaxy,
and it would make me tear up when I went into the storybook
room.
OK.
So--
I never played that.
But it's actually hella much--
I really wanted to play Super Mario Galaxy.
I never had--
I hated the Wii.
Oh, man.
The Wii was fun as fuck.
until I hated the week I even I got raving rabbits I got I got my girlfriend
got her old Wii from her from her mom and then I was like oh we could play Super
Mario Galaxy and then she just played cooking mama and singing-songing that's
why that's when you got that's what you know you got to do you got to put on
that Wiimote you got to put on that nunchuck you just got beat her up I
I didn't realize you were there. I literally I just got the back elbow.
I only use the Wii. Just doing anything with the nunchucks in your hand.
Oh no, I was just playing a game. I literally only use the Wii.
Yeah, just the TV is on, you're watching the news.
Oh, I thought it was playing. I thought this was News Hero.
Yeah. There's been a giant earthquake.
When you hold the News Hero, you just hold the Wii remote like a microphone and you just say like.
like there's a horrible rapist on the loose yeah yeah it's like that's the
little thing that they do on the guitar
It's like in Wii bowling when you accidentally throw the bowling ball backwards and they all like jump.
A giant Tsunardi, oh fuck.
God damn it.
Has hit Japoon.
76% try again.
There's like a screen of just like your boss at the news.
He's just going like.
It's also like you can do the same news reports on different levels of
difficulty. Yeah. And it's like... On the fast news. Yeah.
Oh my god, it adds more details. Yeah, more gruesome details.
Yeah, exactly. Easy is like, "A man died today." And then Expert is like, "15 people were killed in a
horrible car crash." Yeah. Their guts were split open by...
so funny though like an actual news story where like the anchor is just going into this complete
vivid detail.
Yeah.
This guy in front of a house is like the people in the home were completely stripped of all
of their skin and they just described, I've never seen the news describe the whole murder.
You always want him to say like experts are wondering what was in the killer's head but
but he was probably thinking that he was going to feel so amazing killing all these people,
seeing blood fly everywhere and feeling like God.
You know what I want to see?
I want to see them, they're reading off the teleprompter and he's going like, "15 people
were slaughtered by a serial killer when..."
Dear God, do I really have to read this?
Yes.
Okay.
That happened in a movie.
He killed them.
That happened in a movie, right?
Did it happen in a movie?
You know what I realized too?
Anchorman probably.
I guess being a news anchor is just playing news here because you're reading off the teleprompter
and you're like, "Oh, I'm going to kill them."
Anchorman being a news anchor is just playing news here because you're reading off a teleprompter. Yeah, yeah
That's that's be our news here could have some like teleprompter hero is a great idea
That is a really don't just have to do news you could be a State of the Union and yeah
Oh my god do one whenever there's an L. You could do SNL you they do a sheriff you do a sheriff briefing
They have card mode after some police killing card. Oh my god teleprompter hero is
There's a teleprompter that we could have and I bet it would be work with AI
- With new technology, it could be used to generate
detection of your voice.
- Mother of God.
- You might be able to use artificial intelligence.
Yeah, I think that's a, you know,
we might be a little bit late,
'cause I think the Wii has not been made for about 15 years.
- They didn't stop making games for the Wii
until like 2018. - We could still release it
for the Wii.
Everybody still has a,
the Wii is not a console that anybody sold.
- Oh, we do. - Nobody was like,
nobody listed their Wii on eBay or anything.
Everybody put it in their top shelf in their closet.
- Everybody has a Wii somewhere.
Next to like a camping chair.
- Yeah, exactly.
- I have a Wii in my living room.
- Literally everybody has a Wii.
- I guess you're right, I think I have a Wii.
- I think we have two Wiis.
- I don't remember where it's from either.
- Mine is modded though.
I did some nerd ass shit on it.
- Please tell me you did.
- Our game will not be allowed to be played on.
- What is this?
- Okay, so we have a, all right, here.
- All right, here, and put this on so people, yeah.
- Okay, so it's going.
- Whopper, whopper, whopper.
- No, okay, you just failed.
Okay, let me try, let me try.
left bracket verse one right bracket.
(laughing)
Whopper Whopper.
- Oh, this is the Burger King commercial.
- You just read it.
Junior Double Triple
Whopper.
(laughing)
Flame Grilled Taste with
- Blank line.
perfect toppers.
Black line.
I rule this day.
Said that a little early.
Yeah, that was too early.
It's a little too early.
Yeah, there's no--
There's mayo.
That was also too early.
There's no scoring system for him.
That's why we need to program the game.
Yeah.
Catch up.
Yeah, now do that.
Now do both of those.
It's OK if I--
fuck, this is hard.
Yeah, this one's hard.
Impossible or bacon.
- Whopper. - Whopper.
- See, this would be such a good challenge mode.
- Any whopper my way. - Intellipopter hero.
Okay. - Refrain.
- Refrain.
You rule your sizes your way.
- Okay, what did I get?
Give me a grade.
- I think you were doing really well.
Well, first you were an A, not an A+.
- 63. - Because you said a few lines
too early and you didn't correct
even after you were told it's too early.
- So great but not perfect.
- But then, once we got into the challenge mode,
I think that tanked your score,
and I think you're down to a B.
- But shouldn't I have been able to use
some kind of like star power, like in Guitar Hero?
- I said you didn't use it.
- I could've, but I didn't know that I had the feature.
I could've made all the letters go blue.
- You go like this, you go like this.
- Okay. - To activate it.
- Like that? - Yeah.
- Okay. - Okay, now you got an A.
- Woo!
- Congrats.
- That's a pretty fun game.
I would love to design a video game about my own life.
- Yeah? - I would call it like,
Suburbia.
- Damn.
- And here's what it would be, right?
- It would be, okay, tell me it's not gonna be
a Final Fantasy style JRPG with combat
and you fight dogs and cats and things around the suburbia.
- No, it is an alien. - Does an alien come through?
- It is a movement shooter where you run through the church
that I went to as a kid.
(laughing)
- Yeah, Myrtle Grove Baptist.
- Man, it is so lucky that I wasn't smart enough
to know how to make, how to 3D model a level
for like a shooter or something,
'cause I would have made my school.
- Oh yeah, yeah.
- It's the only thing that you know.
- That's everyone, everyone's somebody like.
- Yeah, Gary's mom.
- It's one of those things you just don't,
yeah, you can't, there's no,
your brain just can't process why you shouldn't do that.
There's no, there's no.
- Oh, I could make my school and walk up to the shelves
and go, oh look.
- Yeah, even if you're not doing it.
- Yeah, exactly.
- If you're not doing it for nefarious purposes,
you're still, the first thing you're gonna make,
if you know how to make a level, like, is your school.
- Yeah.
- Even if like, if you're like, oh yeah,
Made my school in a first-person shooter.
Oh shit!
I didn't mean to do that.
I still know the school layout like perfectly.
I can remember everything about the school.
They rebuilt, yeah, they tore down my high school and made a giant one.
But you still have the remembery.
Yeah.
Of the old one.
I wanted to play Counter-Strike in my school.
That was the game I wanted to do the type of level.
For some reason.
Learn some flash lineups for your school.
They built, I think it was probably because of all the damn shootings, but they built
like midway through my junior year, they built like a, one of those fucking...
Bulletproof glass around the teacher.
They built like a containment thing, you have to go in and tell a lady, "Oh, yeah, I'm late
today."
It was like a cube.
Oh yeah, they kept our front doors locked and our front desk.
They did an airlock?
Yeah.
Whoa.
They put an airlock in my school.
Ours they said you can't, they locked all the doors
and you had to talk to the person at the front desk
when you go in but nobody ever did it
and they never locked the doors.
And everyone went inside and outside.
- So basically the security was lacking.
- They didn't even fucking care.
- I used to leave the building
and I would go into the woods and smoke cigarettes.
- Yeah, leaving the building during school
was so fire, dude.
- That was amazing.
I loved walking across the street.
- You never went into the building.
- You never did.
- I went to school for a bit.
- You did not go for long enough.
- I went to school.
- We're talking about leaving the building in high school.
- I took a class at the access center
that was on the school's campus.
I took TV production in high school.
- Little did you know that I actually went
to a fucking classical education co-op.
- You did not go to a classical education co-op.
- I did have a class once a week in a building
and I would leave.
- It was co-op 'cause you would have to--
- Chinese food from a very, very sad, sad woman.
- Do you know what the crazy, one time--
- And one time she made me so sad
that I just never went there again.
- One time I went into-- - Why, what'd she do?
I can't get into it.
- Okay.
- One time I went into my high school--
- More so than I did.
- Like in the evening, like at night.
I think I left something there,
so I can't remember why I was in there.
- It's a fucking liminal space.
- No, it wasn't.
What it was, was it had transformed
into a full Chinese school.
- Whoa.
- And there was dozens and dozens of Chinese people
and they're taking Chinese classes.
And it was a full, it fully transformed--
- They weren't taking Chinese classes.
- The class were in Chinese, so they're Chinese classes.
- Yeah, but not every class is an English class.
- Well, a math class in English, I would say.
- Yeah, they're not gonna call it Chinese gym.
- I didn't know what the subject was
'cause it was in Chinese.
- They're not gonna call it Chinese gym.
He's the teacher.
- But it had fully transformed.
It was a different school at night,
and it was a Chinese school at night.
- Oh, 'cause they're still on China time.
- Yeah, that's probably what it was.
- They haven't adjusted.
They're jet lagged.
- Yeah, but it felt like, yeah, that is--
That's you ever did you was your town but no cuz you could walk places you also could probably walk places
Sometimes you just stay after school
And like kids would just hang out there on the same on the on the campus you to hang out in the library just because it
Was like well, there's nothing else to do in this fucking town. Yeah, you can do that do that until you're like 17
Yeah, you guys both lived in like I went to places that had a bus
Yeah, we do have a wave bus and we didn't have a I think there's no you've been to my hometown
there's no sidewalks.
- Yeah.
- There's sidewalks for like a stretch of the road,
that's only so you can walk from one school
to another school.
- It's funny that you're from such a rural place
'cause you became such a city poke.
- Mm-hmm, 'cause I knew that I was supposed to go
to New York and fall asleep on the floor of a bar.
- Did God tell you that?
- God told me that.
- I got big plans for you, Patrick.
- You're gonna drink five Negronis one night
and fall asleep on one six nine bar's floor.
that's what's gonna happen for you.
- 'Cause you'll be an amazing metropolitan guy.
- More like metrosexual.
- An amazing fake bisexual in New York City.
That is the dream that I have for you, me God.
That's what you're going to do.
- Yeah, you're sitting in your bedroom
and you're looking out the window--
- Dear God.
- And you're praying at a start, please God,
let me move to New York and start a podcast.
- I need to be a Brooklyn podcaster, God.
Yep. My New Hampshire accent. And then your dad. Meanwhile I was toiling. Yeah. I had
to, yeah, meanwhile, yeah, you've made out of sidewalks, I had sidewalks, I had to walk
a mile to school every day, uphill when I was walking home and downhill when I was walking
there. I tried to walk home from school one time and I got halfway, I got right where
the sidewalk ended. Shel Silverstein. Shel Silverstein. Yeah, yeah. I got right there.
You, you know that, that spot in my town that had that cannon? No. I will not play at Tug
War I'd rather play it a hug a war yeah over Stan I thought you came up with that
on the spot and I thought that was so beautiful remember the one where he's
like the me who and the exactly what yeah I remember that motherfucker they got a
TV head they got him on the back of that book yep I remember I when I was like
when I get older I want to look exactly like Joe Silverstein yeah you're on your
way I think so yeah I think it really dissed him in Diary of a Wimpy Kid yeah
That's my dog yeah
Keep shells name out of your fucking mouth exactly Greg Hefley. Yeah, you're
Great you know for a fact that Greg Hefley grew up and became a fuckboy. Yep. He what probably was a fuck
I a womanizer. He did treat women strangely also
How many fuck did how many fucking?
Years is this kid gonna go to school. Yeah, he's been to school 20 years diarrhea of a wimpy kid
That's good
Diarrhea of a stuff the stinky kid stinky shit
The stinky kid in school diarrhea of one time the stinky kid diarrhea is a stinky my
the stinky kid my TV production class
big red book diarrhea is
Still has the fake notebook inside lots of drawings
Yeah, the stinky kid my TV production class breathed into my nose one time and I was through
Brushes, I need breathing you know he was teaching me how to
Breathe no yeah, he's teaching is doing breath lessons
So he's teaching me how to like do something in Adobe Premiere, and then he just like turned me in like yeah
Sure, you're supposed to and I just went like straight green line sponge
The stinky kid in my class
So bad pull up the the author of a diary of a wimpy kids Twitter. He smelled like mowed grass
What's he doing these days? He you'll see really is he doing fucking NFTs? No, what's his name?
Jeff Kinney Jeff search Jeff Kinney Twitter
Oh my god, I'm so fucking on
So fucking black
He likes to if you scroll here, I think I don't know if he's done it so recently
but I have so many questions he he for a while I checked his Twitter I forget how
I saw his Twitter but I saw it for some reason and he was doing a thing where
he was posting drawings of his pages that he was working on for the next book
and he was saying what do you guys think they should say next and stuff like that
and I think that maybe we could really right now get a good submission in and
get something into the next I ever would be kidding I would love it seems like
maybe he hasn't done that in a minute so maybe I completely whoa he's got murder
He honestly you talk was our ash, but he seems chill. I just I didn't talk any trash
I just wanted I was opening it for the contest kind of talking. Whoa you see that on Jeff Kinney
Did he's kind of cool man, I don't know I kind of fuck with him I
Don't like that. I think that I was more into the
Generation I loved captain
Fuck yeah that probably still hold that yeah, cuz that was about pee and poop
You know a lot of this stuff was about relationship with your brother, man. Yeah, I'm funny about that
There was a few things funny. No no no no no no your brother's is no
Can you imagine being Jeff Kenny's older brother? He probably beat him up. I know I'm at his whole family is probably fucking rude
You know that Greg Hefley is seriously. It's a
Self insert yeah, it's a huge self insert
Yeah, and he probably Roderick is gonna come out and say like it didn't go down like that
I want to hear Roderick side of the fucking story. Basically. There was no loaded diaper
It was never had a van my band was not called loaded
You're gonna hear Hurley come out or whatever his name was Rowley Rowley come out. Did you say I was not a square
Human I did not have too big front teeth. No, I know I did not frankly come out and be like indubitably
He'll be the same
He'll be exactly the same yeah, they're right yeah, he's completely right. I'm a fucking
Nerd and I'm actually wimpier. Yeah, I'm actually even more of a dork in real life. Yeah, we we had like
Fuck I can't leave you wrote that as a name and he's like yep, frankly. Yeah there. There was this one author
There's this author that came to our school kind of in the same vein Gordon Korman
And it was like clear that he was just doing that's he was doing a book tour
No, it's clear that like they the school brought him here for the brought him there for a specific reason
But it was clear that he just was like I'm pretty much only here to talk about
Because they kept asking us that they were like you have to think it was like an assignment
You have to think of three questions to ask him. You had celebrities come to your school. We had that guy.
I don't remember but you've told me that people have come to your school. We had so many.
We had so many. Somebody from my my brother's graduating class is on a Netflix show.
No, but you told me that there was like you guys had like Dare come to your school.
We had the Tiger. We had a bunch of anti-drug and like yeah an anti like
homophobia stuff.
- My high school was called the Heroin High.
- You had anti-homophobia stuff?
- Yeah, there were people--
- They had pro-homophobia stuff.
- We had pro-homophobia stuff in New Hampshire
and North Carolina, yeah.
We had an abstinence-only sex education.
- Yeah, I mean, we had that too.
- Really?
- Yeah, maybe like once or twice we had an assembly
that was like, "Gay kids kill themselves,
"so you shouldn't make fun of them."
- We had the anti-bullying shit.
- Ours was "Gay kids kill themselves."
- Yeah. (laughing)
- Okay.
- You know when the anti-drug speaker comes in
and he does, I feel like they all come in
and they're always like, you know,
I was addicted to cocaine in my 20s
and it made me powerful, it made me strong,
and I won every sport I ever played,
and I was a genius, but also, I hated it.
Also, holy shit.
- At one point, it got too expensive
and I had to stop doing it.
- I think that if I was a dare person,
I feel like the best thing to do is go up
and use every single drug that you're talking about on stage
so that people can actually see you.
- Yeah, they see what it actually does.
- And put you in a cage like King Kong, right?
- Yeah.
- And so you do, you smoke weed,
and then you sit there and you get scared
about a YouTube video, and then you do ketamine.
- I was so, were you guys--
- And then you get stuck in a chair.
- So fucking excited to get a turn
to try on the beer goggles from Dare.
Did they bring in beer goggles for you?
- Oh, no, I didn't have that.
- I had it on.
- Really?
They brought, for when Dare came into our class
in fifth grade, the officer, it was a police officer,
dare guy and he had like beer goggles and he's like now everyone get in line like
yeah when you wear these goggles it's like you're drunk do you remember saying
in line be like holy all my friends what is this going to be like all my friends
were already like drinking and shit though so when they did do that it was
like in fifth grade no and I did it in drivers ed when I was 14 and I had a
fire joke I put it on I said damn I want to call my ex-girlfriend that's good
We're like this kid is too funny
And then the other the one other kid is saying the back who also goes on reddit was yeah wanted to kill you
Yeah, they put he was looking at his hand either. Fuck. Fuck. They put me in a clown car after that
Plans to be the class
Yeah, dude, I pretty much fucking owned them. Yeah, and then he put someone who's like, uh, I wanted to fuck my family
I wanted
Kill somebody
Kill my ex-girlfriend. Yeah. No, no
Oh my god, it's interacting with my medication
Just I'm just gonna wear him once there's gonna wear one more time it's but I'm fine now
I'm okay, but I'm on it right right a great American novel. Yeah
Oh that it's immediately at a typewriter the Gordon Corman thing he came to the school and
Wanted us that we had to like ask him questions about the book and then he like
He was there to teach us about anti-bullying and he was like yeah, there's some bullying in my book
Like he bullied people no no he was just saying like yeah, you know like the main character like overcomes bullying
Yeah, whatever, but I mostly I'm here to talk to young writers
Like I remember like all my teachers coming back from that assembly just being like yeah, well we paid fucking
Well none of them are ever
Expensive it was like they it was like every single teacher was
Disappointed when that guy was do you know what that you know what the the the fire one was the best the best?
Coming into school guy the animals guy. Oh
- Owls? - After school,
he brought in snakes, he brought in baby alligators,
brought in turtles, chinchillas.
- He brought in owls and we got to dissect
an owl pellet after.
- Oh yeah, I remember dissecting owl pellets, dude.
- We just went to the serpentarium, he didn't come to us.
'Cause it was like, if you have that in your town,
you go to that.
- Yeah, it's a way cooler.
- We were supposed to go to the Autobahn Society thing
and then I skipped that field trip.
- Yeah, that shit is stupid.
- What is an Autobahn Society?
- That's like a nature preservation.
- Yeah.
- Oh, like, is that what 4-H is?
Skipped that field trip because my mom said it my mom said I could skip that
Because she was worried about me getting like triple e from a tick
Really, I'm really scary. Yeah, my friend growing up had it when he was a kid
That's one of those things you just have to pretend that it doesn't exist cuz I have it. Yeah, fuck
Was it triple encephalitis?
Something encephalitis. Yeah, I don't know
Yeah
It's just a disease that some mosquitoes can give you that if you get it you just die my mom and there's just that's my my
- My friend's Ian, when I was like six years old,
my friend Ian had it, my mom like found that out.
- Yeah, Ian, it's D-Ian.
- Okay, my friend Ian had triple E.
- Triple E. - He got triple E,
and then like--
- He died?
- No, but my mom told me about triple E.
She's like, "Yeah, I didn't know,
"your friend's mom was telling me that he had triple E,
"and he got it from a mosquito."
And the way that my mom told me it
made me think that he was special needs.
So then the next time I hung out with him I was just kind of everything
he said. I was like 6 years old, I didn't know. I was just like, "Yeah!"
I didn't know about Triple H, I was really scared of Triple H though, getting a chair smashed over the top of my head.
Yeah, I was scared of Triple X, I didn't want my mom to see.
Yeah, definitely.
I thought Vin Diesel was gonna come to my house on a motorcycle.
Yeah, I was gonna hear "DuHast" in a big room.
That would actually be cool.
- Okay guys, let's end with another teleprompter game.
Cameron, I think it's actually, Pat,
well either, who wants to go?
We could have a teleprompter off,
you know, go paragraph.
- We could switch every line.
- Yeah, let's go every line.
- Every, okay.
- Dueling, kind of like a target versus,
all right, go guys, go.
- Two year old William Long laughed it off.
- I bought a press conference on Thursday,
but he and his family weren't so joyous.
Two months ago, if you asked me how,
place as I am right now,
why aren't you reading your lines, said mom.
- That's because--
- You're reading the wrong ones.
- Surgery.
- No, you read this one.
William was born at the height of the pandemic in 2021.
He was just 8 months old.
He and his parents.
He was high fever then suffered a seizure.
Was a result of the virus.
You're so bad at this.
His parents rushed him to starting a chain of events that
saved his life because he had a seizure with some double.
You were you okay.
All right, here we go.
I'm going to say for Cameron, honestly, 88% thank you.
Pretty good, especially that was an expert difficulty.
It was tough.
Yeah, that was an expert.
I don't you get a 13 unlucky 13.
That was so fucking embarrassing.
I'll try again.
Okay, ready?
- Shareholder meeting, nope.
(laughing)
Nope.
- Shareholder meeting Friday the 17th.
I hope to see you all there.
- What did I get on that?
- Five PM.
- Play it again, play it again.
- And guys, we have some more exciting stuff
coming down the pipeline.
We were just talking about it.
I hope you're into--
- Fetter World.
- Fetter World, I hope you're into fucking drinking beers.
You know, that's all I'll say about that.
- I hope you like, I guess, how can I not give this away?
- Nikoi.
- I hope you like geometric figures.
- Yes.
- And dragons.
(laughing)
- Okay, bye everybody. - Bye.