(upbeat music)
- And away we go.
- For another legendary installment of Podcasts About Love.
- That's right.
- This time with a twist.
- We're all talking low voices.
- This time with a low twist.
- This time we're all gonna mumble and murmur.
- I do think that.
- It's called mumblecore podcast.
It's a mobile core podcast.
And it's different from movies,
'cause movies, mobile core is different.
Nobody, you know, I'm sorry.
You have to keep your voice down today.
You sound like Buffalo Bill.
Patrick sounds a lot like Buffalo Bill.
You have to keep your voice down today
or else it gets the hose again.
Well, now he really does,
'cause he said one of the lines from--
Reference Thursday, y'all.
I said that it's Reference Thursday.
It is not Reference Thursday, all right?
- It is not Reference Thursday.
- That's no moon.
- Wait, what's that from?
- I don't know.
- Star Wars.
- Oh shit.
- Say any reference, I bet I'd get it.
(laughing)
- Okay, I like this game.
- Okay, yeah, here we go.
- I like this game.
- By God!
- Britain.
- Fuck.
(laughing)
- England.
- Fuck, now I'm trying to think of one
that will really stump him.
- I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready.
- Die, die, die, die. - SpongeBob.
- Aye, aye, aye, aye.
- SpongeBob.
- I thought you wouldn't expect two SpongeBobs in a row.
- Squidward from SpongeBob.
- Three, you really, you guessed three in a row?
That's like, how did we not fool him with the third one?
You know?
- I know.
- Ar, ar, ar, SpongeBob me boy.
- Plankton's enemy.
- You said Plankton.
- You did say Plankton.
- You're destroyed.
- Yeah, Plankton's enemy.
- No, okay, okay.
- Ar, ar, ar, and you thought it was Plankton.
- All right, Plankton's enemy, Cribs.
- All right.
- Reference Thursday.
- I was gonna say, another reference
that we can trick you with.
- Okay, trick me?
- Yeah.
- Stump the reference head.
- No, this is Patrick.
- Me, that's my, be on the phone.
- We got him.
- Be on the phone with my nephew.
'Cause he calls me, ever since he learned that,
he calls me every day and says that.
- Every day?
- No, pretty much, there was a week
where he called me every day and said that.
- He said, he would call you and say, no, this is Patrick?
- He would say, is this the Krusty Krab?
- And you would say what?
- I would just hang up the phone on him.
- Dude, the way that you describe having a nephew
makes it sound so terrible.
- Yeah.
- It's just a huge emotional burden.
- It's not even your son.
You can't even-- - You don't even get the reward.
- You wouldn't even be able to handle it.
- You have to be, to somebody,
there's somebody in the world, a child,
that you have to be as an uncle,
you have to be the number one coolest guy
in their entire life.
- Yeah.
- Until they're like seven years old.
- I have the cheat code though,
you just move away really far.
- I have the cheat code,
'cause it's what I do to my little nephews.
- You don't have a nephew.
- I'd have them by marriage.
- No.
- Yeah, I do, so.
- No, you don't.
That would be your cousin.
- And they don't like me.
- That would be your cousins,
and your cousins don't like you.
- They don't like me, they don't know my name.
- Probably 'cause they--
- They don't know your name.
- Probably 'cause you hit them with BB guns.
- My nephews don't really know my name.
- Don't really or they don't?
- They sometimes--
- They don't exist, how are they gonna know his name?
- Well, I say don't really because I took the average,
but there's three of 'em.
Or no, there's two of 'em,
and one doesn't know my name, and one--
- No, there's three. - He's making it up as he goes.
- No, there is three, and a niece,
but one of them doesn't know my name.
- New details to the story of the compulsive liar.
- You are behaving like--
- See, and I don't remember even how many of them there are.
- That's true, I guess you wouldn't admit
you were unsure if you were lying.
- Yeah, why would they know my name?
- 'Cause they don't exist.
- They do exist. - They don't exist.
Cameron, look at me, they don't exist.
- Okay.
- My Uncle Michael was pretty cool to me growing up.
- That's not your nephew, though.
- That's your Uncle Michael.
- I didn't say that was my nephew.
My Uncle Michael, he has a dope ass scar on his neck
because of cancer.
And he looks amazing.
- I've seen a few guys with scars
over the past few months on the street.
- Have you been hanging out in lion's dens?
- What's, oh no.
- No, what's that?
- That one right there.
- Yeah, I haven't seen that one.
- I cannot believe that you still have that scar.
- I've seen a lot of guys with scars on their faces and necks.
- Scary.
- Isn't that cool and crazy?
- Biker status.
- And it's, you wanna look at them.
- Well you've been hanging out at the veterans hall.
- You're too afraid to look at them.
- Speaking of afraid, I'm gonna crack this open, sorry.
I'm gonna crack open my psychedelic water.
Oh, it's squirted.
- It's squirted onto the table.
- Okay, so this has something in it.
This struck my attention and caught my eye at the--
- And I'm seeing the price tag on it.
- I know the tag.
- And it says Urban Outfitters.
(laughing)
- I noticed that too.
- Urban Outfitters, $6, oh that's Canadian.
- I did not buy this from an Urban Outfitters.
So whoever got this at the deli, they got it from, it didn't sell at an Urban Outfitters,
so they shipped it off to Organic R Us on Myrtle Avenue, and I grabbed this there. And this
is the Prickly Pear flavor, and I saw a lot of reviews for this. I looked them up.
So what is it?
You looked up reviews before picking it up and drinking it?
Yeah, I always watch a review before I listen to an album. Not the true drink reviewer.
Well, the taste doesn't matter because I'm trying to go on a trip.
No, you go completely blind into something.
Okay, but what is it though? Is it...
It's kava, which I've never had before.
What's that?
Kava is some kind of... It's like kratom, kind of.
It's like kratom, but in liquid.
Oh.
Yeah, that does not taste very good.
I'm not gonna...
It tastes like...
I'm already really hungover.
It tastes like toothpaste. Well, I think that this might...
Ooh, now I want to taste it.
I think this might help.
(laughter)
Now I want some.
I want some.
- Well, here's a warning.
- Okay.
- This product is not for children,
pregnant or nursing women,
or persons sensitive to caffeine.
US FDA advises that a potential risk
of rare but severe liver injury
may be associated with kava-containing dietary supplements.
- Wow.
- A liver injury?
Please do not operate heavy equipment
after using psychedelic water.
- Yeah, you gotta put that microphone down
for the rest of the episode.
- This is not heavy.
Maybe to a wimp or an ant.
You are a wimp.
No.
You're drinking a shiny can.
The can is pretty.
Wait.
Holy shit.
Made in USA with globally sourced ingredients and rituals.
Rituals?
They use a ritual on this.
OK.
That's not OK.
I think it's like a ritualistic thing.
What does that mean?
That means you drink it with two of your buddies on a podcast.
There are kava bars, which I didn't really--
There's one next to my old apartment.
- I learned though. - Is it a seed or a leaf
or a mushroom or a root? - It's a root, I believe.
I believe it's a root that,
right now it makes my tongue taste bad.
- There's two kava bars next to my old apartment.
- They have a full bar?
I've never heard of this thing - And I wonder if I'm a gentrifier.
- And now they're making a whole industry out of it.
- Yeah. - They're trying to do it
behind my back.
- Well, it's for people who are addicted to beer.
- Oh, okay. - Is that true?
- Yeah, it's kinda like beer, but for,
it's like Kratom for beer. - I thought that was
what water was for. - No.
- Wait, I thought that this is gonna make me
Fucking go crazy and kill somebody. Oh, oh fuck this man. It's like kratom for beer
I'm gonna polish it off. Okay, cuz what's the worst I get out of that can looks polished enough look at that sheen
It does look it looks like a holographic trading card. Yeah
I think you could probably fetch a lot of money with that at a comic book store if you
Just watch catch me if you can that's such a good movie
I would do this to young Leonardo DiCaprio's penis.
I would make it look this shiny.
Oh, from greasing it?
Yeah.
He's 16 in that movie.
Shut up.
He's 16.
That's a little taste of his own medicine.
I don't know if you guys are going to see what he's been up to.
He said he's going to polish a 16-year-old boy's penis.
That's right.
It would be a little, that's what I'd say.
Yeah.
So hey, little Leo.
You're going to do some stuff in the future.
I'm going to do this to your cock.
- We go back in time and cause him to date a 16 year old.
- No, if I could go teach him a lesson,
I would bring him, I'm not gonna molest him, first of all.
- You said that.
- You said you would molest a 16 year old boy.
- That is not what I said at all.
- That's what you said you would molest a 16 year old.
- You're fucking tripping off that shit,
'cause you said that.
- Am I crazy?
Am I losing my mind off of Kavah?
Yeah, I just thought about, you know the guy,
What's the name of the guy from Vice that does drugs?
- Hamilton's Pharmacopia.
- Yeah, that guy probably would call it Kvah.
- That's not his last name.
His last name isn't Pharmacopia.
(laughing)
- No, he was not 16 in Catch Me If You Can.
That's not a fuckin' 32 year old movie.
- That's 32 years old.
- He was 31.
- You caught me 'cause he could.
- Scroll down, it says he was 21 at the time of filming.
time of filming?
Twenty-eight.
But the other...
So I think basically what we can take
from this is there's no...
Nobody knows.
He's fucking older than I am, man.
That's true.
Wait, you blew my mind with that.
Damn.
I thought we were all the same age as
him.
No, as of the movies that he's in.
But I would basically do...
His cock would look very,
very...
Spit shine it, you know, you could see
your own reflection in it, you know,
like a Maserati.
Yeah.
Why would you do that though?
Why would I suck his cock and fucking blend it with my butt?
Yeah.
Just for a laugh.
His attractiveness or...
Yeah, his attractiveness. He looks so hot in that movie. Look at him.
Frank Abagnale Jr.
He said he wants to have sex with a 16 year old Leonardo DiCaprio.
He's not 16, man!
He said it.
I didn't...
He said it. It's on the record.
It is on the record.
We don't mind.
He wants to polish that thing off.
If you want to polish a 16 year old Leo's pole, we're not going to be mad at you.
That's for I say yes or no to that. Will you Juvia? Will you please look up a picture of 16 year old Leonardo DiCaprio?
You want him and what's eating Gilbert grape don't you let me just see I just have to look
Just to see oh no he looks like a fucking dork
He looks like shit, I wouldn't fucking suck kids
That's terrible. I definitely tell you what if I did it wouldn't be this good. It wouldn't look like this
No, yeah, I'd turn all blank if I did it like OJ
No listen
He was a late bloomer right by the time. I was 16. I looked like fucking I looked amazing
God, I looked so good at 16
So I just basically polished off my kava drink
Okay, hold on sorry. I'm treating you so poorly so curious about it. I know it's something so poorly camera today guys
I think I'm entering into a psychedelic state yeah
spiders spiders spiders blah blah bleep bleep bleep guys are gonna have a bad trip
We're gonna trip off soda though, but yeah the world isn't floating around in space
It isn't you're breathing manually now, and you're blinking
That's me breathing manually. That's how good I am at breathing. Mm-hmm. I'm stick shifting and I'm dry
Statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration
I don't give a fuck about what the Food and Drug Administration
They're wrong most of the time food and drug administration is blocking the cure for cancer
Yeah, that's what I've heard too that I heard a face
Yeah
There's a food that cures cancer that they've been saying you can only it's peach pits you have to put nutrition facts on this food
Or you can't release it. Uh-huh. Am I gonna spit its peach if they eat 16 peach bits 16 peach pits
Uh-huh guys am I gonna be like this forever yeah, this is you were gonna be like this for the rest of your life
I will say which is gonna be short cuz you're going to die I
Honestly, I've already I'm having an ego death, and I'm in right in the middle of you're gonna
Have a real death because you drink too much of that. There's no difference between any
OD'd on this and I'm not even my
Don't touch them like that that was realistic AF
I'm still at home on my phone in my bed.
Me too.
I have five hours of screen time.
That's what we did right before we started recording.
We found out it's about 12.30, 12.45.
It was 12.30.
It was 12.30 and at 12.30 he said that he woke up at 7 and we looked at his screen time on his phone
and he had been on his phone for five and a half hours.
I was watching a lot of videos.
I'm so hungover, it's the only thing that you can do when you're hungover.
I'm also usually trying to train my brain.
I did not drink at all.
That's COVID, bud.
No, I had too much fun.
That's what I've been saying.
You can't overdose on fun.
You cannot overdose on fun.
I didn't overdose on fun because I'd be fucking dead.
You don't just instinctively die when you overdose.
You guys would throw me in a fucking dumpster if I overdosed.
You would leave me for dead.
We would.
- Why? 'Cause you're too tall.
- You would see drool spitting out of the corner of my mouth.
You would see a party hat on my head
and a blower in my mouth.
- A blower?
- And you'd throw me the shredder.
- You would put a gun in your mouth?
- Yeah, and you wouldn't care.
- Guys.
- I would fucking care if you put a gun in your mouth.
- No.
- Guys, I have bad news.
- It's expired?
- I ate the brown acid.
- It's expired.
- It's expired by how much?
- That means it's not gonna do it.
It means you're gonna throw up maybe.
- Don't put that into my brain right now, dude.
- You're gonna throw up from it.
- No, dude, I'm high. - Yeah, your stomach
might start gurgling.
- I'm hot.
I got cotton mouth like a motherfucker.
- Oh, shit.
(laughing)
You should have picked up some Doritos.
- I really shouldn't have.
I should have picked up 14 more of these
'cause I think I have a permanent addiction.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, and I can barely even speak right now
because you guys are both turning
into giant fucking versions of my parents.
- No. - Clean your room!
- No.
- That's what your mom sounds like.
- Clean your room now!
- She does sound a little bit like that.
Caleb right now is having an acid fucking realization
that he does.
He's having acid flashbacks.
He's having, what's it called when you realize,
epiphany, that he doesn't have to clean his room
when his parents say so.
I would love to have an acid flashback.
He's in space.
Every time I've done acid I've just watched movies.
I've just watched, I watched Awesome Powers
and then I watched the SpongeBob movie.
So if I had an acid flashback I'd probably just laugh.
We watch Goldmember.
I do, I keep having TV flashbacks.
Or I watch an episode of TV and a few weeks later
I remember a moment from it.
- And it hits you like a freight train.
- If it's a funny moment, I'll giggle.
- I had an acid flashback that I used to work
at a pizza place and then my dog waited for me
outside of the pizza place for 1,000 years.
- Dumbass dog.
- Yeah.
- That was an acid flashback I had.
- Damn.
- And Zoidberg was there.
- Zoidberg was there?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I've had a lot of, I had an acid flashback
about Mr. Burns, he got fucking shot
and I'm trying to figure it out.
- Whoa.
We'll just wait for your next flashback to find out who did it.
I have a feeling it's going to be a big surprise.
Whoever it is.
Whatever adult did it.
If only I could have fucking bet on that shit.
Dude, I, oh my god.
Do you ever have, I just had.
Back in the day.
Bet, bet, bet, bet, bet, bet, bet, bet, bet, bet, bet.
Did people bet on who shot Mr. Burns?
Yeah.
They did?
Yeah, definitely.
DraftKings.
Yeah.
This is, this is.
That's DraftKings first big game.
Pull up the odds.
They had, they had, I saw the odds of it.
- Homer was a favorite with two to one odds.
Who the fuck would bet Homer, bro?
- Here it is.
- Whoa. - This is in the Mirage?
- Damn.
- Did they even have-- - That's what I'm saying,
dude, imagine if I was fucking here to bet--
- Oh my God, yeah. - 70 to one?
- Maggie was 70 to one, bro.
- Imagine if I was back then and I also knew who did it
and I betted.
- That would be so cool to go back in time to bet on this
and then not stop 9/11.
(laughing)
- What am I gonna do?
- Yeah, what are you talking about?
- There's nothing I could've done.
- You go back in time to bet on the Simpsons thing.
- Okay, so you can't, you don't warn anybody,
you're like, hey, 9/11's gonna happen.
- Yeah, you know what, yeah, that's a good thing.
Go back in time and say, hey guys, so you know,
two planes are gonna hit some towers and blow up
and then put you in jail.
- Yeah, exactly, yeah.
- The only thing that you're gonna,
people are gonna be like, you're crazy,
and then when it happens, you're going to prison
for the rest of your life, and all of a sudden,
you're Osama bin Laden and Barack Obama's saying,
we killed Patrick Doran.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Maybe Osama bin Laden did that. Maybe. Yeah. Maybe he went back in time to
bet on a six-sins game. You go back in time. Okay, I have a mind bender for you. And this
is good for you because you're fucking out off your rocker. Don't give me any kind of
bending land thing. You travel back in time. You warn about 9/11. They throw you in jail
with a machine. Come on. And then they throw you in jail. You're in jail. So you traveled
back maybe 20 something years, right? You're in jail for 30 years. So you are in the present
in jail at the same time as when you were about to travel back.
- That's scary.
- And then you could go to jail and meet yourself.
And it's you who's, and you like go to jail
and you meet yourself and he's like,
we shouldn't have warned about that.
- I wouldn't even drink that shit
and you're making me trip balls.
- I'm tripping you out, right?
- You're making me trip fucking balls, dude.
- Yeah.
- You know, I'd go to jail and I'd shmeet myself.
I'd do a conjugal visit and fuck in a fucking trailer
outside the prison.
- Why would you do that?
- Just for fucking, just to laugh again.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- I think, I guess I--
- By the way, you're 16 and this is--
- This is a scenario where this time travel stuff
has happened and I've been in jail for 30 years
and I'm going to visit myself.
I think I'd probably walk into jail and they'd go,
hey, go to jail.
- Get back in.
- And they'd put me in jail too.
- Get back in here, you bitch.
- I think that would, I think they'd also get put in jail.
- That's what the warden says to you.
- Yeah.
- Hey, get back in the cell with yourself.
- Get back in the cell and get older too.
- The warden is allowed to look at you.
- You're too young and out of the jail.
(laughing)
- Yeah, the warden's allowed to call you a bitch,
did you know that?
- You can say anything. - He is allowed?
- The jail workers can do whatever they want.
That's the type of industry--
- They can't do it by time it's standard.
- It's the same as the restaurant industry,
where a waiter can, if they're willing to forego their tip,
can say anything they want.
- How many times-- - The line cooks get to say
whatever the F they want to you in the restaurant.
They say, "You put those eggs on a plate."
- They're the same as a jail guard and a jail warden.
- B-A-S-T-I-D.
- Do you guys think that the most fun part of jail
is when you leave the jail and you have to go do all the
picking up trash or you do a bikini car wash or whatever.
- I think the funnest part is breaking a rock with a pickaxe.
- Yeah.
- That does look so fun.
- I think the most fun thing in jail--
- Literally real life Minecraft.
- Is all the loaf, when you get to eat the loaf.
- The loaf?
- Yeah, the loaf.
- I guess lunch and dinner time and breakfast time.
- I guess I would--
- And recess, and TV time.
- Recess would be amazing.
- I guess eating and watching TV would be my favorite part.
(laughing)
- And studying the Quran.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, oh my God, joining the Muslim Brotherhood.
- Dude, I personally would love to go to jail
so that when they have an enrichment activity
and say they're like, "Oh, we're gonna give you
"a creative writing workshop or something."
And I could just blow everyone's minds.
It's like, yeah, I was about to be an author on the outside
and so I'm just gonna write a novel.
- You can just lie all you want.
- Yeah.
- I'm in here for violence.
- You're in there for violence?
- Really?
- What's an author, you're an author on the outside
and you go into jail for violence.
- For violence?
- Plate, whoa.
- Yeah, you get locked up.
- Wait, this is a fucking movie idea.
- You get locked up and--
- The copier.
- The copycat.
- A nerd--
- A nerd becomes the president.
A nerd becomes the president, right?
Let's, I mean, whoever, like Buttigieg or something, right?
And then he says, he makes copywriting,
or not copywriting, copycatting and copying
the number one, it's worse than murder.
- Public enemy number one in terms of crimes.
- In most states, it's instant death sentence.
- Yeah.
- I just watched a two hour documentary about Amy Schumer.
- About Amy Schumer?
- Yeah, I watch about probably once a year.
- What's she up to?
- Probably--
- You watch it once a year?
- Yeah, you know, pops up.
- Okay.
- But anyway, that is a great idea for a movie.
And that's like the men's version of the Handmaid's Tale.
It's like, oh yeah.
- You can't copy anymore.
- You tell me, I can't fucking steal a fucking
- Oh my god, the scene, you know, it's like a dystopia,
right, so then they have the scenes at the beginning
where it's kind of just like all over the country,
it's like showing all these different things collapsing,
and it's like a guy showing up to the bar with his friend
and they're wearing the same--
- It's a woman narrating it.
- They're wearing, it's not a woman narrating,
it's a man narrating it.
- Okay, so it's a man narrating it at the beginning
and he says the--
- And I'm telling a scene and you're--
- You're interrupting, let him finish his scene.
- Interrupting is probably even gonna be a bigger crime
than country-catching.
- It's probably the second most crime.
- And he's gonna go to jail forever.
- Yeah, and you show up to the,
and a guy shows up to the bar
with the same color shirt as his friend,
or even the same sports team as his friend.
Not even the same shirt. - No, that's different.
- Same sports team.
And listen, you keep interrupting.
What do you think I'm, I'm telling a story here.
- You're going to jail.
- You are going to jail for a thousand years.
And then the cops come,
they put handcuffs on the guy with the same team shirt,
and they say you're going to jail for copying.
And he goes, "No, it's not copying!
"It's not the same shirt!
"We're just like the same team!
"No!"
He's getting dragged the fucking way by the corrupt police because they don't enforce the laws the way they should
Because it's not copying and I already thought of that and you're trying to get ahead of me
But you have a brain that's like this. I just got your brain is like this. I just know what yeah
Wait you were you were I was pointing out all the cinema sins. Oh shit. I was copying that no
You're copying a t-rex cuz your brains besides a peanut
Patrick can you see me?
(whispering)
- Guys?
(screaming)
- I scared him by moving,
but he couldn't see me because I wasn't moving.
- Oh my god.
- Wait, I was doing that first,
and you started copying me.
- What?
- Yeah.
- Doing what?
- I was being still first.
- Guys, we don't exist.
- I said Patrick, can you see me?
- No, no, no.
- We don't exist in the--
- What are you talking about?
- And now you're lying. - I don't exist in the copycat world.
- Guys, we don't think that we don't exist in--
- Lying is not a crime.
- And now you're interrupting me as well.
- No, I'm not. - We don't exist in that--
- You're a double, you're a double,
you're going to jail for two different reasons.
- No, I was interrupting Patrick, not you.
- I was interrupting Cal.
- Moo.
- I knew a kid who would tell that joke
with just different animals every time.
- Yeah.
- And they would get me every time, it's pretty funny.
- It's pretty cool.
- Yeah, interrupting Cal, moo is a classic.
- Interrupting chicken.
(Cal yelps)
- That's not nice.
because you would need to go on a pilgrimage.
You need to learn something about yourself.
Yeah, you are not a bride,
if you were on the Jim and Sam show, they'd tear you up.
Yeah?
Oh, for your etiquette with the microphone?
What etiquette with the microphone?
Bawking like a chicken.
Yeah, you can't bawk into the microphone like that.
You can't do that, that's rule number one
of the fucking etiquette.
Is that really?
They never did that on Stern.
You don't know that.
I know.
human chicken on there.
- Even he wouldn't bark.
- Yeah, he would do it away from the microphone.
- Stern would not, if there was a human chicken,
Stern wouldn't touch that.
Stern would not even touch a human chicken.
- That's low.
- I would eat human chicken.
- Hunan chicken.
- Yeah, I know that, but I would eat human chicken.
- Yeah.
- If they genetically crossbred a chicken and a human.
- Is that more human than a chicken?
- I don't know what it is.
- More human than a chicken.
- I think if I just, if I saw a food called that,
I would eat it.
I don't really know what it is.
I'm interested in food called think about like look at the size of your arm right now and imagine if that was a chicken wing
Yo, buff ass fucking chicken. Yeah
Imagine that you you're you would eat that for a week
Yeah for a weak-ass plate
Be a terrible last meal and oh, I would chicken a chicken wing a big chicken wing that would be disgusting dude
That's like the bit okay
If you take something that's good when it's small
and you make it bigger, it gets bad.
A big gummy bear is bad.
A big giant hamburger is bad.
- No, I think it's different with meats.
- No.
- I would say like a hamburger, but like--
- Oh, also-- - A big turkey leg?
- No, that's actually-- - At the Renaissance Fair.
- That's a small turkey leg.
- Is it really?
- Yes.
But with--
(laughing)
(laughter)
- Yeah it is.
- I do think that when you get big chicken wings
like from the store, like if you buy your own chicken wings,
if you get the big ones, those are bad, dude.
Those are the ones that have all the nasty
like pink meat in them.
- Oh yeah, that's a good point.
- Fruits too.
- Definitely fruits.
- Fruits and veggies.
- What's the best citrus fruit?
I don't know a cutie or a halo the smallest one. What's the worst one a grapefruit the biggest fucking thing in the world
And they yeah, you know what yeah, they are bad. They are bag
Honeydew melon and a cantaloupe. I like cantaloupe
I like cantaloupe as well and a honeydew tastes like fucking nothing a honeydew melon is even bigger than a grapefruit those fruits
You hate all fruits. I
Don't hate all fruit you do. Oh, you know I know one. I know one fruit you like blue raspberry. Yeah
(laughter)
- Sour berry.
I like sour berries and star berries I guess.
Those are good.
- No, I like red typhoon.
- You like lemon lime.
- Yeah, I like lemon lime, red typhoon, blue raspberry.
- Yeah, strawberry kiwi.
- Yeah, strawberry kiwi, it's my favorite fruit.
- Caramel apple.
- No, I just can't.
(laughter)
fruit fruit strawberry kiwi yeah that's good
so funny
yeah
no i just can't eat most fruits i fuckin
i i the day that i found out
that i was allergic to peaches was like
are you allergic to stone fruit?
stone fruit
what is stone fruit?
a pit
oh i don't know i ate a peach
fruit that weighs one stone
i ate a peach one time and then my lips swelled up
and i was like sad
I was like so sad cuz that's my favorite fruit. Yeah, you have a Stanford. Oh boy pits. Yeah. Yeah, you're probably allergic to pits
That explains a lot. Yeah, there's allergen to me. Yeah, he blows up like a balloon. He's around me
It's being a blown up like a balloon
Cameron you gonna blow him up like a balloon. You're saying he's putting on some pounds you think I've been gaining weight I
I didn't want to say this publicly.
Okay.
I feel like we've been going in a circle with this.
Okay, I didn't want to say, I seriously didn't want to bring this up on The Pocket.
I really didn't.
Okay, you can say it though.
I'm not upset.
But you are, but your body is disgusting.
Like I don't mean that in any way, but you are blowing my-
We're saying this as your friends, you are a behemoth.
You are like bordering on, I'm going to have to send you to the hospital.
I don't know how I'm going to get you there.
You're not going to like this.
I have contacted TLC and there's going to be a show about--
My 130 pound life.
I'm not 130 pounds.
Guess how much I weigh.
450.
Close.
600 pounds.
Get in there.
1,000 pounds.
I thought so.
That's crazy.
Yeah, I'm sorry to have to bring that up in public.
I know, I didn't want to bring it.
I don't want to say, I mean, I've been stuffing my face.
I knew that, the thing is, I know when I'm snarfing shit down,
I'm like just kind of pigging out and smearing my face.
And that's every day before we record.
I know that the reckoning is coming.
Yeah.
One day you will have a heart attack.
My friends are going to roast me.
Yep.
I don't care about the heart attack.
Hey, I would love to roast you on a spit
and cut your meat off with a shaver.
Yeah.
Make Cambridge shawarma.
Oh.
You do--
I would eat that.
I do think of you--
My own shawarma.
(laughing)
- Put myself on a spit and start shaving myself.
- If you had to eat some part of you,
that's the number one way to do it.
- Shwarma?
- Yeah, you just cut off a little slice.
- I don't know about--
- Imagine how good the spit would feel going up your butt.
- No, no, that's not true because a slice is long.
- Yeah.
- You'd want something, the best thing to eat
would be the tiniest piece.
- No, you want like a, but I'm not saying
you have to eat the whole fucking thing, Cameron.
- But you have to cut it off your body.
- I don't give a fuck.
All you want is fat and skin.
You want a crackling.
- So you're talking strictly on--
- Ooh, Cameron cracklings?
- Yeah. - On taste
and not on harm to yourself.
- I'd love to eat his bones. - Yeah, no,
I don't give a fuck about killing myself.
- And I think the best thing to eat would be your whole body
'cause it has so much--
- Eat my whole body, I don't give a mother fuck.
- Sorry, Cameron.
If you wanna eat your whole fucking body,
be my guest, asshole.
- I do wanna eat my body.
- 'Cause that's gonna be a tough, tough thing to do.
- This is gonna be maybe the worst thing I've ever said.
I'm gonna take a picture of you and post it online
and say you have to eat all of this in a year,
who you bringing.
Because that's how fucking huge you are.
- Yeah, damn I don't know if someone could do it in a year.
- You're too much man for this mouth.
- Oh my God, yeah that's why I--
- You are 450 pounds.
- I like to give back to the community
so I take a lot of plane trips that are back and forth.
I just fly to remote places and just come straight back
just in case the plane crashes
and I know everyone can survive
for like months and months and months.
- That's very nice.
- What you don't realize is that you're actually
probably raising the likelihood of it crashing by a lot.
- Yeah, I know, I always have to refuel midair
when I'm on the plane. - By a lot, yeah.
- Yeah, when you fly over Antarctica,
all the walruses said, or the whales said,
we are family, even though you're fatter than me.
- But they come out on the sand of it.
- And I have to sit in the aisle seat,
and yeah, I mean the whole aisle, front to back.
- Yeah, and by aisle, he means an island.
- You're such a, you love the movies, you've told me.
You've told me you love the movies.
- I have told you that a few times.
- But I've learned recently that--
- Patrick, just while I have you here, I love the movies.
- Hey, by the way, I love the movies.
You've told me you love the movies.
Little did I know you love the movies
'cause when you go to the movies theater,
they use your ass as the projector screen.
That's why you love the movies.
- 'Cause it's big and white.
- Big and white. - Only one of the chicks.
- Because that would be odd to have a kind of a concave--
- When I go into the movies, the whole room movies, shakes.
- Damn.
- Heavy footsteps.
- Yeah.
- Fat.
- The doctor has to use the Richter scale to measure you.
- Oh my God.
Don't, don't.
- Yeah, and your fat body is disgusting
to every single person who sees it.
- No.
- I think, this is the worst thing I'll ever say,
but I think if you got bulimia it would be good.
- It would be good.
- It would be good?
For who?
- For the toilet.
(laughing)
'Cause it's hungry.
and you would be putting a lot in there.
- Yeah.
- It's just telling somebody,
like, you should try out bulimia.
- That's kinda cruel.
- That is cruel.
- Yeah.
- That's not very funny to me.
- We should get--
- I don't really find that funny.
I don't know about you.
- Even if we're doing--
- You wouldn't, 'cause you're fat.
- Yeah.
- I just think that it's not funny
to joke about eating disorders.
- We should put you--
- Yeah, your eating disorder of fries.
- That is amazing.
- That's goaded.
- We should get you--
- With ranch.
- With ranch?
- Yeah.
- I've never had a ranch in my life.
You'd go eat the whole fucking ranch, old McDonald's farm.
- If I lived on a farm.
- The farm lived on you.
- If you lived on the farm,
I just would want to be the guy
who selects which animal to eat.
- You'd be the guy, you would be the guy
with the pressure gun. - I want to have no job.
- Oh yeah.
- You'd be the guy that shoots the cows.
- No, I'd be the guy who, I'd be the guy who's,
I'm the foreman or the supervisor.
I stand in the room while they have the bolt gun
and i stand i stand like twenty feet away i got okay shoot it now
it's not a doubt now
judith judith
so they go now
and that's what i think it is that i think you're going to take a look at
your reading your packet
and i think that what
but i don't like that did the page to the package at the pickett
(laughing)
- Oh yeah, shoot that.
- Hand in my waistband.
(laughing)
- A pinky in my waistband, hand on my stomach, shirt off.
- Now shoot the farmer's dog.
- Shoot that.
- Now shoot that.
Lunch break.
- For me.
(laughing)
- Keep killing.
Do that one, then that one, then that one, then that one.
(laughing)
- That would be an amazing job.
- Yeah.
- I kinda think I wanna get into farming,
but it seems too hard, so I won't.
I went to a farm that was owned by my mom's friend.
- Whoa!
- Your mom's rich or something?
- Were they rich or something like that?
- My mom's rich 'cause she has a friend who's a farmer.
(laughing)
- You gotta be rich.
- What does your mom do?
She was your fireman?
- Yeah.
- Does she drive an apple car?
- Richard's scary ass motherfucking town.
Damn dude, this kava is hitting me hard.
- But the farm, it seemed like such hard work.
and there was so many animals to take care of
and there was bees in the house.
- That sounded exactly like a children's book.
- There were bees.
- The farm seemed hard.
There were so many animals to take care of.
- And there were goats that acted like dogs.
- No.
- And cats that acted like stray cats.
- Does your mom's farmer friend ever go down to the dell?
- I don't think they have the farm anymore.
- Do they ever go down to the dell when they had it?
- I don't know what a dell is.
- In the dell?
Do they ever go in the dell?
- I don't know what a dell is.
- Farmer in the dell?
I know that, but I don't know what a Dell is, so you're gonna...
I guess nowadays Dell would just mean computer.
Yeah, nowadays.
Nowadays it would just mean computer.
That's why they gave up the farm.
Nowadays, they got into computers.
Yeah, they got into computers, and now it's probably a Bitcoin mining farm or Farmville.
A Dell is a computer for kind of like a Yolkel fucking...
Yeah, that is.
'Cause if they were a real artist or a tech head, they'd be on a MacBook.
A MacBook or a Surface.
Yeah, or a Surface Pro.
Surface Pro.
Dell Inspiron tablet is good for creatives?
Maybe if you're fucking straight.
Listen, pal, Dell is school library core.
Yeah, absolutely.
You keep unplugging your mic.
I'm not unplugging my mic.
It's your heft.
It's the--
Your heft is pulling it down.
This thing is broken.
Yeah, 'cause you sat on it.
Man.
(laughing)
Oh God, he sat on the whole damn thing.
Damn.
Oh, you're blowing me away over here
when you blow into that.
Oh, God.
He thought the mic was a glizzy.
That's why when fat people blow, it's really strong.
Because they have such big tummies.
And they're huge.
Yeah, they have really strong lungs.
And what do you mean when fat people do?
I'm talking about you, big guy.
Big O.
Yeah.
You're like a Goron.
They did a lung test on me, and I wanted to die.
Did you-- what score did you get?
I didn't see it yet.
You haven't looked at it?
It's best to just never look at whatever the doctor--
Oh, if there's something they need to tell me.
Last time I looked at my medical test records, there's a bunch of yellowed exclamation points
that said "abnormal."
Yeah, when that shows up, don't click it.
And I thought, "I never need to look at this again."
I don't want to know that I'm...
And then I got to the doctor, and the whole month I was thinking about it, "What does
that mean, 'abnormal'?"
And I Googled it, and they said all these long words I don't know.
For the definition of abnormal?
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
And then I get to the doctor, and she says, "Yeah, this is normal.
It says abnormal, but it's normal."
Oh, fuck them.
Fuck them, man.
But so I'm not going to look at my breathing test results.
But what if it says you have water breath?
What's water breath?
What if you can breathe underwater?
Did they do that test with you?
No.
What if you have a natural rebreather in your body?
They did a test if I could breathe into a tube in a glass box.
I'll tell you one thing, if I could breathe underwater, I would be switching careers,
and I'd be a professional apple bopper pretty, pretty fast.
Yeah.
I think I'd be making way more money.
Do they do that on ESPN2?
No, they do it on ESPN1.
Yeah?
Yeah, that's that's a huge
Tank is like big this summer dude. I one time don't some Olympics dunk tank is gonna be really that's where USA is like
Okay, that's where they're poised to take the gold dunk tank is I was sitting in a dunk tank and the kid the kid a kid
Misses and he does the thing he runs up and presses it. Yeah, I'd kill him. Yeah, you have to I
Lives I'd kill him they should on that target. There should be like a spike that comes out. Yes, that is genius or electrical
- It's shocking.
- Or just a normal gun.
- Yeah.
- If you were in the Olympics dunk tank,
'cause the Olympics version of the dunk tank
is the same as curling,
where there's like a thrower and a sweeper.
Would you rather be the thrower
or would you rather be the dunker?
- Probably dunker.
- I feel like you have more of a dunker physiognomy.
- Well yeah, so it's like the dunker thing,
the Olympic dunk tank is not like carnival dunk tank.
It's like a big tube that has like meters on it.
- So you're trying to do a cannonball.
- You're trying to get a big, big fat guy in the dunk.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- So when you throw that, you got a real skinny mini
throwing the fucking ball at the target.
- So Cameron should be the dunker.
- A wiry, a wiry...
- You dunker or the thrower?
- You wanna be the dunker.
- It's so funny every time, but it's so mean.
- You dunk yourself.
- Okay, dunker sounds like the person who dunks the person.
- Well, that's true.
It should be dunker and dunkey.
- Yeah, I think that's more, it makes more sense.
- No, listen, it's from a different language.
- Dunker and dunking.
- Yeah.
- It's the dunker and the thrower.
- I would wanna be the guy who gets dunked
'cause you don't have to do anything, you sit there.
- No, that's not true. - If I would get--
- That's not true, you gotta like--
- I would get so much performance anxiety.
- You're style points. - That's easy though.
I ooze style, I bleeds, I get style every day of my life.
I walk down the street and people say,
"Who's that, who's that, what's he doing?
"Get away from me, what's he doing?"
- You know-- - Show me your dunker,
show me your dunker pose.
This is you sitting in the dunk tank, right?
You're on Olympic TV and you're ready to be,
you're about to be dunked.
This is when the camera pans to you for the first time.
Okay, I'll set it.
- Do you guys have, wait, no, I just need,
do you guys have any glasses?
Do you guys have glasses?
Do you guys have a newspaper?
- No.
- Okay, then imagine those things.
- Okay, okay.
- Okay, ready, ready?
- Now coming up for the Olympic dunker,
dunk tank competition.
- How are you so bad?
- Cameron Fretter from USA.
This is his first time in the dunk tank.
Just tell me when the camera cuts to me.
Me and Caleb are on this side.
I'm the thrower.
This is my introduction.
This is not when I get dunked.
Right now it's on Caleb.
Now Caleb Pitts and Cameron Fetter
from Team USA.
This is their first dunk tank competition.
First time dunk tank has been
in the Olympics.
We're going to see
what this sport is all about.
Now, camera's turning over to Fetter sitting in the dunk tank.
And I believe that he is wearing glasses and reading a newspaper in the dunk tank.
He does not seem to have a care in the world about what's about to happen to him.
He's yawning.
He's yawning. He's yawning and fanning his breasts with the newspaper.
He's pretending that it's a real hot day out and oh it looks like he's sleeping.
Looks like he's sleeping in the dunk tank.
And it dunks!
It dunks, he goes down.
He looks surprised now.
He looks surprised and let's see how many meters he's fallen in.
20 meters.
20 meters deep.
That's really, that would hurt.
That's really deep.
That would really hurt.
60 feet.
That would really really hurt.
That would really hurt.
60 feet.
That would really, really hurt.
To do 20 meters.
And it looks like Team USA is going to be winning the dunk
tank this year.
Well, see, that's because if you're getting dunked,
you want to seem nonchalant so that it hits harder
when you dunk.
Sure.
You don't--
Because you have to play the heel.
You have to play the heel.
There's no way.
No.
You have to be like, fuck these Olympics.
Oh, yeah.
I don't give a fuck about 60 meters.
I put 60 meters in my ass.
Yeah.
He's down 60 meters.
Wait, is that like--
Perfect 10.
Perfect 10 gold.
60 meters and then the water or like into the water and 60 meters under water?
60 meters but then you have to bob back up.
But okay you didn't answer my question at all.
No.
Is it you fall 60 meters and then you hit the water or is it you fall into the water and then go 60 meters down into the water?
Woah so you drop from like fucking 600 feet up.
Yeah you gotta...
Holy shit.
No it's a regular...
No it's the Olympics.
It's the Olympics they figured all of this out.
60 feet the pressure won't fuck you yeah, 60 meters. Oh 60 meters. Yeah, no 20 was it 20 meters
Yeah, but then we upgraded it. Okay. We're starting it. This is already become the most by far the most dangerous Olympic
Best Olympia guys remember when do you guys remember when the the bobsled people?
The highest dive is 52.5. Yes
So it's essentially you're sitting on a pressure plate that knocks you down so hard
That you're basic. It's basically high dive with another down. It doesn't you don't just drop it like pushes you straight
That's all based on the pressure of the thrower uh-huh, so he did a good throw. Yeah, good work. Thank you
It's a team effort. Yeah, he's the style
It's like it's like as if we took gymnastics, and we split the style and the technical points in half
That is such a good way to look at it. I call you're the style. Yeah
Which I mean I do that all day. I'll take technicality. I'm not much much much one for style. Yeah style for me
It's like I'm not really
passionate about it
I'm not really
Okay, I'm not really passionate about style. It's just something that I am you are look at that amazing ah
It looks like anime character right there, oh, I'm sorry fuck you're gonna make me fucking smile
(laughing)
- How did that poke you back in the eye?
- It went into my eye.
- See, but he's so just nonchalant, he's not--
- Look, his brain is never chalanted.
- If that happened to me, I'd be freaking out.
I'd be screaming.
- You guys are literally obsessed with me.
- I'm fucked.
- Have you guys noticed that you're obsessed with me?
- Okay.
- We're trying to make you, we're trying to get in your head
to make you think you're a fetish.
- So that you will go for guys like us.
(laughing)
But mind you, you look like Zac Efron.
You look fucking amazing.
For real, like before or after he slid his jaw open
on his table. In between.
He slid his own jaw.
In between him slitting his jaw.
Do you guys remember that when he got a face surgery
and he said, "My chin was hanging off my face
'cause I tripped on my cup."
Yeah, and then he claimed that happened in like 2013 also,
it started swelling up 10 years later for no reason.
And then everybody was like, "That's fucking bullshit."
And then he was like, "You know I'm really insecure about my face, right?"
Yeah, he should be dude. He looks like a freak.
Yeah.
Man, he looks good in that movie. He just had HGH, it's fine.
Yeah, it's okay for Zac Efron to do HGH.
Look at that physique.
Because he was in a kids movie.
He was in a kids movie, which is why it's okay for him to have a weird adulthood.
His new face, I feel like he's maybe prepping to be in a Sin City movie.
Yeah, that would be really good in black and white.
He is prepping to play a wrestler.
Really?
He's doing some wrestling movie now.
He does look very different there.
Yeah, no, he looks pretty fucked up.
He looks like Zach Braff there.
Do you guys think that we'll ever get to that level?
Battery's low.
Oh, okay.
Do you guys think we could ever be at that level of celebrity?
No.
What level?
Zach Efron's level?
Where maybe we get some plastic surgery?
You don't have to be a celebrity to get plastic surgery.
You can just have to have some money or some good friends.
There is a place in my new neighborhood that I saw is a plastic surgery center and they
advertise BBLs in the window.
Oh yeah, I know that place.
Is that also the place that says like pussy tightening or something?
No, where's that?
That's on Myrtle.
It has a picture of a woman's asshole.
I think it might be this place.
Pink building?
Yeah, next to the atomic wings.
I walk by it every day.
- It's literally the most, like,
if you put those two businesses next to like,
like a sweeping shot and like Blade Runner,
like it's like Atomic Wings,
and then next to it is Pussy Titans.
(laughing)
- Do you think that when you get a BBL,
it's like when you get braces,
they're like don't eat anything that ends with O's,
because when it comes out, it's gonna blow your butt off?
- Yeah, there's a bunch of stuff you can't do
when you get a BBL.
- You literally like--
- How do you know?
- Who was saying, somebody was telling me--
- Nate was telling us that on the last episode.
- That's what it was?
- No, he didn't tell us about what you can't eat.
- He said that somebody was on a plane.
- I think also, can't you not sit on it or something?
- You cannot sit on it immediately.
- And I think also you can't slit it with a knife
or slice it up or put it into a crusher.
- What is the process of the BBL?
- So what's the point?
- The BBL is like they're breaking your rib cage
so that all the fat goes to your butt.
- What are you talking, no.
Don't break your rib cage.
- They break, okay, lipo from your lower body and then--
- They put fat in your ass.
- Purified and injected.
- You thought they'd break your bones?
- What am I thinking of?
- A waist--
- You're thinking of friggin' Marilyn Manson.
- Yeah.
- Oh, I'm conflating the two.
- You're thinking about inflating
where you go with her too. - And I want to inflate my butt.
- Yeah, and also, I don't know why it's,
I don't know what is so Brazilian about this.
- My sister's ex told me-- - Is this what picanha is?
- My sister's ex told me that Brazilian people
are obsessed with butts.
And I don't know if I really believe that, honestly.
- You should see Rio.
- Do you know what Brazilian people are obsessed with?
- Food. - Jiu-jitsu.
- Brazil.
- Yeah. - They always go there.
- They love Brazil.
They love Brazil.
- If they live in America, they always go to Brazil.
- And they love soccer as well.
- Yeah, some of them, but most of them go to Brazil.
is obsessed with extreme sports.
- That's, yeah.
- Bob Burnquist.
- I don't even know who that is.
- He jumped the Grand Canyon on a skateboard.
- Oh.
- For a second I thought it was gonna be someone
I was supposed to know who it was.
- I'd like to jump him.
- You're supposed to know who Bob Burnquist is.
- No you're not.
- I wish I didn't know who you were.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- I want Alzheimer's right now.
- Do you guys think that you're gonna--
- So you can forget that you've never seen your penis
- Okay. - Or your fat belly.
- Do you guys think that you'll die of cancer?
- Okay, I may be fat, but I got a big ass dick
that I can see past my belly, okay?
(laughing)
- Do you have a greasy dick?
- Hey, I may have a big gainer belly,
but you can see my cock.
- I have a stripe of hair down the top of my dick,
like a dog that has a wolf in its DNA.
- I would think scum.
- You know when they have a black stripe,
and you go, that's a killer dog.
- Hackles, your dick has hackles.
- I've never looked at a dog's penis.
penis the fuck are you talking about?
A dog's back?
Did you drink some psychedelic water you crazy motherfucker?
Bro's obsessed with dog penis.
I'm obsessed with dog puss.
I'm obsessed with my dog's penis.
You know Stripe from Gremlins?
Yes I know the Gremlins.
I know all the Gremlins.
No you don't.
Stripe, food gremlin, electricity gremlin.
He's good.
I never realized that Mike from Breaking Bad is in there.
He's the police officer.
and you kind of fucking realize that his backstory
of being a cop in Breaking Bad,
it must have been when he was a cop fighting the gremlins.
- That's why he's so resourceful in Breaking Bad.
- Also he's sort of like Battlescar.
- Here's what you're gonna do.
- Walter.
- Do not put them in water.
- Wait, Walter.
- That's why he hates Walter so much.
- Yeah, I just don't like your name.
- You multiplied my friend, you bitch.
Here's what you're gonna do,
- So you're gonna feed them at 11.30 p.m.
so they don't get hungry.
- Not midnight.
- Not after midnight.
- When do you feed them damn things then?
- Yeah, any time other than,
yeah, I guess every time is after midnight.
- Shit.
- That is a wild thought.
- Here's a one day, definitely.
- I'm blowing his kava mind right now.
- Guys, my mind has been flattened.
I have, there's nothing left of me.
You know, I feel like nothing.
- You, I'm looking at your eyes right now,
- There is nothing behind there.
- Your eye is so red.
- Your eyes look normal.
(laughing)
His eyes look completely normal.
- No they don't.
- I got really scared, I just thought about.
(laughing)
- I just thought about space and how it's too big.
It really scares me at night.
Do you guys ever, when you're going to bed
and you think about how large the universe is,
you get up and you start punching your pillow?
- I've never thought about anything before I go to bed.
- See, me, my screen time is only in the tens of hours
per day and not the fucking hundreds.
So I actually have some time that I think to myself.
- Yeah.
- If I'm alone with my violence,
I think about death and where my grandparents
might be going soon.
- I keep seeing a black specter that's a coat's hanging up.
- I have had a seriously similar experience.
- I remember you telling me about it
and I didn't even open up about my experience
that has also been happening.
- So now let's talk about this because first of all,
can we just acknowledge--
- And we just felt two presences in the past few weeks.
- And can we just acknowledge right now,
this is creepy. - And you're about to feel
a third. - This is creepy.
Luckily we got it on camera.
Can you switch to this camera, please?
You have, and I don't mean to alarm you,
you have bones on your shirt.
That is a bone outfit.
And there's a bone spirit.
- Cam, Cam. - He's wearing a--
- There are two hands on your shoulder blades.
- I can't see them from here.
- This is a speedy-- - And I don't think
the camera will be able to see them either.
- And I'd just like to acknowledge how weird it is
that on all days, the day that we end up talking
about our spiritual experiences,
and just like kinda getting into it,
and we'll talk about it for the next 10 minutes or so.
- Yeah. - But,
you decided to wear a spirit Halloween shirt.
- I didn't decide to wear this.
I didn't even realize I was wearing this.
Okay, can I give you an actual rundown
of my spiritual experiences?
- Go one by one.
- Number one, I felt a presence
when I was standing right there,
and I turned around and there was nothing there,
and it scared me.
Number two, that door opened and closed.
We all saw that and we remember it and it happened on recording.
Number three, when we were walking from our lunch, or maybe to our lunch,
no, it was after our lunch, we were walking back to the car,
and I felt another presence.
And I went, "Oh my God," and I turned around, and you guys said,
"You're being weird."
And I said, "No, I felt a presence."
Number four was going on the whole time,
which is there's a jacket on the door that looks like a monster.
- I think that you're being followed by a monster.
(laughing)
- The jacket looks like a monster at night?
- At night, when I can see it from my bedroom.
- Do you ever put--
- At number five is, soon the world will end.
- Wow, that is really haunting.
I do hate that when stuff at night
starts to take a weird form,
where like maybe you'll hang up a dress
and then you'll put like a jack-o-lantern on top of it.
(laughing)
And then some bony hands coming out of the side.
And you'll walk out of the bathroom at night
You're all tired. You go. Oh fuck me. Oh, just my jacket. I dress am I my gloves and my knife. I have guns
I have gotten scared. I've got scared so many fucking times by my taxidermied silverback gorilla
Yeah, I get it that's scary man. I turn I go into the kitchen you to eat a few women. Yeah
For a yeah when you and your woman make love I keep fucking seeing them
At my Christmas tree. I keep seeing them in my cabinet
Speaking speaking of your giant taxidermy and silverback when you and your woman make love do you like kind of put your hand over and like
Just flatten it so that it doesn't watch. I know this crazy silverback. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, this crazy sick mofo putting a suction cup dildo on that thing bringing them in as a third
I don't need to put a suction cup dildo on it has a penis you filled up the penis
You filled up your be a gorillas have tiny penises oh, yeah, which is perfect for my depth cuz I
I don't want to turn off any potential gay fans who have a crush, but I can't really
take it back there.
You're blowing my monkey mind today.
I've been sent back to the Stone Age.
Is that its penis?
No, they're really, really small.
Yeah, they're microscopic.
- I believe they have the smallest penis to body ratio
of a primate.
- Is that its penis?
- No, it's probably penis is,
just search gorilla penis and really show it.
- That gorilla's penis is big and purple.
- That's a ball that it's holding.
That's not even visible on screen.
- Dumb as an apple.
- I've seen this picture probably a hundred times.
- Yeah, a hundred times.
- Yeah, probably a hundred, a hundred and fifty times.
- I don't think you're gonna find a gorilla penis today.
- Yeah, you have to turn safe search off
or search on something else.
- You gotta go on Bing, bro.
- Go on Bing, yeah.
- You gotta check out Gorilla Penis on Bing.
- But in the meantime, though,
which taxidermy animal would you throw it back on?
- Ooh, that's a good question.
- Probably a raccoon.
- Raquel Welch.
- What's that?
- I don't know, it just said she died.
- Oh, this is not what I was looking for.
- Okay, so don't show this stuff either.
- Yeah, no, this is all--
- That is furry porn.
- I'll try this in the picture.
- These are definitely, there's some creative liberties
are being taken with these photos.
Gorilla's penis is definitely way smaller than that, from what Cameron's told me.
And also it doesn't go into...
That's just a guy's ass!
Yeah, it's not a gorilla.
[Laughter]
Did you search "white girl having sex with monkey"?
No, that just came up.
(laughing)
- Oh no.
- That's awful.
- That's horrible.
- Yeah, no, that's not.
I don't want it to be a part of this anymore, Jubio.
- Yeah, Jubio, you kinda ruined everything.
- That's what he does, man.
He's so shit at his job, man.
- I'm surprised by how easily he can completely ruin.
He knows exactly the thing to click on
that makes me never wanna talk about
whatever we're talking about again.
- He's just terrible.
He's just so bad at his job.
- Oh, we do have a sponsor to have for Chewy, though.
- Oh, actually, Jubio.
Actually, we have been very helpful for me. Yeah, food
Don't type anything. Fuck you. Fuck you the pet store that I go to keeps running out of Moe's food so chewy
There we spot we can tell you dermy Jubio. Oh my god. Yeah, we only had he only has button micro
He'd be so much better at his job if we just fully taxidermy. Yeah, and just put him there, and he's just
Yeah, just kind of looking yeah, we would hands up like a bear
- (laughs) Taxidermy him exactly like a bear
and put him in the office.
- You can put fangs on his fingers.
- Can I get a nod to your head yes?
If you die, can we do that to you?
- If you die, you're not gonna do--
- No, not when you're alive.
- Well, everyone saw that he nodded.
- Yeah, I saw it.
- We all saw it, right?
- Yeah, hold your phone sideways.
He's nodding.
- He's nodding.
- He is nodding.
- That is express permission.
This jacket on my door, it's terrifying.
It looks like a cloaked ghost
and I'm terrified to take it off of my door.
- Cloaked?
- It's crooked, yeah.
- Why won't you just take it off?
- Because this jacket is on the front door, okay?
I can see from my bed, the way my bed is,
I see it out my bedroom door
to the front door of the apartment.
If I take the jacket off, then I'll just see the door
and I'll get scared that it's gonna open.
- Yeah.
- You are a baby.
- Dude, I got so freaked out last night,
or two nights ago, speaking of,
I thought that my door was going to open
because I heard out, like in front of my apartment,
I heard just a guy go, "Help!"
and i i woke up to it and i thought like oh my god
there's a guy is like six in the morning
woke up and i thought immediately
there's a guy going around people's houses
and he's breaking in and he's killing everyone
and i like uh... the pete the fear paralyzed me i couldn't get out of my
bed
so i'll but i knew is just uh... like a homeless guy yelling do you know what
you should do
there's a whole issue content by my apartment you should call on one are l
stein
'cause I don't think R.L. Stine has done any books
called The Homeless Horror or something.
- Yeah, The Homeless Screamer.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah.
- He would do a clever one, though.
- Yeah, well, yeah, it would be like--
- It would be an allegory. - Homeless where the heart
isn't-- - It'd be called
A Voice for the Voiceless. - Takes my heart.
- Yeah. - And it would be
a screaming homeless guy. - Or it would be right.
There was one, I think it's the same guy, I'm not sure,
but I heard him walk by my house and go like--
- R.L. Stine?
Yeah, I heard R.L. Stine walk by my house.
He was going, "I'm going to scare so many people today."
He walked by and he said, "The next person I see is getting fucking stabbed."
He would do that.
Do you guys remember when we were in Portland
and the guy was going to kill that guy with the machete?
Yeah.
I think about that a lot and I think if he ever did that.
We never talked about that.
I think we did a little bit.
He walked by.
We talked about it at the live show.
Oh, yeah.
There was a guy with a chain too that I saw.
Oh, that dude was scary.
I went out when you guys were napping together and I didn't that weird detail
We didn't have to not nap together. There's the only reason that I would be out walking alone
Okay, but you didn't have to say when you guys were napping together. It doesn't matter
What do you want if I say anything else it will seem like I'm a weird loner
But you're making us sound like a friend and by the way we were in separate beds
Yeah, well you were napping together. There was it wasn't in the hotel
And there was a guy dragging a chain
But that we were anyone and he wanted to say hello to me we were in Portland and we were walking to a bar
- A coffin club.
- Yeah, and a guy--
- We were in court space also.
That's just a little detail that makes the story
a little fun. - We already looked dead.
We were walking and two guys are getting in some kind
of F word argument where they're screaming at each other.
And then the big fat guy walked away and walked by us
and we kind of all like, you know,
try to not make eye contact with this guy.
And it's one of those things where, you know,
when you're walking with people and you're talking
and then you all overhear the same thing
and just stop talking completely, it was that.
And so we had completely stopped talking.
- Or you do the little-- - And this giant guy
walked by and looked at us. - The little conversation
to make it seem like you're not sharing.
- Yeah, you just go like, "Oh, yeah."
- Oh, they put a new building here.
- Yeah. (laughing)
And then the guy looked at us and he was like,
"Have you ever seen somebody get fucking killed
"with a machete?
"Stick around!"
And we were like, "Ugh!"
- And then we went to the gothic club.
- We didn't stick around, but I kinda wanted to
have a kind of a chicken fight betting yeah just throwing money down yeah oh
there's also a guy with a laser gun - yeah I remember that there was remember it we
were in LA and that guy we were crossing the street on the Hollywood on Hollywood
Boulevard and that guy had like a skateboard like really broken one it was
just like jabbing people in the fucking chest with it no you don't remember that
he I do he tried to he hit you in the sternum with his skateboard and then hit
an old man and the old man stopped in the middle of the road and just went "What a prick!"
"What a prick!" He kept doing that. That guy's cool. Yeah. But you don't remember that? He
hit you in the chest. Maybe you blacked out from anger. I probably blacked out from pain.
I probably hurt too bad and I fully blacked out. Yeah, he's just walking around just fucking
like, with a bayonet style. I do think living in a city makes you crazy no matter what if
- You stay in there long enough.
- I mean Portland, Los Angeles,
these are two places with the craziest people on Earth.
- I think that this kava might be opening my mind
to sort of a different social ills.
And I might be realizing right now
that New York City is a disease
and needs to be wiped off the face of the planet Earth.
- Yeah.
- But I'll figure that out on my own time.
- That'll happen.
- You know.
- Yeah.
Whatever.
- Who gives a shit?
- Who cares?
- Should we just all three kill ourselves?
- Yeah.
- I think that's a good idea.
Turn the lights off, we're gonna slit our wrists.
Yeah, I don't want anyone to see this.
Yeah, wait, yeah, turn these off,
and then we'll slow 'em.
I don't want anyone to see us kill ourselves.
All right, here we go, ready?
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Don't you, you ruined it.
Why'd you-- You ruined the whole bit.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Okay, now we're really doing it.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
God, it hurt. Jesus.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, God, wait, Jesus.
I didn't know it was gonna do that.
Oh, crap.
It feels kinda good. It actually feels good, yeah.
Whoa.
Am I the only one that thinks this feels kinda nice?
It actually feels fucking amazing!
Yo!
Guys, let's turn off the recording and keep doing this.
Bye.