(upbeat music)
- Clapped because Caleb is injured today.
- You stepped up, man.
- You did step up. - I'm pretty proud of you.
- You're the host who stepped up.
- Yep. - Step host.
Yeah, it's disgusting.
I tried. - Oh wow.
- Yeah, we gotta really wipe down the table.
- It's our cums.
- Ew!
- We did it on episode, it's our cums.
It's not gross. - Ew!
It's not our cum? - It was happened on camera.
- It was DNA. - It's not our cum.
- It was cums that we didn't wipe down.
- DNA.
That's my DNA.
(laughing)
- Oh, that's pretty incredible.
- Yeah.
- I'm a little bit worried
'cause I have had no new experiences
in the last four days because of my neck being like this.
This is the only thing that I can think about right now.
- Yeah.
- Is my neck and how people, when I walk down the street.
- How are you gonna do--
- Especially little kids, they're like, "Hey, hey, hey."
- You're going to open for Adam tomorrow.
How are you gonna even do anything?
How are you gonna do any jokes
that don't have to do with the neck brace.
- Man, I'll probably just fucking destroy like I always do.
- Can we sign your neck brace, by the way?
- Oh my God, that's such a--
- Can I get a Sharpie and sign your neck brace?
- Yes. - You're in luck, buddy,
'cause I throw everything that I use
on the episodes down here. - Oh my God.
- Can you lean all the way over the table?
- Yeah, hold on.
(laughing)
Yeah, hold on.
- Okay, hold on, let me.
Well, it'll be sideways, but that's okay.
- You can stand up.
- No, it's too late, I already started writing sideways.
Oh, this is going to be so...
Oh, you should have done it around. Oh, that's good too.
Here, let me sign it too. Let me sign it too.
You get the front because I like you more.
What? That's not nice.
You should see what I just wrote and you'll take that back.
And you should see what he's writing and you'll take it back.
This is just a guarantee that you write something very nice right now.
What is that? What does that mean?
Have a kick-ass summer.
Did you see what I did?
You gave me a hags? I gave you a hackas. My man. What did you see mine? I'm like I'd
What does it say? It says Cam plus Caleb with a heart with an arrow through it. Oh, I'm not you had to do a swastika
I was about to do it
I was about to draw a swastika on your neck brace as a prank
So that you don't know it's there and you walk around with your bald ass head
You got cam plus Caleb Hart and a giant
Right up the back they would nobody's gonna touch me though even it I could write anything
I want on here nobody me up. I'm already in a neck brace look at my awesome signature
This is a this is a great
Famous, I would write that this is a great lesson for any of our listeners who are maybe far, right?
Nazis or something is that if you want to have like here's my message to you if you're far, right first of all f off
F you, you fucker.
Second of all, if you want a good idea.
This is my message to you.
That's a big fat thumbs down.
I would do two thumbs down but I'm holding the microphone.
That is a double whammy right here.
This is called the double whammy.
I just invented it.
Two thumbs down by the way, that's a little strong for anybody.
It's a middle finger plus a thumbs down.
That's, I mean, two thumbs down.
That's all your thumbs.
I would say, you know.
Five fingers down. Could be a new one.
Yeah, five is all your fingers. Yeah, what is ten toes down mean is that a surfing that is not a surfing thing?
That means when you're standing oak on the ground. It's a Bay Area, but the bay that they surf in oh my god
But I your bloody brilliant. What does that mean though bloody brilliant? I think the Bay Area is kind of cringe
You are you're basically the opposite of this you're in my reach area is
You don't know what fizz is?
And you're talking shit about the bay?
You don't keep it three thou-wow?
You're being so fucking cringe right now.
Whatever.
I'm embarrassed to even be sitting here.
Just for no reason, I should bring this up, I think it's cringe.
What's that? Pig Destroyer.
Hmm.
What's Pig Destroyer? Just some random thing I thought of.
What is that? But it would be cringe.
*laughs*
Get some barbecue?
My mic.
- You gotta get a new cable. - Godfrey's cursing you
with a bad cable.
- I've switched out this cable a bunch of times.
I think it might actually be my mic, yeah.
- Damn, we might have to upgrade.
- Might have to frickin' upgrade.
- You guys at home might have to start paying us
way more. - Should we get, should we?
(laughing)
- Guys, it's so sad for you. - 'Cause we pay for these
on subscription.
- Yeah.
- These are after pay, for the 400.
- No, they're not even after pay,
we literally paid every month forever.
- That's what the $5 tier is really for.
- We rent them for $100 a month.
we do it, we have the podcast like the
under the guise of like us doing a show.
But no, it's just a good day for these fucking
spin off podcast under the guise of
just under the guise.
Oh my God. And it could be that it's the
bonus feed. That's the camera.
Oh, under the weight.
That's so smart.
This this.
Oh, this is $5.
It begins.
Thirty five dollars a month.
You can see under the table.
No, no, it's even better than that.
It begins like a normal episode.
Right. But then this camera slowly sort of
pans down right and we see our legs but then we keep going past our legs and who
do we see the borrowers yeah where the borrowers are like man you see that
motherfucking shoe the other day that was fucking hitting on the motherfucking
ground like that for the borrower accent
Eddie Thompson.
Yeah, they don't know what walking is.
They drive around that.
The shoe that was hitting on the ground.
Yes.
I guess they would be New York borrowers, so they would have New York accents.
They're New York borrowers in New York.
They be calling stuff brolic.
Yeah, it's mad brolic on the floor.
And on the ground.
It's mad brolic on the floor today.
But I heard there's going to be a crumb.
Yo, I heard there's a crumb shower.
Somebody's heating.
Dude, they be lining up around the block to get a crumb.
Where are you from?
I'm from the bathroom.
(laughing)
Pow, pow, pow, pow, pow!
Don't you ever come to the kitchen again, motherfucker!
(laughing)
Yeah.
That is sadly how it would actually be.
That is so fucking tragic.
That would be true.
It is tragic as fuck, but that is what it would be like.
- You know what the borrowers don't realize?
- What?
- Is that if the kitchen and the bathroom borrowers
got over their differences and teamed up,
they could fucking take down the CEO boardroom borrowers.
- Oh my fucking God, you're right.
- 1% of borrowers.
- The people who are way up on the first floor.
- Yeah, exactly.
- The penthouse.
- The kitchen table.
(laughing)
Damn, the kitchen table's C-suite,
looking down on all the other little borrowers.
- Their little suit.
- Look at them walking their dust bunnies around and shit.
- Disgusting, none of them know what it's like
to look at a big apple on the table.
- You ain't never had a crumb fresh off the plate.
Straight from the plate, you have 'em on the ground, man.
- He's got like a sprig of rosemary in his office.
- Just doing backstroke in the kitchen sink.
- Oh my God. - Oh my God.
- That's pissing me off just fucking thinking about it.
- Dude, they are disgusting, right?
- I fucking hate the top 1% of borrowers.
- Me too, they get to watch the TV like this.
- Occupied living room!
- Yeah, occupy under the couch.
That was a powerful movement.
It was a powerful ass movement for the borrowers.
Yeah, 'cause that's true.
Under the couch borrowers,
they get all the change in the cushions.
Yeah, exactly.
And a coin to a borrower, that's the size of the moon.
A coin to a borrower is the table.
That's a table, a rich expensive table.
That's a table that you put on top of a piece of dice.
Yeah, a piece of dice.
A piece of dice.
Can you imagine a rich borrower's house,
just the kind of stuff that would be in there?
Oh my fucking God, string.
Just like a mounted--
Lots of string.
(laughing)
String everywhere.
A mounted ant head sitting on top of the fireplace.
Right? Just looking like that.
Yeah, we caught that one.
Me and the boys on an exhibition down into the garage.
A spider skin rug.
Oh my God.
Or a bee.
Yeah, a full bee.
Yeah, pet.
Oh my God, you're not allowed to have a bee?
I know a guy who...
So I own a bee.
You better watch out, you're going to get raided.
See, that's what would be even worse about the borrowers is the police would be even worse.
Oh my god, police borrowers?
That'd be awful.
The police are already, you know what they should call
the police in the borrower nation?
The stealers.
Yep.
'Cause they don't borrow, they steal.
They take.
They takers.
They take permanently.
Yeah.
Take her permanently.
Permanently.
Yeah.
If you guys were borrowers, what room would you be from?
Straight up.
Kitchen probably.
For me, the man cave.
Damn, actually I would have to rep the man cave as well.
I would have to rep the man cave as well.
I'd probably move.
Man cave nation?
- I probably moved to the man cave after my shit got--
- Straight live from the underground, from the man cave.
- Can you imagine though, if you were a bedroom borrower
and you were the one who had to live in the carpet
that got a cum in it?
- Yeah, that would suck.
You know what would suck?
Is if you're the bedroom borrower
and you're living in the underwear drawer
and you gotta live next to that stinky vibrator.
- Yeah, I actually would--
- Yeah, and you're so stupid and small,
you think it's a roller coaster.
- You shit on that thing, you sit on that like
- It's a fucking rodeo horse, whatever that thing's called.
- The bedroom borrowers, they're like a...
- What? - Mechanical bull.
- Mechanical bull.
- Rodeo horse, all right.
- The bedroom borrowers, they're like the hillbillies,
they're sitting on their porch on little rocking chairs
and there's two guys sitting together and they're like,
storm's coming, and then in the sky they hear
a thundering noise, ah, ah, ah!
- They got a banjo. - And a white rain.
God help you if you live where the lady's a squirter.
You might as well live in Seattle, dude.
They got a fucking--
Oh, we got six millimeters of squirt this year.
They make a rain jacket out of the remnants
of a used condom.
Oh, okay, well that would actually work pretty well, actually.
That would actually, that's a good idea.
Yeah, no, that's actually a wonderful idea.
You have a borrower's mind, my friend.
You do have a borrower's mind.
That's true. I do have, I was, I am part borrower.
Imagine going up to the toilet like it's a volcano.
Oh my god.
Wow.
That's flushed away though.
Hopefully, yeah.
And you're, and you are.
That's you're thinking more mice.
No, no, no, no.
Imagine he puts you under your hat
and you make an M.D. on all that fucking food.
Come on.
You're on this big train,
you're on this train of thought about borrowers
and you're throwing all this rat shit in it.
Imagine you hanging out with your sister D.W.
and you doing motherfucking homework.
Now you're on Aardvark.
Yeah, that's Aardvark stuff.
I thought that they were mice.
No, Mr. Ratburn, the gay guy is a rat.
Okay, well that's fucking--
That's kind of crazy, though.
They were like, hey, here's a--
I'm a gay rat.
We're making the one rat the gay guy.
I think, you know, what I will say,
I think that's fair, but also I'm not sure
that you could call a gay guy any animal
and it would be a compliment.
I don't think that--
A unicorn?
(laughing)
They might like that.
I'm not sure there's any animal you could pick
from that show to be gay that--
- Are you kidding?
- Gay guys, gay guys, sound off in the Patreon comments.
What animal are you?
- Gay guys call themselves different types of animals
all the time.
- Yeah, they say bears, otters, twink.
- They don't have any of those on the show though.
It's rats and mice and aardvarks.
- No, they got a bear on Arthur.
- Who's the bear?
- Then they have a binky.
- Berry.
- What animal's he?
- Binky is a bear.
- He's not a bear.
- Yeah, that's a bear.
- Look up, search binky, Jubio.
- Binky, Arthur.
- Tell me this is a bear.
He's a... no.
There's a moose.
There's no way this animal...
Brains.
Oh, what the fuck is that, dude?
That's a bear?
No, oh, his parents are... wait, he's an Asian?
He's a bulldog.
He's a dog?
What?
That is not a...
If a dog...
If you showed me a dog that looked like that in real life, I would put it down.
Wait, guys, he used to be nine, but now he's ten.
Oh, that's huge.
Oh, thank God.
I think that the only woke character...
Wow.
(laughing)
- Wow.
- Wait, what's the picture next to it?
- That actually looks just like him.
- Look, it's the real-life Pinky.
- Wow.
I think the only woke way you could have a gay character
on Arthur is if it was just a human.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause gay people are human.
- They had Matt Damon on Arthur.
- Did they really?
- But they turned him into an art work.
- But they probably anthropomorphized him.
- They did, yeah.
(laughing)
- They made him look almost human.
- They made him look human.
(laughing)
- They made him walk on two legs.
- Made him speak English.
Kind of embarrassing.
But no, it should be a human.
Who else is on that show?
Arthur, DW, Binky, Buster Bunny.
Bugs, no his name isn't, it's Buster, right?
Buster, yeah, Buster Bunny.
Yeah, you tripped me up.
What is Francine?
Is Francine a bear?
Is also maybe, Francine is--
She's an aardvark as well.
Who, there is a fucking bear on Arthur.
Muffy.
Muffy has red hair.
Muffy's a gorilla.
What, there's so many confusing animals.
Yeah, Brain.
Oh, oh.
Steven, voiced by Steven Krapter.
Arthur Black Bear.
Who is this? I don't remember this guy.
That's Brain. Brain. Brain.
That was Alan Powers. Oh, that's his dad.
His name's fuckin' Alan. Oh, and May Lynn Barnes was also a bear, I guess.
Okay. Okay. We all remember May Lynn Barnes.
I don't. Biggies adopted little sister from China.
The Chinese female bear.
Oh. Um. She can understand what the dog says?
Yeah, there's still a dog in the Arthur universe. Yeah, alright, Ylvis.
Alright, you Ylvis motherfucker. You're the dog named fuckin' Pal.
What he's acting like Elvis over here? Yeah, does the dog say true?
You got me on that Wow
Whoa that was cool, I
Think that's a thing that should be touched privately. Yeah, I don't think we should
Just that it I honestly don't give a fuck about anything anymore since my injury
I have been feeling a little bit like that early when I went into that you have you have an air you have an air
of don't give a fuckness a little bit when I when I went into the bodega I give a
fuck activity I moved I moved I went to go get this right and I've been to over
and it hurt a little even slammed it down on the table yeah fuck it
whoa and I took the camera pics yeah fuck I'll do it again I went to go get it and
I bent over and it hurt and instead of like just keeping that in I went oh and
a guy looked at me and I was like yeah fuck you man whoa I don't give a fuck if
You said that?
No, but I mentally communicated it, I think, pretty well.
You have mastered the subtle art of not giving a fuck, I think.
Ain't nothing subtle about it.
Wow.
Yeah.
Attitude.
I'll flick you.
If you were, and honestly, now that I've had this realization, I will never eat pussy again
because that is so disgusting.
I'm ready to admit it.
You probably have your neck is probably going to hurt.
I bet you miss it so much.
Bro, I bet you fucking miss it so much.
Dude, why do they pretend, why does every, all these fucking ugly guys pretend like it's the best thing in the world?
Mm-hmm.
Dude, chill.
[Laughter]
Dude, chill!
It's okay.
It's fine, it's not like, I'm not like, "Oh, that's the best thing." Just chill out, man.
Relax.
It's always ugly guys. You never see a really hot guy.
Brad Pitt never was like, "Honestly, I just love eating pussy. I eat pussy for hours."
And if he was, if he was, he was doing one of his funny roles.
funny roles exactly burn after reading yeah exactly he's playing a buffoon yeah
yeah and you'll see girls walk around I there there are girls who they love
famously love you can cock snatch no eating snatches there but that's the
same thing that's like eating that's like a lesbian but that's like eating
your own boogers that's like of course you like that yeah I guess who doesn't
like there are girls all women like eating pussy cuz everybody waves their
own farts into their face sometimes.
It's like, that smells good.
There are girls who are running around talking about how much they love sucking weiner.
Yeah, but they are similarly usually not that attractive and kind of just weird people.
Yeah. Yeah.
Thank you. I think anyone who's hyper sexual, if you like, it's not the type of person I like to hang out with.
I'm with you. Yeah.
I don't like I don't know.
I want to be hanging out with hyper sexual bitches all the fucking time.
- I literally wanna be surrounded by 10 dick suckers
at all times.
- You roll up to the club, 10 dick suckers deep.
- Oh my God, I'm rolling my Monopoly dice.
I see the number, I go, you.
- I'm rolling my-- - Today, you.
- I'm rolling my non-monogamy dice, right?
- Yeah. - I'm rolling--
- Oh my God. - Oh shit, I got snake dice.
- It says, yeah. (laughing)
- I guess I'm monogamous.
- Yeah, all right, I guess I gotta stay home.
I can't even go to the friggin' orgy that we're gonna have.
- If I had to suck anybody's dick in the world though,
it probably wouldn't be you guys
'cause I wouldn't wanna ruin our relationship in any way.
I think that it would... I know we've talked about this before.
And I was thinking about this in the shower this morning.
This is putting a Pert Plus bottle in your mouth.
I don't think...
You're sucking off your shampoo bottle and you're like, "This is definitely not Caleb
or Patrick."
You're talking up, you're like...
It's gonna ruin everything.
With the swab.
I got you.
We worked so hard for everything.
This is not going to work.
I'm not gonna do it.
Is not you guys trust me this is not
It's a bottle of Alberto vo
From the fucking Dollar Tree, it's like a heavily. I got a nude body wash damn
I can sniff that on you right now
You're lying, and it's purple and when I rub it on my body. I feel like a Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle
Yeah, that's purple slime. Ooh. It shouldn't be purple a body wash. I know I think cuz it's lavender scent
Yeah, it is, but oh my God, he thought I couldn't fucking smell him.
No, I thought I couldn't fucking smell him, but I did.
What other body wash is going to be purple?
I don't know.
Ketchup?
Mountain?
Grape?
You think I'm wearing grape?
I'm doing grape body wash.
That's a good-- I'd wear grape.
[LAUGHTER]
There used to be-- when I was a kid,
it was like the best smell in the world,
this artificial grape-scented sunblock that my mom had.
And that artificial grape scent is like--
Remember there's a good hair gel that you could eat no I don't
You were just eating it my friend had my friend Nash he had a he had a
It wasn't really all right. I guess all right. I guess it's southern
I was gonna say you make fun of me for having a friend nicknamed chowder all this is his real name was Nash is a
name
Potion castle has ruined that fucking name from every time I hear it now. I think I think it's a fake name
Nash Greer. We all like Nash Greer. I forgot who Nash Greer was for a second. I don't remember what that is.
And was he the guy who... He was not the one who did that backflip though. He had blue eyes.
Beautiful blue eyes. Wow! Wow! His face is small. How many movies has this guy been in? Not that many I don't think.
Can we change that? Sorry I interrupted your story about Nash. This guy Nash, I went over to his house one time
One time is just super super rich he had a he had a pool that they would cover and it would become a tennis court
Wow, and he had a he had a a tree house that had inflatable furniture inside of it
It was like a giant like a little apartment. It was fucking crazy like you couldn't afford real for yeah
Like fucking broke in this tree house
Bathroom attached to his bedroom, okay, and I went over there as a leftist. I think that we should eat this guy's parents
I also think that we should turn his extra bathroom into a soup kitchen
We take his bathtub that's also got hot jacuzzi jets
And we bubble that fucking soup up and he was a child that had a his and hers sink in his bathroom
Yeah, and then I went over there
Very nice hair, and he would put his hair up, and I was like what do you have and he's like?
"It's this hair gel that you can eat."
And I was like, "What the fuck, that is amazing."
And it was like really sour raspberry flavored.
And I put it, and he squeezed it into my mouth.
- Yeah, I don't think that that was hair gel.
I think that maybe he was using--
- You played out some kind of homoerotic
kind of sublimation, I think.
That was kind of--
- It might have been just some goo that he had,
but he did put it in my mouth.
- I bet-- - Gummy hair gel.
- I bet it was just like non-toxic, right?
- Gummy, gummy hair gel. - So if it hits in his eyes,
he doesn't turn into a Resident Evil monster.
- I guess it could have been that.
Please don't buy 15 of the Gummy Gummy Hair Gel
Maximum Hold Extreme.
- Please buy them.
- But yeah, I guess now that I think about it,
he might have been making fun of me or something.
Like I was so stupid and poor that he was like,
just making shit up.
- Yeah, it was probably juicy drop pop, dude.
- No, no, definitely I remember that it came in like a big,
you know how like things that are not edible
usually come in a wider squeeze tube?
- Yeah.
- And if it's edible, it's in a thin squeeze tube.
you know you have tomato paste, you have stuff like that.
And then the big ones are usually different things.
- He has been going like this for the past.
- And you said it was a big one.
- It was one of these big ones.
- And that's when you're thinking about him.
- I'm not thinking about Nash.
- He's like, oh yeah, Nash had a big tube.
- Maybe he did, it's not my business.
- Nash had a big tube.
- I'll say this, I hope Nash is doing well for himself.
I hope he remained very rich.
- I hope he got broke as fuck.
- I heard he lost everything.
I was actually looking him up just the other day.
- No you weren't.
I was looking up to him Caleb's friend Nash
He literally did that with him. Yeah, you know he's so easy
I didn't suck his we were talking about me
Pretending to suck dick on a shampoo bottle and then you're like actually I did that one time with my friend when I didn't get
But that thing in my mouth he squeezed it
Squeeze tube that he squeezed into my mouth him one stroke
So funny that that was the lead into this fucking conversation I
Completely forgot about that
Because I was so taken aback by - that I forgot that we were imagining you in your shower sucking off a shampoo
Everybody
Caleb, this would ruin everything.
- Everything we've built.
(laughing)
- Our empire would crumble if this was either of them.
- We were about to go mainstream.
- Well, I think we were on the precipice of mainstream.
- We almost are mainstream.
- That's what I say.
- You don't want mainstream appeal?
- Okay, that's fine.
I think Caleb will go mainstream.
- That sounded really real.
- Not really.
- I'm ready to go.
- That did sound kinda real.
- I'm ready to go to Aruba, Jamaica.
That's what we're gonna do.
- Oh, I just wanted to hear you sing.
♫ Oh I wanna take ya
♫ Jamaica, Jamaica
♫ Come on pretty
♫ Not to Jamaica
♫ Jamaica, Jamaica
♫ We're gonna go to Jamaica
♫ China
♫ No China
♫ Not China
♫ We're gonna go back to Jamaica
♫ Jamaica
♫ Not China
- Apparently, I don't know if you guys have heard about this,
but apparently China and Russia are teaming up
to start World War III.
- 'Cause of Brittany Griner.
- Because, no, because of Vladimir Putin.
Don't you hit the "bruh" button on me.
Bruh.
Don't you dare.
We don't even have one.
I had one installed.
Bruh.
(laughter)
See, I had it installed right there.
Here, press it again.
Wait, say the China thing again.
China and Russia are teaming up to start World War III.
Bruh.
Yep.
Damn, I didn't even think that Jubilee could do sound effects now.
Yeah, we have a human soundboard.
Oh my god.
Why didn't we think about that before?
This is gonna be really bad.
- I'm going to soundboard.com.
- Whoa, did you see the example sentence on that definition?
- What?
- It said, the example sentence is,
bruh, a male friend often uses a form of address.
Then the sample sentence says,
get off the internet and get a life, bruh.
- Damn, why would you choose that?
Just say like, bruh, pass me the handshake.
Nah, I guess that doesn't make any sense.
That's a lot of nonsense.
- Okay.
- Pass me the handshake.
- I couldn't think of anything that would pass.
- You kind of killed that moment.
Yo pass me the handshake
Yeah, that's me that hand so I can shake it say that well
No, that's like kind of too long and for past me yo, thanks. Oh, that's me. Oh
Pass me your thing
Talking about a hand get my naked ass over here. Let me get my naked ass over there. So I can shake your hand
That doesn't even mean anything
I've gotten to the point in my life where when I go to the gym and I get trained, I feel
comfortable getting completely naked in the locker room.
I like it.
I actually like it a little more than not being clothed.
You are going to be a menace when you're 60 years old.
Oh my god.
Yeah, probably.
You're going to be...
By the time you're 60 though, they're going to have developed some new way to catch people
like you and you're going to go away for a long time.
I'm not doing I'm not like I'm not looking around.
Oh tiny fucking penis gonna.
I'm just standing there.
You said you enjoy being naked.
I didn't say I enjoy it.
I said that I'm comfortable with it.
Yeah, but by the time you're 60, I will enjoy it.
Yeah, when you're it's you get a taste for it.
You guys keep more and more, you know, you're like a psychopath you kill a squirrel you skin it and then you know by the time you're 30 years old.
I have to kill a gay guy.
I'm gay too.
When I was at UNCW, I remember I saw one of my teachers,
I had my first day of class with my teacher,
and then I went to the gym, and then walked in,
I just met the guy, and he was my teacher,
and then I walked into the locker room,
and he was just sitting there with his balls out.
I was like, you should be able,
they should have a different, for that kind of thing,
authority figures should have a different thing.
- They should have a naked room.
- They should have every social strata should have
its own gym. - Definitely.
- Yeah. - Yes.
- Everything except for--
- Teachers' gym. - At the very least.
- Police gym. - But not cultural, only--
- Definitely teachers need a separate gym, yes.
That's like, yeah.
Have you ever seen one of your teachers smoking?
Teachers, honestly, you know people, you know when you're in kindergarten, people are like,
I heard the teacher sleeps in the classroom.
They should because you shouldn't walk around and see your fucking teacher holding hands
with some hunk.
It's always sad when you knew a teacher was single because it's like, you don't have.
It's like, I'm going to have to fill that void.
I'm going to have to step up.
I have to step up and show her a good time.
- You don't have a husband, so maybe.
- Maybe.
- Maybe I could be the one.
- Blink, blink, blink, blink.
- I'm blinking my eyes at the teacher.
- Bat, bat, bat, bat.
- You know what, you don't have a husband,
you need somebody to work on your house.
- Yeah.
- You need a worker around your house.
- And if you don't want me to be your boyfriend,
then I will just give you boyfriend vibes during class.
- And I'll throw all these roses away.
- He's my school boyfriend.
- I'll just give you.
- I'll just have boyfriend vibes.
Okay, listen, I can either be your boyfriend or I can give you boyfriend vibes.
I tried to be my teacher's boyfriend. I got her a Virginia Tech flag.
Wow.
Yeah, because she went to Virginia Tech and then that guy shot all her friends and I showed
up the next day and I was like, "Check this out."
I remember you telling me about that.
Yeah, I won it at Wilson's Family Arcade.
Whoa.
Yeah, which is a little funny to like, because that was the only school flag that they sold
and it was shortly after the shooting. And it's funny to be like running an arcade and
and then a mass shooting happens at a college,
and you're like, we have to order all those flags
and make them 50 tickets.
- Yeah.
- Because people are gonna want--
- Make them really cheap.
- Yeah, people are gonna want those.
- Yeah.
- The last arcade I went to,
the guy let us get prizes that was worth way more
than the tickets we had.
And I can't reveal where the arcade was
'cause I don't wanna blow up the spot,
but we are gonna go sometime. - No kidding.
That's not the last one you went to.
The last one we went to was the shooting one.
- Yeah.
- Bro, I went to Dave and Buster's recently.
- I wasn't thinking of that one as an arcade
I didn't get tickets true. I was bullshit. I went to Dave and Buster's recently and
I hit the fucking jackpot on that Thanos coin pusher
God, you're strong Dave and Buster's is the only good
Arcade because it's the only one so that plate place that we went that was a barcade
It was a places either have their prizes or beer
Yeah
And Dave and Buster's is the only place that has both and food and as place
I went to also had all those things and bowling - okay. Well, this is the most amazing
Is it Fun Spot in Laconia, New Hampshire?
Close to there.
It's in New England?
Yes.
And we're going to take a trip.
Fun Spot!
We're going to drive five hours to get to it.
You guys remember?
We should go to Fun Spot in Laconia because that's like the biggest arcade on the East
Coast.
This one is going to make you scream because they have a VR King Kong game.
They might have that at Fun Spot now.
And they have VR Raving Rabbids Racing.
Shit.
You guys remember when we went to Jungle Rapids in Wilmington and we played, we did a...
Did we do go-karts?
Yeah.
Yeah, that was on tour.
Oh, go-karting in Myrtle Beach.
God damn it, dude, it's so funny.
That we live like children.
We have this rock and roll lifestyle.
We went on fucking tour and we rode go-karts.
That is what rock and roll guys do.
That's true.
Dude, I don't wanna go on tour and do drugs.
I wanna do all the stuff I wanna do when I was a kid.
I guess it's a lot better that we're not doing cocaine.
Yeah, we're all like, wifed up.
We're not gonna go do drugs and fuck hoes on tour.
Yeah, no.
We're gonna go to Myrtle Beach
we're gonna eat is all you can eat seafood buffets.
- We spent so much money on a buffet.
- That is our version.
- I forgot about the buffet,
like it was us and then like--
- We're gonna stay at a beautiful hotel
with a view of the beach, look out the window one time.
- Yeah.
- And then close the curtains.
- Caleb's gonna throw fake dog poo
out of the hotel window because he got mad
that I put it in his hood.
- And it was there for hours when we went to 100 stores.
- We went to four different stores
trying to find an HDMI cable so we could play the Switch.
- Here's what wasn't funny about that.
- Memories.
- No, it wasn't funny about that.
I'm the one who bought the fake dog poop.
- You used it to prank me and then I pranked you back.
- The prank, you have to admit that that prank
was so much superior to the prank we did on Patrick.
- Our prank was that we just put it on the seat
that he was sitting in.
- It was very funny.
- He honestly did think it was real.
At least I didn't think it was real.
- You were coping so hard.
You were coping so hard.
We went to literally like four,
we went to the Piggy Wiggly.
I'm trying to impress the people at Piggly Wiggly and CVS and pretend I don't have poop
in my head.
See, if you had done that and we were in New York Manhattan, then I would have been embarrassed.
If I was walking around SoHo.
You were embarrassed, you threw the poop.
You threw the poop into the-
You threw the poop so- it's probably the farthest I've ever seen you throw something.
So I'm wrong.
You threw it from the hotel into the beach, into the ocean.
Past the dunes.
Threw it into the ocean.
Yeah, so keep talking about how strong I am.
And you're so embarrassed.
Especially when I'm in the middle of this funny thing.
It's not a strength thing.
It wasn't funny.
It was a crime of fashion.
It's not funny to make somebody walk around with a fake dookie.
Nobody made you do it.
You're the one who did it.
You were walking around.
You could have stayed in the car.
You could have checked your hood.
I could have stayed in the car.
I think I've thought about it a couple times.
I just wanted to go to Piggly Wiggly for the first time.
Piggly Wiggly was an amazing place.
Amazing it's so it's so fucking stupid how much I love find it like going to like
Chains that they don't have and like the northeast it's yeah
It is fun man
I've been just being like the South is so many of them to the south is like a completely different version of everything
Oh, yeah, yeah, you know use Bucky was amazing pig we cook out obviously cook out go to Smithfield
Entirely I want cheer wine so fucking bad. Yeah, we have our own sodas and
Why that's different I just that's healthy you're talking about a drink
Healthy shit if we were talking about his fucking diabetes
He's got day. I'm just thinking and talking about my life
Diabetes well Pat is writing a new stand-up bit about how I have diabetes
Really, I've been I wanna I that's why I was talking about Dave and Buster's. I want a new notebook and I've been
I got it for 550 tokens. I think so now he's writing an hour now. I'm writing my full
Joke I
Tried to test it out on Jubio this morning, and he got upset all right do it
Do you want to talk about this Jubio?
Well it was 9 in the morning he started texting me about fucking pants you had to wake up at 9 in the morning
I guess I woke up to ask him what he would let me let me read the text to you
Okay, well I sent the same text to you guys, but I'm reading the text for the prosperity
For the audience prosperity from reading it for prosperity
What would you think if I did a stand-up set about wearing long pants as usual?
So do it now okay, so hold on we gotta okay, okay, okay?
Next up to the stage very funny comedian. You've seen him on
- Yeah, but still.
(laughing)
Ladies and gentlemen.
- Say throwing foods.
- And throwing farts, his own one man show.
Here comes Patrick Doran.
- Wah!
(clapping)
- A bunch of people saying wah.
- I'm doing that.
- Yeah, okay.
- This is how I always go out on stage.
- Oh, kind of jeering.
Okay, I like it, yeah.
(humming)
(laughing)
(singing)
Sing the "Here's to the ones that we"
That's my walkout song.
(singing)
New York! It's great to be here!
New York City!
You guys gotta be the crowd.
Yeah, we are the crowd.
Can you give me like
Yeah, we are being the crowd.
Yo, Long Island stand up!
Staten Island, what the fuck is up?
- Wow. - Oh man, oh shit.
- Wow.
- Oh shit.
Ooh, I gotta say this.
I just got to say this.
So I'm in line at the store wearing my long pants as usual.
And then once I write the rest of that,
it's gonna be really good.
- Oh, that was just one,
I thought you were gonna be like,
just keep going and be like, yeah, and look at you.
- Maybe I, oh.
- Take a look at me now, guess what I'm wearing?
- My long ass pants. - I can change my whole
gimmick up, I can change my whole gimmick up on stage.
- What's your current gimmick?
- My current gimmick is that I really fuck up
every single time that I do stand up
and I forget most of my stuff.
(laughing)
- That's, you know, 20% true.
- I forget most of my stuff and I get up there
and I keep accusing the crowd of hating me.
(laughing)
- I do feel like-- - And I did that last night.
- How'd it go?
- Did not go well.
- You told them you hate me?
I woke up from a nap, Alex and I were trying to fix the internet
and he said, "I'm gonna go to this mic, do you wanna go?"
And I said yes, 'cause I have a couple shows coming up,
I gotta test some shit out, went to the mic,
got fucking bullet somehow.
- Nice. - Went first.
- That's first. - And I went up on--
- For people who aren't-- - All the civilians at home.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I think most of the people know--
- People who aren't comedically inclined.
- I think most of the people know what bullet means now
because of Green Room with Paul Provenza.
- True.
- But then I get up on stage,
I've been awake for 30 minutes.
- Okay.
- I get on stage and I say,
"Guys, I just woke up from a nap.
"I'm so sorry, I didn't think I was gonna go first."
- That was how you started your set.
By the way, professional comedian.
(laughing)
That is an entire job.
- My whole job, and I'm still going up,
and I'm still apologizing, right off the bat.
(laughing)
I'm still, it doesn't matter, I go up and say--
- At an open mic where nobody knows who you are,
Nobody cares at all.
Yeah.
And you're still going, I'm so sorry.
I'm so tired.
I'm so sorry.
And I tanked so bad that I drank 15 beers.
That's a ton.
No, I didn't drink 15.
I drank the equivalent of 15 beers.
In what?
The equivalent.
Dog beers.
I don't know.
Dog beers would be seven times as many as that.
But my new-- so my old gimmick is that the pandemic actually
fucked me up and I am still a little nervous to do stand up, but now my new gimmick is I'm
going to go out with the longest pants possible.
Oh shit.
I'm going up size 36, 51s, Levi's 501s, shrink to fit.
So once I wash them, once I wash them, actually then the waist has got to be way bigger because
it's going to shrink.
to go up with my 42 56 pants yeah and I'm walking around I'm like you see this
shit yep check look at this look at my long-ass pants yeah that's gonna be and
I'm do it I got like a dance with them I go like oh your catch your catchphrase
being a dance is yeah Patrick I mr. p tear that up that's what they gonna call
you mr. Pete tear it up mr. pants drag on them damn floor mr. mr. wedding train
you gotta have all his little cousins and nephews hold the pants as he walks
down the motherfucking stage damn yeah yeah was it in the shower
(laughter)
- It's actually a classic bait and switch joke structure.
So basically here's how it goes.
It goes, so guys, some weird things have been happening
to my body.
That's how it starts.
- Okay.
- I'm sucking this water bottle.
- So I have been completely, when I wake up in the morning,
I'm feeling a little nauseous and I'm getting cramps
and I don't even get my period anymore.
and I actually recently got an ultrasound
and inside of my stomach I saw a human infant.
Yup guys, I think I'm becoming a werewolf.
(roars)
- And you're saying all of it.
- And then I turn into a wolf.
(laughing)
- And my next, the next part of this bit,
the next part of this comedy show,
I'm gonna be sucking off this shampoo bottle.
(laughing)
That it's not my two best friends.
somebody walking up on stage with a shampoo bottle
oh i hate this guy another fucking prop comic
this is not my two best friends penis this is anybody but my two best friends
awww
what's my impression of me sucking on x1 but my two best friends penis
it could be my dad it could be a celebrity
awww
and then the final part of the gimmick is that he just squirts the shampoo into his mouth
and then you said it out but that's what you did
but it's not my new best friend
it's not their kid, it's somebody else's kid
it's not anyone else's kid, seriously
me when i'm sitting on the toilet and i
i've been sitting on the toilet for a long ass time and i get bored of reading the back of the shampoo bottle
I wonder what this is like.
I already read this thing like two full times.
What if I just suck it off?
Hold on, it's not my best friend.
You spit it the first time and the second time you swallow just to see what it's like.
I will say, jizz is probably about as palatable as shampoo is.
Right? I would put them on the same level.
No, no, no. I think if you heat it up, if you heat it up shampoo, it's probably the same.
You've never tasted jizz?
You've never gotten any jizz in your mouth.
Really?
Damn.
Gay.
Let's try it right now.
Yeah, let's try it.
You've never been trying to hit a bullseye right between your eyes?
You've never been nutted in?
But you didn't get to taste it.
I'm really sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I've never been
- It's never been come to my mouth.
- You take the shampoo bottle
and you like kind of like rim yourself with it
and turn to yourself going, no, no, no.
(laughing)
No, no, no, uh-uh.
- Not tonight.
- No, no, no.
You have to take me out first.
(laughing)
- The idea of somebody sucking off the shampoo bottle
is so fucking funny.
(laughing)
- I think the reason I can't do standup now
I can't do anything that isn't thinking about that. Yeah, I can't it's broken my fucking brain
I can't get up on stage without
Funny
Yeah, I got the conditioner bottle and the other hand I'm sucking off the shampoo bottle and I'm doing a little voice
I don't it's a conditioner. I'm like, honey. I'm home
What the hell is this?
I'm like, don't worry, come over here.
(laughter)
And you're not my two best friends.
Are you with the shampoo?
And these are shampoo and conditioner,
they're not my friend's penises.
No, it's actually, they are what they are.
You tie, you tie, you tie.
No, no, no.
These aren't supposed to be people I'm sucking.
It's supposed to be.
I'm married to the conditioner.
But the shampoo enticed me at the bar.
And you tie loofahs to the back of them to simulate balls?
You're grabbing the loofah.
Oh.
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah, I'm sucking off the shampoo.
But over-- little do I know, coming up behind me,
the body wash with a shotgun.
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah, your girlfriend walks into the bathroom one day
It's just like the shampoo and the conditioner both are just dripping little lines of each of them with the loop of hung like balls
I can explain this it's gonna take me a while to explain, but whatever you do before I explain it
Do not go to twitch.tv slash Cameron
(laughing)
- Don't look at anything on there
before I get a chance to explain this to you.
- Okay, okay, okay.
Now let me explain.
So, the shampoo and the conditioner
are just shampoo and conditioner.
They're not my two friends.
And they don't, they're shampoo and conditioner
that do not belong to anybody.
They don't belong to my friends.
So, these aren't their conditioners and shampoos
that I took from them.
- The Alexa is quietly playing behind.
- Birthday, birthday, it's my best day of the year.
Now that we got that out of the way, the loofah is supposed to be balls.
And...
Yes, I know you're thinking, "The loofah's supposed to be balls."
You're correct.
You're right about that.
But, the body wash is mad at me.
The body wash was on his way to come kill me.
But I was setting off...
He had a shotgun, which was soap.
Yep, he had a full...
It's a bar of soap.
I carved, I whittled a piece of soap.
Wittle and looking exactly like a shotgun and yes
I rigged it so that I could pull two little strings and make him waddle over and shoot it at me
And look and look look at this. I'm getting Eiffel Tower
The shampoo and conditioner we're doing it together don't look at my twitch cuz that's where I'm gaming and that's my
That's my person to think I made this video for you
There's a clip or I'm playing I'm playing like Minecraft
Like yeah, I hate my fucking girlfriend fucking takes away my fucking shit
Do not go to reddit.com slash the shampoo and conditioner guy don't look at the subreddit I posted
And also that's not my user
Shampoo and conditioner shampoo and conditioner suckers is
That's gonna make me laugh right sometime. I unfortunately I think that'd be so funny
Just trying to explain that on stage it's like no you don't get it. That's the worst
You can't do anything that is really funny
Anything that's rocks. No. Yeah, you have to do fucking stupid shit about the news
You can't go up and just say so my parents are getting a divorce. I you know I here's a scenario
I'm doing my little play, and I'm sucking it.
Which is what it is.
And I'm getting snuck up on by the body wash with the soap shotgun.
Yeah.
And some of the suds, the shampoo suds are going down my face, down my neck, down my whole body, whatever.
It's a thing of Irish Spring.
I look like Alexander Skarsgård in the Viking raid scene in The Northmen.
Uh-huh.
Shampoo cum all over my body.
Just covered.
I fall I hit my head on the corner of the tub I die
Billy Mays they bring a detective in the detective is like my god the body was killed
He was sucking off the shampoo and the conditioner caught him
The conditioner caught him yes, but then the conditioner joined
Lining up the angles and be like wait wait wait okay, so the suds came from this angle, and they're just seeing the body wash
My god
Just slides our victims unit that's the one time
Our victims unit that would be such a good show
Showers victim unit and then the tagline of that's like the poster. It's like it's Christopher Maloney. Yeah on the poster
at Law and Order S.V.U. Shower Victims Unit,
you're gonna wanna drop the soap.
- Damn.
- Boom!
- This Shower Victims Unit deals with crimes--
- Drop the soap!
(laughing)
- The Shower Victims Unit deals with crimes
that are especially sudsy.
(laughing)
Could be a very good show.
- And 99% of the episodes are not sexual at all,
they're all people who fell over in the shower.
- Yeah.
- Or like got--
- But then there's one episode where maybe like
30 minutes of the 90 minute show how long is it 45 minutes? I don't know 90 minutes 90 minutes pretty long
That's the 90 minute pilot. It's good. They're doing a two-parter 30 minutes of that pilot is
This whole shower thing that we're just yeah
Yeah
Did you just get a facetime? I got a call from Cedar Rapids. I got a I got a facetime from
Orville something I keep getting and I did not put my phone number out. I think it
You bill collector, I think that my medical debt is catching up with me. You got to start rapping at him. Yeah
Yeah, wow. Wow. Wow. Wow. Who wouldn't now?
Who is it now? Oh, that's a good idea
Ring back
Don't really know what that is so my call somebody and you hear it would play a song
So my cousin never even I've never experienced that in my life
My cousin has has one still because he wasn't able to cancel it and then the company that did it went out of business
I'm like horizon can't turn it off. So you call him. Why do you call him right now? Okay? Wait?
I'll call him right now. I will read your fucking number out on the air if it's a fan
Let's see
His name is Matt
I'll show you guys. This is what happens when you call him I
I should look this number up because they've called me twice in a row. Why the hell are you calling me?
What if he picks up? He got it fixed? No way
This ain't right. Dude it used to be some fucking Beethoven song
For real? What if he just picks up? What if he just picks up?
If he picks up I'll just talk to him
It's gonna you're gonna go to voicemail and you're gonna get his it's gonna read his entire number
Shit was so funny for so long
Wait for for 10 minutes. Yeah, you figure out what that number is
But it was yeah, you would call him until like last year and it would be like
What's the famous Beethoven song?
Yeah, it was that one. Really? Yeah, is that Beethoven? I just guess whatever that song I'd think of that as Beethoven
(humming)
- And he was like, and I was like, why did you say that?
He was like, I was 10 and I wanted whenever a girl
would call me to think I was really smart.
(laughing)
- Oh yeah, that works.
- That's pretty funny.
- I miss when you would talk to girls on the phone all day.
- Ring back, my brother dated this girl.
- I didn't email, I was never emailing.
- You ever do AIM?
- No.
- AIM instant messenger?
- My brother--
- AIM at the girls with my Nerf gun, pop, pop.
- My brother dated this girl in seventh grade
who he broke up with immediately after this,
but he was out one day, and she called every single hour.
- Wow. - She called the house,
every single hour, and was like, "Get father?"
- Well, that means she cares.
- Yeah.
- That means she cares about him.
- That means she loved him.
- Yeah. - Dude, I dated so many girls.
- She probably killed herself.
- She probably did.
- After they broke up.
- I dated so many girls in middle school
that I don't even remember their names.
- Yeah.
- Well, does your wife know you've been
dating middle schoolers?
- No, I could have done that to your brother
and I thought about it, but I said,
man, I respect Patrick's brother too much
and I wanna hit him with that joke.
I've been recently thinking that I probably
am losing my memory at a rapid rate.
'Cause I've been trying to remember people
who I was like close friends with in middle school
and I can't remember their names.
- I've been having, I'm sure this happens to everybody,
but I've been having kind of lightning strikes of--
It's Flint, that's Spark.
That'd be cool.
I've been having kind of Moses 10 Commandment moments
where I feel like God is handing down to me
the names of people that I went to high school with
that I completely forgot about.
I'll just be sitting around and I'll be like,
"Oh my God, Chris!"
Yeah.
I had that on the bus.
I don't remember anything.
I've had that too.
I had that on the bus the other day.
But then, is there ever people that you were like,
"Oh, I spent a lot of time with this person
"and I don't remember their name at all."
Yeah.
You don't get that?
Not really.
- There's definitely people whose names I don't know,
but that's 'cause I never knew.
- But you remember their face, right?
And you've definitely had a conversation with them.
- Face, I'm really bad at remembering faces.
- I'm pretty good at it.
- I'm pretty good at names. - If I could see,
I can't picture a face in my head.
- And faces. - If I see a picture
of them, I could get it,
but I can't really remember somebody else.
- I'm just really bad at remembering people.
- If you turned around right now,
I wouldn't know what you looked like.
- People were not, you're not meant
to know this many people, man.
- No. - You were meant to know
40 people maybe, and now I know like 1,000 people.
- My brain was, I think my brain was perfectly made
for knowing this many people.
- You remember everybody?
- I remember pretty much everybody.
- You're the next phase of evolution.
- Yeah.
- I think I just have enough plastic and stuff in my body
that like the names get stuck.
- Honestly, I have more people,
I forget more people from like the past year than I have,
like there's a bunch of people that I--
- Well just you're at that age now.
- Dude, if I forget a person's name,
I feel like a complete fucking asshole.
- Yeah, I go like this, uh!
- I'm the opposite.
- I mean it definitely is.
if I don't remember somebody's,
like the other night when we were hanging out with Dan,
Dan got a haircut and was wearing glasses though.
- No, you fucked up.
- I did fuck, I-- - How did you forget Dan?
- Yeah, I know, that was cut, that was really honestly fucked.
- That was fucked up of me, and Dan, I'm so sorry.
- Dan, how could you forget that?
- You can't roll that back.
- I'm choking up right now. - Amazing smile.
- His smile is like so precious.
- He had new glasses on and a haircut.
- And he had the same attitude though.
- Yeah, he had the same smell.
I could smell his pheromones and recognize instantly,
this is Dan.
If I was blind or like a shark, I could've known.
- If I was literally not human, I would've recognized him.
- If I was a rock, I would've known that was Dan.
- Dan, that is love.
That is much fucking love.
- That's right, Dan. - That is a lot of love.
- But yeah.
- That also happened to my friend,
my friend Nat grew his hair out,
and he got a beard,
and he came up to me in a coffee shop and was like,
"Oh, nice shoes."
And I was like, "Oh, thanks, man.
"What the fuck are you doing?"
And I got so scared.
- Yeah, I think that I'm gonna start--
- It's scarier when you see somebody--
- I'm gonna start claiming that I have some kind of
like disability that makes me forget people's faces.
- Yeah, face blindness?
- I think I kind of do have that a little.
- I thought I had face blindness for a while,
but I think what I actually have is a thing
where you can't imagine anything.
- Oh, when you imagine an apple, what are you getting?
- Nothing, I don't see anything in my head.
- Whoa.
- When I imagine an apple-- - That's scary.
- Yeah, I didn't really realize I was--
- You get zero?
- Yeah.
- Dude, you realize that you're less than.
- I know. - Me.
- Yeah, well actually, here's what's interesting,
is I realized, I think that's the reason I can read so fast,
'cause I don't have to imagine anything,
I just read the words.
- Yeah, I go about one word at a time, very, very slowly.
- That's why you don't wanna read,
I've never seen you read an erotic novel.
- I read a lot of erotic novels.
I just finish-- - For real?
- And I just finish writing--
- And that's why you like movies so much,
'cause I can just imagine a movie any time I want.
- Yeah. (laughs)
- But you have to watch it.
- I can see stuff in my head,
like sometimes I get close to the veil.
Sometimes I'm like--
- You do have to practice it.
- Well, there's sometimes there'll just be something
where I think something happens
and I can suddenly see something in my head
and then it goes away.
I really think I've been chosen by God.
- I have this thing.
- I think you probably have too.
- God has been pressing down on my head from here to here.
- You've been getting into the Bible recently, right?
- Yeah, I did study the Bible.
- How's that going?
Where are you at?
- I have read very little so far.
- It's pretty boring.
- I'm gonna take that one home.
It's actually really not, I mean I'm reading a translation.
I think one of the translations.
- Which translation?
- Stephen Mitchell, Book of Job.
- Oh, okay.
- And it's one of the ones where it's like a poem.
I'm starting with the Book of Job.
- I'd rather read the Mitchell Hurwitz Book of Job.
- You should read-- - Okay, buddy.
That might actually be the reference.
- Don't read, you should read King James Version.
- Yeah?
- That's a serious Bible, dude.
- LeBron wrote that one.
- KJV.
- Oh my God.
- Don't read NIV.
NIV is like, they try to make it sound
like a fucking, like a YA novel.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Don't read that shit.
- No, it's so crazy and beautiful.
- Yeah.
- The Bible.
- You're talking about picturing things in your mind.
Picturing an apple.
I, when I visualize an apple,
I visualize the most beautiful, delicious apple in the world
and I cry because I'm allergic to them
and I can't eat them without my lip swelling.
- You're allergic to apples?
- We already did this.
We said his favorite fruit was blue raspberry
and lemon lime and stuff.
We did it really recently.
- We did it yesterday.
- See my brain just doesn't--
- Your favorite food is bubble gum.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
I did have some--
- No but I do have this thing--
- I had some bubble gum the other day.
I was--
- You have bubble gum?
- I had some bubble gum.
But it was Sam gave me some big league chew, man.
(laughing)
You got really excited.
- I got so excited.
I thought you had big league chew on you.
- Sam gave me some big league chew and I like,
he handed, the thing is with that,
there's no real portion size.
- It's so--
- So he handed me a pinch,
but the pinch was like,
it filled up half my fucking mouth.
- It's so funny that people chew.
- It's like when you chew a...
- It was made...
(laughing)
It was made to look like old chewing tobacco packets,
but they don't even make those anymore.
- Yeah, they do.
They still make chewing tobacco like that.
- Oh yeah, they make...
- Plus it's based on baseball.
- Native American man.
- Just thick cut.
- I'm not calling it what it says.
- You're not calling it what it says at all.
- We got one.
- True.
- Native American.
I learned something about Native American culture recently
that I can't remember what it was.
- Wow.
- So again, just keep going.
- Okay.
- You should get like a turquoise necklace.
I have one.
- You should.
- I had one. - Do you need to go back?
Okay, if we went--
- I don't think I have it anymore.
I had one as a kid. - If we were--
- I had a turquoise and with a rattlesnake rattle.
- If we were driving through Arizona again--
- My great-grandfather gave it to me.
- If we were driving through Arizona again
with that same knowledge that you now have,
would you have been going into those gas stations
and buying just everything?
- 100%. - You'd be fully decked out.
- It's like literally a million percent.
I would be so fucking decked out.
- That is so awesome.
- Yeah, so.
- It's like when me and him go to fuckin' Ireland.
- I'm also, when we go to Boston.
- I have nothing.
- You have, well you just don't have to exclude me.
- You should start wearing a scally cap.
- That's literally the only trait we share
between the three of us.
Other than that we're completely different.
We're like circle, square, triangle.
- You imagine him in like a fuckin' Thomas Shelby hat,
like fuckin' Peaky Blinders.
- Should I go full Peaky Blinders?
- You should go Peaky Blinders.
- Next episode, if you are not pullin' up here
in a full fuckin' Peaky Blinders suit.
I'm a little bit interested in trying out my new style.
Yeah.
I could get a peacoat, right?
Who watches that show?
What demographic is that show?
My dad.
I watch it 10 seconds at a time on YouTube Shorts,
where he's like--
I like when he goes--
He punches a girl with a cane.
I like that one.
It's also--
Cillian Murphy?
He's so cool.
He's very, very cool.
He's the Scarecrow.
Yeah.
And he was a lady in the movie.
When I was in 28--
One of the most beautiful women I've ever seen.
What I don't like about that show
is that there's no earthly way that in,
what time does that take place?
Like the late 1800s or something?
- 1980s.
- No, it's not.
- It takes place in the 1990s.
- Yeah.
- Takes place in, it's Ireland.
- It's not the 1980s, it's like the 1920s.
- It takes place in the 2010s.
- No, it's like the, it's the 10s.
- That's what people dress like in the 80s in Ireland.
- The point is, in 1915,
there's no way you're getting a haircut like that.
- Yeah, yeah, there are.
- There's no earthly way they're cutting your hair like that.
What you that may be true, but also a lot of these things are cycles
And a lot of times a haircut you get in 2023 is exactly the same as when you got in 1983
Remember when that was like the the high and tight like the Macklemore haircut was first coming on the scene
Then Richard Spencer took it down
Yeah, yeah
BOW BOW BOW
Because people were going my mom
Got one
Got one. No, my mom was like I saw this guy
At a bar last night. I thought he had the coolest haircut
I asked him like what the style was because I think you would like it. He was like oh, yeah
It's an old Hitler youth haircut
People were fucking walking around calling that haircut the Hitler youth yeah, I mean yeah, well
Yeah, what but that's like what people were fucking listen like that fella. He already got a mustache. You can leave the hair alone
You can ruin one hair style, and it's a mustache. Yeah, you know you don't get the hair, too
Yeah, you already took down the greatest mustache of all time. Yeah, it would have been legend everybody be rocking
There's the dude the dude from Sparks had it wait. Give me your finger Japanese guys had
The Hitler stash for a long close-up. You'll watch it. He would look so good if we can rock that
You'll watch a Japanese movie. I fucking hate him so much
Dude you ever seen a you know sparks the band that guy I am gonna flip you off in your face
Okay, you know I wasn't because of that I just don't want to talk about the band sparks that guy had a Hitler mustache forever
Yeah, Japanese guys were still trying to make it work in like the 60s. Yeah. Yeah, well they can do that
Yeah, cuz I think they can't I think they're the ones who really can't do that. Yeah
Japanese can't do it
Buddy, have you ever heard of the world war two?
But here's an idea I thought of for a name for a parody movie that I just thought of this is like the next
This is gonna be the next scary movie. This is gonna be the next disaster movie. Okay, it is a cuz we've gotten so much fucking zombie bullshit
Walking dead last of us, etc, etc. You look like a huge fan of the last of us right now
You look like the the kid from up. I was about to say you look like a Pixar character
Yeah, you look like the kid from up right now
- No.
- You look,
(laughing)
you don't look human.
- I look,
- You look like a fucking egg.
(laughing)
You look like speedy bulpy.
- The whale.
- You look like speedy bulpy.
- I think I could,
(laughing)
- Guys I'm having so much fun today.
- A, but it's a zombie parody movie.
And it's called,
Drumroll, can I get a drumroll?
- That's the title?
- 28 movies later.
- Wow.
- 'Cause there's been fucking 28 zombie movies.
- You know what I would do?
I would do a pizza parody called The Last of Crust.
- Ooh.
- And it would be the end of the pizza.
- The Taste of Crust.
(laughing)
- Dawn of the Bread.
- Oh my God.
And then you could do The Walking Bread.
- Yeah.
- And Day of the Bread.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Have you seen this?
- How many zombie movies?
Zombies 3?
- Zombies the movie, it's like a musical
that was on Disney+.
- Oh yeah, I've seen all three of these.
- Joe put that on when we first moved in together.
Joe put that on and made me watch it with him.
- That is bullshit.
- That's not right.
- Motherfucker.
- He gave me, he said that I could have some of his food
if I watched it with him.
So I watched it.
- What kind of weird transactional food friendship
are you in with Joe?
- You know him.
You know how he acts.
- Yeah, he is a weird guy.
He is weird.
Do you ever have friends where you're like,
like both of you, I would probably pay $2,000
if I could have just go into a time machine
and just watch like one day of what your lives were like
before I met you.
Yeah. Really?
You know, like growing up and just be like.
Growing up, how far back are you going?
I've told you a good chunk of stories.
What's like the most, the crucial boy year,
probably 13, right?
16.
16?
Yeah.
Not for me, man.
I was basically smoking weed the entire time that I was 16.
- I was smoking so many cigarettes.
- What grade is 13?
- Eighth. - Eighth grade?
- I think I was designing a website
for most of that year. - You would have seen me
making, yeah.
You'd have seen me, like you'd go summer 2011,
I'm 13, I'm making fucking YouTube poops.
- When I was 13, I think I basically was watching,
who's that guy who made really terrible sketches
on YouTube, Julian something?
- Oh yeah, Julian Smith. - I remember him.
- I was watching Julian Smith and I was like,
I think I'm gonna do that shit.
And me and Chad would sit and make YouTube videos
that we never uploaded.
- I think I was probably playing Minecraft
in eighth grade, playing a shit ton of Minecraft.
- And I definitely had just discovered--
- And TF2.
- I had just discovered,
I think I just watched The Usual Suspects
and I was like, dude, movies are fucking amazing.
- That's probably also around where I watched Fight Club
and was like, oh my God.
I think I watched it like 10 times or something.
- Yeah, I used to watch all that shit so much.
- I said that around the same time.
- Summer 2011 is when I got in trouble
for, from the Comcast Corporation,
for copyright infringement
because I downloaded Saints Row 2.
- Damn, I had the same thing for Sniper Elite.
- I got a letter in the mail that said
if you illegally download anything anymore,
you are fucked.
And then my little brother got us in trouble
for downloading Taiyo Kru's Dynamite MP3 on Utorrent.
- Come on.
- He got us in trouble again,
so he got us our fourth strike,
I think it's like six strikes for copyright.
- Oh, that's good though.
You could download everything in five downloads.
- I'm thinking that it's funny that,
but in like, yeah, back in like late middle school,
early high school, I watched the movies I liked
like a hundred times in a row.
And it's so funny to think about,
that's like when your brain is like,
it's like Play-Doh, like you're developing.
You're like, I'm gonna watch,
like I would never watch a movie
more than like one time a year now.
And back then I was watching like Fight Club
like 10 times. - Me too.
- Whatever you did in those years.
- This is probably not doing anything to me.
- They say whatever you did in those years
is what you will do for the rest of your life.
- Yeah, it literally ruined me.
- And I was literally playing Tribes Ascend
and listening to WTF with Mark Maron.
- Holy shit, I forgot about fucking Tribes Ascend.
God damn.
- I had a, my mom got me this refurbished Windows XP laptop
and the only game I could run on it was Fallout 2.
- Nice.
- So I was playing Fallout 2
and making YouTube poop music videos.
YTP MVs. We need to man. I was listening to Block Party. We should restart YouTube. I don't
know what that is. That band. Really good band. I don't know what that is. I still listen
to them. So. Music wise. No Jermuk Hotel. Yeah I was probably getting into that. Yeah.
And AFI. Yeah. Alright. Well. That's the episode. Let's say Saturday. What do we got? Anything
coming up? I don't know. Are you? Is your stuff already? Saturday the. Are your tickets
already all unbuyable.
Yeah, I mean, I guess there might be some tickets for tonight's show in Providence.
And then next, I guess I can start on like the end of March.
I think I'm going to Raleigh.
What are you bumping around, Drew Bio?
I think I'm going to Raleigh to do good nights in Raleigh.
Do I plug the fucking New York show I'm doing?
Uh, sure. Go for it.
Okay, I guess.
Live Forever at BCC, March 11th.
That's gonna be me, my roommate Alex, and our friend Benny Feldman is hosting.
Amazing.
Alex is also hosting, and then I think I'm on Tiny Boys at Bushwick Public House.
Why are you laughing?
Yeah, what's funny about that?
Because I'm thinking about a tiny boy.
Who's doing stand-up.
On the 28th, I'm gonna be at the gym. I'm gonna be running maybe a mile and a half, two miles in the morning.
Two miles?
two miles. Maybe a McGriddle afterward as a reward if I do a long run. And then I think
I'll probably be headed home, maybe do a little writing, a little research on various topics.
Probably going to eat lunch around two. Then I'll be waiting for my girlfriend to get home.
Once she gets home, I'll ask what she wants for dinner. Then maybe I'll cook some fish.
And then that night I'll probably be on Fortnite. On Tuesday night. Do you guys not care about
plug? I have just as much a record of my stuff as you guys. Should I just fart into the microphone
right now? I might be in Boston. Oh wow! I'm gonna be in Boston around St. Patrick's Day.
I'm probably gonna do some shows. Oh and the March 20th I'll be having a road test. I need
to go. Alright, bye!
(laughing)