(upbeat music)
- All right, notice anything different about me?
- You're gray sweatshirt challenge.
- He's wearing fucking pajama pants here.
- Sissy, you wear a gray, no, it's not that.
- What the hell?
- He's wearing pajama pants.
- You are, bro, what the fuck?
- He doesn't treat this job like it's a fucking thing.
- And you have a stain on your nipple from your lactation.
We have a very serious dress code.
And it, go change.
- Yeah, what is it?
- Go change.
- Black on black on black.
- Go change right now.
Put on real pants.
- Uh-huh. - Okay.
- What was that?
- I was gonna maybe, I could snap.
- And plus we have a one drink limit,
so you have to throw one of those away right now.
- What the fuck is wrong with you today?
- I don't give a fuck 'cause I had--
- He doesn't give a--
- And he just checked his phone.
He turned his phone on and was looking at it.
- This is what it's like dealing with me, isn't it?
- All right, scrap the episode, it's over.
- This is what it's like--
You guys are being babies.
(static)
- You could, why don't we have the whole setup
with the computer?
- Yeah.
- Why not just do it on the, this makes zero sense.
- You can suck my, oh, is this, are you sad?
- That was pretty good.
- That was really good.
- So don't come for me today, okay?
I had, I got two hours of sleep because I drank
an extra strong coffee ice cube.
- Oh no.
- Yeah, so.
- You were supposed to go.
- You might not wanna mess with me.
- Noah just moved in.
We were supposed to go out and then he said,
no way am I going out.
Meanwhile, he stays up till four in the morning or something.
- I didn't know that I had a disease that made me sensitive.
I've become so sensitive to caffeine that I can have,
I'll have four sips of this coffee.
I'm scared to even have one right now.
- You know what that is?
- What?
- We're syncing up.
- I was thinking about that.
I think you and me are syncing up.
I also feel like maybe I've gotten a little smarter
and you've gotten a tad bit stupider.
(laughing)
- I think we've been syncing up for a while.
- Yeah, you're not syncing up with anyone yet.
- Yeah, it'll take a while for me to sync up.
- It is coming though.
- So if you start speaking Spanish,
I think we'll know who he's syncing up with
or spending time with.
- Donde?
That is fucking Spanish right there.
- I never listened to Donde, was that good?
- Hola cabrones.
Yo soy, yo soy.
- Don't call me a cabrone.
- Yo soy muerto.
- You pendejo.
- Whoa.
- Me llamo muerto.
- You pendejo.
- You can't say that about me.
- Me llamo muerto.
- Ooh.
- Where, you're dead?
- I am death.
That's my name is death.
- You're not death.
- Mm-hmm.
- Well, you're just hovering your finger over the--
- That's 'cause you never know when I--
(laughing)
Never know.
Give me any topic.
- That's why it's your new phone.
- Oh, that was actually the number one thing
I wanted to start with was that I got a new phone.
- It blew up just now.
- No, that's just like any time you say something awesome,
you press that button.
- All right, try this one.
- You know, I--
- Brah.
- I gave Caleb my old phone and it was the,
it still had camera access to it.
- I broke it in a week.
- He loves, that phone is gonna be gone within two days.
- No, that phone is like--
- It's toast.
- He has no case on it, no screen protector.
Actually, you do have a screen protector.
(laughing)
- Fuck you, bitch ass.
I'm gonna break every phone I ever have.
I don't even know how you do it.
Dropping.
You drop it a bunch?
Hold it up in front of stuff and drop it.
I would stand up at the aquarium to take a picture,
and I'd get on some guy's shoulder, get real high up
to take a picture of a very tall fish, and then I'd drop it.
I dropped my phone probably 7,000 times.
The phone that I gave him--
And I only broke it 6,000 times.
But I've never had a case of a single phone over that.
This was the last phone that I had that could still use
CamWow for the iPhone.
Except for this one.
Remember that?
Remember the CamWow?
And I shattered it.
He shattered it into a million fucking pieces.
I fucking destroyed that phone.
- He had like a phone that had the screen was hanging out.
- I have an old iPhone that's in my house,
I'm never gonna give it to him.
- My phone had a--
- He's gonna beg for it next week.
(laughing)
- The phone Patrick gave me,
I somehow, I've never seen another phone do this.
By the end, it's in my desk.
It has a hole dead in the middle of the screen
where you can see all the way through.
It looked like you can see like the CPU
through the middle of the phone.
- How did you do that?
- I don't know, man.
- He's trying to fuck his phone.
I must...
You have no respect for technology.
Yeah, you wish you had a soundboard.
He made a hole in the middle of the phone screen and then he looked up lube app.
Lube app to make phones slippery.
No, but I was downloading all the old...
And the vibration app.
Okay, I was downloading all the old apps onto my phone.
I was looking through all the apps that I've bought over the years and there was five different
vibrating massage apps that I guess at some point I downloaded.
- Not even gonna touch that one.
- But I don't know, I don't remember.
- He was trying to touch that one.
- I'm guessing it was--
- He was trying to touch his one.
- I'm guessing it was for a joke,
'cause that sounds very funny.
- Yeah, that does sound like something.
- But if you do--
- That was not a joke on you.
- But I don't know really if it was a joke.
- Yeah, I don't think it was.
- I might have been putting the corner of an iPhone,
and this was back when they had sharp corners.
I might have been putting the corner of my iPhone
right in my ass.
- They never had sharp corners.
- Not, yeah, okay, rich kid, you had the S,
you had the smooth version of every iPhone.
No, I'm just thinking about the iPod Touch.
Remember when the first kid got the first iPod Touch?
It had a 90 degree angle.
Oh yeah.
No, it was rounded.
Nope.
It was rounded.
Then you guys are the rich kids.
You saw the very first one that I never even saw.
Exactly.
Beveled.
Nope.
It was beveled.
Never had a sharp horn.
Never was sharp.
No, no, no.
Beveled.
You're wrong.
I'm right.
Whatever sound you're about to play applies to you and not me.
The next sound you play is about you.
Guys, I don't want to use a soundboard.
I don't want to use...
I'm Micah Jackson and I'll be telling you to pick up your phone, Shimon.
I'm a smooth, invisible, pickin' up phone motherfucker.
Truth my best elf, that's right.
What the fuck was that?
What was that?
Why did you open up voice memos and play that?
I don't want to use the soundboard on you guys.
I want to use it to lampoon events and news.
Let's think of some stuff to lampoon.
Give me something to have a take.
Oh there's some big murder trial.
Oh the Murdaw?
Yeah, the murder murders.
Yeah, buddy if you didn't want to go to jail. He's in there lying so he doesn't go to jail.
Buddy if you didn't want to go to jail,
maybe don't kill your entire fucking family.
[Gunshot]
That's what he did, yeah.
He didn't explode them.
And here's another thing.
Ice Spice. You seen this girl?
This is what your music sounds like.
No, Ice Spice.
No. Ice Spice, here's a new...
You're not in control.
Ice Spice, your new music video with Pink Pantheress,
you dress, you look like a toddler.
And this is what your music sounds like.
You ruined my point, you fucking asshole.
She DM'd me last night.
Ice Spice, you look...
Why is she dressed like a toddler in that music video?
Look what Ice Spice said to me.
She says, "How are you doing
and how is life treating you, beautiful face?
I always see you liking my page, pics, and comments.
Thanks so much. One more time again.
and please always be good.
- Tell her right now. - Oh my God.
- Say, hey, put your belly button back
in your fucking shirt, you hoe.
- I said, "Hello, Ice Spice, do you love music?"
And then she said, "You should know what I love, fans,
"and how are you doing?
"I'm very pleased to read a line from you.
"I sent you a follow request here
"because I see you always liking my posts and uploads.
"Thank you for your continuous love and support.
"How long since have you been my fan
"and been listening to my music?"
and I said I love music and singing.
And she said, yeah you should, Mr. Patrick.
Music is life. - Mr. Patrick.
- Bro, you are fine. - Dude, I have,
I learned recently that I have undeniable riz.
- Ice Spice is DMing you and you're saying,
I love music, what do you say,
fucking give me some pussy?
- No, yeah, Mr. Patrick.
- Yeah, Mr. Patrick.
She's talking to you. - That's your nickname.
- Mr. Patrick.
- Noah already calls me that. - Yeah, my name's Patrick,
but a lot of people call me Mr. Patrick.
- Whoa, you got new buttons on that soundboard.
- You have so many buttons.
- Holy crap.
- Help me, Carl.
(laughing)
- You know, you gotta do this once a year.
That's how I feel.
You need to do something like this once every single year.
- The soundboard?
- Yeah.
Yeah, just one time every year.
Just somebody has to do it.
And this year, because my mental capacities
are definitely neutered because of how many hours
of sleep I got, especially REM sleep.
- Can I tell you guys something too?
I also--
- You put him to sleep.
I'm also not operating at 100% today.
Yeah.
I'm actually hella stressed out because,
and I think I already told you guys this,
but my driving instructor just broke up with her boyfriend.
Dude, I saw that shit.
Wait, hold on.
I saw that shit on the news.
My driving instructor just broke up with her boyfriend.
It's got me stressed out.
I play like bruh.
Or like womp womp womp.
How do you spell bruh?
Bruh.
B-R-U-H.
Wait, hold on.
Oh, I got it.
Say it again.
so might i'm hella stressed out of my driving instructor and her boyfriend is
broke up
the
i'm thinking once a book in your we do this does this is a bargain by the
you get you have so many buttons into the gun every time
you think that's a gun
yet you don't know what a gun sounds like
How is that not a gun?
- That was an, those were two different sounds.
- Somebody reloading a gun and then it exploded?
- No, I have explosion.
Let me run you through what I have.
- Well yeah, 'cause you only used one.
Now what I know you have.
(gun firing)
- Here's gun.
They're different.
(laughing)
- They are different.
- How could I not tell the difference?
- They are very different.
- Yeah, they're pretty different.
- What else do you got on here?
- Man, fuck you, just keep going
and I will show you what I have.
- I'm more intrigued with the soundboard.
Yeah, you can't just act like it's not here. You have to really run through it.
I do have Fun Sounds Volume 42.
If we can't even see it, you gotta just go.
You guys wanna see the soundboard?
You just have to do something with it.
Wait, you really wanna see the soundboard?
Yeah.
Fuck you.
See, that's what I'm talking about.
Do you wanna hear anything from Fun Sounds 42 with swearing Indian on it?
Wait, I...
Can you do it again?
Okay, that's scary. I don't like that. I'm gonna uninstall this
You can't do multiple of these I'm drawing a hard line
What sucks yours is terrible yeah, yeah, do you BEO even under yeah, you even played that
That's that soundboard sound was called Mexican guy saying this sucks. Yeah
that after the Indian guy won. Yeah. What the fuck's going on man? Anyway, we'll come back
to it. We just jinxed ums. Yeah, of course we did because we're fucking amazing.
What was that one? I don't know what that was. Alright, you know what, I'm going to
put this away for now. But just know that at some point I'm going to have a take and
I'm going to have to use my face ID to open up my phone right after I say it. And it'll
take me 30 seconds. It'll be a delayed explosion because I closed my phone, but I'm fine with
that. Yeah. Let's just do today's episode all about...
I think I... What kind of bike do you have?
I'm serious. I'm dead fucking serious. That one wasn't even good.
Yeah, you have shit... You don't like that one?
You downloaded a... Tina, come get some ham!
Okay, I kind of like that one. But that's your last one. I'm cutting you off. You of
all, of all three of us, actually including Jubio, you're the last person... You dangled
the soundboard in front of me. You're the last, you're the last person. You dangled the
I said no because I had it dude. Yeah, do you you're coveting thy neighbors?
But I am come on boy. Are you kidding suck my balls? Are you kidding me?
I would love to have a sound boy a fable called keeping up with the pits is
And oh, yeah rolls you can not everybody can get what what the pits is have actually fucking beautiful
Yeah that actually solved this whole thing
Instantly solved that yeah, I you've ever watched keeping up with the Kardashians and try to keep up with them
Oh my god first of all himself
I
Fucking knew that you were gonna reach for the sound immediately. Yeah, wait keeping up with the Kardashians. You got an edge
It's pretty easy because they're fat
That would have been would have been funny without it you ruined it
Yeah, it would have been funnier with a difference. It would have been funny if you did a fist bump instead of the sound
No, I'm not giving you anything. It's nothing that was not good. What if I did it without even looking
What if I seriously did it without even looking yeah, cuz I'm so good at the soundboard do it. I don't have to look
nice
You're this is how he breaks his fucking phones all the time. You have heavy fingers. Don't you?
fuck
I didn't, this is a long one too.
All right, well, just close that, turn that.
There you go.
(laughing)
All right, let's talk about our lives.
Let's talk about things that have happened in our lives
since we last spoke.
- Oh!
- And I'm gonna finally take the first sip of my coffee.
- I'm no longer in Bushwick, Brooklyn.
- My driving instructor's boyfriend
did not get her flowers.
- Oh yeah.
- On Valentine's Day.
- Wait, wait, did she explain, so tell me how--
- So here's the drama.
Tell me. Give me the tea.
She, on Valentine's Day, she said her and her boyfriend
were not doing something for Valentine's Day.
I was like, "Oh, really? That sucks. I'm sorry."
And she was like, "No, it's okay. He was in the hospital."
Yeah, hospital.
Yeah.
He was in the hostel.
And that's what I-
Getting sucked off in the Red Lake District in Amsterdam.
Yesterday, the song "Flowers" came on the radio.
♪ I can buy myself flowers ♪
And then she was dancing like this.
- While she's instructing you?
- Yeah.
- Well, I know what to do.
- Oh yeah.
- So she's just not like driving.
- Hey, you can do that when you're in the passenger seat.
- But doesn't she have her own wheel
and her own steering brake?
- Just a brake.
- Oh, okay.
- She doesn't have her own wheel?
- No.
- Did that ever exist?
- They had a--
- That's probably impossible.
- I was in 21 Jump Street.
- The driving instructor I had in 2013
had a wheel, he had a Prius with two wheels on it.
- So you had a driving instructor 10 years ago,
Still can't, 10 years of driving.
Still can't drive.
- Well I dropped out, I dropped out of that class.
I've talked about that driving instructor before.
- What do you--
- The guy who rates all the babies.
- Yeah, you've talked about him a lot.
- Yeah, it's the funniest thing ever.
- What is the thing for you that's so hard about driving?
- I don't know, we don't have to get into it on the show.
- Why?
- I don't wanna talk over his driving instructor's boyfriend.
- He's scared of traffic cones.
- Yeah, traffic cones are the scariest part.
He thinks it's candy corn that his car wants to eat,
and he starts going, "Doo doo doo doo,"
eating all of them, driving right over.
- His driving instructor is going through
a fucking hard time, and you wanna talk about me?
- Did she, okay, I hate to ask.
- So wait, I didn't, I'm sorry.
- She's dancing.
- Yeah. - Singing.
- Flowers.
- I don't know the rest of the words.
- I don't know the words of it.
She said the, I can buy, yeah.
So she, that's, well that makes sense,
because she said, "I can buy myself flowers,"
and then she turned to me and she said,
"I have to buy myself flowers
"'cause my boyfriend didn't get me any flowers.
"Yeah, we broke up."
- Shit.
- And I said, "Oh, I'm so sorry."
And she said, "Yeah."
And then I didn't understand what she said after that
'cause she doesn't speak English so well.
- Oh, man.
- Isn't that really hard?
- It's kinda cringe.
- It's tragic.
Really, you think so?
- A little cringe.
- Oh, I guess I shouldn't have brought it up.
- It's cringe for your driving instructor.
- Some irony bros like you guys probably.
- It's kinda cringe for a part.
I'm actually all new sincerity and shit.
And I'm post-ironic now.
And I think that, honestly, we should have your driving instructor on so we can like...
She would love to.
...teach her how to like...
...give her like a makeover.
I want a new...
There you'll be.
She doesn't need a makeover.
She dresses...
Every item of her clothing has Mickey Mouse on it.
Really?
Mickey Mouse shirt, Mickey Mouse pants, Mickey Mouse backpack, Mickey Mouse sweatshirt.
You know who she reminds me of?
Literally, completely Mickey Mouse.
We know who she looks like.
Who?
Mickey Mouse.
Explosion.
Oh.
Fuck.
What we do, we get her in here, right?
Yeah.
With a surgeon.
OK.
Surgically graft her ears to the top of her head.
Yeah, I like where this is going.
Right?
You've piqued my interest.
Then we get her maybe like some back fat or something,
or like some body part.
We can elongate her nose maybe a little bit.
Does Mickey have a long nose?
Mickey's got a--
He's got a circle for a nose, right?
Yeah, it's not a long--
He doesn't have a nose like this.
I think he has a Pinocchio.
Okay, but you think a human has a Mickey nose?
But it would have to be smaller to be a Mickey.
Yeah, yeah, we're closing off this part.
I saw a guy with a Mickey Mouse nose on the street the other day and he looked like a
monster.
Really?
I saw a guy this morning, I saw a guy this morning, just moved into my new neighborhood
and I walked, walking down the street, this guy is covered in like dollar store like beads
and stuff.
He's wearing like a green top hat with like shit all around it.
Leprechaun.
And he has two bags.
Oh, I know that guy.
I was like this motherfucker is about to give me a quest.
- Did he have-- - I know.
I know that something crazy is about to come.
- Was he playing music?
- No, he wasn't playing music.
- No, that guy plays music usually
and he switches between--
- I think it was too early in the morning.
- Sometimes he's Irish,
but sometimes he's full American flag suit.
- Yeah? - Nice.
- And he walks down the street, he plays music.
- He looked incredible. - Last Friday night.
- He's an old guy? - Yeah.
- Yeah, he's the man.
Yeah, and he'll walk in the stores
and he pays for stuff with just coins.
Damn.
pervert lives on my street is three feet tall.
I didn't know Caleb moved in on your street.
If I had the soundboard that would have been fucking sick.
Too bad you don't man.
Too bad you don't.
How do you know that he's three feet tall?
As I see him.
Oh, I mean the other way.
How do you know he's a pervert?
Took a picture of my girlfriend.
through the window. No, he's standing on the sidewalk and he went like...
Did you try to...
Well, there's just something...
Did you see him or did she tell you?
No, I saw him like at the last second and there was something in my brain where I was
like, "I can't...
Yeah.
No, you can't beat...
I can't...
Even if he's a pervert, he's three feet tall, you can't beat him up.
Yeah, I can't say... Well, I wasn't going to beat him up. I was always... I can't be
like... I feel like even in my brain, there's a block against being like, "Hey, man, what
- What the fuck is wrong with you?
You can't say what the fuck is wrong with you
to a guy who's three feet tall.
- Especially 'cause maybe he was doing--
- Specifically that phrasing is very dangerous.
- Especially, dude, the worst thing ever would be,
he's like, right, you yell at him, right?
You yell in the back of his head,
he turns around, he has a Google Maps shirt on,
and he's taking a whole stream of photos, right?
- Yeah, he's adding, making an add-on for Google Maps
where it shows little pins on all the girls
who live in the neighborhood.
- Yeah. - Exactly.
- Or you can click restaurants at the top
and you go to the side and you can click girls.
- Girls should be chipped like dogs.
We should be able to track them wherever they go.
- You should be able to buy girls in a bag like chips.
- Yep, or like goldfish.
- Yeah, but no, there'd be too much air.
There would just be way too much--
- What the hell, there's only one girl.
- They should be in tubes like Pringles.
- Yeah, that would remove the air problem.
- Females, buy a female in a tube, right?
You go to a whole, you go to a store and they have--
- I hate these, the fucking female tubes are too small
to get my hand into.
- Women in tubes like the motherfucking
wands in Harry Potter.
- Yeah.
- Oh, it has to fall off the shelf
and roll towards you like that chef
from a barbeque commercial.
- And then you go to pick one
and the guy at the store's like,
"No, you can't pick one.
"That one belonged to the Dark Lord."
- Oh my God.
- And it was Hitler's girlfriend.
- Ava Brown.
- It's Ava Brown.
- Oh, you guys know her name?
- Yeah, she's fucking hella hot.
- He said it first.
- No, you said it first.
- Did I?
(laughing)
- Ah, rats.
You guys got baited. I would never claim to remember anything about Hitler.
I don't even remember what he looks like, and I'm going to the barber later.
[laughter]
Yeah. So that's pretty awesome. He had a pervert encounter.
Yeah. It was a while ago. I just remembered it now.
Did you look up family watchdog after?
Let me see if I can find the tiny...
I don't know what family watchdog is.
Oh, there's a site that he knows cuz he's got Google alerts on first name. Oh
It's not working any minute now there's a website my money man any minute no he didn't know how to turn his phone volume up
I gotta give you that one. Yeah, I just panicked and I hit my name Jeff
Sorry, it's a website where you can see all the perverts in your neighborhood. Yeah, I didn't know about it
- Yeah, my mom looked it up
'cause there was a guy in my neighborhood
who kept trying to talk to me about comic books.
- Oh yeah. - That's called a fuckin' nerd.
- They should have a nerd registry.
- Nerd registry. - I agree.
Nerds, you should have to register as a nerd.
- I hate nerds. - You're going around
the neighborhood with like--
- I just wanted to know.
- The court is legally required.
- I am an nerd. - I regret to inform you
that-- - I'll be up till 3 a.m.
every night studying. - The court has ascertained
that I must be not allowed within three feet of a bookstore.
- He only gets one word out at a time
and the doors just keep closing on him over and over again
until he says the sentence, I only.
- That would be good in a movie or TV show.
- That's how I think because I've seen so many of them.
- Yeah, you think in movies and TV?
- Give me any scenario and I'll write a script right now.
- Okay.
- I'm basically a writer bot.
- Three friends sitting at a gray table with microphones.
Fade in. Three friends sitting at a table.
Fade in.
A gray table.
Gray table.
With microphones that are gray, pink, and green.
Sorry, are you the writer bot or am I?
Yes. Well, you have to get the input.
Yeah.
Yeah, so I'm giving you the scenario that you asked.
And they're wearing headphones, black headphones and pink headphones.
Okay, I changed the entire thing. Swipe up.
Swipe up.
You see three friends are sitting at a gray table.
Their microphones are different shades.
One blue, one pink, one green.
What?
each representing their personality.
- This one's gray.
- One of them seems very tired.
- That's more of a periwinkle.
- What?
- That is more of a periwinkle than a gray.
- Well that's just gray.
I thought it was blue.
I thought that was blue until you put it
next to the gray thing. - Maybe I'm color blind.
- That's the exact same color as the wall.
Wow, doesn't that look a little blue against his white skin?
- Yeah, no, it's like that.
- It's not that color.
- It's not periwinkle, no.
It is pretty much periwinkle.
Okay, well, my movie's over.
That's a pretty good movie.
I guess my movie's fucking over.
Yeah, good.
Well, we actually just wrote the script, didn't we?
I just got the...
It bombed at the box office as well.
It was a huge bomb.
It's not gonna get a sequel?
And I'm never gonna work in this town again.
No, you could work in Branson, Missouri or something.
We should go do spaghetti podcasting in Italy.
That is such a good idea.
Isn't that the best idea I've ever had right now?
Okay, where it's all dubbed over.
We change the...
Oh wait, you meant like spaghetti western.
[Laughter]
I'm open to either.
I thought that you meant we go to a restaurant with this in the middle of the table.
And we just slurp noodles.
And we eat a bunch of...
That already exists, it's a mukbang.
What's that big... what's the... is it Ketchup... Kakao I Pepe?
Ketchup.
Ketchup I Pepe.
The one where you eat it out of the big wheel of cheese?
The big wheel.
Yeah.
We just get a big one of those and we eat just spaghetti the whole episode.
That would hurt.
I have some kind of gluten intolerance.
Something happened to me.
Okay, we can get chickpea pasta.
That stuff sucks.
And he's like, what was he, like 20% Italian?
He's allergic to pasta?
Yeah, because I'm...
His own ancestors hate him.
Oh, yeah.
I could have told you that.
That's way too far.
(laughing)
- Hey man.
- We don't like talking shit about ancestors on this show.
- Leave my, say what everyone about my body,
talk about my current, talk about my immediate family,
my beloved, my betrothed, my future children.
But if you talk shit about my ancestors,
we're gonna have a serious problem.
We're gonna have a real fucking problem.
- Well your future children are gonna have brown teeth.
I know that for a fact.
- You know what that's called?
♪ Evolution ♪
- Korn.
♪ It's evolution ♪
♪ Evolution ♪
- What?
- Yeah, that's another part of the same song.
♪ Celebrate ♪
- That was a different song.
- That song sucks.
- Evolution?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, that's probably their worst song.
- That album is so bad.
- Korn is just terrible.
- Is that the one, what album did that come off of?
Untitled?
- Jesus, that's how you know it's bad.
- That was the one where they started having--
- They didn't even want to give it a title.
- There basically was a Christian invasion into Korn.
Oh monkey or head right?
Well now also I think monkey is too.
Wow.
Someone else and now there's two of them.
They wrote all those songs about getting molested.
No that was actually, that album,
Untitled, not sorry to be a corn historian here,
that was actually the Christian Exodus.
That was when the Christian guy left the band.
They made that album and it sucked.
And then he came back and it was good again.
So big surprise, the Christians were actually the glue
holding together the entire group.
Like some podcasts.
(laughing)
- Like some podcast where if the Christian left,
it would be a disaster.
- Uh-huh.
- Who knows?
- We don't have a name Christian.
- Yeah, I guess it's Jubio.
- Jubio's Catholic, doesn't count.
They go directly to hell.
They don't even get judged.
Yes they do, they worship a false idol, Mary.
- And Pippin.
Mary and Pippin.
Lord of the Rings.
- We're hitting it out of the park today.
We're knocking--
I'm destroying, I'm crushing, I have a soundboard.
- You have a crutch. - First of all.
- You have a crutch with that soundboard
and then I tried to do what you're doing.
- You're like a-- - 'Cause I'm also tired
'cause I had to help Noah move in last night.
- Sorry, wait, how many hours of sleep did you get?
Did it end with an O?
- Oh, did either of you guys have a trauma
within the group, the person that you see twice a week?
Did that happen to either of you?
No, I don't fucking think so.
So, Jalel. - No, no.
- Shut the fuck up.
- Yeah, we need to listen to him.
- You've never had a driving instructor breakup.
His driving instructor is going through a very hard time.
Do you know how long I have to be in the car with her
while she's been broken up?
45 fucking minutes.
Oh my fucking god.
Two days a week.
Do you know how long the car that I learned to drive in was?
This big.
10 feet, it was a limo.
You are a molecule.
He learned in a limo.
I learned how to drive.
That's how fucking terrible I am at driving.
Look, that's why he's dressed up like his day off.
His day off.
He's supposed to be in a tuxedo right now.
I've been walking around, I keep my keys.
'Cause he doesn't have his car today.
I asked him for a ride in,
'cause we're lunch buddies now, we're neighbors.
- Why are you talking such hello fucking shit
on my clothes, bro?
- You're wearing disgusting work
and you got stains on your clothes, bro.
- Guys. - People look at us now.
- Okay, how long-- - This could've been,
this shit could've flew like six months ago.
- How long have you guys known me?
- 10 years. - Probably four years.
- Four years, right?
And when are you guys gonna get it?
- I've known him for 10 years.
- When are you gonna get it through your thick, thick skulls?
- He hasn't known me for 10 years,
but I've known him for 10 years.
- Get it through your thick skulls.
I don't give a fuck about anything,
because I'm amazingly cool.
So stuff like this doesn't matter to me at all.
You guys dressed up.
- I got some of your coffee.
- You guys look like you are working for a band,
backstage moving speakers,
and I look like what?
The lead guitarist.
- You don't look like the lead,
you look like the guy there not letting into the van,
'cause he smells too bad.
(laughing)
Somehow you smell bad enough to not get let into the--
- You can have the rest of that, it's kind of hurtful.
- To the metalcore show.
- You have a metalcore, it's your heart.
- Yeah, hard, cold as iron, no mercy.
- That's why you-- - 'Cause I don't give a fuck.
- Became so rude to me in the last recent episode
that we were doing.
- That was really good.
- And if you ever wanted to see me
snap a lid off of a bottle, today's your day.
Bye.
- Snap a lid off of a bottle?
- Somebody didn't go to fucking my school.
- Somebody didn't go to my school.
That was see now. He's got coffee in him. It's just in his hands. You know he's feeling radiating energy coming off of this guy
He's like a fucking that people do the thing at you got a red eye
Where you pop the you got a water bottle you you twist it and then you jump on and it shoots the cap
You know we used to that shit was so sick. You know we used to do was kill animals with yeah, we
You know the hood milk cartons like the little tiny well
I don't know why I thought hoods the only one that made those well
It's like you know it's cool. No you guys know that hood is just a New England. Yeah, I know that that's so we
I didn't know that yeah, yeah like that like the
hood see
These yeah, what Walberg talks about Boston slang, and he's like oh a hood see that's just like a little tub of ice cream
Yeah, I didn't know I thought I thought that's a girl. I didn't dick
I didn't realize until this very second that I haven't seen a hood see since I haven't seen a hood see cup in
- That's crazy. - Going back to Boston
for the same patties though. - The little wooden stick.
We should get some hoodsies.
- We gotta go get some hoodsie coats.
(laughing)
Dude, I want that strawberry one.
I'm thinking about that right now.
- Sitting at the bar drinking Guinness, eating hoodsies.
- I'll stick with my frozen yogurt, thank you very much.
- Dude, a hoodsie and a Kelly's roasted beef sandwich.
(laughing)
And also we're in Boston fitted,
Boston fitted Celtics sweatshirt,
or Patriots sweatshirt, Celtics.
I'm in my Bruins PJs.
- Bruins PJ pants, Celtics sandals.
- Yeah, and you're eating hot cross buns.
- You don't get it, you don't understand.
Yeah, hot cross buns are a big thing in Boston.
- Whatever happened to hot cross buns?
I feel like I used to hear that song all the time
in elementary school and I never hear it anymore.
- It was a one-hit wonder.
- It fell off.
- I don't know who made that,
it was probably Akon or something,
but definitely people don't listen to that shit anymore.
- Yeah, sounds like a damn Lil Yachty song.
Yeah, when I say put on that old school.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah, put on that old school.
Camp town races, ooh!
Damn.
I hear camp town races pretty often.
Yeah, that was my song.
Well, it's 'cause you're always on a carousel.
Yeah.
That's your driving school.
(laughing)
On a carousel.
Yeah, I guess Hot Cross Buns is every other kid's song
you'll hear once in a while
'cause it's an ice cream truck song or a carousel
or it's in a TV show, but Hot Cross Buns sucks enough
that you will never hear it again after you learn to play the piano the first time.
You learn it on the recorder.
Yeah.
That is until you guys come to my daughter's wedding
and it's the daddy-daughter dance.
[LAUGHTER]
[HUMMING]
Literally the worst song of all time.
Just sobbing.
Just like, you have mascara on and it's going--
I can't believe I'm giving away my baby girl.
--running down your face.
And it's played on the recorder by your nephew.
It's becoming so funny to me to say Hot Cross Buns is the worst song of all time because it's true.
It has to be.
It's literally the worst song ever.
It's the worst song that qualifies as a song.
Yeah.
It has an original melody.
I fucking hate that song.
But it is terrible.
Well, that's the thing.
You lot of people haven't heard the 12 inch remix or the 12 inch 12 inch dance
mix of hot cross buns. Hot cross buns has to be the only one of those songs that
nobody's nobody's ever mixed by. Nobody's ever like we got to hop on hot
cross.
We need to get OVO for to do hot cross buns. They fucked it up. What do you
think that song's about?
One a penny, two a penny, even the lyrics.
We need the rap genius verified on Hot Cross Buns.
Hot Cross Buns, one a penny, two a penny, Hot Cross Buns.
I didn't know that it was one a penny, two a penny.
I just thought it was hot, hot, hot.
Get that ready.
Wait, hold on.
Hot Cross Buns, lyric, what, who?
Give him a second.
Yeah, give me a second.
Wait, are you ready yet?
He's a mad.
Hot Cross Buns, who wrote the lyrics for this song?
Lil Pump.
(laughing)
- Fuck, doesn't that feel good?
- It does feel pretty good.
- It's like an amazing punctuation, dude.
- Oh man.
- Yeah, but that song sucks dick.
- We're basically in the--
- I never wanna hear that song again in my life.
- In the lunchroom, we used to take the hood milk cartons
and if you fold the tip of it into itself
and you just get it real flat on top
and you just fucking slam down on it,
it sounds like a gunshot.
- That's pretty cool, yeah.
Just do that in the cafeteria and scare the fuck out of everyone damn. Yeah, we're crazy now
I'm imagining don't you hate when?
Y'all kids were motherfucking crazy
Don't you guys hate when you get in the you get in the uber and the uber that they're playing rap music
and then the Uber driver gives you a look in the rear view
and then switches the playlist and starts playing Hot Cross Buns.
(laughter)
You know what else we used to do in middle school that reminds me of that
is you ever do the thing where you had "get ready"?
I got you.
You take paper towels or toilet paper and you get them really wet
and you throw them up on the ceiling of the bathroom.
(rap music)
(laughter)
That shit was so sick.
Yeah, we're different back then.
When people found out how to do that and it just went so over people.
Every time someone would go to the bathroom,
they'd throw like six of them up there,
and they're just like 100 slimes
on the ceiling of every bathroom.
- I wonder if I've talked about this before,
but in eighth grade, we found out
that you could take the mirrors off the wall
in the bathroom.
(laughing)
- Like they were just hanging?
- No, you could just, if you pushed up on one,
the mirrors in the eighth grade hallway,
you could just pull them off the wall
'cause they were just shitty and old.
So it was a growing problem.
They had like a meeting with everybody
and they were like, if you take those mirrors,
like you just take them off
and then hide them in a stall or something.
Or like take the mirror off
and then just put it like behind the trash can, not in it.
And we just kept taking the fucking mirrors off.
And all like, just, if you fuck,
if we see the mirror gone one more time,
none of you are going on the eighth grade DC field trip.
It is not fucking happening.
- That's so sick.
- I still get worried every once in a while
when I look up to the ceiling
and kind of in my peripheral vision
think I see one of those sticky hands
just stuck there forever.
You know, 'cause those would just never come down.
- Those leave a stain. - I ruined my family's wall.
- Yeah.
I ruined my family's wall. (laughing)
- How?
- With the sticky hand?
- Oh, yeah.
- Mom, I ruined the wall with the sticky hand.
My sticky hand ruined your wall, ma.
Sorry.
It did though.
Yeah.
It was a hand print.
I got a sticky--
It's like slapping a woman's ass.
I got a sticky hand at Dave and Buster's last time I went.
I got some from the dentist several times.
Or a second the last time I went.
You got sticky hand from the dentist?
Damn.
That's hot.
I'm never going to the dentist again.
I keep thinking you're gonna like have a sound ready.
Yeah, you're just browsing.
You're just doing Instagram but with the sound board.
Hey, Jubia, do you have anything to say?
Just say one single thing for me.
No.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Got him.
That's very rude.
[Laughter]
That's not nice.
Julio, you have the power to soundboard him whenever.
But you can't, you don't actually have the power.
You have the power to soundboard Caleb into a position.
I'm a professional.
You're not a professional.
You're afraid of my sound.
I am.
I think you are afraid.
You're afraid.
You're too afraid.
You're typing gay with two A's.
Gay sex videos.
No, do not play gay sex porn videos.
Because I'm going to get horny.
Actually, some of those looked okay.
Explosion sound right now.
See, if I had it as a physical board.
We need more sound effects and more like, you know when you see somebody is starting
a podcast for the first time and they've spent a lot of money on a little studio in their
apartment and they have a soundboard that they keep pressing whenever somebody says something,
we need to revert back into that.
That's so sick, man.
We need to make this look like it's the first time we've ever done a show and we're just
sitting there and we're telling just the worst story in the world and somebody hits the,
"Damn!"
We need one of those.
We've always needed a really stupid producer.
- We need to get rid of Juvia.
- Juvia's too--
- Juvia's too just normal and kind of tame.
We need like a fucking really, really dumb guy
that we borrow from fucking Gas Digital
to come over here and press buttons,
press fart buttons for us.
- Yeah, yeah, he just sits there and hits like,
finish him, and it's like it makes no fucking sense
in the context of the story.
- That should be the only one we have.
- Yeah, so I talked to my mailman
for the first time the other day.
- Finish him.
(laughing)
- What?
finish finish finish finish kill kill mailman every word text to speak that was
funny I love you I think you guys are slowly inventing Stephen Hawking yeah
not slowly at all no that's more it's less like Stephen Hawking it's more like
- And he was a scientist. - Like the master
from the first Fallout game. - And he's a scientist.
- And he was a scientist, he didn't invent himself.
- Damn, damn.
Finish him.
- Yeah, how ironic is that,
that the greatest scientist who ever lived, right?
Greatest inventor. - Was in a wheelchair.
- No.
No, the ironic thing there is that he's a--
- Somebody missing the whole point,
somebody missing the whole, like,
it's like, yeah, no, it's so crazy.
Stephen Hawking was in a wheelchair.
- The craziest thing was that he himself
was invented by God.
- Yeah.
- That's fucking crazy.
That is a bit of a mind-blower.
- I still can't believe he's dead.
No, that's really getting me.
Somebody just be like, that's crazy.
- I don't understand.
- People say that.
- That's what people say about him.
- People say that all the time.
- That's not an odd thing at all.
People are like, I can't believe he was so smart.
- No, it's that he talks like a robot.
That's the thing.
- No.
- Well, it's that his body shut down.
- It makes sense that a scientist talks like a robot.
Most scientists talk like robots.
- I guess it's not really ironic at all
that Stephen Hawking was like that.
- No, he had Futurama bonitis
and he just sat in a wheelchair for 40 years.
It makes sense that a scientist would live in a machine.
He's like Max Headroom, where he'd...
Max Headroom? What about Max Headroom?
He's a computer man.
Oh, really? I thought Max Headroom...
I'm thinking of Max tonight.
Stephen Hawking just out of nowhere, just like...
"The theory of..."
I don't see Max Headroom. That's not in my reference pool.
That shouldn't be in yours.
The one 40-year-old listener...
You somehow, through your entire life,
You have grabbed all of the worst media
from every single decade and just stored it
in your head in a perfect vault.
So that you have all of the really stinky bad things.
- Not true.
- Yeah. - Stinky cheese man.
- That's one. - Let's get back
on stinky cheese.
- Stinky cheese man. - Let's talk about that again.
- I don't remember why we brought it up the other week,
but I will say that's a funny fucking--
- I remember exactly why.
- Oh yeah, I remember. - Funny, well.
- We're not gonna get back into it.
We'll leave it.
- Leave it. - Leave it, leave this.
- Leave this right now.
And I keep looking at that tube over there.
Which tube?
The blonde ass tube.
Should use that for something.
The black tube?
Oh, oh, the tube.
Can we just get the tube?
Go get it.
Go get the tube.
All right, hold on.
I'll get the tube.
Go get the tube.
He's going to drink his drink out of the tube.
Whoa, hold on.
Caleb was on some super power shit today.
No, no, the tube.
Look at this.
Caleb is drinking Marvel juice.
We have too many tubes over there.
The one on top of the shop vac.
Oh, that.
Right? Shouldn't this be used for something?
Well, Caleb tried to use it.
I'll have to look at this one though.
Here, can I have one end of it?
Okay, now you hold this up to your ear.
Okay.
Hey, T-Tip!
Can you hear me?
If my headphones were off, I think this would sound cool.
Hey, T-Tip!
No, it's all cut in the middle.
Yeah, it's probably the cut that's ruining it.
If this tube was like a full...
Alright, this can just be on the table.
I just really couldn't stop looking what
That's what I said when you guys pull out this fuck who cares about this - pulled out the tube
You made me I wanted to talk I didn't I wanted to talk about cool looks on the table
It looks like a fucking normal
If anybody's still listening to only audio this is gonna be the thing that pushes you over the edge. You gotta see others
Look at this tube
It looks incredible. It's squiggly and silver
- Tattoos that people get.
- If you are listening to this podcast,
I want you to know you are fucking your entire life up.
- Oh yeah.
- Clicking on the video version.
- Click the video.
- Looking at this fucking tube.
This is ludicrous.
This is maybe the best.
- This is ludicrous if he was a worm.
- This is the most fun I've ever had.
Right here.
Wow, that is some fun shit.
Oh my God.
All right, but now the tube needs to go
because this is too distracting.
- The tube needs to stay.
- This is way too distracting.
- Just leave it on the table and relax it.
Just relax it.
Hey.
Chill.
Stop that right now.
If I was a worm, what would you guys do to me?
I would put you...
I would do this.
I would go...
You'd put him down in front of your pants.
Yeah.
And you'd get lost.
I'd be a biting worm.
You would...
Worms have teeth, right?
You would die...
You would die in my fucking puke.
Actually, I would not die because there's so much dirt in there.
It'd be perfect.
You would travel for a worm.
- You would die in my pubes.
- Your fertile soil.
- You would die in my pubes like into the wild.
- When you're at the gym and you stand up too fast,
a bunch of soil falls out of your shorts.
- His penis is razor thin, so you'd probably
fall through there and get, it'd be two of you.
- And then I'd regenerate and I'd be two, yeah.
- I'm gonna tell you straight up,
you're thinking of jellyfishes, not worms.
- Worms do that too.
- Worms do that. - Jellyfishes do not do that.
Worms are the things that do that,
and jellyfish are not. - You never grab a pile
of worms and just try to rip it all apart.
- Yeah, you've never tortured worms to make mayo more?
- No, I tortured bigger stuff,
'cause I actually had balls. - Like what, jellyfish?
- I tortured jellyfish. - You tortured jellyfish?
- I would catch jellyfish.
- And you're not even, you're not even,
you're thinking of the wrong-- - And they have no
pain receptors, and I would torture them.
- You're thinking of the wrong animal.
Anyway, you're thinking of starfish.
- Yeah.
- You're thinking of this dust dump
that I just rubbed on you, that's what you're thinking about.
- Lizards can do that too, with their tails.
- They can't make a new fucking lizard.
- They grow a new tail.
- They grow a new tail,
and then the lizard goes on the other side.
- And with a, okay, with a worm--
- With a worm or a starfish, let's be real, those are tails.
They're not making a new animal, they're living tails.
It's the same thing.
- You're not gonna get more scientific answer to--
- You're a Christian, you're not scientific.
- He's a Christian scientist.
- No, I'm the Christian scientist.
- No, you are genetically a Christian scientist,
but you are not--
- I'm a practice, I have no,
listen, in a moment of weakness, I went to the doctor,
they charged me $20,000, I'll never be back.
- Oh yeah, you were doing that sleep study
or whatever the fuck?
- No, that. - Or your blood work.
- Yeah, I had blood work.
- Or any other thing?
- Yeah, I went to the doctor.
- The checkup or the-- - Yeah, I had a checkup.
- Or chemo or dialysis. - Or chemo.
We don't really have to talk about my medical thing
except for that I'm never going back to the doctor
ever again. - I think we do.
I really wanna go get voluntary dialysis
'cause I do feel like it would make me feel a little better.
It's like when-- - What is dialysis?
- Dialysis is where they electrify your entire body
until you die. - When you call your sister.
- Oh, isn't...
Oh!
- Yo, that was good.
- That was, I had to look into the distance.
(laughing)
- I actually don't know what that is.
I think they put some vitamins in your kidneys.
- Yeah, yeah, it's what you get if you only drink
like, muscle energy.
- In my brain, dialysis is like an altered carbon
Blade Runner kind of thing that you just do to old people.
- Yeah.
I don't do something to them because I just there's I the only reason I think that is there's a
Walk by sometimes a dialysis center. I see a bunch of old people in wheelchairs. They just leave on the curb
Have you ever been what like walking down the street and you see an old person and you're like?
if I like ran if I ran fast enough I
Could just run I could just like drywall. Yeah, just run right the flash and turn in to turn them into red mist. Yeah
Because I've been to in our neighborhood in our new in our neighborhood because we're neighbors now
I
Have seen a lot of old people who look like that and I thought what if I just do it?
Yeah, if I just run what have you at the speed of light?
Ruesome public murder ever executed that's what you think
No, no, no, I run through an old person like it's it's not a murder if they turn into red mist
Then they get to be like a force girl
First of all if you see if you're serious about this
We're gonna have to start fucking training
NFL combine style because you there's no way you can reach a speed high enough that you can red mist a fucking old you don't know
You are slow bro. Stop you are the slowest of the three of us. Yeah, there's no doubt in my mind
That is a hundred percent true. That's my short legs
Because you have no you're in short roasting his L's yeah, you got your a he just you didn't have to say so
You're all fucking torso. You're built like the lobster from fucking spongebob. That's true. Yeah, okay
That's you. Yeah, right your torso your head and listen
I love your torso, and I love your head, and I love fucking I love this I have this barrel thing going on
What are you saying? Yeah? It's you're not fast cuz you're not aerodynamic
What see that how it goes down like weird you just you are
Stupid you're talking about your rib cage
No
I've got that the fucking the pectus carinatum or whatever the thing the thing that pokes out
So my whole fucking thing is all if you keep talking about pectus carinatum. Yeah, I
Don't know how to pronounce it contagious
You're gonna get it. You're gonna get you could use a little bit of it. Yeah, I know what it is. It's this
It's when you're it's a shirt
See how like that things poking out right there. Oh wow you do you have a horn yeah?
I got a horn my fucking shit. Yeah, I wouldn't call that a bit of a shirt off never seen a barrel like let's take a look
At it. You've seen it before I've probably oh
You're a fucking sick freak. I have this weird thing. We're on my blades on the back. There's the other one
There's the other one pectus is excavated
I have the exact opposite. Yeah, I've never seen someone with the
Out I see a million people with the in yeah a lot of people get the in you get the out around when you like
You're 13 and then your mom looks at you at the pool the public pool and goes what the fuck is wrong with you?
You should have been wearing a binder. I had one
It looked like snowboard bindings with maxi pads, and I fucking we've talked about this
You think now that I remember it you're right that we have yeah
I don't remember, but you are you need to get your bones shaved down if you ever want to be an actor
Do you guys ever see
You guys ever sit walking down the street. You see a really old person you think if I
Threw it back on you. I could give you more pleasure than you felt in 30 years
That's kind of the opposite of what I was saying. That's the no that's not the opposite of you what you're saying
That's the opposite of yes, man. Remember. Yes, man. Oh, yeah, no lady says
Let me suck your cock. He said hey guys moving a dresser
And then he's it says the most incredible orgasm
He fucking comes right in her mouth. Yeah, imagine her
Afterwards
It was me if it was me, and I was in that situation
I was doing yes, man, and that lady asked me that I'd fucking kill myself on the spot
Yeah, instead of say yes for real you wouldn't fucking old lady. What's the oldest person you would fuck ten thousand I mean
Okay, no mummy
Oldest person no mummies that you would fuck cuz obviously if you've seen the return of the mummy
Then you know that there's hot mummies. Yeah, mommy is stir crazy hot
in that? Probably 115. 115? You'd fuck this guy. Yeah. You would fuck that guy. This guy,
look at his, is that one tooth? Look at his bean right there in his mouth. He has one
bean that he eats a day. Ugh, dude. Look at that bean. I don't know. Dude, I don't want
to be old so bad. I'm definitely going to die when I'm 50 by choice. If you, if you,
- They should come up with a work plan.
- I'm definitely gonna, I'm gonna--
- 50, that's early.
- Yeah, no. - You're halfway there.
- I think that's the easiest--
- You're halfway done? - You're halfway to 50
and like most of what your life so far
has been being a kid.
- Yep, that's it.
Once my bones stop working, once I stop being able to jump--
- I would rather be dead than not be a kid.
I saw-- (laughing)
- I saw this thing-- - I literally, I--
- You're being like four and being like,
"I'm gonna kill myself when I turn 18."
I literally I have no desire to like have gray hair.
I have no desire.
I can't wait to have gray hair.
Steve Martin.
I wish I could have gray hair tomorrow.
No, like I don't want to like--
as soon as I start, the only thing that I can eat is soup.
Like I'm fucking--
You think a 50-year-old-- well, I guess you, yeah.
I'll never get there, dude.
You're going to have your teeth--
I'm so gross.
I'm a longevity man.
Yeah, I'm ready to go.
I don't want to see my grandkids smile.
Why?
Because they're going to be smiling and say,
Look how weird Granddad looks.
- I only like Grandpa when he gives me candy.
- Yeah, you have a-- - Fucking, I hate my grandkids.
I hate my grandkids.
- I'll say this right now,
I cannot wait to experience the love of my grandchildren.
(buzzer)
- Yeah, it was--
- No, no. (laughing)
No, not that one.
There we go.
I cannot, I think that the love between grandkids
and grand...
- Well, you have a good relationship with your parents.
- Oh, here's something I was thinking about the other day.
- It's the number one.
- Do you know what I realized?
Maybe this is a stupid realization,
but I realized like, oh, when you're a kid,
like the toys that you have and you play with,
your parents choose all the toys you play with.
Your parents completely control that.
- Holy fucking shit, wow.
- So when I have kids, I think I'm gonna get--
- Fucking wow.
- I'm gonna get my kids all of the like,
just a bunch of fucked up like secondary characters
from like tie-in toy lines from movies
that nobody's ever seen or will ever see again.
- You're gonna go on eBay.
- Because yeah, they'll be playing with some shitty toy
that like, and they love it,
it's their favorite toy in the world.
They never know what it's from.
And then one day they're like 25
and like Johnny Mnemonic comes on TV
and there's something like, what the fuck?
(laughing)
That's my toy.
- You're gonna go on eBay and look up like
a lot of McDonald's characters.
- Yeah, specifically stuff for movies and TV shows
and stuff so that they have a chance to see it.
And they realize that--
- Like you're gonna get like the little teacup thing
from Beauty and the Beast, that's gonna be their only toy.
- It's a bunch of made for TV movie tie-in toys.
- Star Trek villains that were only on one episode
that they made an action figure of.
- Yeah, exactly.
My kids are gonna be like, "Can I have a T-Rex?"
- That literally, my mom would do that.
My mom and my aunt would go--
- You can have the Indoraptor
from Jurassic World, Dwarven Kingdom.
- My mom and my aunt would go to the flea market
and just get the, just like, "Oh shit,
"that's only a dollar, shit, my kids want toys or whatever."
But the difference between that is I'm curating it
for maximum psychic destruction.
Real quick, my kid will have a cronk.
A cronk?
Your kid will have a crank.
Your kid's gonna grow up and be a graffiti artist
like a fucking new generation.
Oh yeah.
My kid's gonna have a crank that he can turn
to power all the stuff in the house.
That's a good idea.
Did you guys ever have a shaker flashlight?
Yeah.
And you practiced jerking off with it?
You shake it.
Not a shaker, I really just had a crank.
I had a crank and a shaker.
No, you should have a shaker flashlight.
- I didn't have the shaker.
- Yeah.
- Wait, where's the people on this bottom rich?
- Where the fuck is my brother?
- Yeah.
- There he is.
- Wait, you did that to your brother?
- Yeah, shaking fucking shit off.
- Where the fuck is he?
- They're running around the house shaking them.
- The power's out, I'm scared.
- I'm so scared, I'm so scared, I'm so scared, I'm so scared.
There he is.
(laughing)
I think there might be a ghost in there.
- Right here on the, where is he?
Where is my brother? Where did he go?
He's it!
Or no, I'm it!
Got him.
So simple.
Mom, I'm playing Manhunt.
Just shaking that shit.
And then I got into the bathroom, and it was just, it just came so naturally.
Yeah, I got in the bathroom at a later date in my life.
I got in the bathroom like way too late.
What age did you get in the bathroom?
What age did you start getting into the bathroom?
I was really into the bathroom recently. I'm like it's kind of weird like a lot of people get into the bathroom when they're young
I'm like just starting I honestly I still haven't yeah, you haven't gotten in there. Just seen what that's all about
In the bathroom, I don't know honestly like I was in there a little bit like in elementary school
But it just like wasn't for me really it's one of those things that when you get older you realize like yeah
The bathroom actually fucking slaps
Yeah, you go through if you love the bathroom middle school and high school you're like that's gay like I can't like that
I didn't realize like in college like who gives a fuck what anybody likes. Yeah, like who cares it doesn't matter
It doesn't care matter if I like that there does the bathroom ever care the people fucking make fun of it
It has like a shitty fan base, but it's still fucking like no
You literally when you get older you realize like yeah, the bathroom fan base is literally like like yeah, it's annoying
But yeah, it's like if you like it if you like it, then you like it
You know, it's like don't let the fan base of like be yourself if you like the bathroom you like the back exactly
If you like going to the bathroom like don't let that kind of weird social pressure
Posting my my my topsters top 100 appliances in the bathroom. Mm-hmm. It's like the top 100 albums thing. It's a last FM
Yeah, my weekly number
20 will surprise you the Bluetooth shower speaker. Yes
sharper image
- Death and Beyond for $5.
- And I wish I had an explosion queued up for this.
I want my shampoo and my body wash,
and you're gonna say I don't have any hair,
I want my shampoo and body wash
as little pumps attached to the wall in the shower.
- Oh, like in--
- Oh.
(air blowing)
- What? - That'd be nice.
- That's how it comes out?
- No, that's my explosion
'cause I didn't wanna open my phone.
But like, that's like in a hotel.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - I love that so much.
- No, it's cool.
Everything should be built into--
- That's right.
- That's good.
Everything should be built into the room.
- Yeah.
- There shouldn't be anything
that you can take out of your house.
- My--
- Yes, if I eat, if I should take a bite of a hamburger
and then let go and a string should pull it back
into a hole, right?
- Yeah, you have to pull it across the room.
- Yeah, I can pull it out and then it just goes right back.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, they should do that with plates.
- Walk and get it.
- They should do that.
- I have plates like that.
- All the plates.
- All the plates that you can--
- You wanna eat in front of the TV.
- Everything should be connected to a string
- Yeah, as soon as you're done, okay.
And it all just flies.
- Oh my god, and it goes through like a car wash style,
and it cleans it off as it goes.
- Yeah, and you're like, if you're trying to bring plates,
like if your kitchen is downstairs,
you're trying to bring it upstairs,
it's like the string is just like tightly turning
every single corner, and you're like dragging it.
- And then you go and it goes like,
bing, bing, bing, and it flies around your house.
- Yeah, well I was thinking maybe--
- Chops your kids down.
It could be like, okay, the string is long enough
you can eat on the couch, but you can't eat in bed.
Maybe the wife could calibrate it that way.
- Okay, I like the idea,
but take the wife and get rid of her.
- She's on a string too.
- And the guy, yes.
Oh, wife on a string, like soap on a rope.
- Why?
- You put it up yo ass.
- No.
'Cause you use it in the bathroom.
(laughing)
- It's 'cause you stick that whole thing up yo butt.
- Soap on a rope, what a great idea.
- Yeah.
- I think I might go to the bathroom later today
'cause I'm feeling kind of nostalgic for it.
(laughing)
- I would love to go into the bathroom,
hit the Siri, play Kiss Me.
Kiss me in the bathroom.
- Seeing your sink in the kitchen and being like,
well I don't know why but I just got crazy deja vu
for the bathroom.
(laughing)
This seriously has bathroom vibes.
(laughter)
- This kitchen sink has mad bathroom vibes.
- Damn, we were trying to go for like,
basically heavily a bathroom inspired kitchen.
- Yeah.
- It's like kinda chic, modernist, but then also bathroom.
(laughter)
We kinda split the difference between craftsman style
and bathroom.
- The property brother's like, getting someone a house
and the person's like coming and trying to like,
peek in and see the renovations and they're like,
no, go, you're gonna love it, just go,
You have to get out of here, okay?
Just go relax, go on a date with your husband, it's fine.
And then they're like, all right.
They're covering their eyes, they're like, come on in.
They open their eyes and every room is a bathroom.
- And then the bathroom is the only thing
that looks like a living room.
There's like a fridge in there.
- A couch toilet.
- And then the person turns around
and you see that they have the biggest fucking ass
of all time, a giant planet-sized ass.
- And their husband just made of crap.
- Yeah, well that's the thing, yeah.
Husbands on Property Brothers are a different breed.
Hit the sound board.
- What do you want?
- Anything.
- Okay.
- Husbands on Property Brothers are a different breed.
- Hold on, it'll take me just a--
- Brah.
(laughing)
- Wait, say it, no, I'll--
- Husbands, I'm just saying,
Husbands on Property Brothers are a different breed.
(harp music)
- Maybe not that.
- It's okay, that moment's passed.
- There we go.
- Was that the Property Brothers?
- Yeah.
- You're saying that?
- Surprise mother.
- Surprise motherfucker.
- Oh, okay.
- Wait, yeah, wait, okay, here we go.
When you walk in and there's a birthday party
for you in your house.
(laughing)
- Dude, I am going to, I'm gonna make somehow
my dog mad with this fucking app.
Yeah, he's gonna be like, you gotta chill.
- It doesn't look like it's an app.
It looks like it's just in your browser.
- Okay, do you work at fucking iPhone?
- Yeah.
- I do too.
- I know more about iPhones 'cause I've had mine
for probably longer than you've ever had a phone.
- That's kinda cool, man. - See that?
- You realize that this cost me--
- How much did that cost you?
- 180 bucks.
- And you're gonna spend another 180 bucks in two weeks.
- No, I won't.
- Yeah, you will.
- You're gonna have to wait a while.
- Yeah, that's true, he won't.
he'll get someone else's old phone.
- Oh, that's true, yeah.
- I'll steal his shit out his damn house.
- You don't know where it is,
and you don't know what it looks like.
- Cameron, do you wanna have,
I'll bring a bunch of DVDs.
- Cameron, do you wanna have a rag smelling party?
(laughing)
Cameron, you wanna smell this rag really quick?
- We should smell DVDs again.
- Yeah.
Did you, we've said the name of--
- Did you know?
Did you know?
- No, the knife throwing DVD.
- We should also do--
- I lost it.
million turds and a billion furs.
Yeah, we should just do the classic episode.
Maybe this smells like something.
But we've said the title of that DVD that,
well, about knife throwing, right?
No, not even a little.
You said we were going to upload it to the Patreon back in the day.
Oh, yeah.
And I forgot to back it up to my computer.
And then when I moved to New York, I lost that fucking DVD.
Really?
Yeah.
That's so fucked.
So, if you can help us, right?
Yeah.
can help us find that DVD where the fat guy with the ponytail
blurs his face and says--
You don't remember the name?
I don't remember the name.
It's something knife throwing, and it's
by a knife throwing company.
But in the video, remember he says like--
Knife throwing company.
I can teach you how to kill a man by throwing
a paper clip at their neck.
Yeah.
That would be so sick.
That was the sickest video ever.
We need to find that again.
I think I could kill someone with these.
I dare you.
He says that he can't--
Rah!
he can't show his face because he's a green beret.
- Oh yeah, he's anonymous.
- Yeah.
- You have a show this month, go plug it.
- I do, I have four shows this month actually.
- Don't plug shows, just plug the good ones.
- Why not, there's people who live in New York that listen.
- Don't plug bar shows.
- All right, you don't get to book a gig.
You wasted your opportunity, bye.
- Shareholder meeting.
- Oh, shareholder meeting.
Okay, and then on the 16th of March, I will be in Boston...
Nope, I'm stopping this.
...with Conor O'Malley.
[LAUGHTER]