(upbeat music)
- Okay, I'm gonna get to our guests.
You guys hang tight for just one second.
I asked Patrick.
- Still?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
I asked Patrick to get me a cup of coffee, right?
And we had doubts.
Everybody had doubts.
- Well yeah, so--
- 'Cause he didn't wanna do it.
- I'll provide witness here.
He left the room and I said,
"I don't know if he knows how to do that."
- Yeah, and I was like, I had this horrible realization.
I said, "You know what?
"I think you might be right."
That's something he's never done before.
- 'Cause he doesn't drink coffee.
- Doesn't drink coffee, and only that.
It's not that he generally has a hard time doing stuff.
It's just that.
So he left and I was a little worried,
but he came back with this, right?
And I'm thinking, "Okay, by God, he did it."
He hands it to me, I feel it, it's cold.
I go, "Okay, it's iced coffee.
"He got it out of the wrong thing."
Wow, very funny.
He claims he did it on accident, right?
But then I take my first sip, hold on.
It's Dr. Pepper.
(laughing)
He put Dr. Pepper.
- If you want your coffee, it's over there.
- You also did get a coffee and you hate it?
Dude, fuck you.
Fuck you.
You are a piece of shit.
I don't like, you are pissing me off today.
Somebody wants a Dr. Pepper.
- It's actually Dr. Pepper.
- It's a diet Dr. Pepper.
- That's really funny.
- Yeah.
- That's really good.
- You know what sucks is I filled it up
outside before I came in and I didn't know that when you put the lid on
There's like that tiny hole right there. I put the lid on outside there. It just fucking sprayed it just
Were you were you even thinking like like that I was gonna feel it realize it was cold you thought yeah
I thought that you would think that I accidentally got you a cold coffee. You're a bad guy
extra money
- If you somehow heated up a fucking Sprite,
I am going to shoot you in the head.
- I wish I thought of that.
- I still put it in the also Dr. Pepper.
- That one's coffee.
- I swear to God, the first time we were here,
you did not the same thing, but you also fucked up on coffee.
I don't remember exactly, I think that one
was maybe more genuine.
But I remember we were waiting and waiting
for you to bring coffee back.
I swear to God.
- It might have been, yeah,
'cause I think that's when that deli was first getting built.
- So you were trying it out.
- I went and got some construction workers.
- I'll go ruin something over there to kind of celebrate.
We're here with--
- I'm saying you might be in a loop.
(laughing)
- Probably about the same time last year too.
We're here with Girl, God, Grace, and April.
How are y'all?
- We're doing good.
- Doing incredibly.
- We're doing great.
I'm April, that's Grace.
- This is Grace, that's April.
- We're doing really good.
- Are you guys getting ready to start
- The longest tour ever right here?
- We are about to do the longest tour ever.
- We're about to do the world's longest tour.
- They're calling it the world's longest tour.
They're saying it's not even allowed to be this long.
- Yeah.
- Somebody should stop me.
- They're saying we'll never be allowed
to go on a tour this long.
- Osha's gonna step in.
- They're saying that we're exploiting each other.
- Yes, they're saying we're exploiting each other.
They're saying it's insane to book a 300 seat theater
in Phoenix, Arizona to do anything.
(laughing)
They're saying that that was a bad decision.
They're saying that we shouldn't have done that.
Don't listen to them.
Here's what you do.
They're saying that that was a mistake.
Add a late show.
That's what you do.
Oh, no.
There you go.
You add another show.
You add a late show.
Because people will be like, oh, the demand is insane.
We've actually--
Well, people aren't buying tickets to the early one.
They're like, I'm going to be too awake.
We've actually--
I'm going to be in a tired head space.
I need to be drunk.
We've been telling everyone that the show is sold out.
That's why we have so many tickets there.
Because to create desire, we've been saying, oh, it's sold out.
You can't come don't you want a late-night giggly sleepover vibe? Yeah
Don't you love the like you do a show in our pajamas learning when I was like younger?
Y'all don't sleep you don't sleep in pajamas I do you don't have PJs on with a butt flap
That's pretty crazy. Yeah, that's amazing sleep
Yeah, I think that like if you need anything to help you sleep if I thought I mean like a blanket or underwear
Sleep at all. You're also it's like you didn't
Using performance enhancing cloth, yes
- That's true.
- Do you guys ever think about how before you were
like doing shows like that, like selling shows on tour,
you would see people post maybe on their Instagram story
like low ticket warning or something,
and now you're on tour and you have a show
that is a 90 cap and you've sold four seats
and you're posting low ticket warning.
- Low ticket warning!
Low, low, low ticket warning.
- And you go, oh, okay.
- Yep, yep.
- And you're trying to trick everybody.
- They don't realize that what you're saying
is low ticket amount sold.
(laughing)
- Yeah, warning, warning, I'm going to kill myself
if the tickets remain this low.
(laughing)
- That's really good.
- The tickets sold.
- I'm gonna do a live stream where I hold a gun to my head
and threaten to kill myself if tickets don't sell out.
- Please, please, please, please, please buy these tickets.
- I'm gonna make the news.
I'm gonna get on the local news by doing that.
- A law of touring is people will,
whenever you're on like an earlier tour
or you're going to a city,
you've announced some cities
and their city isn't like announced,
they'll be like, "Oh, you gotta come to Orlando,
you gotta come to Orlando."
- I can't believe you're not coming to Orlando.
- And then that same person six months later will be like,
"You were in Orlando?"
(laughing)
- Oh man, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I can't make the show.
I actually don't live there.
(laughing)
- Hey, I'm sorry, I can't go to the show
because I checked out your comedy and I hated it.
(laughing)
- I actually saw a clip and I don't stand for it at all.
- That's what I do, I use a VPN, I send my IP to Indiana.
I leave 150 comments on every Instagram reel.
Oh my God, come to Indiana, please.
(laughing)
All of a sudden they're pulling up in Indiana.
But you do show up, but just people.
- You're the only person in the crowd.
- And I'm going like this.
(laughing)
- What's up, yo?
- Now that I have you here, I'd like to talk to you
about my restaurant idea.
(laughing)
I think that you two.
It's Smashburgers, but it's done different.
It's a new kind of Smashburger, where the bun is also a burger.
What if the mayo was just mayo?
Not a Thousand Island thing.
It was just straight up--
I'm pretty much done with the Smashburgers.
I'm ready to go back to--
No.
Yeah, I'm going to fuck it.
The problem with the big boys is a bad quality--
Yeah, tell them the problem with big boys.
Bad quality smash burger is like fine. Yeah, but a bad quality like thick burger
Like that's been like in the freezer for a year tastes like shit
It's like to stack on a night you fucking yeah, I'm glad that smash burgers have taken that over
Yeah, I like the big like trend cuz that like
26 or 20 14 to like
2018 that's all you could fucking get is like like a $20 burger that way tall
Why do you have some burger era in your head of four years?
All right, we still kind of scold him for having a mental there's no what was tell me what was before 2014
What was the burger?
I'm going to give you a year and you're going to tell me what the burgers were like.
I think before 2014, you'd have a regular sized burger that was over ketchuped.
Yeah, I'm going to tell you in 2024, my type of burger is going to take off. It's going to be everywhere.
It's a smash burger, but it's smashed the other way.
It stands up in between the bun. It looks like a capital letter I if you look at it from the side.
But you still cook it top and bottom so it's completely raw for about 8 inches in the middle.
- It's a raw strip of beef.
- It's called a smash burger hot dog style.
- My dad used to make hot durgers when I was a kid.
- Oh, smash hot dogs would be great.
- You cut the hot dog in half.
- I made a hot burger in the toilet this morning.
(laughing)
- Come on, man.
My dad, David, he made a hot durger,
which you split.
- Hot durger.
(laughing)
- That fucking dad.
That's probably the day my mom was like,
I gotta divorce this guy.
(laughing)
'Cause he was in the living room.
She was like, I've got an amazing idea. It's called the hot burger.
She was like, Hey, I'm busy. Can you make dinner for the kids?
He's like, I got it. He's cutting hot dogs.
That's the problem with marriage is you have to get married to someone before
they come up with that idea.
There's always an invisible clock in everyone's life of like good relationship.
Well, cause now my dad's a, my dad has, he's a billionaire because of that idea.
Wait, you're Caleb Durger?
My dad David Derger.
Oh my god!
The hot Derger.
You're Caleb Derger.
It became such a ubiquitous thing in my house that my dad stopped calling them hot Dergers
and did just start calling them Dergers.
It's not that much of a step.
But that's how many times we eat them he'd be like, "Do you want Dergers tonight?"
It's interesting how many migrant workers have gone missing at the Derger plant.
Probably a lot.
- You do a dangerous job making durgers all day.
- Can you clarify for me what a hot durger is?
- You take a hot--
- A hot durger.
- A hot hamburger bun.
A hamburger bun.
- A hamburger bun?
(laughing)
A hot durger's on hamburger buns.
- You take a hamburger bun,
and instead of just cooking a hot dog,
you split the hot dog in half,
and you cook both sides,
but you leave the one end of the casing on
so that it has, so it's connected.
- They literally do that at Moo-Ya.
- Yeah, but my dad did it at Booyah.
That's what he called the kitchen.
Every time he took a bite of the Durger.
- Wait, does he cut the hot dog--
- Lengthwise. - Lengthwise.
But then does he cut it horizontally too?
- Depends on the bun.
- So it's just stick it out of the bun.
Well, I'm gonna be real. - You use two buns, right?
- Yeah, well you use two dogs.
You use two Durgers and you make kind of a lattice.
- Oh, a double.
- Yeah, you make a tic-tac-toe.
Yeah, you make Lincoln logs with the Durgers.
- That sounds really good.
It's just a hot dog.
It's really clever.
Both sides.
That's the innovation.
My dad was trying to maximize
surface area.
That's like a math problem.
That could be like a crispy perfect way.
He's pretty smart.
There was a YouTube video of
a guy.
So it was an advertisement
for a novelty meats
website.
And the whole video is this guy
selling big hot dogs.
And they're like the size of your
forearm. And it's a whole hot dog.
and he advertised it like you just cut off the like you cut off the part of the hot dog that you want and then you can just put it on the grill and just make it like that.
So it's basically like a big ass thing of bologna.
But, whoa, it was a good I watched that video a lot.
I thought that guy was really funny.
I really like hot dogs.
That's too big.
That is way too big.
That's way too big.
Hot dogs are like as far as stuff that's like that can give you cancer.
Hot dogs are like pretty much the number one food.
- Oh, yeah. - Oh, for sure.
- There's no better thing to eat at 3 a.m.
- They don't tell you this, but you're not supposed
to put them up your ass.
It's actually bad for you.
- That's carcinogenic.
- It's actually carcinogenic.
- Oh, there's the thing.
- Get it in through your anal.
- More people are getting-- I actually have--
it actually-- ass cancer, for that reason,
runs in my family, because we're just all incapable
of not putting the hot dog up my ass.
- My problem with the hot dog--
a big hot dog like this, it's like,
all right, you're adding a lot of meat.
Come on, give me some more casing.
- Mm-hmm. - Yeah, we need more casing.
- More casing, we need more casing, you're right.
- A whole lot more casing.
- I have hot dogs at home for that reason,
but I always have hot dogs in my kitchen,
so I can't turn my back when she's over.
- That's right.
- She's like a clutch dog.
- I turn over and I'm like,
how do you shove that whole six pack in there?
(laughing)
- It's really good.
- Backwards through practice and training.
- It's kind of prairie dogging out a little bit.
- Yeah.
- The hot dog, 'cause so many are fitting.
- I love the idea of like insisting
that something is hereditary in your family,
but it's actually just all the way down the line,
you've all been so stupid enough to do the same.
Yeah, actually getting hit by a car is hereditary.
(laughing)
In my family, actually.
- I've been recently just not looking both ways
before I cross the street.
But not on purpose, I've just been walking with other people
and then just being kind of pulled out of the,
yeah, Noah had basically pulled me out of the crosswalk
the other day 'cause I just wasn't even looking.
I think I'm getting close to an accidental death.
- Well, you can actually build up a tolerance.
- You can build up a tolerance.
- Maybe I get hit by a golf cart first.
- You're working your way up.
- Five miles per hour, 10 miles per hour.
Really before a golf cart,
you could probably just have Patrick run at you.
- It's like--
- That's scary, that's scary to watch.
- It's like drugs, eventually even getting hit by a truck
won't do anything for you.
- That's true.
- You're gonna need bigger cars to get that same height.
- And then you'll have to get hit by a plane,
which is what some people said is why 9/11 happened.
- Yeah.
- Some business folks.
- Some business guys.
- They set it up.
- What they don't talk about is the extreme high
that everyone in this house has experienced.
- Did you guys ever--
- Real quick, I just want you to know,
you just foreshadowed the most insane arc of our lives,
which is that you said you're getting ready
to be hit by a car, and I have my road test
in like two weeks.
(laughing)
- Okay, wait a second.
- Something's bad.
- We gotta watch the news for the next month.
See what's up.
- I lost my thought, that was so--
Oh, did anybody ever tell you guys that when--
- No, just joking.
- No, I'll just drink my Dr. Pepper.
- Oh hey, Caleb.
- Did anybody--
- Caleb, Caleb, she doesn't, don't listen to her.
- I'm gonna ignore her.
- She's got eight hot dogs up her asshole right now.
- This will keep you preoccupied.
- My bone!
(laughing)
- Did anybody ever tell y'all in middle school
or some shit that burning alive actually feels really good?
- No.
- Really?
- You've asked us about this before
and we've told you no, that person was just crazy.
- I think that you wanna try it.
- I don't think that--
- I don't think that's how you can cry.
- I don't know if you can cry.
- What I have heard is that drowning feels really good.
- That's definitely not.
- I think dying just feels good.
- That's really not.
- Yeah.
- It feels amazing to die.
- Not for the first part of it.
- I love that no one can prove to me that.
- That's true, when you go to heaven
and you're in the clouds.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Floating up and seeing the entire world.
- Yeah, that probably feels pretty good.
- It's like an ecstasy as you're about to go.
- Well, yeah, 'cause you live,
every part of your life flashes before your eyes
and you remember all the times that you had sex
or you watched a funny movie.
Is that the same feeling that someone gets when they're jacking off and hanging themselves, right?
I think so you can't breathe
It is real
Every celebrity does it every celebrity died that way yeah Robin Williams died that way
That's what you know some people say that yeah, actually
my brother said
- That's how David Bowie died.
It's how Princess Diana died.
- Most celebrities, yes, that's true.
That's what she was doing in the car on the avenue.
- Dude in his speeding car is,
I mean, she pulled it off, she came before she died.
- The ultimate dream, yeah.
(laughing)
She had a belt that was wrapped around the steering wheel,
around that guy that was with her, and around her neck.
And she was kind of in this like perfectly suspended,
where any way that she moved,
it would add tension to her neck.
- That's really good.
- That's why she was in a white Bronco.
- She was in a white Bronco,
And she was running from those LAPD.
They have really good belt loop.
The wheel has a very good belt loop thing
that you can put the belt through.
That's why I think OJ didn't do the murder.
Oh yeah, explain that.
There's a lot of evidence to him having been,
you know, jacking off with a belt around his neck at that time.
In the house. He was in the house.
He just didn't want to admit it.
That's why the gloves shrank too.
Yeah. Right.
It is so fun to ... I don't think he did it.
I think if somebody says that OJ did it, I still think they're racist.
I'm like, "Yeah, no.
You're wrong."
I also think he did not do it.
He's innocent.
There's a crazy maniac.
He's still on the loose.
I still need to learn about this case.
Well, hey, do you need to learn about it or do you need to just learn how to trust a friend?
Yeah.
I think we need to look at all the evidence.
You don't think that we know what we're talking about?
I'm still down the middle.
I think if they were to reopen the case right now, I could probably be on that jury.
You'd be a jury.
Yeah.
- I'm gonna assign you to the case as a detective.
- Whoa. - Put you in a trench coat.
- That's really good. - Imagine being
trying to figure out the OJ case.
- How do detectives do that shit?
How the fuck do they get to a body and go like,
I get-- - This room smells weird.
- Yeah, it smells like their brother.
- Well, they train.
They train. - They train.
- A lot of nose baits. - They train.
- Well, they practice on a bunch of cases
of people who've been killed that don't really matter,
like homeless people or people who are weird people
who people don't like, and then eventually
they work their way up. - And you have to work,
- Work your way up from solving simple things
like is he dead to how did he die?
You have to really start at the bottom.
- That's really important to be able to tell
if someone's dead first.
- Totally.
You have to kind of learn how to do that.
Yeah, I used to want to be a detective,
but I was really bad at telling when someone was dead.
- Yeah, she thinks I'm dead all the time.
- I would spend years solving a case
only to find out the guy's been alive the whole time.
- Really?
- You didn't even see the body also.
- I didn't even see the body.
I just kind of jumped to the--
- Maybe he missed work.
- Yeah, it was just a big thing.
- Sometimes I'll be talking to April
for like 10 minutes and she'll be like,
"Holy shit, are you a ghost right now?"
(laughing)
I'm like, "No, I'm still here."
- It's so annoying when you're talking to April
and she tries to put her hand through you.
- She's constantly poking me.
- Oh, okay, okay.
- Listen, I've been fooled before, okay?
And I'm not gonna let it happen to me again.
- Who fooled you?
- It's not, it doesn't matter.
It's not important.
- Ghostly Carmichael.
- It's, yep.
- Ghostly Carmichael, is that what you said?
(laughing)
- That's the name of the famous ghost in Fooled April.
- Ghostly Carmichael.
- He's always getting into,
and I think that there was a certain amount
of romantic tension between the two at one point.
- Yeah.
- And I think that--
- Wait, between me and Ghostly Carmichael?
- Between you and Ghostly Carmichael.
- I don't believe him, I don't think he's real.
- Only from his direction though.
- Oh yeah.
(laughing)
- But he was really trying to make you believe
he was real so you would date him.
Or he was still alive so you would date him.
- I have a Casper question,
but you two might be the ones to ask about that.
- Yeah, probably. - Yeah, totally.
- With Casper-- - And why's that?
- I just feel like y'all maybe know something about ghosts.
You've been talking about ghosts for a couple of minutes.
With Casper, is Casper confined to,
does he have to live in that fucking house?
- Yeah. - Really?
So if you're that,
because you're like a kid-- - It's actually his punishment.
He did something horrible when he was alive.
- He was seriously-- - Those walls could talk.
- His eternal torment is living in that house forever.
- The live action movies, I do think he has something--
- That boy was horny.
Let's just say that boy was corny.
- In the old school cartoons,
he would be on the moon and stuff sometimes.
- Yeah, really?
- He'd be everywhere.
- So he was, at one point he was a boy?
- If you were.
- At one point he was a boy.
- What the fuck did he look like?
Did he look like that?
- He looked like that, yeah.
- He was bald and giant eyes?
- He looked small and pointy on the bottom too.
- Of course he died.
- He was killed by the government.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- This is not how he looked.
- He was road killed.
Roadkill and his body just sat on the side of the road
What I really don't believe that yeah, I don't believe that at all I don't believe
Remember him that was the headline by the way in case you missed it if Casper was in my house though
Especially if I'm like a bolt like a growing boy
- Wait, what is that?
(laughing)
- Does that just mean he died as a kid?
- Yeah, my son wanted to be Casper so bad that he died.
(laughing)
- I took him out back for his birthday.
- He wanted to be Casper.
- Wait, somebody needs to--
- I had to give him his birthday present.
I had to go take him out.
- Yeah.
- Wait, somebody needs to let Casper's--
- Casper's low-key bad.
- Someone needs to let his spirit free.
Yeah, 100%.
- The Casper movie is so weird
because there's this romantic tension
between Casper and the girl.
- Is he pointy on the bottom?
Am I misremembering?
- Well, that's the thing.
If I was a girl growing up in the Casper house,
I'd be fucking that ghost every day.
- But it's like a toddler.
- Oh man, you were, hey, he's not a toddler.
- Hey, come on.
- I know, he's a buddy.
He does, it's weird that she's into this--
- He's like 80 years old.
- It's weird that she's into this smooth toddler.
Is that he died as a hairless baby or he died as a
In this version he died like as a 14 year old or something, but he certainly
He basically be a couch I just be like kind of experimenting with my ass
- With your ass.
- I don't know what girls do.
I don't fucking know.
- If I was in the Casper house and I wanted to free him,
I feel like the way you free him is you probably just have
to defile his grave or something, right?
I'd be out in the backyard trying to dig him up
and piss all over his body.
- You're digging him, why is he buried in the backyard?
- He's a ghost in the house,
he must be around there somewhere.
- Though you die, I think--
- There used to be a lot of ghosts in the house.
- I think there's a lot of ghosts in the house.
There used to be a lot less land.
Yeah, there's way more land.
Alright, fine. Then I go, okay. I go to the...
Bury someone in your backyard because there just wasn't land for a day.
Or maybe he was like...
Then I just go to the graveyard. I'll dig up every kid and see which one's...
Just piss on all their bodies until he disappears.
Rub a bone.
Rub a bone against your dick.
My bone!
Yeah, we get it, April.
Nice bit, April.
He still has a bone now.
If I had a I would Casper would be a serious Ghostbusters situation for me. I'd be wanting him exterminated
Calling the Ghostbusters on they're like torturing this ghost child
I would yeah, I would call the Ghostbusters and on Casper and I would see like their antics
I would see they're a little goofy and I'd be like no you guys get out of here
I need people who are fucking serious about this.
We're gonna fucking kill this ghost and get rid of him.
I don't want you joking around and dancing.
No, you wouldn't want to do that. You'd get hit by one of Bill Murray's sarcastic quips.
I'd slap Bill Murray.
I'd slap the shit out of Bill Murray.
I'd be like, "Bow!" Back of the hand. Right to the face.
I'd knock his teeth out.
I do think I could take on all of the Ghostbusters.
Dude, if Bill Murray pulled up and started eating my fucking critch for guys, dude,
I would be his old man shit.
I'd say, "Believe this, bitch!"
- Have the Ghostbusters ever tried just using a real gun on you?
- I don't think so, they should.
Especially the fucking Stay Puft Marshmallow Man.
You blow some holes in him.
- I honestly feel like a gun could just kill it.
- Yeah, probably.
- I think it'd be fine.
- A lot of their ghosts are just monsters.
- It is ostensibly a ghost, or ostensibly this mythic thing,
but it has heft in a way that others don't.
- It explodes.
- Yeah, because they use their fucking proton packs
and unlike all the other ones,
it just makes it go on fire.
- Yeah.
- Like it's not like.
(laughing)
- True.
- They have such an easy,
I rewatched Ghostbusters pretty recently
and I was shocked at how easy of a time they have
defeating the big bad.
They really just have to like shoot him
and when that's not quite enough,
they're like, all right, let's cross the streams
and then that works.
(laughing)
- Yeah, oh, that's what it was.
I was like, don't they just like, don't they just think like,
"Oh, it's not real anymore. It's Freddy Krueger."
I conflated the two.
Wait, that's the ending of Freddy Krueger?
Is that really?
No, the real ending of Nightmare on Elm Street is even funnier than that.
They drag him into the real world and they like get him or whatever.
And then at the very end, the kids are like, "All right, bye!"
Like they're leaving and they go and they get into a car
and the car is the same colors as Freddy Krueger and it goes, "Ha ha ha ha ha!"
And he drives away.
- The mom gets pulled through the tiniest window.
- That's happened to me.
- Yeah.
- Whoa.
- But at the end he's a car, he turns into a car.
- Yeah.
- He turns into a car.
- That's like the twist ending is that he was a car all along.
- I don't know if he was a car all along.
- It's a twist ending.
- The whole time he was a car all along.
- The twist ending is probably that they're in a dream.
- No, you know what I mean.
- He's a car all along.
- In the real world he's a car all along.
- That's kind of the experts here
on what people were all along.
(laughing)
- He was a car all along.
- He was a herbie?
- What if they retconned it and made him back
into a pedophile the rest of the movie?
- He was a boy who got transformed into a car.
- Yeah, he was a transformer.
He was a Decepticon.
(laughing)
- He was a transformer.
- I would watch kind of a dark Transformers reboot
about just a single Transformer car.
He's not a pedophile, but maybe he's--
- I thought you were going in the same line
as Freddy Krueger.
- Oh, a Transformers version of Dexter.
- Oh, yeah.
- Where he's like a Decepticon,
but he gets hired by the LAPD to destroy,
to kill every single person in Skid Row.
- I want a sitcom about a decepticon.
- Yeah, no, he just comes and he starts hitting 'em.
I think it's just a bunch of news stories
that are like crazy hit and run in Skid Row.
- A decepticon hitting a guy and then the cops show up
and he turns back into a transformer
and is like, "I didn't see anything."
(laughing)
- What, you think I can drive?
- Yeah, you think I can drive?
I'm a huge robot!
How would I fit in a car?
I can't drive one of these fucking cruisers!
Yeah, I'd drive a fucking, I'd drive a beetle.
I have a Volkswagen.
I can't fucking kill anybody.
What are those wheels in your chest that are covered in blood?
Are those supposed to do anything?
Trust me though, if I was a car, I'd look cool as fuck.
But I can't be one. I can't be one.
Not today.
Oh, why do I have these wheels?
On my arms?
- Oh, that's just how my people do things.
- Yeah, that's robot jewelry.
- This is jewelry, yeah.
- You could get away with actually killing somebody
with your car by being like,
"No, my car's a transformer," and it took,
I had no control.
- "Is this Tesla right now?"
(laughing)
- I guess you're right.
But then you have to be like,
"No, see, he's gonna transform."
But then it's inaccurate.
- That's really good.
No, I'm pretty sure my car is a transformer.
- Yeah, what kind of car do you have?
- I haven't seen it transform, but I'm pretty sure.
- It's a transformer, but it's like gayer than any of the--
- My car's the one fruity transformer.
(laughing)
Hello.
I'm a decepticon.
- She has a bright canary yellow Fiat.
- Oh, that is a gay car.
- Or like a bright canary yellow Faggot, you know?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- I get what you're saying.
- Yeah, it's the gay transformer.
- The one gay transformer turns into a gay ass car.
- I think Michael Bay might be,
probably next movie there will be a gay transformer.
- There will have a gay ass transformer.
- They've literally had to hold him back
every single movie. He's been like walking towards the computer to write a
script and they're like, "The interns are grabbing him. No, no, no, we need this job!"
They're showing him like a Beats pill. He puts a Beats pill in his ass.
He puts a Beats pill in his fucking ass.
The 100,000 like interns whose job it is just to render like different body parts
of the transporter, like, "No, please! Please, no!"
He has like a, they even, yeah, they got that.
"We're gonna get in trouble! We'll get in trouble if you make a gay one!"
Michael Bay's like, "I get it, we can't do gay, we can't do gay.
"We're a gay Filipina."
(laughter)
And they're like, "Oh yeah, go ahead."
"We're not gonna do the gay one, but here's my pitch for a new Transformer named Rickshaw."
(laughter)
They're like, "Go right ahead."
"Go right ahead, that's fine."
His gay Transformer would literally have like a baboon ass.
(laughter)
Like a bright, with like neon signs pointing into an asshole.
His anus would prolapse into a cannon.
(laughing)
- That's really good.
- That's really, that's really good.
- You're just seeing him go to a gas station.
(laughing)
- Jessica, and they're like,
"Oh wait, how do I fill it up?"
(laughing)
- What about, there's a transformer
that turns into like a sex machine when he's in the car.
(laughing)
- He's never in a car.
- He turns into a little box and goes, "Ahh!"
(laughing)
- He has no idea how cars work also.
He's like, "So gay."
(laughing)
- It is cool that they have transformers that turn into--
- They should have a hot girl transformer.
- They do. - Do they really?
- Yeah, they do. - No, not--
- They have a hot girl spider transformer.
- Yeah, they have a literal hot girl transformer.
- Oh yeah. - Oh wait.
- Does it have tires here?
- Yeah, it's like the not Megan Fox, the other girl,
and then she turns into a robot.
So she's a transformer who can transform into a human?
- 12 or 13 and seeing that--
- Imagine your girlfriend's arms just fall off.
- What the fuck, they could be anywhere.
(laughing)
- They could be.
They literally could be.
- They have one that's a big spider too.
- The spider lady, I think they took like the,
I was reading some article about this.
- She's fine fine, how lady?
- They took all of the designers or whatever
to a strip club to like make the,
for like reference stuff. - Oh my god.
- And they, all the notes about the--
- They didn't know how to woman look?
- No, they were transformers, design artists.
- They had to go to the fucking strip club?
- They were like, the design notes and stuff
were like so horny that they were like,
all right, we gotta like,
we gotta cut back on this.
- And her pussy's fucking red.
(laughing)
It's basically like a big target.
- Hot pink, red.
(laughing)
Right, red.
- Right, red.
- And she probably gets her period
and nuts and bolts fly out.
(laughing)
Yeah.
We should go back to that.
- Yeah, that's good.
- Yeah, that's good, right?
- Do that, do that.
- And the boobs are two tires.
- Yeah.
- The boobs are two tires 'cause she's a motorcycle.
- That's really good.
Oh, she's a motorcycle.
- When she squirts, it's movie theater pop.
(laughing)
- And her lips are candy.
- She gets wet and there's just oil dripping.
- And also, yeah, she has long hair, too.
- Normal hair.
Normal hair.
It's not even metal.
It's real hair.
- She reminds me of my mom.
- It's real hair.
(laughing)
- Oh my God, a trans woman with real hair
that turns into a car that just has hair on the front.
(laughing)
- Why does this car have a wig?
- Who's the hottest Transformers babe?
- It's just human hair.
- How, dude, what kind of pipe was that?
- Whoa! - Oh my God!
- Holy crap! - What the hell?
- They need to chill. - Oh my God, those knees.
- They need to chill.
- Why is there a lens flare on its boob?
- That's its nipple.
- That's part of it. - Nipples are lens flares.
(laughing)
- How strong was, Shia LaBeouf had the most insane pipe game
of all time. - Definitely.
- In those movies.
- He was funny AF in those movies.
- He was pulling some fire women.
- Definitely. - Back to back to back.
And he was like 15.
- Yeah. - That's so crazy.
- I think he was 12.
- Yeah, he was one or two years old.
- That's the weirdest part of those movies
is that child of F is supposed to be like a teenager.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- And he's fucking-- - He doesn't look
like a goddamn teenager.
- He's fucking Megan Fox on his friend's head.
- Absolutely. - Like his best--
(laughing)
- That's actually true.
- His best friend in the world is like,
"Can you open up your body?
"I'm gonna fuck a tanny."
(laughing)
In the middle of you. - Imagine you've had sex
with a guy like a bunch of times and all of a sudden the car you've been having
sex the whole time like wakes up. Oh shit, oh shit, it's been here the whole time.
Oh shit, the car left.
Like Megan Fox's character is like, I've never had a threesome and Sheila Booth's character is like, what do you mean?
Every time we fuck in my car, that's the threesome.
It would have been.
Bumblebee is a member of our relationship. This is a throuple.
- Every time they're having sex in the car,
like a mechanical penis starts to come out.
(laughing)
- Just very slowly, just kind of lift.
- And then Shia keeps hitting it and it goes back down.
- The seatbelt buckle.
- Yeah, the seatbelt buckle starts to turn up.
Or like the hood of the car opens or something.
Yeah, that's good.
- It just, "Vroom."
- That's really good, yeah.
Shia, why is your car, what's happening with your car?
Oh, don't worry.
- Bumblebee, you can't make it bigger than mine.
Come on.
- It would have been cooler if he,
instead of him owning Bumblebee,
if he had bought Optimus Prime.
- Does he own Bumblebee?
- He drove so much truck around.
- Wait, does he own Bumblebee?
- He bought it for like three grand.
- Oh wait, I love the idea that--
- He bought it for Bernie Mac.
- He's actually like enslaved.
- Oh yeah, he's a slave.
Yeah, Bumblebee is a slave, 100%.
- But he likes it, he wants to stay.
- Do the cars respect ownership?
- Bumblebee is--
- That little Bumblebee at the end of the first movie--
- Sorry, sorry Bumblebee, but your insurance lapsed.
(laughing)
- We gotta crush you into a cube.
- I forgot to pay the car, you're getting a repo.
Unfortunately, Bumblebee got repoed.
Bumblebee can't talk, he can't even talk, he can only speak through the radio, and then
at the end of the first movie, the Transformers are going away, they're leaving or whatever,
and then Bumblebee, he gets the ability to speak for the first time, and the first thing
he says is, "I will stay with the boy."
Bumblebee is the same logic as Pluto in Mickey Mouse.
He's pretty much a dog.
He's the only one who can't talk, and he has an owner.
Interesting.
It's just you don't ask the question.
Well, there are some that even more can't talk.
Some that are just go like, "Rawr!"
And they're just big monsters.
- Some are dinosaurs also.
- That's so true.
That's really true.
- There's a lot of Transformers lore
that I did not even fucking think existed
until I met Cameron.
- He knows everything.
- Really? - I don't know anything.
I only know about the Michael Bay ones.
- Have you read any of the comics?
- No.
- The comics are crazy.
- Yeah, I would like to.
- I didn't know you knew about Transformers too.
- You would.
You would know about Transformers.
That's too many. - Two people in my life
that know a lot about Transformers.
- That's too many.
I don't even know anything about Transformers.
I just like them.
I just think they're cool.
- It's a modern day space opera.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- I have to look into it now.
- I don't know about that.
- It's pretty sick.
- It's very cool.
- I only saw the first three though.
I didn't see the rest of them.
- Dude, five is so sick.
- I saw the first one, that's it.
- Are they good past that?
- Five is really good.
Four is kind of bad.
- Okay, why?
- Five, the earth explodes
and they fight on all the different parts of the earth.
- Oh, that's cool.
- They're like flying around.
- Wait, I saw the one with, who is it?
- Mark Wahlberg?
Or some guy who looks like Mark Wahlberg?
- That's the one.
- TJ Miller's in that.
- Oh yeah, it's like Mark Wahlberg and his daughter?
- Yeah.
- Okay, that's the fourth one.
- And TJ Miller dies.
- I saw that one.
Oh, whoa.
- He does.
- Oh yeah, he gets him turned into metal.
- That's so cool.
- Yeah, 'cause he's like,
isn't TJ Miller one of the science guys?
- No, he's like his dumb friend.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
- He's just like, "Holy crap, there's freaking
transformers."
- And then he gets brutalized.
- Yeah, and then he gets turned into a metal statue
And then it explodes.
Wow, that's so cool.
It is pretty cool. It's the only part I've ever seen.
Even, they even like, they wrote Megan Fox out of the movies like completely no, nothing.
They just like, she was in a movie and then she wasn't in a movie.
But TJ Miller, they were like, no, we're going to kill him on screen really crazy.
This character's not going to be in anymore.
We're going to really destroy him.
That's the only scene from that movie I've ever watched because I just YouTube just TJ Miller death scene and it came out.
The scene where he's Mark Wahlberg's in like a barn and he gets up and just goes,
I think we found a transformer.
Yeah.
He's so fucking sick.
He's still got like the Boston accent even though he's in like Kansas or something.
He's supposed to be like a bum kid.
You know what his name is in those movies?
Gigg.
Cade Yeager.
Oh yeah, we've talked about Cade.
And he's in love with a girl named Vivian Wembley.
She sounds rich.
Yeah.
She sounds sexy.
She's a beautiful British woman.
Does her legs up?
Oh, she long legs.
Is that the daughter?
Or is that a different person?
Yeah, that's his daughter.
(laughing)
- He's in love with his daughter.
- That's a beautiful British guy.
(laughing)
- That's really awesome.
- I would love to drop Mark Wahlberg
in the middle of London and just let him
do whatever he wants.
- There's a documentary.
- Listen, if Mark Wahlberg was in London,
things would have gone down a little bit.
(laughing)
Just in general, just in general.
- Everything would be different.
It'd still be fucking Peaky Blinders over there right now.
- Oh yeah.
- He would have made sure.
- Yeah, the Irish would take over.
- Yeah.
- Is he Irish?
- Oh.
- Is he?
He's a he's he's Boston Irish
It's funny
Thank you
I like wall bowls
You know it's Wow actually
But it's
Where you buy the domain google.com or something hoping someone will go there by somebody will accidentally walk into wall
We have to sit on this domain, I think that Marky Mark is gonna fuck in he's gonna make a wall food soon
Yeah, he's a used car dealership in like, Ohio. Do you know that?
Yeah, he's got like in it like
He goes he goes to every talks to every
- He thinks every one of them might be a Transformer.
- Opening, yeah.
- Come on.
- Every day he walks in and I'm like,
"I know you can fucking do it."
- I know you can do it.
- I think I found a Transformer.
- No, no, Mark.
- No, the Chargers, I know the Chargers
is gonna talk to me.
- No, Mark.
- It's gonna fucking talk to me.
- No, no, no.
- Go home, go back to Boston, Mark.
- Come on, Mark.
- Mark, we don't want you here, you don't own this place.
- I know, I know, you put your name on the,
you only bought your name on the building,
- You only bought your name on the building,
you don't own anything else.
You don't have to leave us alone.
You just bought the words, you need to put them somewhere.
- He takes out a sack of McDonald's hamburgers
and he gives them to each car,
and then just takes one out and smashes it on the hood.
It's like, is this food?
Do you like this?
- You like the food?
- He's a--
- I'm gonna feed you, you're my car.
- He has like a half a billion dollars.
- Dude, I'm surprised he doesn't have more than that.
- He's also hella Catholic.
- And ripped, by the way.
- Yeah, and he sleeps like one hour a night.
- God, we should do that.
We should figure out how to do all that.
- You already sleep one hour a night.
- That's true.
- I gotta work on that though.
- I'm almost there, I'm almost there.
- He's pretty much sleeps one hour a night.
- That's Catholicism.
- Yeah.
- You should join his, what's his app called?
It's called like--
- Hallow.
- Hallow, yeah.
- I've seen the app.
- What is that?
- It's a Catholic app?
- Mark Wahlberg's Catholic app.
- What does it help you with?
- It helps you do like,
- Be Catholic.
- Catechism and stuff.
It helps you remember the prayers and shit.
- I don't really know that much about Catholicism.
- What's his stupid fucking--
- Mark Wahlberg's app.
- There's a--
- Join Mark Wahlberg as Father Stu on Halo.
- Oh, so it's a Halo exclusive.
Look at that fucking (laughs)
- Wow.
- It's a shitty DVD cover.
- Yeah, I'm making a movie and I'm only releasing it
on my app.
(laughing)
That's it.
- So, we've only had 12 viewers so far,
But when you scale that to how hard it is to use the app,
it's not easy to be a movie theater.
That's basically like 100 million people saw the movie.
Wow, these are some good reviews.
That is definitely a real quote.
This is the best app I've ever downloaded.
Guy who's downloaded a roll of an app.
I like that you can't see the font in the background
are the same color.
It's really quite poorly made.
I would like to--
let's see if we can find some--
Whoa, Jim Caviezel's on there.
Mark Wahlberg-- no, just choose Mark Wahlberg.
Choose your paragraph.
- Obviously, I'm going with Mark Wahlberg, it's his ad.
- I went from not praying at all to praying twice a day.
That's a pretty big increase.
- That is a huge increase. - Just continue with Google.
- Yeah, just signed into Google there.
- There we go.
- All right, we're gonna get right into here.
- I'll do a prayer.
I would like to get religious pretty soon.
- Oh, a 14-day free trial.
- Wait, what?
You have to pay for this?
- It's cost-free.
- Of course you have to pay.
- Caleb, Caleb, get your card out real quick.
- Yeah, let's just say--
- Look, getting close to God isn't easy.
- So Visa always starts with 4117.
(laughing)
- Pajaradrone.
- Pajaradyrone.
- Pajaradyrone, yeah.
- All right, what's the card number?
4 4 7 0.
Okay, no Zivisa.
- All right, now let's do a bunch of random numbers.
- Yeah, just throw in a random card.
I think it'll work.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- We need to make an app, man.
- Can we get a free trial?
- Wow.
- That was too many numbers?
- Yeah, I think that was way too many numbers.
- Yeah, I think you put in too many numbers.
- No, I think that's the right amount of numbers.
- That's the correct amount of numbers.
- No, it must be too many numbers
That's why it's not working.
- Let's see if we can guess a credit card number.
(laughing)
- If we guess a credit card number live on the air,
it'll be great.
- What, how hard can it be?
- And we're gonna be here until we do it.
(laughing)
- We're not getting up until we guess a credit card number.
- I've always thought it probably can't be that hard
to guess a credit card number.
- I mean, it's just chance.
- Yeah, exactly.
- I could sit down and do it right now.
I mean, it might not happen, but it might.
- It's probably the same odds as like playing the lottery.
- Yeah.
- But you can do it for free.
- It's even better.
- Exactly like the lottery.
- Yeah, it's the same odds as the lottery.
- What the rules are, because I bet someone's figured out,
well, visas start with 4323,
and they go from this set of numbers
to this set of numbers.
- Yeah.
- I need to just get a job at Visa.
- Maybe, that's good.
- So stealing cards.
- That's really, really good.
- I guess credit card numbers all the time,
but it's not really guessing, you know?
It's just like knowing the rules.
- Oh yeah.
Have you guys ever seen those videos?
- I haven't paid for anything in years.
- I see numbers in front of me constantly.
- My whole life is free.
- The whole world is just a series of math equations.
- I just bought a house.
- I know how all of you are gonna die.
- Car, kills himself after he kills me with a car.
Drowns in the bathtub.
- And I'm a mortal.
- Actually, car, same car, same car.
(laughing)
- Whoa.
- And I'm gonna be on the street taking it all in.
(laughing)
- Whoa.
- Just leave your phone, non-citizen.
- That's how you die?
- Yeah.
- That's how Grace dies.
- Heart attack from like, "No, my friends!"
(laughing)
- My friends!
- "No!"
- I die from the grief of realizing
I should have done anything to stop it.
- Patrick's gonna be the first person to die
since like 1300 to die of fear.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Do people die from that all the time?
- I almost died from that a couple times.
- My brother's old house.
- Halloween is the worst for me.
I go to the hospital every year on Halloween.
People used to die from fright, but now it's just cardiac arrest.
My brother had a house that burned, after he moved out, it burned down and it was a girl
and her grandma lived there and the girl died in the house from the fire and then the grandma
ran out and got so scared that she had a heart attack and died.
Which is some like Coen Brothers shit.
That's crazy.
I'm talking about dying.
That's really unfortunate.
Your heart, it's not even about a heart attack, you're just so scared that you just can't
be alive.
There's no physical way, there's no reason why you died in the coroner report.
It's like Looney Tunes, you come out of your body and that's just it.
and then you're just a blue thing just kinda floating.
- And then you're a ghost away.
- They always look--
- That's what happened to Casper.
- Yeah, it's exactly what happened.
- He was just scared of puberty.
(laughing)
- Oh, my body's changing!
(screaming)
- And then he got flown out of his own body.
- Yeah.
- He one day woke up to this giant cock
and just jumped out of his own shit.
- Oh no, there's pubes!
- And by the way, he's shaggy.
- I need to be smooth, I need to be pure,
I need to be clean!
I
Just thought of the best evil plan of all time
What's that I will learn to astral project and I will make someone else learn to do it with me or I'll find someone else
Who knows how to do it?
Well astral project together and then right as they leave their body. I'm gonna go into their body and steal it
Bagans
series of paranormal books that came out around when we were kids.
And he was always getting into hijinks like Astral Project.
And the guy's name was Zach Files?
Yeah, the guy's name was Zach Files.
Wait, Astral Project? That's a hijink in that show?
It was a TV show too, but it was also a series of books.
Kind of like a series of unfortunate events or something.
Oh, okay. I don't remember those.
I thought you were talking about Zach Bagans, the ghost hunter.
Nobody's read the Zach Files.
No.
You made it up.
I think he did.
I made it up.
I don't believe it's real.
I wrote it.
That's so awesome.
You guys are the greatest publishers ever.
It's a great YA book that's coming out this year.
Do you guys have any kids in your lives that you want to order?
It's a great book.
The author, I hear she's really nice.
She's really great.
She's really, really good.
I feel like everybody has one.
Someone called her brilliant.
Everybody has one thing like that that they loved when they were a kid that nobody else
has ever fucking heard of.
Oh, yeah.
And I know exactly the one.
It's like the kangaroos and they have elemental powers and the kangaroos have super powers
and they can fly.
And they can do all kinds of things.
And I think that's what's so cool about it.
I think it's so cool.
like that that they loved when they were a kid that nobody else has ever fucking heard
of. Oh yeah and I know exactly the one it's like the kangaroos and they have elemental
powers and the kid falls into a well. What are you talking about? They're called warriors
of virtue. Warriors of virtue. Is that a spin off of the cat warriors? No. A spin off of
the cat warriors that's about kangaroos? No they're their own property it's called warriors
- You guys have read the, has anyone here read
Warriors and the Cats? - I read like one,
I read like one in fifth grade
and I was like, I can't do this.
- Yeah, I read like, you know, just like 30 in fifth grade.
(laughing)
- For me, that one thing is probably this one porn video.
It was so good.
- I gotta come back.
- When I was like five years old, it was amazing.
- I know of one.
- It was my secret planet that I used to travel to.
- Yeah. - Oh, that's good.
- That no one else could go to,
and my secret spaceship. - That's really good.
- No, I've actually been there.
- No, I don't think you have.
- I have, I've actually been there.
- No, 'cause we have detectors there that detect people.
- No, I've actually been there a few times.
Well, they didn't work on me.
- Oh, okay.
- You're in fantasy land.
What you're saying makes no sense.
- No, no, no, he didn't code them to recognize women.
- You've never been off-world.
- So I, so.
(laughing)
- My alarm should have gone off.
- I've been-- - You're air-tagged.
- I've been off world.
- You have not been off world.
- You've not been off world.
- I've been off world.
I've literally been off world.
- Imagine how much it would suck if you lost your wallet,
you checked the air tag and it's like zoomed out
to show the galaxy.
- Oh no.
- Yeah.
- It's fucking space junk now.
- You get a--
- My Air Pods, my fucking Air Pods are in the--
- You just open the thing, you can't even see the dot
'cause it's so zoomed out, it's just a full picture of stars.
- Yeah.
- Oh great.
One time I tried to throw my air tag as high as I could
and it just never came back down.
(laughter)
Damn, you're fucking strong.
I know, it's crazy.
Somebody needs to get an air tag on one of these UFOs
that are running around the block.
Oh, yeah.
Somebody's got to get an air tag on one of these UFOs.
Actually, it's foolish of you to think there isn't one.
You know, they all do have air tags.
Where do you think the air tags came from?
Yeah, exactly.
That kind of technology makes no sense at all.
It was here before us.
Air tags were here before.
(laughter)
When we arrived, the air tags were here.
People will be digging up in their backyards,
they think they found an arrowhead.
No, that's an air tag.
It's the original air tag.
It's a primitive air tag, yeah.
It's the same metal that they use.
It's like Halloween 3.
And they have the chips in the back.
Yeah, back in medieval times, I used to air tag my son,
and I just always could tell where he was.
I could just tell.
I do think that you should be able to,
everybody should have a chip in them.
They're like a mark of the beast.
Yeah, that's good.
She got that chip in her.
Yeah, exactly.
It would be nice to get a chip in me,
because then I would just know that I was going to hell.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Just come out with it already.
Just do the mark of the beast already.
Obama, come back, put a chip in my right hand.
Yeah, there's dudes like those fucking stupid--
what are they called?
The cyber whatever.
The guys who put RFID chips in their hands
and lock their doors.
- Yeah, that's cool.
- I saw some guy who had a chip in his head
and some sort of implant that like,
I don't know if it was a speaker
or it just reacted to music,
but it made his whole head like,
going, like his skin would like wave out.
- Whoa. - Yeah.
- It really looked gross.
Like it really looked pretty disgusting.
And I don't know what the utility of that was.
- Yeah, what is that called?
There's a word for that that I'm like completely blanking on.
- Cool as hell.
- Yeah.
- Technology.
- Transhumanist?
- Transhumanist, that's what it is.
- I don't believe in any of that crap.
Keep it away from my daughter.
(laughing)
Keep that shit away from my daughter.
- Are you grooming my kid to become one of those robot dogs?
(laughing)
- I don't let my daughter--
- Are you grooming my kid to be one of those robots?
- You come around here with those AirPods,
I can tell that you're trying to groom my kid
to love technology.
- Apple is grooming our kids.
- You send your kid to kindergarten,
they come back with pink hair and red eyes
(laughing)
- What the fuck are they doing in there?
- And a tog made out of the tape and done with a VHS.
(laughing)
What the hell's going on?
- My five year old daughter is so strong,
I can't even hit her anymore.
(laughing)
She hits back and it hurts like hell.
- It hurts me.
- She's got these rubber dogs.
- And her eyes are fucking cameras,
so she remembers everything.
- And obviously her hair is all ribbon cables.
- And obviously her hair is still real hair.
(laughing)
- She was like,
My daughter told me she was like,
- Obviously she still has real hair.
- Oh, what do you think?
What do you think?
(laughing)
What do you think would happen?
They're not gonna put any kind of fucking cables
in her head.
No, that hair is normal.
- They replaced her feet with a bunch of robotic crabs.
So she's always scuttling around.
- I tell my daughter,
you better get rid of all that robot crap.
She says, I hate you.
I'm running away.
I say, oh yeah, we'll see how far you get.
She blasts off through the roof.
(laughing)
I see her on the moon now.
She's in satellite images.
She's a cloud of smoke.
She packed up her books.
I'm pretty sure she's having sex with the ghosts of the moon.
Of the civilization that used to be on the moon.
That has since fallen.
It's so fucked up what's going on in this god damn country.
My fucking kid's got a second Saturn in its chest now.
I've been playing games on my kid.
(laughing)
- But it is fun though,
it does make game night a lot easier.
- I gotta fuckin' blow on the cartridge every night
to put his bedtime story into his chest.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- I gotta fuckin' huff and puff.
- Son, get down here, I'm trying to play,
daddy's trying to play a damn game.
Get down here so I can play my games on that.
- Hey, daddy's got 2K.
- Yeah.
- When you just got the new 2K, get over here.
- When you play a video game on me,
I black out until you're done.
- Good.
- Okay.
(laughing)
You're a growing boy, you need to sleep.
- It doesn't matter what I do,
well, you're blacked out playing the game.
- All these cyborg kids, I heard there's a new cyborg kid,
they're putting a breathalyzer on him
to make sure you're parenting him right.
- You have to blow on him.
- You have to blow on the back of his head.
- Before you order him to do his homework or anything,
you gotta make sure you're not drunk.
- I've talked about it before,
but it would be so amazing if they made a TV
that went in the back of your girlfriend's head.
- My son's breathalyzer's on his dick, is that normal?
(laughing)
- I think you choose, you have to choose where to put it.
- No.
- Yeah, you get to choose where to put it.
- You're like, I chose to put it on.
- The doctor talked me into it.
- I don't think so.
(laughing)
- What do you mean doctor, there's no doctor here.
- So I flipped a coin.
So I flipped a coin, big deal.
(laughing)
- You don't wanna know the other side of the coin though.
- Thankfully it was the good side.
(laughing)
yes it was a three-sided coin
it's not important what the other side was, ok?
it doesn't matter what the other side was
but anyways, now I'm blowing my kid in more ways than one
every time I want him to do his goddamn homework
it's not sexual, but uh
that would be maybe...
son, it's time for dinner
wait, wait, what?
I think it's great that every...
- I'm getting cramped back and forth.
- Every pod, April finds a way to talk about her future son.
- And blowing him?
(laughing)
- But in this time, I guess you did it for good reasons.
- Yeah.
- We're talking about a cyborg kid, this is not a human.
- I'm talking about a dystopian future.
- Exactly.
- I'm talking about how much it would suck.
- This is a cautionary tale.
- It's a cautionary tale.
- This is a Margaret Atwood--
- This is 1984.
This is a brave new world.
- Margaret Atwood's new novel.
Parents have to suck off their kids.
(laughing)
- For some reason.
- It's called The Handjob Tale.
- Yeah, it's what it's called.
- It's a Margaret Atwood book
that starts with the main character's watching child porn.
And she's like, "Yeah, everybody does it."
- What book so that I can not read it?
Yeah, no, tell me what book and what pages
so I can not read them.
(laughing)
- Oh, yeah, it's Oryx and Greg,
and probably like the first few Jap days.
- Cool, so I'm gonna go, I have to go not,
(laughing)
I have to go not read that really quick.
Really quickly, I have to go not read that.
- She's a one sick puppy, I could never come up with that.
I'd probably put-- - Some twisted ideas.
- I'd put the girls in bikinis if I was her.
- That's what I would do. - Some red dresses.
- Can I say something?
- Like maybe they're watching--
- Yeah, speak on it. - Can I say something
really quick, Cameron? - Yeah, go ahead.
- So lately I've been reading some science fiction.
- Okay. - And it's kinda funny,
'cause I've been reading science fiction,
I think to myself, that's funny,
'cause a lot of modern science is fiction.
- Yeah, evolution, abortion, gay marriage.
- Gastropubs.
- These are scientific--
- Gastropubs are fucked, yeah.
- In what world, what's gastro about this pub?
- Oh yeah, what I do in the bathroom after?
- Yeah, that's right.
- That's where the gas--
- I trow, I trow all the gas.
- That's where the gas go.
- I trow the gas out me.
- I trow the gas in the toilet.
I trow the gas.
(laughing)
That doesn't make any sense, you fuckin' gastropub.
That's why they're always Irish themed, because you trow da gas at ya.
If I don't see bubbling...
Oh, it's Irish?
Oh, I trow da gas at me!
That's an Irish accent.
If I don't see bubbling blue and green liquids when I go into a gas drum pub, I'm shooting the whole place up.
I'm gonna fucking shoot the place up with a fucking gun.
There's one of those science bars down the street over there.
Well, I'd be careful because I'm going to go check it out.
I'm going to pretend I'm the science inspector.
If it was a real gastropub, the crazy thing is,
because of all the molecular gastronomy that would be happening,
you fire one bullet and it would all blow up.
Yeah, true.
So you can tell they deserve it because you fire a few bullets and nothing happens.
Exactly.
Yeah, I wouldn't even aim for people.
I'd aim for the beakers.
As a terrorist, I need to get my hands on that little thing
that Walter White uses in Breaking Bad where he blows up the whole place
- Oh, that's good. - Oh, yeah.
- Stuff cold. - We better pray
that the terrorists don't get that.
- That is, I was watching, I was like,
"Bro, do you really want people to know about this shit?"
- Um, actual terrorists here, and--
(laughing)
- We actually already used that.
- First of all-- - And we learned
about it from the show. - Oh, fuck.
- It's a white crystal, he throws it at the ground,
it blows out every window in a two-story building.
- And a bunch of car alarms go off outside.
- And then he just walks out, not a scratch on him.
Whatever that is, is an amazing, amazing super weapon.
- I'm imagining like a guy that's like,
- I've seen a guy from the Islamic State being like,
"It's so fucked up that they showed a white guy doing that."
(laughing)
Every guy I know who knows how to do that
is not a white man.
(laughing)
- You had it up there, Jubio.
You were passing.
- Wait, why are they googling?
- We almost found out what it was
and you went back to the cyber guys.
- Go back to it.
You need to show a picture of this thing.
- Why were they googling pictures of my dad?
- That right there.
- This is not meth.
Wait, they're faking it.
- It's perfect, it's a gift.
See, I really need this.
- It's the little thing.
- Oh my god.
- Can we make it even smaller?
- Yeah, let's shrink this gift down.
- Can we make it even smaller than that?
- No, that was the opposite.
- There we go.
Oh, there it goes.
- Yeah, get it smaller.
Get it as small as it can be.
- It's too big, I can't see it.
It needs to get smaller.
- I'm making a spilling my whole field of vision.
I can't figure out a single detail.
- I'm overwhelmed, I'm overwhelmed.
This is how it's supposed to be.
- Do you think that that was a wake up call
for police officers and law enforcement in this country,
where they were like,
"We need to start looking at the scientists."
- Yeah. - Probably.
- We need to learn about science.
- Because scientists probably--
- You think there's a cop sitting in the back
of every single science class?
- Yeah, there's one--
- Trusted pinwheel hat.
- Actually, one person in every science class
is the science marshal.
The undercover cop in every high school science class.
- Just the one guy in your science class
who has tissue paper on his face
'cause he cut himself shaving.
- And the one in my high school
always tried to sleep with all the girls
and was really cuddly.
- He was like, "What, I'm a high schooler."
- I'm a clearly high schooler.
- He was like, "Oh, you guys like science?
"Okay, I just took this concoction, now I'm 15."
(laughing)
It's okay.
- Yeah, it's fine, it's totally fine.
- As a police officer, after Breaking Bad came out,
whenever I was arresting somebody,
kind of a hoodlum type with a hoodie,
and seemed kind of young. - A thug.
Yeah, a thug. I'd have him up against the car, holding him, and I'd be like, "Who's your science teacher? Where's your science teacher at?"
Listen, as a meth dealer, that's actually very traumatizing for us. I just thought you might like to know that so you can change your ways.
I actually find that traumatizing when that happens. Just speaking from my perspective as an actor.
Whenever I yell at April, she really freezes up. So if you really want to know where her dealers are in the Adiata, you've got to kind of buy her Mickey D's first.
- Okay, that's a good tag.
- Right now, the shamrock shake is back.
- For real?
- And put the McDonald's logo at the bottom of the screen.
- That's none of my fucking business.
That shamrock shake, I will never have one
for as long as I live.
- You are insane.
It is one of the greatest things ever made at McDonald's.
- Here's what you gotta do.
You gotta bring Caleb coffee, put shamrock shake in it.
- I'll fall for it.
- And that's how we're gonna get him
to drink shamrock shake.
- I think that I'm finally an adult
'cause I can't do a milkshake.
It's not that I'll still watch Transformers.
I'll still watch Yu-Gi-Oh!
But I can't drink a milkshake.
And I think that makes me--
no, not anymore.
Actually, I just stopped right now.
Something just made me realize I shouldn't watch Yu-Gi-Oh! anymore.
Something about it seems kind of gay to me now.
Yeah, actually, I always thought it was stupid, too.
Yeah.
I mean, yeah, I just thought better of you than that.
It's just mega shit.
You know?
Yu-Gi-Oh!
I actually did stop watching Yu-Gi-Oh!
maybe three years ago. So yeah, I remember you pulling up to recording one day with
like a Yu-Gi-Oh t-shirt and I was like, Oh, you can have a Yu-Gi-Oh t-shirt.
That's cool. You have a CKY t-shirt on. That is,
they're a good band. That is the same. That's the same as you.
That is not the same as Yu-Gi-Oh, cause you learn about it at different times.
You can make money playing Yu-Gi-Oh. True.
You can make money getting in a shopping cart and having your friend throw you
- Not anymore.
- That's true.
- You actually can't make money off of it.
- That's true, that's actually true.
- Pat still kind of thinks that's a job
he could maybe get away with.
(laughing)
- That's like his fallback.
- I'm only doing the podcast to kind of try to get in it.
- Yeah, it's so I can fund, like, I'm gonna buy--
- How pissed were you when they made a new Jackass
and you didn't even get a little bit asked to do it?
- I don't want to talk about it on here.
- It really pissed you off, didn't it?
- I actually--
- I don't want to talk about it on here,
but my audition tape was really fucking good.
- I actually got a callback for the new Jackass.
They asked me to be in it too and I was like, I would love to be in it, but honestly, I don't
really care enough.
Yeah.
I made a video of me just kind of cutting myself.
Like self-harm cutting on my leg.
Cutting this in your leg.
And they were like, that's not jackass.
I was in the mirror going, you're worthless.
You're nothing.
You're a piece of shit.
They said my stand up was too good.
I believe it.
Speaking of your stand up, guys, where can people go look for your tour?
What's the website?
Girl.live.com
Doing a million and billion cities
I'm going to list literally all the cities off right now
List them
If you forget any of them I'm going to verbally abuse you
On Thursday we're starting in Richmond
And then this weekend we're in Orlando
And then Atlanta
Nashville, Detroit
Milwaukee, Chicago
St. Louis
Iowa City, Denver
Phoenix, San Diego
San Francisco
Portland, Seattle, Los Angeles.
You did really good. That's all of them.
That was really impressive. I couldn't remember all that.
So you can go to girlguidelive.com and you don't have to buy 100 tickets, but it's, you know.
It's definitely helpful.
It's encouraged.
Yeah, it's really encouraged.
Especially if you're in Phoenix.
And the CAPTCHA for all of our tickets are "Select all the real women."
Yeah.
If you want to buy tickets to Girl Guide, you can select all the bio women.
All right, thank you all for coming on.
Thank you all for coming on.
- Don't buy a bunch of San Francisco tickets in my name.
- Buy a bunch of San Francisco tickets.
You'd fit right in, right?
- Hey. - Gay city.
- Okay, bye guys.
- I went there for some reason.
- Thanks for having us guys.
Bye bye. - Bye.
Peace.