(upbeat music)
- You take that back, I am not in my flop era.
- He is in his flop era.
- I think he is.
- I am not in my flop era.
- Patrick is in his flop era.
- Two things I realized this week.
Number one, Patrick clearly in his flop era.
The history records will show.
- The flopster.
- This is him flopping.
2023 is his flop era.
- You're the flopster, you're floppy bro.
- I'm not floppy.
I'm not floppy bird.
I'm not I don't wake up. I don't wait up and eat flop jacks. I don't do that. You know, I don't have a flop
Pacino you do uh-uh you do you eat?
You do eat food. I don't eat flop suey and you eat flop
I don't even
flop deliver
Fleas
Yeah, I don't have a flop fleas at the flop
And you guys got arrested by the flops.
I did not get arrested by the flops.
For being in your flop era?
Uh-uh.
Number two thing.
They said, "Sir, please stand right here and flop in a straight line."
You said, "Certainly, officer."
I wasn't gone up the soda flop.
You were.
You were completely gone off a soda flop.
Nope.
Lolli flop.
I did not have a lolli flop.
Yeah.
Or a flopsicle.
You had a flopsicle.
I did not have a flopsicle.
Actually, you didn't have one.
You invented one.
I did not invent a flopsicle.
I'm not a flopper.
Yeah, you are.
You are a complete flopper.
The number two thing that I realized is that I...
The number two.
It's okay to be...
It's okay to be tired and mentally...
Okay, America's flop model.
America's flop model.
I think half of his face is about to flop.
Damn.
He can't speak.
He's gonna have a stroke.
A stroke?
Stroke.
He's post-flop and pre-flop.
You're pre-flop.
And he's flopping right now.
You're about to flop so hard.
He is flopping.
You're flopping right now.
I'm not flopping.
you're saying is a complete flop, a bomb. You're bombing, you're flopping.
No. You're flopping. I'm not flopping.
Number two thing I realized. I am Patrick's ultimate idol and hero. I realized that recently.
He's been patterning for two years now. Can I say something? He's been patterning everything
after me. He wants to be me. I'm his idol. I'm his hero. Every single time I talk to
him, he is dropping subtle hints that he is looking up at me. He looks up to me, basically,
is what I'm saying. And I'm his hero, I'm his idol. And I just want to say that publicly.
So next time if you ever see me and him doing something similar, I always did it first and
I'm his idol so he's copying me.
I'm not copying.
You are.
I'm not even floppy.
And he also just got a song in the flop music flop 40.
Oh he did, yeah.
And it wasn't Lolliflop.
It was Lolliflop by you and two clones.
Two clones of me?
Yeah.
It was not.
Was not lolliflop. What would you say over if you if you looked at your lives?
Like she flop it like a lolliflop
If you see shorty wanna fly off. He's even flopping right now. He's bombing
Well you just need to stop flopping good, I don't flop that much anymore you've got a bomb on us you flopped a bomb
(laughing)
♪ You flopped a bomb on me ♪
♪ Oh you flopped a bomb, Pat ♪
- You don't know the words.
- Put that away.
- I'm not putting it away.
I have to, I drank all the cold brew
and my girlfriend's mad at me.
- That was a flop for her.
- That was a flop for her, yeah.
- Okay, smooth flopperator.
- I just got into Sade.
- Really?
- I really just did.
- An interesting thing to do late in life,
kind of a flop.
- Late in life.
(laughing)
I don't have much time left.
Late in life.
Yeah, what are you guys going to do in your sundown years?
Next year?
Yeah, now that we're getting into those.
Inventor, magician.
That's pretty good.
I'm running towards 30.
Forest.
I'm scared.
Literally, I'm not going to see 31.
Why?
You're going to flop too hard one day?
Maybe.
Splatter when you hit the toilet?
I think I told my ex-girlfriend one time, I was like, "If I'm not successful by the time
I'm 28, I think I'm done."
Kill.
I'm just going to ...
Me and Cam used to talk about that all the time in college.
We were always like, "Yeah."
At 28, if you're not doing anything by the 28th ...
I think ours was earlier than 28.
I think, yeah.
I remember Cam said, "Yeah, I think what I'll do is I'll give myself one year to have anything
cool happened to me after college and then if it doesn't happen then I'll work at McDonald's
and then when I turn 24 I'll kill myself and I was in a pretty bad enough place that I
heard that and instead of being like whoa I was like it's actually a pretty good plan.
Yeah I guess that makes sense.
Yeah and luckily for me COVID hit.
Yeah and then something very cool happened.
Something very incredible happened.
Half the population died.
Yep.
Well you got to imagine.
Dude.
Do you realize?
in the Marvel universe, we would be profiting
so fucking hard off the Thanos.
- Oh my god, are you kidding me?
- Can you imagine how many, if we all survived,
how many people who are better than us at this
would have just been dead?
- Can you imagine though, if like two of us lived
and one of us died, the sympathy tour
that we could put together.
Oh my god, we would be no other, nobody could pack up.
Every venue's at half capacity.
- He dies at the gym or something,
because you let a weight crush his neck.
- Well no, I'm still talking about--
- Oh, the snap?
Oh, there you're talking about normal life.
- Flop, F-L-O-P, that spells flop.
- Nope.
Did not flop.
- Flop, flop, flop.
- Floptastic four.
- Anyway, so yeah, when, who's going to die,
eeny, meeny, miny--
- He's gonna die at the gym.
- Let's flip a coin.
- A three-way coin. - A three-way coin.
- Okay.
(laughing)
Let's do it. A three-way coin. Flip a three-way coin. Google that.
Oh my God, that was...
Work on that in the meantime.
That was already a result.
There we go. Roll a three-sided.
So who's one, two, three?
I'm number two.
I'll be number one if I have to.
What? I should have been number one.
I guess I'm three.
All right, ready?
The result was... it's two. It says roll number one, two right there.
Well, you need to roll it.
Okay, this thing doesn't work.
You're just re-rolling it a bunch. All right, this is nothing.
You're flopping. You're flopping and you're a ruiner.
It was two, so I die first. So when I die, not going to be the gym by the way.
It's going to be in the Piranhas or something.
No, Glory Hole.
It could be Piranhas at the gym.
Glory Hole at the gym? What gym do you go to that has a Glory Hole? Equinox?
Yeah.
Planet Flopness.
It's nothing. It's completely nothing.
Flops Gym.
Yeah, what's your what laundromat to go to the flopping laundromat? Yeah, yeah, you do
go there though. But when I die, and like I said, it doesn't really matter how I die,
a beautiful woman will be involved in some way, maybe murder suicide. But if I die, what
do you guys beautiful woman will be involved because she's gonna say you did something
and you're gonna kill yourself? No, kill her. No, I'll kill her. I'll kill her. I'll kill
her. I'll kill her. I'll kill her. I'll kill her. I'll kill her. I'll kill her. I'll kill
No, I'll kill her first I kill her and then I kill myself
He laughs at his own flops how embarrassing is that his own flops
He's laughing because your face got red no yeah
Laughing no blood vessels flopped yeah
Anyway when I die and you guys go out on the new tour yeah the Caleb death
It's called the Caleb's Bones Tour.
And you show my bones?
We have a, we do.
Like the Dead Sea Scrolls?
Oh yeah, we do like a road show.
We do, we have a little like, uh, we have a little like, like podcast about this museum.
It's in a trailer that we pull around to the back of the venue.
We keep putting like, pretty good idea.
We get a VIP ticket, you know, and a touch kit with bones.
We keep putting like alligator bones in it too.
Yeah, replacing all Caleb's teeth.
It's like, it's like your normal body, with just an alligator skull.
Just every stop you replace one bone with an alligator bone.
by the end of it, it's just one big alligator and you're like, yeah, this is
our dead friend.
And we let everyone rub the bones for good luck.
I think my bones, I think my bones are bad luck.
Yeah. Your bones are yellow.
I wanted to find out.
I think I have yellow fucking bones.
You have yellow mummified bones in your body.
I got mummy bones, man.
Because you get sick all the time.
Do mummies don't have, mummies do have bones.
Mummies bones.
Do mummies don't have bones?
Mummies have bones.
Or I asked a question that I interrupted myself with the wrong answer, then I
correct myself. Is it true that they take out the mummies brain through its nose?
Yeah, well they used to. Talk about a booger. I don't think they make mummies anymore. Talk about a booger for real.
They had to use a hook. They have like a...
You can try. Yeah, do we have a hook?
Yeah, I don't think we have a hook. We have an exact mummification stuff.
So they go and they go all the way up. Yeah, and they go like this.
And they spin it around in the person's brain. Yeah, and they pull it out through their nose.
I don't think my brain I don't mean to brag. I don't think my brain would fit through my nose
No, it would I'm sure they're not getting the whole thing. I mean, it's what like it's it's BC get it in chunks
Well, but I don't think they were you put her back then so they had tiny brain. Yeah, that's true tiner brains
I I would love to go back in time to mummy times and
Help them out by just just perfect head shots. Yeah, just go back with a big Barrett 50-caliber shooting all the mummies
- You know what I would do?
I would go back, I would--
- I thought you meant, "Ch-ch-ch."
- No, I would go back--
- That too, actually, change their lives.
- That's an even better idea.
I'd go back there with a Canon 7D.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I'm taking photos of them, I'm like,
"You are a natural beauty."
- Work it.
- I'd walk in there, I'd walk into the embalming room,
and I'd be like, and I'd see them, you know,
trying to pull out little pieces of brain with the hook,
and I'd be like, "No, no, no, step back,
"let me show you how it's done."
And I'd open the mummy's mouth,
I'd pull out little pieces of brain with the hook,
and I'd be like, "No, no, no, no, step back.
"Let me show you how it's done."
And it'd open the mummy's mouth,
and I'd put my mouth on the mummy's mouth, open,
and I'd just go (blows air)
I'd suck a whole brain out.
- You have an oyster in your mouth
so you can trick them into thinking that you're like God.
- I'll take all their brains out with my suction.
- I had an oyster the other day,
and I told the people that I was with that I liked it,
but I really did not like it.
- You don't like oysters?
- I'm not too big a fan of oysters.
- It's a booger. - I love oysters.
- That is a booger.
You
Then that would make sense yeah
Texture of a booger then you would like oysters. I never really got the taste for an oyster
I feel like I would if I kept going, but I don't really doesn't understand
Why do I want a cold boo first of all the best thing about boogers? I understand. I understand aphrodisiacs you I mean more than anybody
You are I yes
You are the ultimate
Idol
That's what you will die first because you'll probably die from fucking yeah
I'll probably let a three
fucking falling down an elevator shaft
See and that's it. That's kind of charm that will attract a harem of women to you
Yeah, it's disgusting what Cameron does on the weekends. I will say you know what he does
He's like doing some Thomas. It'll be a
Stuff yeah, he's doing Thomas middle greasy case if he goes to the goth
sex club. I eat for lunch. And then I go to the goth sex club. I load up on Mexican. I
load up on cards. Waffle from the waffle maker, greasy ass quesadilla, olives. And then hit
the sex club. No shower, no toothbrush. Then I go to the goth sex club. Milk shake in a
Gatorade bottle. Paint a bullseye on my asshole. I'm walking into that sex club, shaking up
the Gatorade bottle. Grease my hair back with Crisco. Yeah. And if I'm losing my energy's
flagging I'm rubbing my hands through my hair like I'm fixing it and I'm going. Just misunderstanding
what goth is to the point where you're just making yourself a disgusting trash monster.
I cover myself in. I burn a cork and I put it all over my face. I put all the ash on
my face so I look like a hobo. And I'm walking around sticking bindle, guess what's in that
stick and bindle. Creamed corn, just in the bag.
Just dripping everywhere?
Plastic bag.
Plastic bag on the end of a twig.
Do you guys think that...
On a twig that's long enough for me to put over my shoulder.
When we get older and all of our girlfriends and wives die...
Yeah, because they're dying first.
Because they'll die first. We pick them for that.
I'm sorry baby, but you're not going to outlive me.
You're done. Can we agree...
gonna die and then it's gonna make me really good at woodworking.
You're not gonna be a wood...
No, no, no, no. Something's gonna snap in my brain that turns me into just like a
stoic.
You're gonna think you're really good at woodworking.
Yeah, and you're just gonna bring out the worst tables ever, the worst shit of
all time.
I made a pencil.
On a lathe, you're making a single pencil?
There's no graphite in it at all. Yeah, it's just wood.
Check this out.
This is my new business, Pat's Pencils.
Pat's Pencils is good.
But I think I'd become a Houdini style escape artist,
but I would die on the first attempt.
As a widower?
Yeah.
I'd get into my armoire, because I'm older.
I can afford an armoire.
Straight up, I'd be so depressed as fuck
if my girlfriend ever died.
I would be sad at first, and then I'd go out and party.
[LAUGHTER]
I heard that.
Heard that.
Yeah, I would be sad for a couple of weeks,
and then I would basically be on a carnival cruise.
I've been doing back to back carnival cruises to get over it.
Right. Like, I don't know. The sea is calling me.
Meanwhile, I'm on a cruise boat that has a water slide on it and I'm pushing the
kids out of the way. I'm doing the water slide over and over and over.
And if a parent comes over and is like, what the fuck is wrong with you?
You have like, I have a death certificate from my girlfriend. I hold up.
I say, look at this. Next to a photo of her in a locket.
Yeah. Guys, I have a movie idea.
Okay. It's a A24 movie.
So I don't want to hear this.
Wait, no. So that's how you know.
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
That's how you know it's good.
Oh, right.
It's an A24 movie and it's about a guy.
And he's sold.
I'm sold already.
This is pretty good.
His wife dies.
He's in his late 40s.
Now you're losing me.
Or his very late 40s.
Maybe he's 49.
So like, so 60s.
No, he's 49.
Maybe he's even early 50s or mid early 50s.
51 to 52 to 53.
65.
So he's wife dies or I guess it's an A24 movie, his husband dies.
And then he is sitting on...
Okay, so already we're kind of leaning on the bury your gays trope.
Just getting the gay characters out of the way by killing them.
Do you want to get buried gay guys?
Because maybe you should stop interrupting me.
Flopper interrupter.
My TV tropes page is going to be a mile long and I don't give a fuck.
Listen, so his name is... who cares?
That's not his name. But he has a name, but it doesn't matter. He has a name,
though.
Scott.
Scott. Something like that.
See, that's why you need us here.
His husband dies, and then he's sitting on the couch, and he's flipping through
the channels, right? And he's watching ESPN. Well, no, he's watching ESPN2.
Logo. He's watching the Logo channel.
Commercials come, right? And he sees a commercial for Sandals Resorts, right?
Okay.
And he sees the family, and they're playing, and then he books a flight, and
and then it's like an hour and a half of him
basically doing like,
there's a movie that's like that,
but he's just like walking around sandals.
Yes, but he's just having the time of his life.
He completely gets over his husband.
- I bet it's called "Mandels"
'cause it's for only gay men.
- Why does it have to be,
the nice thing about,
here's what I like in movies,
I like gay stuff enough,
but I don't want it to be the whole movie's gay.
It should be like, oh, yeah, we know he's gay,
but he doesn't ever,
there's no guys in it,
and he never has sex with a guy.
It should be it should be something like like they're just kind of yeah
Yeah, and you're like, okay I can check that I'm a good guy cuz I didn't turn
But I don't want to see they don't they don't like show they just show one scene in the wood nor completely like normal movie
Yeah, just like a guy maybe it's like I don't know like an action movie or something
And then there's one scene where he's like on he's like driving his car and then he looks at it like he gets the grinder
Notification sound he looks at his
Yeah, okay.
He looks over and goes...
And the lead, and Scott is played by Jim Norton, I think, would be a really good kind of twist
for that.
Yeah.
All right.
That's your movie?
I just like the idea of a movie where a guy gets over his dead spouse by just going on
vacation.
Yeah.
And it's just like instantly solved pretty much.
And he doesn't meet...
No, he's not interested.
Maybe people come on to him and he's like, "What the fuck are you talking about?"
I'm not gay.
I mean, I'm gay.
I feel like this is a good concept, this is a good starting point for the concept for
a first movie.
I feel like then, you know, we can build a franchise out of this, movies two, three,
four, etc. and we don't even have to worry about the origin story, it just is on vacation
in the other movies.
We don't have to remember the gay stuff or the death or whatever.
Vacation, Scott's vacation.
Scott's no family vacation.
It's like Alien to Aliens, you know, it changes genres.
I just had an idea, you know how there's movies, you know how there's a couple of movies where
- He goes on a bunch of vacations.
- He goes on a bunch of vacations in the second one.
And it's more of an action vibe.
- You know how there's movies where people,
where this happens a lot also in life,
where somebody is in a straight relationship
and they have kids and stuff,
and then their spouse dies,
and like, what's that movie, Beginners?
- And they start lizin' it up.
- Yeah, they were gay the whole time,
and they're like, "Oh, finally I can be free."
But like, it's complicated.
- Michael Jackson thriller ending.
- Why is there not--
- That's true.
(laughing)
- Turning around.
- That's funny.
Why is there no movie where a guy pretended to be gay
his entire life and then his husband dies
and he's like, "Oh my God, I'm fine."
- I now pronounce you Chuck and Larry.
- That is not that.
- It's close enough.
- No, but I mean like--
- It's the closest we have.
- What if you had a high school boyfriend,
but you just, maybe as a joke,
somebody pranked you to that.
- Yeah, it was an accident.
and then 40 year marriage is just let's not even get into the specifics for
whatever reason. It was just an accident. It was just some kind of accident.
Some awful accident. Some confusing accident. But then 40 years later,
he dies and you finally are like, oh my God, I can be myself.
Hooters, Dave and Busters. Yep. All that kind of shit. Playing hockey and all
that. Oh, dude. Wouldn't that be cool? That'd be a cool movie. And it's like
kind of like you're learning. Oh, and there could be a scene where like you,
he he like finds a girl and they start hooking up and he like
and she's like,
sorry, I never learned.
My whole life.
No, sorry.
I was accidentally gay from the time I was 15 until a couple of days ago when my
husband died.
Yeah.
You know, I could see,
- I could see this movie, I think that if you just,
if you make the ending that he's like,
you know what, I actually am gay,
that movie could be made tomorrow.
- You think so?
- I think that that could be,
they would do that. - He realized that he wasn't,
that he was-- - He's like, okay,
maybe I'm gonna try it out.
I'm gonna try being straight, and it's a comedy about,
yeah, it's a comedy about how being straight is crazy.
- And it's called As an Arrow.
- Oh. - Oh.
- That took me a second, but that's good.
- And it only clicked for me.
it as a curved a twirling arrow. Oh my god this is so smart. As an arrow with a...
No he's wearing the arrow that goes through his head. That's like that.
Oh my god and he's in front of his husband's grave. And it's Steve Martin.
Yeah this is amazing because Steve Martin it looks older than he is.
Flop. Flop.
Pronunciation. Flop alert.
Pronunciation.
You should put a big alarm on the wall.
Flop alert.
I'm going to hit you.
You keep flopping like that.
Okay?
I'm going to cut your pay.
I'm going to dock your pay.
Don't dock my pay. I have to buy more wicker furniture.
Flop.
I have to buy all this fucking wicker furniture.
It sucks living with girls.
moved in with my girlfriend. She bought all this wicker dresser, and as soon as I saw
it, I was like, "Mo is going to climb the fuck out of that thing. That is not a good
idea." And she said, "Don't worry about it." This morning, I woke up to her screaming at
Mo to get down, and he's looking back. He's got his claws into the second dresser just
looking at her.
Full Spider-Man. That's the reason why at my house, all our
furniture is made of ice.
I wish, I hate wicker furniture so much I keep sitting down on it and I hear
and I'm like damn I'm getting heavy. I don't have any ice furniture all my
furniture is pewter. Pewter Schmidt, Carter Pewter Schmidt. It's actually computer furniture.
Richest fuck guy. What are you talking about? Carter Pewter Schmidt.
Don't know who that is. You have messed up his name I know that. Carter Pewter Schmidt.
There we go. Twice you just said his name wrong and I've never even heard that
that name and it was wrong. He said you know you know Carter
Peter Schmidt. No. Yeah, you do computer computer Schmidt.
Oh, that's part of the table. Carter Peter Schmidt from is it
this guy? Doctor Heinz Doofenshmirtz is that what you're
thinking? I think that's what I'm trying to say. I don't ****
with him at all. No, he's a **** but I will like listen. You
doctor Doofenshmirtz. I don't **** with him and a lot of
people say that but I know what you assume about me when I say that and
actually I don't much fuck with Perry the platypus either. I think that he's whack.
I think they are both not so great. What the flip? And I am more on the side of me.
I don't have allegiances to other people. Yeah. I'm a lone wolf.
That's actually cool as fuck. And I would kill either of them if I was in the show.
I would kill either of maybe your two friends to get ahead. I would kill
- I would kill anybody to get a head.
- Definitely.
- Or anybody.
- Yeah.
- To get some head.
- I would kill anyone for any reason.
- Yeah, I think I would too if I had enough wanting to.
- I would probably practice on women and children first.
- 'Cause they're easier.
- Yeah.
- And then I would move on to older men.
- Older men.
- First though, you know what, I will say,
I think guys my, then the most dangerous game.
- Speaking of being a serial killer, I think a huge,
a huge, no, that's not the most dangerous game at all.
That's probably the least dangerous game.
I mean the group we--
You could be lured in by a piece of cheese on a box.
No, no, no.
Like the guys that I'm speaking in second person.
Guys that look like me, like you two.
Guys that look like you.
You think a guy that looks like me is dangerous?
Yeah.
I think I could lure--
Probably dangerous behind a photo board.
If you were doing most dangerous game with Patrick,
what do you-- how are you getting him?
Because I'm thinking I'm getting--
I'm just going to walk up to him and grab him.
He's like, oh, hey.
Hey, Cameron.
You have no idea how good I am at hiding.
- I'd use retro game consoles to lure you
into big pits where you die on spikes.
- No, literally all you would have to do
is just put some kind of skateboard stuff.
- Some British comedy DVD entry.
You'd kill yourself if I put it off of a cliff.
- No, if I was in a Most Dangerous Game situation,
I would kill myself immediately
so that the other person doesn't win.
- Wait, they win instantly.
- No, that's not a win for them
'cause the whole point--
- Oh, they wanna hunt.
want to hunt me, right? So the thrill of the hunt is like null and void because I
took out whatever I like. Well, okay, let's okay.
To the flare gun they gave me. I just want you dead out of my mouth.
This scenario, it's a good thing to argue about, but let's be real,
they're not going to pick you. They're not, no. Yeah, you're just never going to be on
that island. If I'm on that island, it's as a butler. Well, no, but the butler would
be listing off names. And I'm the worst butler. And how about Patrick Doren? And
the guy would be like, no, he flops. He'd be a flopper. That's how I would catch
I'd put a pool out and you'd be like, "Oh."
You'd be like, "Oh."
I'd be in the pool and I'd be stimming.
No, you'd be jumping and flopping into the pool.
Yeah, I'd be stimming in the pool.
You couldn't help yourself.
That's my stim.
I'd be stimming with the jets in the pool.
I'd be steaming you in the pool.
You know what I'm saying.
Yeah.
I'd put my feet on there and get a full massage.
But a mistake that a lot of serial killers make nowadays, that if I were to be a serial
killer that I would do before I went out and started bloody swath of women and getting them
after dark in their apartments and the galleys and dumpsters, whatever, whatever, I would
probably first remove all my DNA.
Every part of DNA from your body.
I would just get rid of my DNA.
Burn it off.
You could just change your DNA if you had a splicer.
I would just, yeah, I would just splice it.
That would be so good.
Splice it with a cow.
Oh my god, this is a cow that's going around killing people.
But they would never expect a human if they keep finding cow DNA.
And they would think...
At first they'd be like, maybe he's wearing a cow skin jacket.
- And there would be an article in the New York Post
called Human Tipping.
- Okay.
- And it would be--
- The cow's going around tipping humans.
- The Human Tipper.
- The cow is--
- The Human Tipping Cow is walking around New York City.
- Again, another movie idea.
- The Human Tipper.
- That is--
- And he's part man, part cow.
- How are we not millionaires?
I don't understand.
- We have a million great movie ideas
and nobody listens to us.
- Scott's Vacation, The Human Tipper.
- Let's think of a third movie.
- What's the one where they get real small that we did?
Shrinkers. Shrinkers in the whole Shrinkers series. That was my idea.
Yeah, that's Cameron, yeah. Yeah, but we talked about it. We talked about it.
We talked about it, but just I want to claim ownership over Shrinkers.
That's okay. You can have that, but Shrinkers is Cameron's problem.
Well, then I get Human Tippers and I get Scott's Vacation too.
Well, I came up with Human Tippers DNA.
That whole thing.
Dude, did you come up with that name? And he said cow.
What movie?
You know, the person who comes up with the name of the movie doesn't get the movie.
Well, you were just saying plans for your life.
No, wait, it wasn't Scott's Vacation. It was As an Arrow.
As an Arrow.
- As an arrow. - As an arrow.
And I came up with the title, so I think I get that one.
- No you don't, 'cause I came up with the entire thing.
- I came up with the part where it was actually--
- Well you came up with human tippers
and I came up with the cow thing.
- Okay, so me and you cut him out.
- Okay. - And I came up with shrinkers.
- You didn't come up with shrinkers.
- I came up with a movie-- - There's literally proof
that I came up with shrinkers. - There's proof, run it back.
- But I don't even remember which one it was.
- What? - I don't remember
any of my accomplishments, 'cause I'm so humble.
- No, 'cause you flopped every single time
you accomplished anything. - I did not flop
every single time I make a movie.
You've only flopped.
I have never, ever flopped when we've come up with movie stuff.
Your movies, if they were in theaters, people would be, okay, here's your movies, right?
Your movies, the only person who would be in the theater to see your movies would be
there doing an inglorious bastard, set the whole thing on fire, shooting bullets into
the crowd, but there'd be nobody there.
There'd be nobody there because you didn't sell a single ticket.
- If your movies are showing at the AMC,
the workers would refuse to sweep the theater
if the credits were still playing.
They would not be going.
- Hey, here's your movie theater, right?
Here's somebody going up to the concession stand
outside of your movie.
Yeah, could I have 50 tomatoes, please?
- And could I have a box of flopcorn?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- It would be in a box.
- And they would be throwing the tomatoes.
- It would be in a box, it would be in a bag.
- And they'd be going to eat the flopcorn,
realizing that it's-- - 'Cause it's a small size,
'cause they don't even wanna spend
that much money at the theater.
- Yeah, 'cause people would buy tickets
just to throw tomatoes at your--
- So you're saying it would be the best worst movie ever?
- Huh?
- Flopcorn and soda flop for me.
- You're saying it would be the best worst movie ever?
- No, it wouldn't be,
people would not like it like that either.
It would not be a troll two kind of thing.
- Well, the movie is called Patrick's Tomatoes.
- Flop. - Patrick's Tomato Target.
(laughing)
- Just a movie target.
- That was genius.
- Okay, that was the first time in what,
30 minutes that you have not flopped.
- That's not true.
perfect that you stuck the landing on that one. That was a perfect one. That
was a pencil dive. You hit the bottom of the pool.
It turns out it's a lot safer to flop because the pool's only two feet deep.
Patrick's moving tomato target. It's three hours long. Oh my god. I would do
it singing at IMAX. Yo, wow. Huge ass theater. It's like I can grab the target.
It's harder too because the screen's so far away. I had to do special showings at
the aquarium just so they can get the pig full through my max. Oh, that'd be sick. Yeah,
damn. Or at a... Drive-in. Oh, a drive-in theater. Yeah. Oh my God. Maybe so you could
build a PVC pipe... There'd be so many car accidents. ...kind of tomato cannon and blow
it up. Oh, I was thinking like it's kind of like a derby and people would drive around
in a circle at the drive-in. Or a movie. It's the movie Tomato Target movie. A movie is
a derby... You know, I would... No, you're driving around the drive-in movie theater
trying to hit it from your car.
I would be so mad if I was having people over to watch a movie and I was like, "Alright
guys, let's watch Pulp Fiction." And everybody else is like, "No, we want to watch Patrick's
Moving Tomato Target." I'm like, "Please, we can do it at somebody else's house." I
already saw that, so I don't want to watch it.
It sucks when you get the special edition on Blu-ray and it changes the target from
red to green.
Yeah. Patrick just kept going in and editing it after it was released. It's like, "Just
Leave it in its original form.
- You have to get the D-Master off of Pirate Bay.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Give the people what they want.
- They don't want the green target.
- Yeah, they want the red.
- They want the red target.
- In Mexico, I do.
- What's the whole--
- That's true, 'cause they got the green tomatoes in Mexico.
- The whole tomato, just the stem is green.
- Uh-huh, uh-huh.
- No one wants to-- - Speak on it.
- No one's thinking about the stem.
Everyone's thinking about the stem.
- Why?
- Big, red, juicy beefsteak tomato.
- Why is there not more interactive movie theater experiences?
That is such a good idea.
- Go to the Museum of Science in Boston.
But I mean like, I should be able to go to AMC
and there should be a Talking Tom movie
where I can speak.
- They have video games you can play
before the movie at AMC.
- But why not an, like why not like a triple A,
like very like high budget version of one of those
where you can like make the decisions on your phone.
- You wanna watch Bandersnatch in the theater?
- No, no, no, 'cause I want there to be aliens and nudity.
- To me, that's what most 3D movies are to me
'cause I go to a 3D movie, I pretend I'm in the movie
I'm like go left go walk through attack hello I do fight hello
all right you argue argue your marriage story and movie and movie and sequence
and and and and it now start to get 15 minutes is the entire and and in the
movie and turn it off and movie and movie it's not a bad idea I've been in
the movies in a while I was thinking about going tonight I did not but
nothing looks very good to me right now.
I'm going hella to the movies.
I've not seen a movie since the Batman.
I don't want to--
Actually, no, I have not seen a movie.
You saw Avatar, right?
No.
Really?
Haven't seen a movie.
I thought the Batman was the last movie I saw in the theater.
Last movie I saw in the theater was Sonic 2.
Really?
Actually, if you count--
You go to the movies less than I do.
I don't go to the movies at all.
Wow.
The last-- if you want to get really technical--
Let's get it.
The last movie that I saw in a theater
was when we were at the Grand Canyon,
or no, no, no, what's that big crater we went to?
- Meteor crater.
- Meteor crater, and we went into that theater
with the Jackie Lopez.
- Jackie Lopez. - Jackie Lopez.
- That's the last movie I saw in the theater.
- Okay, we'll count that.
Last summer?
Holy shit. - That's the last movie
I've seen. - That's crazy.
- That was an amazing movie.
- Yeah, that was really, really good.
- Jackie Lopez, they went out.
- Speaking of interactive movies.
- Yeah, they blew up a meteor.
- You blow up a meteor with Jackie Lopez.
- You fly around. - Yeah, who is it?
Jackalope, which is a rabbit mixed with antlers.
Yeah.
Mixed with antlers.
Is it a real thing?
No, it's not real.
Yeah, it's a real animal.
Yes, it is real.
It's real.
I'm getting mixed signals.
Knowledge flop.
Somebody I was talking to at one point in my life
thought a jackalope was a real thing.
It was probably me.
I don't think it was you.
It was probably me after we left that theater.
And I was like, are we going to see a jackalope?
(laughing)
- I don't remember, I have no idea.
- My mom didn't believe that a narwhal was a real thing.
- See, that's the thing--
- That's one you don't think is real as a kid.
- Yeah, that one--
- But my mom was 40.
- That one is real, I think I get the two,
I'm like, there's no way a narwhal is real,
but a jackalope, that could happen.
- It is, there equally is.
- A jackalope is one of the animals that could be real.
- It could absolutely be real.
- Yeah, it's an easy one.
- It could definitely be real.
- Through enough genetic splicing.
- No, narwhal is real, no, it just like could be normal.
Just like if it had little antlers coming off of a rabbit,
that would make sense to me.
A narwhal, I think, is less--
A narwhal is literally like a fucking-- it's nothing.
You know, a narwhal, that's a tooth, not a horn.
Yeah.
It grows out of its mouth.
It's a big, long tooth.
Its body is the real confusing part.
Because it's not like a normal fish.
It's basically just a blob.
The body is just a mouth.
Yeah.
Is it a mammal?
It's all it is.
It's a whale, I think.
Oh, wow.
Well, with a big tooth.
Man.
That's where the name comes from.
Yeah, wall.
Narwhal.
Yeah, North Whale, I bet.
Because it has a tooth on the north.
Because it's from the north.
From the north side.
North side, north side.
But yeah, I think that I, you also don't see narwhals that often.
No, not very often at all.
I don't, I mean I saw a picture of somebody eating one.
I guess if I was, I guess if I lived in the Arctic Circle I would see them more maybe.
- If I lived in the Arctic Circle, yeah,
I would probably think a lot of animals weren't real.
- Do you guys believe in deep, dark, downstairs animals?
At the very bottom floor of the ocean?
- There are some of them so weird,
they're like hands that run around down there.
- What's that, that anglerfish?
- There's little goobers running around
on the bottom of the ocean and it's pissing me off.
They're going, "You'll never catch me,
"you'll never know I exist."
- Longer than a long girl's hair.
- There's some that are thinner than a needle.
- How scary was that animal at the bottom of the ocean?
- A hundred points of scary.
- How scary do you think that one is?
- Speaking of scary, here's my scary.
- Here's my scary one.
- That one big scary fish.
- Yeah.
- Well that's, I always, I think that there probably is--
- SpongeBob movie scary.
- There probably is a full on--
- Mate monster.
- Mate, don't even give me that.
- There's a full on kraken.
- I have to go to bed after this.
- Yeah, well that's the thing, dude,
they didn't even know, they thought the giant squid
was fake until like 2006 or something.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Yeah.
- That's for like--
- There's a full crack.
- For as long as humans went in the ocean,
they were like, "That's not real, whatever."
- What if there's like a humanoid type guy down there?
- There's copies of all of us down there.
Just like, just some guy.
- People are always like, "Parallel universes."
- It's the ocean.
- No, it's the ocean.
That's where the parallel is.
- The ocean is an actual parallel universe.
- That's where the parallel is.
Every choice you made, the ocean,
your ocean self made the opposite.
- That is honestly making me so actually scared.
- If you're a nerd, your ocean self is a jock.
If you are a goth, your ocean self is a prep.
If you are a boy, your ocean self is also a boy.
It doesn't go like that.
- It doesn't change gender.
- Here's my UFOs.
- Gender is just a concept.
- Here's my other movie, UFO Twist.
We've been seeing all these UFOs.
They're not from up there.
- Here's my movie, UFO Twist.
And it's mist twist, Sierra mist alien.
- What?
Sorry, I just had my life deflated.
- UFO Twist.
- I don't know what that means.
- Lemon lime alien, man.
- Why are you flopping in the middle of my conversation?
I'm trying to have a conversation about something cool
You're just flopping all over every word that I say.
- I'm making up a new alien.
- Just add that buttermilk to soda, fuck you.
- Soda alien.
You need to go be sent to a flopical island.
- You need to go, no.
- On a flopical vacation.
- You don't suck, you're one of my closest allies.
But you are flopping up and stinking up
like smelly shit right now.
- I'm not flopping.
- Talking about soda.
- Soda alien, mistwist the alien.
- This guy's soda, so damn floppy.
- I'm not floppy.
You're floppy.
That one?
Tell him I'm not floppy.
I don't think you've been flopping as hard as he thinks you've been flopping, but lemon,
lime, whatever.
Lemon, lime, alien.
Yeah, that's going to be a flop.
That was especially because me and him were talking about a cool, scientific.
We were going science.
We were going science and you were just interrupting with like a five year old.
This is science.
This is not science.
It's science because it's space.
Okay, you know what?
We'll pause our life changing conversation.
Go ahead and explain soda alien.
They just changed the name of Sierra Mist from Sierra,
it went Sierra Mist, Mist Twist, Mist Twist, Starry.
Starry, space, lemon lime alien, mascot.
We get into PepsiCo, we explain to them
that they need a lemon lime alien to promote Starry.
We make a million.
- And you were like, this is a home run.
a home run. This is a home run idea. This is probably one of the best ideas I've ever had.
Flop ball! You're out! Flop. That says flap. You flopped. Me and him were talking about
how cool it would be. You know what, I can admit my flops though. If you ever were presented
with a flop, I think you would go psychotic.
The thing about that, I'm flopped since birth.
Yeah? You only flop?
I'm in like, my whole life is a Rocky training montage of learning not to flop, but I haven't
finished it. It won't be done until I die. So it doesn't bother me if I flop.
It's in your genes.
I'm ready for it.
You're in the army, on your helmet, you're born to flop.
like someone I say yeah I flop and I like doesn't hurt much I flop before yeah you
know I'm kind of like grizzled death by a thousand flops yeah oh I wouldn't like to
die that way that's gonna how he's dying right now yeah anyway but I I worked I go
through all my flop I was born in the flop molded by yeah you merely adopted
the flop yeah that kind of type type deal flop Hardy yeah look in that picture the
Flop Night Rides Flops.
Flop Hardly.
The guy in the army thing, the army helmet, that photo from Vietnam.
He's got like "meet his murder" written on his helmet or whatever.
It says "Flop Eric".
Pretty good.
Photoshop challenge for the fans.
Photoshop battle.
We need to start doing Photoshop battles again.
Somebody Photoshop him to be just sideways falling into a pool on his stomach.
If you could just do that.
that. Please make it a gift. Yeah. And have it in rainbow letters. So I can just respond
to everything. Flopping into peanut butter? Is that what you just said? What? How did
I just hear that? Hearing flop. Hearing flop. I'm having a full on. What did I say? What
did I say? I thought you said that you want them to photoshop me flopping into a pool
of peanut butter. I said make it a... What did I even say? Make it a gift so we can upload
to Twitter. Oh my, the word in my head, I heard peanut butter. Peanut butter. I don't know.
Upload it to peanut butter. The thing is, I've gotten. You've got to get this gif onto peanut
butter.com. I've gotten a small enough amount of sleep this past week that I was trying
to, I feel like I genuinely could have messed up and said something that sounded like peanut
butter, but I was really trying to walk through it. Are all of us feeling, are you guys also
I'm feeling like you're kind of running on E today.
- I'm going through a shift.
- A flop mode.
- I'm gonna be real with you, Patrick.
I'm taking it out on you, but I'm feeling a bit floppy.
- Can I drive Patrick home?
- No, I'm not going home.
I have to go to the gym after this.
- I also have to go to the pet store.
I have to get more cat food.
- Which gym are you going to?
- The most expensive one in the entire city.
- Whoa, is it that one next to the mansion?
- No.
- Oh, the mansion.
- The mansion. - The mansion.
- Wow.
- But I do think that, by the end of my life,
I'm much more interested in if NASA came up to me
and then SESO came up to me.
- Yeah.
- And they were like, NASA says,
"We'll take you to space," and SESO says--
- Says, "We can air your flops."
- No, this is a different SESO.
SESO-- - What's SESO?
What do you mean?
- It's basically the C version of NASA.
- Why'd you say SESO?
- Because I just heard that in my head,
So is that a CISO?
CISO, like we got--
it would stand for something.
JASH.
No, not-- OK, not--
JASH and BUN.
Not that CISO.
A different one.
S-E-A-S-O.
Oh, Sea Org.
You're thinking of Sea Org.
Scientology Sea Org.
No, this is S-E-A-S-O. And they go down--
That's still a very powerful Navy.
They go down into--
They're one of the most powerful navies.
And they're the best.
They're probably the best Navy.
Sea Org only has two ships.
- They're the biggest ships in the world
and they're gonna take us to Xenu.
- See, so if NASA said--
- Xenu.
- If NASA, he's flopping all over what I'm trying to say.
Will you do something about this, Cameron?
- He's crying.
- If NASA said, "I wanna take you to space,"
and CESA said, "I wanna take you to the bottom of the ocean,"
I'm going to the bottom of the ocean.
It's way more interesting to me than space.
I don't care about space.
- No, I'll go to space.
- Yeah, I'd go to space.
- Sorry, did they ask you too?
- Yeah.
- No, I don't think they did.
- I don't think CESA--
- I think they did ask me.
- You did ask me. - It don't exist.
- You wish.
- CISO asked you which TV show from the 90s
should we put on our platform that we have the rights to,
and it was a choice between Joey and--
- Joey. - Friends,
and you chose Joey, and that's why the whole company flopped.
- I made the decision.
- You made the decision.
We met Caleb, 'cause he was a rep at CISO.
- Yeah, CISO wanted you to write and direct a show
called Funny Commercials.
(laughing)
- And you pick that up and go into space.
- I would do that, I'd make funny commercials.
- I would too, that's actually--
- That's easy, you sell a four minute commercial
for a fart, you sell a fart, easy.
- They used to at the end of every year on TBS,
it was hosted by Kevin Nealon,
and it was called the funniest commercials of the year.
- Really? - Yeah.
- That's so sick.
- And it was like the top 100 commercials,
and it's Kevin Nealon walking around Times Square just like,
and here's an ad from Japan that's gonna make you go,
cool, I like that show.
That's easier than America's Funniest Home Videos
'cause the commercials are already on TV.
Yeah. You don't have to take 'em
from the video and put 'em on the TV.
It's so crazy that like--
They still have that show.
Commercials suck now. It's called the Super Bowl.
Commercials suck now 'cause they've gone woke.
Which commercial went woke?
I thought-- Oreo.
How did Oreo go? Rainbow filling.
Really?
Oh, they got rid of the white part of the cookie
and they replaced it with a rainbow.
Like they're trying to do the entire world.
Oreos used to be about unity between black and white.
It used to be about the perfect ratio
of two black and one white.
That every single household should be.
Then they changed it to a rainbow filling in the middle
to represent two black guys who are gay.
Come on, man.
And that's wokeness gone amok.
Wokeness has gone a little amok in regards to Oreos.
Did you see Joe?
Two black guys and a green guy in the middle?
- What the hell's going on?
It used to be me between those two black guys.
- Hey!
- Now it's some green guy.
- I'm sticking with this little fucking green guy.
- Yeah, he's taking my spot.
- You see that Joe Rogan's opening up a new comedy club?
- Dude, Comedy Mothership.
- Is that what it's called?
- Yeah, we're gonna go do that.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, let's do it.
- Is it in Austin?
- Yeah.
- We should definitely go to a show at Comedy Mothership.
- We could do it.
- You think we could?
- Yeah, whatever.
- Dude, that'd be so amazing.
- Yeah.
- And we go up there and we are tearing the fuck out of--
- Should we just do our own version of Kill Tony
up here in New York City?
Where we just have people come up,
but we're just real nice to them.
- Yeah.
- Where they do their standup, we're like--
- Friendly way to save Tony.
- Yeah, we go--
- We do save Tony.
- Where's Tony?
And we go--
- Hi, Tony.
(laughing)
- Hi, Tony, with the bottom of those boys.
And people go up and they do standup, we go,
that was actually really nice.
- That was really funny.
- Yeah.
- You should take that on the road.
- Yeah, take that one minute on the road.
- That's what that whole show is.
- The show is that they get homeless guys to come up
and do one minute of comedy and go (mumbles)
and then they go--
- I've seen the only clips I've ever seen from that are like--
- Tony Hintzler goes, "You look seriously,
"I can't tell if you're fucking homeless or a hipster."
And they go, "Oh my God!"
And Dom Irera's there and he falls over
'cause he gets so high on the cigar.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- The only clips I've ever seen of Kill Tony,
and it really for a long time made me believe
that it was him letting disabled people
do standup for one minute.
- It was.
- Yeah, because every single clip I've seen
has been like disabled person crushes at Kill Tony.
(laughing)
- That's 'cause that's the only chance you have
if you, to do a one minute standup set and do well.
- Yeah.
- You need to have something that is,
well how do I say this?
- Yeah, where are you going?
- You need to have something that is immediately funny
when you go up.
- Yeah.
- So you need to have some,
- You need to have a tiny, you need to have one tiny arm,
or your head's too small,
or you have one leg shorter than the other.
- You go up there on Kill Tony,
you get caught weeks later when the clip is uploaded
'cause you've been faking a disability.
- Yeah, I would do that.
I'd fake a disability to be a Kill Tony superstar.
- I would love nothing more
than to be a Kill Tony superstar.
That's my dream. - You go up on a lawnmower.
You're like, "Yeah, I just can't afford a wheelchair."
(laughing)
- They're like, "Okay."
- Yeah, I'm disabled, I'm paralyzed from the waist down.
I couldn't afford a wheelchair.
The only thing that my family can afford is our John Deere.
- If I'm getting--
- You can't hear the set at all.
(imitates engine revving)
It's just (imitates engine revving)
just puttering.
- If I get-- - It's the worst engine
in the world.
If I get um...
(Inaudible)
(Laughter)
If I get paraplegiarized
and my legs go
they're unusable
First of all I will get the arm strength like daredevil
that will come instantly
Will you be one of these people who walks around on their hands?
Even better, what I'm gonna do is
I will tie my lower body to a pogo stick
(Laughter)
Only my giant buff arm instantly got strung by the daredevil effect. I'll walk or I'll jump around on that. Yeah
They'll call me they'll call me Cameron in the box. They won't know they have a
Common that it happens to me. They'll call me LD abloh
In Diablo Blanco, yeah, do you know they have extreme pogo?
No, they hit like like skateboarding and like BMX. Oh
That's such a big dudes jumping off of like buildings and then like doing like front flips with the handle
BMX is already bad. Oh, you really you can't stray any further and also the also they do it with unicycles
Yeah
But it's just too easy to honk and drive by extreme pogo and say extreme homo
It's too they shouldn't call it that well guess what what they also could they also have that
Homos they have extreme homos. It's already - it's extreme jumping. Yeah
What just extreme jumping? Yeah, that's fine. Yeah, just get rid of the pogo stick
They have extreme homo just jump around those contests are crazy. I don't think so
Roll the clip
Don't find it don't roll
Extreme homo.
Don't do it.
No, don't look at it.
I don't want to see that.
It's not our place to look that up.
Dubio just has that on his computer.
Extreme homo.
Roll it.
You've already got it.
You've got it queued up the whole time.
You've got it in OBS already to go.
Do you guys want to get into an extreme sport together?
You said that you wanted to learn how to ollie this year and you still have not hit it.
I'm going to try to get into an extreme sport together.
- There you go.
(laughing)
Do you guys wanna do, get into an extreme sport together?
- You said that you wanted to learn how to ollie this year
and you still have not hit me up.
- I don't even remember saying that.
- You said it on an episode.
- He got so excited when I said that,
that you put that so sweet, that you remembered that.
- Both of you, I think, 'cause I remember the conversation
was he's gonna learn it before you.
- Oh, there's no way.
- Don't remember that.
- I'm an expert at learning.
I'm a fast learner, fast learner.
I mean I have like four skateboards at home. We can just go try this. Yeah, I'm down
We could go film this right now cut the episode here. We film
15 minutes
Not to mention a pandemic yeah, yeah good point I was thinking earlier. I think that he's afraid I'm not afraid
I did why I did an Ollie one time in high school, but it wasn't not a good one, but I did one before
He's learning to drive so he's he's already in do oh yeah, cuz he's the extreme sport
He's about yeah, too is way crazier. This is my version of
Learning to drive is learning to skateboard. Yeah, because I think that I just have such a skateboarders brain
Mmm. I don't think you look at the world the way that escape does I do
Cuz I look around I say fuck that fuck that and fuck you to you old bitch
To grannies and grandpas. I'm going fuck you. I'm a skateboarder. That's right. I disrespect you
I'd be graffiti on me.
I'm gonna smash your front door in and come in your house and get you.
Yeah.
I'm gonna pin you down and feed you.
Food.
I'm installing a trough in your house.
I'm gonna find you, granny, and I'm gonna pin you down and feed you food.
This is me at the front wall of your house.
I'm like, "Bam! Bam! Bam!"
Until it splinters. I'm coming in through the drywall.
I'm knocking down your door with my--
And you might say--
I'm kicking the door down, and I got a bowl of oatmeal in my hand.
And I'm like grandma
Welcome to your fucking nightmare you think and when I say I'm smashing it through the drywall you might think oh like the kool-aid man
But no, I'm not doing it like the cool coming in bit by bit first
That's my hand then my foot. I was like a demon climbing out of the mirror world. Yeah, okay, and I'm not leaving gradually
I'm not leaving
I have my face painted like sting from the WWE mm-hmm, and I might but painted like Darth Maul
Yep, and by the way when I break through the door it's your butt. It's gonna be like Homer's makeup shotgun
(laughing)
- You're gonna have Darth Maul's face.
- Yeah, you're gonna have Darth Maul's paint on your face.
- And then, by the way, legally,
if you look like Darth Maul,
I can legally do whatever I want.
Because nobody's gonna, everybody's gonna be like--
- I'm a lightsaber.
- Oh thank God, Darth Maul.
Oh thank God he died.
Oh thank God somebody cut Darth Maul's head off.
- Darth Maul came to the real world
and someone chopped his fucking legs off.
Be careful.
Be careful, he's gonna get some spider legs.
- That's what I would do.
- Darth Maul came to the real world.
Someone chopped his fucking legs off.
If I saw somebody walking around in Darth Maul makeup, I would be like, "There's a 50/50
I chop his legs off and it's good."
You have to kill him.
Yeah, I have to try.
Because if you chop his legs off, chop his head off, right?
The investigator finds it, face down, right?
Picks it up.
"Ahh!
Oh my god, it's Darth Maul!"
Fuck you, bastard.
Kick his head into the Hudson River.
That's right, some hero just killed Darth Maul.
Get the fuck out of the real world, Darth Maul!
Go back to your imaginary world.
Go back to Tatooine!
If you don't go back to
You're in line for like the next Star Wars movie there's a guy dressed up like Darth Maul there do Darth Maul
I'm gonna slap the makeup off his face now fucking insensitive to be to dress up like Darth Maul
Yeah, I literally a movie whose main characters probably got into conflicts against Darth Maul
He's not even in the movies. He dies at the end of the Obi-Wan series or no. It's Star Wars rebels
He dies then there's a whole thing
There was a there is a guy when I saw I saw force awakens like the premiered night of got to the movie theater
Like two hours early. I don't know why the fuck I did that smoked a bunch of weed and then
Guy there dressed up like Darth Maul and I was so high and scared that I was just staring at him
And he asked me if I wanted to take a picture and I went
Yeah, don't ever ask me that again
He sat directly in front of me too
So I fell asleep in the theater woke up and looked if I saw you fell asleep opening night
I'm walking through the entire line for the Star Wars
Midnight showing I'm sorry
So we meet again Darth Maul
It appears for your legs to be shot again. You've decided to enter your wrong world
And I think by now this is the fourth time and you know that the punishment is your legs are will be gone
and I will be kicking your head into a
Radio show I walk around to third with the chopper, and I'm not talking a gun. Yeah, I will chop
I have a choppa.
I've got your blizzy.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Blade.
That's a blizzy blade.
Did you guys see that Disney made a real-life lightsaber?
Yeah.
I didn't watch the video, but it because I...
They need to back the fuck off because they're in too many markets.
They have a monopoly on theme parks, animated TV shows, live-action TV shows, live-action
movies, animated movies, hybrid live-action and animated...
4D animated ride.
CG effects, CG effects, 4D animated ride, animated movies that play during rides.
- Driving rides. - Band-Aids.
- And now they're trying to get into weapons.
- Cruise ships.
- Band-Aids, children's toys, snacks.
- Leave the lightsabers to Apple.
'Cause you know they're gonna make
the fire-ass lightsaber.
- Well you know they're all owned by one company, right?
- I don't want some busted fucking Dell lightsaber.
(laughing)
- We need Apple to come out with a white one.
- Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, I'm like, "Mom, don't buy me this fucking Dell."
- Yeah, this whack-ass lightsaber.
It's got stickers all over it and shit.
- Lenovo. - Man, fuck kids.
- Fuck you, Mom, I don't want this Alienware.
I want a MacBook.
- Nah!
This thing looks like shit.
- This actually-- - This gateway ass.
- Your mom buying you an elegant Alienware gaming PC.
Fuck you mom, I want a fucking MacBook.
- I wanna do graphic design, mom.
What the F is this thing?
- What the flip? - What the flip?
- What the flip, mom?
- You can't swear, mom.
- No, yo. - I was never allowed
to swear, mom. - You can't have 64 gigs
of RAM, no, mom. - No, I want 12.
- I want 12. - 512 megabytes.
- And wait, how much did you pay, 1,000 bucks?
- Double it, bitch. - I did a RAM upgrade
on my laptop and I don't see it. I guess I don't know what happened, but somehow now
my computer has an odd number of RAM. It has like 23 gigs of RAM.
Really? That's what it says?
Yeah.
So that makes no sense.
It literally makes, it's like 23.7 or something.
It's probably, were you trying to put 24 in?
No, I put in 16 maybe. I think, well I already had 8 and I think I put in, I don't remember,
I think I put in 16 more. And it says like 23.
Well, what's 8 plus 16? That's 24.
(laughter)
That was fire.
Yeah.
Yeah, maybe I even put in 30, no,
'cause it must be something different because some--
I think that you were creating a bomb accidentally.
I think, yeah, well, I'm just worried
that something's gonna happen down the line
that I'm not expecting. It's going to.
Yeah, you should not have that.
That's usually my worry about most things,
is that something's going to happen.
I think that I've only ever seen RAM be 8, 16, 32, 64, 128.
I've never heard of 23.7 gigs of RAM.
That's a good amount of RAM though.
That's why I was confused.
I mean, it's definitely a lot of RAM.
What the fuck is RAM?
Random access memory.
Okay, Daft Punk, motherfucker.
Yeah, that's why I wanted to say it.
Okay, you robotic dancer.
Like the Legend of the Phoenix.
Robot flop.
They are robots.
(laughing)
You guys, so on our next tour, we should hit Ibiza, I think.
Yeah, Ibiza.
Ibiza.
And get some kind of very long drink.
Oh.
And we should do like what Zach Bagans does and try to contact Avicii.
Like, oh my God.
That is a good idea.
I would love to try to contact, to trap him.
Oh my God.
I would put him into like a genie lamp.
Hologram Avicii and we can just have him like remix us every day.
the thing I'd put them into like I put them into that I do our zoom and I'd say
now pump out some I'd swallow them and I download stuff into it I'd be downloading
do a leap song yeah it's all him
yeah well I'd actually want the Skrillex remix well that's the thing is I would I
I would change up. He looks like white Drake now.
Really? What do you think? It looks like white Drake.
Looks like white.
For real? Can you show me Skrillex?
Skrillex now.
You just searched Skrillex.
Well, he does look like white Drake a little bit.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
See right there.
He looks like a chef.
He looks like a chef. I hate it.
Yeah. Isn't that sad?
Yeah. I mean, it makes sense.
And now he makes music with Blade and it doesn't go
instead anymore.
Yeah. He had to change his shit up.
But change his shit up entirely and completely.
I used to pretend to hate Skrillex, but that song "Bangarang"
He made some amazing music.
I think Skrillex was cool.
When I was younger, I was like, "Man, fuck this gay ass dubstep bullshit."
Now that I'm a grown man, I fully appreciate it.
Interesting.
Now that I'm a grown man, I have a taste for classical.
Really?
Dubstep.
So what have you been listening to recently?
Skrillex.
That's not classical. I mean classical.
He's listening to Venetian Snares.
named Avicii. You could convince me that that was an Italian composer, but it's out of a
German drug addict. Yeah. Germany is Swiss. Fuck him. He's dead. Switzerland. A German
drug addict is what a Swedish guy is. That's what most German, if you're like, in German,
if you say like American, it's like Americanish. I think that entire area... Germany? No, not
Germany, but like Sweden, Norway, all that kind of stuff.
The Scandinavians, wipe it off the map.
Then where would all of my amazing particle board furniture go?
Don't need any of those places. All of those places are terrible.
And the fact that they all have different languages just pisses me off.
If we're talking about different countries, can I close this out with a message?
Yeah.
An important message.
So I am headed, at the end of the month, I'm headed to Mexico for my American-ish friends.
He's going to find the chupacabra.
I'm not going to find the chupacabra, but I have an important message here that is actually really important.
This is a message to the cartel of Mexico.
Speak directly into the camera. GBO, maybe you could pass this along.
Yeah, that would be great if you could pass along.
To the cartel, I've seen what you guys have been doing,
I've seen what you're up to,
and this is a warning right now
to get your affairs in order, okay?
Because unless you shoot my plane out of the fucking sky,
you guys are done.
And I'll be dropping my flight number
on the morning of my flight, so check my Twitter page.
I dare you to fucking try.
Take me down.
It's not happening.
I'm coming there and I'm cleaning y'all up.
you're gonna be screaming for help.
What you did to those American tourists
and the industry you perpetuate with the drugs,
the sex trafficking, I don't know if you do sex trafficking,
maybe you do.
- Yeah.
- It ends on March 30th.
And that's a promise.
That's all I need to let them know.
- There will be a video that's like a slow fade
of just your head on a pipe.
(laughing)
- Your head is like, your head's a grill ornament
for like a GMC truck.
- You're gonna be one of the guys
that they don't even kill for money,
they just like practice on you.
- Yeah, you're somebody's like--
- I'd like to see them try.
- You're somebody's blood in, blood out thing.
- Exactly.
- Like you're like, yeah, you have to go,
if you wanna join, you have to shoot that guy.
- They will have decided to kill you
30 seconds before they saw you.
- No, no, no, no, it's not, Ninja Stars,
that's all I'm saying.
- We do have a Ninja Star you can bring.
- We do have a Ninja Star.
- All right, bye guys.
- Bye bye.
Shareholder meeting.
Shareholder meeting March 22nd.
And then Cameron's going to be in Mexico.
And then you're going to be in...
I'll be in Raleigh.
The 23rd through the 25th.
And then I'm going to be doing a
bunch of bar shows.
Awesome.
If you're in Brooklyn, look for me.
Oh!
(laughter)
Flump.
Did your tooth chip?