(upbeat music)
- Okay, the bass versus cringe.
- Let's go through what we went through this morning.
- So I texted Cameron this morning.
- Should we just--
- Let's just go, okay, so first things first.
- I wanna hear it beginning to end.
- Let's read each our sides of it.
- Okay, so I texted Cameron at 10.59 a.m.
I said, "Is SpongeBob based or SpongeBob cringe?"
- You didn't say, "Is SpongeBob based
"or SpongeBob cringe?"
That's gotta need to be turned up a little bit.
- Is SpongeBob based or SpongeBob cringe?
I just turned the headphones down on my fucking shit.
We need to buy new microphones.
- No.
- The fans don't pay us enough.
- No, we're gonna push through it.
- We need to buy a new Cameron.
It's Cameron's fault.
- No, hey.
- I'm sorry.
- He's mad because he didn't even want to like be in on the conversation at all.
- And his air fryer only goes up to 400.
- And he got a cold room in his house. - And I spilled my stuff and I picked the wrong shirt to wear.
- You look too strong. - I'm wearing a weird shirt.
- I didn't realize until the camera was on.
- I look so strong. - And look at that lighting.
- Look at the lighting on that camera. - I look way too strong in this.
- No, you have to look down there. - Oh, okay.
- That looks natural. - See, it's completely fine.
- Alright, let's get back to... - Let's make the lighting crazy today.
- Let's get back to base versus ground. - Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- So at 10.59, and he said exactly what he said.
You read it out perfectly, so no argument for that.
- Cameron responds with a perfect response.
- Let him say his own piece here, man.
- We're doing it like a script.
- I'm T-ing you up.
- Okay. - I like that.
- And then Cameron responds with a perfect response.
If you're a kid who likes SpongeBob, it's cringe.
But if you're a member of Black Twitter,
it's based to like SpongeBob.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah, now let's move on to the next topic.
- This is sort of a symposium on--
- These are basically, I'm getting, yeah,
base versus cringe, Cameron's perspective.
The next question I asked, are skinny jeans cringe?
- Simple answer for me, yes.
- Damn. - Facts.
- See, I didn't respond to that one.
- Don't have to say much.
- He didn't even respond, but he did respond
to the asking for a ride into the office.
- I mean, some of this stuff, the thing is,
it's easy to write a long-winded answer
where you're kind of thinking your own thoughts
out on the page, but to just get it down
to one single word-- - It's called brevity.
- Brevity, and it's the soul of--
- Wit.
- Which thing?
- Of wit. - Which it is.
- Wit is what it's the soul of.
- What?
- So, okay, so after that I asked Cameron,
another exercise in brevity from Cameron.
- Yet another exercise in brevity from Cameron.
- Is being a hipster, baster, cringe.
- This one-- - And I said,
this is a two message response from me,
so it's actually not brevity.
- Oh, okay.
- 'Cause I released a statement and then I--
- Legitimately had a follow up.
- I had an addendum.
- Okay, an addendum.
- Go ahead.
- Cringe, being a hipster, cringe, second message.
But shaking yo hips is based.
- Yep.
- Does a hipster shake their hips?
- No, I just thought that, it's just an addendum.
It's just like, oh, just so you know, also.
- Okay.
- But then I had a,
then it turned into full on just like a debate.
- Yeah, this one we kind of, a debate.
- I asked Cameron, not a debate, but more like--
- It was more of a discussion.
- We were philosophizing.
- And openly, yeah.
- Yeah, exactly.
- And I said, I noticed that Nu Metal
used to be something that chuds named Kyle listened to,
but now people think it's based.
- Oh.
- And what I said was, some of it still stayed cringe,
but according to my research, much of it is now based,
especially when done by artists like 100 Gecs.
- I said I saw that 100 Gecs is a boy and a girl.
'Cause I don't know too much about them.
- Yeah, yeah, I don't really have any interest
in that kind of tunes.
No, boys and girls shouldn't be making tunes together.
- I agree.
Captain Nintendillo what what the carpenters what about she and him she and
him come on that shit was um oh if it was based that shit was based I'll admit
it was some based trad bullshit I loved it cuz she dressed up in skirts and he
- If a boy and girl--
- Nowadays it'd be him and she.
- It'd be she/he.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
One person.
- Remember that one?
Remember that one?
- He/she?
- Like yeah, that thing when you're like a kid
and you go to the movie.
- That's why I shaved my head.
People call me he/she all the time.
- People will call you a he/she?
- Look at me.
- Yeah.
- Look at you.
- Look at my feminine figure that is so highlighted
by my extremely 40 times too small shirt.
- That's the funniest one 'cause like a grandpa
could say that with such like--
- Grandpas can say anything.
What world do you live in?
- A grandpa would say he/she and it would sound like--
- With his chest. - With his chest.
- Mm, true. - Such vitriol.
- Yeah.
- See I'm so, I'm pretty much on like a new wave
of consciousness now. - Raw meat.
- Yep.
- Cringer based. - Yeah.
- I'm gonna say I've completely flipped around on this.
I used to think raw meat based.
I'm starting to think that the only way
that anybody should ever eat any meat,
it doesn't matter, Wagyu A5, no.
Well done.
I want you to get a Wagyu.
- Lots of thinkers are jumping ship.
- Yeah, a lot of the people used to go,
it's cool to go to a store and order your steak
medium rare or even rare.
- This is coming from someone with an air fryer
that only goes to four.
- Well, but that's kind of where I learned
is that the best place to eat a steak,
you know what the best kind of steak you can have is?
You pop-- - You can't even reverse sear
in that air fryer.
- I can reverse sear in whatever I want.
Ass hat.
- What are you gonna do with that?
- You don't use an air fryer to reverse sear.
- You're gonna do that with your corn broom?
- You don't need a, you don't put the,
you think you put an air fryer on 400 degrees,
450 to reverse sear?
You have no idea what you're talking about.
You reverse sear at 250 degrees.
- I'm saying that I have the ability.
- Me too!
- I have the ability to--
- You don't have a single ability.
- Caleb takes a-- - I have toast.
I have bagel.
I have rehydrate, I have--
Do you think those are abilities?
These are abilities--
Those are modes!
These are abilities on my air fryer.
Those are modes on your utility.
And then it goes up, okay, okay, 400.
Mr. 400 himself.
When do I ever need to go past 450?
He said, the reason why we had this air fryer discussion
in the first place--
Corn broom owner says what?
The reason why we had this air fryer discussion
in the first place is because--
Corn broom owner says what?
What are you talking about?
Oh, oh God.
We had this discussion in the first place
because he ate, oh!
I ate fries for lunch.
Here's the thing, you want to talk about cringe verse based.
You want to talk about cringe verse based.
This guy ate french fries for lunch.
And you might be thinking, oh well he went to the store and he got some french fries.
He made french fries for himself.
Wait, okay.
Because I was experimenting with my air fryer that goes up to 450.
I was finding out, I said 450, too high, 400, too low, 425, just right.
I discovered it now, now I can make my girlfriend beautiful fries.
- Which is more based or more cringe,
fries for lunch, fries for dinner?
- I think if you eat fries for a meal, it's cringe.
- No, if they're loaded fries.
- What if it's out of necessity?
- Yeah, all I had was a potato in the kitchen.
- That's the same, you just did the hypothetical thing
where you say, but if you had to.
- Yeah.
- Well then it's fine.
- I'm not saying, can you do it?
I'm saying, is it based or cringe if you have to do it?
- No, none of--
- It's based if you have to,
because you're actually facing a hardship.
- It's cringe to do anything out of necessity.
Anything out of necessity is cringe.
If you are like drinking your own pee
on the side of the street, I will not help you.
- That's based urine therapy, urine therapy, look it up.
It can actually, because you're recycling.
- Yeah, urine therapy.
- I was and then I stopped going
'cause I didn't wanna pay for it.
And then I found urine therapy.
I started recycling my body's own,
I started the toxins co-out, I recycled the toxins,
I put the toxins back in.
Because you need to constantly need to be at battle
with yourself within, and that's not what they tell you
in therapy, they say you have to cure all that stuff
that's going wrong with you.
- Can I say something that might be a little controversial
right now, that's kind of on the cutting edge?
- But we're already way into controversy on this episode.
- This is gonna ruffle some feathers.
- What's his name right now?
- Urine therapy. - Steven Crowder.
- Steven Crowder versus Noam Chomsky.
- Urine therapy is cringe.
Urine therapy, thinking that urine therapy,
urine therapy is like when people discovered NoFap.
- Mate. - It's cringe.
you have lost a lot. NoFap works though. NoFap is based and urine therapy is based.
NoFap is based but posting screenshots of NoFap is cringe. I agree. And that's what I mean by
urine therapy is cringe. All men struggle with a NoFap journey, but the real samurais do it in
silence. I'm not coming on this. I don't want to talk to you guys about my urine therapy. If you
need help to not fap, you're cringe. I agree. If you need a support system that's like,
bro, it's okay if you relapse. You saw a picture for Flash Dancers, it was an ad for Flash
Dancers on a taxi, and you're like, I needed to go in the Starbucks on West 14th. I had
- I had to jack off, I had to log into Mr. Skin,
and I had to jack off in the Starbucks bathroom.
- HBO, HBO. - HBO, cringe or based?
- I'm gonna say again.
- No, I'm gonna say used to be based.
- Now is kind of moving towards cringe.
- Mate, I've noticed something I've noticed
in working on this philosophy is that it seems
that a lot of things that were once based become cringe.
- Sopranos is cringe now because of meme lords.
- It might have a chance to come back if the memes die out.
Or if...
Facts.
Yeah.
[Laughter]
That's a really good point.
Yeah, HBO I think is solidly in...
Succession is cringe.
But think about it though.
Succession became cringe.
Think about it though.
But it used to be based.
But it's on this Sunday if you guys want to come over.
It is on this Sunday?
I'm down.
Yeah, it is on...
Well, I'll be out of town.
We can all come to...
Oh, he'll be out of town.
You can come to my new place.
Or you can come to my new place.
You have an old place.
My place is brand new.
I don't know, we just switched it up.
But he has a better couch than you do.
You guys have a better couch.
- Okay, we bought the couch.
- Okay, we invite everyone over to our house,
whether you like it or not, there's nothing you can do.
- We bought the couch because it had a funny name.
- They bought a couch on Wayfair called the Dingler.
- And I went over.
- Oh, that's what it is.
You guys have been keeping it a secret.
- Noah looked at it and said, "The Dingler,"
and I said, "At that price, I will purchase it."
- How much was it?
- Like 300.
- That's not bad for a new couch.
- I think that you should, actually, that is good,
but it's my new theory that I've developed.
It's cringe to buy a couch without sitting on it first.
- Wow, that is definitely cringe.
If you buy a couch based on--
- And I can say that because it happened to me.
- Tell your story, tell your story right now.
- Bought a couch on some website, can't even remember.
It was a girlfriend's choice, and I said,
"Yeah, okay, we don't need to sit on it, that's fine."
And look, it folds out into a bed type thing,
So that's nice, that will be good, we'll buy it.
And it's not so expensive either.
Least comfortable couch ever has been sat on.
You guys remember that couch, it was Cringe.
- I remember how cringe that couch is.
- It was cringe, not comfortable to sit on,
not comfortable to sleep on.
- Speaking of cringe, somebody may have a little bit
too much headroom in their shot.
- That's important to talk about.
So, the way I became based is when it was time
to buy a new couch, we decided to sell the old one,
we go to a furniture showroom, okay?
And this, people take notes.
This is a base tactic.
You go to a furniture showroom, you walk around,
you sit on all the furnitures,
you go up to the lady who works there,
and she gives you her card 'cause she likes you.
And you say, "Which one is the best
"and also cheapest or most expensive?"
And you sit on all the couches, you find your favorite.
Then you go home, you Google the name of the couch,
you buy it used.
You have sat on the couch, but it is cheap.
- So this is what he should have done.
- I'm so glad that both of us put our mics down
so that we weren't even tempted to speak at all.
- But that is my personal journey from cringe to bass
when it comes to couch purchases.
- That is fucking phenomenal and I wish,
you know what?
- And do you know what I just remembered?
- If you had told me that before,
I would not have made the mistake of buying the Dingler
because it was online. - A lot of people
just don't know about this tactic.
- I bought my couch from a guy on Craigslist.
- Yep, and it's made out of corn
- No, it's an Ikea couch.
It's not very good, it's not all that good.
- Ikea's cringe.
- But the guy who sold it to me--
- Going to Ikea's based, but getting the stuff
from it is cringe.
- Well, that's why I got it used.
- His couch is made by the second little pig,
and his couch is made entirely out of sticks,
and the first pig came over too to help to stuff the pillows.
- Do you know that nobody who listens to the show
has ever been to my apartment?
- We've talked about it, though.
- That I live in a--
You live in like an--
- I live in a Colonial Williamsburg.
- You live in an apartment.
- One of the staged Colonial Williamsburg apartments
where I'm always in there and I'm spinning twine.
- Yep.
- You live next door, and I mean this like,
I actually met him.
You live next door to Rumpelstiltskin.
- No I don't.
Next door?
- You live next door to Rumpelstiltskin.
- Yeah, I remember the story.
I remember the story where he lives in an apartment
and not in a fucking field around--
Rumpelstiltskin knocks on your door.
Shut the fuck up.
He tries to trick you every week.
Rumpelstiltskin's cringe.
He is cringe.
I agree.
He lives next door to Caleb.
He knocks on the door and Caleb opens it.
He says, "Hey, how's it going?"
He says, "Hey, do you have a firstborn son I can borrow?"
Trying to trick him.
Meanwhile, he doesn't know Caleb is not sterile.
Not familiar.
Sterile.
I'm not sterile.
Or I'm clean, I guess.
- Yeah, you can put your hand in someone's body
and it's fine, they don't get sick.
- But I'm not, my cum is normal.
- Well you don't have a kid and Rumpelstiltskin's
just kinda camping out waiting.
- I am getting a little bit, I'm getting a little bit scared
that I might be sterile.
- Yeah?
- I might be infertile.
- I think we're all pretty sterile.
- I think we're getting to the, I'm getting to the point
where it's like, I've never had a scare.
- Me neither.
- And I'm like, wait.
- Well that's 'cause I don't nut.
- All the, yeah.
(laughing)
I can't nut.
- Nah, I fake it.
- I can't do it.
but yeah, show me how you fake it.
- Well I know I'm fine, 'cause I look down
and I see hundreds of Wigglers.
- You see the Wigglers?
- Yeah, I see them.
- Really?
- Swimming in clear jelly.
- Yeah.
- I pretty much--
- Vaseline with little frogs hopping around.
- Every single time I've nutted, it's been fake.
Sorry, I'm glad you don't have a subscription to Patreon,
my girlfriend, not gonna say your name
for personal privacy reasons.
- Derek.
- Nope.
- I'll say it.
- Jim.
- Not Jim or Derek.
- It's Derek and Jim.
- But pretty much what happens is every single time--
- Beckett dating a girl named Jim.
- This is Jim.
- You guys have to come up with a name, Jim.
- I wouldn't be that surprised.
You could have gone one of two ways.
You definitely went the other direction,
but you could have shown up with somebody
who was three feet tall named Jim,
and been like, "This is my girlfriend."
(laughing)
- Jim is so funny.
- Yeah, but so what I do,
like die hard I tape a little baggie of crema mushroom
to my back.
- Oh nice.
- Oh, but then it's got those little black specks in it
of the mushrooms.
- Yeah, well, I mean I just say I have a problem.
- It's not healthy to have something perfect
that has no impurities in it.
- And then I shoot a load of crema mushroom.
- Impurities so you know it's real.
- I wanna get a fake penis.
- Yeah.
- I wanna get one of those big rubber penises.
- Hollowed out penises.
- Yeah, and trick my own wife.
- Thinking you got a new penis.
- Whoa!
- Whoa, what happened?
Yeah, it's about like the size of your arm.
I walk in and I clearly have a giant...
It's the size of your arm but it can't get harder.
I'm wearing brand new grey sweatpants with the tag on and I clearly have a giant fake penis in my sweatpants.
I walk up to her and I'm like, "So what do you want to do tonight?"
And you're like, "Hmm, you got any plans?"
Well no, you wait to put it on and then you go, "Oh, I think I'm getting a boner. I have to go into the bathroom really quick and get my boner."
And you have it taped.
get my yeah, it's you have it's taped under the sink like a
shotgun. Yeah, but then you have to walk out. You have to walk
out and you have like one of those little wooden dowels taped
to it. Like it's like a plant that needs help growing.
You have it in a splint. Yeah, I really do love those old like
feel like those porn videos don't exist anymore. What cameras
are too good now. Oh, the OG Mud Bones. Yeah, the ones with the
fake dig. Yeah, because the guys always have like, like, it's
like, it's like you're pretending it's an elephant
and they have to pretend to nut so they go like, "Ahhhh!"
- Yeah, yeah.
But it's completely like, it's just mushy rubber.
So it just, and it's all one tone.
- When they were shooting everything on VX1000s.
- Yeah, exactly, they could get away with that.
These days, dude, no way.
- And iPhone.
- It's gotta be, well, it's CGI now.
- Yeah.
- I remember it could be CGI.
- Popcorn should be putting ping pong balls all over it.
- That's a great idea.
That's how you solve this whole STD crisis.
- Yeah, yeah.
people are getting STDs back and forth.
- CGI them.
- Yeah, you just CGI their penises.
If you wanna be a porn star so bad,
okay, we chop everything off of you
and we replace it with ping pong balls.
- Just like Gallador.
- Yeah, and then we just put you guys in a room
and you're this close to each other.
- We can place new limbs on you like Gallador.
- Yeah.
- So when I was in high school,
there was like a dodgeball tournament
that they would have every year.
Like you could just sign up you and your friends on a team.
And my buddies named their team OG Mudbone.
- Yeah.
- And somebody else--
- That's a funny show.
- Somebody else, pretty funny,
somebody else had to like,
somebody else's team name got changed
and then they threw them under the bus like,
"Oh, we can't have this, but like,
"they can have OG Mudbone."
And they were in the assistant principal's office
and the assistant principal was like,
"Well, I don't know what that means."
And they were like, "Look it up right now."
- Wow.
- And they made the assistant principal--
- That's fucked, that's fucked.
- They made the assistant principal look up OG Mudbone
and everyone got called to the office.
- That guy's a tattletale. - I saw.
- Yeah, that kid's a tattletale.
But imagine the assistant principal
having to look at that fucking.
- Yeah, just having it just hit a woman's vagina,
go completely L-shaped instantly.
'Cause that's all those videos were.
'Cause it wouldn't go,
you couldn't put that thing in a donkey,
like let alone a five foot woman.
So those videos, the penis goes towards the woman
and then it hits her mouth or her ass.
- And then it just--
(laughing)
- Just get a kink in it like a hose.
- Do you, have you, and all the jizz in those videos
looks exactly like that soap that,
you've been to my house, you know that soap in my bathroom?
- He loves soap.
- What do you mean?
- That soap, that soap in my bathroom that Alex bought.
Next time you're at my house,
squirt it into your hand and really look at it,
'cause it looks like fake cum.
- You want me to squirt it in my hand and go--
- We can go to my house right now
and we can all look at this soap.
It's lavender scented and it looks like jizz.
- I don't even know what soap I have at my house.
- I have a new soap.
- I don't even wanna say.
- He's gonna make fun of me.
- Say, say, it's a bar, isn't it?
- I have a tobacco scented soap.
- You have a bar with little leaves in it.
- Yes, I have a bar that has--
- You have a bar with mint leaves.
- I used to have one with leaves
and I complained because it didn't smell very good.
And so it got replaced with a bar,
with a yellow bar with little specks of orange in it.
So, is that the funniest thing you guys have ever heard?
And yeah, it's made out of some kind of fat animal fat.
- And that's, and you--
(laughing)
- Yeah, real quick.
- Yeah, I got it from Captain Ape Hab,
and you keep that next to your basin?
- No.
(laughing)
- To him, a bidet is just like a little clay cup
that he splashes up his butt.
- You know what, you're my bidet.
- There's a river that runs through his apartment.
- No, it's not, I don't have a room for it.
- He takes baths in and does his laundry.
(laughing)
- Do you know how hard it was this morning
for those little birds to get this shirt on my body?
- No, you're not a little bird.
- You don't have little birds.
- I go, don't try and get in on it.
(whistling)
- He's not, yeah.
- And the birds come in and they go,
Caleb, can we make you a soft scrambled egg?
- I hate going to his house
'cause I always sit on his fuckin' washboard.
- Yeah.
- He has a bunch of--
- I wish you'd sit on my washboard, you sticky bitch.
- He has a bunch of servants that work for him for no pay.
- Yeah.
but they are white.
- Irish.
- Yep.
- Yeah, they're Irish.
- Which that's up for debate, I guess.
- I think Irish people should still be slaves.
(imitates drumming)
- You wish you had your soundboard.
- I didn't know it was ironic leftoid Wednesday today.
- You left your soundboard in a wooden box at your house.
- I do have a little bit.
- That's a good one.
(laughing)
- They're getting worse and worse.
Every time.
- 'Cause I don't know too many, I know corn brew.
- You don't know that many old things.
- I was talking to somebody the other day
and they saw my apartment.
- By telegram.
- All right, that's okay.
My apartment does kinda look like a 60 year old lady
adopted like a 12 year old Korean boy who loves video games.
- Yeah.
- And just has like, 'cause I have one little section
of the house.
- You have that one big monitor that has that 3D background,
that it moves, it's like the anime woman.
- Oh yeah.
- You have your waifu background.
- Yeah, Noah got all mad 'cause he went to my house
and then he texted me, he went to go watch the dog,
and then texted me, "What the fuck is wrong with you?"
I was like, "What do you mean?"
- That was funny. - He sent me a picture.
It made me laugh, but he was acting like
I was being all crazy because I said that.
Well, because the background used to be a picture of Rex,
and then my wife complained.
(laughing)
So I changed it to being like a 3D hentai thing,
of like her pussy is like dripping nasty.
- Yeah, that was so gross.
- That was the grossest thing.
- The best thing is you can--
- It made me laugh so hard every time I saw it.
- If you move your cursor over to it,
you can like put your, it like moves her body.
- You got like a virus down like that.
- Yeah, it's gotta be.
No, I use wallpaper engine.
- Oh, okay.
- And I actually, for a while I had it changing.
Every single day would be a different--
- White goon?
- No, for a while it was just different,
like there's so much porn on there
that I found like 50 different ones of Mrs. Incredible
where she's like stretching her vagina.
(laughing)
like all this nasty shit.
And so every day when she would ask me to change it,
'cause she thought I would be like, "Oh yeah, no problem."
And then it would just be a different one
every single time.
It's pretty fun, but--
- Yeah, it's fun.
You gotta have little pranks like that for yourself.
- Yeah, and at some point I gotta upgrade my RAM
because I think it was really,
my computer started really chugging.
- Make sure you get the right one.
- You know what I did last night?
I was talking to 'em, like before I went to bed,
just for like a minute, had my girlfriend--
- Talking to the ceiling.
- Had my girlfriend convinced that
no one hears from Susan Boyle anymore
'cause she got me toot.
(laughing)
- A really brutal one too.
- I was like, yeah, no, she like, it was like bad.
- Yeah, like I don't even wanna say it.
- Yeah, no one talks about Susan Boyle anymore
'cause she straight up was like, it's like years.
- Yeah, it was like, she was attacking people.
(laughing)
- Jesus.
- Can you, I mean, honestly, like I would feel,
if I was on a train car, like late at night
and it was just me and then I looked over
and Susan Boyle was the only other person on the,
I'm switching cars.
- Yeah.
- That would be scary.
- I would not, I would start singing
so that we would do a beautiful duet.
- You wanna do La La Land with Susan Boyle?
- Wouldn't be La La Land, no, I'd be singing,
what's that song?
- La La Land.
- E-40 and--
- Let's Fuck.
- E-40 and Gangsta Boo.
- Yeah, me and Susan Boyle singing that on the train.
- Nice.
- Do people come on, she's like,
"You want that, I want that."
- Yeah, I want that.
- I was talking to--
- Yeah, I want that dick, yeah I want that dick.
- I was talking to Chad last night
about how when we were in middle school,
his mom was real strict about the music he would listen to,
the movies he would watch and stuff.
And me and him had a shared playlist
of just every song we liked on Spotify.
No sir.
And his mom came up and was like,
oh yeah, what kind of music do you listen to?
And put his headphones on and just clicked shuffle.
It's like a 5,000 song playlist.
and the one song that came up was "Let's Fuck"
before they made "Samoo."
(laughing)
It's pretty unlucky, man.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, who listens to that song?
- Who listens to that song? - Me!
- We listen to that song in the car
or boat or truck tour. - Yeah, but it's just funny--
- I liked it, I still like it.
I listen to that every once in a while.
- It's just funny to imagine someone just turning it on--
- It's like a twice a year song.
- Yeah.
- You either listen to it in the car
or it comes on in the club or something.
- That's what I'm saying, it's funny to imagine a guy
who's sitting down alone and he puts it on in his headphone.
- Or you put it on to eat pussy.
- Yeah.
- Like you're like, I need to use,
this is how I get in the zone.
- Put it on to amp yourself up.
- Yeah.
- You ever listen to like, you ever like have your--
- Or listen to it on the treadmill?
- Oh yeah.
- And you're doing the thing with your hands,
you're kind of doing the air drumming a little bit.
- I've seen something crazy since I moved to New York
and started going to the gyms here.
- Yeah.
- People go onto the treadmills and they--
- No.
- Buddy, it gets worse.
People go onto the treadmills and they dance.
- Yeah. - On long--
- People do some insane stuff on the treadmill.
I go, like, I feel like, not that I know that much
about exercising in general, but I see,
I feel like every time I go to the gym
and I see people on the treadmills,
there's always at least one person where I'm like,
that is not something that you are supposed to do.
- Well, you guys are going sideways and backwards
and lipping around and lifting their knees up to their chin
and stuff, like, what are you doing?
- Okay, go, Jim.
There's an amazing guy at the gym I used to go to
where he would get on the treadmill
and he'd crank the incline all the way up to the max
incline where he's like basically walking,
like facing the ceiling.
And he dresses exactly like Tobey Maguire's Spider-Man
when he's a wrestler,
like a full red and blue hoodie jumpsuit.
And he just walks just like this
and he holds onto the thing.
And this guy is sweating gallons of sweat
every single time.
It's the hardest workout I've ever seen.
- When I used to go to Planet Fitness,
there was a guy who sometimes would go,
he would run backwards at like,
like really fucking, like 10 speed,
and he was holding weights in his hands.
- I love that shit.
- It's so awesome.
- I wanna do that.
- You know what else I don't get?
People who go on the treadmill
and they just walk for 40 minutes
and they're not like watching the TV or anything,
they're just listening to music and walking for like--
- They need to let me bring my TV into the gym.
- They have plenty of TVs, and you do have a TV,
it's called a phone.
- I don't think so.
- Nowadays it's at your fingertips.
I am going to start bringing my iPad to the gym.
- No, I have a CRT TV.
- That's cool, I'm pretty excited to watch it.
- Speed drawing.
- I'm watching a million different kinds of pixel art videos,
like animated, like Neon Cat.
- You can do that on your phone.
- But it doesn't have the same glow as a CRT monitor, you fool.
- Get out, leave.
- He doesn't even get it.
Actually, he wouldn't get it.
His TV has a crank on it.
(laughing)
- A crank.
There's no TVs with cranks this doesn't exist
He's gonna say TVs wouldn't or something. Yeah, I said it had a crank I guess
Yeah, I guess I'm used
I do want to get a new TV
Like a 15 inch TV, well, I'm saying I want to get a TV on it
He is a zine it flopped it you're hitting your batting like good 400 crank was really good. It was good
Just leave it hit it again. You know you need to know when to go in to fold them a
TV with two cranks though
Damn, yo, so two people can watch it
Now I'm in this bad situation where I want to get a bigger TV, and she's saying no we have to get a projector
And I tell I literally I talked to like this
I was like if we're gonna get a projector. I would want to spend like six thousand dollars. Yeah
Yeah, are you ready to do this also? No live in a normal house?
There's no chance a projector will ever use it
They're all it like you have to have no windows in your house at all. Yeah, like a Alamo draft house, bitch
I want to watch fucking sports. I'm trying to get your Squidward. Yeah office though. I'm trying to see Squidward's own show
- Oh, there is a projector over there, I found one.
- What?
- There's a projector all the way over there.
- But it's one of these little like Pico ones.
- Yeah.
- I want like a, I would literally wanna get
- It only goes in 701D. - The same one they have
in a movie theater.
- Yeah, that's what you should,
if you're getting a projector - I don't have room in my house
- That's what you should be getting.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause there's no, yeah. - $45,000.
- I used to have like a - Yeah.
- Put IMAX reels into it.
- I used to have like a home theater projector
that had like a DVD player built into it.
- That's cool.
- At the time, it was one of those ones that in 2003
was like $5,000.
- Oh my God, how'd you afford that?
- It was my ex's dad's and he gave it to me.
- When you were 2003, you were six.
So that was my--
- You had a girlfriend, you had an ex-girlfriend at six?
- No.
- Oh.
- It was when, it was in 2018.
- Is in the future, okay, I get it.
- Then I lost the remote so I could not watch like a single,
like we would put something in,
and it's just like damn, I can't even.
- You know what I wanna see make a comeback?
Something I haven't seen in a while.
A universal remote control.
They're still around.
I have not seen one at somebody's house in a decade.
If you have the Roku app and someone has a Roku TV
and they're on the same Wi-Fi--
I'm not talking about your bullshit iPhone shit.
Oh my God.
I wanna see a giant--
Yeah, he doesn't wanna talk about iPhones.
I'm not gonna get into why, though.
Tell me why.
Go ahead, why.
'Cause I have a wood phone?
Shut the fuck up.
You ate fries for lunch.
He contacts everyone on the Pony Express.
- Rose and iPhone, like I, like Roman numeral,
like one, like the first phone, like one,
like from the Roman times, iPhone.
- And it's made out of a rock.
- That was almost good.
- It's made out of a rock, and it's made out of a rock,
and a pillar, 'cause it's Roman.
- That doesn't make any sense, man.
A pillar?
A pillar is giant, there's no such thing as a small pillar.
- Hey man, a pillar's what you sleep on.
- Okay guys.
- Okay guys, let's move on.
- Yeah. - Come on.
- Is there anything, what else about my ancient life?
- You have to mention something else.
- So I was, I had, I made coffee this morning.
How do you guys think I made coffee?
- You bought it from a native.
- You were on the frontier.
You were on the frontier and you made it over a campfire.
Okay, next.
- Yeah, okay, and I got into a war today.
I did a whole war with a different warring tribe.
And how did I do that?
What was my weapons, how did I do it?
- Yeah, and the tribe was made out of wood.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. (laughing)
- The whole war with the wooden tribe.
- Yeah, I was in my cave.
- And the war had a crank on it.
- Yeah, wood war three.
- I woke, wood war three, that's good.
I woke up in my cave today.
What's my cave made out of?
- Metal. - Metal.
- It's from the future.
That's called a subversion of expectations.
- You were expecting something,
we come in with something else.
- Yep, and you're a cyborg.
- And I went to church today.
What kind of church do I go to, guys?
- You sit in the pew and they say P-U
when you get in there, 'cause you fucking stink like shit
with your little soap bar.
- I've heard you do that before.
- I've heard you say that one before.
- A little stinky little soap bar.
- You didn't say, you weren't gonna go like,
oh, you're-- - You are--
- It's Apollo, maybe. - You literally,
you bathe in Jess Pachuli, and you have one big dreadlock.
And I'm looking at you right now.
- I don't, I don't, you're--
- And you have one big dreadlock.
- Why do you have to specify you're looking at me?
I don't have any luck.
- I'm looking past you, and all I can see is a fly--
- I don't have any dreadlocks. - Who is high as hell,
and he lives in your dreadlock.
- A high fly? - And you have a,
- You have a white dreadlock, like the Matrix twin.
One though, one big one, and it stands straight up
and it looks like, honestly, I don't wanna be offensive
right now, but it looks like a white Cheeto.
- And I don't think I have that.
I don't think I've ever had that.
- You have one big white Cheeto dreadlock.
- Yeah, and it's got a crank on it.
Yeah, it's made of wood.
You realize how much of an asshole--
- Your shirt is made of wood.
- Can we not bring up the shirt?
I'm already feeling so bad about my shirt.
My shirt choice.
- Wait, your shirt looks good.
- Yeah, this is--
- Makes you look strong and cartoony.
- This is not--
(laughing)
This is not the kind of--
- This is from Montgomery Ward.
This is like a, this shirt from like 1960 something.
- This shirt from 1960 something.
Why are you talking like that?
- I turned urban.
- Of when you saw that I had an old shirt on?
No, I don't know--
- This, honestly, because this is like a Montgomery Ward
and it's fitting you like this,
this is actually a child's shirt.
- This is not a child, bro, you think any,
what kind of strong-ass, buff-ass child
are you hanging out with?
- This is supposed to be for a little fat kid.
- Rose, an expert on children's clothing.
- Okay, wait, you know what, wait, wait,
hold on, I would like you to get up
and untuck your shirt and pull it down.
- You are not making me do that.
- No, no, no, if we're gonna talk goofy shirts,
get up, get the fuck up.
Right now, show these people what happened.
I'm only showing it because it's actually a new kind of style that okay. Yeah. Yeah. No no go ahead and show people
Okay, so this is a shirt right now pull that thing all the way down low and it's not being stretched
And that is not true
Yeah, I bought a pack of t-shirts. Yeah, and I did it
Yeah, let them know
So yeah, so yeah, I bought a bag of t-shirts I bought them from
From the store and it turns out
And it turns out that yes, they were tall
I'd accidentally bought tall tees
You look so crazy when you can't see your leg
Me my doll has no reason why I'm not gonna sit down for the rest of the episode cuz I look tall as fuck
Oh my god, it's hugging my get my fucking beer gut
No you look thin
Yeah, it makes you look it makes you look really like if you were this was the beginning of your waist
Or the beginning of your legs you would be tall and you would be like way too side
Yeah, I'm not that bad you look handsome and thin it looks like wearing a onesie. Yeah
It's actually not that bad anymore
Well you have to do is you have to draw a logo onto it and put it right here
Material it's made it's like yeah mesh. It's like cotton sheets
For old people to pee on their bed. It's the pad in a band-aid. Yeah a hundred percent. It's perforated. Yeah Wow
So those are our funny
Cameron do you have well he's got a he's good talk about funny different kind of funny sure about funny
Oh she cast a fan of the funny. Oh somebody would die funny when we got that call
I met the dude who placed the call Noah in Boston, and he gave me the thumb drive of his side of the call
So I have that if you guys want to listen to that later
Whatever happened to bringing over people to your house and putting on music and just sitting there and listening
You've been to my place. I got that new record player stand
So we got it by voices do I get there which one for me?
It's a red vinyl. It's the one with which album. I forget the name of it which one the one with my valuable hunting knife
Oh, yeah, that's um fucking alien lanes alien lanes. I did get alien lanes the fucking best one
Great you got the fucking best one and it's on red vinyl. Do you got it from Looney Tunes and all you guys know?
In Boston I miss it there so much. Oh my god
Ralph big shout out to Ralph love her. She let me stay with her. You're doing a vacation vlog. Yeah
I slept on Ralph's couch people
Nor to be so you're gonna sleep on a needle tonight. Yeah, well I did see a celebrity in Boston who?
James Adams
- So a statue.
- Oh.
That's not a celebrity sighting.
- I'm sorry, wait, James Madison.
- Yeah, James Adams.
- And George Washington.
- I just believe, I was like, oh yeah,
that's probably a president, I don't know.
- And I saw a lot of statues.
- You didn't see George Washington.
- I saw a George Washington statue in Faneuil Hall.
- Okay.
- Is that, no, that's not who that is.
- No, I saw all sorts of people.
- Nathaniel Hall.
- I saw all sorts of people, all types.
They're everywhere all the time.
I think in this big ass melting pot of a side. I saw adults. I saw teenagers. I saw fathers
and sons. I saw mothers and daughters. Damn. Well, they get professors. I saw students.
I saw did not see any scientists. Damn. Was they getting it on though? I was out. I was
out hunting for for the police officers who are going to do that thing to Trump. Mom and
daughter. Mom and daughter porn is really, really hot until you start thinking about
the situation.
And you go, yeah, the fact that after
the aftermath would be bad, the
aftermath. You can think all day
about, oh, it'd be so hot to fuck a
mom and a daughter.
That's a life ruined.
But two lives.
You should think about that before
you like all of that
stuff is disgusting.
Incest.
Patrick's on the anti it's
way incest based or cringe.
Just simple.
There's a lot of different types.
Yeah. Any two boys cringe.
Any two girls.
- What about boy girl?
- Boy girl, if I'm one of the boys, it's based.
- I guess it's basically legal.
- That's wincest, my friend.
Pound that out.
You guys remember that?
Yes sir.
- I won't be pounding it out 'cause I remember it.
- Yeah.
- That's gross though.
- You wish, you wish it was gross.
- So pornography.
- Pornography is cringe.
- Actually, now that people have started hating it,
- It's based again.
- Okay, so what about--
- Contrarianism is a yes.
- Well, it's cringe if you say it, but we just do it.
- Which is more based versus cringe, okay?
- Japanese style things?
- Porn is cringe or maybe based, that's not what I have--
- Japanese stuff is based again.
- It's based, it was cringe for a while,
but it's coming back to base.
Pornographical videos or not safe for work porn gifs.
- If you are a guy who only jacks off to pictures still,
that is the most based shit I've ever seen.
solo pictures of naked women,
I could see the most beautiful woman in the world
completely naked and I literally,
like it won't do anything for me.
It's like looking at a fucking crossword.
But if I, like it's that level of arousal.
But if people still like that, that's based.
GIFs?
- Animated GIFs.
- Animated GIFs?
- GIF of a train coming to the station.
- If you can jack off to that,
then you are a train.
- Okay, you might be a train.
(laughing)
If you see a train enter the station,
- And that gets you hard!
- Which is more-- - You might be a train.
- Which is more based or cringe, apples or oranges?
- Which is more based or cringe?
(laughing)
- I guess oranges are more for,
coming from a personal standpoint, for me.
- Yeah. - Not for most people.
- That's not how based and cringe works, though.
- Apples, unless they're cooked, are cringe.
- That's crazy.
- Yeah. - And oranges are based.
- What you just said is cringe, Mike.
- You have a dessert birthday party brain.
- Oral allergy syndrome is actually fucking cringe.
And it's actually-- - I agree.
- It affects some people. - I agree, it's really,
really crazy.
- You have the kind of allergy where if you ate
just a certain diet for two weeks, it'd be gone forever.
- Maybe.
- You have that kind of level of allergy.
- Well no, 'cause it's like--
- You have an autoimmune disorder.
- Let's test my allergies on the podcast.
- I'm down.
- We'll get a bunch of fruit--
- 'Cause you don't have any--
- A bunch of burst of collagen.
- That's if you're, it'll kill you.
- Yeah, you never-- - It won't kill me.
- Your throat never closed up, right?
Then you're fine.
- Well, I mean, if we have Zyrtec on hand,
- We'll get an EpiPen and some Zyrtec.
- So it's not a real allergy.
- Yeah, and if you just, if you--
- I'll eat a cherry, and then you'll see how bad it gets.
- It's not that bad.
- No, dude, there's like an old photo of me
where my front lip is just like this,
and I talked like that, and my eye was all red
from itching it.
- Your eye turned red from itching?
- Yeah.
I ate a bunch of cherries from my friend's farm.
- No.
Maybe you're just allergic to stuff from your friends.
- Friends' cherries.
- Maybe they were dosing me.
- Maybe they were dosing me with allergens.
- No, no, no, no, no, I mean like maybe your friend,
like if you get a gift from a friend, that makes sense.
You would maybe have an allergic reaction
that could leave a cold mark.
- So, cherries.
So say whether you're allergic or not allergic.
Okay, I'm gonna say some things here.
- I love 'em when they're, I can eat it all.
- I know, it's a one word.
This is one word. - So you have to say raw.
You have to say raw before it all.
- Raw cherries.
- Cringe.
- No, say you're allergic or not allergic.
- Allergic. - I wanna show something here.
- Allergic.
- Raw carrots.
- Chocolate cake.
- Not allergic.
- Okay, that's all I needed to--
- Well, chocolate cake with cooked cherries on top,
like a Schwarzwald-Kirschdorfer.
- You said cooked is fine.
- Black Forest.
- So, okay, see-- - So, still not allergic.
- See, that's not-- - Schwarzwald-Kirschdorfer.
- That is how you know it's a fake allergy,
because God didn't design anybody to eat chocolate cake.
- Yeah, he did. - No, he didn't.
- Bruce Bogtrotter, or whatever--
- Yeah, milkshakes.
- Yeah, are you allergic to milkshakes?
- Can you drink a milkshake?
- Sometimes.
I mean, in my old age now, I can't.
All the sugar puts me to sleep.
- But the milk is okay?
- Milk is the best.
- Milk, that must, yeah.
- Yeah, you have a thing.
If you are more allergic to raw carrots
than you are to milk-- - Well, it's hazelnuts.
I'm allergic to certain nuts, too.
It all falls under the birch pollen thing.
So I'm allergic to a pollen.
We've talked about this ad nauseum.
- I'm gonna paw you into the bathroom.
Lock the door.
You're not gonna Paul me in the...
Watch you poop.
You're gonna George Michael me in the bathroom.
I don't know what that is.
Pop that raw cherry.
Yeah, that's one raw cherry I'm not allergic to.
This is the one that's in your butt.
I'm gonna cook it.
I'm gonna make a prolapse.
Do you guys have butt cherries?
Can you pop it off? It doesn't bleed?
That's what...
Somebody explained that to me.
That kid that showed me Three Guys One Hammer
when I was a kid. He explained to me that that's
what a cherry pop is.
It's like, oh, you have sex with a virgin
and then she bleeds everywhere.
And I was like, sex is gross.
Sex is gross and disgusting.
- It is, the first time.
- And then he showed me Two Girls, One Cup
and I was like, sex is really gross.
- So this is these girls' cherries
that falls into the cup?
- Ew!
- They got their cherries popped?
- That's the cherry pop from the butt?
- Oh.
- That's not right.
- Ew.
Weird sauce.
- I'll soda pop the cherry.
- I looked at that list, that lolshock.com list,
every single video I clicked on,
and then I said weird sauce, and it became normal.
- It's normal.
- When you say weird sauce, it turns something normal.
- I do wish that I had, I do a little bit wish
that I had a hymen, because there's no proof
that I've never had anything in there.
- Never, oh, your butt.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- There's no, like, if there was a butt gynecologist--
- I bet they could figure it out, though.
- Well, but maybe not for me.
- Yeah, there is a butt gynecologist.
It's Cameron you're saying?
That's kind of good actually.
Yeah, he's got some kind of butt gynecology.
Can we just get like a lower third?
(laughing)
Cameron Fetter, butt gynecology.
- Put your feet in the stirrups.
No, not that way, lay on your stomach.
(laughing)
- You gotta flip over.
- Flip over, turn over.
(laughing)
I'm trying to look at it from the back.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause I'm your doctor.
- I'm your doctor.
- I'm your butt gynecologist.
- I need to look at it.
- You guys are laughing,
that would actually be a really unprofessional way
to go about it.
- Not if you're a butt gynecologist.
- No rules.
- Butt gynecologist, the first,
you take the doctor's oath
and then you take the butt gynecologist oath
and it's just have some fun.
- And you listen to Down 1.50, Jeremiah.
- I vow to have some fun.
- Yeah.
- And you put your hand on 101 Silly Billy Jokes.
- And you swear to George Carlin.
- And the waiting room music, I play--
- You put your hand on the stinky cheese man.
- I play a bunch of music that has a bunch of like
slide whistles and stuff.
They go like, whoop whoop whoop!
Let's get it started, circus remix.
You're playing Afro Circus from Madagascar.
Let's get it started, Circa 2001 remix.
Different lyric.
If you guys were becoming the president,
what are you swearing in on?
Because I think I've spot one, two, three
hardline atheists in this room.
Yep.
Oh, okay, wait.
I'd be swearing in on Dianetics.
I have an answer as an America hater.
What?
I will be swearing in on a landmine.
- Damn. - Put my hand down on it,
take 'em all out.
- Damn. - Boom, boom, boom.
- I'd swear in on Dianetics to become
the official religion of the United States,
and then I'd say, checkmate, atheist.
- I would make the lady hold a piece of poop
that I could swear on,
'cause you know they have somebody hold the thing?
So I'd walk up and I'd just squish the poo
into her hand. - And you'd be wearing a glove.
- Yeah, and I'd be like, ew!
- I think it was like a plastic cup of diarrhea.
- Then I just-- - And you crushed the cup.
- That was pouring out. - Like a Danimal.
Remember the Danimal drinker cups?
- You crushed those?
- Zach and Cody were in the commercial,
and then you like, they were like,
"There's a sweet steak, so you can go on a cruise with us."
- I remember Zach and Cody having a sweet steak.
- So I learned that it's not a sweet steak.
- You literally ate a glue stick as a kid or something.
- No, no, I used to huff it.
- I was a huffer.
I was a huffer in art class and I used to huff.
- I tried to huff paint thinner.
- You were a chewer?
- I tried to huff paint thinner
'cause I learned about it through this song,
Lacquerhead by Primus.
- Yeah.
(scatting)
- No, we're not doing Primus songs again.
- But they're fun.
- Every song is fun.
If you guys get to do Primus,
then I get to do Miley Cyrus.
- Miley Primus?
- Sometimes I'm hot and sometimes I'm not.
- Miley, do Miley Primus.
♪ This world turns slowly ♪
♪ It cuts you deep and it leaves a scar ♪
- You heard that song?
- I'm gonna fucking cry, bro.
- Yeah. - What song is it?
- Nothing Breaks Like a Heart.
With her and the guy who made
Don't Believe Me Just Watch, that song.
- Bruno Mars or Bart Bronson?
- Bart Bronson. - Or Action Bronson.
- Did you know that Bruno Mars gave Trinidad James--
- I'm the one who told you that story!
- You did tell me that and you told me on the podcast.
- Yeah, and you're telling it back to me.
- Okay, I have another fun fact about Bruno Mars.
- You have a wooden brain!
- Do you know that Bruno Mars is actually Filipino?
- Your brain and body needs a cram.
- I have a Bruno Mars fact.
He has millions of fans worldwide.
Even to this day.
- Wow, yeah.
That's a good, I didn't know that.
I really didn't know that.
- You'd think he'd fell off,
or lots of people would think he's mad now.
- I heard that his album 24 Karat Gold Magic is really good.
Can you attest to this?
Are you one of his fans?
- I don't know, I've never listened
to one of his song music.
- He made some kind of duo album
with Anderson .Paak called Starsky and Hutch or some shit.
- He performed one time at Sports Bowl,
which I don't watch, so I've never seen that performance.
- Yeah, that's a no for me.
- What is that?
- That's a no from me, I don't wanna see all that bullshit.
- I thought it was supposed to be a ball.
It looks more like an egg.
- They literally--
- And that's also, that's a song.
- It looks more like an almond to me.
(laughing)
- At the Sports Bowl Olympics.
- So where's the ball?
- We're tossing around an oversized almond.
- I'm just seeing a bunch of morons throwing a nut.
What the hell?
- When they--
- Oh, interesting, a bunch of morons in tights
trying to get their nut.
- They have literally--
- Looks a little hobo-erotic.
- Like all these mainstream artists at the Super Bowl
and it pisses me off because--
- That's the--
- Sorry.
- It's fucking mainstream, they have mainstream-ass
bubblegum shit like Bruno Mars, Justin Bieber.
- I don't want bubblegum shit, I want bubble guts shit.
I want beer songs with Toby Keene.
- Yep, beer.
♪ Riding through the night ♪
- That is such an awesome--
- ♪ And the evil force is saying ♪
- The old crappy standup bit is about how football
is actually gay because you stand on your hand
and a guy's ass. - Here's the sports ball guy,
okay, he goes to the game and he's like,
oh, a bunch of grown buff men
wrestling each other in tights, seems pretty gay.
Yeah, I'd rather have the cheerleaders dancing up on me
and rubbing their butts on my penis.
- Yes. - And he's sitting
in the stands saying, where are the cheerleaders at?
- But football is gay because they wear purple.
- It's gay 'cause they have team names.
- Yeah. - And the guys
should not be wearing purple.
- Oh, what, you wanna be a Bronco?
(laughing)
- Oh yeah, you wanna be a bronco?
- Oh, you're a buccaneer?
- Yeah, oh, you can play dress up.
You got a friend who dresses up?
You're gay, man.
- It's like someone who names their apartment.
- But they actually do a lot for,
they actually do a lot for the armed forces.
- Yeah, this place is actually called the mothership.
- Yeah, that's what the apartment is.
- That's what it means on a football team.
- Pretty much.
- Me and my friends need a name and a logo.
- Or you go to somebody's house and they name a room.
- Yeah.
- They're like, yeah, this is called the command center.
- Yeah, this is a living room.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- You know it ain't like that.
You know it ain't like that.
- Got it.
- It ain't, it ain't.
- No, that's a designation, that's not a name.
- You have--
- That's a legal designation.
- You have the loom room in your house,
and you spin straw.
- You're the fruit of the loom room,
where you eat underwear.
- Yeah, I do.
- Fuck you.
- Women's underwear.
- Gay.
- How's that gay?
- 'Cause you're eating it to absorb its powers.
(laughing)
- Yep, gay.
- Yeah, you weren't gay before you ate it,
but you became gay after.
- I became gay after eating pink underwear.
- Yeah, because you were eating it
trying to get a lace power.
- Here's a stand up, yeah,
I'd love to know Victoria's secret.
- Yeah.
As long as it's the size and depth of her vagina
and the length of her nipples when they're hard.
- And rap lyrics have gotten weird.
- Go ahead.
- Have you noticed that maybe
Stacey's mom is Jessie's girl?
- Hey guys, I'd love to do a little bit of a joke here
about rap lyrics and how strange their slang is,
but unfortunately I can't understand the damn things.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I tried to--
- So here, I wrote down a lyric for me to kind of
dissect and analyze for you guys.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
rap, rap, rap, blah, blah.
- It's crap.
(laughing)
- Folks, it's crap.
- Folks, this is crap.
- And football is played with an almond.
- And football is kind of for gay guys.
(laughing)
- And rap is crap and football is for gays
- And blues music and wearing raw denim
is for real straight guys.
- Let's analyze the lyrics of opera.
- Yeah, there's nothing straighter than raw denim.
There's nothing straighter than raw denim.
You pay $500 for a pair of pants
and you have to sit in a bathtub with them.
- You have to sit in a bathtub with them on.
- And they, if you sit on your friend's white couch
in a pair of raw denim.
- Yeah.
- Fucking cone denim shit.
You sit on your friend's couch,
you leave a big indigo stain.
- Clothes shouldn't be raw.
- You still have a big indigo stain
on your friend's white couch
because you are sweating bullets
because the Cards Against Humanity game is getting heated.
- It's getting a little too edgy for me.
- It's getting too edgy.
- Let's analyze some Cards Against Humanity cards, shall we?
- You're like, I'm sitting here,
I'm sweating fucking bullet sweat through my pants,
and you are like, I'm gonna have to speak up soon
because somebody just played Unborn Fetus,
and I'm like, can we play another fucking game
like Chutes and Ladders, 'cause this shit offends me.
- Yeah, 'cause actually my aunt had a miscarriage,
so can we maybe throw that in the trash?
- And turn off this little Uzi vert.
- He is actually a fucking predator, or something.
I don't remember.
- Or a satanist. - It's one of those two.
- What did he do?
- Satanical.
- He threw a pregnant lady off a building?
- Who cares?
- I guess I kinda said that before I really realized
what you said.
I guess throwing a pregnant lady off a building,
if he did that, I guess I care.
- I'm not so sure he did that though.
- I might have made that up,
but someone was complaining about him.
- It's okay to make up something
about a guy who's satanic like that, though.
- I think the more, he probably wants to do that.
I think kind of the more evil and terrible a person is,
the better their music is.
Like that kind of holds pretty true.
- Yeah. - The Beatles.
- The Beatles.
- John Ringo, George and Paul.
- John Legend, The Devil.
- The Devil on Spotify?
- Yeah, see The Devil's on Spotify.
I mean, I wouldn't say that this,
he's done all that much bad stuff.
He's more-- - He punishes the bad guys,
so it's almost like he's good.
- Whoa, Illuminati by The Devil?
Who are these 257 monthly listeners?
What is wrong with you?
Do you realize who you're supporting?
The Illuminati?
Oh man.
You're the devil.
He's literally not even hiding it anymore.
You have to imagine that this band, The Devil, or this guy, The Devil, has to be one guy
who lives in the Midwest and is like, "I'm going to make black metal and my name, yeah,
I'm going to be The Devil."
Yeah.
Or it's like-
I can't think of a name like Endless Winter or something like that.
Yeah, I'm just going to go with The Devil.
Straight to the point.
- I'm a Mayan teenager who is like,
this is the darkest fucking shit
I've ever made in my fucking life.
- It's just so funny to me, like,
there's been so much, they've been trying
to make evil names for so long now.
- Yeah, yeah.
- It's been-- - Now you're gonna
beat the devil up.
- Yeah, the devil, you just gotta go for it.
- Yeah, the devil-- - The devil.
- The devil. - The devil.
(laughing)
- That sucks 'cause then like,
somebody takes the devil, right?
Then you have to like throw numbers or something in there.
- They don't care, there's probably a hundred guys
Devilish than copying I bet there's a hundred guys who all made exactly the same another true bomb from Caleb another truth bomb. Yeah
Truth bomb activated truth bombs over Brooklyn
Holy shit, that's it falling Wow
And that's it's blowing up and that's it's blowing up
Yeah, and that's it's a blowing up. Are you guys getting increasingly a little bit scared of a nuclear detonation?
No, if that shit happens, I literally I'm gonna just put my sunglasses on and watch the blast
Do you ever I always think about like how horrible is that if like you if you when you imagine dying in the apocalypse
It's always like you and you're the people closest to you and like you look at each other with one kind of I always think
I'm gonna be at the grocery. Yeah, yeah
And you just like look at some like like what if you look over the only person near you is like like a kid picking
His nose. Yeah, it's like old me man
I have to be like have my last moment of humanity making eye contact with a guy bagging groceries
- I'm a smacker in the face.
- That's the thing, you just go,
"I always wanted to do this."
(laughing)
Just hit a lady in the face.
- That's not what I always wanted.
- And then the nuke doesn't drop.
- One old lady flip off.
- Movie idea.
- I would hate to see him, last moment,
stuck in a grocery store speaking of a kid
with a pick in his booger nose, right?
And he's like, "I've always wanted to do this."
And then maybe you start, you go in for a kiss.
- No.
- Yeah, you would.
- If I was in the grocery store--
- You'd try to eat the booger off his face.
- If I was in the grocery store,
I've always wanted to try another person's booger.
this
I've always wanted to taste it.
Another person's booger.
If I was in the grocery store when the nuke is going off, and I'm about to be in the blast
radius, I'm literally pulling out a liver from the thing.
I'm eating raw liver one time.
I'm finally going to try, what I'm going to do, I'm going to try a flat ground backflip
right then and there.
Yeah.
That's a good one.
Because even if I break my neck, it's like fucking...
Are you going to wait until like, you know, there's like eight minutes before you die,
right?
For your flat ground backflip, are you doing it right when you find out, or are you waiting
for maybe like 7.55 and you have five seconds before you're like, "Oh, I'm going to die."
you're gonna die. - I don't know.
- 'Cause then also if you don't land it,
'cause if you try it right away and you don't land it,
you maybe hurt yourself.
- You're looking, everyone's looking at you just like,
what the heck? - Not that it matters,
I guess, but it would be pretty cool to time it
with the flash of white light that kills everybody.
- So it looks like you are like--
- Yeah, you're silhouetted on the wall.
- That's actually a great idea,
'cause what if I end up doing the last backflip
that anyone ever does?
'Cause the world is gone.
So what if that's like, I time it,
so I'm like, well, at least I got to do my first backflip,
and it was the last backflip anyone ever did in history.
- And if you don't land it, nobody will be able to tell.
- Yeah, or at least the last backflip for a little bit.
Because even if, you know, 15 back--
- Somebody's gonna--
- But if they're all in underground bunkers,
nobody's gonna be like, day two,
like, oh, time to do a backflip.
Like, there's no, it's gonna be a while
until somebody backflips again.
- Yeah. - You know, so at least have--
- But I will say, it will be--
- There's gonna be someone.
- If nuclear energy irradiates corpses
and creates a zombie apocalypse,
I think a lot of people will be doing backflips
shooting crossbows and stuff, so you might actually--
- I don't think that people who store guns and crossbows
and get prepared for shit like that
are really in any kind of physical shape
to be doing a back flip. - They have to do a back flip
but they're gonna avoid getting bitten.
- Every single, like when we would watch
Doomsday Preppers, every single one of those guys
is just like, just cell phone on the clip,
right here into the khakis with the biggest gut
in the world.
- Well that's like a camel's hump,
you survive for weeks like that.
- Hey buddy, got a license to carry that Galaxy Note 2?
- Yeah. - Right there?
- You're worried that thing's gonna explode.
- Yeah, 'cause that thing is--
- 'Cause they famously have problems.
- But that thing, they're ready to draw that
at any point in time.
- That's basically like-- - Hello?
- Yeah. (laughing)
- We have to go.
- That's a-- - Flush it!
- Hi mom.
- You know who should be wearing those?
I hate to say this, I'm not even gonna say it.
I'm not even, I don't wanna say it.
- Say it, say it, say it, say it, say it, say it.
- We said cowboys, now we got Karens
walking around with the cell phone on their hip,
ready to draw at any point in time. Start recording.
Fuck.
Yeah.
No, needs a dunk. There we go.
That one was a little softer. That's fine by me.
I always do it right with him.
That's because I'm a little timid
because I know how much these microphones cost.
Yeah, I don't really want to break these mics,
so I kind of want to pull back on the loud dunks.
I want to see if there ...
No, there's no dent or anything on my microphone yet.
I mean, that's not ... A dent doesn't matter.
It's just going to break the inside of it.
It won't break the inside.
You know it'll break the inside.
- Wait, let's try to...
- No, this is not good radio.
- I need a one donk.
- Do it on my end.
- That's a different flavor.
- No, I don't like that at all.
- I guess if I was about to die from a nuke,
I'd try every flavor I never have.
(laughing)
- Like what?
- Your mic is off.
You turned it off, turn it on.
Not even funny, stupid, nobody can hear you.
Bad, dumb, biggest flop ever!
Biggest flop ever!
I would be in the grocery store.
I would say--
No, there's a worse flop.
I think Wood TV or whatever you said earlier
was the biggest flop.
The biggest flop was like two episodes ago.
I think I'm on a come up.
You're on the way back up?
I'm on the way back up.
You hit rock bottom two episodes ago?
My credit score is going down.
That means I'm going up.
'Cause you know how you make good comedy?
You have to struggle.
Yeah.
I'm struggling right now.
They tried to charge me for like half of a month's rent.
For what?
For a place.
But what did you do?
They told me that I'm supposed to pay for half a month's rent and I was just like, "I'm not
doing that."
Aren't you supposed to pay your whole rent?
Yeah.
It's kind of a discount.
They're saying that I moved in on the 15th of February and I did not.
So did you tell them that?
I did not respond.
You might be the worst at explaining situations of anyone I've ever met in my life.
I know.
in such a difficult time talking to my roommates about it.
- 'Cause you're just going, they wanted half of,
and they go, "What are you talking about?"
- No, I just take screenshots of every single thing
that they say to me, and then I just send it.
- 'Cause you are good at screenshots.
- You are really good at screenshots.
- You parse this for me, I can't understand it.
- I'm bad at screenshots.
I don't even know how it works on my phone.
- I'm gonna go make french fries in the air fryer.
That goes up to 450.
- I always press the wrong buttons.
Yesterday I tried to screenshot something,
and I just clicked the power button twice.
- I like to crop the screenshot and go (mimics screeching)
and then you send it and then you delete it.
- Oh wow.
- That's what I do.
- Yeah, it's so fun.
- I have all of them saved.
- Oh brother.
- My phone is only screenshot photos.
I don't take any photos of anything.
- You have a screenshot of your phone.
- Most of my photos is I see animals.
- It's zoomed out, you're in incognito Google Chrome browser.
- What am I looking up?
Go ahead.
- He's looking up POV.
- POV.
- Adam 22 solo videos. - Butt job.
Butt job.
- Butt job.
- He's looking up women giving guys butt jobs.
- What's a butt job?
- When you fuck the butt cheeks.
Don't go in, but you fuck the butt cheek.
- I've never seen that.
- I made it up.
- No, that probably exists.
- It probably exists. - Any permutation
of people's bodies-- - It might be,
we got like a one second left in the episode.
- We got a one second. - Jubio,
you're gonna pull up butt job videos.
- No, you're not gonna do that.
- Pull up, but there it is.
- Wow.
- This video is on Ellen dancing on a treadmill.
- This is a guy dancing on a treadmill as he walks.
So I see this basically every day when I go to the gym.
I see this kind of thing.
- This is what I see, yeah, no.
This is exactly what people do.
- Yeah.
- They lift their legs really weird
and they spin around. - And I'm like,
what are you doing, man?
Who's this for?
I haven't seen that.
Nobody's done a back flip.
- Well, this is what a butt job looks like, everyone.
- Wow.
Yeah, no, I 100% people doing this.
- This is all the sperms in my penis
getting so excited that they're about to be shot on a butt.
All right, that's enough for me.
- Yep.
- Bye guys.
- You got anything to plug, Caleb?
- Tonight, and no, yeah, tonight we have two more shows
in Raleigh, North Carolina, opening for Adam Friedland.
Good night's comedy pop up in Raleigh.
Go check that out.
- And then me and Cameron are going to be making
a pita pocket in my air fryer.
- That goes up to?
How much?
$4.50
Broke
Bye