(upbeat music)
- We're in a rush today, so let's try to do the episode
really, really fast.
- Why are we in a rush?
- Half the time.
- 'Cause if your fucking butt was stinking up the room,
we're gonna die if we're gonna be here longer than an hour.
Listen, I've been chill lately, Pat.
I've been chillin'.
- He has not been chill.
- But today, I'm gonna tear you down.
- Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, no, no, no!
No, that is not what we do around here.
You do not tear him down.
I'm gonna put you in the dirt today.
Don't you dare put him in the dirt.
But, if you had to give an example
of what that would look like,
I'd like to see it so that I can condemn it.
I don't wanna handle this right now.
I don't think I can handle this right now.
You're gonna handle your, a boy's cock.
Yeah.
So that's a comment. He said yeah.
Yeah. Wait, wait, wait, hold on.
I'm gonna handle a cock, I'm gonna be gay, I'm gonna--
No, okay, I'm just, listen.
Really? Can I just,
I had a bad set last night.
you have to stop bullying me.
- That's your plan is to handle a cock and be gay?
- That's a plan?
- Wait.
- Can I just say something really quick though?
- Yeah, go ahead.
- I know we like to, we joke around.
We do, we put each other down.
We do the flop joke.
We do the fail joke.
And it's fun.
But if you guys ever say the flop thing about me,
I'm flying off the handle.
I'm tearing down this whole set.
- Yeah.
- I'm windmill kicking you in the face and I'm leaving.
- I would say that even just you saying that
is the beginning of a giant flop for you.
- Watch what you say.
I think that you're flopping and failing.
Because you don't know what I'm capable of.
We're two minutes in and this is your--
I know what you're capable of.
You don't know what I'm capable of.
I know that if you do this--
Nobody knows what I'm capable of.
I know, I've seen him in the gym.
He's capable of a lot.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Is he doing like the tire thing
that's supposed to be exercise?
I do deadlifts and I throw it up in the air
and I catch it.
He's one-armed snatching 400 kilograms.
Yeah, what I do, I walk over to someone else
who's deadlifting, I grab it out of their hand
and I throw it across the gym and it hits the other wall,
it goes through, it goes out into the street,
it crashes a car.
And you know what a car is?
The damn ice cream truck.
That's a bigger car than normal.
- What his workout is, is he goes into places
and he starts stealing stuff just so he can
lift the security up and fight the security.
He gets the security on each arm.
- And it's also to practice my stealth too.
- Yeah, and also, that's actually a pretty good workout.
That's like a CrossFit workout.
- A stealth workout.
- You fight the security.
Just doing stealth stuff.
- Yeah, you go to a gym in the Elder Scrolls world
and it's like there's a section where you do stealth
to level up your stealth stat,
there's a staff you can pick up to do--
- It's trained by a Bosmer.
- Yeah, yeah, it's just all the different skill,
they have a bunch of little setups
of all the different skills.
Why don't they just do that in that universe,
instead of leveling up by adventuring?
- They don't need the gym 'cause they have adventures.
- But adventures are harder than the gym.
- But you can pay probably like 1,000 gold to somebody
if your barter is high enough to--
- Well see, that's the gym,
you'd be able to level up your barter too.
There's magic and potions in that and there's probably a potion that you can take that makes you buff as shit
Yeah, they're you can't just say probably the games out there. It doesn't exist
No that exists
I don't think a
500 gold to learn how to make potions and then I don't know if I was in the gym
Kind of is the closest thing that we have to adventure in our our
Yeah, the gym and Pam's adventure to love adventure
their adventure through their life and
That's actually a good point people say I'm going to the gym. I'm like
He's not real
Mm-hmm. I'm not smart me neither. Yeah when people say stuff. I get pretty easily. I'm pretty hungover today you guys I'm gonna
Level with you. I'm gonna hang you over my knee and slap
G VIX in the past 24 hours
This one or the drink the beer the beer nice Polish beer is you wake you pull them off
I polished off some G-Vec.
That's, that is, you have just stumbled into the, we need, in our neighborhood.
Let's check this one out.
In our neighborhood, we have to sell that shirt.
Check this one out really quick.
99 bottles of G-Vec on the wall, 99 bottles of G-Vec.
Take one down, pass around, 100 bottles of G-Vec on the wall.
Hey, hey, whoa, okay.
These Polish people are not too bright, if you ask me.
Speaking of I
There's like all those Polish like delis and stuff in the around where I live
And I went into one and I saw that they had
Lay's beef goulash chips, they're stupid you ever have some crazy ass those stores are actually so good
Though you're gonna Polish. I try to have an idea
You ever seen that
Have you ever seen that yes be careful wait. He's Polish. I don't remember. Yeah, oh damn it never know it's okay
I'm like a race traitor or something
Polish guy having something about the light bulb
Oh, yeah, I was just thinking you were saying you stupid no no no, but something about the light
How to get the light bulb above his head
They have a village or cave
- A triangle. - A pierogi.
That they all live in.
- Never had a pierogi. - I think they live
in grocery stores. - I think they change
your tune. - I do think they live
in little tiny grocery stores
that are the size of this room.
- In meat markets that you walk in,
and they have an empty case,
and every single meat is hanging from the ceiling, right?
That's nasty, I don't wanna eat these meats.
These hanging meats. - Every time I will go
to the Polish grocery store, they follow me around
like I'm in a shoplift.
They're pickled, disgusting food.
- I'm getting pretty, I was racially profiled the other day.
- Yeah?
- How?
- I walked into a, I'm not gonna say what 99 cent store,
but I walked into a 99 cent store.
I don't wanna put them on blast for being scared.
- You need to choose your words carefully
'cause there's not a lot of them in New York.
(laughing)
- That's a good point.
- You could be putting this place on blast.
- Yeah, I know, I don't wanna put them out of business
so I'm not gonna say what was going on
- Or what it was called.
- Don't tell them if it was 99 cents and up.
- It was 99 cents and up.
It wasn't just 99 cents.
So that's--
- You are putting this small business on blast.
- Yeah, I'm sorry.
- Only in New York would they have a store called 99 cents
and up. - It's actually the largest
one I've been, yeah, actually it wasn't even in New York.
- It wasn't New York.
- I went in and the guy--
- Was it the one by Stop and Shop?
- It's the one right across from my house.
I went in and the guy, that's the thing,
I go into this place probably every single day.
and I get something or I get something for the show.
I'll get, that's where I get all the toys.
All the toys are from there.
They know me as a toy guy.
And I walk in and the guy's talking to the lady
at the register, the owner, manager dude.
And then he sees me and he looks at me,
gives me a stinky, stinky eye.
He's like, okay, I'm not liking this guy so much.
And then I turn a corner into one of the aisles
and I'm getting like a sheet of paper or some shit.
Prank guest vibes.
And I see him.
99 cent paper.
Maybe, yeah, maybe they've seen prank casting.
(laughing)
They're just kind of scared.
- It's like walking up to the register
with a piece of paper.
- Oh no, I know what this guy's about to do.
- If you see--
- One piece of paper, sir.
- If you see bad grandpa walk into your store,
you're like, that's, I would say, no, no, no, bad grandpa.
- You'd have to be 86.
- Yeah, if bad grandpa had just come out
and I was a store owner, I saw any old guy walking in.
- Dude, I'd have--
- I'm kicking his shit.
- I'm trying to rip your skin off
'cause I know what's underneath that.
I'd have a sign in front of the store that says, "Grandpas need not apply."
Yeah.
"Grandpa's entrance around the back."
Because you know that he's going to put a turd in a wheelbarrow or something.
Yeah, his nuts are going to get stuck in my vending machine.
Exactly.
And I don't even own that.
Some guy paid to put that in here and he collects the coins at the end of the week.
Some poor dude.
And I'm going to have to sign a release.
If that grandpa came into my store and he did a thing where he rode a motorcycle through
a plate class window or something, I'd be like, "Oh, great job, dude.
You hurt yourself."
Yeah.
Where's the part where I care?
Hey, nice job, douche.
You fucking hurt yourself.
You fucking douche-tabash, grandpa.
You pranked yourself, you dumbass.
Yeah.
You hurt yourself.
What do I care?
Yeah.
All you did was break my window.
I don't care about my window.
Oh, no, my window!
No!
Oh, no!
Boo-hoo!
Fuck you, douchebag!
That's what I would be like to my grandpa.
You farting douche-nozzle.
But basically, this guy, I saw him.
I watched him the entire time.
He was watching me on the TV, because they have all the security cameras right there.
Were you wearing a hoodie?
He just sat there.
I was wearing a hoodie.
- I did, thought that I was a gangster.
- Oh shit.
Hood up?
- Hood up with the shysty.
- Shysty?
- I had my--
- Spiked gauntlets?
- I had my shysty on, I had my brass knuckles on.
- And my spiked shysty.
- Riding boots?
- Had my riding boots, I had a flamethrower.
- I have my spiked shysty on, it's got spikes
all over the damn thing.
- I had a big canvas bag with a dollar sign on it
and I was walking around and he was just being a bitch to me
and then when I left, here's the worst part,
I didn't buy anything.
So when I left, he's giving me the stink eye
all the way through.
He's thinking, if this guy--
- I hate leaving a place and not buying something.
- Me too, because I always--
- I feel bad.
- I don't feel bad.
I think I'm gonna go to jail all the time.
- Yeah, no, that's why I feel--
- They're gonna accuse me of stealing.
Okay, if I go into a place, I either,
which this doesn't make any sense,
I either want to, I have to buy something,
or I have to use the bathroom there.
And if I don't, 'cause if somebody sees me use the bathroom,
they say, well, he didn't buy anything,
but at least he put the most disgusting shit in the world
that I have to clean up.
- You know what I think?
When I walk into a place and I walk around for a while
and I walk out without buying anything,
I feel like I'm a ghost.
I feel like I'm like a lost spirit.
- You know what I'm saying?
- Going into a store.
- I feel like I'm going past everyone,
they can't see me,
but they feel like a breath of wind on their cheek
as I walk past.
- Going into a store, not buying anything,
but just going around like.
- Yeah, that's what I feel like.
- One of my worst feelings,
which I don't know, I'm a grown man,
I shouldn't feel like this,
is when I go into a store and I have something in my hand
from a different store and I walk around and I'm like--
- I hide the can in my pocket.
- Yeah, I do the same thing and then it looks
like I'm stealing it.
- I put like a half--
- Especially if they sit, like if I walk around
with this kombucha and I see the kombucha on the shelf,
it's the worst moment of my life.
- I had like a Celsius in my pocket
walking around the store one day.
- 'Cause I-- - Just like already
drank everything.
- Well 'cause-- - Like I'm like really bad
at stealing. - Guys like us,
we say no to receipts.
We don't get the receipt from the bodega.
Exactly, I'm not gonna walk around with a receipt.
And then we go to the dollar store,
and I say, "Did you get that chopped cheese
"from the shelf over there?"
I say, "No, I didn't, but I don't have a way to prove it."
What the fuck, I'm not a founding father.
I'm not gonna walk around with a fucking scroll.
Yeah, go, "Oh, well."
My certificate of claim.
Here it is, there's my signature there at the bottom.
There's the last four digits of my credit card.
And I'm not signing any receipt that I get.
I don't keep any receipts.
Never, never. It's really bad.
You don't need to keep receipts,
it's not that big of a deal.
- Most computers handle--
- That's true.
- Most computers--
(laughing)
- Why am I calculating?
- Hand movements.
(laughing)
- Most computers--
- I'm inventing a new--
- Computers have handled most of the receipts.
- I'm inventing a new, we've all been doing
the same hand movements for a couple years now.
- Yeah.
- We need to break out, we need to get more--
- Do you know which one was introduced
by Pierce that I can't stop?
- This one.
- Yeah, it's this.
- It's this, this, this.
- I do this all the time.
- You shake your hand back and forth like,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- Yeah, 'cause he just does that.
- Yeah, yeah, you definitely stole that one.
- I think it's so funny that I started doing it
and now I just do it naturally.
- Being in the car with him for like 12 hours.
- It's true, 12 hours a day.
- We did a 12 hour tour. - 12 hours a day.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- For 12 hours. - For 12 hours.
- A day, 12 hours a day we were in the game car.
- Yeah, we did that for 12 hours.
- Yeah, see, now we can use the hands on.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I'm gonna use my hands on you.
- Do you guys think that we should join the creator clash?
- Maybe.
- Yeah, actually, what is that though?
- That's the, he just wants more excuses for him to,
He's looking for an excuse to do steroids.
He wants a juice.
Yeah.
He wants to go on trend.
I'm literally drinking the juice.
I'm actually drinking a...
Why are you guys jealous of my health these days?
Ginger Lemon Health Aid Kombucha.
Because you're not supposed to...
The thing that people like is when we show up hungover and we show up depressed as fuck
and then we say how much we want to kill ourselves and stuff.
Cameron, go ahead.
Something philosophical.
Sorry, he had his...
Philosophical?
Mm-hmm.
The myth of Hercules.
Yeah.
What do you know about Hercules?
Right now, what did he do?
He was strong.
What, did he fight anybody?
He fought...
Achilles.
Shut up.
He fought a couple of monsters.
Yeah, okay.
He fought the Minotaur.
Who did he have a friend who was the same strength as him or who kind of gassed him up?
No, he did.
No, so what, and how strong was Hercules?
Very.
So, do you need friends or do you need monsters?
Wait a second.
And also you're ugly and weak
Okay, and middle finger to the face. I think that I will be ripping your head off
I'm about to have a creator clash. Yeah. Yeah, I'm about to create a bunch of sperms. Yeah my creators
I call them because they create babies. Oh, yeah, and they're clashing with you with each other. I
Think I would I would
Like a year ago when Matt did it he was like do you want to fight me in the next one?
and I was like, I don't think I wanna do that.
- Yeah, I think I would be--
- There's still time.
- I think I'd be scared of who I would become.
- Or is it not, is there no time?
- Yeah, no, you're not, I'm saying right now,
you're not allowed to do that for me and Cameron's safety.
- I think I'm too much of an evil psycho to do that.
- You would literally, it would be like
when you started taking Propecia or whatever
and you just became a monster.
- Well, I just started crying all the time when I did that.
When I took, what was it called?
- Finasteride. - Finasteride, yeah.
I would just sit at my house and I'd be like--
- Same thing, same thing.
- What the fuck is going on?
- Yeah.
- And it really scared me so I stopped taking it.
- Yeah, that shit is nuts.
That shit makes you not nut,
and it's like butane in a pill or something.
- I do remember I nutted one time,
and then it--
- You nutted once?
- Not to brag.
I nutted one time,
okay, I bragged.
I nutted one time when I was on Propecia,
maybe just one time in like the whole month
that I was on it.
- Yeah.
- And it was literally like water clear.
There was no swimmers.
- There's nothing.
swimmers were, they checked out.
They were checked out of the building, the ball zing.
- That must be, it must,
Propecia or Finasteride or whatever,
I think Propecia is the, not the,
Finasteride is the pill and then Propecia is the brand name.
But whatever that is, that must be like fucking
weed to sperms.
Makes them all lazy and shit.
- Whoa.
Wait, you're kind of making me want to go back on it.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
Weed for sperm.
There's a possibility--
There must be weed for sperms.
Think about it.
Although--
That's why Chompy Chong has so much hair.
Listen.
You had no swimmers come out, right?
You're shooting straight liquid, like, clear jizz.
Yeah.
And it was basically--
Your sperms are sitting in your nutsack.
If you guys are talking about--
Your sperms are sitting in there just--
yeah, I don't think I'm going to go to work today.
Yeah.
I'm calling out snake.
Your sperms are in your nutsack eating Cheetos.
- You guys are taking weed for sperms.
- On your pube couch.
- I gotta get some damn crocodile for sperms.
- Yeah.
- I gotta get my things hungry.
- 'Cause your sperms are too,
they're too excited. - What is crocodile?
- It turns their skin completely dark.
- Yeah, it makes it, it turns them into a monster.
- You wanna have crocodile sperm?
- Yeah.
- No, crocodile.
- I wanna give them--
- I don't think that's a real drug.
- It's a real drug.
- I don't believe it.
- I need some damn bath salts for my sperms.
- That's right.
- The high on face--
(laughing)
The high on Crocodile was like, it was like so good
that people were like, fuck it, I'll turn into like Tree Bark.
I don't give a fuck.
It turned people into monsters.
Yeah.
It's like a Batman drug.
Really?
Yeah.
I always thought that was like a fake middle schooler drug.
I think that's the only time you ever hear about it.
'Cause it's too extreme for adults.
'Cause it's the perfect drug
for a middle schooler to talk about.
Yeah, it is so funny.
Yeah.
I've talked about before the guy that would sell us weed
told us that if you put your finger on your taint and then smell it, it is potent enough
that it can make you hallucinate. Wow, that guy was so dumb. I kind of get that. He said
that if you smell poop hard enough... Do you know, it's not poop. You got poop on your taint?
What the hell, it's kind of wiping... Wait, hold on. He said it. Well, he maybe made a
mistake that I made until I was 15, which is I used to wipe back to front. Yeah, well,
- Well I would just scoop all the poop onto my tank
and just leave it there.
- Yeah.
- Well I pretty much--
- That's why it's called the loading dock for a reason.
(laughing)
- Nature's loading dock.
- It's called the tank 'cause you taint it with poop.
- I actually did wipe back the front.
(laughing)
I had one of the most embarrassing moments
of my entire life was I was in the car
with my dad and my brother and I was like--
- You told us this.
- I've told you this?
Okay, I just, okay, thank God.
- I'm saving you from saying it again,
but also you don't have to say it, man.
- Yeah, I don't need to say that.
That's too embarrassing, I'm sorry.
What's the worst day of your lives?
Worst day of my lives?
I mean, I had a pretty--
Of your lives?
I had a bad set last night.
So that'll do it.
And then I drank a bunch,
and then came home and ate a bunch of ice cream.
Sounds lit.
That does sound litty.
Actually was kind of fucking sick.
Who cares about bombing, dude?
Bombing's fun.
I'm still in a phase where I'm like,
damn, I don't know if I suck or not still.
So every bomb I take to heart.
But once I get over that, I'll be good.
I pretty much bombed the entire weekend in North Carolina.
Yeah.
And it was just--
I didn't bomb when I did my birthright show.
So that was good.
Yeah.
Unless I did--
See, better.
Unless everyone who went and saw me in Boston
thinks that I had the worst set of my whole life.
It's OK to bomb, dude.
That's part-- that's the same--
nobody gets-- it's not more enjoyable to see
a comedian be good.
Yeah, that's true.
They just want to see you just say something.
You know what gets more--
- That just, I'm gonna become the random comedian.
- You could be the random one.
- The random cringe comedian.
- You could do that.
- You could be.
- Then, what's your thing?
'Cause he's like racist and like bald.
- Whoa, I'm not racist or bald.
- And I'm the random cringe comedian.
- I mean, I've always been kind of intellectual humor.
- Yeah.
- That's my alley.
- He's a humorist.
- I've always been like.
- He's the humorist.
- No, I'm the humorist.
I am.
I am very humorist.
- You're not a humorist.
- I do kind of jokes that are like more set ups
to like riddles and stuff.
And I just go like.
- So I was at a bar last night and I saw an elf.
- See you were being random.
- Yeah.
- And a little bit cringy.
- But I'm trying to set up a riddle as well.
So I'm trying to blend two things.
- I don't know how many riddles involve elves.
- And I don't know how many--
- Well the elf gives you the riddle.
- Riddles aren't usually random save for interrupting Cal.
- I have a riddle for you.
What does the narwhal do at midnight?
- That's a random riddle.
What does the fox say?
That is certainly a random riddle.
- What does the narwhal do at midnight?
- Bloody hell if I know.
- Yeah, I don't even, that must be completely random.
- That's what we should do with it.
We should ask our, you know those videos
where they ask a hundred year old veteran
what it was like growing up?
- Dude, that video that's going around
of that old man where they put like--
- They need to ask him that question.
- You know what they should be asking that guy?
Why the fuck are they putting HDR filters on you?
That video is disgusting looking.
That 100 year old guy, they have like two or three HDR filters
on that thing. - He looks like he's
made out of a brain.
Yeah, I really don't like that.
I hate people with wrinkles, I hate people
that have bad skin.
- I hate old people.
- Yeah, oldies. - I talk about it often.
- I hate when you, you know like old people,
when you meet them and you touch their arm,
you can like put your finger here
and then without lifting your finger
you can move their skin down to their wrist.
- Or you touch an old person on the arm
and you see them again three years later
and the indent from your finger is still there.
- It's just a bruise.
- It's a bruise that's straight through your arm.
- Throughout the whole arm.
- I can't wait to get like that.
What I'm really scared of recently is some weird disease.
- Yeah.
- That I can't remember the name of.
- Ebola.
- No, not Ebola.
- Let's go back to 2014 and get random with it.
You basically never left 2014.
No, I did.
Look at your hat.
That's not 2014.
This is 2014, I am.
That is 2014-ish.
The colors.
I just like the fit of it.
Maybe it's more 2016.
Yeah.
I'll give you the benefit.
I can handle that.
Yeah.
2016, though, bro.
When Vine--
That was the golden age.
Dude, when Vine was at its peak and King Bach
was doing backflips.
Do you guys remember--
Oh.
I fucking miss King Bach.
You remember there was--
You miss Curtis Lepore?
Yeah, there was.
That's so weird.
My buddy Chowder would retweet it, or re-vine it,
and people would get mad at him,
and he just thought it was funny.
Really?
I'd just whack off to it.
Yeah?
Yeah.
It's only six seconds.
That's all you need.
No.
That was your cringe randomness.
That's all you need is six seconds.
Wait.
That's not true.
Why are you roasting me?
That's so quick.
They don't call me Mr. Nut so quick.
Mr. Nut so quick?
- When I go into the 99 cent store?
Oh, Mr. Nut so quick.
- Yeah, you're like, yeah, I really want them
to bring Vine back so I can finally have a video
short enough for me to cut.
- No, that doesn't make any sense.
(laughing)
- That makes sense.
- That doesn't make any sense at all.
You guys are bitches.
- I'm not a bitch.
- I'm not a bitch either.
So who are you talking about?
- I'm sorry.
- I must have been talking about two--
- Imagine if he was on steroids acting like this.
- Oh my God.
- If he said, "You're a bitch!"
- That's not how steroids are.
- That was my bad, I'm sorry to the listeners real quick.
- I probably will get on TRT when I'm 35.
- You're gonna get on HRT, get your hair back.
- That's what that is.
- But I would get the other one.
I would get the one that gets even less hair away from me.
- Oh yeah.
- Or even more. - Less hair away from you.
- Oh, oh, oh, okay.
What are you, a grammar fucking genius?
- I'm an intellectual, you already went over this.
- Grammar Nazi. - It's proof you're not an I.M.
- That's the funniest, I mean, I guess it's just Seinfeld
bringing the word Nazi into the public,
like you can just call somebody blank Nazi.
- Yeah, so I feel like I kind of normalize being a Nazi
in a way that I'm not so happy with.
- I'm pretty uncomfortable with it.
- And he also, get this, just learned this
from a photo on Twitter, dated a 17 year old.
- You're kind of like a neo-Nazi.
- What?
- Yeah, you kind of remind me of neo-Nazis.
- No.
- And like people who kill minorities.
- For what reason?
- Just like the way that you talk
when the cameras are off and stuff.
just kind of reminds me a little bit of that kind of stuff.
Yeah.
Do you think that it was more Jerry Seinfeld's fault
or Larry David's fault?
Because I just learned for the first time ever
from watching season seven of Curb Your Enthusiasm
that actually Larry David was kind
of the mind behind Seinfeld.
Larry was definitely the mind.
So maybe he was the one.
And he does seem like the kind of guy to like the nuts.
Well, Jerry was the body.
He's bald.
Yeah.
Larry David's bald.
Skinhead.
Yeah, skinhead.
Wait.
And he's rude.
He's rude, too.
- Does that remind you of any kind of Nazi?
Yeah.
- All of them.
- They're all pretty fucking rude if you ask me.
- But it's the ones who aren't
who you have to really be scared of.
- The nice Nazis?
'Cause you go, oh.
- You ever seen Inglourious Basterds?
- Oh, you're so sweet.
Wait, hold on a second.
- The polite one?
The polite one is the most evil.
- Yeah.
The polite one.
- Destin.
- Mr. Destin.
Mr. Destin was the worst character.
- His name is something.
- It's on.
- Landa.
Colonel Landa.
- Oh, oh, I thought you were talking about
the sniper.
- Oh, the guy who-- - That's another example.
- But he's not so nice, he's kind of trying to--
- He's a bit rude. - He's a bit of a pick up artist.
- You thought he was polite and nice.
- Yeah, because you-- - I thought you were
talking about that guy.
- Patrick got rizzed by the Nazi and Inglourious Bastard.
- I got rizzed up by him. - Patrick is watching
the movie going, oh.
- Patrick got Nazi-rizzed. - Batting his eyes at the TV.
- Oh, he knows about French cinema, okay.
- That's you.
- And here's me, shut up you Nazi bastard.
- Yeah, me getting rizzed by all the Inglourious Bastard
themselves.
That's right. I got rizzed by every Jew in the movie though.
BJ Novak.
Oh, okay.
He got that BJ Novak rizz.
That's right. I'm liking the rizz coming off all these chosen people.
Remember when BJ Novak tried to make a movie of himself and nobody cared about it?
Vengeance?
Yeah.
Oh, speaking of movie.
What?
I've never seen you so excited.
What do you need to tell us?
So we've been talking about how we would do downsizing.
Yes.
By the way, it's already picked up.
Shrinkers has re-entered the conversation.
It's back in the lexicon.
Shrinkers is back in the zeitgeist, our zeitgeist.
Of course.
We've influenced Hollywood before.
No fucking way.
It is.
Tell me.
I already have chills.
I saw this bus on the way here.
Huge ad across the bus.
I think I've seen this one.
Jason Segel, Harrison Ford, shrinking, now streaming.
- No!
- Quote, "Best new show on TV, variety, Apple TV Plus."
- Oh my God.
- Look at what Hollywood does to--
- Shrinking.
- They have stolen so much.
We have predicted the future on this show so many times.
- Let's put it right here.
- We have predicted every single TV show and movie
that's basically ever come out.
We predicted, what I saw the other day,
we predicted that Kanye was gonna see a funny Jewish guy
and get rid of all the police.
I predicted they were going to do John Wick 4.
Yeah, you predicted John Wick 4.
I predicted that weeks ago.
And I will probably pretty soon predict something,
but I haven't done that yet.
No, we've all predicted.
There's going to be a compilation in the future,
and that's a prediction.
While we're kind of just like patting ourselves
on the back of our predictions, I
think our best prediction ever was
there was an old tweet on our Twitter account
that somebody retweeted that said, the virus spreads,
dot, dot, dot.
- When was that? - That was before COVID.
I don't remember.
- That was like two years before COVID.
- The virus spread.
- I have no idea who tweeted it or why.
(laughing)
- Chris Lucero did.
It's kind of funny. - The virus spread.
- Pretty good.
- That's my favorite prediction that we did.
- I didn't really.
- We accidentally predicted COVID.
We may or may not have been directly responsible for,
I mean, think about our meteoric rise.
- I have a prediction.
We did predict this wait wait fuck can we just make this a whole prediction?
I think in it. I think we have to do a prediction minute. I predict that Sidney Sweeney is gonna die in a car accident
There's pretty much like one of the thick like when she's fixing one of her like Model T's or whatever
It's I forgot she liked her head cut so fucking sexy to me
Yeah, imagine perfect for the next Transformers movie imagine her using her
Bay like grabbers to unscrew something yeah, you know
Or not or imagine if she was made out of clay, and she and she could chop her boobs off
She could chop off her and she could
Okay, I have a dog friend all right all right
Green okay, I have a prediction guys go ahead there will be in New York City a new statue will be built
in the next 10 years.
- What will it be representing?
- I'm about to fucking cry 'cause of how scary that is.
- I don't wanna say too much,
but it will be a historical icon.
- I have another prediction.
- Okay.
- We will be seeing a lot more
artificial intelligence in the future.
- And we will be seeing a lot more,
a lot more, which we already see a lot.
- Yeah.
- But we will be seeing a lot more of Timothée Chalamet,
an indie movie that's in film.
- Timothée Chalamet.
- As well as big budget studio artists.
- He's gonna have a Marlon Brando style giant fat body
at one day.
By the time he's like 30,
and people are gonna be the same thing.
Have you guys read all these stories about Marlon Brando
where he would, when he was losing weight
for whatever movie he was in,
whatever war movie he was in,
he would have the pizza guys come and throw pizza
into his house so that his wife wouldn't see it.
- That's like the whale.
- He's a true, he was a true whale.
The other guy, the real whale movie, he's wearing makeup.
Marlon Brando was a human whale.
Here's a prediction that I have.
Uh-huh.
The whale is going to, one of the actors, no.
You're gonna be seeing more of one of the whale actors
now that he's won an Academy Award.
Oh wow.
You're gonna see him in a lot more movies too.
True, okay.
But basically, we've done a lot of movie predictions.
Yeah, here's a non-movie prediction.
Okay.
World War 3 will be fought on the plane of the mind.
Wow. I've always thought that ever since I was a kid.
Why isn't World War 3 just like a video game?
World War 3 will be fought on the plane of the mind.
World War 4 will involve dinosaurs.
There will be reanimated new mobile game.
What are you doing?
That's just my prediction. There's going to be a new mobile game.
2062 that sweeps. Okay. Dr. Yeah, there's new mobile. Dr. Sue. Dr. Seuss has prediction over here. Okay, 2062 humans shall be blue
Okay, keep going, but there's there's new mobile games every day short
But there's gonna be a new one that takes the country by storm Pokemon go style
It's gonna be like everyone's like have you played this one yet? And you're like no, I wrote down
I don't I don't do that. Mm-hmm. Let me read this. I can't remember what it was
You know what I did predict? That Betty White was gonna die before New Year's.
Really?
Yeah. Me and my friend Greer both said that Betty White was gonna die.
Speaking of Pokemon...
I think I said Betty White will not live to see 100.
Well that's... yeah.
Here's the other one. Pokemon Garlic and Violence.
Garlic and Violence.
That'll be the name of it.
Garlic and Violence?
Isn't the new one called Garlic something?
- Scarlet? - Scarlet.
- Oh, garlic and vine, that's why I thought it was funny,
that's why I wrote it down.
I was smoking weed.
- Yeah. - Okay.
- What's-- - Here's a prediction
I wrote down. - That's your foam corner.
- Here's a prediction that I wrote down.
- Wait, no, here's another good one, actually.
- Caleb's foam corner.
- Here's another one.
Dude, these are so crazy.
- Yeah? - Oh my God.
- Let me look through my predictions.
- I wrote a book called "The Santa Delusion."
(laughing)
What the fuck?
- That's a good one.
Oh, I remember what this one was.
Whoever we were with said we weren't going to remember it, and we wrote it down.
This is an idea me and Patrick had.
Here's a note on my phone. Pizza alert.
Oh my god! Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, what was pizza alert?
Pizza alert is you walk into a pizza store, and your phone starts going off, and it goes like,
"Alert! Alert! This guy is very hungry, and he needs pizza!"
And you go, "Sorry, I have to go to the front of the line. Sorry, look, my pizza alert."
Oh, that's pretty smart. I cut the line yesterday at Madison Square Garden.
(laughing)
- Pizza alert, pizza alert.
This phone belongs to a very hungry man.
- That's good.
How does it determine your hungriness?
Do you just press a button that says I'm hungry?
- It just plays the alert.
- Yeah.
- I forgot about pizza.
- Okay, so it's not like a system.
- I don't know if it's like a prank or a trick
or just a thing that happens.
- Well, I think, what was the--
- I think that literally the whole thing
was a pizza alert going on.
- We were in his car.
- It'd be better if it was a--
- We were in his car, we thought about that, right?
And then-- - I don't even know.
- I remember, 'cause it started out with like you making,
I think I had to go somewhere or something,
and you were saying, like, I'm gonna call you.
- Oh yeah, that's what, calling someone,
setting their ringtone to like pizza alert and calling them.
So they're waiting in line at the store,
and their phone goes off, and so it's going,
pizza alert, pizza alert, this man needs pizza.
That's what it was.
- An even better system would be
if we could somehow hack the Amber Alert system.
And we do it so that people are sitting in a pizzeria
and then they get an alert that says,
that says pizza alert, a guy wearing gray shorts
and a UNCW t-shirt is about to walk in.
He's very, very hungry.
- Yeah.
- He needs pizza right now.
Other one that I wrote down was,
imagine trying the toilet water
and finding out the dogs are right.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Which would be kinda.
- Oh yeah, 'cause dogs like it.
- Yeah.
- I had a similar prediction I wrote.
Parsnip, sweet potato, red onion, syrup, chicken, pecans.
- I had a similar prediction actually.
- That one did come true.
- Tilapia, asparagus, peanut butter, jelly,
bread, hummus, pita crackers.
- Tilapia?
- I like tilapia.
- Look at you go.
- Look at me go.
- Why are you getting offended?
Why are you getting offended by him saying look at me go?
You're looking a little offended.
- What does it mean though?
I'm confused.
- It doesn't matter.
- It means you're eating fucking good bro.
- Yeah, you're eating healthy.
- You wouldn't get that?
- Is tilapia healthy?
- It's the healthiest fish you can get.
- Yeah, 'cause it costs so little money.
- Yeah, and poor people are usually healthier.
- Poor people usually get the best food first
because rich people think that it's dog shit.
- Also, they're farmers.
Rich people eat so bad for you.
Rich people eat fish eggs.
That is not good for you.
There's nothing in a fish egg.
- We had caviar that one time.
- Did you, when you ate caviar?
- At the ball?
- The last time we were at it.
- I did forget about the ball.
- At the ball, we had caviar.
- Whenever you eat something--
- And it got on my gown.
- Oh, I forgot about that.
- It was awful.
Luckily I had a tide to go.
But when you're at a thing and there's caviar,
or I guess that's the only time I've ever had caviar,
was that time that that guy brought some caviar to the park.
But when you eat-- - It was warm.
- You're supposed to eat it really cold.
- You're supposed to eat it cold?
I don't think I've ever had caviar.
- Also, what an awful vibe to show up with,
is like you just have caviar in your hand.
- Was it a joking thing?
- I think that they worked it at like a fish market
and they just put a bunch of--
- Oh, I'm bringing caviar, look at me.
- It kinda was, it kinda was.
- It was, yeah.
- It kinda pissed me off, if I'm being honest.
- Bringing food as a joke is so fucked up.
- It wasn't even a joke, he was just like,
I think he was trying to be like,
look how cool this is, I have caviar.
It's like, bro, I'm a millionaire.
I don't give a fuck about six pieces of shit.
- I don't give a fuck about caviar,
'cause I'm a fucking millionaire.
- Bro, these pieces of food are fucking tiny.
- Look at my clothes, you couldn't tell I'm a millionaire.
- I eat ham hocks.
- Yeah, I don't like eating a thousand of something.
I like eating one big one.
So call me when the egg is this big
and it comes out of a giant or fish.
I want one pig trotter for lunch every day.
Is that a foot?
Yep.
There's four of them.
That's too many.
Yeah.
I want a brain.
Listen, I'm a vegetarian,
so I'm the type of guy to pull the apple
out of the pig's mouth at the banquet.
Yeah.
And take a big bite.
Or you could also be, Eve would do that.
Yeah.
I saw a trotter at the butcher the other day.
The butcher at the grocery store I've been going to.
I showed you guys those kind of impaled.
Oh yeah, the koi.
Yeah, the koi.
Yeah, they have koi on the street.
They're kind of big.
I said that we should do it.
We should like buy one off the street.
It's a fried guinea pig.
Oh wait, that's that?
I really...
They were making them on the street in front of the Popeyes.
Yeah, they just have them on a big spit and they're like impaled all the way through their body and they're like this and it goes through their mouth.
I would not.
I really, I do. I don't know how they give it to you when you buy it, but I really want that you buy it and they give it to you in just a big hot dog bun.
- Yeah. (laughing)
- It was a really long hot dog bun with a--
- Well, that's not too far from here.
We could go, if they're back out there right now,
we could go get that koi. - It's cold and a little rainy.
- We could get some koi, put it on a big plate.
- I'm already full.
- The koi tasting episode. - I have beef jerky.
- Yeah, I don't need it. - 'Cause we did,
we talked about koi. - I don't think that,
I honestly think that that is,
that would disgust people too much.
- It would cause a discussion is what it would cause.
- It would disgust people.
- Yeah. - People would disgust.
- But I guess, remember we just said it tastes like chicken.
- If we have a Peruvian fan, it would disgust them.
- Tastes like chicken is such a cop out, man.
Everything doesn't taste like chicken.
And I've tried only chicken for the most part.
I've pretty much eaten mostly chicken as far as meat.
- Some chicken doesn't taste like chicken.
- Plenty of chicken doesn't taste like chicken.
Have you guys seen that video where the lady
cuts open the chicken that she bought
and it has yellow in it?
- No. - No.
- Oh God. - What's the yellow?
- What kind of yellow? - Who gives a fuck?
Is it just yellow? - Is it just fat?
- No, it's like weird tumors.
- A moomis. - A moomis.
- I don't know why that--
- I don't know what word I was looking for.
- That almost made me gag thinking about that.
- It's the most disgusting thing I've ever seen.
But I've been showing it to random, random people.
- That, we have to move on, I can't.
- You have to move on?
'Cause cancer is so disgusting to you?
- No, just that--
- So you walk into the St. Jude's and you say--
- He's throwing up, bro, stop, he's throwing up.
- That was, I'm picturing when they cut open the Tauntaun.
- Well that's you.
I didn't say shit about a fucking,
Why is it Star Wars?
Imagine you cut open a chicken and it's got all that fucking guts and shit.
Imagine you cut open a chicken and it's got Luke Skywalker in there trying to keep fucking
warm with the frozen food.
I'd say okay.
Luke Skywalker who's five inches tall and he's shivering inside the chicken.
He's like, "What planet am I on now?"
You're talking from Hoth to the house planet.
I'm recording him with my phone.
Nah, nah.
Only in Brooklyn.
Only in Brooklyn, only in New York.
I have Luke in my chicken.
They put a Luke Skywalker in my motherfucking chicken.
Holy shit.
I mean, little too.
I'm on live.
Yeah, I'm on IV live.
You cut open the chicken and he's like, ugh.
Yeah.
Like he's awake.
And I'm just like shoving a camera in his--
oh, nah.
Wait, Luke Skywalker's in the fucking chicken.
- When you wake up like a dog or a cat.
- They put Luke in the middle of the butter ball.
What the hell's going on?
- He's stretching.
(laughing)
- Yeah, he's doing a full downward dog.
- Yeah, you have the chicken on a baking sheet,
you have him next to it, just completely spread out.
- Well, and also I would cut all his skin off,
like a crocodile, leave it on his head,
so that people could know that it was him.
And then I would cook him and I would eat him in two bites.
- Yeah, two bites, get like a Gochujang barbecue.
- Let's suck his clothes off first.
(laughing)
- Oh no, Luke Skywalker in my chicken.
- You suck the clothes off like an oyster.
- You're supposed to boil a loop in his clothes
for the flavor.
- You put a little bit of just vinegar
and like hot sauce on Luke's clothes
and you suck 'em up.
- Yeah.
Well you're supposed to do like when you poach an egg
and you swirl it.
- Yeah.
- You're supposed to do that with his clothes.
- The tornado.
- Yeah, you're supposed to tornado his clothes.
- I think the more I thought about it guys,
I don't think he would be in a chicken,
I think that he would be in a frozen turkey.
I think that makes sense.
Because there's more room in a frozen turkey
and they're more common.
You'd be like, "Nah, dude, they put Luke in my turkey."
(groans)
I do.
- That is so funny to me that there's a tiny
Luke Skywalker in a turkey.
(laughing)
- Yeah, those are kind of the only two that you could get.
Not a lot of cavernous meats sitting in the,
not stuff that you can cut and chew at all.
- Yeah, you get these in-between slices of ham.
- Oh, no, man.
Oh no, man.
- You zip locked Ellie back, you're like,
"That's a little heavier than I thought it was."
- Facebook, I hate to show you this, but.
- This is at the Walmart.
- You lift up the corner.
- This is at the fucking Walmart.
- You lift up the corner of like a slice of ham
and it's like his little hand is there
and it like pulls back.
(laughing)
- Or he pulls a slice of ham over him like a blade.
- Yeah, you lift it up, he's completely tucked in
and it's rolled over like a duvet.
He's just smiling.
- He's got his fingers up.
- Oh no.
- I can't do anything but--
- Luke, get out of my fucking hand.
- Stay out of my ham.
- What are you doing in my oven?
- I love a gold roast turkey.
- Stay out of my ham.
- Yeah, he got stuck in the Oscar Mayer,
and he's just, that actually--
- Bro, there's a Luke in my popsicle, bro.
- No.
- He's in the plastic.
- Nah, I would kick him the fuck out of my shit, though.
- Yeah, definitely.
- Would you, if you were eating like a rat, right?
Like you accidentally, you got like a ramen or something,
like that recent story, you know the recent story,
where the person found the ramen--
- Rat found in beans.
- Where there was the, yeah, rats in the beans.
- Remember that picture?
- That's the funniest picture ever.
- If you search rat-founded beans
and just do that while we talk.
- If you ate it and you were like,
like those people that found the salamanders
in their rice cooker and they were like,
this is some of the best tasting rice
I've ever had in my life.
Would you even care?
Like would you, 'cause if it's the best,
that was the best rice they've ever had
and there was dead salamanders in it.
- Julio fell asleep at the work.
- He completely is asleep right now.
- He's asleep at work right now.
He's asleep.
- So yeah, this is the one time that I want him to--
He's like, "Oh shit, oh shit, wait, what am I doing?"
You're looking for a picture of a rat in some beans.
- Rat in beans.
- No, not eating beans! - No, no!
- Oh my god. - No!
- Rat in beans.
- This is a fucking YouTube video, you asshole.
- I actually do wanna watch a little bit of this.
- I don't wanna see those, that's too much.
- Rat in beans, right?
I need to see.
- Do you guys like rats as pets?
- I actually do. - I think they're cute.
- I like them too. - There it is.
(laughing)
- No, it's that one.
- Yeah, this is the one.
(laughing)
- Ratt found a tin of baked beans.
- Wow.
- Oh man.
- Oh, this is the kind of shit that I'm getting into
as a comedian now.
- That's a pretty good idea.
- Despite all my beans, I'm still just a rat in some jeans.
Some meme stuff.
- So I'm going up on stage, I'm saying stuff like that.
This is why I'm bombing every single night.
I go up and I say like,
flippity floppity, this meme is now my property.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
That's how I feel comedians.
I'm going up on stage.
I'm saying that.
And people are really not
being receptive to my comedy
because I'm like.
I go up there and I'm just like.
There's no context.
Yeah. That's what I do.
I go. I do this thing.
I pointed a guy and I have a JPEG
of a gun printed out like
the fist. And I say spell
whomstive.
Yeah.
And people are.
Swiggity swooty.
I'm coming for that booty.
Yeah. And people would really
don't like all this stuff that I do.
I guess maybe it's just a little dated,
but I am trying to be the first r/dankmemes comedian.
Yeah.
I've got that little RuneScape elf.
I would say that you're more of a--
I would say that you're more of a late stage
capitalism comedian.
Here come dat boi.
And I did make a, there is on my website,
Patrick.business, there is a t-shirt
that's gonna be out for sale.
It's here come dat boi, right?
Oh shit.
- But, oh shit, here come dat boi.
But it's gritty.
- Uh-huh. - Wow.
- And he's riding a sickle instead of a unicycle.
- Okay, oh.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- How does he ride it?
- It's on a shirt, on a red shirt,
printed with yellow. - Uh-huh.
- Oh yeah, China colors.
- And it looks distressed and vintage.
- Is it deep fried, the image?
- Bro, I wish I thought of that.
(laughing)
I bought 1,500 of these,
'cause I know they're gonna sell out.
- Yeah, you should've done a deep fried image.
- You should do a deep fried special edition.
- Dude, imagine a deep fried meme t-shirt.
- Fuck.
- Yeah. - Big Chungus
on a t-shirt, deep fried.
- Dude, what if you deep fried it,
and you put maybe some kind of Carlos,
or Carlos Marx on the fucking thing, right?
And then Carlos-- - Carlos Marques.
- Yeah, that's right.
Carl Marx on the thing.
- That's the guy, that's the red guy on the shirt.
(laughing)
Calling Che Guevara like,
oh yeah, that red guy on the shirt.
- It's Carlos Marquez.
- Carlos Marquez.
(laughing)
- There needs to be,
there needs to be a Karl Marx or Che Guevara type guy
for us normal Republicans.
- Yeah.
- Like we can't really--
- There is, bro.
There is.
- Fuckin' top G.
- No, like a guy who was in charge of a bunch of people
and maybe killed millions.
- Yeah.
- Karl Marx was in charge of,
Karl Marx killed millions?
- Hitler was a communist.
- Yeah.
- This guy doesn't know anything about politics.
- I really don't.
- He's a socialist.
- I keep my hands and toes out of politics.
- Yeah.
- I don't look into history, politics.
- But you're in there throwing elbows at the women's parade.
(laughing)
- Ah, fuck you!
- I'm crowd killing you.
- I'm trying to go to Subway!
Yeah.
[GROWLING]
I'm doing it whenever someone picks me up, and I--
Am I making that up, or was there a woman's parade?
There was a woman's march.
That's what it was.
And they had some hats.
I got--
Come on, yeah.
I remember I went to the--
As if there's a difference between a march and a parade.
Yeah.
What's a parade?
I went to the--
Fuck off.
I got women.
I had to go to the women's march.
Parade?
You had to?
Yeah.
I didn't want to go.
Wait, why were you there?
My ex made me go.
Really?
Yeah.
Wow.
You are whipped.
I was. This guy wasn't real.
And I got lost.
How old were you?
I was like 18.
You got lost at 18?
I got lost. I got separated from the group somehow.
19 years old lost.
I think I went to go pee and then I got separated from my group.
Can you please help me? I'm a lost 19 year old and I need to find my girlfriend.
I was like.
That is literally me at the mall.
I was trying to. I went to the front of the one in Cambridge.
I like went to the front mr. Bean didn't know you're leading the
Pussy hat on your face like a face hugger for you're doing the mr. Beans big vacation thing you're still you're goose stepping
God can you imagine the the the freaking prankster would put on Nazi uniform March of the women
- Yeah, well that's what I would be like,
oh my god, wait, they're all Nazis.
I would fall for it pretty fast.
- Yeah.
- But I was trying to find my ex and her friends,
and I was just going through every single,
I was like walking by, I'm like,
excuse me, I'm sorry.
Just saying I'm sorry to each,
it looked like I was saying I'm sorry to each individual.
(laughing)
'Cause I was trying to like go through.
- Damn.
I'm sorry. Excuse me. I'm sorry. Excuse me. I'm sorry. That must have been hard because I'll have the same fucking haircut. Yeah
Who's here I was about to say I don't think I was trying to think of the last time I've been lost and I was
Gonna say I haven't been lost in a long time, but I actually did get lost recently and I didn't even realize I was lost
I was at the doctor
And I basically I had to get a shot.
And then I got the shot and I was like,
okay, am I good to go?
And they're like, yeah, you're good to go.
So then I started walking out
and I left the doctor's office
and I was walking out of the place
and I was like almost out of the doors.
It was like, it's in like a big hospital.
And I was like at the main part of the hospital
and I got a phone call from a random number.
I was like, who is this?
And I picked it up and my doctor,
she's like, where are you?
- Damn.
- You're supposed to be here.
Did you leave?
And I said, yeah.
So I accidentally got lost and they were looking for me.
- Wow.
- That's scary. - His patients escaped.
(laughing)
Isn't that so funny?
You just walk out and they call you and say,
"Where are you?"
(laughing)
- My big recent fear recently has been
I'm afraid of stuff falling off of buildings and killing me.
- I was at Borough Hall, I was skating,
I saw a lady get fucking like,
decked out by this piece of a,
like a slab of a building.
- Like that big? - Yeah, it hit her and she--
- It hit her and she went-- - It landed around her neck
- and it started glittering and shining. - No, it hit her right here
- on her neck. - And it landed around her fingers too.
- Damn, I got blinged up! Holy! - It was so fucked up.
'Cause there was people working on scaffolding.
You're the second person in one month who's told me that they've seen that happen.
- They probably were at around Borough Hall. - No, no, no, it was somebody else.
- It might have been me telling you that I saw that. - He's definitely said that before.
I know, but I'm telling you-- You guys don't trust me?
- I know exactly who the other person is.
My wife told me that she saw that happen.
- I'm his wife.
- No.
- Work wife.
- Little bit.
- Yeah.
But yeah, and then I saw the video of a guy
who he almost gets split in two by a piece of glass,
but it just barely goes on the left side of his head.
And so the piece of glass, like the edge misses his skull.
So the like, the pain hits right here
and goes like, and like slides down.
- And the pain probably hit all over.
- And the pain probably felt everywhere.
- Okay, you guys are stupid.
And I'm done talking now,
so I hope you guys enjoy explaining your--
- All right, his mic's off.
Now we can-- - Now--
- Now we can cook.
- Now it's gonna get crazy.
- So you can't talk unless you turn it on.
- You can't talk if your microphone is off.
- Okay, stop talking.
- Not anymore of that. - Garfield Corner.
- Oh my God.
- Please can I be part of the Garfield Corner?
- Yeah, you lead it. - Yes, fine.
Prove yourself. Prove your worth.
(laughter)
Imagine...
Garfield.
In an...
different... In the Oval Office?
No.
We gotta have Garfield colored microphones.
You guys have had the worst bumps of all time today, by the way.
I'm protecting against the bump because my last microphone broke.
Yeah, that's a good point.
I'm pulling back every time I do the "might have broke his microphone"
with bumps.
- I might have broke his microphone with bumps.
- We're like G.G. Allen, okay?
We're putting the microphones in our asses and our teeth.
- I lived in Manchester.
He was the bad man of Manchester.
- Yeah, you live in--
- There's correlations in all of the--
- I say G.G. Allen, I see G.G. Allen,
I say G.G., good grief.
- Yep.
- Yeah, good grief, Allen.
- What's that all in his body?
- Oh my God, it's poop!
It's poop and blood!
- Pee and blood.
- Good gracious, Allen.
- Golly gee.
His name was Jesus Christ. Wow. His name was Jesus Christ Allen. I don't give a fuck about him. Yeah
No, I don't really care about him either. He made rap. I would have liked it
Yeah, I don't like rock if you don't like that kind of music if he was alive right now
I'd try to straighten him out. Probably you don't like his song
Fucking I'm a giant rapist
No, I never that was pretty much like all of his music. I'm a giant rapist
Yeah, it was called Gigi Allen and their AIDS Brigade. That's pretty funny. I'm starting to like it more. Yeah. Yeah, you like anal cunt
Not another yeah, they were from all still pretty fire really
Yeah, yeah
So want the story that everyone everyone?
Tells or the one the quote or whatever that you've probably seen before is the guy from anal cunt Seth Putnam
He was in a coma
And he came out of the coma and they're like asked him like what was it like being in a coma and he's like it
fucking suck dick I hate it being a coma is the worst fucking thing ever I think
they had already written a song called them there's there's a there's a song
they had already written called being in a coma is fucking gay yeah yeah it was
just yeah that's what it was I'm anyways like yeah I was just as gay as I said
I think he wrote another song yeah yeah there's a really good picture of Seth
putting him getting it like wife is sucking his dick while he's showing okay
that guy's from anal cunt yeah can you believe it and the basis the basis
- I didn't know that. - ...Anal Cunt.
Somebody's having a complete freakout upstairs.
I'm sorry. Sorry to the audience.
Sorry to everybody.
I don't know if anyone can hear that.
No one can hear that at all.
He went, "Hey!"
If you're watching March Madness.
Is the bassist from Anal Cunt or one of the...
It's not Seth Putnam because he died somehow else,
but at the there's a mall in Rhode Island where he was doing like elevator pranks
or something what and he was like doing that thing where you like hold the side
of it and like go up or something the basis died in or an escalator he was
holding onto the side of a guy by a escalator he died in an escalator
like you felt like how do you die in an escalator accident my dad recently I was
on the phone with my dad.
Yeah.
And he was telling me he was like,
Brag.
He was like,
Yeah, I'd love to be on the phone with his dad.
Yeah, I don't even want to, I don't even want to tell you this
because it's so horrible, but you know, you know, however long,
I don't even remember how long ago it was.
He was like, yeah, so recently a bunch of people, they died on
an escalator.
Yeah, they all just got sucked in and ground up.
I don't even know why I'm telling you this.
But yeah, you know, one lady got like caught in the bottom
of it, then it just kept pushing, pushing him down into it.
They were just getting ground up like meat.
- Yeah. - Oh, God,
what am I saying? - It's so horrible,
I don't even know why I'm saying this to you.
(laughing)
- That's such an awesome way to tell me no.
- And it truly has scared me so bad.
- Of escalator?
- It was like in the past few weeks,
he said that, and now I get so scared
whenever I ride an escalator.
- You know what I think will kill me?
- What?
- Is the faster walker at the airport.
- Yeah, faster walker. - It's gonna go too fast
and it shoots, flings you forward.
- Oh my God, I have a strong suspicion.
- I didn't know what you were talking about until,
I thought you meant just the people
who walk fast at the airport.
No, no, no. Here's my suspicion. I think that it will be wildly accelerated by a Final Destination
style Grim Reaper. I will shoot forward off of it and I will die from rug burn. Imagine
dying from rug burn.
Dude, that'd be sick.
I imagine it all the time.
It shoots you forward and you don't even fall down, but you're going across the rug and
it grinds your shoes off your feet, then it starts on your feet.
And I'm just grounded nothing.
And you're getting shorter and shorter as you go.
And I'm going, "Whee!"
- It would be kind of fun.
- Yeah.
- But that is how I'm imagining it,
is that I would be going so fast
that the floor would grind me completely to pieces
over the course of the entire terminal.
- Yeah, I'm probably gonna die
from just too many body modifications
and different types of punk attitudes.
- Like, you have hidden piercings
that you don't talk about.
- It's true.
- Yeah.
- And not like the funny ones on your balls.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- No, no, no, no.
- You have a piercing that just goes straight
through your abdomen all the way around,
like at the handle on the side of a carry-on.
- Yeah.
- I have heard--
- Like a air force on the bus.
Something's like a picker up, or I don't think I've ever shown you guys
But if you've ever heard like a clank or a noise like that when I sit down actually got a full curtain of chainmail
Across my butt so I can protect myself with a gym shower. I believe that there's like a there's like a dude
That happened a lot in gym chair people try to fuck you yeah
What gym do you go to fuck?
It's just how I look yeah, you do it like a hole
Yeah, you think a slut yeah, but people stop trying once. I see that chainmail once
- This guy is a psycho.
- Boy, I don't even wanna fucking fuck this guy's butt
in the shower.
- I don't wanna be involved with this guy's life at all
in any way.
- This guy's crazy.
- That guy freaks me out for some reason.
- I don't wanna sexually attack this guy anymore.
He's crazy, he has a chain butt.
- That's what I go to the gym, when I go to the gym
and I'm planning to lift weights or something,
I put in yellow snake eye contacts and someone comes up
and I say, "Hey, how many sets do you have left?"
How many sets do you have left to go,
and turn around and open my eyes really wide?
- Six sets left.
(laughing)
- Just going to the gym and clocking in
to be a snake guy for one hour.
- You're on the treadmill on your body like this.
(laughing)
- Your stomach slithering on the treadmill.
- I'm straining for a marathon.
(laughing)
Like snake skin boots and like pants and shit.
Just full snake outfit,
trying to be as realistic as possible on a treadmill.
- You're in the treadmill and you're like,
I'm training for a 6K.
Don't you mean a 5K?
And you're like, yes.
(laughing)
I'm going to, I made a masonic.
- You're doing curls or you're just doing,
you put the weight in your hand,
you just kind of do the worm.
- I'm lifting all the weights with my mouth.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- 'Cause you're wearing a shirt that connects to pants
so your arms are just not existent.
- Yeah.
- And your feet can't even like,
it's just a full tube of snake skin that you're in.
It's going like.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I'm not allowed to shed my skin at the gym anymore.
- Pretending to be a snake guy just would be so much fun.
- I mean, there is that snake guy.
- No, but really going for it.
- Like going for it, yeah.
- Pretending to be a guy snake.
- Getting your arms chopped off.
and then getting-- - That's not pretending
anymore, you're a snake. - Amputated arms
and then getting your fucking foot,
your feet and legs fused together
so you're a full snake guy.
- Well, yeah.
- Oh, yeah. - Yeah, but then
you're almost mermaid-esque.
- Well, no, 'cause mermaids have arms.
- Damn, that's some real shit.
- And you also, at this point,
your eyes are tattooed to be completely snake-like
and your tongue is split.
- And you have a snake brain implanted into your brain.
- I think it'd be pretty hard to get a job
if you were a snake, though.
You don't need a job. People just give you money. If there's a...
If I see a normal homeless guy on the street and he's stinky and he's dressed in tattered
clothes and he's just sitting there, I'm not going to give him money because I've seen
a million of them.
Yeah.
But if you see a homeless guy who has $600,000 worth of cosmetic surgery to make him look
exactly like a snake...
He stands out.
And he's in character too. And he's saying, "Please, help me."
Need money for mice.
Yeah, exactly.
Exactly yeah
If I give you if I give you a dollar you're gonna go out and you're gonna spend it on alcohol
So I'm just gonna give you a map
Need money for mice or mice
And you can just walk up and you can feel a little
I'm kind of falling in love with more. I think about
I've shown you guys black alien right yeah the black alien project. Oh, yeah the guy who's turning into an alien
- He said that he's only like 13% complete.
- That can't be true.
- He got his fingers removed and shit.
- Ugh!
Removed forever?
- Yeah.
- Oh!
- His hand is like--
- I hate that people do that, man.
- Why?
- Cutting off the parts of them that are really good,
like fingers.
- You didn't care when I said cutting off your arms
and fusing your legs together to become a snake.
- But fingers are how you play video games.
- Oh my god, you're right.
I can never do it again.
Imagine if you-- well, you could still--
you don't need your pinkies.
If you had just like a claw like this--
I do, the way I play.
I play GameCubes like this with one hand.
This is actually-- if you're a stoner,
you should get two of these two fingers removed.
I think if you're a stoner, you--
Perfect joint holding fingers.
If you're a stoner, you don't need to get anything removed.
You already got your brain removed.
Exactly, yeah.
Perfect joint holding fingers, my dude.
I got some guy who lost his hand.
He's got like full acid third degree burns.
He has no eyelids.
Whoa, nice joint holding fingers, brother.
Can you imagine you walk up, you see--
Joint holding fingers, my dude.
Looking cool.
Imagine you see the black alien on the street.
And he's maybe at this point, he's maybe 75% complete.
He looks inhuman.
And he's got the three fingers.
And you're kind of like, I need to figure out
what's going on with this guy.
And you're like, are you trying to turn into an alien?
Like, what is this?
What are you?
Are you a black alien?
And he says, perfect joint holding fingers, my dude.
- Oh, and then you say, "Wait."
- "My dude."
- "Perfect joint holding fingers, my dude."
- And then you go, "Okay, I think body modification
is actually getting cooler by the second.
I wanna have 10 fingers on both hands."
- You know what, the body mod that I would get
probably make my nose bigger for more smells.
- Yeah, I know I said it.
- I have a bigger nose than you and I can't smell more.
- Just last episode, but I've been really fixated
on completely sewing shut one of my eyes
and having the stitches in front of it.
You want a vagina.
No, I don't.
You do.
I can just tell.
Yeah, to have to use.
But not my body.
To let my boys hit.
All right, wait, we have to go.
We said that already.
We have one hour and it's over.
I know that this was-
Who is this?
This is your uncle.
Bye.
Uncle Steve.
This is Patrick Business.
Patrick Business.
Oh, wait, shareholder meet-
Nope.
Nothing.
Bye.
(laughing)