[Music]
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to
Podcast About Me
Give it up. Thank you live studio audience here. Give it up for the band.
We got the band in the house.
Wow.
It's amazing.
Yep.
Wow, you guys hear that?
It's sounding like the summer of love.
Yep.
And we got guests later on.
Later on we'll have a lot of guests.
Well, and now I'm outside and I'm...
That's really loud.
A lot of loud stuff happening.
But, uh...
Say hello to my little friend.
Little Caleb is here.
I'm actually a little ass fuck.
Hey, Little Caleb.
I mean, no, no, no. I need to be small. I need to be small for that.
You can't just be doing my normal voice when he says,
"Hey, Little Caleb," and I say, "What's up?"
Put it back to Little Caleb.
I refuse to be Little Caleb until...
Oh, what's up? It's me.
[laughter]
Hey, Little Caleb.
Stop switching it on.
Hey, what have you been...
Have you done any
crazy tricks on the tech deck lately?
lately. I got lost in. You got it. It's ruining the word.
Establishing that he's small. I had to fight a dust bunny. I
didn't. I did. I did. I did. I did. I didn't. I did. I didn't
have to. I didn't have to fight. I didn't have to fight a dust
bunny. I did have to fight a dust bunny. Guys, we just have
we upgraded our shit. All of I don't know if you've noticed,
but we are on a serious serious XM level of technology, professional technology
right now when it comes to audio equipment. We have finally bridged the
gap from
small potatoes to steak and potatoes. We're like... That's right. Exactly like
a serious XM podcast. We have a full
thing. We have this. Some kind of thing. We don't know what it is. And Cameron,
how about you show us what it can do?
great ladies and gentlemen, welcome to
and make my voice do something funny.
We only know how to do my voice. Okay. Can I, can you move your microphone over
when I need to say a funny voice? It's too, no, you'll have to come over here.
It's too, you can't move these microphones. There's honestly, it's worse
in a lot of ways, but oh wait, actually this doesn't do this is amazing. Well, I
can't move mine. I can move mine around. You can't move your, unless you like,
You need to be on the other side of it. You misunderstand everything.
I don't understand anything.
But yeah, thank you to...
Some guy.
Some fucking guy.
Who said to not shout him out.
Yes, I hope he gets fired for this.
I think maybe it's a firing situation.
Cameron has been too focused on the soundboard.
I'm sitting here.
That's because it's so much fun.
What do you want me to say?
All I'll say is you guys are looking...
(Bleep)
Where what?
(Laughter)
You guys are
(Bleep)
You're lucky I'm (Bleep)
Why do you keep saying that about us?
I keep saying
(Bleep)
That was so long!
Jesus Christ!
Why did it not beep out "Motherfucker"?
Oh wait, wait, wait, wait.
Beep yourself out if you're gonna say it.
Yeah, I forgot that we need to stop cussing.
Oh, well that's, we're gonna do that next, that's next, next episode.
Well no, that's just for the D&D.
be because we did we there's a whole timeline thing. I feel like yeah,
okay, all right, well, then next we look forward to something crazy. Okay, so
tell us about Mexico. Then how was Mexico? It was pretty incredible. Yeah,
I
almost instantly assimilated completely. That I became fully. I mean, look at
your new hat. My hat can't punch in because dubio isn't here. Yeah, my hat
says Mexico, which is what I call it now. May Wow
And I actually, I was able to fully become a member
of the culture and of the history and lineage, ancestry.
- Can I ask you one thing? - And everything.
Yeah, go ahead.
- Anything happen with the cartel?
'Cause you did send them a message.
- Yeah, so I did, you know, I ended up meeting with them.
- You broke bread.
- Yep, at a WeWork.
And I had a meeting with the--
- Is that where they work?
- We actually, yeah.
So that's where they do a lot of their meetings.
Over an iced cafecito.
- Is that milk?
- I don't even know what it is, to be honest.
I think it might have been a drug.
- Oh, okay.
- We were able to reach an agreement.
I met with the Salamancas.
- Really?
- Uh-huh.
- You meet with Hector.
- And Tuco.
- And the brothers.
- As well as the Frings, the Fring.
- Those pindajos are loco.
- I met the Fring.
- Fring is not based in Mexico.
- The Pollo Hermano?
- Wow.
- And we reached an agreement,
and I think their activities will be severely limited
from the time going forward.
So what tell me what applause going? Yeah, that's
all the way.
Everyone is taking the cartel down.
Fuck you cartel.
We got to get bro on that.
So bad. Yeah, bro. We'll be on it. These are these are not I know it
sounds because they're so perfectly tailored to what we do. These just
came with this.
This is all just stock voices and so it also it has the the voice
effects to what's on the other page. Let's see. I'm not done talking about
Mexico.
I forgot we're doing Cameron's vacate. We play the music again and then we'll
report. Yeah, play the music again and then we'll say we'll have a proper
intro.
Now, ladies and gentlemen, it's time for Cameron's vacation corner. Yeah.
All right, so Cameron went to Mexico.
Yeah, I actually I was able to assimilate so fully I and I was
telling Caleb this okay.
I was telling him this just yesterday.
I actually had the whole time.
I did not have a single bout of Montezuma's revenge.
My stomach was pristine from the Mexican food.
that I was devouring.
- Gringo's, that means diarrhea.
- Yeah.
- It means diarrhea brought on by a foreign culture.
(laughing)
- Just the music, it makes you so sick to your stomach
to be in a new place.
(laughing)
You have diarrhea.
You're so disgusted by how different everything is.
- Yeah, but I actually, this is completely true,
I did not have Montezuma's Revenge at all
until the moment I got back in the United States.
- Wow.
What did you eat when you got back?
- Bread.
- Oh my God, that's what I'll do.
- I don't remember.
Wait, okay, so what are we calling that then?
What are we going to call that?
That is basically what they call it in Mexico when you come to the U.S.
and they call it Michael's Revenge.
Well, he landed in New York City.
That's a big puns revenge.
So you have Michael's Revenge.
I've been having Michael's Revenge from Mac and Cheese, PB&J, Hamburger,
Cheeseburger.
You got so used to being in Mexico.
I assimilated fully.
Yeah.
I actually got enough tap water in Mexico.
You're more Mexican than Julio.
I'm more Mexican than American.
Yeah.
You know that Cheech and Chong song? Can you sing that?
Which one?
Mexican Americans.
No, I don't. I think that that song is almost disrespectful.
That's disrespectful?
Which I get to make the rules about it.
Yeah, that is true.
You're going to be laying down a lot of law with us.
Wait, what kind of Native American are you?
Mexican. Mezzo.
Yeah, yeah. I was wondering about you.
Genuinely, that's what I would have been told.
Yeah.
Wow, really?
Yeah, Mezzo American.
Wait, so that means that you actually did go to the motherland.
man. Maybe that's why you have such a terrible stomach situation in the United
States. Exactly. You need to go home. My stomach felt better than it ever felt in
Mexico. Now I get back and I'm basically spraying pale poo. Yeah, you were in
Mexico, you're eating parrots and iguanas and stuff. You're feeling amazing.
Did you guys see the video of the guy, the dude in Florida who catches an
iguana and makes tacos out of it? No. I saw a bunch of iguanas. My uncle used to
have an iguana named Dino. That's cool. They used to have pet iguanas back in the day.
It died and then we had a funeral for it and we all had to go to my grandpa's house and
watch him bury it. Wow, was it named after the Flintstones? It was. Something about the
Flintstones in Mexico, they barely have any electricity. So it was basically Flintstones.
They only get electricity from generators. Weren't you in like a hut though? I don't
think that's true. Well, who knows more about it? Have you guys been to Mexico? I've never
there's someone who is supposed to be here who knows a lot more about it.
Who would be able to challenge me on that. They have no electricity,
no cars. They ride horses. Really? They dress like cowboys. They dress like
shit.
They have barely any food, almost no beaches. They have a lot of restaurants.
No trees either. A lot of restaurants with a picture of Goku out front.
Oh yeah, yeah. They did... Okay, every place... Goku burger. They had a
bunch of pharmacies that are like the tourist pharmacies. Pharmacandia. Yeah.
Yeah, very good. I love next to one day, but they're like the tourist ones that
you're supposed to go in and get like Pepto or whatever. What are you there
every single one of them on the on the window have on the wall is just pep.
No, they have every single one of them and I sent you a picture of this. They
all have the exact same printout like sign decal thing on the window of two
like monstrously buff black guys like gigantic black guys and it says we sell
anabolic steroids come in and ask every single place the same picture of the
I'll pull up the picture.
Yeah.
I mean, we can, we'll pull it up.
I saw this picture probably 20 times.
I'll put the picture in, in post.
There's some incredible things going on in the culture over there.
Do you know what the most popular song in Mexico is that I heard every single day that
I was there?
You'd think that, but do you know what song it actually is?
It's the song that goes...
That's your right.
Look, here are the...
They have this sign at every single pharmacy.
I can't get it close enough to the camera, so you guys are just going to have to imagine
it.
don't worry. But that's that song that goes dance for me, dance for me, dance
for me.
Really? They play that song on the radio a hundred times a day. Is it Joe Jonas?
Is it? I have no idea. I heard it one time in my life before I went to
Mexico, and I heard it a hundred times more. I think that's Baby Rexa. Yeah?
Yeah. Are you a Rexar? I'm a huge Rexar. I like that one one. I like the
one with... I'm good, yeah. I'm feeling good. I'm pretty sure this one's Baby
Rexa.
Yeah. This is my favorite Baby Rexa song. I think you're right. I do wonder
made this song because it is really good and it has just a perfect like right here you say
the baby rex hour dance with me dance with me dance with me the baby rex hour is that Dua Lipa?
Dua Lipa made this one oh don't say that she flopped no she made that song she recorded that
she flopped onto me and tried to have sex with me at a party because i was really really drunk
and i had to push her away it's a true story yeah i told my girlfriend that Dua Lipa was my ex and
And she didn't think it was funny.
I don't think anyone thinks it's
funny, really.
I think no one thinks it's funny,
but me.
Pretty good.
It's a complete.
Lately and now that we have this.
Soundboard is good.
Yeah.
Go Patrick.
And it's going to you're going to
tell me every time I flop with a
the sound, I think I might kill myself.
Yeah, I'm really excited for this new era. Yeah, I think that probably there
will be two episodes where we use the sound board and then we're gonna have
to outlaw annoyed by it really, really bad. So we need to stop with it pretty
soon. Yeah, luckily that's that true. That is why I didn't load any new
sounds onto this. So we have one episode right now with all of these sounds like
this. Yeah. And then we do another. So we have all the bruh and the vine boom and
all that stuff. And then we are done. We did it all. I didn't want to. Yeah, we
don't. Well, let's not do it on the episode immediately after. Let's wait
like three weeks and then just bring it back. There's just out of nowhere. I'm
going to I'm going to be using the soundboard maybe once a month going
forward. It's going to make it very impactful. Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to be
really surprised. I will say of the three of us, you're the only person I
distress with that. Oh, absolutely. If I was behind that thing, dude, I'd be oh
my God, you wouldn't. I would be doing Funkmaster Flex. I'd be dropping bombs
every fucking twenty seconds. Well, that's you guys. I am gonna bring my
drum machine in. Okay, we're gonna have a musical episode. Can we do five
fingers of death? We're literally gonna do five fingers of death next. Dude,
we're gonna do that on Monday. That's such a good idea. Five fingers of death
with no swearing. Yes, a no swearing, five fingers of death where you're just
putting up like... That is the best idea. Oh my God. You're a genius. Yeah, I mean it
looks like five fingers of death because now we have these mic arms. Yeah, I know.
Look at... I actually, I was able, I also wanted to tell you guys, I sampled, I
didn't just sample food and music and steroids in Mexico. I actually was able to
sample a little of the local film as well. Oh yeah. I was able to, and the hotel they
had they were playing a bunch of Espanol movieos.
What is it in Spanish?
El Fumo.
You watched El Fumo in Spanish?
No, so what I watched actually was this movie.
I don't know the name of it, but I did.
It was all in Spanish, but I think it was maybe, I think they maybe localized it over
here at some point.
but it was starring Ben Diesel and Elijah Wood.
And it was kind of a fantasy movie.
I haven't seen it.
I don't know if they have that genre in Fantastico.
It was a Fantastico movie with Ben Diesel?
What's the name of that genre in English?
Science fiction.
Science fiction?
Or, sorry, fantasy.
It's fantasy.
Yeah, Fantastico.
Fantastico.
And I think they were haunting witches.
But I don't know what the movie was called.
I only caught a little bit of it, but Elija Wood was really, really bueno.
Bueno?
Bueno.
Did he look guapo?
Yeah.
See?
Is it scene city?
No, it wasn't scene city.
Scene city?
When you were in Mexico, did you try at all to speak the native tongue?
Not at all.
I forced everyone.
What languages do you know?
I said hola one time and I didn't do it again.
I don't know any languages.
He barely knows English.
I know English, profanity, sarcasm, and real shit.
Wow, okay, wait. Can you get that with some kind of sound effect?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, wait, wait, wait. Okay, say it again.
I know, English profanity, sarcasm and real shit.
[Music]
Okay, no sound but can I can we just have five minutes where I'm little yeah, it's
just weird because there's overlap. It sounds strange. Will you shrink me real
quick? Yeah, I'll shrink you.
Okay, let's just continue doing this. Okay, so I don't know if you know I got
a new vacuum lately, lately, late late recently. I mean I got a new vacuum
recently and Kayla was over my house
and let's just say
(slow motion speaking)
- Yeah, that is too.
- Wow.
- Yeah, we can't figure out how to work this.
I'm sorry. - Don't worry about that.
- We'll figure it out later.
- We'll figure it out eventually.
- I really wish that,
I really wanna leave the country this year, I think.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah, or leave.
- It was pretty incredible to leave the country
and go and find a new country for myself.
- I need to get a passport.
- It's really easy to get a passport.
- Really? - Do you have to have,
to go to Mexico, do you need the passport? Or can you just get one of those new driver's
I think you need a passport.
You can't do a real ID.
Well not a real ID but like they.
That's what it's called.
You need a passport.
That is what it's called.
No it's like an ID plus or something.
No it's called a real ID.
No real ID is for flying.
Okay it's two different things.
Well how are you going to get to another country?
Well you can cross on the Canada border or the Mexico border.
Do I sound like a hot girl when I talk like this?
No.
Okay.
I'm not a hot girl.
I'm a hot girl.
I'm a girl when I talk like this?
Uh, no.
No.
You sound like a borrower.
I will say this is what I sound like.
No, no, no.
Okay. This is what I sound like in my head.
Yeah?
When I'm sitting alone at night and I smoke too much weed
and I'm thinking about the Matrix.
This is how all my thoughts go through.
The Matrix?
And I'm thinking about the Matrix?
Oh my God, five fingers of death, be like freestyle. Oh my God, I just do it as in
the okay. Wow. All right, this is too distracting and it's honestly hurting my
head. Yeah, this is what you asked for. Yeah, I know. And now I'm saying, well,
we don't want the echo. We wanted the tiny. The echo's bad. Yeah, I'm turning
it off. You don't even know how to use this thing. I don't because we didn't
have time. Yeah, you're trapped in there. I'm trapped now. I'm in a big case.
Okay, there we go. Thank God. All right, we're done. We're done. Now we're done
with this, that we're going to have a normal episode. Yeah, yeah, we're just
going to talk about normal stuff. Did anybody see an amazing
amazing? What an amazing? What are you saying?
Did anyone see
a
an amazing episode of television recently? I blew their mind last night.
I saw
um most of milf manner last night yeah that show yeah somebody needs to talk
about that show somebody needs to talk about it yeah
seriously somebody have you heard about the show
yeah oh my two moms and they fuck me in the show
or they fuck some guy two mils what's a milf
i would love to have a milf show where where i teach milf's manners because a
lot of them come on a little too strong can i give
Give myself applause. Is that okay?
Applause is fine. No, that's real shit.
A lot of these milfs lack manners.
Yeah. And a lot of them
are look, and a lot of their arms
are manly.
Charlene. Yeah.
She used both. But seriously, they're all down.
And one of them looks like some kind of
alligator. One of them,
one of the guys on the show,
independently, I
guess, I came home, I sat down
on the couch, my roommate
mate Noah was watching it with my girlfriend and his girlfriend.
And I sat down, watched the episode, immediately pointed this one guy.
And I say, holy shit, that guy reminds me of Rex.
And they all start laughing because they said Noah already said that before.
Wow.
OK, that's exciting. I need to watch more.
I'm sorry. I'm surprised you didn't point at a MILF and say that.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, you might have been actually pointing at a MILF.
There is one guy who acts exactly like Rex on that show.
and his mom is the main character of Friday. She's the actress who plays the
woman in Nightmare on Elm Street 5. Five. What's that? The dream master, the dream
child or whatever, where she has the baby on the inside of her and then
Freddie. It's into Freddie with a big like spike of spit. I watched a bit
spike. I watched like one episode of Milf Manor. It wasn't the first one. It
it was like the second or third one, and they do this thing where they like
they're like everybody, all the moms write down the dirtiest thing that
you've ever done and some and they're like, I had sex in a jacuzzi, I gave
a double blow job, but then one of them, like the sweetest of all of the
moms, who is like the one that is the least
trying to... Sexual. Yeah, the least sexual one, hers is that she fucked
her son's best friend. Oh, yeah. And the kid immediately goes to the pool
when like starts like drinking a handle of vodka, like just like seeing how
what like literally like I'm going to hold my breath under the water forever.
God damn, it's so cool, but it's like
you think going on a show like that, that you're so young was her name. Yeah,
she's a milf, but she wasn't even the youngest one there. Yeah, her name is so
young. She was fifty. I know they're all their ages. If I was a milf, I'd be
doing dirty shit. One of them looks like I would be, I would literally be sucking
mud monster. I don't remember which one it is. If I was on MILF Manor, those MILFs would be learning a lot about the Yuuzhan Vong.
I don't remember which mom it is, but one of them looks exactly like a Teddy Graham.
Oh yeah, I know who you're talking about. She looks exactly like a Teddy Graham.
I would look exactly like a vampire. No, not April J.
April J. looks like a cat. I like her. She got so much surgery. I would do her.
She was fine as hell before. Hey, everybody, some people maybe listening right now don't know the character names and haven't seen the show before.
before. Well, that's our homework assignment for this week.
So maybe we describe...
Look, I'd be on MILF Manor,
I'd be on MILF Manor talking up and down to these MILFs
about Tom Bombadil and stuff.
I'd have them, I'd be holding court.
Oh my God, wait, you would be so good.
I'd be holding court.
They'd all be in a jacuzzi, right?
They'd all be sitting there.
I'm standing outside of the jacuzzi.
I'm wearing a linen shirt with linen pants.
See, I think I've said this before.
if I if I was on the bachelor, if I was a bachelor, which I would pray to be the
bachelor, I would be telling them only about Godzilla stuff and I would I would
tell all of them. I don't remember which one they are. I don't remember. What's
your name again? Did I already tell you about that? You're standing there
holding a martini glass shaking, shaking it like this and just saying like I
can't remember if you're did I already tell you about you just get kind of co or
now?
Was that you or the other one? I think.
How many people do they usually have on the bachelor, bachelorette?
Like 20, right? A bunch, yeah. That is crazy. I cannot remember 15 women.
No, literally, I wouldn't be able to remember. In like two days. I can't
remember you guys' names. The main difference between me and y'all is I'd
remember every single... Dr. Dre vibes. I'd be remembering every single
Milt's name and I would tell them each individually
what my Star Wars OC does.
You'd be up late doing flashcards.
Uh-huh.
I remember those names.
Cade Darkblade is his name.
That's cool.
And he still has the Jedi Padawan ponytail,
even though he's running away after Order 66.
Wow.
He is living on Dathomir.
One of you is shaking this to this table so much.
You are with your leg.
I'm not touching anything.
It lives-- it doesn't matter.
He's living on Dathomir because it's like, damn,
that is an evil planet.
It doesn't matter.
He's living on Dathomir.
[LAUGHTER]
That's an evil planet.
and guess what double sided orange light saber my my of a synthetic kyber
crystal that my my star wars, osea's name, billy bubbles.
What does he do? He has pink skin really like bubble gum yeah, he's to give
yourself applause for that. Mine would probably just be Caleb
Caleb.
No, I don't know what the last what are they? What are the last names in star
wars? What about like maybe your last name backward skywalker to be Caleb
trump?
yeah
Caleb Trump
yeah, I be Caleb
that be my O. S. Yeah, yeah, Caleb Trump from
Dantooine from Washington, D. C.
From the nation's capital yeah, yeah, Earth exist in Star Wars. No, I thought
that they were going to make Earth exist. They should yeah. Well, they got
Lizzo on it now yeah. I thought she's gonna eat. That's what you're saying.
now you're saying Liz. Oh, you know, I've got they have they got you there's
something wrong with that's not right. That is too far, but we're just going to
move past that because I know that's not where your heart is. No, I was going to
say that I thought she was going to eat grogu. Don't you think that instead of
having Liz? Oh,
tear his legs off. Instead of having Liz, I want to spit and just cooking him
shaving parts of him off like he's
that green, that green shit from... I know she'd have him on a stick.
That green shit from Forrest Awakens that she puts in the thing and it
expands. Yeah. She's cutting that up. I would be breading him 'cause I
wouldn't wanna see the green. Yeah. But don't you think that Lizzo, they
shouldn't have had her in the show? They should have just... They should have
just used her name. They should have just... Instead of having her be a
Lizzo the Hut, you just have... Bro. Dude, what you... First you say she's
a... Okay, this is our reaction to that. Yeah. There ain't no way I'm
laughing. Jokes like that ain't funny. We don't like that fat phobia,
man. We don't like don't you think Liz would be a great name for a
slobbering alien lizard
yeah
interrupt. I got a text just now from Jubio why he's not here. What what is he
was asleep? Yeah, big surprise. Well, that's okay. He was taking a siesta
yeah siesta. They like siestas over there.
Yep. He knows something a little something. I learn that he knows other
side of the pond across the pond across the cross El Pondo now and Pondy toe
to an eater. That means a little right. There's also dogs everywhere with no
owners. Yeah, they're scary. They are actually not scary. Well, depends on
what part of the country you're in. There's a there's a town that they just
run. Yeah, they run and where I was to well, they don't run. You're scared of
the dogs. You didn't even be there for you were scared of the pictures of dogs.
you think I'm scared, buddy? You said they're scary yeah to fucking Mexicans
to me. They love the look at his shirt. He's in the dog pound. It says to me I'm
I'm I would go nice
says
to me. I would go and I would be can we get like a trumpet on the nails in the
back of a trumpet, you know, air horn. I would love to be one of the people
play the trumpet.
it
that's a louis armstrong sample
wonderful world. I would love to get you know how
you know how people get hired or not hired, but they do like incentives to in
certain states or they're like overrun by deer. Yeah, yeah, hunting. I'm sure
that they have something like that for dogs in Mexico. So many wild. The thing
- As the dogs, they do that for themselves, I think.
- They kill each themselves?
- They run into the street
and they sleep under cars and stuff.
- In Brooklyn, it's cats. - That's just what dogs do.
- They all look like zombies anyway.
- In Brooklyn, it's cats, and that's the difference
between the states and Mexico.
- There's no cats in Brooklyn. - Did any of them ever
come up to you and say hello? - What the hell
are you talking about?
- Yeah, well, I didn't wanna touch any of them.
That's the, it was so, I feel like there were so many people
who were there, like we weren't there during spring break,
but I feel like we were there with enough of margin
that we still saw some spring break type people
who were there.
dude, did you go to MTV's part? We went to MTV's party
and
he's against a I'm calm. Those a compliment to you and your and they
would always whenever the dogs are walking around, they'd be like, Oh my
God, and they'd like walk over is literally a dog that looks like a dark
souls enemy like it's like got like mange and like you can see its ribs. I
was just like eating, eating out of the trash. Yeah, it's like disgusting one
eyes different like it's maybe a brand or something else on of the dead shit
and they'd run up and be like scratched, like rubbing.
They'd rub all over its body and be like, "Oh my God, hi!"
And then turn around and keep eating tacos.
- Yeah.
- What do you think, a Zolo or a Chihuahua?
- Probably the best.
- Two types of Mexican dogs.
- There were many types.
- Yeah, well there's two specific types.
- I think some of these dogs maybe came over the border.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Going into Mexico.
- From America.
- Have you ever seen a Zolo?
- They weren't Chihuahuas.
- A Zolo dog?
- Probably.
- It's one of those hairless dogs.
- Is that the Mexican pet urban legend one?
- Yeah, I think so.
them. They look cool as fuck.
Yeah.
There's not wild chihuahuas running.
There is wild chihuahuas running around.
No, I think I think that my
theory, because most of the dogs we saw
were like big to medium size.
I think the small ones, the big ones
just eat them.
Yeah, that's what I do.
Yeah, I would do that.
If I was a dog, I would eat a
Pomeranian immediately.
And I wouldn't be a pit bull or
anything. Knowing just knowing what
you know about me, I'd be like a
Basset hound.
No, no.
What kind of dog would I be?
I would not be a chihuahua.
You got the yip. You literally are a yipping...
I don't think I'm a chihuahua.
You're a yipping yapper.
Yeah. You like need to be put in your crate,
like covered with a blanket.
I would not be a basset. He would be a basset hound.
Yeah.
Because of his depression and anxiety.
I can see you have droopy...
I can see you as a dog having big droopy jowls.
Really?
Yeah. And like look almost uninterested in like...
Like you...
Lifting?
Yeah.
What are those dogs that should have been put down years ago? Yeah,
they should, but they should put dogs down based on their facial expressions.
If you, I think there's a moment you can look, oh my God, that just
reminded me this. I saw something that I was like, if this happened to
me, I would literally kill myself. Okay, somebody tourist with their...
Me? Yeah, me. You. Somebody had their dog on a leash, like their pet
dog that they brought to Mexico. There were like three stray dogs that
that were like hanging out and the person was walking by with their pet dog.
The pet dog stopped and just like stared at the stray dogs and like just was
standing there staring at the person like come on come on and the dog wouldn't
move. It was just looking at the free the free non pet dogs and it just like
literally was there for probably 15 straight minutes. The owner couldn't get
it to move and it was just staring at the dogs that weren't well. Okay, but
isn't that great? I would think it was it was struck with fear. Do you think
it realized I think I don't have to be on a leash that it thought for the
the first time you can be free. You can be a dog that's not a pet,
but isn't that crazy? I think that maybe the other dogs were looking at him and
saying, Oh my God, you don't have to eat your brother, but yeah, you're
literally eat your well, they still do eat poop. Well, that's true, but I
don't really care about that side of it. I was just thinking as a dog owner,
can you imagine the feeling of you? You suddenly your dog is I think about it
all the time. So the strings I the other day I was walking Phil and I was like
is the middle of the street, and I was like, "That's where I walk him." I looked
around there and I was like, "He is like an animal, and there's not a single
pixel of green anything in my view. He's literally just touching only
concrete, only seeing concrete everywhere he goes. He's only ever seeing other dogs
that have only ever seen concrete. This will kill this dog."
But yeah, can you imagine the moment, though, when he is
suddenly sees the truth that you can be a wild dog.
Yeah.
That's what's been happening with Mo.
There's a bunch of stray cats that stay underneath my fire escape and Mo will just watch them
from the window because he's still got his nuts right now.
So he's in heat.
He's running around my house.
He's running around my house just meowing.
Fucking put a rubber band on him and let him fall off.
That's a good idea.
Honestly, that would take a lot.
take a lot. That would take a good chunk of money. Let me save a good chunk of
money. Dude, he's a cat. Even if he dies, it's a fucking cat, you're free. But he,
like, there's this one cat who's just getting her back blown out, dude. I heard
it last night. I heard just a cat going, like, 'Meow!' And he's, he ran to the
window and just was, like, sitting there listening. If you heard a human woman
make that noise on the street, would you say, 'Pfft, she's getting her back blown
out'? No. No, she's getting attacked. She's not getting attacked. That cat is
getting attacked. That was the sound of a cat in heat. Yeah, someone's fucking hitting it from the back.
You are sick. And why was he sitting there all perked up like he's ready to
jump out the window and go... Because he's evil. He's evil. He's an evil animal.
He's turned on by perversity. Yeah. Look at my arm, dude. He scratched the shit
out of me this morning. That's not a good creature. No, he's not good. That's a
creature prone to assault. Every day I regret picking him up off the street. I
feel the same way about how those dogs feel whenever anybody shows me any video
from National Geographic or something of a cannibal, like some country, and I go,
so I should be doing yeah. I could be living like this. Yeah, if I was like
people always, always all the time, I'm like, oh, I'm so glad I wasn't I'm like
born in America. I wasn't born in the Middle East or like Africa or something.
Dude, I wish so badly that I was born into a cannibal in the woods in the
middle of nowhere, where any time I saw a white person, I ate them like that's
like like they take a photo of me and that was was that JFK's grandson or some
Russia went to or now is some some rich to be if you're on the computer right
now, don't touch anything. Some rich kid went to
some country and to like took photos of cannibals for like a couple of years and
was like they're my best friends and they eat and they
like that. I would love to be on the other end and be people I
speaking of ancient cultures. We went to some Mayan ruins. Oh yeah, and we got a
good tour guide. Did you try to read to see when the end of the world is actually going
to happen? Yeah, I figured it out. What is it? It was actually supposed to be in 2012.
Really? Yeah. So what happened? We stopped it? I think that maybe they counted years
differently or something. Yeah. Shit, that's sad. Do you know the theory is, right? That
the world's already ended and we're in fucking purgatory right now. Shit. Every single one
of us represents a different stage of grief. I have to say, these mics... Yeah, what would
be the fan theory about about us three who would represent what what I would
represent I would be a little over two deadly sin I'll be less than pride
probably probably be
what are the seven deadly sins avarice and lust and really what is that rise
wrath I don't think avarice is greed yeah ever since great okay I really be
don't say I'm a little everest I guess maybe I probably be greeting gluttony
because I'm going around the country like Bourdain eating all the money and
sloth food you'd be cool sloth. I do see a mixture of sloth and gluttony. Yeah.
And then you would be, uh, you'd be wrath. Yeah, you'd be wrath. I'm sweet
and greed and wrath, greed, lust, envy, pride, every dollar I make. And what
world am I greedy? I would have away any money. I give away all my money.
You're sitting there on a, you're, I, we've been to a, and listen, you've seen
his wicker grown. I'm going to be completely, I'm going to be completely
real. I feel like you guys are making jokes out of it, but I'm going to be
100% genuine. Mine would be spilling my seed.
Wow. That's your own and ism masturbation.
Yeah. Yeah. Masturbation is honest, because I feel like with these mics, we
are kind of going into a little Joe Rogan territory.
We're just going. Oh, yeah. Let's do that. Yeah. Going a little deep.
I have been retaining my semen.
Really? I see it. I've I've been sowing it.
Yeah. And you've been sowing it. I've been doing the opposite.
How long? So I've probably like two months.
That's a long time. Two months I've been just holding it in.
Every time my girlfriend, she tries to, like, she's like,
"Come here." And I say, "Get the f***."
Get the, wait, say it again. Say, "Get the," again.
And I do a tornado spin. Say, "Get the." Say, "Get the."
Get the f*** here. Yeah.
I do a tornado spin.
She's not getting any of this.
Here, come.
Dude, I, don't you guys, don't you think that... She is not touching this thing.
I think that those, that the thing of people who, like, like cum,
I think that's like honestly they should be like locked up. Who likes come the
zombie girls and guys? Oh, you're talking about sluts. Yeah, I think so.
Let's be locked up in a
oh yeah, yeah, sluts like how much how many mental gymnastics do you have to do
to get to the way you're like? Yeah, I think actually that's cool. Why not just
like it's just a just booger instead, just like like like people like oysters
like icing or frosting or something instead, because that's the yeah
cinnamon roll. I know pineapples. You can make your jizz taste
in a book. That's not true. No, you can make it taste like a B vitamin.
That's what I'm saying. Just spray your face with this.
Trust me. You make it taste like a B vitamin shot that you buy for
seven dollars. That's what it tastes like.
You know what it tastes like. Just guessing. I don't think you mean
All right, that's a hard reset on that conversation. So we'll move on.
But my tour guide, he kept, he was pretty knowledgeable.
It seemed like about the Mayan stuff. Not that I know that much about it.
So he could have been completely lying, I guess.
But one thing he kept doing is every like 10 minutes,
he'd find some way to like tangent what he was saying into being like,
yeah, and you know all across the world, every culture has
legends of giants and believe that there were giants that walked the earth. So I'm not going
to say too much about that. That's a different story for a different time. But everybody
around the world believed in giants at one point. And he said that like maybe five or
six times. And then at the end when we were leaving...
The Kandahar giant?
That's a giant. Very good.
No, but do you think that like... because remember that story blew up about like a couple
months ago.
You're blowing up his story right now.
Yeah.
I'm sorry. I just I got excited. Keep going.
he well this isn't even that worthy of a final thing, but we were leaving he was
talking about like coral reefs and sea level and stuff and he kept every time
he mentioned global warming. He said supposedly
pretty good, but he kept he kept doing the thing where he was like he said
something about giants or he said like in every culture. There's a there's a
symbol of someone with seven heads, but that's a story for a different. He said
every time he said that's a story for a different time. He must have a separate
core that you're supposed to ask him about. Yeah, definitely. I think he was
giving you like dialogue tree options where you're supposed to say, "Can I, can
you take me on your special tour?" And you kept saying, "Where's the bathroom?"
Puedo ir al baño. Puedo ir al baño. Baños, baños. There were, I also learned, I
now, I really don't like people from Italy and people from France,
which I already didn't like, but I had some face-to-face interactions that made
me like them even less. What, tell me what the face-to-face interactions were.
so it's and French French French person. I like to call them the galls by the
way.
They disgust me so great. Can you believe what they did to Rome? The
galls are awful. Rome was so great. Yeah, they were fucking with Rome. Galls
are stinky galls. Bro, if Rome is your up, you are my up. Absolutely, I'll
ride for Rome. I'll ride for Rome. Which is not in Italy, because it was old
enough that it doesn't count. It's Rome, it's a different thing. I'm more
thinking Vatican City. The French people, they're riding a bike and they're
know when you ride a bike and you ring your you ring a bell and you say on
your left. Do you know what French people do instead of that? They just run people
over? They whistle. Oh, but wait. They come up on you and they go I'm not gonna I
can't really whistle. They do that right right behind you in your ear and I say
"Merci." "Merci?" Isn't that horrible? Dude. I wanted to fucking clothesline this guy on his bike.
They're riding around Mexico with on their bikes that have like a bag of
groceries with a big baguette sticking out of them. Yeah. Yeah. And they're
telling you mercy. What's quesadillas in Mexico? Yeah. True. Well, yeah. Over
they have one big tortilla.
Yeah. So tell me. Okay. So I get that about the Gauls because they are
disgusting people. Yeah. They've always been the worst of Euro. But pray tell,
what did Italiano do to you? He this guy was on my tour. So this is one guy. I
just like to say is it could be having nothing to do with him being an Italian
It has a lot to do with him being Italian.
Was he a male?
Euro-Italian or Jersey?
Yeah, Euro-Italian.
I said people from Italy.
At the beginning.
His name was Valentino.
Oh God. Alright, I'm with you.
Yeah, and you know what, he was just
annoying the whole time. He kept asking
the most annoying questions. He did the
thing where... When do we get the pizza?
Italian Elon Musk.
but the play the trumpet again,
but the thing the thing that he did was so that was so crazy. Yeah, is he
started and like what after we were at which we're touring teaching it's up and
we're talking and the guy that he thought it was chicken eatery. Yeah, he
did think that yeah, the guide the trumpet, the guide was telling us about
like oh yeah, the and the Europeans, you know, they stole all the car when they
like the conquistadors came in, they took all our carvings in our gold and
they put them all in museums over there and we're working on getting them
back. So we could they can be in teaching it, so we can like give tours
of them and stuff and the guy like the guy came like clearly stored this
information. His head came up to the guide like ten minutes later when we
were like at the bathrooms and he started a huge argument with the guide
where he's like just so you know, museums shouldn't bring back any stuff.
He was like he literally was like it wasn't even like like he straight up
was like yeah, that stuff isn't stolen because it didn't belong to anybody and
he started like a fifteen minute argument where he was like and it should
stay in the museums because it's in the museum and it's cool over there. I
will say I will say yeah, I agree. It was so crazy. He's to do it to but to
specifically the tour guide who is like a like clearly very passionate about it
too and the tour guy was just like it was to the point. It was the type of
argument where the tour guide was not even like arguing back. He was just kind
he's standing there with his arms crossed and the guy was just talking at him
and being like and that stuff it doesn't belong to anybody and it's really
nobody's goal. Here's what I would say. I think if you took that tour guide and
you brought him to the Metropolitan Museum of Art here in New York City,
and you showed him how many eighty year old women take photos of every single
thing with their iPad, it's true. He changes mind. Oh yeah, he would of the
most sacred religious thing that his country's ever had. They're doing this
and I have it yeah and they're doing that. They get this part of the tour. We
swimming on part of the tour.
They look at Venus de Milo and they're just like, "I'm going to eat that pussy."
We went swimming on part of the tour. Valentino, I think you can guess how long his swim trunks
were.
Oh my God, he had his cum gutters poking out.
Tell me, was he packing?
It didn't look like it to me.
He's wearing a spongy, amazing shape.
Honestly, he was not in amazing shape.
Too many carbs.
Pastas de Hilo he's eating every day.
there was also a guy who was trying to was trying to who was doing the
basically is Peggy Hill Spanish on the tour and this the Italian guy got in
the like the tour van and the guy was and was like oh like where are you from
there was like introducing each other and he was like it's auto unis and the
and the Italian guy like clearly thinking the Italian guy was Mexican
like oh like and the Mexican Italian guy was like oh United States. Oh, what
state and the guy could get the American guy again went it's auto unis
(laughter)
- That's amazing.
- It was really great.
- I really want to be a tourist so bad.
- It's so great to just let go and just be free.
Be a parasite in a country.
- I do that shit when I go to like Louisiana,
when I go to like anywhere, like in New Jersey.
- That's 'cause you've never been to another country.
- I've never been to another,
I do this shit in states I haven't been to.
- You do it in towns you haven't been to.
- We go around, when we went on tour,
I'm like going around like Atlanta. Yeah, okay, we're driving through.
You're we're we're we're driving through like Lubbock and you have the window
down. You're like, what do you guys do here? Yeah, talk slowly. Hello.
Do you raise cattle in
and doing some reason doing sign language stuff?
Just doing this for this.
just wiggling your hands around. Yeah, I really what is your biggest export in
Shreveport? I need to get I need to learn Spanish very bad. Yeah, yeah, but I
think the only way to learn Spanish, I learned to move to Spain,
you have to move. I learned well. I learned a good amount by going to
Mexico. I think Mexican, I think you could probably learn some Spanish in
Mexico as well. I learned this phrase,
Centurion de Segura's dad.
Well, that is the century of Tom Segura's dad.
That's what I thought at first.
No, centurion is basically a protector.
It's clear actually.
Yeah, protector of...
I'm thinking of the Latin root, my friend.
It's actually, if you want to know what it means, it means seat belt, and centurion means belt.
Okay.
So I learned that, which I never knew before. And get this too, the symbol for parking is an E.
Yeah, for E-parking.
parking. I asked I asked really what it was and it's a really long word that I
don't remember. Okay, it's way longer than parking. It was a long enough word
that I thought that can't really mean parking. Estabon does yeah, it's Estabon
yeah, but seeing an is seeing an e seeing a black e in a red circle can be
kind of man can make the sensor button. If you're going to say that word can be
kind of jarring because it is because of the right angles
black e
Come on, you can't be saying that.
Yeah, that's an air horn.
Hit the air horn for that.
That's an easy, yeah.
(laughing)
Yeah, Patrick got you, I gotta say it.
But if you see it out of the corner of your eye on a sign,
'cause a symbol with black right angles and a red circle
is not something you're expecting to see on the streets.
And it really, if you're not looking closely,
it can really get you.
You can really be able to turn your head and be like,
what the fuck is going on over there?
I would say in America and most
countries, I feel like they purposely avoid yeah, black,
kind of harsh angles. It's literally a red circle, like a
red circle and then white inside and then black. Sure,
if the stop sign was all at the stop sign had the black letters
yeah and let's say just two s's at the beginning, it would definitely be a
pretty bad sign,
but I did see some swastikas in graffiti really. Yeah, I saw two of them.
That was so... Sid Vicious would wear shirts with swastikas on them.
There's that South Korean pop star who's walking around with swastikas on.
Oh, the Q, yeah. Swatting the QAnon stuff.
Yeah, because he does it with...
Didn't somebody a while ago take a picture with Taylor Swift with a swastika shirt or something too?
Taylor had one?
I think they might have.
I think that that happened.
That might have been a shop though.
I think that happened a long-ass time ago.
I think she's a clone.
Yeah, personally.
I think she's a clown.
I think her music is actually fucking bubblegum ballad.
- Bullshit. - It's ass, bro.
- Yeah, yeah.
- It's basically-- - Fucking ass music.
- It's like ass. - It's almost like
she doesn't even-- - Wait, censor all that.
You can't be saying it. - She doesn't even write it.
- She writes music like fu--
Are you-- - You guys have to keep
talking, I'll do it. - She writes like
(beep)
music.
- You've been, whenever he censors you,
you actually don't say the words.
You go like-- - 'Cause I don't know--
- (beep)
- Shit. - (beep)
(laughing)
- It's so funny when the censor happens
in the middle of the word.
- I just took a fucking shit.
Or wait.
(laughter)
- No, wait, we have to delete that.
My mom will hear that.
Let me try again.
- My motherfucking (beep)
(laughter)
- I'm gonna go take a (beep) shit.
Okay, this is too much fun.
It's too fun.
- Hey man, do you wanna go take a shit later?
(laughter)
- Notice how he never censors himself.
- My, what?
- Himself.
- You don't censor yourself because you're a
mother fucking.
Now you suck.
You suck.
You got owned.
It's weird to censor myself.
It feels it feels like giving
myself an air horn or something.
I wish that we all had a button
that would like we.
I bet it's possible.
I bet they have an app or something.
One of those Lego things.
You know, like the Lego
robotics.
The Lego robots.
Did you guys have.
Did you in your high school.
Did you have a Lego robotics
team?
No, what kind of fucking Disney Channel High School you go to? We
went to a high school that had a film program. We didn't have a film program.
We had a TV production program.
Because the public access center was on the school campus. That's cap.
That's not cap. That's cap. Yeah, you're capping. Bro, I told you guys about
the time
that I was at the center and that kid hit his... He was
dab pens and he hit his dab pen in the green room where the...
You had a green room?
The talent, which is just the vice principal.
Whoa, what the fuck?
That's what I'm saying, dude!
What kind of high school did you go to, bro?
We always let him talk about the TV production class.
It's crazy.
He went to the school from iCarly or something.
Yeah, that's insane.
What other cool stuff did you have?
So this kid hit the dab pen in the room.
It was one of the earlier dab pens, so the ones that still smelled like weed.
The big ones, yeah.
Where you had to blow it in to turn the shower on and smoke it.
smoke a spoof or whatever that was called.
Yeah, I don't know what you're talking about.
Sploosh or spoof, it's a sock.
Sploosh is the thing from holes from holes.
It's a cardboard tube with a sock.
It's apples from holes.
Yeah, it is.
It's a cardboard tube with a fucking dryer sheet and a sock and you have to blow into
that so it doesn't smell.
Oh yeah, I know that.
And he just hid his dab pen in the room and our teacher and the vice principal walked in
and was like, what is that smell? And he found out that they like could smell it.
So he just ran away. Well, ran away forever. He ran away into the woods.
That's crazy. Not to make this the vacation episode. Yeah, I mean it already
is. Yeah, but when I was on the plane to Mexico, the guy next to me, he was
vaping in his seat. But what impressed me, I have no idea what he was doing
with the cloud. You can ghost it. Yeah, you can ghost that sheesh. How? You
just swallow it. I censored myself so he wouldn't do it. He was swallowing it.
That's what I thought, but I was like, I've never tried that because I've never had to.
I don't know if it worked or not.
It's pretty hard.
I was doing it, but he was doing it with like it was like it might as well have
been. I was watching him very closely because I was like, what's he going to do?
The sleeve is going to put it in his like water bottle or something.
I was I would always do it into my sleeve, like which is the most conspicuous way.
Yeah, yeah. Because there's no natural movement.
Are you going to do that? I'd see you do that.
and then like through your sweatshirt sleeve, there would be a cloud of smoke
going through.
Well, that's what I would. Yeah, I guess the only times I did it was in a movie
theater and I would just do, I would just, cause that doesn't matter that much
on movie theater. No one's going to see it. So I would just do it into my, into
my collar.
I, uh, man, I forgot that I jeweled for so long. I have no, like that's just an
afterthought. Nobody has jeweled. You know what I'd have though, if anyone,
20, 20 bucks a pop, I would sell you. Oh, they sell every vape flavor in Mexico.
they have vending machines. Whoa, do they have everywhere? I didn't look too
closely. If I had... I guess I say they have every flavor, but what I saw was
if you have vending machines everywhere that had, they were only vapes and
like a range of every color. No chips or anything? If I had... No, literally
just vapes. I didn't see a single snack vending machine, I only saw vape
vending machines. If I had Mango Jewel again, I would start vaping. Go to
Mexico. I would start vaping. I'm not doing those Elf bars though, those
those things are scary as fuck. I think some of the vapes in there were those.
There is a world, guys. The Mango Jewel was the greatest flavor in the world.
I want you guys to be... Flavor. Flavor. Now that you've been. Yeah. Are you
open to the idea that one day we move this whole operation? 100%. It would be
incredible. I would move there in an NC of one-half. The amount of space that
they have for rent there in Tulum, in the tourist area, where we could get
beach front. It would be cheaper than this basement office. Yeah. It would be...
that is currently leaking, it's raining inside right now. You can't hear it
because we have professional microphones. It would be beautiful, right? Yeah.
These would get stolen every single day.
It'd be amazing. I would have the... Oh my God, I would start doing like
cross white strips and I'd be tan like Wayne Diamond. Not a single thing of
mine got stolen besides my heart by the beautiful landscape. Wow. Yeah, no,
I think a lot of that's overblown. I'd be completely... I would look exactly
like Wayne Diamond if I lived in Mexico. I'd be linen shirt, linen pants,
dark tan skin, white ass teeth. No, no, no, no. We would be fully assimilated.
We'd be wearing... Yeah, I would have... No, I'd have like... They sell...
Everyone wears Patriots and Red Sox merch, too. Really? How much tanning I
do, how much tanning I would be doing, my eyes would be so white 'cause
of my sunglasses. I'd take 'em off and it'd be jarring. And you would be
more jarring for you. You'd be blonde. Kind of like a reverse Uncle Fester.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Or I have a lot of hair. Yeah. Speaking of the
Red Sox thing, I guess that's a big... In Mexico, I know this because...
I should be Cameron Fester.
There's a guy.
You should.
Cameron Fester would be good.
The guy who works at Gordo's said that his uncle, the Mexican guy there, Fabricio, said
that his uncle was a Red Sox fan.
And then he took a selfie with my mom and dad.
It seems like there was a lot of Boston sports fans.
I thought you were going to explain why.
He explained all that and I did not say anything.
You literally said I know another guy who is a Red Sox fan.
You know, wait, you knew a guy who was a fan of the Red Sox?
He said that it's big down there, the Red Sox are a big team.
They are.
But why, I guess is my question.
I don't know.
Also, I saw in a souvenir shop, they had a poncho, a Patriots poncho with the Pats
logo that said Patriots. And I was talking to the guy because I was like, I was
thinking about like, I'm probably not going to buy this, but I was like just
looking at it and the guy came over and was like, oh, you want to buy it? And I
was like, no, I'm just I'm from Boston, like where the Patriots are from. And he
was like, oh, Boston. Yeah, I think we might have some Boston merch, like
Boston sports stuff somewhere. So we didn't know that the Patriots even were.
Well, because it's not actually from Boston.
No, they're from Foxborough.
- No, yeah. - Foxborough.
- New England. - But, I know it's
the New England Patriots, but he doesn't even know
what Boston is, is what I'm saying.
But he basically was going to go look for Boston stuff.
- Famous Mexican Red Sox player,
Speedy Gonzalez.
- He didn't play.
- You can hit the cricket on him.
- Yeah, we're gonna give a cricket,
and actually we're gonna do a cricket
and a trombone for that one.
- Yeah.
(trombone playing)
- But, because that feels a little too mean,
we'll give you one applause.
- There we go.
(cheering)
I like the I like the wand. I like the record scratch, but maybe that's just my
I'm coming to record scratch is I think my favorite. I'm into trying to not log
stuff. I like the trumpet still the trumpet.
Yeah, we are in a new era.
We are in an incredible new era.
This show. It's kind of scary not having to hold my mic though. I'll say that.
Yeah, I don't know what to do with my hands. So funny. I have been going like
I've been crossing my arms and shit. I'm not even playing with the screw anymore.
With your nail.
Yeah. Well, you weren't here when we talked about the nail.
He has a nail. I found out that he has a nail that pokes through his side of the table.
I knew about that nail.
There's a nail that goes nowhere.
He plays with it all the time.
Yeah, I know he plays with it. He hurts himself on it.
Wait, you know everything. You actually are lying.
I sit next to him.
He pays attention.
You both sit next to me.
I sit next to him maybe more than mine.
He is not listening.
Yeah. I guess you're more aware.
He's aloof.
Yeah, you're more aware of the shit that I do probably. I mean,
having to sit next to me on like a plane and stuff,
that is pretty rough. It's really rough for you. I know he doesn't give a shit,
but you, I know I'm sitting there going like...
He's posing for the stewardesses. Wait, what did you say? I'm trying to get
the stewardess's attention. I've never noticed you on a plane. What do you do
on a plane? Well, think about how he acts in the passenger seat of your
car. Where he touches things? Yeah. Yeah. Does that bother you? And then
- I was thinking about that in the emergency exit row.
(laughing)
- Oh yeah.
- He's tracing, E, X, E on the fucking red sign.
- I'm turning--
- He's touching the handle.
- He's like, he's not good on planes,
we're taking like a two hour flight.
- I was beautiful on the planes.
- Really?
- You guys would have been so proud of me.
- I would have been proud.
- I read 100 pages of some 19th century literature,
I watched Eight Mile, I watched Men in Black,
and I chewed my gum.
- How long was the flight?
- Four hours.
times have we sat next to each other on a plane in the emergency exit?
Because there's maybe twice. Yeah, there's more than what like it's two
hour flights. And I know I'm trying to in my head, I'm like, oh, this will
make him laugh and it'll make it easier for him to fly. Yeah. And I'm
pretending to pull the door open. I'm sitting there doing a I'm getting
like I'm trying to pull the emergency rafts and stuff
from under the seat. Put the oxygen on your balls.
Well, I want, okay, I've finally, I've grown and matured enough from
being, having a primal fear of airplanes that I think I'm finally ready. I
want the oxygen mask to come down on one of my flights. I did see a
video the other day. I wanted to happen. I've... That was like a, it
was like the aftermath of a really bad turbulence and the plane was completely
silent and there was just like shit everywhere. Yeah. And I was like,
"Oh, I've never actually had a scary experience on a flight." Yeah, for sure.
like that is and the flight is the plane is still flying. Yeah, like I've I
thought that I've had bad. Well, so the what the the the oxygen mask, because I
don't want even little turbulence. I'm still I can't deal with the turbulence.
I like turbulence. The oxygen mask, I think, would be would be awesome. Yeah,
feels good,
because when you have the oxygen mask, I mean, if you don't, if there's the
oxygen mask doesn't come down, yeah, there's a chance we all pass out due to
depressurization and we just don't know what's happening, right? Yeah, that's a
and the oxygen mass comes down, that's the only time you're a hundred percent
sure you're getting enough oxygen. Yep, yeah, well, but don't you kind of isn't
that kind of the ideal way to go on a plane is that you you the ideal way to
go on a plane is to your destination. That's true. That is
land safely. Yeah, that was a good point. That was fire. Yeah, I guess you're
right. I'm just thinking about I go into every I do feel so it's the only time I
feel so comfortable with the thought of my own death is when I'm on a plane
because I'm like literally there's nothing I can do. Plus a lot of people
are going to die with me. It feels exactly
it feels the exact same way as how I imagine. Imagine how embarrassing it would
be to be the one guy who died in a plane crash. You know the kind of calm
serenity. Imagine just sitting next to the guy who died. That happens. You know
how calm you feel when you see a plane that you weren't expecting flying over
you, like not a commercial plane, like some kind of weird plane that you've
never seen before flying over you. You're like, oh, okay, so that might just
drop a bomb on me and I'll just die right. I always feel like any way you
mean. Oh, I thought you meant in a plane. No, I'm worried about I guess. I
think that like helicopters to be a helicopter is going to hit a building
or oh yeah, I guess I see think about that fly off and cut your head off.
Yeah, helicopters are not good. I agree. No, I don't think I ever had to get
med flighted somewhere. I say no, no, no, I'd say you take me. I bring the
car. Yeah, bring
ambulance. I am. I know we're on the side of a mountain. I know what happened
Randy Rhoads, okay? This shit is not gonna happen. I'm just as good at guitar. You are
not taking me out. I don't want to be the video of the lady spinning a thousand times.
That was too funny. I don't want to be that. If I crash in this helicopter, I will be so
fucking mad at you in the afterlife. I'm gonna haunt you like those kids haunt John Landis.
They haunt the fuck out of him. That's why his son is all fucked up. That's why his son
has a rainbow SJW hair because he had but does the opposite of that kind of stuff.
He has a because he tries to bring more kids to life. Yeah, exactly. Yeah, and
of the way that's very bad. Yeah, that's a scary fellow, but God is movies are
good. Oh, God, bright, bright. Holy shit. Yeah, craziest movie. I've ever
guy needs to be. We needed like this guy needs to be basically Woody Allen or
Polanski. He needs to be. He needs to be able to run away to another country and
make whatever he wants forever. Everyone needs to sign a petition for him. I need
Chronicle 2! His cream was all over a bunch of people's tops.
He was creaming. That boy was creaming his crops. He's wearing
SJW pants. He literally dresses like an SJW.
Alright, give us one more soundboard thing to place out because I gotta leave.
guys that's been podcast about Liz the battery is running low that was the
perfect ending
(beeping)
[BLANK_AUDIO]