Now. Okay, so no coffee for me today. Really? With a white label, yerba
mate soda. I don't like those ones. I like the Genkia or whatever it's called.
It's not called that. Bleep bleep blah. Bleep bleep blah. Yellow cane.
Yellow Cane. Speaking of Yellow Cane, I want to watch True Detective Season One
again. I was thinking about it. I haven't seen it since I first seen it. I gotta check that show out.
I never watched it. You've never seen it? No. I saw the last episode of True
Detective with my dad and I was like, oh I don't. Which season did you see?
Did you see Mar- oh really? Yeah. Dude, why'd you watch it? You're a fucking idiot.
It's so- I didn't care about- Also, you can watch it again. It was on when I was in high school and I didn't care
about TV. You said F and immediately
that's two right because F and that's true. I was even going to let it slide,
but I'm completely right darn it dude all right. Well, we're still not cussing,
but we are cussing, but we're paying the price. I have two bucks. This is my
allotment for the rest of the episode. That's why that's why it should be coins.
No, you don't under you are trying to make your brokenness of virtue. It's not
a brokenness. It is brokenness. It's not a broken chronic. It's that you are a
broke boy. You're a broke bird. People don't respect coins. Can we say broke
boy? No, I was replacing a different B word. That's meanness. That is meanness.
So, okay, is there just... Okay, how about this? How about this? You're
kind of... You're like Aladdin or like what's a... Oliver Twist. You're a rat.
You have the virtue of Oliver Twist. You know how funny that would have been
with a high voice? What, your burp? That burp wouldn't have been very funny.
Well, yeah, it wouldn't have been. I mean, people have heard that before. What
are you talking about? A high pitched burp is funny. It's always funny.
it's fine. It's okay, but you could come up with better stuff to do in a high
pitch voice. I also think I think a low pitch verb verb verb of funny. I just
drink my little beer, but my brain will start activating pretty yeah yeah. My
brain still working on activating me to my allergies or beating the beating the
hold on now. Is this out of me really? Yeah, you said beating the devil out of
me. That's better because then it's like you don't want to use this. Yes, the
but Jesus is okay. I tell you a bub's Jesus yeah, it's as hot as
the sun. It's hot as the dickens out there. I'm sweating up a dickens
speaking of all of our twist. Yeah, it's twistedly hot. I've put in my air
conditioner unit, my AC unit really last night. I haven't done. I cranked it
to sixty degrees. Whoa, I woke up and Phil get this. He had icicles coming
out of his nose. Oh my God, too cold. Yeah, wow, you see I haven't put my AC
yet I'm kind of relishing the couple days of sitting in my underwear on my couch and
yeah playing on my iPad.
You can do that.
You can just always do that.
You have a leather couch?
No, you have a linen couch.
I hate being hot.
Go ahead and drop a bomb for me.
I don't have the bomb anymore.
But oh wait, I can do a different sound though.
What do you want?
Here, say it again.
Guys, when it comes to weather, I hate hot weather.
Oh, that's that's a fine by me. Yeah, yeah, that kind of sound
you know. I can't even say the word, but it reminds me of a certain
body part doing a certain
something is all I have to say to that. You can't say
I'm thinking wait. Yeah, this is what it would sound like if you
that's a guy getting one. Yeah, yeah, and by the way, if you're at home
thinking that I'm thinking of something dirty. I'm thinking of somebody
raising their hand. This is what yeah what this is what mine sounds like when
mine does the thing we're talking about. It sounds like this
that's when it was at all everything. So I'm going to hit the toilet water.
Yeah, when it hits the toilet water, what's that you never had that happen?
Oh, that never happened to you. Yeah, wait, he doesn't hit the toilet water.
When he why are you getting one on the toilet? You hate when you're you're
getting I can't say no. I'm not I say the anatomical working down. Okay,
you're looking down into the toilet. Have you ever tried to don't you hate when
you're and you're getting a one you're pulling down your pants, your trousers
to go number two, so you can say number two. Why did you say? Why did you say
trousers like pants was a cuss because pants can be a cuss come on let me quit
don't you and you can sag your pants. Nobody's sagging their trousers in the
UK. It's pants is underwear exactly yeah, so
my bad, my trousers, his pants, my bed. So if you say if you say I'm wearing,
I'm going to wear pants outside. The British will say, Are you daft? Yeah,
put daft on the list. Please. We're not allowed to say that. Okay, you can say,
but don't you hate when you pull your trousers down to go number two and your
testes get itchy from the bath mat? Yes, yes, I do hate that. I don't like that.
I quite hate that. Yeah, yeah, I don't test it because I got my
whole house. Every pretty much all of this stuff in there is all this like
it's all loofah material. So when it does, when my testes touch the loofah
material on the ground... Your whole house is loofah? Pretty much.
Really? Pretty much everything. I was at his house for the first time the
other day, I can confirm. The whole thing is loofah. It's mostly loofah.
My girlfriend put... Did you guys know that loofah is a plant? Yeah.
That's pretty cool.
What? You're lucky I can't curse right now. Why is that? 'Cause I was
attacked on this program
foretelling you that
Yeah, nobody cares
Hey, here's a whole bag of quarters dimes nickels and pennies go call somebody gives a crud fatality
Yeah, that's right and go ahead and give me the high voice real quickly
Hey, yeah, I'm gonna do this again. Hey, yeah
Yeah, I'd like to get one to get to a page a 13 movie please and I'd like to sit in the front row
One ticket to Welcome to Bootsport.
I'd like to get a great romano.
One ticket to Welcome to Marwen, please.
I'd like to get...
Yeah, one ticket to Boy in the Striped Pajamas, please.
One ticket to... I'd like one ticket to Melancholia, please.
Yes, please.
Um, uh, excuse me.
Hello. Um, can I get three... I mean, uh, one ticket to, uh, Philomena?
Yeah, one ticket to Leon the Professional.
I'd like to get one ticket to Leon the Professional.
Um, yeah.
My mom said that I can buy Sunset Overdrive.
Yeah.
I'll write one DVD copy of A History of Violence, please.
Do you have a Blu-ray of Brown Bunny?
That's what I want. Yeah. And Modern Warfare 2.
That is funny though.
It's still funny.
High voice. I'm not sure.
You just make your voice really high and ask for a DVD.
Yeah, it's basically.
you put my put my voice up again.
Can I get
can I get one
copy of the movie Michael
the angel one the angel angel one. I got in trouble for that. Yeah, I'm a
movie because Michael because it was PG thirteen. Yeah,
no, no, is because it's blasphemous
because it's an angel that acts like a fucking
gosh darn it. You are an angel that acts like an a hole like I'm acting today.
Yeah, with my cussing, do I really I gotta say I did not anticipate me being
the potty mouth of the group. You really there pretty. I was going to be the
thought that you were going to be the one who was constantly. I thought I was
going to come in here. I will say F and S and S. My I completely unconsciously
let slip some some Fs on the last episode and nobody even noticed. I guess
I'm kind of like a stealth cusser, because you you are maybe me and him
just kind of tune out any time you talk. Yeah, that might be
so he's like
it's like what it's like what the you guys didn't grow up in Christianity,
but there's a lot of people in Christianity who would they do like they
just do like the like they mouth the word. Yeah, I had a
Mormon friend who did who did that, but he didn't mouth that he would he would
make like a make this noise you go like I can't even do it. You know
that no go what the
me and my buddies and this is not on the list or you're on the list. I can say
it me and my buddy Liam. We used to say him write it down. We used to say
can't talk about we put him on the list. Fock Fock, meet the Focker's the
Focker's and we started saying Fock that movie yeah yeah name was gay Lord
a locker. What a name, I know a name who came up with what kind of sick. When I
turned on that movie and I heard that name, I was like okay, so this movie
must be fiction. Yeah, these days they there's no way there's no way this
really happened. He would probably be named
gender swapper today. Yeah, yeah, actually, I know someone who has
something to say about that. Who's that
to the pot? Sorry? Yeah,
way woke but
wait our new our new recurring character,
oh my God, wait, why three one thousand
that's how many that's how many genders
oh my God woke by wow wow you are you are really something yeah, so woke but
tell us about
what do we ask about about I guess we ask what yes
Okay, well, we didn't ask you about that.
Is surfing SJW? No,
it's just something in my personality. You just like surfing. That's interesting.
You're an SJW that has personality. That's a first. Yeah, wait. And I have
blue hair. You have no hair. You're a robot. I am a robot with blue hair
installed into my brain. It's in your brain. The hair is in my brain, yeah,
'cause I'm an SJW. Holy crap. Yeah.
All right, make us say I don't like any more. You don't like you didn't even do
the first here. So what was the ask woke by ask here? I'll be woke by now. Okay,
so ask her yes or no question.
I thought you
bought. Do you think that Joe Biden's the best president ever
affirmative action yeah. That was the one that I did yep woke, but I can't
believe I forgot my own joke guys. It's been eleven minutes. We already did all
the characters that we've had planned. Don't worry guys. We will have other
characters.
We're at this episode is going to be called USA Network. Yeah, there was one
more character. I do now yes, okay, I'm going to do as I just get them all.
I'm over yeah,
- Wait, wait, who's that?
- It's your girlfriend.
- Wait, baby, what are you doing here?
Baby, what are you doing here?
Baby, get, I can't.
I'm at work right now.
What?
What, don't just say ooh.
I hate when you do this.
Hi, hi, hi.
What are you, you sound like a ghost.
Stop.
You are making me really horny while I'm at work.
Don't teehee me. Don't teehee me. Don't weeheehee me. Stop. No.
This ends right now. We're breaking up.
Whoa.
You don't like breakups?
No, we're breaking up. I never want to see you again. Get out of here.
You're not my girlfriend now.
Okay. So I break up with you and you immediately go to my fucking best friend
I try to or my
oh my God, you make me that was all
the character stuff. It's all traps to make you lose my every character has
made you swear. Yep, that's because I'm an actor okay, and I'm an amazing actor
at that
dude. This is my last dollar and I'm down to my last dollar over that. See
you, I can loan you back the money. If you need a McGraw saying that I'm going
try not to need you to sign a form, though, if you we literally you need to
start selling Cameron. Yeah, we should just make a separate bank account for
the swear jar. We should make a new LLC called swear jar limited
and we use it. We're laundering money. It's a yeah. It's like a charity. Yeah,
thing and all it does is it makes us there's still a bunch of yerba mate all
over the swear jar. Who cares? Just keep I do. The table is gonna leak.
the table's going to leave. You are so smart because I can't say the I word
yeah. We do need to figure out what we're doing with this money. Yeah, yeah,
I don't. We talked about an anti swearing charity. We don't I really
don't want to give it to anybody. No hobo,
nobody who doesn't work. I don't think that we need to give it to a hard
worker who is
who does never sweared. You know, I do our betters. We should give it to like
like a millionaire because they'll probably double it, but millionaires
double it and give it to yeah the next person. Well, no wait. That's per we
need to give it to an entrepreneur. We need to give it to a millionaire or a
billionaire who's going to invest. You know what, but I just want to say a lot
of millionaires are kind of they collect a swear behind the scenes. The swear
jar, an iron man, the swear jar is going to go to buying us twitter blue
the podcast. No yeah,
yeah,
that I know
that's funny. That's a funny idea. You think that's getting verified? You think
that's really that funny? It's funny. Yeah, and you know what else we should
buy with it? Hulu.
That's actually a good idea. Yeah, that is actually don't have Hulu right now,
though. Yeah, Cameron doesn't have Hulu really between Hulu. So maybe
we should do Hulu. Yeah, no, I don't want Hulu and I don't want Max. I'll
tell you what
stop naming your crap after a day name after my day is allowed after my day
classmates names. Stop that I don't see crap on the list anywhere. I think I up
as a yeah, I say crap yeah all right. I think we can all say crap. Oh, I know
where it is.
That's a different see you am
oh yeah, that is actually what that is. Oh wait, but they're both they both are
obviously we can't say yeah
wait you did you added Falk
sexual. I actually was I was wondering maybe we can have a little panel here on
what we think about this. How do we feel about explicit violence? Oh, that's fine
and ripping the shreds, violence, you mean like wait, dripping to shreds
discussions. That's fine yeah, it's no cussing it, but we also have like
meanness and we're going on TV. Well, but that's a tree, but like so if I say
I want to rip off Taylor Swift's head yeah that so that's sayable. You can say
that okay, but you can't say on a rip it off and take a dump in her mouth. Take
it s
is okay, because yeah, because that's a lot or or you don't want to say to say
oh, I'm going to get so high and then rip her head off right and then use your
head as a bong. Yeah, you can't say that I'm going to use your whole body like a
bomb. It's going to be one big grav bomb. I'm a smoker s out of I'm going to use
her like a car, but the grommet is in the belly button. What's a grommet the
thing that you pull the that's called a grommet where marijuana
Oh, I didn't know that. I thought it was called a pen.
I don't know.
Oh, okay.
You're not a big smoker.
I don't like weed at all.
He got me a Willy Wonka marijuana bar the other day.
Yeah, for your bachelor party. I thought you were going to take a bite out of it and then
go home.
What? I haven't smoked weed in weeks. I'm off weed.
I didn't know that.
I don't like weed anymore.
Then who's... I spent like $45 on that.
Yeah, I don't know why you did that.
$45? That was $45?
$45 chocolate bar.
It was a bachelor party gift.
the bachelor party. You know what I would have liked is an actual forty five
dollars.
Actually, forty five dollars. I borrow a life changing fire. Well, it was a
three hundred milligram edible. Yeah, which I bought because that's gonna I
bought it because I knew that it would scare you. It is. I'm like scared to
have it in my house. I feel like I have a gun in my house. Yeah, yeah, I feel
like I need to put it in a thumb safe. Well, we're also especially right
before the summer. It's gonna melt and go into the air. Yeah, that's what I'm
really worried about it. It's aerating it. Yeah. Well, it's you know what flavor it
is, right? Chocolate 100 grand
is a chocolate bar. Yeah, but it tastes exactly like a 100 grand. I don't think
okay, if it tastes exactly like it, then eat the whole thing and give me a review.
300 milligrams of weed would actually I would actually be in a mental
institution. If I ate that whole thing, I'm not kidding. I would be 100%. I would
be catatonically vegetative. Yeah, yeah, that's why I bought it. I'd rather eat
vegetables. Yeah, I would rather I'd rather eat greens. No weed. I'd rather
eat metal than eat a three hundred milligram. I would rather eat like a lead
of you. I thought that you were taking edibles and then going to sleep. No, I
bought that for you and that I bought that for you. So every night you can
take a little nibble like you're a rabbit. I stopped doing that because I
had scary dreams. Yeah, I had scary dreams where I was every night. My dog
was dying. Crazy dream. What's been happening? I've been having just like I
I don't know why, but all my dreams have become very vivid.
I used to not dream that much at all.
Yeah. And now every single dream that I have, I wake up and I'm like,
Oh my God, I just lived in another universe.
Really? You're doing full Salvia style.
Yeah. I woke up,
I woke up and I thought that I went to a town called Doran, Texas.
And I was walking around telling people like, you know, that's my last name.
Right.
Wait, that's actually so sick.
I went when I was look like you know, no one looked like when I was a kid. I
went to town Cameron Montana. No, I got a picture next to the sign. Wow. I've
been having a really crazy issue recently. You know what a dream I had
with my name. I just want to say one one more dream. My head went back in
time and I had my phone. I went back in time through my phone somehow and I
went to the recording studio where Genesis was recording misunderstanding
and they were like, we don't want to put this song out. It's not good.
and I had to show Phil Collins the Wikipedia page for the album Duke,
and I was like, dude, you need to you need to do this. That is actually
good. That is actually the worst and most boring dream I've ever heard in
my life. That's not bad at all. What are you talking about? I cannot
believe that that's the kind of thing your subconscious dreams up. What do
you mean? It's like an episode of TV. That is insane.
How is that bad? That's cool. I got to meet Phil Collins. I had a dream
got a demonic centipede. Yeah, all of my stuff is like I have a dog's head and
nobody notices except my my mom like that kind of stuff. I straight up it's
like sicko re aster type stuff that I'm doing yeah in my dreams. When you're
over there, I'm having I'm having dreams where I go to different you're having
literal dreams like your dreams are coming true. Yeah, yeah, I mean you're
like all of my dreams are nightmare that that Chris Griffin video we made. I told
that was a dream. That was a dream. Yeah, it's all just dream like this is my
dream. Yeah, yeah, I have I write it in my notes app. I wake up my my girlfriend
heard me the other day when I was saying that one into my phone the the Phil
Collins one. She was in the living room and I woke she heard me wake up go like
and then I held my Siri button and I went Siri notes app Siri notes app. I
I went back in time to Phil Collins and now yeah, she had came in the other
room. She's like who are you on the phone with? Who are you calling Siri on
the phone? Who are you on the phone with talking? No, who is Siri? Who is
this? Who is this bitch?
Wow, that was so he knows that he can 'cause he is using coin. Yeah,
it's like that's what I mean. Like he can literally say whatever he wants.
Yeah, it's so annoying and he misses every single time. That was like 30
because I'm in the middle. Just get a dollar. How hard is it to bring dollars?
I have one dollar. Okay, all right. We'll say you better save it and you better
use it. Good. Okay, because
you missed,
but it was worth it.
And you're not by the way you are not at when we stop recording. You're not
going and getting that dollar. It is going. No, I know it's going in there.
Okay. This is for real. This is money goes to the all money goes to the jar.
this is not for can look how full this jar are yeah. I know we're gonna need
okay, that's pretty that's kind of me me yeah, that's a bit of a me me. Oh my God,
look at this. What do you have? Do you have a loony? I have a nut in here. See
that is like that is just so clear that that you don't even think of that bag as
having money. Yeah, it's not exactly. I literally was going to say that we're
like that's money that you've already you've already sacrificed. Yeah, that is
junk coming. This is my this is my laundry money. That's like that money
is your son who went to the laundromat. That money is your son who went to a
way to war and you just have to assume he's dead. Yeah, until you figure out
you can use a coin star and bring him back to life. That could be a dream
that I have. Did you guys ever do coin star growing up? Yeah, I did it a
lot. We would save all year and then put it in the coin star and we always
thought it was going to be like five hundred dollars and it was always like
forty dollars yeah yeah. I did it by hand. I would count out my oh you
rolled it yeah. We did that a couple of times. You roll your own yeah. I roll
my own. That was so it's so annoying when you have a bunch of them yeah. I
thought it was fun. I was a little yeah. God, I would I used to when I when we
were in Boston, I still think it's fun to count coins. You are just so do
little stacks of four quarters something wrong when you hold it in your fingers
like this and you move it back. That's what you think about is a holding it.
it's nice. What do you know what I was doing with that money when I was a kid,
putting it in my mouth, and I was tasting every as well. I was also doing
that. And that was the best. I think we were three coin tasters. Pennies taste
better than quarters. I think we would have been able to reach across the aisle
of being annoyed by each other and realize that we're all coin tasters.
You should have seen me... I really, really, like when I was younger, I
really liked the taste of pennies. I really liked copper. Coins tasted good
back then. That's why all my pans... I loved all metal. All my pans are
copper. You guys should have seen me at the water fountains. Did I was doing
full like Lana Rhoads on the fucking thing of the water fountain, just sucking
it in.
I have no dollars and you mentioned Lana Rhoads. That's okay. She's a woman
okay. Sexual in nature, please, please give me that dollar, but I put my entire
mouth on the water fountain thing every single time and I would just
the the the the the point out. Oh, the spout of the water, the bubble. He's
talking about the bubbler, the bubble, I'll put it my mouth on the bubbler and
I would suck it like a nipple, because when I hear water fountain and in the
context of coins, I'm imagining a wishing well. I'm a man really that
serious about bubbler. I
it's not no, it doesn't it's I don't I don't know like when I hear water
fountain, I'm not thinking of the button that you push. What what this is? This
is not our dollar. What is it? This belongs to Tristan. Oh my God, oh mate
come in on the it says Tristan right there. This isn't ours to give. We need
to find Tristan. Oh my God, that's who all the money goes to is Tristan. If
you're out there, hit us up, hit us up and claim the this dollar other things
that I would eat when I was a kid. I would eat mud pencils mud, but oh, I
would chew on pencils for sure. Oh, I do the I would choose my living heck out
of a all of the die out of my sweatshirt sleeves. Yeah, I would suck on my
sweatshirt. So yeah, I would my grandmother told me that a kid died from
sucking on his sweatshirt sleeves because it made a ball of dye in his stomach
that they had to cut him open and get it out, and it was so big it filled his
stomach. I couldn't eat anything. I do believe that. That happens to dogs.
When my cousin would get stressed out at a movie, he would suck on his T-shirt.
Yeah, that's basically what I would do. Yeah, I would do T-shirt collars,
jacket sleeves, sweatshirt sleeves. Oh, the... In a hoodie, the string in a
hoodie. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Put that in your dang mouth. Oh, my God, all the
way down the throat. Yeah, exactly. Yeah. I would suck on chocolate chips as
the kid yeah, I would look on lollipop
jawbreakers. I'd have a big jawbreaker hanging out of the side of my mouth.
Basically, it was so that rancher not really jolly rancher and aid candy. No,
I will. I remember really do
band aid. There's a
that looked like band aids.
No, it was like you ate you ate band aids. I did not eat band. You ate a
look. There's been gummy aid. Whoa! Oh, there was that's. Well,
so that's when that's when parents complained about candy cigarettes and
they're like well, we're making the boxes. Yeah,
yeah, we already have it. We already have the factory to make boxes that look
like things
we can just switch it. A strange switch from cigarette
to lever. There's only two sides. If you leave that lever in the middle,
it's going to look crazy. I
really was not a huge candy man growing up, but I liked can deal. I me and my
friends
had basically an ed ed and eddy routine where we would literally go through the
entire school day trying to find coins in some way or another, and then we'd
stop at the corner store on the way home when walking from school and we get
candy. There's a be like, yes, I have twenty five cents a day. I could get
lemon heads really annoying, simpler time lemon, beautiful. Why did we like
lemon head? I liked the what do you tell it about? Cherry heads get me
I loved Lemonhead. I loved Lemonhead. I talked about it before. I liked the Lemonhead character design.
I was like, there should be a TV show of them. Yeah, we did talk about that before.
There's this really annoying kid in my class named Kyle and he went on a rant to the teacher one day.
He was like, I went to the penny candy store. There was like, it was like one of the last
surviving penny candy stores in the country and I went there and guess what? Because of
Massachusetts taxes, the candy was fifty one cents. It's a penny candy store. A
kid should never be saying the phrase one of the last surviving. That's how
you know a kid needs to be smacked around. That kid was annoyed out of and
he would sing that Comcast song.
What's the Comcast? It was like C. O. M. C. A. S. T. Now I did a really
monotone. I don't know it. I wish I wish now that I heard it. I wish now that I
I had a lot more. Yeah, there's a lot of those sicko nerds grew up and you were
doing that stuff. You were home schooled.
So how are you gonna always home schooled? I had I got plenty of bullying
in and middle school. Yeah, yeah, you're making life hell for some Christian
ruined probably thirty full lives. Yeah, when I was a child, yeah, thirty full
lives and I and forever, you know, but some of them escaped and some of them
had pretty decent lives after. And so what I wish that I'd done is gone when
when they found out when they before school shooting yeah. So I had no fear
now. This is after I had no I was a real is a taller than you. I'm gonna. I
will when you when they found out that you were getting home schooled yeah. It
was like
the end of Return of the Jedi. It was like the end of World War Two. Yeah,
yeah, everyone's all dancing. It was me dying in a bunker by myself and they
were like, Oh, my God,
we
I had the realization like literally probably a couple of weeks ago yeah
that all along I thought I was a nerd. You were a I was a bully yeah, yeah, I
was just
everybody grows. I was the I was the bully who bullied all the people who
were more nerdy than me yeah, well, just you realize that you were just like
kids are just so because every once in a while, like what have every once in a
while I'll just be like oh yeah, I'll be telling some story about high school,
and be like oh yeah, this kid that we all used to like torture and make
like put finally put it all together. I was like wait. Well, that's what the
whole thing is. I don't have like what is it? There's not none of those kids
were nice. Yeah, all of those kids had one kid. There probably was one kid at
the very bottom and yeah, you had one. We got
yeah, but then we had a few and but if it was today, you would not be able to
bully. No yeah,
literally I think yeah, it's completely true. There's some of this some of the
stuff that other people did that I was not part of was like like a hundred
percent would really it would be what did they do? People would freak out
about it. There were they like made there were these kids who made like a
fake
when you remember Google Plus. They made a fake Google Plus profile for this
kid
and they and they already they were they posted the craziest shit on there and
they dollar
gosh darn it.
they posted a bunch of just talking about ruining a kid's life and still
putting a
well. This is
this was middle.
Google first came out, this was when everyone was on it. I did not know a
single person. You were whack. They all the cool kids, exactly the cool kids
are on Google plus it was so bad. It was it was like bad to the level of like
there was a whole there was like an administrative thing in the school.
Oh man, they like remember any of the posts yeah they posted. I'm trying to
remember. I feel like they probably
I can't remember anything word for word, but the thing I remember that really got
them in trouble is they started posting a bunch of P O R N O G R A P H Y with
captions like I love this.
There was a
P O R N O R. No, actually it wasn't. It was it was really fun. It was just
normal. It was yeah, the kid, though he yeah he didn't deserve that there were
did he ever these kids at my school that were making fake Facebook pages of
teachers in the school. They were like they were
they all impersonated our gym teacher, Mr. Noon, and all the posts are like I'm
going on a run
and stuff like that.
I'm doing pull ups, I'm doing monkey bars.
and they fed they like I guess they like took a picture of him in school and
then like oh man, he was kind of like an agro dude and like
found out about that and was livid and all those kids got suspended for do
you ever see the videos just to give context to about this innocent this kid
that they were torturing Google plus this like the main thing I remember
about this kid is that he was it was probably like seventh or eighth grade
and he like every day would read the graphic novel of the Bible. Oh wow! I
know that
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I
do remember I did get in a fist fight about atheism versus Christianity when I
was
yeah, because my friend Jesse said which side were you on to
come on. You know that I was a straight crusader warrior for God, yeah, and I
lost pretty bad, about a foot taller than me and
basically I said that his mom was going to hell and he got really mad and I was
like who gives a crap you don't even believe in hell yeah exactly. Why would
he care? Yeah here came out old righty and lefty yeah. I threw the first punch
and I immediately got you through the first punch. Wow yeah dude, that's the
Christian code to say your mom is going to a t double hockey sticks and then
punch him well because we were talking about abortion. Oh, so that wasn't the
first thing, you know it's started with a portion. It's really cool that when
you were like eleven or whatever you were like
I need to I need to talk about I was a culture warrior. So
here's the things these are things that did not play about okay
abortion,
the United States debt. Yes,
marijuana laws. I didn't want marijuana legalized because I did even as a child.
I knew that that was just wrong. Yeah, I saw super high me when I was in
freshman year of high school, and I was like we need to make this s h i t
legal yeah and and also I did not like cussing yeah. I did not like cussing
until I lost my faith. Yeah, but the entire time that I was a faithful
Christian, I did not want to remember. I thought a lot of humor was disgusting.
It is until I was twenty three. It still makes me want to vomit. Yeah, I
don't know why we've been doing. I mean I'm glad that it's it ends today. It's
over. I just remembered. I just remembered also the the reason they got
a lot of trouble is that they had, along with Mr. Noon, was like a network of other teachers.
So they were all just impersonating the teachers.
Wow.
They had a whole fake Facebook.
They had a whole fake Facebook thing.
That's crazy.
And it was Mr. Noon and Mrs. Harmon, who was the home ec teacher.
What a perfect name.
And all the most...
Was she beautiful?
No.
She was an old German woman.
We had a lady named Mrs. Lovejoy.
Mrs. Lovejoy.
Wow.
his Harman's Facebook. I remember he's remember how you could have usernames
hers was it was
the username they got for her was wooden spoon,
because she's the she's like the cooking teacher. You did not
you did not go to school very creative children. No, no, they were not very
funny that what he that is so funny idea is funny, but when you said that they
went on the P teacher's thing and said I'm going for a run.
that is funny. That is really funny. Yeah, that is really funny because that's
the only
he's who you think is looping and jumping rope all day.
Do you guys think you could have been teachers? No, no, no, but you maybe I
don't know. I wouldn't want to be. I don't think I was a teacher and you if
you have it. If you grow up with a teacher in your life, yes, there is
miserable all the time. It doesn't I don't understand how you could ever want
to be a teacher. Sounds I agree, even if you're just a kid in a teacher's class,
yeah, can you look at that's that that you know what that is that's you have
some kind of malfunction in your brain where you're like you know what someday
I want to have power over this for a future version child. There's so many
there's so many teachers that like
you can tell like, okay, you got into this profession like you they hang out
with like all the cool kids in school and it's like, oh, you got into this
profession because if you care, you were trying to continue your popularity or
you weren't popular and now you want to be if you care like a little enough
about money or and stress to become a teacher, there's something wrong with you.
You should become instead a monk, yeah, that'd be a much or a police officer or
a monkey or a police officer or a human or a specially ops agent like green
race style yeah, but I also think that this the being a teacher so hard
because you spend all of this time with these kids that just completely stink.
I'm not going to say that, but they stink and then you finally find one
that is like really, really good honor student, really curious kid and they
always get hit by a stray bullet or die in a driving accident yeah, and then
you know it just happens every four years. The but they do get a page in the
yearbook, so it's all worth it. Well, but then yeah, then you then like every
four years, you're just you're just going. What was a quote I had about the
kid four years ago got hit in the head by
got attacked by a hawk and then you're just copying and pasting that under
black and white photo. You know what the bit one of the biggest like Shane like
I'm thinking about like the cool art teacher like when you're in school and
think about the cool art teacher and I think back to like the cool art teacher
and like that's not right. I told you guys about right evil to be
high school art teacher, right? Yeah, yeah, the guy the guy that was in
like a
web series where he's a vampire hunter. If you're talking, if you're talking
to the kids about magic, the gathering or your you're you're bringing in
guitar hero,
and you're allowed to go outside and smoke, you bring in guitar hero,
Metallica on the day before Christmas break and you make the whole class
watch you get. That's actually a master of that. That's cool. One hundred
percent. That's a cool. That is that's that's what that's what my art teacher
seventh grade Mr. Stumpf did. And you're like, this guy's really cool. He liked
tool. He would come in wearing tool t-shirts all the time. This is not
something like the cool art teacher. I'm talking about the art teacher. He was
ripped. He was handsome too. He started to sound cool to me. Wait, I've seen a
picture of this guy. He was ripped. I showed you his vampire web series. No,
you just showed me a picture of him. Oh yeah. And he was shredded. Fourteen year
Neil Patrick seeing a guy played guitar here. I'm talking about a vampire.
I was twelve. This is the coolest guy. I will do it. Yeah, he was like every
single mom in the in the PTA was like and that Mr. Stumpf,
they all wanted to. They all wanted to well here. I l him. The art teachers are
all the art teachers are that is a there should not be an art class in school.
No, there should
but it should be taught by a robot. Yes, or the kids, the kids should be
teaching. It should be taught by one. Yeah,
there should not be art. There should not be English. It should only be
it's only be math taxes. How to meet your spouse? Yeah,
yeah, we're dancing class. Wait, if the kids design the curriculum where the
kids, by the way,
we got to do eight classes. Yeah, I know we've done this before, but I think
we did our individual ones. What are we actually if we if they put us on the
board of the New York State School, like school board first time to read versus
taxes, how to do your taxes, you don't need that there's turn. No, yeah, how to
do your taxes, plus how to how to tip at restaurants. No,
no, how to treat servers with respect. No, I'm not even looking at you. No, no,
no, that you think that's right, but put a book on
the world, but would not be involved by the way you're getting. You're getting
five words of what this is. This is an impression of the current New York
State. Okay, go ahead.
We're going to teach a class on how to draw Steven Universe.
Okay, you use your woke by words very well. Yeah, that was good. That was good,
but yeah, that's basically what it is right now. It's how to draw Steven
Universe. Yeah, it should be how to draw cable. Yeah, how to how to swallow,
how to draw, how to draw,
yeah, how to have it, how to get it down,
how to eat sushi, how to tolerate
yeah, how to have allergies. It's all that kind of stuff,
but we would get in and we're doing how to draw taught by Rob Lee field. You
walk in
yeah, you walk in first thing you're given is a guy and you are going to
start rolling Brazilian Jiu Jitsu three hours. Martial Arts Brazilian Jiu Jitsu
Gracie, it's the Gracie school. Well, I would like to expand it to and then two
hours of lunch. I would like to expand it to maybe Jiu Jitsu and then also include
the fighting styles from Mortal Kombat, where they use weapons like how like a
Mortal Kombat. Sometimes it's like okay, this guy can fight karate, but then he
also takes out like a ton for
or something Katana fighting in gun Kata. Yeah, gun Kata in one hour blocks for
three hours. Then we're breaking for lunch or first two hours, two hours, two
two hours to lunch bison white rice broccoli. Yeah, that's it. That's it.
Every single kid gets that. I don't get I don't give a and for
ghost. No, then you take your C four instead of milk. It's ghost energy or C
four. Yeah, that's chocolate. Kids are trading. Oh, I have I have crush berry
and no
Pokemon cards in the lunchroom. Baseball cards only. Yeah, it's cards and
ninjas, American baseball cards, American baseball cards, none of these because
jujitsu and katana fighting and gun kata that's in a foreign stuff. We have our
own trading cards of like rich piana and like
like any other buff guy, cutler and sage north cut yeah. All these people next
class ronda rousey. This is coming back for this coming out from back from lunch
nice and nice and full yeah after that is our hero. Then we're doing it because
your brain is so primed right because well, honestly, honestly, do you know
what it is? What it's the exact opposite? It's because you are going to face such
adversity and try every suggestion you try to give. You're going to say
chicken wing, yeah, which is what pizza, because that's what improv thinking
about food, because you're full, because that's what happens when you're full.
It's basically it's called trial by fire. Yeah, it's boot camp. Yeah, and then
after that is a hero. And then, by the way, there is a full hell week. Yeah,
let's go the first week when you would normally go to like a team building
summer camp. We're making you swim into the Pacific Ocean. Yeah, and this is a
school on the East Coast. It's
none of this West Coast BS. No, no, no, we're going to make you swim into the
cold waters of San Diego in the middle of November. We have, we have a weather,
we have weather, weather, weather, altering devices, so you can do a polar
plunge any time of year. That's right. We will make sure that we do a polar
plunge on July and then and then fifteen and you're in school on July. Fourth
you're in school every day around three sixty five and then comes the circuit
training crossfit circus training circus training where we're going to have you
bouncing a ball on your nose like a seal, but none of the human parts of the
circus you're all doing all the all the human parts are going to be taken over
by a soon. Anyway, right, we need new animals yeah, okay, so we're going to
have you. We need Andrew to be doing a seal thing you're going to be doing the
elephant stuff. We're gonna be feeding you peanuts yep, you're going to be
you can't even have peanuts in school. We're going to change that a peanut.
We're going to do a
diet peanut in a cafeteria is way worse than an active shooter. Now it is
a hundred percent, and if you're wondering where your money for tuition
is going, because I know it's a lot. Yeah, it's a big number.
Almost ninety nine percent of that money is going to hire the most talented
ringleader in the entire world. Yeah, Mr. Amazo and if you're going to yes,
and if you're complaining about books, if you want to complain about, I didn't
know about this guy. Yeah, this is a big problem. Like what is Mr. Amazo look
like? He has big swirl as big swirly eyes and a sinister smile as well as a
purple skin tight outfit and a cape and who and compression shorts
because he's
yeah, big a combat boot. He's yeah, those shoes are big. That's why he's got to
wear those compression shorts. So you can't see his thing and if by the way
guys. I know a big problem right now is book cost. The cost of books.
Luckily, guess what? One single book, People's History United States. That's
all one copy, one copy because ain't nobody reading that whole damn thing
about a whole D thing. Yeah,
yeah, thank you. Sorry, guys, and there's no swearing in the school
yeah, except casual Fridays. Yeah, where you can let loose and say whatever casual
Friday schedule is guitar hero all day or you're obsessed with guitar. You're
I'm
video games. What games are banned in this school
and you band when you get home to what about counter strike and Valorant and
all this kind of
aim. Can I talk a little? I know we're not at the end of the day, but I want
to talk a little bit about how the transport system works. You go to and
from school. I'd like to explain this to you guys. There's a tube. Yes. So
there's a tube that you hop in at the end of the day, and it takes you to
what you might think is your home. Yes, it looks exactly like your home. Your
mom seems to be there. Your dad seems to be there. Your little brother's there.
They're acting a little weird, a little mechanical, but they seem to be there.
That's right. You will never be truly home. We've constructed one to one
replicas of every student's home to make sure we can completely control their
environment, make sure their homework is getting done, make sure that they are
doing their sleep cycle. Mom has a belt that has a cattle prod attached to it.
we have a don't do your homework. Mom's going to your that's right. We replace
mom with M O M and D A D. Yeah, an acti key New York style, simulatory reality.
Yeah, you are going to be walking around. We're going to have people playing you
who are playing somebody else. You're going to see yourself when you get
yeah,
the actor playing you, the robots don't know that it's training and then also
every day when you get home, you have to battle. You have to battle to keep your
spot in the family against yourself. Yeah, if you don't do well at school that
day. Yes, who's going to school for you? Your clone, your
no, not a clone. Yes, where and guess where you are watching.
You are watching from the chamber and you all know what the chamber looks
like. Guess what happens if you if you're if your robot clone goes to
school and you get sent away. Guess where you're getting sent. That's right
outer space. Yeah, I know that sounds maybe cool and fun. Oh, I got to go
to a space station, but no. Have you ever seen Star Wars? Yeah, trash scene.
That's what's happening. You're going to the trash room and there's no cool
monster there to admire? No. And if and we do, why would you even admire that?
Well, let's talk about corporal punishment. Okay, because corporal
punishment is less... We don't believe in that here. No, we believe in it to
the maximum. Have you ever seen... No, no, no, no, 'cause there's no such
thing as corporal punishment, it's called tough love. We believe in... That's
right.
That is right. We believe in incorporeal punishment, where we have a room that
we have confirmed is haunted, and if you misbehave, we send you in there,
and ethereal spirits will come down and possess your body and... And they will
actually torture you until the day they will edge you yeah
they'll force you to
for hours. It's torturous. You don't want to go there. This is in a middle
school. This is a college. That's why the sexual it's a middle. Well, no,
they're ghosts. They're not good people. Yeah, okay, it goes probably go
somewhere wandering. The earth goes happen to do yeah exactly and
the guess who else is there the residency and your dice clay
okay, resume clean material, he's doing a clean material, but he is teaching
gory gory dot the mouse went up the clock. Yeah,
and we have hired the
school lady from Matilda and she will be putting you
trunchbull, this trunchbull will be putting you into a iron maiden. It's
the chokey. We've actually upgraded the chokey. It's now fully vr yeah.
The Chokey is a sensory deprivation tank. By the way, after
after deprivation tank, so you think because you have VR goggles on yeah, so
all you see is like you hear like the drips of water and you see it's
completely dark until out of nowhere, just like a faceless like Xenomorph
looking like the
half human Xenomorph comes up, runs at you and just goes
we also have a there's another VR version of the Chokey right where you
put on the you don't. So in this situation, you don't know you're being
dishonest yet. Okay, like okay, we don't usually have any games. You want to
play a video game? Yeah, you're like okay, yeah, I guess I'm getting rewarded.
You put on the VR headset. It's Mario. Yeah, you're in Mario one and you're
like, oh, I know what to do here. I walk forward and I jump. You walk forward.
Yeah, you're in the chokie. You jump. Yeah, you've been in the chokie all
along. You think you might be on a treadmill or in a wide open field? No,
you're in a room filled with glass and nails and you jump. You're going to get
like a bit of a haircut and also you are a Goomba.
Oh my God, the world
you're like, oh no, Goomba, I'm scared you take off the VR goggles. The Goomba
was not VR. I know there's a real
eyes. Yeah, we put a real Goomba in the school. We have a Goomba that we
created through science and it escaped the science lab. Yeah, it was a person
before we
a person. We've heard one of the kids into a goomba really bad like like
tusk. It was like a man and then we put him in a box that was shaped like a
goomba. We should do that movie, but about a guy who's obsessed
and he turns just along into a that's way better. That's a way better idea
for a movie that is, but then also after crossfit training, there is a
sensory deprivation tank and we will play
crimson and clover over and over and over again. After the sensory deprivation
tank. There's a sensory overload tank where it stimulates all your senses at
once for an hour straight. We basically put you into an episode of Johnny
Tess. It tickles you and it pumps flavors into your mouth and it puts
cells into your nose and it smells. There's like a sweet and sour back and
forth. It smells a thousand times. You're going through, it is like you're
going through the E.T. Ride at Universal at five times speed over and over
again. And it has, the flavors are, it's a Gatling gun that just alternates
like sweet, sour, umami. But it's also, yeah, it has, well, it also, it has
AI in there, so it can tell when you're getting, if you get too used to
the cycle, you're getting a little desensitized. Okay, now bitter, yes,
throw better in there. Yeah, bitter toothpaste, salty, yes, salt.
Basically, it's
what
into your mouth.
Yeah, yeah, and then, yes, it was created by
aperture of science for for your ears. It's probably playing some messed up
noise sound like Jesus. Yeah, yeah, playing some death metal, like ghost or
like on this side on this year, it's goes day to remember on this year. It's a
classic backer. Act Bert backer act. Do you know the way to say
that's right? The machine story. That's on the other. There's a cochlear implant
on the back. Also, for your eyes, it's playing the machine movie.
And it's and it the machine movie. It has the commentary track done by Mark
Hamill and he's doing it in the Joker's voice. I just have a really good if
if they were going to reboot the twilight zone, okay, you go you're going to a
movie theater, you say to me that it's got a machine
you go to the movie theater to see the machine. Yeah, you sit down, it starts
playing, you're like it's playing oddly slowly. It seems like it's playing a
point a one percent speed and it's going so slow. I better leave this is going to
take too long to watch you go to leave. The doors are locked. Whoa! You have to
watch the whole thing at very slowly
exactly
you guys kind of feel pissed off that they never asked us to write on that
movie. Yeah, I do well. They asked me and I turned it down because they didn't
ask you guys. That's really
we wrote that on the show two years ago. We wrote the machine. I mean we saw okay,
so we wrote a different for people who don't know. We wrote about an inventor.
We wrote the machine for Bert, probably five or six years ago. We wrote it as a
stand up, but he came to us and we used to he used to like right and have us sit
on a couch and kind of like pitch stuff and then one day we were like yeah. We
just have this crazy idea for like a thing that you could do. Well, what
we're going to happen, we said we have this crazy idea that we're going to do
yeah in our trio act yeah. He was like well actually it wasn't even an idea.
It was something that actually happened to us. Yeah, we actually had my idea.
Basically, I'm at memory. Yeah, half three, the one third of it happened to
Caleb, one third of it happened to me and then one third of it happened to
came. The part that happened to me was I was on a train yeah and the part that
happened to me was I went to college. Yes, and then all the other stuff
all the other stuff. The Russian mafia and that was just his life.
That was just his life. Yeah, so he had kind of a crazy life,
but one day we were like, let's put all this together. Let's incorporate
college and the train. And the train with his life. Yeah, 'cause I was
like, this story will never work 'cause it doesn't have a college or
the train. Yeah. Nobody will be able to relate to the story. Exactly.
Yeah, and then we did it. Yeah. And then for a while, we were...
It was a one man play. A three man, one man. A three man, one man.
One man show that we were all in one big pair of pants together.
Yeah, it was also about weight loss.
Because at the end we take the pair of pants and we say,
"Look at how much weight we've lost."
And we also have our shirts off when we do it.
By the way, you guys should come to our next live show
because we will be showing you how much extra skin we have from our weight loss.
We'll be hiding audiences.
Once we get back on that road, I'm going to be showing you my nipple skin.
is like it. I like because I know that we're not going to get sexual. Yeah,
don't get sick. We're not getting sexual, but the what my nipple skin looks like
and I'm going to get into. Yeah, just say this is medical. This is medical.
This is medical. Say it. My nipple skin looks like an uncircumcised penis. Okay,
from the back and I from the back, you can see my my butt looks like bunny ears.
Oh wow. Yeah, it goes all the way down. I have two uncircumcised penises on my
my chest and when I do that, you have penis is sexual. We said no sexual
gestures and you literally just did that when you talk about penis. We're
talking about a comical. You think doing this on a penis is not sexual? No,
I'm saying
that you justify all that stuff you do to yourself. No, it's true. You as a man
who has an
is not sexual. When I pull the skin back to pee, it is you feel it and you feel
good.
That's what I say when I pull it back. That's so sexual. That's incredibly
I'd like to say just that I we wrote this thing for Bert and then it was just
like we kind of didn't hear about it for a while. He starts doing on the road.
We're like yeah, whatever. It's fine. He gave us like five hundred bucks and
then we saw the trailer for the movie five hundred. Yeah, you don't remember
that. I don't think I only got five hundred. Oh well, you got more. You got
more than that. How much did you get or you mean you got five hundred mil right?
I did chill. There's no way you make five hundred million dollars. No, I
didn't make I made I made five hundred dollars. I made nothing. You didn't make
anything. You should probably talk to him about that. I thought that we all was
that well, you didn't send. He did not send an invoice. Yeah, you did not. I
thought invoice me whatever. I put a million dollars. He was saying he was
saying send me an invoice and then I was like oh sorry.
Where are we going to get paid?
Yeah, that I could see the confusion. Yeah, I thought he was telling me to use
my invoice, but then they do this movie and basically they the machine like I
hate to say it has gone Hollywood. Yeah, Mark Hamill's in it. He I mean the
biggest the biggest celebrity in the world, Mark yeah, because he was the
joker. Yeah, I mean
I I just I feel I mean Mark Hamill from body bags. Yeah, of course, yeah, I
feel crappy because like you, you took the no you crappy is okay. I know I'm
just I'm I'm just that's a hand of that's a that's a you know you're
making your life cap cap cap. Yeah, that's cab. That's got you
but yeah, Mark Hamill like to do it with like such a a list like superstar actor.
Yeah, it just kind of made me feel like I don't know at least make us like at
always put us in the movie and I think it's like three slave brothers or the
waiters. The thing is
waiters that we do honestly the thing that pisses me off. Yeah, okay, mark
Hamill, obviously famous actor, very popular right now, huge get to talk. I
think he's in terms of skill. He's more of a commercial actually does star wars.
He does joker. He does this type of thing, you know, and I know for a fact
that if we had been involved in the movie, yeah, I could have gotten Philip
anymore Hoffman yeah and we
I have footage of him that nobody else has ever seen of him doing a lot of the
stuff from the machine. No way that I worked with him to produce, because I
thought maybe it would be a funny gag to put into our three man's one man. So
with current technology on the current technology, we could literally copy and
paste him wow on the topic of Mark Hamill. I thought that he was just like
a Twitter guy before he became an actor. I think he will yeah, because he
he's one of those s h t i t my dad says type yeah yeah yeah he's like he like he
kind of like blew up yeah like that yeah through to it. I actually think he he
blew up off on Google buzz, Google buzz really yeah, oh my God, I forgot about
Google buzz. I was so popular on there yeah on Google buzz yeah, what's Google?
I never heard of this. That was Google's yeah, you it was only a book before
Google plus what you never heard of Google buzz never I had five, but I was
Google plus to the death. I loved Google buzz. I was on there like just got a
sandwich y'all. Yeah, me too. I was a my space. He's like using it. I was going on
there and saying like new metal is the shoes. I was a my space kid. I also had a
my space. I was a my space kid. I'd set my I still remember my photo. I had my
beanie barely hanging off my head and I was like looking this way. It was like
Caleb and it said you could put your body type in and it was athletic. It's
Ectomorphic. No, 5'3", more to love. Yeah. Because I was a little chunky. I had MySpace
when I was 9 because my mom let me have it. Bad decision on her part. There was a lot
of people trying to add me. I was 9 years old. Then I lied. 9? I lied and said that
I was 13 in my bio. Yeah, I think 13 is the... My mom pulled me aside one day and was like,
"You need to stop lying about your age on the internet." And I was like, "If I say that
I'm 9 and on MySpace and my bio, Tom is going to kick me off." Yeah, Tom was 9. I used to
to be I when I was when I was a kid and I was on like like going like looking at
forums and stuff, I was so I would get so embarrassed that I was a kid. Oh yeah,
yeah, I'm twenty five yeah yeah. I
like I'm actually like I'm seventeen. I used to lie on runescape so much about
my everything about me yeah. I told people Fortress, I told people I was on
runescape. I told people I was Irish and I knew like Gaelic and I would like go
to Google translate and translate stuff into like like Gaelic or Scots or
whatever and then just send that and it just made no sense. I'd be like, "Whoa,
this kid's Irish." Yeah. And then little do I know, I find out when I'm older.
Yeah. I was Irish the entire time. So maybe I wasn't lying at all, but I don't
think I know gay. Ancestral memory. When I had MySpace, I got in trouble because
my Uncle Jack was my friend and I had just seen that CKY tour documentary and
there's a scene where they go to Littleton, New Hampshire. They're playing
a show in Manchester or something and Chad Ginsburg is like, "I need to go and piss
on G.G. Allen's grave and give him a bottle of Jack Daniels. I need to go do that."
I was like, "Oh, so my favorite band right now is G.G. Allen." And then in my music section,
I had CKY, Bloodhound Gang, G.G. Allen, and my uncle called my mom and was like, "You
you need to start watching what your son puts on that computer because he is saying he likes
Gigi Allen and then showed my mom a video of Gigi Allen, like the documentary. My mom
was like, "Get that off of there! Get that off of there right now!"
That's kind of like...
She didn't even make me deactivate my account. She just said, "Get Gigi Allen out of your
top band."
That triple is really bad news. That's like future Vape Store employee.
My favorite music was all...
Zky Bloodhound Gang, Gigi Allen. Yeah, yeah, mine was all like alternative
metal that I found, like that it was all like stuff that you would get
recommended on like the iTunes store. If you I said PIS, you also said Gigi
Allen, it was all stuff that you'd get recommended on the iTunes store. Like if
you listen to five finger death punch, like it was like the stuff that like
nobody had ever heard of yeah that I still don't I've never heard anybody
skillet no see no yeah skillet is a real. These are not real bands. I was
sick of pretending. I didn't only listen to rap my entire life until like two
years ago. Yeah, yeah, I only listen to rap. I pretended to like rock music, but
I didn't really like it. Yeah, I liked I like the Halo three soundtrack, and
then I like only rap my I used to like on the iTunes thing in like two thousand
2008, I found out that the celebrities would have iTunes playlists. So I would
look through and I thought that was the coolest thing in the world, and then it
was like, "See what Dane Cook is listening to?" And then they would write
like the playlist. They would have like this many songs. It was like, I think
Dane Cook. I remember Dane Cook had "What's Her Name" by Green Day, and like
the description he wrote is like, "Such a beautiful song." I'm just saying I'm
getting nostalgic right now, because I'm thinking about when you go on the iTunes
and you didn't know how to like list like you could you'd listen to the snippets
the like 20 second snippet of a song and I didn't know I didn't know how to like
find it on before I knew how to like find it on YouTube or just get it off
like media fire or something and just be like I need to hear the rest of this
song just be listening to the snippet over and over. Yeah, the snake I need to
spend $10. Did you go to that with the bloodhound gang skits that were that the
like just met the cut off? Yeah, so I'd show my brother like like what's that
There's like a Bloodhound Gang skit where it's like they ask a,
they are doing a homeless guy and it's like advice from him and it plays all this way.
They're doing a homeless guy?
No, they're doing a homeless guy voice and it just says try throwing your socks in the trash before you get the holes in the feet.
Yeah, wait, okay, what is a homeless guy?
The voice on the album is "try throwing your socks in the trash before you get the holes in the feet"
and I showed that to my brother and it was the funniest thing in the world.
Do you guys remember Barnes and Noble used to sell CDs?
Yeah, you could sit there and listen to the CDs.
Yeah, but they don't have the listening part anymore.
Barnes and Noble nowadays, it used to be a bookstore.
Barnes and Noble used to be a bookstore. Now, it is a vinyl lover's paradise.
It's vinyl and Criterion, wall to wall.
And hey, do you like posters?
Yeah.
Go check out Barnes and Noble.
Do you like the Guardians of the Galaxy soundtrack?
trick yeah you're gonna love that ish on vinyl all right we've been doing so much
kind of nostalgia but yeah we need a big pop yeah but give us the give us all
little kid voices again I think that's perfectly
I'd like to buy a dark side of the man poster.
I would like to buy this poster of two women kissing.
Do you guys sell volcanic rock?
Like little pieces of volcanic rock?
I'd like to buy some.
So are we in Spencer's Gifts?
Is that gonna...
Do you have any t-shirts with the F word on it?
It doesn't matter where we are. Just do a thing.
What's so funny?
What are you laughing about?
It's your voice.
What do you mean?
Yeah, actually, okay, I don't mean to...
I don't know if I'm allowed to say this.
You sound kinda gay.
What are you talking about?
You think this is how gay people sound?
I think this is what gay guys sound like.
Wait, wait, check this out.
That's pretty good, yeah.
It does just sound like South Park voices.
Yeah.
Um, yeah.
Yeah, can I?
Bro, I sound like Cartman right now!
Yeah, do you guys know what channel Comedy Central is?
77!
77 is 55, I think.
That's okay.
Oh wait, they changed it to 50. It used to be 77 and then they changed it to 56.
I'd like to buy one flight to Las Vegas.
Yeah.
I'd like a Shirley Temple, please.
Uh, can I get a Coors Light on the rocks?
Can I get a Coors Light and Coca-Cola mixed together please?
Thank you.
Thank you very much doll.
You look beautiful.
Toots.
What's up baby?
Hey baby.
I almost said the B word.
Hey what's up girl?
Oh you look fine.
You look fine.
What's up baby?
Let me hug you real quick.
Let me hug you.
I wish I knew the lyrics to Rap God right now.
I'd do those.
Yeah.
I'm beginning to feel like a rap god, rap god.
I'm a beat up, I'm a rap god.
*Farting*
28, bro.
2BO, you do a voice.
The 28th.
Yeah, the Mexican guy's voice.
That is a funny voice, 2BO.
Bye.