(upbeat music)
- I have, I have something I need to run by you guys.
- What is it?
- Okay, so I'm thinking of completely rebranding
my onstage persona.
Okay, do you?
- All right.
- You guys ready for this?
- Yeah.
- Okay, so I need to set the stage here.
and can you have the you have the the effects queued up yeah one second okay.
Oh he's got he's fidgeting with this thing. I think it's not it doesn't I'm
gonna be the country's number one gross out comedian.
Okay, can you can you and I will operate? What does that mean? You just do the
effects real quick. Okay, so imagine okay. Imagine my voice is deeper. It's
not that much. Imagine my voice is for a little bit. He said a little bit a
couple of semitones.
What do you say? A couple of semitones a little bit deeper. So imagine
Madison Square Garden sold out, sold out one night only. Okay, only one night
sold out. One night sold out. It's all I could afford. He's making his voice
deeper, not like just yeah, you are. No, well, okay, because that's what I sound
now. Okay. Because it's I'm rebranded. Okay. So I go out. I'm in a trash can, arms and legs
out of a metal trash can and I have the trash can hat. Right? I hit the okay. That would
should be okay. Wait, that's just that's just the beginning. We ought to keep
going nasty P. That's just the beginning. So then okay, so clap again. We have a
five in the audience and then the audience is like
what time is it? It's
I'm nasty mother fucking P yo yo nasty P nasty be over here over here over here
And then I take out the sludge cannon and I'm spraying the front row.
I'm spraying the front row.
Spraying the front row with trash, water, and juices and stuff.
It's literally, it's like, so you know, like all the trash that they have at Madison Square
Garden, like they're having like all like, it's like hot dog bits and like popcorn and
like beer and stuff.
My underwear.
man, I'm spraying the whole front row and I'm like it's time to get nasty
hit the air warm
nasty mother fucking
but I have a big long beard that has a lollipop stuck in it. Listen. I don't
this feels I like it. Okay. I like it, but it does
and I don't wash my
no, I heard the wash. I heard that you do not wash your eyes. We heard that
so it's the first thing that you said. The only time I shower is when it
rain.
That's not a shower
sitting in the water. Maybe you should say like when it rains. I don't go
outside, so I don't show when it rains. I avoid the rain rain because it's
technically a shower to me. The only time I see soap is when I'm
there. We get
that's a better kind of see. That's what I was going to say. You've already
I've gotten into it, but I was feeling like this was very much style over
substance, but I want to hear the writing. I want to hear like the
crowd. All I have all I have so far is the two great two great ones right
there. Yeah, that was good. You know you need more stuff like that. You know
you need to
red fox. You gotta wash your ass. I'm saying you don't gotta wash your ass.
Yeah, my ass is like a cast iron pan. Okay. Yes, that's good.
And then would you have a sidekick? Maybe. And how much time? My opener.
My opener is the clean brothers. Clean Caleb and clean Cameron. And then we
would come out and we'd be the clean brothers? Okay, so we come out and we're
the clean brothers.
Okay, okay.
We're squeaky clean!
Oh beep beep beep beep beep.
That's me walking.
This is me cleaning myself.
I don't fuck with the...
This is too much fuck.
I don't fuck with the Clean Brothers, even though they're my openers.
Wee wee wee!
I'm sliding across the stage.
Wee!
But why are you out during the opener?
You should be backstage waiting.
Oh, this is when I bring you guys out at the end.
Why would you bring...
Wait, so you're our opener?
We shake hands and we drop the characters and we're like, "Oh, we're the clean brothers.
We're the clean brothers."
We're the clean brothers.
I bring you guys out at the end.
Why would you bring...
Wait, so you're our opener.
We shake hands and we drop the characters and we're like shaking hands.
We're just like, "Oh, great show, you guys."
And then we wash our hands.
We all do a bow and then wave to everybody goodnight.
So it doesn't really seem like we're your openers
and it really seems like we are a...
You're part of the show.
...a 30... like a splitting time.
We're double headlining.
Yeah.
So how is the money going to get broken down, I guess?
Because we're doing 30 minutes, I'm guessing.
Yeah, but then you split that up amongst yourselves.
we are a little more than thirty minutes, because we because we and we because we
come out of the and you got it's more like five minutes. I feel a little
shitty about that then, because I feel like hey, you know who feels really
shitty, probably your nasty. Yeah, see I'm already getting sick and tired of
this. This is going to be a really, really tough. What do you mean? I think
that if we're splitting the money and you you're saying we split it in half
one one section for each act, but then me and him have to split our half. I
don't think that's fair, because I think I'm looking into the audience. Most of
these people are clean. Yeah, there's no very few people. They're getting nasty
from the spray. That's your fault. Yeah, but who's the how are they showing up
exactly? What show? No, they're clean. You leave nasty and they're wearing
shirt. They're my they're wearing is white tie dye t shirts that are no no
no. They're wearing they're wearing the clean brothers. Exactly. The
understated t shirt shows like going to a war concert. It's a split audience.
Some people are there. Some people are like I like the so why are we splitting
money. Oh, then we'll figure that out. So can we go thirds? Yeah,
we'll do it in thirds. Okay. Okay. So what about
what about 75% for the clean brothers and 25% for you? That's not how
it works. Well, you already said yes to thirds, so why not say yes to
thirds? We have a crew we need to pay. Okay, okay. Exactly. We have
twice the production budget. Yeah. You guys,
the fact that all you guys are talking about is the money and not
the art right now is really starting to piss me off. 'Cause the art's
already... We've got the art down. 'Cause we mastered the art. Yeah, we
don't need to worry about the art anymore. We don't care about... But the
the only art that you guys have is that you're the opposite of nasty P. You are
the opposite of the clean. We actually came first. Yeah, come for we were a
weekend up in the sand. We did nasty P. We have there's a bunch of vinyl
records of the clean brothers at
in the bathroom
the clean brothers. There's a lot of brothers alive from their song wash.
There is a novelty record called wash your hands. Yeah, yeah, your hand
brothers and you got inspired by that. You did a parody version. It's like
weird out going on tour with Coolio.
Yeah.
Okay.
Coolio is taking the money because he's the bigger artist.
It's how Eat It was bigger than Beat It.
I don't think that is true.
Yeah, it's true.
No, I really don't think so.
I think more people have heard...
You think more people have heard Eat It than a Michael Jackson song?
Yeah.
I don't think so.
All right.
You can say that all you want.
You're just trying to make up for the Clean Brothers not selling as well as Nasty Petey.
The Clean Brothers, by the way...
We clean up.
Yeah, that's right.
And nobody dirty.
and you know where you've never been on the Ellen DeGeneres show. In the shower!
Okay, why are you doing the... you're always on. You're doing the character and you're
not even on stage. Yeah, because it's inspired a lot by my real life. You don't
wash your ass? I don't wash my ass, I don't flush the toilet, I don't wash my
hands after I pee sitting down. You don't have to. But you pee sitting down. I pee
sitting down just in case I have to poop. Okay, so you're like a gay, dirty guy. Yeah.
and you in case I have to poop by sitting down, bro is not bro is not about that.
He doesn't want it to splash around his bathroom because he's secretly clean.
See that's why it's down. If we don't split the money the way I was saying
earlier, which I think was ninety ten.
If we don't put the money that way, we will be leaking. We're going to walk
New York Post, the second oldest publication in America, by the way,
that's still really the New York. What's the oldest one?
The Bible, New York Times, New York Times, Ripley's, believe it or not,
the New York
the New York Post. We will be leaking to the New York Post that you are
actually clean. Well, I can I can just say that. Yeah, of course, I'm not
nasty all the time. Okay, well, there goes your idea. There goes all the
nasty hillbillies with banana peels on their head. Do you think that Gallagher
goes home? Gallagher smashes a watermelon in his house. Yeah, he has to
practice right now. You just walk out and do that. He goes to it. He goes to
the he goes to the practice hall that he has on his mansion yard. That's his
house. You think he has like to yard his man to yard is like that big white room
from the dark night yeah, but just different just
he has an Alfred yeah, he has a he has a lucius yeah he's developing some new
unethical watermelon in his lucius like if you're going to keep smashing this
watermelon like I'm walking yeah, you finish that, but like I'm not yeah, I
will not be here. I'm going to get fired okay for what I these hammers that I'm
giving you these big now
it. Yeah, all right. So right, I mean we had to get that out of the way. I have
an idea, too, that I can. I just wanted to address the obvious in the room. I
don't think that was obvious. You just I mean, okay, it was yeah. I'll be I was
obvious. Yeah, yeah, just the obvious. It's gone. Okay, nasty pee.
no, it's gone. Oh, that I see. I even forgot about it. Yeah, yeah,
we'll address that on Wednesday. That's yep. That won't be addressed today.
Yeah, we're not even gonna talk about that. And you know what? And I can't
talk about it without getting emotional. Yeah, so we're not gonna talk about
it. It's gone. The J. A. R. Yeah, it's gone from J. R. E. So
and that's what we're calling the show now. That's another. This is the
episode is all about rebranding rebirth. This is the this is called our Phoenix
episode. Okay, this is called our okay. That's the episode. All right, our
Phoenix, our Phoenix, our Phoenix episode. Yeah, because we're rising from
the ashes and we're starting everything over. Yeah, is what this is about. We're
starting the starting back at episode number one. Yeah, the numbering will
reset. We've probably done this.
We've probably done this twelve or fifteen times. Episode one, our
Phoenix episode. This is like the new 52, the comic books thing. Yeah,
and we have new characters now. That is such a good name,
the new 52. The new 52, because it rhymes? Yeah. Yeah, I bet they were...
I don't know if I ever understood that. Is it 52? It's 52 because they
had 52 series that they were rebooting and they got rid of a bunch of
stuff. It's so obvious to me. But it's so... I bet that they maybe had
50 or 51 and they were like, "Two more. We need to get another.
that we need to come up with another thing. Nifty fifty would have been good.
The
nifty
three fifty three that would have not been good for business, but you can
core fifty four that would have been good. The
these are the core. This is the new Canon, the new core. The
six fifty six. The six fifty six, that's the best one. The heavenly fifty seven.
the great heavenly fifty seven yeah, the fine fifty nine yeah that's yeah the
fifty and now the risky sixty. Okay, I'll get so risky, so you're pushing
over fifty now yeah. The thing is, if I had if somebody told me come up with
fifty two ideas for comics, I would know where I even start honestly. I would I
would do exactly I would it would because I if they somebody told me to
come up with fifty two ideas for superior comics, I'd be like Superman,
Batman,
well, I would do what I would do what they actually do now wonder what I would
come up with one and then I would be like but okay that one, but it's a girl
or it's an old man.
If you were to tell somebody to come up with an entirely new superhero,
I think at some point they would accidentally just make the flash again.
They would just that's the obvious super yeah.
Have I ever told you that no I came up with black. I called him black cat,
but it was do you remember book protectors? Yeah, I would had a black
one and I would put it over my head and I would run around my house and
punch my brothers and say, really like that. I had a green one. I put it
on my head. I said I was a goblin. I look just like black. That was it
was a great man. Yeah, I wish I haven't seen. I know I put it on
my head like like so it would be two point. Oh, I goblin. I put it
over my entire face and then the corners of it would poke out. Yeah,
see I had the corners, but they were goblin ears on. I was like one
four years old. Goblin ears are much bigger than cat ears, so it doesn't
sell very well as a goblin. When I was four years old I came up with a superhero called
Moat Man and his power was that, I don't know where it came from, all I know is that his
power was that he would ride the vacuum. His power was that he could ride the vacuum and
that was like his steed. When I was a kid I got addicted to the smell that came out
of the vacuum when it was on. Oh, yeah, my face in the exhaust and just smell it. And
my grandpa would say, what are you doing? And I'd say, I'm looking for something. I have
corn in the microwave. I'm thinking about it right now. I know that smell. It's right
or the dryer vent on the side of the house. Yeah, next to it. Get that. That's that smell.
hot air smell is so good. I love hot air. I still sometimes I'll use my wife's
blow dryer. When I get out of the shower, I'll blow it directly into my face.
Yeah, I'm not kidding. You should grow out one hair. I use the blow dryer more
than she does. You should grow out one hair and just blow dry that one. And
comb it and twirl it. You just want me to look like a big baby. I want you to
look like Mr. Saturn. Yeah, I'm not going to do that. I just won't do that.
That's below me. Standing in front of air is so awesome. If it's either a fan
he would he would call a big if it's hot out you like cold air. No yeah, I hate
wind you not wind, though, like a fan or an AC shut up when you're in a crowded
hot room and you stand for the AC. You take all the air and I don't go in a
crowded hot room. Yeah, you do I go in front of the AC. I just rip ass in front
of it. Why would you do that? Because I'm nasty P mother? No,
no, I would squeaky clean you if I told you if I got into a car accident,
everybody in my family died and everybody who's really close to me died,
but I survived, but I was really, really like could barely move any part of
my body. Would you guys bathe me now? Bathe you yeah, like with a sponge, I
think you wouldn't you wouldn't be bathed because in this situation, I'm
trying to get pussy
are you you're only your head works. Yeah, I'm just a head base. If I was
just ahead. Would you babe me like a bowling ball
if I was only ahead? I guess so, because that's I'm not going to be like having
a rub on your dick or anything. I would not. If I was just ahead, you would be I
would get a restraining order against you because you would be you would be
doing crazy stuff with me and I'd be
never age and right now when you do stuff like that, I punch you, but if you
did it
like if you did it and I was ahead, I would have no arms to punch. No recourse,
no recourse whatsoever. You would you would like because you'd be so afraid
of like me pranking you.
Why would you prank me if I was a head, but I know that you would you would
like you would put him in a plastic bag and throw him out of the window. I
would put him in the freezer and then open up the like keep opening up the
freezer and go, oh,
yeah, doing a different face every time you open the freezer, but that we need
to entertain you. One day, if anything, he only play with you, I would do with
I know that's and I don't want to be played with.
But it would be to entertain you.
Here's what I want you to do.
Click next Tarantino movie because I'm sitting on the couch watching them all.
What would happen is that you would be so afraid of getting put in the fridge and stuff like that,
you would look exactly like that spider from Toy Story.
I would build you a body out of Tinker Toys.
You know what I'm talking about?
That little spider with the claw?
You know the spider from Toy Story?
Is there a toy story fan child child? I'm not a child baby. Actually adult who
likes childish movies. I'm grown childish adult, but I'm pulling a memory
from childhood. Hey, Pixar, Pixar. Here's a message to you.
Start making good movies again.
Start this year when I when I was like in Oakland because those movies are
yeah now. I don't want to see in Conto. I see the trailer even and I don't
I want to see Rigardo. I like to watch
Rigardo.
Yeah, that's one of the movies they make.
Okay.
I don't want to see big hero scenes.
I usually, I watch a movie trailer and that to me is like a
full movie.
Yeah.
In itself. I love the music. I like the words that pop up on
the screen.
Yeah, me too.
I like to see when it says, "This Christmas," stuff like
that. I get full enjoyment, even if I'll never see the movie.
But Pixar, your trailers...
They're trash, brother.
They've become trash.
Yeah.
The last good Pixar trailer, Cars 3.
because when cars died, oh, he didn't die, but he got hurt. He
got badly, really, really badly. Do trailers like that for the other characters?
All I want to see is like you're bloody to a pole. I want to
see Buzz Lightyear get in a street fight and get one punch
kill street beefs. Buzz Lightyear. Yes, that's what I want to see.
I do not want to see him in a different dimension that they did
bugs. Lightyear. When I was in, I was in Emeryville last summer,
I kept seeing people going up to the skate park where my girlfriend was staying, close
enough to this one skate park that is next to the Pixar building.
And apparently, huge problem the Pixar people have, because the Pixar campus is shut down,
you can't visit it because of COVID precautions.
I think it's just because they don't want people like...
Buzz Lightyear has COVID.
Yeah, Buzz Lightyear had COVID last summer and it was crazy.
What kind of bullshit is that? But there is a huge problem. He's from space,
so he doesn't have the same immune system as us. That's not true.
It's like when you go to a foreign country and you don't have resistance
to their germs. People come to us... You realize that we are the new Daily
Show and people come to us for their news and you say shit like that.
My idea that I said earlier that we didn't get into was about news.
Okay. Wait, let him tell his story and then I'm gonna get into your idea.
But a huge problem on the Pixar campus is that people keep walking,
trying to walk past the security guard to go look, 'cause they have a
big like they have the the lamp and the ball in the front of the place. Oh,
the lamp and the ball. Yeah. People keep trying to like walk and go like look at
it on the campus, but like you're not allowed to. You're not allowed. That's
gotta be one of the worst stories you've ever told. Yeah. I'm sorry. I took a
Claritin earlier and it's kicking in right now. That was crazy. That was so
much set up. Don't let you
every single day. I'd see a new person try and get past and be like it was
worth a shot
and I don't know. I'm Jesus Christ.
This is not enough caffeine. That's okay. You did nasty. You did nasty pee.
I did nasty pee. So you're still up. You're still way up. Yeah. Okay. Tell
me what your idea is. So let me pitch this to you. I'm literally like I feel
feels like I'm in a different dimension from Clareton. Yeah, you are that
allergic to the allergy medicine. I took to Benadryl last night, so I'm still
like you got to get on Zertek bro. I got to get back on Zertek. You need to
get on the shot. Fire ass pill.
Oh, what was your news idea? So the news everybody you ask anybody nowadays and
they will tell you the news is stressful as fuck. Let's ask him. Does the new
stress you out? I can't watch it. It's stressful right yeah, because it's like
every day, Ukraine, Russia, nuclear warfare, to learn what new crane is new
diseases,
Donald Trump rising back up like a villain in a movie, all the speaking of
our Phoenix, speaking of a Phoenix, yeah, the dark Phoenix,
Lord yeah, but it's stressful because all this all this shit just keeps
happening. It's like twenty sixteen never ended shit just keeps going on and so
my pitch for a new news network or maybe even just a segment and then in new
news network. That's good, so maybe we can use that, but it's
maybe instead of saying all the crazy scary things that are happening. Maybe
they report the stuff that isn't happening so that you don't get stressed
out. So, for example, you turn on the news and it would be like breaking news.
China is not at war with Canada,
and it would be and they're like and also Canada is not at war with Mexico
and they can maybe they could do every country that's in every news new. This
is stop. I'm pitching my idea. If I brought you into if I brought listen,
if I brought you into
the pitch meeting, I was CNN later today. Yeah, I would lose the pitch
because of that yeah. Okay, I would have lost my show your details for the
end yeah the notes, but basically there would be one hour that's all about
different wars that aren't happening. Then they would do like this celebrity
is alive. Okay, now it's guy like that all the celebrities that are alive
and their birthdays and their birthdays yeah yeah well, but but they wouldn't
mention the celebrities if it was their birthday, because even that can be
stressful, because it's like oh my God, what I get
to get them, but also it's like okay, it's quite a Tarantino's birthday,
everyday movie day. He's another year closer to death. You're right. I don't
want to know how old Brad Pitt is yeah. If I find out how old Brad Pitt is, I'm
sure I would exactly it was his birthday today.
I'd have to like I'd have to get him a a fucking Walgreens toy. Yeah,
I was
I'd rather just not even know yeah,
well, thank God it's on the eighteenth of
they could be like a new store has not opened up in this location and
well, that's not good news. We like it's not about good news. It's about
things that aren't happening, so you don't have to worry about anything
changing. Okay, so I was
I was going to say
four ends, new news network. So I was going to say four ends, nice new news
network, but it's not really nice. It's not it's the new neutral. It's a bit
yeah, it's neutral. It's not a news.
The new nothing news network where just we tell you when something doesn't
happen. Exactly right. Yeah, there's no asteroid headed towards earth. Exactly,
exactly. You know, that's exactly what it would be. There is no science, no
new recipes. There's no there's not a recipe. There is no new recipe has been
invented. No new food is one of the new recipes. If you want a new recipe, go
watch CNN. Exactly, exactly. The cooking news network. Go watch the Food Network
if you want a new. Don't come to the quadruple in network or the quad, the
quadruple, the triple in network. Yeah, yeah, because we are. Fortunately, we
have to issue a retraction. A new recipe was just discovered today. You can't
issue and that's the great part. You can't issue a recatch. We're not
issued any retraction. We would like to issue no retractions for that's not
what I got. I don't think that's when there was yeah, it's not what they
basically the more I think about it. It is opposite. It should be you know
instead of the news, it's called the olds
wow, so it's in on
non the nothing, but nothing
but it's also it's not really the old, so it's the new
it's something that didn't have network. Yeah, what's in between new and old
present now it'd be called the present. It's not that either. No, I think it's
still news. I think it's breaking news that nothing happened. That's the
because we're still I mean we're not, we're still hiring like anchors from
other networks and stuff like we're not building a whole new thing. Can we get
less? We're definitely have Lester whole Anderson Cooper. We're gonna have
basically everybody. So these people are trained to deliver news and not this new
type of it's going to take so there's well they're still going to be doing
like breaking news. Yes, like and yeah, be really excited and like there's
going to be a lot of flashing lights on the screen and a ticker and are we
going to do for what screens sports is hard because they have to do a sport
that nobody plays. So maybe they do like nobody played the Mayan ball game.
Yeah, no one's played the mind ball ranking fifteen hundred. You nobody got
injured in a game that didn't happen today.
nobody is out in that weird Mayan head game that nobody plays anymore. Yeah,
wow, and the weather is not happening. Literally, I'm going to be like Logan
Roy. Yeah, that's good. He died.
You haven't seen it yet.
You haven't seen that yet.
He died.
Yeah, that's right.
so
spoilers on this episode.
That's our new thing. That's another Phoenix thing. That's another thing
that we're these. We spoil movies. We spoil TV. I feel like we've been always
been. We always
spoil, but we're like it. We're turning it to a we're going to watch stuff.
Just is going to be that we've never even seen. I'm going to watch. I'm
going to watch. What's a fucking show that's on TV succession. I already
did that. I'm going to watch the bear. Yeah. Yeah, and I'm going to say
I've never seen anything in that. That's a perfect old show. Nothing happens in
that show. Yeah, that would be they would also air Seinfeld. Wow
wow
that's all about nothing happening. Yeah, nothing happens in that bloody show. I
don't know why people watched it
actually stuff happens. The more I think about it now, a lot of stuff
actually happens in that show. Oh, it's a show about nothing. There is so much
shit happening. There is so much right under the wire. The four words
Oh, I'm just doing nothing.
Yep, just barely doing it. Basically sounded like you were yawning.
And he liked it.
Yeah.
Look at how much he liked it.
He's giggling like a little giggle bear.
Oh, man.
I would like to make an actual show about nothing.
Yeah.
And it would be called, you know what it would be called?
White screen.
No, no, no, it would be the opposite. It would be called, "What I Think Happens When You Die."
Whoa.
Yeah, and it would be...
An atheist perspective.
It would be called, "What Happens to Atheists When They Die."
Yeah.
And then I have a sister show a spin off like a better call Saul called what
happens to Christians when they die. And then I would have another spin off. So
I would have a fat man. What happens to me when I die and it's and you're a king
on and it would be me. It'd be me killing all the characters from the
second show. Yeah, and I'm giant. I'm 50 ft tall slicing them up with samurai
swords. I I got I'm very excited. It's being of shows there. I don't know if
you guys saw this. They're doing a season two of prehistoric planet. No,
the dinosaurs show. Oh, that one that all cgi one that's on apple tv.
Well, here's the spoiler.
We're
real. I'm very excited about it because of it's about dinosaurs, which are
cool, but I'm also very excited because in the first season they showed and
showed to t rexes fucking. They showed a bunch of dinosaur pussies shooting out
eggs. They showed they showed dinosaur poop and a dinosaur eating poop or
something right and that's all in the first season ramp it up. I'm nasty
season two.
they're going to have to like, you know, they're going to have to wrap it up.
Exactly. What's good? What's it going to be? Yeah. Yeah, dude, they're going to
show
they're going to make it's going to be like that one porn angle where it's
behind the balls.
They literally, yeah, they did. They did T-rex is fucking doggy style. They did
diesel. They poop. They did what else? They're going to they're going to make a
hyper realistic version of walk the dinosaur. Yeah. You remember that one? I
I remember the song. No, no, the
it was on LOL Shock. The Shock website. I don't remember that one. That was on
there. That one did not deserve to be on there. It's a 3D animated thing of
two dinosaurs 69ing. That's on YouTube. You can look that one up. Yeah, that's
not really pornographic. It's not pornographic unless you're into dinosaurs.
Unless you are a dinosaur. Unless you're scared of dinosaurs. Yeah. If you're
really scared of dinosaurs, do not watch Walk the Dinosaur.FLV. Are you guys
scared of alligators? Yeah. I don't get, I'm not scared of them. Why not? I don't
know. Is it because you live where they aren't? You know what I don't trust
about alligators? No, I used to live where they were, but I think, but I
didn't, I didn't see them that often. Maybe that's why you're not scared of
them. But you never once want to see them on the street. When we went to
alligator adventure. Yeah, that was so fun. That was awesome. That was sick,
but I don't trust alligators because they sit there and they let that, like...
They open their mouth. This Pepsi is making me burpy.
they open their mouth and they just leave it open. They have that like trap door
thing on their mouth. Yeah, it just goes like they like close your throat, their
throat. They close their yeah, I don't trust that one bit exactly. Yeah,
because that looks like a perfect seat. I guess I'm more scared of crocodiles
though than alligators. Well, of course, yeah, obviously, I think there's
something reasoned with yeah, crocodiles have no crocodiles are robots. Yeah,
they're robotic crocodile. Which ones do you feed a leg of raw chicken to? You
I feed either of them or leg. Crocodiles are bigger, though, and more
aggressive. I think I can reason with both of them.
No, crocodiles will eat a human. Really?
And alligators probably won't. Alligators will run around, though.
Well, we saw that giant crocodile. Crocodiles will run around, too,
though. But I mean, alligator will... But you won't see that many
crocodiles. You're probably more likely to see an alligator if you're like
them. Yeah, in North America, for sure. You know what I found out one
time, speaking of just amphibians, reptiles and stuff? My dad, afraid of a
frog afraid of a frog. I want a specific frog. I one time my dad left he left the
shop vac out on the porch growing up. He left the shop vac out
rained. He didn't touch it for a couple days and then he was like, all right, I
gotta move that. Then there was a frog inside the shop vac and my dad asked me
to go and and dump the shop vac out because he was afraid of the frog. Yeah,
and I was like, "Are you fucking kidding me?"
- Are you daft?
- "You're my father."
- Are you daft, Kyle?
- "You were my father and you were afraid
"of a tiny little frog right now."
- Yeah.
- And that's the day that I started calling him a bitch
and I started slapping, slap boxing him.
(laughing)
- There was a hurricane that happened in North Carolina.
I think it was Fran, one of these 90s hurricanes.
And my dad--
- One of these 90s hurricanes with names like Fran.
(laughing)
- Daria, Hurricane Daria.
I
whatever happened to a good old fashioned hurricane named Herbert.
Yeah, exactly. Now, the Jersey's George.
Now, what about Hurricane Lucille? Yeah, come on. Nowadays, you got
Hurricane Hayden. Yeah, Hurricane Braden, Hurricane Caden, Hurricane
Sox, Tungsten. Exactly. It's fucked up. Hurricane Tungsten. Tungsten.
That one is scary. That would be scary because Tungsten is a type
of metal. I'm really glad they've never named a hurricane. Hurricane
destroyer. A bullet is headed straight for Florida is tungsten is a metal. Yeah,
but I one of these ones, one of these 90 style hurricanes like Fran was coming
through North Carolina. My dad really smart guy left the door open overnight
and well good, because then there wouldn't be any back draft. That's
probably what he was thinking. He was like, I'm gonna save on air condition,
but then there was 100,000 million frogs in our house when we woke up and we
had to call some guy to come kill all the frogs. Wow, yeah, and I think he
I literally just used a shop vac and just vacuumed up just hundreds and hundreds of frogs.
Watching my dad afraid of a frog is like the...
I'm not afraid of anything.
That is one of the craziest moments of my life.
No reptiles scare me.
Reptiles do not scare...
I'm scared of bugs.
I hate bugs.
I never want to see a bug as long as I live.
I was afraid of bugs because I knew a cheap bug would have a trouble eating me.
I guess I'm kind of scared of snakes.
Not in the sense of like if I saw it, I'm scared, but like I don't want to deal with
one.
Yeah.
I like snakes.
I put a snake in my backpack one time.
I've talked about that, like if I walk down if I'm hiking or something and a
snake goes like
across the path, I that doesn't scare me, but if I was, I guess, but if I was
I guess
so it gets rattle and the showing its fan held aside, I said, I'm going to
eat you. Yeah, now that I think I started that, I was like, I guess I guess
what I'm saying is I'm afraid of being attacked. Yeah, do rattles rattlesnakes
only attack when they feel threatened, right? I think most animals, except for
the ones that except for bears, bears just kind of will do whatever. But have
you seen all these videos of people who are on hikes and they run into a bear
and then they that I am terrified of bears? Yeah, the thing you're supposed
to do is you're supposed to go hey bear yeah bear. Well, it depends on the
type of bear. Yeah, that's the worst part. It is like to do the middle.
There's like different things for every type of bear. I do not like being
read. Yeah, if you if you there's some bears, do you see you're supposed to see
them? You go
and then there's another where it's like oh, if you do that, it will kill you
instantly yeah yeah is that that's the
you're not there's no point in running. You're supposed to just cover your
trails. You're supposed to play that and put your back like brown bears are the
ones that you're just supposed to be like hey and then black no brown bears
are supposed to play that giant black bears are like human size. They're like
black bears. I think you can scare off and grizzlies. You're supposed to play
that, but also and polar is you're supposed to be hot. You're supposed to
get really really, really save the
thrower and throw a coca cola. You remember that that bear with alopecia?
Yeah, that thing was cool. Yo mama's cool, but grizzly bears also okay.
The okay, hold on this guy. Wait, hold on bear with alopecia, and he's saying
is my mom. Look, look at him. He's a bear with alopecia. He's not a bear,
not a bear that weight
191 pounds of lean muscle.
Yeah, it's not as funny to call you. You're a hundred. It's funny to call him
ugly muscle.
Funny to call Cameron fat, but you I feel like if I called you fed, you would
know what I eat you. You'd eat me and put me on his bed. Now you'd be in the
mirror gripping the sink and just go.
No, that's what I do. And you guys, I go in the mirror. I go in the mirror and I
pull all my fat down to see, make it look like I have abs.
Yeah.
And then I go, "Ugh!"
And I make a HDR video where I'm like doing this.
Oh, like Passionate Daddy?
Yeah.
The guy that Noah keeps showing me.
Oh, yeah. Chad found that guy. I love that guy.
Oh, Chad found him?
Yeah, Passionate Daddy.
Passionate Daddy.
So he posts...
Can't show it here, but...
Yeah, he posts like his Instagram is just all pictures of like Delta 8 he's bought.
Yeah. He basically is Chad.
I'm ready to fucking smoke this tonight.
Yeah, he's got his trunk. He's just showing trunk.
Oh, he's showing his dick wells, whatever they're called.
Dick wells?
What are they called right there?
You're thinking of cum gutters.
Cum gutters.
He does not have cum gutters.
Well, he's got his pants down to like right where his pubes go.
Okay, he has the belly, the round belly, but then he has like two circles that make up his thighs
and then like a perfect kind of triangle of fat that holds his penis is Fupa and
then yes, that's what it is and then his Dick is pretty big and it hangs out
down. It goes below the if you don't see the tip of the penis on Instagram,
you're fine. Yeah, you can show yeah, yeah, you can't. What is that about?
Why can you show as much as you want to take that pick, but the tip of him with
the drone, the tip, which is not the tip is the point. It's the it's the exact
same thing as as free the nipple. Yeah, the tip is the nipple for guys. The tip
is the sexual part. The tip is the nipples for guys. Boob, if you cover up
the nipple. Yes. Who was that dude from Orange is the New Black who posted the
shirtless selfie with women's nipples on his body? Do you remember that? I don't
know. I don't remember that. You went on Instagram and you searched man with
woman's nipples.
That's how you found that. There was, it was like a, like he was doing it in
this like male feminist way where like the
caption, it's literally a picture of
himself shirtless, two other women,
like one woman, one woman, like two
different women's nipples on his bodies.
And he's like, yep, just repost him
like this shirtless.
And he's got like his eyes like it's
like just posting this right now
because apparently Instagram wants to
sexualize these two women's nipples.
It's like you've turned yourself into
like into a Frankenstein.
you
on a frankenstein to women's nipples on to yourself to prove a point. There's
two
asking the women. If you can do it, I mean like can I use one of your nipples
in my
the I he's like if I were to use one of my one of your nipples in my selfie,
which one would you prefer? I
this for the instagram wants a sensor, this frozen women's torso sitting in my
fridge. How disgusting is this website?
what are we talking about? Bears, Grizzly bears, they can't run downhill because
they have too much muscle on their shoulders. What is in that cup with
that? Because they have well, that's how a Grizzly bear. It has the big hump on
its back. Yes, I've seen crazy muscles in their in their shoulders and that's so
they can go. I mean they can go downhill, but they can't run because
they bears run really fucking fast, too. They can run like fifty miles an hour.
Yeah, they're very fast, but not a Grizzly bear can't do that downhill. You
need to go down so, but you need to play dead, but if you're going to run, go
go downhill, but you're going to die anyway. You just are as soon as you see
a barrier, I'm assuming. Have you ever seen a video of a bear like chasing a
car? No, it's the scariest thing. It's going car speed. They can go car speed
for short bursts. Holy shit. Yeah, it's so horribly and fucked. Yeah, and mooses
too are scary too. These are the nipples of Chrissy Teigen and Miley Cyrus.
Whoa. Oh, I remember that guy. Yeah, it's Matt McGorry, free the nipple.
Chrissy Teigen has a blue nipple. She, I guess her nipples are completely blue
like a, like a Navi. Did she used to be a Navi? Do not have nipples or I mean
not a cook. She used to be, they don't, which is one of their worst. Believe
me, I know. Why do they spend so much time in at the Avatar movies
obscuring the, where the nipples would be? Here's the guy, by the way. Well,
what I like about it is they obscure where the nipples would be, but then
you can think about
but then what I like is they but they also just like they like they all the
Na'vi wear the tiny like tropical bras, basically. Yeah, but they just always to
block where the nipples will be, but they also just have them like swing out
of the way the entire movie. So you can see that there's actually no like why
not just those tropical bras? That's like the Na'vi equivalent of the coconut.
that's a not be a equivalent of a t shirt. Actually yeah, well, no, just the
objects that they're using to cover the yeah is the coconut and coconuts on that
planet very flat. I would jack off to the avatars if they weren't so big yeah
they're too big yeah,
it is his foot. Well, you know what you know, I would know what to do with. You
know what the actual issue is. It's not that they're too big. It's that that you
only realize what you what's actually happening for you is you only realize
they're too big when they're next to a human, and why would you jack off to a
Navi when there's a human right there?
Does that I think I think the thing I think the thing that is a concord? Yeah,
I should be jacking up to the set of the blue avatar. That's how it's going on
in your brain. That's the biological switch. The problem, the obvious problem
here is that their sexual organs or hair.
I don't so you hear when you check when you jack off to a Navi, they're
definitely still have you are jacking off to hair. They do have they have
stuff. They have
James Cameron has basically gone on record and said that the hair thing is
not sex. No, it's not bonding. They do it with the animals. It's bonding.
That's true. It's more of a kiss. Yeah, it's no, it's more of my dog. It's
honestly more of a deep sleepover conversation. Yeah, that's what it is.
Yeah, it's like when you're with a Navi woman and you're putting your hair in
her hair deep text. You're just like you're like what if we like got a time
share together? Yeah,
we're tone together. When was the last time you guys had an actual just real
ass night walk conversation
on some on the real tip where you're walking and you're saying what the hell
is all that look up at the stars. I want to have one of those every night. Look
how I've had so many of those of my cousins walking down the street and
looking up and being like what yeah, what are we doing?
bro. This universe is as large as a fucking as four or five as big as a
did. I was going to say I thought that I had a conversation like this with my
girlfriend the other night, but then I remembered that the conversation that we
were having was me explaining
blueberry guys to her
like the what in God's fucking name are you talking about? We did an episode
about grammar like explaining like the guy, but you thought that was a
conversation about the universe.
No, I was like, I was like, when
was it like a conversation where
you're like, oh, like this is like a
great moment.
We're having like a really nice time
together. We're laughing.
We're like talking and like about
like, like deep stuff.
And we were like talking to each
other about like, like what
makes a person want to do
this? And it was us
looking at a video.
His name was like Blueberry Matthew.
And he's like,
the fucking video is so good.
It's him in a coach's outfit and he goes like,
"Okay, when you're out there, I want you to be the ball." And then it cuts
to him in the blueberry costume and his voice is high and he goes,
"But coach, I am the ball."
That's pretty good. I wanna see that video. That is a really good idea.
Yeah. It is really good. I had a deep conversation the other day.
Somebody asked me what my biggest fear was. Wow. And I said,
"The entire world blinking out of existence in a single second." And then
and they said, Why are you afraid of that? And I said, I guess it makes no
sense, but I had a I had I had a deep thought last night. What was it when I
was falling asleep and you know when you get your demons?
Dude, I can't be well. We were taught we were talking about about AI about the
about the Caleb was telling me about this. We had a deep conversation. Last
night, I have a deep conversation on the guy. We got deep from Union Hall,
but Caleb was telling me about this AI experiment where they wanted. They told
AI that you have to be evil and try to destroy the world and it made a
twitter account and like tweeted like I want to destroy the world,
hashtag destroy, yeah, whatever I like domination, yeah, and so I was like and
we're like laughing about like that's so funny that the like I thought that
that was how you destroy the world and I was lying a bed and I was like,
Oh my God, you could destroy the well. I was thinking I was literally like
I've been thinking like that experiment is not ethical because there's
although there is a one percent chance that you press go on that experiment
and the you know the AI like makes a twitter account. That's like it's the
twitter account and it says like
it makes an account as Vladimir Putin and it gets like a verified check and it
tweets to Joe Biden. It says I am launching a new right now and Joe Biden.
He thinks it's real and he launches back the new. He launches new at Russia and
like that could happen yeah. It could that would be so funny. If that's how
the world ended is that Joe Biden got faked by like by like a Moji instead of
this is a
hundred percent. The he is the he's the president who would get who got fooled
by the sushi roll
what the hell and his man's got a narrow, but I was really like a thing
like the how could verify how could they think it's okay to do an experiment
like that yeah because they could that a I could ruin geopolitics. I agree. I
think that are I think that we should sign that letter that says that we need
called all our I think I think it needs to end research. We did so much a
ice.
You still do it. I still did. It's every day. You text us something that is if
it's if you text me more than six words, I know that you wrote it with a
I. What do you mean? You all any time in my birthday poem? Yes, that was a
I. Everything was a I know. I know you because of his poultry gift, his
gift. Well, I get was so heartfelt. His his was not robotically cold. Okay,
but I was first. I gave him no because you sent him a cheerio my own. You
know, I'm a heart shape cheerio. Okay, so doesn't even remember my gift. My
first gift was a kiss. Okay,
second guest was a guess.
Second guest was a gift was a heart shaped cheerio, which I thought was very
and I got him a video. I don't think it was paltry. You saw all the video
and then you robotically generated something that I was cold and had no
emotion. What are you talking about? You want to read it? I can pull it up.
I'll pull it up right now. It was not. It was it was somewhat heartfelt.
Yeah, the nipple thing to free the nipple picture is really funny. It was
somewhat heartfelt, but again, it was written by essentially you hired a ghost
writer and it wasn't even human. Yeah, I would have liked for you to at least
hire. It's like you. It's like you. It's like you went up to a
cockroach. Can you say, OK, wish my friend happy birthday. Cameron's gift to
Caleb oh so small, paltry and meager, barely a gift at all.
Better luck next time, Cameron, dear,
or your friendship may soon disappear.
Cameron's gift for Caleb was small, not much effort,
no thought at all, but Julio and Patrick knew just what to do.
Their gifts brought joy and love, laughter anew.
- And where in that poem does it say
happy birthday, Patrick?
- That's a good point.
- It says Caleb's birthday, and that was in addition to the--
- Does it say happy birthday?
- It was in addition to the happy birthday video.
- Does it say I love you, Caleb,
we can kiss for one time?
- No, it doesn't say that.
like here's a heart shaped cheerio. That's the shape of my heart. He would
never kiss me. No, he has never kissed. I know you have not ever. Here's was
kissing all over me yesterday. He was me like fifty times.
What
what are you even talking about? What are you serious? Are you? Is this a
are you
is this an allegation?
He kissed me a weird number of times.
Today is your birthday. It was in addition to this. So this was pretty
scandalous, I'll admit. He sent me this video. And I did a little... I put on
my Sherlock Holmes hat. You sleuthed. I sleuthed a little bit. And what did
you find? I found out that that was a video that was uploaded to YouTube
a long time ago. And he said that we need to do a copyright strike on
them for stealing that from me. I was trying to make you feel better about
your terrible gift, but in reality, I liked Cameron's paltryness the most.
Okay, yeah, all right.
I don't know what was yours. He Leo gave me a picture of a bunch of flowers.
Yep, that's true, which was very, very sweet. That might be the best one. It
was a bunch of roses with one golden rose directly in the middle of bulls. I
well, and it was twenty six rows. Can we do a reverse image search on this on
these on this photo real quick? No, I don't see why we why we need to, but
you can go ahead and do a reverse image search on the cheerio. You won't find
anything. No, it's an original picture. I think I think if I do a reverse image
search on that, I may find a lot more cheerios.
So yeah, if you wanna make yourself so fuckin' hungry you can't see, I think
that I'm gonna get, I think
right now, what time is it? One o'clock? That is, to me, that's the problem with
cheerios is that one is not enough.
I am still so hungry. How horrible would that be if you looked at the back of
a Cheerios box that's serving size of one Cheerio, 200 calories.
They make a Cheerio like how Mini Wheats were originally just one big thing.
Oh yeah, the big... So you just have one big Cheerio.
That was so crazy to find that out that Mini Wheats wasn't the original
thing. 'Cause they used to be just Wheats. Yeah, it used to just be one
wheat. You just get one wheat. That is some crazy shit. I think my next cereal
will be raising brand
raising brands. I love raising. I've been cycling doing all different cereals.
I don't eat cereal. I like cereal because I don't have to do anything. I woke up
at five in the morning and I had a skirt steak and two eggs. Yeah, see, I can't
do that. And I immediately wanted to vomit. It was so disgusting. Yeah, I need
I need to eat as soon as I wake up, but I also don't want to do anything.
My girlfriend got this like
aids from you. No, she got this cereal that is like
it's an organic.
It's an organic cinnamon toast crunch that tastes the same as cinnamon toast
crunch. And it's like, just get fucking cinnamon toast crunch. Why?
Wait, no, that's exactly the reason to get the organic. Yeah.
you just that's the you just did a reverse reason. It doesn't have
rebo flavin and stuff in it. You don't want rebo flavin. What are you talking
about? That's all of all of the no, no, no, the good for you. Well,
it's in a
there's really nothing that's good for you and sentiment toast crunch, but you
should stop eating so much sugar because sugar is I don't eat a lot of
sugar.
Can you okay? I told somebody this the other day you have before in the time
that we've been in this office just over a year. You have come in that door
at eleven in the morning with two different bags of candy. Yeah, so just
like that's crazy. There's not that is crazy. Candy is a would do. We would do
candy.
But that back
D and D. How did you shoot that? I have a skill. That was cool. I'm going to do
it again. It won't work to me. Yeah, it just came right back. Boomerang. Oh, my
my God boomerang status yeah, but you need to stop eating candy. Do not
intervene with me right now. You need to do not do not make this episode of candy
intervention. This is a full
I've been meaning to talk to you about this for I've stopped eating as much
candy as I do. Thank you very much. What does that mean? As much as you do
once a week now that's not true. That's more than that. It's I eat candy once a
week. Your eyes are closed because you're lying and then you rolled your eyes
right after now. I can do you're bullshitting me. I don't eat that much
candy anymore. When was the last time you candy yesterday? You had candy
yesterday.
You did I didn't have candy the day before that you did.
What was it? What did you eat? Probably? What did you eat? I don't even want
to. It was a chocolate coin.
At least that's a that's somewhat an adult. Yeah, that's respectable.
whenever when I do go for candy, I don't eat. I eat candy maybe once a month,
one
maybe on a if I'm really in a craving month, but I will always go for
gummy bears. Yeah, I've never eaten. That's the only candy I ever crave. I
like gummy bears, but I have never and will never eat a bag of any candy.
Yeah, I'm a I will have three pieces of candy. Yeah, and if I have a
Reese's Cup, I'll have one Reese's Cup. Yeah, yeah, I never I never create
chocolate. I don't ever want chocolate except for chocolate cake. I don't like
desserts either.
You're fucked up. I like chocolate cake is fire. I like broccoli. Dessert to you
is beef jerky. You know what the best dessert is actually? The best dessert is
barley. Sweet, sweet, sticky Thai rice with a mango on top and condensed milk.
That is completely true. That is the best dessert bar none. Dude, rice pudding
from the from the Indian place that you remember that putting it in my house.
Yeah, remember that Indian spot? I mean, this is chocolate pudding. I used to
eat five hundred calories of chocolate pudding every single day when I lived
chocolate pudding is bad. Shut your bitch ass up. That is more. That is more
of a baby thing to eat the candy. Well, there's a completely honest. What about
scotch pudding? What is good? What I surprise you if I swirled it
with what vanilla
you probably get that you probably get the yogurts that have the little the
little things that you mix in no the on the top of the races, the reasons,
Rosie and over to the show body flips
and I get the s'mores. I can't believe you're trying to act superior. But can
you eat chocolate pudding? Yeah, I don't eat chocolate, but I used to you used to
okay yeah. When I was in college, I trying to gain weight, I had chocolate
pudding, but I don't need it anymore. Okay, because I don't need that kind of
bull. Yeah, you don't need that kind of bullshit. Okay, everyone's going to have
a dark chocolate almond butter cup with coconut pieces up top. Okay,
seventy eight percent cacao.
What do you what do you eat that with all your wooden spoons in your house?
Yeah, a spoon with a crank on it. Why would I eat a why would I use a
spoon to eat a peanut butter cup?
Because it has no binding agents.
There's no binding agents in this chocolate. I use my hand, I put it in my
mouth.
What's wrong with you? The chocolate has no binding agents. No, what do you eat
know, a metal straw. Yeah, I do have a metal straw. I know you that I use for
know your
from one and guys guess what I'm investing in. He has a whale bone straw
with
no, I do not have a reed straw that I use when I go underwater and I breathe
through it when I'm hiding in the Vietnamese war.
I am buying a reverse osmosis filter so that I can stop drinking tap water.
What is that? I don't know you don't know what it is. I really don't know
it's a bread. No, it's not a bread. It is a fire. Nope. It goes under your sink and
it goes. It does your water three times and then it pops it back three times so
that you can drink it. You can drink it anyway, but it's bad for you. Tap water
is one of the greatest inventions in the world and people want to talk about how
if you like cancer, I love cancer. Well, then I join there. Remember the last I
sent to you guys last night. There being two stores,
there's a store in our neighborhood called I Like Food and then there's a...
I've been there a bunch of times. I've never been there. It's good. It looks
good. I Like Food. I Like Food. Is it a grocery store? No, it's a
restaurant. It's food in a bar, but they got a good sandwich. I remember
having a good sandwich the one time. It's called I Like Food. And when you
get the food for takeout, they put a sticker on your bag that says
I Like Food. That's a great name for a restaurant. And a little cartoon
So that's called I like food and then I found another, I found another store last night.
I think I was looking up I like food because me, when me and Noah moved in together, we
saw that place and we thought it was so funny.
I was looking it up, I typed in I and then it was I like food and under it was a store
called, a barber shop called I had cancer.
I immediately thought, I was like, oh yeah, these are sister stores.
the best store that me and cam have seen is the Sopranos Barbershop. Oh yeah,
that is very funny. Sopranos Barbershop. I do like that one. Wait, what was that
one?
There is a store in our neighborhood that's literally called like Most Amazing
Chinese Massage or something like that. Yeah.
There's Happy Bebe 100. Oh, Happy Bebe 100. That's a good store. Happy Bebe
100. Happy Bebe 100. With a star in the middle in the name. Yeah. Yeah,
that's cool. There's a place with... This is not a store name, but my
my favorite my favorite misspelling on a sign is there's a place there's an ice
cream place
that they have well. First of all, they have on you have a picture that says
ice cream with cheese and it has ice cream in it with a bunch of melted
cheese,
but in their flavors they have instead of rum raisin, it says rum rising
there's
Dunkin Donuts, no G. Dunkin. Yeah, that's what the hell is up with that.
You spelled the name Duncan wrong. Yeah, exactly. Either goes D-U-N-C-A-N or
Dunking. Yeah, you know, you don't split the difference. No, no, no, no. I was
looking for that. There's like, I gotta find that massage parlor, but it's the
funniest name. Why? You gonna get a massage? I do need a massage from a big
early guy. I want just a lumberjack to step on my back till it breaks so I can
finally... You don't really want that. End all this pain in my body. Can I get
you in the gym? I don't know. That's a no. Can you get me in the gym?
Me and Cameron are already in the gym. You guys go to the gym. I have to end
that Planet Fitness membership I keep getting. I've been trying to call...
That is crazy. We've been... For as long as we've been doing the podcast,
you have not made one phone call or gone on the website. I have. They shut
down the one that I you can do it online. We can also remember also years ago. We
showed you
hard to if you're lazy. Yeah, yeah, you know what? You know what I did try to
shut it down, but then I went to that planet fitness down the street
for a day and then that justified me still have the only thing that that
planet fitness is good for is when you get off the train, you have to pee so
bad your bladder and burners and you go inside and you pee and your jeans. But
This thing is I got that planet fitness card. I have the planet fitness black
card, so I can go to any planet fitness in the country and also I get access.
It's 20 bucks a month, 25 a month. You could have two Netflixes. Yeah, but you
can have two separate, one where you watch girl shows and one where you watch
boy shows. So the recommendations go, don't get mixed up. Here's the thing
about
spa access.
They don't have a spa. They don't have one here. They don't have one here, but
the one in Manchester, New Hampshire did have a table.
I bet that spot was bumping.
It was like a massage thing.
Oh, the water massage.
You had to pay extra for that.
Yeah, and I paid extra for it.
Why don't you just go to my gym has a steam room, buddy.
I'm thinking maybe.
I'm on third.
I should go to the gym, but I don't like, I don't think I'd
like who I'd become if I went to the gym.
You like who you are right now?
if I got really if I if I
will know him strong. Everybody always says like I can't go to the gym. I
don't want to get insanely. It's so funny. It's like
what do you think it's like going to the gym? You know how hard it is to
do that? I don't want to get muscles, but I do
but he is insanely. Yes, we are going to get Cameron scary rib. Yeah, and
with his frame, he will be a problem. Yeah, he gonna be a problem on the
court.
I don't think he gonna. I think that if I got like abs at all, I could
dunk right now. I think people would look at me different. I think I bet I don't
mean this is an insult. I bet you have a two inch vertical leap
this high is high. I think that you could jump. Let's I'm actually not sure
how high my vertical cameras that I have a I could do a really good long. We'll
get a Cameron Joe. Okay, I could jump really far. I think I know after we're
done recording, we'll go in the back yard. Maybe I could pull the and we'll
do a jumping. I'll do a jumping contest, a jumping competition. I think I
I can't jump that. I think you're probably right. I'm very inflexible
legs. Yeah, see that's why we're going to flex them up. Yeah, I'm pretty sure I
broke my toe yesterday. Why are you doing? What skating? Oh,
you know how bad my last showed you yesterday. You ever think about you?
I broke my fast this morning with honey nut Cheerios. Do you ever think about
your poor mother
sitting at home, worrying about you wearing a negligee right with a really
low cut looking out the window, lighting a can seven that's seven PM.
One is starting to say yeah. All I think about is getting changed behind one of
those Asian privacy.
Our phone won't stop buzzing because I'm sending a real Moji's exactly one every
ten seconds.
Do you ever think about that? Do you ever think about her sitting there in
the living room? She has her snapchat location on I'm seeing exactly where she
is on the map. I keep calling her and she keeps being like, please, you have to
stop calling me. I'm waiting for a call from my son from the hospital.
Do you ever think about so what I'm saying is, do you ever think about how
you are ruining my game by making your stupid mom worry about you all day and
night because you're out there skateboarding?
I don't give a shit.
Damn when I am your stepdad, things will be very I'm sending her subway
surfer screen shot. You think you think this middle finger is bad now. If you
my stepdad, you'd be getting it way worse. You'd be in a fucking full body cast if I
was your stepdad. If you were my stepdad, you'd try to send me to boarding school.
I would literally, if you had a car, get sugar in the gas tank. You would be
waking up every day, you'd put on your slippers, there'd be a razor blade in
it. Every single day, I go to my own gas tank and you siphon the gas out.
So I get... Oh, and I'm doing that every day regardless of what you put in it.
So one day, "Oh, nice surprise, there's sugar in it. It tastes great today."
- Shampoo would have hair loss stuck in it.
- What fucking hair do I have to lose?
What shampoo do I use?
I'm the perfect stepdad.
I was made in a machine to be your father.
- No.
- Yes, I'm a year older than you.
Which gives me supreme authority.
- We're the same age.
- Oh, what age are you?
- You were born in '97.
- Oh, wow, that makes us the same age.
What age are you?
Are you 25?
'Cause I'm 26.
Hit the air horn.
Okay, hit the...
(air horn blaring)
Yes, and you see--
only a couple of months older than you see this now yeah. What a baby little
kid thing to say you're four months old, a baby step son thing to say you're
only four months older than me step dad. He's the baby. No he's not he's a
great guy. He's the baby is born in ninety nine right. I was not born in
ninety nine fucking jewel. I love him on I was born in ninety. You need an
attitude nine and I'm putting you through the Caleb pits attitude
adjustment program. I'm the I think ninety eight is a cut off where if I was
born in ninety nine, I would be a completely different person. Yeah. And
you guys would be not like you would have a zoomer. I would have a red hair.
I would be a girl and I would have one leg. You'd have a faux hawk.
You would have a... That would be so... I mean, I can imagine it right
now. Cameron with a red faux hawk. Yes. I wanted to get him. I wanted to get
him. I wanted to get him. I wanted to get him. I wanted to get him. I
wanted to get him. I wanted to get him. I wanted to get him. I wanted to get
him. I wanted to get him. I wanted to get him. I wanted to get him. I wanted
to get him. I wanted to get him. I wanted to get him. I wanted to get him. I
and a red flannel and he's taking a photo like this. I'm so glad that I don't need
glasses, because I don't think you can do pick any glasses that are okay.
What do you mean? No, they're all bad. They're all bad. People, people,
recently I've been going for some the fact that well, the fact that you have
to make a conscious choice and the doctor can't just be like, that's right.
Fuck you. The fact that you can't just have yeah, I think your glasses are okay,
but I don't think those would look good on me.
We have a pair of glasses right over there. You can put on, but I'm saying I
these I don't look good in glass. The point the
the thing if the doctor could just prescribe you the frames yeah, that
would be the perfect thing. The thing, but the problem pick you have to be
like I think I'm going to look good. I'm going to I have to try to pull
them off yeah, yeah, the problem is something else about what whitey. I
think that whitey's and white guys. Has there ever been a white guy who has a
good beard? No, oh, no right, oh yeah, a good beard
LeBron James. No.
This is something that I've been thinking of for months.
Speaking of white guys in glasses.
And I've been waiting for a chance to say it.
I don't know any of these guys.
Chet Hanks looks good with a beard.
I don't know any of these guys, but Chet Hanks does have a pretty decent beard.
But I guess he's got a blonde beard too, which if you can pull off having a blonde beard.
That's true.
That shit looks disgusting.
But you're right that white guy beard, whitey's beards are not as good as others' beards.
It's true. It's completely true.
But speaking of white guys in glasses, there is like a centimeter difference between just
regular white guy in glasses and white pedophile. If you get frames that are just a centimeter
too big or something or the frame is like...
For me, the issue is less... Maybe it's an issue for you when you're picking out glasses
because they're going to look like a pedophile in them for me. It's more
like I'm going to look too stylish. I'm going to turn too many heads. I'm going
to be like people in the restaurant, I be tripping and dropping their frames.
You get those aviator frames on you. Yeah, like Tom Cruise. Yeah, no, he's
not looking like Tom Cruise, this guy and those in those fucking aviator.
Okay, no, I will not look like a pet. I'll look like Jeffrey Dahmer, but he
wasn't a pedophile. He's just an evil killer who was gay and you think he's
pedophile because he's gay. No, I think he's a pedophile because he's a
murderer.
Pedophiles don't usually kill pedophiles. You can call them murderers.
Yeah, they always because they just want they're pleasure all the time.
They don't have to deal with death. God, I hate them.
There's a what do you mean? What's wrong? Why do you say pleasure like
that? I was trying to think of the right word, but you were
a fire. Yeah, they have pleasure. You were saying that, like they are going
on a tropical vacation. Yeah, it's a euphemism. I also heard like a lot of
I heard I heard the girls gone.
Talk about
you'll drum.
That I heard
they don't have to care about fucking kid in the butt. Is that
what you rather say?
See
what the hell
no, that's what he that's he thinks of it.
There we go.
Yes, that wasn't cricket.
The reaction you guys yelled.
I got a rise out of you and that's honestly all I care about in
comedy is getting a rise out of people and now I don't care to
make myself laugh
pushing the envelope. It's a cool as fuck. Actually,
no, that was not a joke. You can't say fucking a kid in the butt like that.
Well, if you do that after I guess it's kind of it kind of is a joke. I guess
anything you say, this is how I feel. If I when I don't like the pedophiles for
kids in the butt,
that's how I feel when I think about it. That's how you feel. That's how wait.
That is the audience reaction to you saying that you don't like it. So this
this is you talking in the audience.
No, that's what I heard.
That's what the reaction was.
Say it again and then do the right one.
A pedophile fucking a kid in the butt.
This is crass.
This is not the kind of thing I want to be doing.
It's not crass.
Say you don't like it.
It's political.
Can we not say it again, though?
I don't like that thing.
There we go.
Okay, so that makes more sense.
But in my head, when I think of that thing,
when I think about it,
Why are you thinking?
the episode is over. I don't want a shareholder meeting on the 28th.
And
I don't know, some of the 20s.
No.
28th is... But tune in on Wednesday to see the story of the swear jar. My
birthday was four days ago. Oh yeah, the swear jar. Oh wait, today's 4/20.
Oh, we didn't even smoke about it. We did the whole hour, didn't smoke a
single thing. Well, that's okay. I was pretty fried. I was fried. I was pretty fried. Okay.
Alright, bye guys.