I
Was a good clap that was a probably the best one so far
Slept so well last night that we're gonna have the best episode ever
Mind if I start the episode with a couple hashtags yeah, oh my god. Oh, okay. Well let me think about this
yes, can please say yes, going to okay, but before you I say yes, you need to be
aware that this is what is going to when people are looking for this episode,
this will come out, yeah, when they click on the hashtag, this episode, okay, I
don't have two hashtags for today,
okay, go ahead, my hashtags are hashtag one last episode, hashtag Patrick
forever,
whoa, those are my one last episode, why Patrick forever, yeah, what is he, is
something gonna happen to me,
what are you saying, is something happening to me, no, they're separate
they don't have to do with each other. Even individually I don't like them.
Can I say one hashtag also?
Hashtag one last time.
I don't like these hashtags. Hashtags keep going for quite some time.
Yeah. Hashtag one last time. Hashtag one last one.
One last time in here.
Hashtag RIP Petunia Fish.
Who's that? John Mulaney's dog.
Oh, God. Wait, the dog that was in all the videos?
The dog that was in all the stand-up specials and stuff.
The stand-up movies? That just kills me.
yeah, just because I am his dog
and I died. Yeah, well,
well, that's one of those. What kind of dog is that a pug? That
is one of those dogs that only lives to be seven years old. I
think a French bulldog. Yeah, they know. No, these ones live
forever. Really, but they die violent, awful deaths because
they're they're 10 years of the last 10 years of their lives
are so bad. They're sniffling the first two years. The first
two years of their lives are fine. And then the rest of their
lives, they can't breathe at all. They had they have their
their noses are so clogged that they have like a pressure differential inside
their body and they explode like an airplane. You reach a certain age like a
doctor. I am a doctor. Oh my God, you're right. You are a doctor, but okay, so we
did the
microphone. Juvia, here's a hashtag for you. What hashtag get a life
to who and why? So what is up with? What does that have to do? Patrick, not
forever, Patrick for no time, Patrick for one last time, Patrick, hashtag one
last because he's done. I
I had a actual prophetic dream last night. Oh yeah, I had a it was the
craziest thing ever. I had a dream that
I had to go into detail to show just say what it's the broad stroke. Okay,
the broad strokes are
I had a dream that
I needed to talk to somebody about something and I thought that it was
and you can go a little you're a little bit
at
we're moving to a new place. We're moving to a new office and I and the
landlord basically
wanted
or I needed to
I don't know. I don't know. I
we need to talk to somebody. I had to the old tenants. I we didn't even need.
I didn't know that I needed to talk to them, but I had a dream that I went over
to the old tenants at the place and I talked to them and I figured out that we
can. I figured I chopped it up with them and I got along really, really well and
then we were able to move in in the time where we originally wanted to yeah,
which didn't seem like an option as of yesterday, which and the reason that it
didn't seem like an option was because supposedly we had to talk to these
people
and we not even that we had to talk to them, but they didn't want us. Yeah,
that early, because there was a firewall that needed to be built. They were
building a firewall, because they thought we would hack them and then I
woke up
and as soon as I wake up, I get a call from the future landlord, who's a very
smart guy and I get a call from him and I answer and he basically says the
entire thing is solved instantly, because I think that I in my dreams,
because you talk to the which that I talk to the old tenants yeah, which was
the thing that was the obstacle. I have a feeling that in your dream, I want to
I and now I want to get their phone number, call them up and say remember
what was your dream last night.
Let's go and say remember me
what was from your dream. What was your dream last night? Tell me right now,
don't say my name just because also I don't want to influence them and say
yeah, I'm going to be the future tenant because then they might make up. So
you have to be a stranger to them. Yeah, to call and be like I need to we
need to dress up like oh, I'm with I'm with National Grid and we're going to
come out and check on what your dream was. What was your dream last night?
What we need to do is when the first day that we move in, we paint ourselves
like a translucent blue, right? Like we're forced ghosts. We'll figure it
out. Okay. And we walk around there in the halls of the building and just
walk by a window that they have or something, just look in.
So they think like, "Oh shit, I just saw a ghost."
Right? So then when they see us... Make it so they see our face. So they
think they're having a prophetic vision of us. Yeah, yeah. And then...
Oh, I get it. Yeah, see them and we're not blue anymore. Yeah, so I thought
you were saying we just dress up like ghosts and then ask them still if they
had a dream last night. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
we're not going in, we're not going in like like ghost of Christmas past,
we're going in, you know, it's ghost of Christmas future. What's crazy is I
actually had a a prophetic experience this week as well, and I didn't think
much of it until I heard about yours. Mine is less but less cool, but it's
just I think reality is breaking down around us maybe, but so what happened
I went to see the new evil dead movie with Alex okay, and while the previews were
playing, I made it. I had a I had my book in my pocket. I was reading on the
subway. My book was Wuthering Heights. I was reading it and I was making a joke
to Alex. It's like I'm going to read this book during the movie and I took out. I
showed him the book right. Silly joke funny and then the movie start very
funny joke. The movie starts
the movie opens on a character sitting down and reading and what book is that
character reading Wuthering Heights and then there's a part of the movie where
where the character reads from the book that you could have read along. I
could have read a lot. I could have found the page and read along. You
stand up in the
guys hold the
but it was pretty crazy. By the way,
and you know what's scary about this prophetic experience is that moments
later that character's scalp was ripped off. So you're looking around behind
you, checking the seat behind you all of a sudden, some little kid is pulling
on the back of his head.
Tomahawk
happening about your head. I'm sorry. Can I just do this real quick? I will say
that is my version of the subway surfer with the with the family guy things as I
go and watch a Suspiria and you and I watch and I have a book underneath me. I
do that at home. Sometimes I put on a movie of already seen and I read a book.
Yeah, the movie is back. That's just the smart version. It's how you accumulate
information. It's how you make links between media absolutely and I'll be
listening. It's the only way that your brain can connect like the movie Star
Star Wars with the novelization of star. That's why I in separate that's why I
always am reading that if there's a book that gets turned on a movie, I have to
read the book while I watch the movie. The problem with the novelization of
like the move like Star Wars and stuff is like you do have to posit because
there's a lot of deleted scenes like bigs dark lighter on Tatooine. Don't
know what is that Luke's friend who dies and they have no in the original movie.
They have like no build up. He just like meets him at the rebel Academy and then
in that he plays a much bigger role.
They're supposed to be like a cool action figure of him and stuff.
He's going to be like a cool guy.
He is a cool name.
What does this have to do with books?
There's a deleted scene in the book.
The novelization. You just wanted to talk about it.
You just wanted to say that.
I mean the cool, the Star Wars book,
The Splinter of the Mind's Eye, did you ever read that?
No, I saw the sequel.
The graphic novel. Well I read that.
You saw it? I saw a picture of it.
I saw it on a bookshelf. Yeah, I saw a picture of it.
That's the one where they hired whatever his name is to write a sequel novel before the
movie came out.
So it's like Divergence.
But the funny thing about it is that because Leia and Luke, or they didn't reveal that
Leia and Luke were brother and sister yet.
So the Splinter of the Mind's Eye, the whole book, they're like falling in love with each
other and kissing each other.
Oh yeah.
That's so sweet.
And then like Luke is training Leia to be a Jedi and shit.
Yeah.
And they're completely in love.
And then the next movie came out and they were brother and sister.
We need to make a cover of that is Darth Vader and then Leia with a like a purple lightsaber
or whatever.
I don't remember my cover.
I think the mind's eye.
Mara Jade Skywalker has the purple lightsaber.
We need to make a Wookiee Pedia Dramatica.
Yeah, we do.
Dude, that'd be so sick.
Wouldn't that be cool?
Wookiee Pedia Dramatica.
And we're just like, and the Wookiees are gay.
Yeah.
And 50 gay Ewoks had butt sex on the fuck planet.
You guys realize that Ewok is an anagram for woke?
Whoa.
Okay, there's a lot of things that we say on this show that are kind of just stupid and
funny that actually just blow my mind.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
That blew my mind.
Endor.
Ronda.
Doner.
Oh my God.
Yeah, like a kebab.
Kebab.
Doner kebab.
Why'd you say kebab?
Because that's how they say it.
Like a kebab.
That's how they say it in the show.
What the hell is going wrong with you?
Kebab.
Anagram.
Bobca.
Bread.
little guy with a big nose, Turkish guy who'd hit. Oh yes, he yes car. The video
I do remember the bat. You remember him? Luke anagrammed to
yeah. So his name is cool. Skywalker.
Cue Skywalker
and Skywalker Sky Clawer
squawk.
Wait, my God, there's so many. The truth is revealed on solo. Guess what?
that's an an a anal holy shit on solo shanel, so
it's all what the fuck you're right.
This is scaring me. There's so many anagrams in star wars. What's the
Voldemort one? What's his middle name in that?
Marvolo Tom Tom Marvelo yeah,
that they just had to fill in the middle where they're like Tom. We got riddle
fuck
- Marfolo.
(laughing)
- It's the stupidest, there's this kid,
I did the high school film festival thing in high school,
and the dude who beat my short film,
it was a movie called Revolution.
- It was a movie?
- It was a short film called Revolution,
and the whole thing, the whole,
(laughing)
The thing it was like it's like a news article or whatever, and it's like
graffiti has been popping up all over town and the graffiti is just the word
no vile route.
End of the movie is that coming together in the same way as like the Harry
Potter thing, and then it just spells revolution. I was like, Oh,
I fucking wonder what no vile route meant. That is no vile.
What was your short film about? It was about a puppy bowl tailgater.
Pretty fucking epic puppy bowl. Tail. Okay.
The guy who tailgates the puppy bowl. Do you still have this video? I do still have the video.
Can I see this soon? Yeah. It's not online? No, it's online somewhere.
But I entered it into the film festival.
Somebody else did because the person, it was like we were in groups in the classroom and this kid
was like, "Do you want to join up in our group?" I was like, "Okay, yeah, because I don't know
anyone in that class that well." And then I found out that he only had me in there because I had no
no one else in the group and then he was trying to ask out the other girl who was in the group
and then the group dissolved and then I had to make the whole short film within like a
day.
Creative differences.
You used to rule the school with my videos on.
I was in stuff too.
In the morning I'd go to P.E.
I lost the fan vote.
Play dodgeball and jump and roll.
I was second place.
Second place fan vote.
Wow.
cheerleaders in the crowds of singing the quiet class in home room science
and math. I'm sleeping
the bell is ringing yeah yeah, here we go in the Mr. Peters calling
my
principal. Peter just called my name
because I hate this school and one day I'll rule the world
and one day I'll kill my brother. That's about a classmate. I prequel it's the
prequel to Viva La Vida. Yeah, it's Viva La School Viva La School Viva La School
days eating at school.
It's a good idea.
What else did I want to talk? Oh,
no, I forgot it again. It's was it something about me. It probably was
because you're the main character of my life and I think about you all day and
night.
>> Well, you pointed at me, you went like, oh.
>> It's just a habit I have.
>> Yeah.
>> Point to point.
>> I point to people, too. I think I go like, oh.
>> Oh, I hate graffiti. You were saying graffiti. I hate it.
>> Why do you hate graph?
>> I think it's--
>> Why do you hate writers?
>> I hope I never see graffiti again as long as I live.
>> Bro.
>> I don't ever need to see it.
>> It kind of turns my stomach when I see somebody put graffiti on the fresh wall
of a business.
what you guys need to do. Fresh, by the way, F R E S H. None of that
H R E C S H. What you guys need to do right now.
Go on to Amazon dot com prime ship at two copies of Mark Echoes getting up.
Actually, no, you can buy it on steam. Go home by Mark.
I hope Mark Echoes gets out in the gallows and then we drop him through
that little square and you can find out the whole twisted world of amazing
photography. I was rather put a star in my gallows yeah and the hole where they
fall through instead of a square that be like a star. I would do it like a bronze
die cut pasta and I come out the other end like a different shape. I would do.
I would get it. I'd get it make a cast of the person who was dying. I make it
their exact shape so that nobody can be falsely executed. So if they try and
switch out like so, so I'd put like you know what you put like put like a round
peg into a round hole deal, but I well exactly what if they put it so it was
a skinny guy and he gets a fat guy to replace him, but otherwise it works
well skinny guys that's okay. They don't have much to live for. What if
I'm not going to what if somebody's really skinny and they have put like a
baby in there and you're like well, he fits in the hole, but baby wouldn't fit
through the hole is too short. It wouldn't go all the way down. You could
put a baby. We have a perfectly fit the baby. You could put the whole baby in
the head. I guess maybe I'd build a robotic version. How does that the
perfectly thick and he's already dead? If you've already hung him into the
hole? Well, no, because it's the floor that comes out. Which one is the gallows
is that the hand? No, that's a hanging. No, the you know what I'm talking about?
That's a stockade stockade. Gallows is hanging. That's not where you're thinking
about this whole time. Tomatoes at the people in the stock. Ah, that's okay.
That's what I thought when you can put the whole baby in the head hole. I think
a lot of these stock traders up at the top should be put in our traders who
should be put in stocks.
Wait, drop a put the oh, you don't have the thing with you.
don't have the drum machine. No, we could have just let him cook for like two
minutes and we wouldn't have to do any work. That was already pretty cool
though. Yeah, I don't think they needed a beat. That was one of my better lines
for a while. Can you do like just right now, just acapella off the dome? No,
you can't make me do that shit. All right. Well, what are you doing? I just
wanted to hear him for you. I'm, you know, you just, you're tired and you
don't want to talk. I am a little tired. Mo has been ruining my sleep because he
he bites me. My sleep to make him make me feed my sleep. I've had the worst sleep
in my life for like one week and then last night I got one good night of sleep.
I put my phone in the other room at 11 o'clock. I put on, yes, I have a
sleeping mask. I put my sleeping mask. I told you about that. I put you on to
that. It's real good. I love it. I sleep with my arm covering my eyes. I love
this. It's not enough for me. It's not enough for me either. I need to get the
mom from Matilda. That's how I sleep. And then I sleep. She has a sleeping mask
that has eyes on it. And it scares Matilda.
I like that thing. I don't know if you remember...
What doesn't scare Matilda, though?
She's a bit of a fraidy cat, bitch.
She's afraid of child abuse for some reason.
She gets so scared she develops powers.
Listen, I tell you what, if my dad was fucking four foot eleven,
I would not be afraid of his bum ass.
No, I'd be rubbing, I'd be putting vegetable oil on the floor.
If Danny Rubino was my dad, I'd be tipping him over.
I'd be putting vegetable oil on the floor.
You'd rub your dad?
him when he fell down. What
why would that help you avoid being here?
He doesn't know how to hit now because he's covered in Crisco and I'm
bad dinner. If I remember correctly, not baby carrots, it's really not that bad.
Her dad's a scumbag who puts sawdust in the cars. Yeah, he's got no
read. Does the odometer yeah, he switches the
the vert was cool. It was cool. That blew my mind. Did you guys know that
Danny DeVito directed that movie. No, I was thinking of a different fact
actually.
Yeah, that's a fact that I
feel like I've learned that fact with full surprise, maybe ten times every
time I learn. I really learn. Why didn't you keep making movies man? Yeah,
that's a fact that I just autistically very remember immediately. When I saw
that when I was younger, I was like, whoa, I feel like I feel like I learn
it every year. Yeah, and I yeah, I would have believed probably because I keep
I would have sooner believed that Matilda directed that with how heroic it made
it look yeah. That's what I was saying. I was like wait. Why would this guy
direct a movie where he's the bad guy? This doesn't make any sense at all to
me. I want to see I want to see a movie from his perspective. I knew yeah. I
heard the new Superman movies directed by Lex Luthor. No, it doesn't make any
sense. Exactly directed by Superman. Yeah,
exactly. It's so stupid. Yeah, yeah, also a movie from the dad's perspective
would be pretty good. I'm thinking his name is Frank, a movie called Frank.
Would you guys name and always that's yeah, you're thinking of always sunny,
but it might also be his name and Matilda. Now that I think about his name
is Matilda's dad in Matilda. What if that is the same universe? Whoa, why
would yeah, maybe if they have the same name, his name is Harry Wormwood,
Harry. Yeah, it's close. So it should be called Harry or maybe Wormwood.
Wormwood is good. What is good? And it's about a guy. He's got a guy just
trying to make a fucking living and then his daughter starts throwing
the electric books, Adam and shit through the fuck that and she emancipates
herself at the end of the movie exactly and I'd go what the fuck I don't want
this
yeah everybody wins at the end of that. That's what yeah Matilda at the end she
crossed her and she's like that's right. I won't let you spend any more money on
me and I won't let you feed me or clothe me or have a roof over my head anymore.
You're done yeah. I'm going to go live at the library. I can shut up go ahead.
I'm going to live with Miss Librarian. Yeah, that's right. You don't get to pay
for my education at this beautiful private school anymore. Yeah, I'm going
to go live with a damn teacher nerd. That's what I say. Okay, nerd
dork. I hope if I hope to God that I have a nerd kid who just leaves
instantly. Yeah,
that's why he was such a nerd that they learn how to emancipate themselves and
get the fuck out of that. So we're so we're all three of us are so anti
abortion that if we were in a position where we didn't want a kid, it's our
biggest hope is like well. I hope it's a really smart nerd who becomes a chess
prodigy. That's a flying machine and I never seen
goes James and the giant and I think I think I'm like sit down in my living
room. I think to myself like he's probably in China right now or something,
but no he fell into the ocean exactly, but you at least get to do this. Yeah,
I get to imagine him like the end of Dark Knight Rises. If my kid did some
James and the giant peach it, I would I would step up and be his dad, because
it looks fun as hell. Do you guys ever think about how fucking shit it would be
if you were a parent and what's the worst? Well, that, but also like what's
the worst case scenario for a parent is that you do, you have like a Casey
Anthony kind of situation. She was, well, she killed her kid. I know. Well,
that's up for debate. But what I'm saying is if like Casey Anthony, what if
your kid is just like weird and like not that bright and just crawls into
something bad and then goes missing and then all of a sudden you're on the news
because people think that you put your kid into somewhere. It's like the only
reason you're on the news is because you're because you're beautiful enough
that they want to keep the cameras on. She got a she got a BBL. I'll handle
this. You see that you guys see that case. I actually did see that. He got a
damn BBL. Yeah, that's insane. That is well. I mean, what are you going to do?
What are you going to do? What are you going to do?
No, what happened? Her BBL when it died? Yeah, I think it was more like
Oh yeah, it did. Bubbled. Yeah, this is not the kind of thing we want to talk
about. Probably not dying child. Yeah, I'm gone for one second to plug in the
laptop. You guys are doing an impression of a drowning child that actually
drowned. Well, we don't know. We don't know. It's a pretty good be in China.
Yeah, no, they found a bot. They found the bones. No, I think. Yeah, they
faked it. The baby faked it. They've I think that's what I'm talking about.
I'm talking about you have a Matilda style kid who's really, really smart.
what's to keep them from not faking their death from getting a couple of dog
bones and shaving down the head exactly and then that you're pulling their teeth
on that and you're fucking,
you know, whittling down the dog skull. It looks kind of like them replacing
the
replacing bores or it's like yeah. This is inconclusive fucking long.
Yeah,
my child skull, they find that they find the skeleton. It's got a collar on, but
you replace the the tags. It's as you
you put it in the laundry yeah now I'm going to jail
put like a week on it yeah. Meanwhile, this kid is has found a civilization in
the center of the earth or something and well this king this kid moves the
fucking Taiwan. He's the next dali. You turn on the news like like forty years
later and he's the president of some with that. How much does that have to
suck to have your kit you you birth your kid and then like two years in you
never be like. I kind of think he's going to be the
sucks. Damn it, that would suck. I
would love to
to father the white Dalai Lama. Yeah, that would be maybe the well. Is that a
rule that the Dalai Lama has to be born in a spoken rule that it has to be
Taiwanese? I want maybe they spoke it or maybe it isn't a rule at all. Has
there been a white? Anyway, the point is I would love to be a father to the
great Dalai Lama. There will be especially when my birth to it when my
kid grows up and he's like the adult Dalai Lama is doing all the dollar and
I'm just sitting. I'm sitting in my armchair at home. I'm watching to be
like that's my boy.
You're hoping for a shout out like he's a
and one more thing I'd like to thank my dad for showing me how to sit quietly
for a long
yeah. When he like I see him on the TV, he's asking another kid to suck his
song. I'm calling him like you can always come home. You know, yeah, no
matter what you do, we love you. I know you didn't do that.
You're
you have like the first white Dalai Lama and he's doing right guard extreme
commercials.
He's like he's like yeah, I'm in a roller derby thing. It's like look. I
do sit around all day pretty quiet, but that doesn't mean I don't sweat a
fuck ton. I made
be rink he'd be like yeah, he'd be like he'd be on the TV and a commercial be
like
yeah, I don't I may be the dog a long, but I don't like these busted as robes.
That's what we're adidas yeah
or he would come out with a line of his own adidas roads. Oh my God, he comes
out with like
is the ropes with the
stripes, the stripes all the way up to be so hard. I'll be so hard. Then
they're kind of like he has a ration. He has Bart beads, yeah, art beads yeah.
what he was a part of. He understood. Oh, I get it now. I don't understand even a
little bit. I don't know shit about the Dalai Lama. I know he's bald as fuck and
wears tiny glasses. My Dalai Lama son would not be bald. He would have long
ass hair. Take your hat off. Oh my God.
Oh my, I never even considered. Holy crap. That the white Dalai Lama might be
here right now.
who knows he might be amongst us.
Whoa, that's kind of do I look exactly like the Dalai Lama? Can we get like a
robe?
At what point is this not good?
Wait a minute, that's nasty. Here's a dirty shirt, a dirty shirt, so you wrap
it around. Yeah, I need the back side of it.
Oh, my God,
I kind of I dig the logo on your. I kind of feel like this is a bad
got him offensive Gandhi costume. What do you mean or something? No, you're the
white Dalai Lama. I don't know. I don't feel good about this. You guys made me do
this. I didn't know it was pet. Pat made me do this. He handed me so many things.
You look no, no, no, no, no, because he have a gong. They're
coming.
They're replacing him soon because of him, like sucking on little kids. I think
the only way they replace him is if he has to die and they already have chosen
the next one, by the way. Really? They already chose him? He's like nine years
old, yeah.
Really? Are you lying? No, no, no. There goes my dreams of coaching you. The guy,
the current Dalai Lama goes and finds the other Dalai Lama and says, "You're
me." You're, okay. "You're me, so you'll become him." Yeah, but what if he does
like a trade up now that he's seen you in your robe and your little glasses?
He's like, "Oh, I was mistaken." I don't think that, I think that the Dalai
Lama, you know how people always say that? You don't think he listens? You
don't think he watches every week? I just don't think he has that much money,
so I don't really want to become him. I want to be the first on a llama.
We think he's a broke hoe. I want to become the host of at midnight. I want
to be a a community. That's what I'm saying, though. You can just be the
Dalai Lama and do that stuff. Yeah. In fact, you're more likely to get on TV
shows. If you're that, that's your that's kind of they say we're looking
for people who can bring a unique perspective and bring a kind of story
that Dalai Lama story that that is that people can relate. Yeah. How about a
cartoon about being a Dalai Lama? Yeah, yeah, exactly. That's a good idea.
that it's a really good car to about being the now that he's like on the
kid's tongue. It's
punching up to make a TV show like the one they made about the British Royal
family. If you make one, I think he was always weird. People mostly just didn't
like him because he did, but that's I think that's the that's the
people didn't like it. I know the people didn't like him because of some stuff
like some like you know stuff about like warring countries or whatever like
of the country want to be free. Which I do not care about that at all. I don't even know
what those countries are called. I only know countries based on if their food is different.
That's the only thing that I know. If they have different barbecue, Turkish barbecue,
British barbecue, Korean barbecue. Korean barbecue is my number one. That's why I think
that's the greatest country in the world. American barbecue as well. I think it's probably
Korean and then American and then there's a bunch of other countries. No, shut the fuck
countries, then there's a bunch of other countries. Oh, no. Okay. So you think
Korean barbecue is number one. Meanwhile, guess what they do in America? They cook
the food for you.
Oh, you know what? Good point. In Korea, you have to do it yourself. I think
Korean barbecue is number two. And you have to use scissors. Yeah. Fuck that. I
forgot, 'cause I-, the only time that I eat Korean barbecue is when it's-, you
know, it's-, it's 'cause it comes from North Korea. They can't afford a kitchen.
Exactly. They don't let-, they don't, yeah. You have to-, yeah, you have to do
it yourself. The only time I eat Korean barbecue is when it's, like, a new
limited time a thing at McDonald's limited time edition thing limited
edition meal at McDonald's yeah McDonald's Korean barbecue that's what
you're going with right now yeah I think the last time I had Korean barbecue
with that one think we all got Korean barbecue together in Boston yeah that
was maybe the last time I got it that was ages oh my god yeah we took pictures
of the red napkin I don't remember that we got a lot of oil on the napkin cuz he
he was wiping his face a lot. I took a lot of pictures.
Why do you remember a detail like that? That's crazy.
'Cause you have hair in the photo. You just scared me. What? You guys know I
remember shit like that? That is such a crazy detail to remember.
We thought it was really funny that we were taking pictures of us holding up
our napkins like it was like a trophy. Like we were like, "Clean Plate Club,"
we're holding up the napkins like and this was it. I don't remember years ago.
Yeah, yeah, that is I'm a photo. You are weird. How am I weird for remembering
good times? That's true that we had. I guess that's right. Yeah, the way you
know, honestly, the thing that you crossed the line into being weird is
that you said, because he was wiping his face a lot. Yeah, that was the thing.
You should yeah, yeah, definitely you can remember the photo. We can't
remember the exact like the reason why the photo exists.
why was that? Why is my face? Yeah, also I don't think you guys said that that's
just a thought you had to then was like Caleb's wiping his face a lot and you
still remember that. I don't know why I remember it, but yeah, you know what I
want us to have guys. We haven't made a memory in a long time. We haven't. I
want to go. What are you talking about? We I guess you guys don't think about
our friendship the way that I think about it. You think about it pretty much
every week. What's our last memory? What's our last three of us crazy
experience? I feel like we've had a lot of we've had a lot of duos duos
memories coffin club for sure.
Uh-huh.
So but that was like a year ago.
That was months and months and months ago.
Yeah, that's true.
I mean that was way to go.
We need to go to a sports game and get on the field.
I think we should go to a lake.
I think you're right on a pontoon boat.
Oh, we did and get we could go on a canal.
Happy dad seltzer.
Yep from the Nelk boys the Halloween show.
That's that was a big that's a show.
That's just a show.
That's not a memory.
Yeah, pure fun excursion a field trip.
I know what I used to last. You know what I do. I guess the last field
I feel exactly a field trip is what we need. Yeah, as I was
thinking about, I'm thinking about the League of Legends thing. That's the
type of thing that we need to all exactly. That's what I'm saying.
There's I feel like there's been too many
experiences that we only two of us have had. Yeah, yeah, it's like
usually I'm thinking about it. I was like we did it one last weekend.
Just me and Cameron with that drunk. We had a beautiful dance to
get there. I and we talk about that already. Our new best friend.
Yeah, you guys did that. No, we talked about it in the meeting. Okay. I the
thing is and I don't want you guys to think that I'm coming after you talk
about it because it was just he's going to use about the eyes. I am. I know
that we need to have three because we do too, but it's usually just you two and I
get completely excluded and I'm not. I don't care about who was at the League
of Legends thing. Married life. How long ago was that? I don't even know.
That's what's happening. You guys did something last weekend. Very invited to
that thing and didn't come. I don't I don't you know I don't check my mailbox.
Who was I don't know if I get invitations. Well last week, last weekend we went to a
bar that had a jukebox and Cameron gave me a dollar because he knew my last
dollar. He knew that I saw the jukebox and I got really excited. This already sounds like
movie level story that I wish that I could have been a part of. You were
we're completely invited. We played shows, not the dinosaur junior version of
just like heaven and the drunkest man in the world. They like it with us and
kept hugging me and Cameron and then was getting mad. I love you. I love you to
us and was getting mad. I know what he was doing as he was right. He was
saying I'm in love with you, which is the line in the song, but he was just
saying it all. He was said the only line song that he knew
I'm in love with you.
And then the Dinosaur Junior version cuts, you know, it goes like the last
bar.
Yeah, no, I don't know this. Okay, that's why this, that wouldn't work for
me. If you guys, if we went in and... It cuts off and then the guy,
it's switching songs to the next song, but it's taking a while 'cause it's
a CD jukebox and the guy's standing there going,
"What the fuck?" Turn the music back on, what the fuck? He's screaming at
thought that they cut the song, maybe because we were having too much fun.
Yeah, and then he flipped Cameron off and ran outside and then he came back in
and then he went out again. That's my problem, man. I'm going to a place like
that. You guys are playing songs that everybody knows and I'm trying to get
them to play Worldwide Choppers by Tech Nine and I'm wrapping it to the
bartender. Somebody played Blue Suede by Vince Staples immediately after. See,
that's what I would have had probably that moment with that guy. Yeah, yeah, I
would have been a walked up blue sway, blue sway, the blue flight. No, I would
we've probably done out of the throw back rap or
Caleb would have been walking around waiting for somebody to sing with
them. Just blue swine, blue swine, blue swine. Here's who I am at the
jukebox. We should go to a sports game or a lake or a museum. I
don't think a museum... We should go to a museum and play pranks on
everybody. I think we need to go right back to Coffin Club in Corpse
Paint again. And here's what we need to do. We need to all go to
the jukebox and cue up that one Dr. Dre song and then say, "Smoke
weed every day at the wrong part of the song, all in unison. And I'd be like,
"Oh, smoke weed every day. We need to do that." That is so cool to do that.
Yeah.
See, that's why I love touch tunes so much. You know what my favorite
public prank at a place is? What? My little prank that makes me laugh every
time that's so dumb is I go to... What if I go to a place and it's
crowded, like a store or something, just really loudly saying to whoever I'm
with being like, "Yeah, it's so sad that this place is closing down.
guy. I'm just glad we got to come here before it closes
for people to over
that it like F A O short
random
it really gets me. Every mom and pop stores with only one employee.
It's so sad they're demolishing this play
man, just because I know it doesn't nobody. It doesn't mean anything to
anybody. It's not tricking anybody. It just it's so sad. What I'm going to do
here next week
(laughter)
That's so sad.
It's so sad what I have in this backpack.
(laughter)
It's so, so sad.
Oh, man. I don't want to put it in the bathroom. I don't want to put this backpack in the bathroom
in my home.
But I have to.
I have to do it. The voice is telling me to.
Yep. Sorry. I hope that we get another son of Sam soon in New York City.
Yeah. Oh, we will.
Sam Kinison, I hope.
The son of Sam Kinison.
(laughter)
That's actually a pretty good idea. I like that idea.
That is a good idea.
That's actually a pretty good idea.
Yeah.
And I like that idea.
That's a good idea.
He's walking around, he's doing new, updated for the times, kind of woke kind of stuff.
Sam K-
My partner!
Ahhhh!
No, if Sam Kinesson was here, he would be the opposite of woke.
Dude, he would be demolishing all these blue haired fuckers.
He would be out there with his fingerless gloves and his long hair and his shapely body.
Uh huh.
He looked like the onion from-
Actually, he would be woke.
Yeah, I just realized he looked like the onion from VeggieTales if you look yeah, he looks like a piece of garlic. Yeah
Elephant garlic. Yeah, really really big. Have you ever seen his SNL intro?
Did it sound like
Now Sam can I say no?
No, so he walks out and then like motions for the the band like the guitar player in the band to give him his guitar
Oh
Soloing he was so wow too cool to live
He's soloed and then does his like, he does just his stand up as the monologue and then
like, you know, then the episode starts.
One day when I host SNL, I'll probably do something like that.
Rick Moranis got his ass though.
The Rick Moranis thing is very funny.
What was the Rick Moranis thing?
Rick Moranis goes up, starts playing the guitar, then starts blowing into the guy's saxophone.
And he like goes and he starts operating the camera, he's got the camera on and then he
like, yeah, he just goes through the entire thing and does everybody's.
Dude, Rick Moranis.
That guy is very funny.
wife got his jaw slid. That's why he got his jaw slid. Because he's always in other people's
business. Well, because the cameraman, he held on to it all those years. It was either
the cameraman or the biggest Sam Kinnison fan in the world walked up to Rick Moranis
and was like, "Here's for old, here's for Sammy, bitch," and then knocked him out. He's
like, "You don't make fun of Sam Kinnison." I would love to say that to somebody. I would
love to say that to somebody. I would love to say that to somebody. Sam Kinnison death
story where he got his head decapitated in a car accident that flew 40,000 feet down
on the road and it slid until it was just like basically a little piece of hair
and then his brother was like holding the piece of hair and was like that's
not real. Yeah,
the piece of hair, I was a little ration for a mortal and then the hair moved
like this and said, Oh, my God, the light I'm going into the light. You know
that that's right. I heard that
or maybe the details aren't right, but basically he told his brother that he
was he saw some kind of light. Yeah, yeah, which gave me hope as a child.
Yeah,
that was the and you realize there and then you realize they're shunning a
the flashlight into his eyes to check if his head head, head, body, head is
concussed
you think that's what it is when people say they see the light. It's because
they see the light on the ceiling in the hospital or just realize that it's
making me scared. I think it is that or they get checked for a D U I yeah when
they're dying, because that's the first thing they should do is what do we send
out to see? Do we say that they were drunk while they were driving? I would
like to start driving driving Sam Kinson. I think that he was drugly driving on
cocaine and I thought he was in the back of a limo because of the auto the
on now he's in limbo yeah, the unlicensed autobiography can't decide
what to do and that's the only time he could ever do limbo by the way, yeah, is
if he was if he had no head yeah a lot easier. He was just a piece of hair
that's because that's what happened his head flew and as it went, I know I'm
visualizing the mortal con there literally is a mortal combat fatality and
and it was just one single hair out the very top of his hair. The peak of his
head
was just sitting there on a little piece of dandruff. Yeah, that was all that was
left of Sam Kennison and then that you know what they did a bio pic about him
that and he wanted to be alive. They said that he wanted he had to be buried
open open casket. So they basically sat that little hair in a cashew or a
pistachio shell. No, no, no, no, no, he had already bought the coffin because he
knew this was coming. So he bought a coffin for his four hundred pound body
and there's just a single piece of hair with a piece of dandruff sitting in
there and women are coming up beautiful women dress like goth goth moms that
have the veil over their head and they look like they're in a music video and
they're crying Miss murder hair, yeah, this murder, and then a really old guy
came up. I looked in the coffin and he went
to yeah and he covered him and snot well. No, it blew it away. I didn't blow
and nobody can find it and then another guy came up and he sneezed even harder
and nobody find. I think that was a me little kid me and refer. Do you think
that was a damn rack of cocaine? I heard it was a brain cell and he was alive all
the way until he got buried, but then little kid me. I was at the funeral in
nineteen eighty nine and after the old man sneezed, they served hors d'oeuvres
they don't know, and so I'm eating my mini burrito right and I take a bite.
Oh, my God, what the hell is a hair? It's called a to keto. What the hell is
moving around my body? Oh, my God, it's climbing into my stomach. It's going up
my spine and I'm gonna crash when I get old. I basically became the Dalai Lama
style Sam. I thought that's why you were bald, because it rejected that hair and
it all the hair shot out of your head. I didn't want any hair in your body
anymore.
How does that make any sense? He's got one really long blonde pube. That same
can't even have pubes.
wouldn't that be cool if you just didn't have any pubic at all? Yeah, I mean you
can get a laser. I'm starting to get so old. How old are you? My pubes have
started leaving my pubic area. They've started going down my legs like I'm,
like I'm dropping them. I've had that problem my whole life. I mean this whole,
I just started getting that. You've seen, I mean you guys have seen my legs and
shorts, you know, my legs are really... I don't tend to look at your legs and
records. Hey buddy, you should look without a barf bag because it looks
like without my x ray glasses
and you're looking at my penis or my extra regular
size. The extra can you on you? If I worked at a massage parlor, yes, I
would walk. I always saw you walking down the street. I would literally
lure you in and I would comb your entire body with a lice comb just to make it
you're really smooth. You know the really thin comb. I want to wax your
entire self until you look do if I if I know I want them to look like that would
be the most painful. I want to know that you know the that Air BnB commercial
where they have the monsters that have the hair. No, I you'd look like that.
Some people might have seen this commercial dude loves Air BnB so much.
This guy can't get a watcher fucking enough of Air BnB. Hell watches TV like
it comes on and on to be yes. Oh yeah, that's TV
to be. No everything's hunky dory with your hair, but I would like to rip it
off, which if anyone works for to be who's listening here, hit me up hit up
Cameron for a movie idea, hit me up for giving me everything.
If anybody works for to be hit me up for giving me everything I've ever
wanted, yep, making my dreams come true. I've I've I've seen the things that to
be send people and I want them. Okay, if you work it to be, I want them now. If
you work it to be, I'm going to yield my message that you send me and give
another one to Cameron. If you were to send messages to people to be they do
coded messages, then they send somebody like a big I've seen some I've they've
seen they send some incredible gifts to people and I really want okay to be if
you're listening,
here's my idea to be inner tube for the summer that you guys would not believe
this stuff. It's a thousand times better than an inner tube. Here's what I want
to
I'm employed right now.
Look at my hands.
I don't know that I would even say perennially.
I would say year-round maybe.
Look at my hands.
Look at how-
Alert.
Podcast about list is about to issue a correction.
Cameron here.
It really hurts me to have to do this, but I need to issue a correction for today's episode
and I need to apologize to Caleb.
I made a mistake when I corrected him about the word perennial.
I was thinking about a flower blooming and unblooming and it led me to make a mistake
and perennial actually does mean the thing that he said that it meant.
And in the heat of the moment, I corrected him falsely, and I feel really bad about it.
So please, Caleb, accept my apology, and please, listeners,
accept my apology as well for providing false information.
What's up, guys? It's Caleb from Podcasts About Lists,
just checking in to say I accept the apology.
I'm a hard worker. Wow. There's scabs. Yeah, that's a stigmata right there. I'm lifting
stuff all day. I get scabs on my hands. I have those. I have. Oh my God, why are my
hands yellow? Simpson cigarettes. Yeah, that's probably cigarettes. You don't that's bologna.
I haven't smoked in. You don't smoke. I saw somebody smoking a cigarette with one glove
stuff to hold the cigarette. You know, he used to do that. You know, he used to do
that was
yeah,
well, she had both gloves. Well,
what's that guy's name? Peter? I wear a glove on one hand to smoke a cigarette,
and then I like love on the other hand, it's because I handle a lot of asphalt.
Peter Cushing had a little white smoking glove that he would wear on the set of
Star Wars. That's sick, yeah, that's so cool to be like that guy who like looks
perpetually like a I play. I played smoking glow Dracula in a movie. Yeah, I
do a Christian bale type thing where I would be transforming for the role, but
I would get actual fangs in my head and I would never get rid of them ever. Do
you ever think white you get like I would get white whites as well. The
whites of your eyes like and I'll get my skin whitened because I don't think I'm
pale enough to sell Dracula. I think that I don't think people would believe that
I was directly. I think that you are beyond the pale. No, I don't think I'm
he's pale enough to play. Hey, hey, ease up on that. Don't you dare say he's
beyond the pale. Sorry. Not bad. Don't you dare. That is our friend. You're
before the pale. Thank you.
I'm gonna get very pale to play Dracula. That implies that there's something
that's gonna happen. I think that you could play Dracula. Honestly, I think we
should... Not without my fangs and with... Not without my skin being paler.
I have... Oh, no shit will do... Oh, I lost my fangs. No shit will do stuff
to you, to make you... No shit will do stuff to me? Will make you look like
Dracula. Oh, no shit will do stuff. I think that we will we will make a
Dracula movie. Yeah, I need you need a black widow's peak. I have a black hair
peak.
You are the furthest thing from Dracula. You are Dracula's number one food item.
You are literally the value meal that Dracula would eat every single day. I
have a Dracula. I have a full Dracula costume. No, but you just don't look like
him. You have a beard. You're too. You're too. Just
you too stocky to be dry stocky yeah. You know what I always think about here's
something I was thinking about
what stocky stocky your big boned
that's the what that's that's true. I didn't say you're too portly.
I would never say that
you're too stocky to play dracula. You have to your shoulders are too broad.
Okay, you're too masculine to play dracula. I guess there we go that worked.
what about wolf man? I could play a will. You could play a no man. I could be
you're not sure man last night. I do I could you I take my shirt off. I look
like damn wolf man and I could be the human baby.
You'll be good bride of Frankenstein. Yeah, you get the big you'd be good
baby new year, baby. New Year does not have the definition that I have on my
core. I mean you could be like baby new year on a pride float. I could
Okay, so you mean you're thinking then magic Mike that I could be mad, you
know, you know what also you could do really well. You could play a really
good phantom of the blink fitness.
I don't go to
that's well you that's a movie. You don't actually have to go there. It's a
J. Well, you basically would be a fucking phantom of the mean
there's some club for rude people.
Oh, it's okay. Hey, buddy, what turn back around? I'm
fish tank. I'm going to miss all this. You know,
I'm going to type on this and it's going to be said, you remember this thing?
What
from before? I remember that. I remember that.
Broken.
Let's see the lights in these died a long time ago, but I just never fixed it.
We were going to put something into there.
Never did that.
I'm going to miss this guy.
We're killing him.
We're not able to take him.
He's just in this.
The plasma ball is completely destroyed.
We need to get a new one.
Look, it still works.
Look how bad it looks now.
It's because it's been on all day.
It looks really sad.
I'm just going to miss this whole place.
You know what? This set was a great big experiment.
big experiment. Yep. And now the next one is going to be a circus. Yep. Oh, a
circus, a clown circus. I think that's a really good idea. Yeah. I'm still
thinking about what kind of thing to do. Yeah, I'm still thinking, I'm thinking
circus or maybe... I've been kind of lobbying for Wild West. Yeah, Wild West
would be fun. Yeah. I think I'm gonna rewatch Westworld. Guys, I have the
perfect idea what what if it's just like a dope hangout place? Oh, that a tree
house, a Nintendo sixty four, I think a basement tree house, a basement of a
tree house with nerd shit all over the place. Yeah post does yes and a flat a
flat screen TV that plays halo plays red versus blue clip. Wait post us and
video game cartridges, dope ass aesthetic that we are custom with faces on them
with a turntable and frame Pokemon cards
and records. Oh my God framed of every trading card ever and framed of every
Chris Nolan movie in a line. My God, except for this Oppenheimer one,
because it's to
yeah to SJW and also to new. They don't make it on DVD and even then they
probably make it on day one when they buy that when they make that on DVD. I'm
buying ten. Is that as I know that price is going to go up? Is that movie black
black and white? I think so. I'm pretty excited for it. I want to see colors though. I bet
the explosions will go into color. Sin City style, the explosion is full color. Better
Call Saul style. It'll be Wizard of Oz. I just finished it. And the complete spoiler
is that Better Call Saul, the final episode was long. An hour and nine minutes. I tried
to trick Cameron into thinking that he had a kid.
You completely tricked me.
And it didn't work.
It didn't work.
Did it?
I believed it.
You did?
No, I did not believe it.
Why would I believe he has a kid?
What does that mean?
I don't know.
I thought maybe you would believe that him and kids get away.
Do you know what's funny?
The one time that I made up a fake, I made a joke fake spoiler, when Patrick said he
didn't watch the episode of Succession yet, the one where Logan dies, that's out again,
we're going to spoil that again.
I texted him and I said, "Guess what, spoiler, the dragon dies."
but it was before I was watching the episodes before Logan died in the
episode. So that isn't that kind of prophetic a little bit. So we've been
having prophetic attacks to our to our bodies. Yeah, something I've been having
something, a tax allergies. My allergies have been so fucked. Today was the first
day of allergies from really this past like a week or two has been like you
saw. You saw me on Monday, right? I was I was a shell of myself. I think it's
because I haven't been smoking. I think that smoking protected me from allergies.
Uh-huh.
And now that I'm not smoking, I've just been being attacked.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I did a set on Monday where I was asleep the whole time.
No, you just bombed.
I bombed because I was asleep.
You were wide awake, you just didn't do very well.
I was like this.
No, you were awake.
I was half awake.
I don't think so.
It was my allergies and I took Benadryls.
I think that you just...
[whistles]
You know?
know just bombed. Well, it happens. Yeah, and I'm blaming the allergy. Okay. Yeah. No, that's
fine. But you have to say you were asleep. I was pretty much asleep. No, you were wide
awake. Yeah, I talked to you before and after you seemed alert. Well, it was my Benadryls
that did that. I believe that I believe it. It threw me off. Yeah, it threw well. No,
No, it's pretty now. I think about it's kind of just like pretty normal. Yeah
Damn
No, it was okay
Yeah, I was I remember getting home that night and just falling asleep immediately after you cried for a while
Yeah, yeah, I went to the doctor because my allergies are really bad
I thought it gave me a sinus infection because my head was hurting
And I went to the doctor and they had looked in all my holes and on my head just the head holes
and you better and they said and what the doctor said she said yeah, it looks
like what you have is a combination of two things.
Damn allergies and brain tumor, allergies and something else. I just
said something I said you probably I think it looks like you have allergies
and then something it's probably just two things. What
you need to go to a different doctor yeah, it's an urgent care. I didn't
want to make an appointment with a doctor take way too long. I did I hate
and they made me wait for thirty minutes in the in the room, not in the waiting
room in the actual like exam.
Yeah and there's okay. I know I know it's it's it's hack and anointing to
like okay. You have to tell the the nurse and then you also have to tell the
doctor, but the thing that was making me left this time is it first of all I
told the nurse and then another doctor came in later and I told that doctor
and then that doctor left and a third person came in that I did tell it, but
when I you're a sketch, the doctor came in the thing is making love with the
thing. The doctor came said when she came in she was like so I heard you're
not feeling well,
because if you like it, like yeah, there's a guy in there is not feel and
also just the idea that a doctor walking. So the nurse says you're one
hundred percent you're good to go. Yeah, no ring. I heard you're not feeling
what like clearly just not like forgot that I was in the room and then had to
go in really fast.
I heard you're not. I heard you're not. I think that's a hard job being a
doctor. No, I think it's pretty easy. I know being a doctor is what I will say.
I go of the road job in my experience. It is very easy to be a lead doctor
which is what they call the top doctor at the doctor facility. But if you're any
doctor who works under a lead doctor, I'm a lead doctor. So if you're the people
who work under me, you treat them badly. Yeah, because I have to because that's
how they live. My life gets easier. A lot of doctoral business is, you know,
like telling like your inmates and like your
like staff of joke. We say victims. Yeah, victims
walking around the doctor's office.
That's a kind of a backstage, if you will, joke for the doctors.
I don't say that to the people's faces.
That's the aristocrats for doctors.
Just saying, calling them victims.
No, come on. Everybody loves the aristocrats, even the doctors.
My doctor came in and said, "The aristocrats for me?"
Yeah, real quickly, I've got to test this on you.
So this is family.
I start laughing my head off, cure my cancer.
Like that, laughter, best medicine.
That's a pretty good idea.
you know, be crazy is a TV or a stand up show called the best medicine.
I feel like that probably exists. No, no, no, there's no way that exists and
it's hosted by a guy like this. This is good. Yeah, the best medicine and what
are some of the names we would see on there? They're all doctors. Dr. Ken
John. It's an all. Yeah, Dr. Ken John, Dr. Eddie. Oh, the guy who in better
call Saul plays the vet. Maybe he could become a real life. Veteran. Oh,
Joe de Rosa yeah Dave
Filoni, no Dave Foley Dave Foley from MTV. Yeah
who else is doctor doctor house yeah,
patch Adams patch Adams. That's not going to work all doctor all doctor
comedy show
for it's a good idea. There's four doctors called best medicine. Yeah,
it's for doctors, because like you know how they have
You know how they have those stand up shows where it's like by veterans for
veterans and then it's like, no, you never heard of those. No. Oh,
they have like a, like there's like a vet or like a,
a veterans comedy thing where it's a former army members who were like,
and now I'm in stand up. Now I'm doing stand. Are you talking about, uh, we,
by the way, we should do a USO tour. Yeah, we need to go to,
pretty good idea to go to Iraq and we need to perform in, in,
in camouflage. Wow, that is really a great idea. Just like John Stewart,
exciting idea, just like Louie in the episode with the duckling. Yep, that's
a great idea. That is a really good idea. That's enticing. We should bring
Jubio with us and sell him to the Taliban. Yeah,
'cause look, he looks tall, Jubio, and he could save. Yeah,
he looks tall and he is like, you know, good bait for like them to like dress up
like them and then put him out. So then, like they're like, is there a sniper
outside? Just send you be out there. He's like what, like six seven. He's a
monster. He's not that tall.
I don't know. No, no, I think we were going to say that he looks middle
eastern and he went for tall. He doesn't look middle eastern. No, I mean, why
maybe yeah, maybe it looks like me or you, Jubio does not look Middle
Eastern at all. You don't think so. I do you do you do yeah, show yourself. He
could be Persian get get
he could definitely be. He could be from anywhere. He's got a boy.
That's why I like him. Yeah, this is the this is the person we're setting the
an Alabama yeah we're sending this is
put this on put this picture up right now. This is a Patrick with a gaff tape
haircut to we did this and we said he looked like Drake,
which we thought was pretty cool. I forgot about that is really clean. You
look really
amazing
one bookmark
Patrick. Yeah, that's so stupid. I think it's cool. I think I
buddy ears to even line up. They never do. I think that it
might be a good idea for me to start getting into actual wigs.
Yeah, I think that I could just have a lot of different
identities. Grow your hair back out. I think that I might actually
I have to get a new license. I think I might actually wear a
wig. Yeah, because they can't tell you to take it off. You
know you kind of maybe can they don't not if they don't know that's true. You
could tell them you have cancer.
Cancer. I have cancer. I have cancer. Oh yeah.
Walking in walking in and he's in like a like a hospital gown and he's wiping
his tears with a nap. If you're going to get your new driver's license photo,
they can't tell you to stop crying because you'll just cry harder if
someone says that to you. Yeah, what if you imagine if you got a driver's
license photo on your
running down your face? This looks like a mug shot yeah, a new or what are they
yeah? What are they going to do? Yeah, they have to they have to try to
comfort you, not give me my license. Yeah, I think if you got like a
come back, if you got a blonde surfer wig, I think that look good. I always
think you know that's why I lost my hair because I tried to bleach it. That's
not why because I well, it was part of I believe my hair like four times. I
I never had dandruff until I bleached my hair and then I believe my so bad my
damn hairline. Oh, there's probably a big red line because this is all that's all
bleach man. Yeah, yeah, that's pure bleach. Yeah, I push my hair to yeah,
but you have great hair. I was going to go bald, but I was thirty and then I
and then you celebrate it. Yeah, you sped it up. Yeah, yeah, so don't do
that and by the way, I think God was I think that maybe God is not involved in
my hair. Maybe God plucked your hairs out and they're waiting for you in
heaven for one.
you mean that baby new year
God needs you to serve as the Dolly
says they're doing red light therapy on my head. Maybe I think that the
Christian God has selected you to be the next Dolly Lama to discredit
the movement yeah and bring light to Christianity. I chose a Dolly Lama when
there are five, the first Christian
yeah, you know what you could do
kill the Dolly Lama. No, I was going to say just get like a little curly blonde
big damn. Maybe people maybe there are people like a little curly blonde afro
if do you think people try to assassinate the kid Dali Lama when they
pick him? Yeah, that's why he goes into as you go into hiding. Yeah, he's
playing all day. I do. I bet that bodyguard for him is so cool. He's like
you're in a row. His name is chance. Wait, Christopher Big Black Boykin
faked his dad because he got a job for the Dali Lama. Oh my God, that's
totally right. Lama kid gets to go around skateboarding and mall parking
shots and Christopher Big Black Boy can tackle security guards who make $4 an hour.
Yeah.
Damn. Do you ever feel bad about those guys and those shows?
What?
Like, why is he harassed? He's just, the guy's doing his job.
That was just a sketch.
Oh, I thought it was real.
No, no, no, no, no. That was a sketch for the DC shoes video that came out in '04.
Well, why does he have a bodyguard in the first place?
He had a bodyguard, like it was like a sketch that went into his part in the DC video and
and Jeff Tremaine sold that sketch to MTV or whatever and made it a whole show.
But also even just as a skater, skaters are mean to security guards.
Skaters think security guards are cops.
They are cops.
They're not.
It's just a job.
There's something you're going to really like.
There are better people.
If you go on YouTube, look up skaters vs. Karens.
I hate skaters.
Both of them, right?
No, I, in that war, I'm with the Karens all day.
I think I think no, the care what a skater calls a Karen is not what a normal
person. You got to see these.
This lady won't let me grind her baby.
Yeah, shut the fuck.
You got to see these Karen's in these videos, though.
They won't let me smoke marijuana under their window.
This guy loves I want to go smoke marijuana and I want to smoke marijuana
right next to the dryer vents and your house and make all your laundry smell
like lay down your eight kids and then skate all the way across their backs.
Just grind their entire on your car.
What the fuck you can.
I stand on your car to take out my run on your car. Yeah, yeah, there's a good
there's a sometimes it's like a video of like an old man, just like just
punching a sixteen year old good and that's not a Karen. By the way, that's a
veteran. That's Kevin.
Kevin's a cool name. Kevin's not the name for a male Karen. No, definitely
not. I would say maybe a Patrick can a Patrick. Yeah, I don't think it's that
doesn't rhyme with Karen. It doesn't have to rhyme with it has to rhyme with
It has to be evocative of an annoying type of person.
Yeah.
Patrick's a saint.
You have a little Minecraft kid name, Caleb.
Whoa!
No I don't.
He's right.
I do have a Minecraft kid name.
You have a camera in there?
You can hear it in Fortnite.
You can hear the moms like, "Caleb, get off!"
Fortnite's a fun game.
Actually, Minecraft's a fun game too.
Minecraft is not fun.
You've been playing all day!
Get off!
I'm going there.
I like Minecraft and I like Fortnite.
I get on there. I like Minecraft and I like Fortnight. You don't I do you
don't usually both for hours. No, no, no, yeah, but now it's not and you're
the actual Minecraft player and you're the actual Fortnight player. I don't
play Minecraft. He plays so much Minecraft does now. It's your now. It's
your come in here and he's he's playing Minecraft and he quickly all tabs into a
skater game. You seem cool, but I know one of these guys. He's building a
he's building a one to one recreation of the White House.
yeah and not yeah he's not like it, not like in a doom, wadway, just know like
I think it's really cool. The architecture is really bad. He's on the
discord server for the like earth minecraft thing and he's making yeah
perfect recreation of the entire making a perfect recreation of my hometown.
You know, he contribute to the eggs to make recreations of like villages in
Thailand and stuff.
He really wants to make a like a hill in Kansas or something yeah yeah. Please
let me do that. Please. I'm applying to make this plot of land and craft on the
Earth project. Meanwhile, I have a forty five hundred dollar
racing set up so that I can play and I'm dropping twenty thirty limbs in a
fortnight game crown royale. I'm playing flight simulator. I've genuinely thought
about that. All my credit cards to get one of these. Yeah, I genuinely thought
of like getting like a VR headset and like a steering wheel and like pedals and
stuff to try and teach myself how to try. It's not a bad idea. I was I was
actually considering that just the other day. I'm not even kidding. I thought
about that for so because, like, my biggest fear,
my biggest fear with driving is crashing and killing somebody, right? Well,
that's and maybe getting, like, a few people upset with my driving. So
I think if I just do exposure therapy and in VR, I don't think that that I
think if the purpose is exposure therapy, I don't think VR is gonna work.
the purpose I'm going to be in VR and I'm driving and I just crashed the car and I
have like a rumble seat and everything and I'm crashing my car and everything
I'm like just crazy that's 200 200 miles per hour I'm getting 200 miles per hour
in a Lamborghini and I'm just going Ryan Dunn into like barriers that doesn't
work because that will not make you you will not you will have you will have fun
doing that it will make you want to do it and nobody will be mad at you and
they will congratulate you for playing so and then that's the annoying thing
thing is you're going to get to the MV to do the driver's test. The guy's like
all right, we're going to bring the car around, pulls up
Lamborghini Mercy. Wait, I need to put on a I need to put on a full headset that
covers my eyes before I can drive this, but as soon as you see that Lambo,
which is what they give you the DMV to do, you're going to just immediately
kill you and this innocent DMV lady. Yeah, no, because it's my well, I'm
saying and guess I'm saying it's my biggest score for that. I'm saying it's
my biggest fear is killing somebody in a car, but this is all you're going to