(upbeat music)
- That was a really good one.
- I think you're supposed to clap into the mic.
- What, fuck you.
- Okay.
- He could've heard it anyway, man.
- Yeah, that's true.
- What's up, Eric?
- What's up, guys?
- How are you?
- Well, I'm amazing now.
- Yeah, 'cause now you're doing your favorite thing ever?
- Podcasting.
Do you feel like podcasting is entering the same strata as, not, I think it's past
television.
Yeah.
That's obvious.
But entering into movies, high art, stuff that hangs in museums.
Yeah, I think we're in third wave podcasts right now.
Yeah.
Started out with the Marons and the like, I'm trying to think of who else.
Jimmy, Pete Holmes.
Pete Holmes.
Yeah, Car Talk was really big for a while before the guy passed away.
now I don't know what the second wave was, but now it's third wave and we're just going crazy on these things.
Do you think it's a golden age?
Dude, I mean, I feel people should feel lucky.
The golden age of podcasting or is that past?
Because the golden age was probably, yes, like the mayor, like you made it weird.
Yeah. Come on, that wasn't a golden age, that was a bronze age.
That was the bronze age?
That was, they didn't know what the fuck they were doing.
Yeah. They didn't realize they could do this shit.
They could, they had no idea.
I'm so jealous of this setup.
You need one of these. It's like the breakfast club.
It's bad. We need Angela Yee in here badly.
Oh my God.
But yeah, I think that we're entering...
I think that there will be in probably five years,
classes at certain colleges like Oberlin and stuff.
Vassar.
You will take a history of podcasting class.
I think there is a podcasting class at Vassar.
And there will be a history though, like an art history one,
where you will be learning all about...
Adjunct professor.
You will be an adjunct professor,
but you will be learning about the watermelon guy
who ran off on Mark Maron.
- Gallagher, yeah.
- Gallagher, you will be learning about all the times
that Pete Holmes made it weird and awkward on his show.
- He made it so weird.
Does he realize how weird he made it?
- I hope not.
- I think he was going out
with the intention of making it weird.
I think he wanted to make it weird.
'Cause the name of the show.
- I think it's, you know what I think is weird with him?
Letting people have sex with your wife, that's fucking weird.
(laughing)
Why are you doing that, Pete Holmes?
- He's a Christian swinger, is that his whole thing?
- Oh, is he a swinger?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I mean, hey yo, you know,
people are getting all into this right now.
- Yeah, swinging?
It's back on the rise. - Yeah, it's what everybody
likes these days.
- People heard all these stories about their uncle
going to key parties in the '70s,
and they're like, "Damn, I gotta get more pussy
"than my uncle."
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- So now they're-- - I don't like it at all.
I think it's wrong. I think it's wrong. Definitely wrong.
Well, we're three really good guys. And so I think our moral compasses are so
like, are not right, but so right. So right in the middle. We're very, we're
also
maybe we're just quick to, to, to, to try to be right about everything because
we're so used to it, you know? So maybe swinging is actually, maybe it is good.
Maybe it's, and maybe we're just, I mean, I've never tried it. I don't think I
will. But it does just disgust me so much.
People would want your ass so badly, Caleb. I just gotta tell you.
If I showed... No. You're fucking around. You would be in high demand.
If I showed up at a swinger party... Well, I think that that might be true,
but I think that's because most of the people there are 60 years old.
Yeah. So you think... I would show up and they would think that I was...
Well, it would be like you'd get invited to some Brooklyn one.
I don't want to even think about this. In some gross... Think about some Bushwick
swinger party in some tiny ass apartment with black mold. Everybody got the
armpit hair popping out, leg hair, the whitey tighties. I'd be sitting there, I'd be looking
through people's keys, seeing who has the coolest keychains there.
Hey, hipsters.
Because they're all on carabiners.
True.
Yeah.
I want to get some whitey tighties, by the way.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're not scared?
No, scared of what?
The dookie?
Oh, you mean, well, I'll get some blue, navy blue.
Those are not, those are bluey-dooeys. That is not a whitey tighty. That is not a whitey
tighty.
- I have a picture of Mr. Brian Cranston
in the first season of Breaking Bad.
- Yes.
- Where he's like outside the motor home
and he's got the--
- And he got the nub.
- He's got the nub, but he's also got the--
- The garters?
- What are they?
The Clark's chukkas.
- Yeah, I know what you're talking about.
- Okay, he's got those, or the desert whatever,
not desert boots, but, and he's got the whitey tighties.
I think he looks sexy there.
And I think I would like to look like that.
- You wanna enter into--
- You're just trying to do that,
you're trying to get your Halloween costume together.
trying to get your ducks in a row for that.
- Or like something to shoot for.
- You're gonna be Heisenberg?
- I guess I could be Heisenberg.
- You would need to put on a shaved head.
- Yeah, I'm not--
- That's fine.
But I do think that is a little bit your swag
of like big t-shirt, tiny little thing
covering your penis and butt.
- You're talking about the Pooh Bear effect.
- Yeah, the Pooh, yes, I was talking about the Pooh Bear.
- You know about that last episode?
- We were talking about last episode,
the fact that I walk around with just the big shirt on
and no pants at all, my dingle hanging.
Do you still have that really big shirt I got you?
No, my wife made me throw it away.
Yeah, I think it's here in the costume.
Oh, maybe I think it's right here.
I gave him a 4XL shirt with a drawing I made.
And you threw it away?
His wife did not like it.
I mean, okay, so it's 4XL, so that's four shirts worth of material that I have to store in my house.
It's a tent.
And I live in a tiny one-bedroom apartment, 475 square feet.
Yeah.
Well, I...
I wasn't going to ever make that work.
also got you I used to when my money was right. He's the just send my friends
gifts all the time. I got him a kingdom heart snap back. He did. He used to buy
me. That's why our old office, which you never went to our old office was so
fucked up and full of shit. Swagged out. No, it was terrible. It was so bad
because it was just a place where Patrick every single day would buy
something that cost 99 cents because he thought it was funny and then just leave
it in the office and it was just trash. I got it was stuff that I got for my
friends. That's the only reason why I want to say this though. I feel like if
you're giving gifts, whatever at this income or whatever income you're at, it
says a lot about where you're headed in terms of like your character and what
you're gonna, how you're gonna be hooking up the day ones. That's some real shit.
It says a lot about you. Do you like to give gifts? Me? I like to give money
because and not not kingdom hearts hats and stuff. I give straight cash.
Forty dollars? Yes.
And with singles.
Being quiet to your mom, like I got you mom.
I feel like I'm Drake.
Just whatever cash is in.
Loose bills, like one twenty and then the rest is like ones and fives. Yeah.
Mama go get a car wash, here you go.
You know that I treat you right. Mr. Gandalfini did that. Really? He was giving
people on my envelopes. I think he got to I don't want to go on the Sopranos, but I
think he got to into the character. Well, yeah, that's that's what that is right
with Junker. Well, they both got to into the character, which is so fucking scary.
Do you think? But don't you as an actor, by the way, I've filmed like I told you
I'm filming this in black and white because you know that you're not a camera
turn on. I just kind of like my little chain. Yeah, you did change. I know right
where the angle is every single time. Yes, you can hit it perfectly. Yeah. So
What is, are you waiting on that big Heath Ledger Joker role?
The one that will consume you?
- Yeah, what's the scariest role you're gonna take?
- Scariest role I'm gonna take?
Probably some type of professor.
- Why would that?
Do you just think you'd be so good at embodying that role
that it would just be terrifying to you?
- I think so, 'cause you remember "Beautiful Mind"
with Russell Crowe, and he's so differently smart.
- Australian, oh.
- Yeah, oh yeah, and he's Australian or whatever.
but he goes crazy in it.
I would love to bring kind of facts to it,
to be like super into it.
- You want to play, I've always,
and I've talked to you about this, I know.
I think that you would be an incredible Sherlock Holmes.
And I think that you-- - The American?
Or would I go British style with it?
- Oh, wait, wait. - I think that you could do
even a third, you could be a Canadian or an Australian,
some other English speaking country.
- Yeah. - Their version of--
Has there been an American Sherlock Holmes?
There hasn't. I think that there was.
I mean, Robert Downey, but he was British, but he was British.
I'm talking like. House MD.
House MD. You guys already have.
I know people make comparisons of who you guys should be as the podcast, but Cam is
clearly Sherlock. Yes.
You're clearly Watson.
OK. OK. And you're clearly the supervillain that's about to destroy London with a...
Moriarty.
I don't know too much about Sherlock Holmes. I know he's a detective.
You've got to study the texts.
Yeah, I mean you are a complete Wasson.
Yeah?
Yeah. Just bumbling around.
I've got to check it out.
Wait no, Wasson's smart.
He's bumbling?
No, no, no. You're his cat or something. You're like something that knocks over beakers and
shit.
Like beaker?
Yeah, you could be.
You're like beaker, yes. You're like beaker a little bit and I'm Professor Honeydew or
whatever his name is.
Bunsen Honeydew.
Bunsen Honeydew, yeah.
Don't try and test my muppet knowledge.
I wouldn't even think of it. But I think that that would be a good role for you.
I know Muppets you've never heard of.
Because that would give you a chance to play. You know those scenes that get posted on YouTube
for movies and television that are like smartest scene ever, smart monologue about life and
stuff. I was just watching True Detective season one last night, and I always thought
that that is the coolest role ever. And then last night I was watching, I was like, I think
that this is so, so bad.
Really? It went bad style? Who? McConaughey?
McConaughey? Yeah, McConaughey is Russ Cole. He's just like in the car.
His name's Russ Cole? Russ Cole. Oh my God. Are you serious? Russ. First name Russ,
last name Cole. That's like a middle schooler coming up with a cowboy name.
Yeah, Russ Cole and he's in the car like, "There's something so messed up about
The world is all fucking weird.
The world is completely browned.
I remember being 17 and looking at YouTube, I was obsessed with YouTube and I would look
at SNL auditions because people would post their tapes.
Even back in 2008, 2009.
People would post their like, yeah the whole clip of like themselves self-filming.
Yeah trying to get on SNL, trying to get like someone please contact their producers.
And there was this one guy who mostly his whole audition was just McConaughey and I
thought it was so good.
I left like five comments being like, literally dude,
like nobody's doing it like you.
(all laughing)
Like I was obsessed with this guy.
- I thought you were looking at,
I thought you meant like,
like you were looking at like Will Ferrell's audition tape.
I didn't know people were going Jake Novak, like back then.
- Oh, they've been doing Jake Novak style.
- People have always been trying to get on us.
- And God bless Jake Novak, by the way, please.
- Literally, it is so fucked up,
collectively, what everyone did to him.
- He has to get on "SNL".
He deserves it more than anybody.
- A walk on thing.
He deserves something.
He should be, because you know, they have SNLs in every country.
Do you know?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
He should be on like SNL Brazil.
We talked about...
He would crush that.
SNL Quebec.
Oh, I didn't know they had a Canada.
Which they have like a really like the cast name is like if SNL was trying to come up with an SNL Quebec.
Yeah, they have a French kids.
Oh, they're all named like Guillaume, Guillaume or something.
Guillaume.
Bong Bong.
Yeah. Hong Bong?
Oh.
Bong Bong.
That's a French name.
Yeah, that's actually a good one.
Bong Bong is not a French name.
I think that's a candy.
I think Jake Novak would thrive in any kind of sketch comedy scenario.
I really think that he's talented.
And also, the thing that people don't realize about SNL, it's not like he's going to get
up there and write the shit.
No.
Right?
They're going to write stuff for him and he's going to knock it out of the park every time
because he does have an amazing voice.
He has a beautiful face.
He'd be perfect for impressions.
He has kind of a Dana Carvey kind of look to him.
Yes.
Let him on, dude.
way socially conscious. Yes. Which you can't say that much about. Oh yeah. Wait I forgot.
Bad Gun. That song's a banger. Land of the free, home of the brave. I know. Land of the
AR-15, home of kids in the grave. Home of the kids in the grave. God damn. What? Trying
to keep the disposition sunny. I'm trying to always find the unfunny things funny but.
Whoa. You got a memory like that. I try, I listen to it a lot. He did. He listened to
You're showing like strangers on the train.
Kind of, that is what Patrick does.
I do that a lot. I show people videos on my phone.
It's really annoying, but
the videos are always really good.
And then you win them back onto your side.
It's annoying when I put the phone up
but then they see the video
donkey hit by train, Pakistan railway.
No, you're watching these?
Have you ever seen that video?
No, I can't watch a donkey get hit.
What? A donkey?
Dude, you...
I watched a video of these ants helping each other across like a little gap in the leaves.
There's three ants and they're all, or four ants are all working together. They form a
bridge and three of the ants make it across and they don't go back and help the other
one.
And you cry.
And I literally, and there's multiple videos of this. Apparently this is a thing for the
ants. And I was thinking, fuck you all. I was getting so mad on behalf of the stranded
ant, dude.
Fucked up, but they don't think of themselves even as people. They're like, they think of themselves as ants or whatever
They're like part of a bigger system. Yeah, they got like a hive mind. Yeah, right. I don't know. No, that's bees
Yeah, bees have the bees definitely have a hive mind. I think ants have a similar thing. Yeah. Yeah
I think you're gonna have to change whatever
Roles you're getting ready to play because of how shredded you're getting in the gym recently
We, well, you know that we are lifting all the time.
Do you know this, Patrick?
I know that about you guys.
We're going, yeah.
I'm like, I have to like, I'm not stretching at all,
so I have to move my neck like this.
Dude, I'm getting stronger than you can imagine.
(laughing)
Yeah, we do not do stretching.
I hurt myself once a week.
Caleb, what was it, your Achilles?
I thought that I ruptured my Achilles like Kobe
Oh, damn.
Two days ago, but I just hurt a little bit.
You guys don't stretch at all?
Not, no.
I have the time, motherfucker.
I'm doing the like loser stretches of just like the hamstring.
And I'll go like this.
This? What is that doing for you?
That gets the forearm all loose.
Oh, OK.
But yeah, no, we've been consistent too.
I stretch. I stretch a lot.
When are you going to get in the gym with us?
We're trying to get everything.
I might try to start going.
Honestly, I did.
I saw my side profile in a store window and I was like, damn, I got I got long.
I got long width wise.
You got long width. You look skinny.
Yeah, you do look skinny. I was just thinking you're looking skinny.
I don't know. Maybe it was a maybe I was looking at a fun house.
Yeah, you need to stop going to the circus.
I got to stop going to the circus.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
No, but I stretch. I'd like I mean, because I'd like still skate.
So I like my bones.
I wake up in like 16 bones crack, I think.
Really? It's that's normal.
It's good to crack so bad. It's good to crack.
Oh, it hurts to wake up. Yeah, really?
It's fine. Yoga or something.
Yeah, I started doing I started doing the I found this like this guy who's like the
skate yogi on YouTube and he was doing these videos and like the first couple
minutes of the workout was easy. It was like a 10 minute like Oh, do this before
you go skate, you'll like, you know, all your shit will be limber. And then he's
like, Okay, now lift up from your feet like that, like trying to lift your whole
body on the way to your feet. And I tried that and I just bled out like
It was the weirdest noise I've ever made in my entire life.
I didn't, it was so involuntary.
I was just like, there's no way I'm doing this.
And I had to, I had to stop.
I think that my body is not meant for stretching.
It hurts me so bad to stretch.
I mean, you know, sometimes when we do those stretches
where you sit down and you lock your legs
and you try to touch your toes.
The feeling that my legs give me,
it's like, that's the worst feeling I've ever felt in my life.
It's gotta be number one.
- Stab, not stab, but-- - Slit.
- Yeah, maybe slit. - Sliced.
You'd rather be sliced than do that.
- It's just the most,
why do our bodies hate what's good for them?
- Yeah. - You know what I mean?
- It's true. - Why the hell is this?
- Why is it that vegetables taste like doo-doo
to people like us, but candy and bread tastes so incredible?
- I don't know what it is.
- Yesterday, I had probably the worst diet
I've ever had in my entire life.
I ate breakfast, lunch, and dinner,
all three of them were sandwiches.
- Jimmy John's, we had Jimmy John's yesterday.
Jimmy John's. I had a breakfast sandwich, a tuna sandwich, and a Jimmy John's
sandwich. Those were my meals of the day. That is such a bad way to live. You do
that every day, don't you? That was a good couple years of my life. Just three
sandwiches a day? Sandwiches and chips. Three square sandwiches every single day.
That is so fucking good. I also want to be the first maybe on a podcast to welcome Jimmy
John's to New York City. Yes. Port Green, bordering on Best Buy. They do it right
right there. Yes, they really do. I didn't know they didn't have Jimmy
Johns in... I thought Jimmy Johns was
like a Jersey franchise. Oh, fuck. That's Jersey Mike. Jersey Mike. Wait,
hold on.
That's fucking embarrassing as shit. Can you imagine being the first morning
radio... You realize you could do this?
Yeah, I was thinking about what was the first
ways that they put on a soundboard for like a stern or whatever.
But I mean, they were probably putting like amber alerts.
They got probably all the utilities back then.
All those children were getting that.
The buttons used to only be for amber alerts and like weather reports
and stuff like that.
And then one guy was like, a child has gone missing in Orange, New Jersey.
Oh, my God.
Tornado alert for your county.
Oh my God!
Oh my God.
Yeah, that'd be fun.
You know that thing that they do when children go missing
or they're looking for a body in a field or something?
Yeah.
And you have to go comb the premises.
With the dogs.
With the dogs, but also in a human line.
Yeah.
Or they'll do that if they're trying to find someone in the water.
I was thinking like if I was asked to do that, I would get bored so fucking quick.
That's why we are doing a podcast.
Because what do you need in your headphones when you're doing this shit
to keep yourself focused?
Doing busy work like the dishes or hunting for a human body.
You put in the air pods and you pop on a fucking pot about list.
The two things everyone's always doing.
If I could listen to smart lists all day.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Looking for bodies all day.
Pot about list or your podcast Joy Tactics, which people should go and check out.
You can do it with Jack Benson or Nate Veron.
around and yeah we go crazy.
They do go crazy.
Yeah. What do you think?
How do you feel being
how many months in are you?
Oh, what do we when we start end of
January?
So, oh, whoa.
First of all, what I didn't realize
it was that I didn't realize it was
that that long
again. No, that that short of a time.
Yeah, it's been like three and a
half months. Yeah. Three and a half
months. I fucking I thought that you
guys were around forever.
You guys have blazed a trail.
Yeah, dude, we're kind of top of the charts.
They are top of the charts.
First of all, welcome to the family.
Yeah. Second of all, thanks, guys.
How has it changed your life more than any decision you've ever made?
Bar none?
Um, yeah, I guess other than
becoming atheist.
Yeah.
So on the same level,
yeah, when you went back, right?
Yeah, I'll go back.
That's why it was awful.
Every time, probably every week.
Yeah, yeah. Every time it's bad, you become Christian again.
Yeah. It's either God's fault or it's my fault because I didn't have God with me.
Yes.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Did your mom ever hit you with a, "That's God punishing you," when you hit your head on the door or something?
My mom was not that much of a psycho bitch, it seems like your mom was if she was saying that shit to you.
My mom was Irish Catholic, so yes.
Yeah.
Yeah, my mom never said anything like that to me.
I would hit my head on like a door or something. She's like, that's God's
pun. That's God punishing you. And I guess it's supposed to be a joke, but it
was not a joke to my child mind. You know what I was really scared of? I bet
you we've never talked about afraid of God because you also grew up kind of
evangelical, right? Were you so afraid of being left behind? Of course, I'm
still afraid of being left behind the most. I feel like the rapture. Yeah,
I've been joking so angry, even thinking about making kids afraid of that.
So crazy.
And do you know about the books Left Behind, of course?
Yeah, dude, and the movies.
I didn't know about those until I met him.
And they had the Left Behind for kids books.
That's what I was just going to bring up.
And there was like 30 of them.
Yeah.
And I read them all.
I would sit in the library with no friends.
I would sneak into my little Christian school's library and sit in the corner and read Left Behind.
And I was like, and for those of you who don't know what Left Behind is, I'm sure most of you do,
but it was a narrative fiction, like long series
about these people that were left behind in the rapture,
in the Christian rapture.
- Fictionism, I mean, future history maybe.
- What, they get crazy though with the wars.
- Well, it basically, it's the left,
it's biblical left behind tribulation for one book
and then it's the walking dead.
- It's literally.
- Of like, the war breaks out and people just kill 'em.
- There's zombies in it?
- Oh. - There's crazy shit.
You know what they say in Revelations is that once the Rapture comes, whatever, the Antichrist
is going to rule the world for seven years.
Seven years. Tribulation.
And then at the end of that, there's going to be a war that lasts something like 10,000
years.
Too long.
God and Satan fighting. And then everybody gets to go to heaven at the end.
Well, not everybody.
Oh, some people are damned.
Yeah, so I mean there's a bunch of different ways that people think about it, but yeah,
basically there's people, like I remember our pastor said that he was like,
even Christians have to go through all the,
like 10,000 year war and stuff. So he's like, basically there's just,
you're just fucked. It's going to suck. And also Obama's doing it. He's,
so it's going to be here soon. Uh, did, were you,
were your parents ever scared of like microchipping? No, really?
My parents never even talked to me about the rapture. I was the like a fanatic.
Really? Yeah. That's kind of crazy. You were the little religious kid.
Yeah. I learned about the ret. Remember in, in 2010,
there is that guy who was saying like,
like there was a huge thing where people were like, yep, 5/12/2010 or something
like that. Or like as if the fucking perfect God almighty would let you know the
date. Do you remember that? There was a, there was a preacher.
He was putting billboards and shit up and he was like, the day is going to,
I did think that was going to happen.
Of course, because it's on a billboard.
What if it does happen?
What are you, 15?
No, I was 12, 13, something like that.
15 would be a little old to be trusting a billboard on something like that.
I would have.
You know what, I was just like, there's that one part of my brain that was like, "Well,
what if it's true?"
I felt like that about 2012, Mayan apocalypse.
Oh, the Mayan and the Kony.
Yes, Kony.
I thought they were tied.
they were tied. I was like, God will not let this stand. He has to destroy the earth.
My first girlfriend broke up with me on the Mayan thing.
So your world did end.
I did. I think I had that in the Twitter drafts when I was 15. I was like, damn.
My world fucking ended in 2012.
Good lord.
That movie, I really liked that movie.
John Cusack.
Yeah. 2012, John Cusack.
Oh, I liked that too. Remember that movie, Two Knowing with Nicolas Cage?
Really cool movie.
I haven't seen that one.
All about apocalypse.
Two freaky ass kids that know all about shit?
Oh, I thought that, yeah, I thought you were talking about Witch Mountain.
Okay, I do have a religious experience that nobody's ever been able to explain to me.
It still scares me thinking about this.
When I was a kid, I had a dream one night, and I had a couple of religious, like God,
I had one dream where I walked out, it's like I was awake in my dream in my house, everybody's
Everybody's asleep. I walked down to the living room
and the Holy Spirit came out of the living room,
like coffee table and like came up as like a ghostly figure
and was like, you are going to hell.
I'm like seven.
- This was a dream?
- Yeah, yeah, this was a dream.
I had another dream that I'm in our family mania
and I'm looking to the sky.
Remember James and the giant peach?
- Yep.
- Where that cloud turns into a crazy animal.
- The rhino.
Similar to that, I had a dream that the cloud,
I'm looking at the clouds, they're making crazy shapes.
I'm like eight and the clouds make a fit God's fist and it comes down and
punches the shit out of the minivan or rips the top off,
blows all my family out and crushes me to death. Fuck man. Jesus Christ.
The trifecta is completed with the scariest one,
which I can't explain to this day. Maybe I heard something.
I didn't remember it, but I have a dream. I'm eight or nine, whatever.
And I know I'm in hell and it's freaky because you know,
the way they describe it in school and church was like, it's hot, fiery,
ice cold and it was pitch black. I just knew I was in hell. I couldn't see anything, almost
blind. And then I'm hearing like the dank drips of hell, whatever. And then I look over
and in the distance is a hooded figure with like a bright glowing head. Okay. And he takes
the hood off and I know it's Satan. And he's bright glowing, like crazy, so bright you
can't even look at him, like the brightest thing you've ever seen. And that was before
I learned that Satan was a fallen angel. You know, like a bright glowing angel.
So you were touched?
I don't know. All this shit made me so fanatical about God and being like, I didn't even, heaven
sounded like shit to me because of what you do in worship all the time. And worship is
so fucking boring.
It is really boring.
But anyways.
That idea of hell is kind of cool though.
That is dark.
That is cold.
Well no, that's hell froze over.
Hell froze over.
Oh yeah, true.
In some of the ancient descriptions they talk about hell being cold.
And you knew that already.
No, I'd never heard of that. That's why I was like, I don't know why.
That sounds like...
I had a similar dream as a child where me and my dad, we made a snowman outside and it chased
us and we were in a monster truck. And that stuck with me. I swear to God, me and my dad,
I talk about it every single time I see him.
My older brother has a dream like that too.
It's just one of those dreams that just sticks with you for the rest of your life.
It's one that fucks up your brain so much that it's like, oh, this is like, I don't know
but I'm going to have to talk about this all the time. My older brother has this
dream he only referred to as the poop dream where he's in on an operating table
with his butt up.
They take the poop out of him? No, the doctor comes in, he says, he told me,
he's like, the whole room is lit green like Fight Club
and he's on an operating table and a doctor comes in and cuts his butt off and
it just shoots poop out.
That doctor is a... He, quack.
He woke up from the poop dream just screaming.
And I guess my mom, it happened like a few times.
And he woke up, my mom like came into the room like, "What?
What?
What's going on?"
He's just in the poop dream.
I had a scary dream last night.
I dreamed that I got addicted to vaping again.
And that was my entire dream.
I never knew that you were addicted to vaping.
I was a vaper for quite some time.
Yeah, we all were.
Yeah.
And the Juul came out.
I never, the Jewel was a little past my...
Yeah, past your nicotine prime.
It was great because you could sneak it into music festivals.
Yeah.
They're outside, motherfucker. I'll smoke whatever I want.
The fucking Boston Calling, they were super, because it was on the Harvard campus for the first time ever,
when I like got, I spent my student loan refund on it.
And they were yelling at you about vaping?
Well, I wanted to sneak cigarettes in, and I had them in my, I had them in a plastic bag on my dick.
That is some terrorist shit.
Yeah. I could have snuck. That is seriously terroristic. I could have
brought anything in that cigarette pack. Yeah, the cigs on the dick. Mm-hmm.
They were in a plastic bag.
Yeah, that is kinda nasty. They didn't get all broken. Not by your dick.
But then the jewel came out. Not by yours. No, mine's not even touching 'em.
Something about that story, I was telling Jack about this yesterday, and maybe
you heard it too, that I... Something about recently, people have been telling
little anecdotes that have not, they're not emotional at all, but they make me
almost cry. And something about that story made me tear up for some reason.
You're thinking about my addiction to cigarettes? I think I have a brain tumor. Yeah. I think I
have some kind of giantly massive brain tumor that has filled up my entire head
and it's pushing out tears. No, you're being, you're just an empath and you're
thinking about like me being 19 years old addicted to cigarettes. No, I was telling Jack yesterday that somebody told me recently, they were like, they said
that something they were like, did you know that this one song was not like it
wasn't it was originally written for this movie? And I was like, really? Like I
said, I like sort of like tearing up for some reason. Yeah, something is wrong
with me and I need to go to the hospital today. Are you taking like new
medication? No, I don't take any medication at all.
Well, I take a bunch of different routes that are
that too.
Yeah, I was thinking today that this is kind of a, I was, I didn't know if maybe
this three person crew, all of us would roll in like super hungover, because I
feel like this is the hungover crew. 'Cause we like to get all twisted. 'Cause
sometimes, you're almost always a yes. I'm a maybe and Cameron's a never. And
I'm a maybe. And you're a maybe, yeah. So it's two maybes now. Two maybes and a
yes. And guess what, not hungover. Wow. What'd you do last night? It was May the
4th. So you were drinking some... Did you watch Star Wars? So you went to the
cantina. I did, I drank some blue milk. Wow. Blue milk from where? From Star
course. Did you really know I wish you had done that. I did have a course
banquet though. I watched ours. I made pork chops. You watched
pork chops and phantom menace.
You watch Phantom Man. I watched a new hope. I watched a new hope two nights
ago and I watched Phantom Menace last night. I just downloaded a Star Wars
ebook called the Darth Bane trilogy. Oh yeah, I know about him. Darth Bane.
Yeah, that's the guy
- Yeah, he's the one. - There's not a lot of nice Darths in
- No. - No, he's the protagonist of the
- Darth basically means bad in
- Darth means father. - Star Wars.
- Oh no, Vader means father. - Darth means dark.
- Oh, dark father. - Darth means dark?
- Yeah, Darth, I think Darth is Dutch.
- Super Darth in here. - For dark.
- It's dark in here? Or Darth in here?
Darth means, in what language? - Darth in here, Darth in here.
- Oh shit. - Darth.
- But what language is this where Vader is father?
- writer. - Writer is father in German, so it's dark.
Oh, because the Imperials or the Nazi.
- Yep. - Okay. That makes more sense.
- Whoa. - Whoa.
Wait.
God damn.
[Humming]
George Lucas Productions
That was insane dude
[Laughter]
The end of every Star Wars movie
George Lucas Productions
[Laughter]
That was fucking fire man
I heard some good ass news
I watched Phantom Menace last night
George Lucas might be at the helm of some new Star Wars movie.
Really?
That could be cool.
He's too old. Doesn't he just fucking roll around and chill now?
He just kind of rolls around.
He's got that Skywalker ranch.
He's cool, man.
He's sick.
He really is cool.
Have you heard that...
He's so much cooler than Spielberg.
Spielberg's such an old, dorky loser.
Unless he wants to work with me.
Spielberg does suck.
Yeah, and then he does want to come and produce a movie with us.
A pot of bottles feature.
Maybe put us in Indiana Jones or something. I would love oh my god three the three triple short round situation
Yeah, yeah, three little kids that and they're played by us. Yeah, they're like you know, and you know
He loves digital de-aging technology de-ages us into children and we're walking around like Indy
Are you sure you want to do this and he's like?
- Oh, make it the kid's voice.
- Yeah, yeah.
- We're like, "Indiana Jones, please, please,
I don't want to go into the cave, I want to go to school."
(laughing)
- And he'd say, "You fucking stupid fucking kid,
I'm gonna talk to the other two."
And then Patrick, you would go, you would go like,
well, basically you would go--
- Do I have the voice on?
- Okay, there.
Oh Indy, do we have to go into the cave?
You gotta go into the cave kid.
I don't wanna go into the cave, I wanna go to the ice cream parlor.
And then Eric you would also be in this movie and you would basically go...
Hey yo Indiana Jones.
(Laughter)
I love your shit man, respect.
Okay, I like this
that
that is funny to me. Everything I know
so good. Yeah, these chipmunks had the right idea man. Yeah. Who do you think
was the first guy? First of all, who listen who made that song the first time
I think it was a voice and then who said that sounds like a fucking chip was
- The A-Kon? No. - No!
- The Chipmunks were from like the 60s. - He just got the high voice.
- He stole from the Chipmunks. - Yeah.
- A-Kon did. - He stole Lonely from the Chipmunks.
- Yeah. - But yeah, like...
Who was the first guy that was like, "It might sound good to do a high voice"?
'Cause I would not think that it would.
I think it was... I think somebody dropped a soda onto the mixer.
Maybe it was like ancient Greek theater where people couldn't play...
Or that women couldn't be a part of the thing, so...
I think Helium had to be involved.
Definitely. Oh, that's what it was.
Helium for sure had to be involved.
They were like, "Well, what if we
go into the studio, we pump the
studio full of helium?" I think the first
attempt as the chipmunks... The first time was in the 1940s
they hit the helium balloon and somebody said
"There is a house
in New Orleans!"
And they were like, "That's gonna be huge."
The greatest song in the world. And by the way, that sounds like
a chipmunk to me. Yeah. I hope I'm
not saying anything controversial because I don't mean
to be bad, but I think it was probably back
Back in the Greek days, because a lot of the performers, some of the performers were eunuchs.
True.
And I think, and maybe that was happened to them before their hormones.
Oh, that's a good point.
Maybe that's it back in the day.
So when you get your shit sniffed.
You turn into a chipmunk.
Yeah.
Oh my, chipmunks, what do they love?
Nuts.
And you don't got none.
You got none.
Oh my God.
So your voice gets high because you're constantly looking for your nuts.
I never understood the eunuch thing.
Remember Varys from Game of Thrones?
I understood him.
Varys.
him. But he was kind of like, what about having your nuts chopped off makes you mysterious
and snake-like?
I think he probably had a lot of rage about what happened to him.
So he said, "I'm going to be a backstabber."
Maybe. And he's a gossip. He's a rotten gossip, Pat.
He's got no balls.
You don't have the nuts to say it to my face. That's basically what they're saying.
Did they ever say that in the show?
That's what I would say if I was Jon Stark or Snow.
Jon Snow, Jon Stark.
I don't know the difference.
Jon Stark.
That's Tony Stark.
I was Tony Stark and if Tony Stark was in Game of Thrones, those dragons have a
different idea. If Tony Stark was in Game of Thrones, I'll tell you what, that game
would have been one episode. Yeah, because they're all playing because the
game is they're playing checkers. Tony Stark's playing chess. Chess, he's got
the crazy computers. Exactly. And he would be the only millionaire in the time.
That's a good point.
Yeah, that's a really good point. Yeah. But I think if you get your or what was
was the reason why they would do eunuchs? Is it because I thought it was
funny? It was for high singing voices. Was it? I would be so pissed off
if somebody did that shit to me. I would never sing, I would never
reveal my voice. I think it was for like servants to make them...
I mean, I don't know which cultures, but for certain cultures, it was
like for servants to make them non threatening to like... Oh, it's like
neutering a dog. Yeah, yeah, I think so. Oh, okay. So it was not
not chill. I feel like that would make me even more threatening. I'd be
throwing fists back and forth, that'd be poisoning people's shit.
Isn't that what happens in Game of Thrones?
Oh, that's exactly right.
My context clues here.
Somebody handed me a drink at a thing recently.
Was it that party we were at on Monday or Tuesday?
No, it wasn't that, but that would have been a similar scenario.
We were turning up.
We were going crazy at about three beers.
Me and Eric were daggering on the dance floor.
You were daggering him like in Jamaica?
Yep.
Wow.
But someone handed me a drink and it seemed like a nice guy and I held it and he's like,
"Seriously dude, don't worry about it. I didn't do anything to it."
He said that?
And I took it and I was like, "I'm sure he's a nice guy.
Whatever I get in the bathroom, pour it right in the drain."
Wow.
Yeah.
That would also be maybe the worst thing you could say to somebody
right before you drunk them with the drink.
You don't say that.
It's all good, man. I didn't put anything in there.
Yeah.
I guess you'd say that to be funny about it, but even then,
even if you're joking about it...
You don't know if this guy's doing double reverse psychology on you or something.
There's a level of trust that you have to have with that person for that joke to work.
Did you know that guy at all?
Never met him.
Really?
Was it the bartender?
If it was your best friend?
Yeah, it was my best friend.
If it was your best friend who gave you that and said that, that'd be fine.
I'd be like, "Oh, he's pretending to roofie me."
Yeah, I don't really.
And I don't play those type of games.
Yeah, that's not cool.
Yeah, by the way, I'm going to shoot you when you drink this drink.
That's not cool to say.
What does that red flashing light mean?
That it's recording I think.
That it's recording. I'll double check.
I hope.
Lonely.
It's so lonely.
Does that sound like the chipmunk from that song?
It kind of does.
Lonely.
Did you press it?
Nope.
It sounded so real.
That was just me. That was my stuff.
What's that?
You saved the day.
Did I really?
Yeah, it was going to the bandmate who's going to die.
Whoa.
Because I plugged it into the wrong hole.
I plugged it into the wrong input hole.
Eww.
I told you I've been around cameras before.
It kind of seems like it.
I didn't realize that you were that kind of...
What was that laugh?
That scared me a little.
Do you think that you are on the precipice of a giant voice acting role?
Of course.
I'm trying to break into that industry.
Maybe new, like Little Mermaid.
I think movie.
You heard that thing I just did?
What?
The chipmunk that I did?
- Oh, did you hear what Pat did?
- No, you never said it. - No, do it again.
- Okay, God.
(imitates car engine)
- Oh, so you Meatwad.
- Yeah, basically I have that voice
and then my normal voice, and that's gonna get,
that's my whole reel right now, my voice acting reel.
- You wrote a show that's you and Meatwad
talking to each other? - Yeah.
- Doing like a comedians in cars thing with Meatwad?
- Why was he never on that show?
- Why was Meatwad never on comedians in cars?
- I don't know who this Meatwad.
You never seen Aqua Teen Hunger Force?
Oh, he's the hamburger.
He must have, he went to bed early.
He's not a hamburger.
I don't think I actually ever saw Aqua Teen Hunger Force.
You're missing out on some seriously good shit.
And that by the way seems like a little before your guys' time.
You don't know anything about my age.
Yeah.
Well, I guess not.
Because I was born in the wrong generation.
Me too.
I should have been born in 1994.
I think that people have said that to me my entire life.
Everyone thinks that I'm 30 because of my hair.
The first time we met I thought you were my age.
Yeah.
And then, but now I know I can see you.
He's younger than me.
How old are you?
25.
Bastard.
25, yeah.
For just a few short more months and then you join me up in the upper 20s.
I'll use my health insurance.
The high 20s.
My high health insurance.
Did I tell you my plan for my birthday?
I'm not actually going to go through with it, but I kind of want to.
Suicide.
What is it, dude?
It's technically suicide.
What is it?
I'm going to spend the day of my, a month before, just in case something really bad happens
when I do this, whole day, jackass stunts.
On your birthday.
All day, a month before, just in case I get severely injured and I need a month to recover.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, that is social suicide.
What about the continued care though, because, tell you what, some of those injuries will
keep you in the hospital for days.
Yeah, that's why I'm doing it a month before.
Okay, so what kind of jackass stunt would you do though?
Jump off a building with an umbrella.
Dan literally talked about doing that and he broke both of his legs.
Oh yeah.
Well you put me on the spot.
I didn't have all the explaining.
So you just stole his idea that he got hurt from doing?
I could.
Why would you do the exact same one that he did?
That's one that Bam did.
Okay, well he did it.
You need a new one.
Okay, jump from a building onto a tree.
I can't see you're stealing all of your jackass, you don't have a jackass brain.
I don't.
I have one right now.
Cover myself in hot oil.
Yeah.
You know who did that?
The amazing atheist.
Hot oil?
Burning oil?
Okay, hot water, fuck you.
Amazing atheist put hot oil on his penis.
Get pretty close to a volcano to the point where maybe my hand catches on fire.
Did you know, I could do jackass things.
Did you hear about the couple that died 40 years ago and they made a movie about them?
There was that girl that was on TikTok who went on a cruise and they did a
destination expedition to a volcano.
No, but in the lava didn't even hit him, but there was a group of people there
and the gas was so hot that it burned everybody to death except for her.
What?
And so she's in the hospital. She's with like, you know,
Why did they get so close?
They weren't even that close.
On a volcano?
Yeah, yeah. And the gas just bodied them.
Well, okay. For my birthday.
You want to do that?
I do not. I do not fuck with
lava or magma. I could do those.
Again, that's from Jackass. You do not have a creative
self-pranking brain. That's good though, lean into it.
I don't either. Well, that's the thing. I think it's more of a tribute to
Jackass. Who gives a fuck about that, dude? Do a
new thing. If you ask me, they've been doing tributes to themselves every fucking
movie since the first. Yeah, it's enough. Yeah, come up with some new shit. I went
off on Steve on our podcast. What do you say? Well, I think he's milking the
BAM Margera mental health crisis. And also, yeah, if you own damn ass. Yeah,
busted podcast. I kind of agree. But also on Steve. Oh, if you have been sober
more than one year, then I'm done hearing about it. Shut the fuck up.
That's enough. Oh, I had to, I was almost died and I have all these holes in my...
I was addicted to Whippets. Yeah, I was fucking addicted to Whippets.
Shut the fuck up, dude. Get a job. You do your podcast from a van. Shut up, bro.
He started his own skateboard company, made himself pro.
That's fake. You can't do that. That's, you are cheating. That's giantly cheating.
Yep. And I also, you were funnier when you were on all the drugs, buddy.
Get back on the Whippets. Get back on the whipped cream.
also stop doing stand-up comedy right now because it's actually an art form that a lot of people
work their entire lives at and you are parlaying your fame to become a regular at the comedy
store which is some people's number one dream.
Your closing joke, Steve-O, is that you get tased or punched by the biggest guy in the
crowd. What is that?
Yeah. How do you know that? You've seen him live?
I've seen him on the Charlie Sheen roast where he says he couldn't think of a closer so then
and he had Mike Tyson punch him in the face.
- I don't think he still does that.
I think he did that for that.
- Yeah, well then he also, I think his final--
- You thought that was his big--
- No, his final stand up thing, his special,
is him doing a stunt at the end.
- Oh, okay.
- Oh, like stapling his balls to his legs.
- Yeah.
- I haven't seen his special.
- One time, I used to, I fake doing whip-its one time
at work.
- Really?
- Everybody else was doing it, they're like,
"Eric, do it, do it, do it."
- At work?
- Yeah, 'cause we had whipped cream canisters.
- What job?
- I worked at a deli.
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah, whipped cream canisters, everybody was doing it and so I like faked and
then I pretended to be so out of it. Do your impression of it right now.
Oh,
it's just faking it.
Like coming. Everybody else is like, "Whoa."
Wow yeah, let's do it again. Yeah, give me another one. I'll manager from
that job, Jody Jody, you're so mean. Whoa,
come on now about 10 years ago now, but I hope you don't gotta be so
mean. Why you gotta be so rude? I don't know.
You don't remember that song? Why you gotta be so rude? We were making
♪ Deli food ♪
- Oh.
- ♪ We were doing whippets too ♪
- Damn.
- Why did this shit make your voice sound so good?
- I know, the singing voice?
Yeah, it's because you can hear yourself,
so you can actually tell what you're saying.
See, us three, we probably all suffer from allergies,
so when we get in there without a live studio monitor
trying to sing--
- Right, it's over.
- Way off, way, way off, because of the congestion.
- I'm on stage singing with my headphones on.
- Yep.
I'm hearing myself sing.
I want something just like this.
Do do do do do do.
That's my new favorite.
I think I'm going to do that at karaoke next time I go.
What song?
Coldplay and the Chainsmokers, Something Just Like This.
Do do do do do.
Is that the music video where there are monkeys?
How much you wanted something, how much you wanted this.
You know what I'm talking about?
No.
The Coldplay music video where they're all monkeys.
You're thinking of the Discovery Channel.
No, I'm not.
Yeah, you are.
The Coldplay video where there are monkeys.
I've never seen that one.
dumb as a rock. Neil used to show it to me.
I used to rule the world, the seas would rise when I gave the...
This makes you want to go all crazy with it.
Yeah, the world.
We need to get an auto-tune filter.
Oh, that'd be perfect.
Oh, please get one.
We were doing...
I used to rule the school.
It's like a little kid at school.
I used to rule the school, see the classes
♪ Classes and teachers too ♪
(laughing)
♪ And in the morning I was in homeroom ♪
♪ Yep, yep ♪
♪ Then I went to my other class ♪
♪ Yep, none of it rhymes at all ♪
♪ But it's more about the story ♪
♪ It's about how scary it would be ♪
♪ And then a robot would say ♪
♪ I used to rule the computer ♪
(laughing)
♪ Or something like that ♪
♪ I don't know, can't think of what else ♪
♪ Viva the chips ♪
♪ Give me a random filter ♪
for you there, buddy. You are number two, so I'm going to hit you with this one.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
No, have you? Yeah, they're really hard to use. They make you move it, make it.
Yours sounds so... Yours with the pitch up, you do sound exactly like that voice.
Like a Daft Punk voice? Yeah, I feel like mine is just way... I think I have too
much range in my normal talking thing. You have kind of a... I never noticed you
have a bit of a monotone to you. Do I? Yeah, I think so. I don't think so, man.
Or maybe it's a suit. Maybe you do have an amazing voice, but maybe it's the,
the, as soon as the pitch comes on,
maybe you're doing that because it sounds funnier.
Yeah. Maybe I just started working with this new guy. Who's I won't blow up his
details, but he works in Europe.
Blow up Jody's fucking detail. I did blow up Jody's.
So let's wait 10 years on this guy.
Right, right. But this guy has somehow the most calming voice I ever heard.
What did he sound like?
Hello?
Is he from Sweden?
Oh my God. It is a wave.
know a wave of calm. I'm just like asking more details because it's so calming.
When I like that, he goes, hello, Swedish guys do kind of have calming
voices for some reason. Do the most calming voice you can right now. Really?
And it's really try to calm us down or else you get shot and killed. OK, all
right, I'll do the most common calming voice I can think of. Silence of the
lambs. Yeah, you're dead. You're trying to do Morgan Freeman. Oh, that's kind of
that was scary. That was that was full. I'm trying to do it in the basket. I'm
gonna try. Does this sound coming? No. Now I'm hearing it. No, you're right.
There is a beautiful river that you're walking alongside of and there's noises
from every animal in the forest. Isn't calming me. This is common. This is I
I would say it works.
Pretty calm.
This is calming?
I think that was pretty calming.
And the most beautiful woman you've ever seen is topless.
Now I'm calm.
Walking right towards you with a giant, she has the face of Tig Notaro and the body of
Alexandra Daddario.
And she's walking directly at you.
But now she has a knife.
No!
Oh, I lost it there at the end.
Alright, do your calmest voice now.
Okay.
Hi.
Welcome to...
- Hi, welcome to my doctor's office.
(laughing)
I hear that you are in need of a cranial nerve exam today.
What's your first name?
- Greg.
- Thank you.
Last name?
And what is ailing you today?
How's your stomach feeling?
Excellent.
I'm scared of doctors. I hate doctors.
What? I listen to probably...
Do you listen to Dr. ASMR all the time?
Dr. ASMR, really?
That's calming to you?
Oh yeah.
Because he sleeps like a...
Vampire.
Like Master Chief.
Yeah.
He goes into every night...
Oh, you've got the sleep app.
I've got to get that.
He has a sleep app.
I do, dude.
Do you keep a mask on too?
No.
A sleeping mask?
Sometimes I put a pillow over my face.
So you do that and you wear headphones that play ASMR, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so...
You, Jesus Christ.
Can I lay like this?
no sense. You die every night. You die.
Essentially.
Yeah. All the senses are gone.
And I welcome it.
God, that's so sick.
It is scary.
Do you, so when you are looking up ASMRs, you're not listening to the ones that are
girls like, "Oh, I dropped my ass," or something. I don't know.
They drop their ass.
I have never written one of those, okay? That was the first time writing one and it was
on the spot.
Okay. I listen to almost exclusively like fugly men.
You have to. Because you might pop one while you're trying to fall asleep and it's a girl's
voice.
My whole perception of ASMRs is warped because the only ASMR that I know of is this video
of this guy, his name was like Tony Bamboni.
Tony Bamboni? Hello Poopsies?
Yeah.
What?
Seen him.
Yeah.
Who the fuck is this?
He would do the fairy ones.
Who are Poopsies?
the one that I saw it was him as a wood nymph or something and he is caught by
paparazzi. What does he do? Is he trying to be funny?
Stop, stop.
No paparazzi, no paparazzi.
That's calming. That was more calming than the first one.
That was way better than your scary one.
The problem was the first time you did it, you tried to sound too tough and too
much like a deep voice guy.
Yeah.
You need to have a nice calm voice.
- Hey, welcome.
- 'Cause I have a pretty low register.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, low cash register, broke boy.
- Yep.
- These people are legit good at like,
there's this one guy I listen to,
who's probably, I listen to probably 300 hours
of him talking.
And I don't know, he just is talking
for an hour and a half sometimes.
And sometimes I'll just stay up and listen
'cause it's a little bit interesting.
He's just going off his own.
- Does he tell a story?
- He tells stories, he gets into his opinions,
'cause he run out of gas.
- Yeah.
- Doing the role play out of certain points.
So your real opinions come out and that's, I think it's kind of beautiful.
So he starts talking about the vaccine and shit.
He starts talking about like how when he was growing up,
like his parents didn't appreciate
like how he wished he could have been a better father in certain ways.
Whoa. I mean, he gets really into it.
Imagine being that guy's kid or something.
And that's the only time you ever hear that shit is in a whispered voice.
And your dad's talking in a black ear.
he's hoping that his children look up his ASMR channel.
- Yeah, they fall asleep to it.
I don't think if my dad did anything,
I would watch it or listen to it.
- Yeah? - Really?
- Yeah, I remember-- - You'd be too scared?
- Yeah, kinda.
I remember my dad used to write,
for his fantasy football league,
he used to write a newsletter every Monday.
And I one time read it, and it was like,
literally all just complaining about his family.
(laughing)
Well, my son sucks at football.
No, but you?
Yes.
No.
And I was like, "Yeah, I don't think I want to read any more of these."
Yeah.
I had played Little League Baseball, and I remember hearing there was a kid on
our team named Doug, and he was horrible at... I mean, I was bad, but he was bad.
And his dad was so embarrassed. That one time I heard him say behind me, he's
like, "Fucking Doug."
And then he walked away and came back after the game.
What a perfect name to be saying like,
"God, fucking this stupid kid. Fucking Doug."
Like, why do you name your kid Doug?
Bill and Strong and Doug was like a scornful.
I just saw the craziest guy walk by.
Sorry to interrupt.
What did he do?
Tattoo all the way around his old guy.
Tattoos all over his face.
That's not that crazy.
That was, I mean, to see them walking, looking in, just like...
Not in Brooklyn, baby.
Yeah.
That's true.
Are you guys going to be doing man on the street type interviews now that you're in retail?
We could.
Should we?
Put a sign out, come on in.
Yeah.
I thought about it.
Let that fucker in.
We should do a couple episodes where it's just anybody.
We'll just leave the door open.
Anything goes.
You walk in.
This spot is so mother effing sick.
Yep.
And so close to all our houses.
It's close to my house.
Ridgewood.
Stand up.
I mean, I'll let everybody know that it's my house.
Oh yeah.
People basically know exactly where I live at this point.
Really?
who lives like two doors down, who one time he like stopped us when I first moved here
and he was like, "Hey man, I really like the podcast." I was like, "Oh, thank you." And
then he walked into the apartment next to mine.
No.
But he's a nice guy. He's a nice guy. But if he ever crosses me, I will attack him.
You think you have people that would recognize you in Des Moines?
Iowa?
Maybe.
Yeah, yeah.
Definitely. I was a hot bed for leftist podcasts like this. Yeah. And like Joy Tactics.
Oh yeah, they love our asses.
Explicitly political podcast like us and Joy Tactics.
Yeah, I interrupted the Little League stuff though.
No, that's about it.
Because I saw a crazy guy, but I had a,
I hit an inside the park home run
in Little League.
That just means that everybody is
such shitty.
That's not an indication
of your skill. That means that you
were playing against children.
My parents talked about that,
was a big proud moment and then I realized later like, oh yeah, that means that they were just
all everyone else was just super slow.
Well, yeah, because all the kids, I mean, did you you know who they put the worst kids they
put in the outfield and those kids when a ball gets out there, they go, fuck me.
That was this kid Scott.
Fuck me.
When I was when I played for the crisscross applesauce on the field anyway, so you got
to put the losers.
Exactly.
That was that's where I was center.
They put me second base and then I was next to Scott.
Scott Bolio, I think was his name.
That was not his name, motherfucker.
Scott, he sounds bolio.
And he had just seen Over the Hedge and really liked Hammy from Over the Hedge.
Which one is Hammy?
If you remember that movie.
Steve Carell's little squirrel character.
Oh, okay.
Who has ADHD.
Oh, Hammy.
And he would sit there and he would quote Hammy at me.
He wanted to be Hammy, I think.
That's cool.
And he would sit there and just scream like Hammy quotes at me.
I've never been so annoyed in my life just listening to this kid.
I remember a movie that no one talks about anymore.
Kids in middle school and shit like emulating characters from movies was so funny, dude.
There was a kid who later became my friend, but he was when Napoleon Dynamite came out,
he would just talk like Napoleon Dynamite and like say all the Napoleon Dynamite lines.
Yeah.
He was very, very cool.
And he had a Napoleon Dynamite backpack, which is pretty badass.
And you were probably what, six when Napoleon Dynamite came out?
I was in this is probably third grade or something by this point.
Man, there's never gonna be a hit like that again.
No. No.
A sleeper hit like that.
Nobody, the Mormons are done.
No one's buying DVDs anymore.
Not yet.
Is that how Napoleon Dynamite got big?
Yep. DVD sales.
Bring physical media back.
That's what used to make shit pop off.
Bring it back.
Was physical media. Renting, rental stores.
DVDs look better.
You used to be able to rent DVDs, not have to worry about it.
And don't just, I want specifically.
I want DVD ROMs that have games on.
Yeah, we've talked about this extensively.
The Elf DVD.
Very good games on there.
Santa Claus 2 DVD.
I want them to make one for three billboards outside of
Ebbing, Missouri where I can play.
You can make your own billboards.
I can play a word hunt or something.
That's what I want so badly, dude.
Yeah, that shit was the best.
The Banshees of Inisheren.
Media is fucking dead.
Yeah, I know.
It's over.
leaning on us so heavy and we're sitting here like trying our fucking best.
This is not our best dude. This is,
I've only touched maybe 18% of these numbers. So this is,
so now I could be at the WGA writers strike right now.
Oh, and I can be saying, Hey, ho, ho. There's that guy. He's back.
Did you see him? No. What is that fucking guy? He came back.
We got to face you away from the windows.
You could be sitting over there.
Yeah, or you could just maybe control your brain a little more.
That guy looks cool though.
Damn.
He does not seem like he looks cool.
He has tattoos on his head.
He has, you see that all the time.
It's like a tattoo helmet.
If somebody has a tattoo...
This whole thing, this whole part of his face is fine.
The rest of it is tattoos.
Well, you like tattoos though.
Yeah.
Yeah, I hate that shit.
Yeah, tattoos are foolish.
You hate tattoos?
I don't think I'm getting another one.
Yeah.
I don't think I need to.
You got one of the best I've ever seen, but I have some of the most busted tattoos on the planet.
He's lying, he has cool tattoos. He has a donkey.
Oh, I've seen your donkey.
That I thought was a horse when I got it.
I like the donkey, I think it's cool.
Well, that's the kind of tattoos that you like.
I like the donkey.
You like kind of stick and poke.
I don't like stick and poke.
You're going to come in one day with just a tattoo of a line.
Why are people getting that tattoo?
What's the line?
Just a black line on their arm and shit. Fuck you.
Black line around?
Just a black, yeah. What are you getting a line for?
There's that, I don't know. It's all these like
influencer style tattoos that people
are getting where it's like, oh I don't want to get. If you ever say that again
I will shove that microphone so
far down your mouth. Influencer style tattoos.
I will kill you with a single flick.
You ever seen that spot on, next to
Brookland? What's it called? That tattoo
place called Minimal Tattoo? That's
awful. It looks like an influencer like
vibes place. Yeah.
What is it, you get a tattoo of a triangle?
Fuck that dude. Something like that, yeah.
Oh, these are just multiple shapes on my arm.
No fucking shapes.
No, no, no.
I got this thing, I got this guy, he's cool.
I'm looking at these people's arms trying to do math and shit.
No, no, no.
Well, you guys know the story of my worst tattoo.
I don't think it's the worst, but my first tattoo,
it's this one, it's the 45 with the crown on it.
Trump.
Okay, well that's...
(laughing)
That's what I'm saying.
You know, my college improv team,
which is even more embarrassing, I feel like,
is called the 45 Kings, much respect to the current cast and crew.
45 Kings sounds like a white guy who does raps.
That sounds like an Italian guy.
Like an Ohio.
A white guy who does raps as in wrapping cars.
Yeah.
He has like a garage where he puts Pepsi wraps on people's cars for money.
But what about this tattoo?
Just that it was a stick and poke and is my first thing and I thought it.
I mean, look at that. Would you look at that and think Trump is king?
You know what I did think? I would say God Emperor Trump is what that guy was thinking
when he got that tattoo. I saw that and I was like, "Oh, why does he have the new Bam Margera
logo tattoo on his knee?" Does it look like that? It looks like that. No way. That's so
much sicker. But it's a 43. Oh, he has 43. Yeah, and I think it's supposed to be representative
of his son or something. His son, Phoenix Wolf Margera. That's his son's name? Phoenix Wolf,
That's fucking badass. He's going through it right now. I feel so sad. We're praying for him. We really are I got
I got like close to blackout drunk one time and was talking about Bam Margera at a party and I was close to tears
Oh, I mean, it's it's sad. Yeah, really the way
Addiction he was
Video I've ever seen a BAM in the last eight years. The first comment is always
It's always Bam died when Ryan Dunn died.
And it's like, come on now.
That's every single one.
Well they didn't hear the song that Bam put out immediately after Ryan Dunn died.
What was it?
Captain, er, Fuckface Unstoppable.
Bend my dick to my ass.
He did that for Ryan Dunn?
Like the year after Ryan Dunn died.
That was the first thing he put out.
Everyone's like, "I wonder how Bam's gonna like, you know, I wonder how he's gonna,
yeah, I wonder how he's gonna like, you know, come back from this first thing he does.
Bend my dick to my ass so I can't fuck myself." It's a dubstep fucking anthem.
If I was him, I would have, I think if that happened to me, if you died in a horrific
car accident and you exploded at 120 miles an hour and it was completely your fault,
like the ride down thing, I would move to China or Tibet or something.
I would become a monk. Yeah.
Because you'd finally know peace because I wasn't in your life.
Exactly. I'd finally have a clear head for the first time ever.
What the fuck am I doing here? And I would move to where I belong,
which is up there in the mountains. The white lion. Yes.
Thinking I'm going to like be like the boss or whatever.
A big tummy rugger of a lion's face.
I did become the monk that they all like train Kung Fu on.
He beat the shit out of me like a crash test dummy.
Yeah. Yeah. They say that they're calling you the white lion.
I'm like, yeah, I'm calling my mom. Basically, I'm the white lion.
Who does Batman study with in Batman Begins?
Ray Shaogul.
Oh, Ray Shaogul.
I'd go chill with him.
Liam Neeson.
Speaking of Batman.
What, you have a Batman mask over there?
There is a Batman mask over there.
Yeah, it's not mine.
So I think it's Alex's.
I think it's Alex's.
Oh, it's for Alex.
Yeah.
We share this space with him.
All right. We got to go to the gym, but you want to tell people where to find Joy Tactics
online.
Oh, yeah.
Well, it's on Spotify, Apple Music.
Apple Podcast.
Oh, maybe I'll do that. It's on YouTube.
It's on YouTube, too. We put it everywhere. Jack and I are editing the fuck out of it.
And also the Patreon.
Oh, and we got a crazy-ass Patreon.
Because I know y'all got to eat.
We got to eat.
You got to eat.
Yeah.
There's new restaurants every day.
Alright, thank you for coming, Eric.
God bless you guys.
Thank you for having me.