I think in action, okay, so today we have you have water in a Gatorade water
in a Gator, I got water in a Fiji and and a coffee, which I have learned. I'm
a pretty often a two beverage user user. I see the thing is I will have a drink
but I'll have it on my walk over most of the time.
He is the weasel. I will have no drink
on set because if I had a drink you guys would hear me slurping all episodes.
It's because it's a technique thing. You have a
poor drinking technique. Oh yeah. I have a terrible drinking technique.
What do you do? What I do is I do this. I binge drink. Test it on this.
I binge drink pretty much everything. Show the people. No I'm not drinking any caffeine anymore.
I had a prime blue raspberry. It's not even a sip of coffee that would be too much.
A sip of coffee would turn, I think the whole world around me would slow down.
That's kind of what you want though.
No, the whole world I'd be in bullet time, like over the hedge.
You'd be like over the hedge, yeah.
Yeah, I'd be exactly like over the hedge.
Do you guys ever feel like living in the United States of America is the real bullet time?
Yep.
Oh.
See, if they wanted to switch to video, if they wanted to really, like, if they wanted
to make a spreadsheet of something, all of our damn hats.
So somebody just yeah, somebody made a if our if our the only employee that he has to do
one thing every day and he's not it is one thing we do.
We do be able to pull it up for us. He's the one that present. He showed us this. He's
completely gone. Yeah, he sent us this. This is somebody made a let me see what their name
is. I'll give them credit. Bobby Brown bail bonds. He is on strike two of not showing
coming up to maybe he's on strike. Did you guys consider that? Oh my God, I
might not even consider that for what camera switcher strike. Have you not
heard there's a camera switcher strike going on really? Yeah, it's him and like
two other people. He works for the WGA and the Wimps Guild of America. That's
right. Yeah, the Wimps and Girls of America. Yeah, so it looks like so
somebody made a
spreadsheet that has the beverages of every episode that we've done on video
shows the beverage. So this will be one for Gatorade for for so yeah, that's I
guess I wanted this is something I did want to address. I'll let you complete
talk about what this is, but I am I do I will need to clear the air. Okay,
go ahead, go okay. No, you go ahead. Okay, so what I would like to say off
the bat is that I
am just like a madman with my beverage choices. I've always yeah, I have known
that I kind of I always noticed that you would love to bring a cup of coffee.
Well, I like bring it like this. Yeah, and I do like walking around
holding the coffee from the top already a spill right here and guess that's not
that well you because I don't fucking sit there in the middle asshole. No, you
spilled that, but I do like walking in like this. I feel you know what it is. I
feel like I like feeling like I'm going to work. So I like feeling like this is
like when I used to have a like an office job. This is how I would show up.
I've never had an office job, so I drink when I'm going to work. I'm pounding back like a 200 milligram caffeine thing.
For me, an office job means taking a K-cup and drinking five or six K-cups to take away their K-cups.
Me, I'm so fucked up from not sleeping the night before.
Shotgunning a monster on my way to work.
Eating the cream, drinking the creams.
yeah. Oh, we need to get we need to get some of those cream so that we can get
those creams, those creams, those
you remember one time we had that rancid tea. We should get that. Oh yeah,
one time me and Cameron at our old job. We had we made we submitted all the
time and we made this tea and it was only time I've ever seen spoiled tea.
It was completely rancid and then we tried and then I like we made and like
we could smell the tea bag and tell it was like rancid. Then you look it up in
every single review of the it was like fifty fifty. It was like there's some
type of tea where like it's like a yeah you half the time it completely goes
bad and it tastes like
vomit yeah. Do you remember when there was the controversy in our old office
about blueberry? I do remember the blueberry. There was a very coffee.
There was a controversy of what a fuck they bought our old office because
somebody bought a variety pack, a cura cake up a blue mountain or green
blue bound coffee variety,
yeah and it was and it had
like yeah. It was like you know, like it was like every flavor like breakfast
blend, dark roast, light roast,
yeah it was three. It was those three and then blueberry and the blue berry
one. When you turned it on on the cake up, it smelled like a diaper yeah,
smelled like it filled the entire office with entire office. I'd never had it. I
started drinking it because I eventually got got brought over, but we had this
same guy that we worked with who would miss him. I miss him so much. He was the
best guy ever. He really was. I actually love him, but he would I remember this
dude yeah. He would like when everybody started saying like oh God, that coffee
smells terrible. He started being like I actually like it yeah and started
making it every single day. How I remember it was like everyone was like
God that smells horrible, like who's even having this and then like and we
like didn't know who it was like who was drinking it all the time because we
come in, it would smell like blueberry and one time seeing him making it and
be like yeah, you're the one who's been making the blueberries like yeah. I
love it yeah and then he kind of just leaned into it more because we hated it
and we and but then eventually we ran out of every other kind of coffee and so
here I am sitting there making the blueberry coffee right kind of just like
and the first time I was what am I going to do go to Starbucks? Fuck no,
I was broke, don't get donuts right next to the whole reason why I liked that
job was that I could get free coffee, free coffee, free food all the time.
you get to work an event and you just take all yeah. We used to have to go
like I mean that's what I I depended on that yeah on every other day.
Basically, I would have to go and film you get some kind of a set up like a
P a system. No, it's just a little that was the only only time until like this
year that I ever had a lobster roll. Yeah, I would always feel like a cat
that they were like giving scratch to at the end of the event. That's how they
like that's how they would lick my lips and look at like sixteen grapes that
they had like left over that were all the like bad. Well, that's how they'd
spokesy to do those jobs, because no one would want to do it, because it was you
would have to sit in a room for an hour and a half and film the most boring
presentation of all yeah, but like our boss would send out emails or the
subject line, which is like a hundred dollars and then like in the body of
you like if you work this event, they're going to give you food. Yeah, you get
ten bucks an hour plus
I'm fucking there, and it would be a mad dash to reply to the email first and
say I can do that yeah skipping class to do yeah literally. I would do that all
every time I'd skip it, I would skip anything to get like and I would do I
would take I would take the leftovers yeah like I would just hope to God that
everybody would leave the room before taking the leftovers and assume that I
was going to clean it up and then I was put it in my backpack. So I'd go home
with like ten turkey sandwiches. Truly, I did that in high school, though I did
that. I would work these like events. I would like go there's this guy. I forget
name but I worked for him and my job was videographer and I would just go and I would record like
all school assemblies for the elementary school and stuff like that. So I would just be skipping
like, it's a, it's, I'm amazed that I graduated high school because I skipped so many classes
just to go do like, it's like, oh I'm sorry I have to go take this Sony Handycam and film
like the first graders choir assembly. You liked it. Yeah. I would get free sandwiches
and then he would take me to Walmart after.
As like a reward?
No, he just needed to go.
My job, my other job in high school was videographer for the
football coach.
His personal videographer.
Yeah.
Around the house.
Can you take a video to show my wife how to watch this?
Like Brian.
Following around Joe Rogan, taking videos of everything he does.
You were doing his blog.
Yeah, pretty much.
They would make me stand in this little fucking thing on top of like next to where the announcers were for the football game.
So I just stand up there with a camera.
And if I like missed a shot like you get really mad at me.
But I had to like he was like all right you record once the whistle starts.
So I had to like record every single fucking play.
So he would have like a playback thing the whole game the whole game.
But he didn't have like a good enough camera.
He didn't have a good enough camera.
so all the footage is like like so you know, like they have the digital zooms
on those cameras, all digital zoom yeah. So I just like blurriest fucking
because I couldn't let you near the field because you'd scream. Yeah, I
would be screaming. Yeah, I would be I'd be
I'd be
jumping over
Okay, I need to clear the air. If I was oh, wait, I need to clear the air.
Somebody this is weighing on me, this chart that this person made. I didn't
count, but they put a whole lot of entries for Gatorade. They did a whole
lot of Gatorade. And specifically, they put Gatorade and the flavor or the
color or whatever of Gatorade. At least 50% of those,
that's water in a Gatorade bottle. Fuck me. And I feel like, okay, I'm not
gonna, I mean, I'm not gonna say like, okay, you have to be zooming in on
this video, but I feel like you can tell the difference between water and
Gatorade. What if it's a Gatorade Zero? I honestly, I can't tell. It's not
Gatorade Zero, 'cause they wrote the flavor 'cause they look at the bottle.
Gatorade. You could be pouring Propel into your Gatorade bottle. What if it's
Gatorade Zero color? They also put, they said on the thing, they said,
like, "No, some of those Gatorades could be water in a Gatorade bottle."
So they knew. So they knew, but they still... They had a hunch. But they
still made it look like I drank a Gatorade every single day. And I'd like
to say, pretty much every time that I had a Solo cup, which there's a
lot of solo cup. That was water. I'm a water drinker out of the solo. We still
have really solo cups at the old office. I drink water. I had no drinks pretty
much. That's not true. You had a lot of drinks. I had a good chunk of drinks,
but I thought, as soon as Jubio sent me that and it said list of drinks,
I was like, "Okay,
I am gonna have a revelation about how much soda I drink." So I'd like to...
And then I realized, "Oh yeah, no, I'm not drinking as much soda as I
I'd like to defend myself. I am somebody who is easily parched. I have a
parchable mouth. I have a salad. The number one way to get I think I might
have coffee. I might have type two diabetes. Yeah, well, sometimes I think
that because I pee pretty much once an hour. Yeah, I think that too. I
probably because of diabetes. It's probably because all the things you're
drinking, but I want to drink those things. So what does that say
that you're thirsty.
So why am I thirsty?
Probably because I have a fucking deadly disease.
It might be a kidney problem, not type 2 diabetes.
You could be.
Diabetes is a kidney problem.
It is a kidney problem.
Okay.
I thought it was a pancreatic problem.
Nope, it's kidneys.
Alright.
I was going to say we could have like a whole like fundraiser to get you on dialysis or
something.
I don't need.
I'm not dying yet.
He's dying.
from what I've known him for four years now, five years, every single day he
tells me I just shit liquid, like black liquid. I think my insides are failing.
I don't say any of this. I didn't shit. I've had normal shits recently. My shits
have been perfect. As long as I've known you, every single day you tell me
something like, "I think this is it. I think this is the big one. I think I'm
done." That's not true. That's what I say. That's what he says. He says he's
always having he has he has diarrhea, but he like likes it. He likes to tell
everyone he's like he loves
a little
come out of the bathroom when you go. I just had a diarrhea. Well, because I
feel like allergies and then you're okay. Here's the thing about diarrhea
because I can't breathe. That's why that noise is I diarrhea in the work toilet.
It's best you guys hear it for me. We hear it from you before you say a word
Hey, hold now hold on no no a hundred percent you are you. I think I hate to
say it what you are the loudest shitter. Oh, there's no doubt every time that
every time that you would go to the bathroom at the old office, you just
hear
it's like somebody let go of a fucking balloon. Yeah, see I always was like
what's going on when you do that with the balloon. You guys like
it was like what's going on until I seen this spreadsheet and says I drink
about four
so yeah
diarrhea all the fucking time. You're
drinking the worst coffee in the world from the bodegas. I've had diarrhea in
weeks. It's been probably the longest run of my life. I do not believe that
because I've heard to use the bathroom here. That's not diarrhea. That's just
far tiding between the poop
farts hiding between the you've never had that where like you go, you put out
you put out a turd and then there's like you have like six inches of part air
and then another turn.
The title is farts hiding between the poop pieces in the songs like I told
you that you were fifteen and not yeah. I have you guys been keeping up. Do you
know about this this e sports situation that's going on in the world. I don't
know pay attention to that. I pay attention to mostly skateboarding and
music. Yeah,
I mostly pay attention to literature.
There's this guy you guys will be interested in this guy. I think no as
maybe told me probably a little bit just due to he's a valor player used to play
for a team called Sentinels. Yes, he's told me. Yeah, so he's he's having like
like a full psychotic break and it's very sad, but it is it's creating some
pretty amazing stuff. He's been doing these streams where his face is like so,
so three months ago he got arrested trying to buy a Lamborghini, 'cause they
wouldn't, they wouldn't sell him a Lamborghini, 'cause he didn't have the
money for it, and he was like, I'm not leaving a T like one, he just like sat
on a Lamborghini until they arrested him, and then he was like radio silent for
months, and then he started like tweeting about how he's gonna go live
again, and so he's been tweeting. So I just have to read some of these. These
are he's posting like pictures of like a really fucked up weed set up and then
he's like Uber eating McDonald's and just posting his food every single day
and in between he's saying stuff like
like
am I an AI?
I'm going to Porsche tomorrow morning to pick up my car, plus a $100,000,000
check to settle this war.
He's tweeting the inward
now. Oh my God, I just saw that he's calling himself hunter is the first
name is hunter. He's calling himself hunter or taga because he thinks that
he's marrying chin or
he's taking her last. I'm going to go masturbate to Jenna or take a source
material source material, which I don't know what that means means he's
animated her in source film maker. He's posting he's referring to himself as
Eric Cartman
he's he's saying all nuclear weapons must be deactivated. I believe you know what
I'm on yeah, he's yeah, he's kind of spit. I mean he really a lot of this is
is like spitting honestly he's he's
keeps talking about Joe Biden. He's saying can I have the presidential
position
and I think that'll work. I think if he tweets at Joe Biden and retards
everywhere in politics here in America, but we can fix that. Marry me, Jenna
Ortega back from jail again.
man.
Man, he what are his live streams, though, so the streams are he goes live
and he plays Valorant and he's so clearly cooked on Benzos. He has like a
most insanely puffy face looks like he's been stung by a bee. He like keeps
forgetting to mute and unmute his Mike and and the entire stream is him playing
Valor and just frying being really, really good, but then also he's getting
calls from every single person in his life constantly and they're telling him
stop streaming and he's just like
he just like mumbles out everything yeah. This is my one of my favorite ones.
So like I said, he's calling himself Eric Cartman, twenty four year old Eric
Cartman here. Great idea to stream soon. Sure, people will be reasonable and not
hurt because why would we anyway? Nothing else matters power through control, not
dominance. This nation doesn't take war lightly, but nothing can stop the United
States. Is everyone brainwashed or am I retarded?
he's just got these heaters after heater after heaters and then my favorite one
is this where he says
where he said he he kind of gets you here. He he says I feel at peace. This
was like after he had this stream where he like was
mumbling and his face looked all fucked up. He says I feel at peace currently
figuring out the situation slowly, but I also feel very alone because I can't
interact with people close to me. Thank you all for the support. Recently, it
means the world to me, so I'm going global now with my ideas
to gain some political
damn. It's something I've been trying to do is go. I thought you were saying
like you're trying to have a mental break. No,
it's so crazy that one day you can just like snap like that. It's literally
just sounds like a matty gold to need valor ranked. I'm somewhat addicted to
the thrill of such a game. I mean it's a true miracle.
It's just so scary that you can just snap like that one day and then it's
like you have no idea that you are
like completely crazy. Everybody who does that and knows exactly what they're
doing. Yeah, they're all playing, they're all playing a joke. And they have to be
held accountable for every single thing that they did. Yeah, I do, I mean I just
think like,
I don't know man, I feel like there's no, if you do something like that, like play
video games for a living, there pretty much is no other ending but that to it.
Yeah.
Right? Like how else do you get out of that life?
That happened to, what's his name, Atika or whatever.
I don't know who that is.
He was the Super Smash Brothers streamer. They used to have a big mural of him by my old apartment,
like my first place in New York. There was a huge ass mural of him. He like had a,
he had like a psychotic break and then like killed himself.
It's like the saddest, it's the saddest like streamer story besides like, what's his name?
Wings of Redemption.
Crying Chris, the streamer.
Crying Chris had a really sad story.
Crying Chris had one of the saddest
streaming stories in the world
because it was just like, you know,
he started out really good like
Modern Warfare 2 player in like
2011 and then out of
nowhere all of his streams,
Trickshotta, FaZe Clan, whatever,
and then all of his streams are just
him playing Nelly and Tim McGraw.
Well, he started...
It's all in my head.
And he's playing like,
he's playing Heavy Rain muted.
Heavy Rain on mute just crying.
He was playing Heavy Main on TF2 and he would only do taunts.
So he would get killed.
So he was like, "I've lived a million lifetimes."
It was that heavy.
That's sad as fuck.
I guess the end point of being a streamer is either that you are caught doing something you shouldn't do
while the camera is on because you forget or you completely get driven crazy by the pressure that that hasn't happened yet.
I think that's actually what...
what what is going to wondering when it will happen, what the thing is going to
be. Is it just going to be that I stand up and I'm not wearing pants? I feel
like I or am I going to like throw my dog out the window. If I was a streamer,
I think I would probably try to get that out day one. Yeah, I think I would like
turn on the thing is you really here's my penis. You really want it to be
accidental nudity because any yeah that I feel like the ones you always hear
about are like yeah. He cut his girlfriend's head off. Well, he didn't
realize that the camera was on cutting. Yes, saw your head off to be like
looks like I was
running to the key board and pressing a button.
Yeah, these streamers are sick. There's
people. It is the craziest profession in the world besides professional chef or
like that's or volcano skydiver, yeah skydiver, maybe back flip front flipper,
navy seal with PTSD or trying to work in
before hit man in an acting class or you see the new episode. No, I haven't seen
the last two. I've never seen a single episode. I don't care. People shit on it
because it's Bill Hader with his head up his ass. Let's talk about it. All right,
let's go. All right, let's set so a panel on Barry. Barry, the season four
premiere was intense. Fuchs is in jail, Barry's in jail. Snowho Hank is trying to buy some
sand. What else happens? You've got to watch to find out. You just gave all the fucking
spoilers and then you say, but you have to watch to find out what he does with the sand.
That's not a spoiler. You're trying to buy sand? That's in the trailer. Oh, the sand thing
is a spoiler. Barry, I watched the first season. Barry, this show with other more
for quality program. I'd rather
go with a bunch of other actually good shows. Yeah, I think it's underground.
Maybe make a show about different kinds of areas right now. My everyone, I
think for every point in my in your life, you have to have something that
you have never watched, never seen or anything and that's because you're a
born hater. You just insist that you don't really bad. I don't believe it.
I think you have to have a philosophy. Yeah, I know it's the one your
philosophy. I mean you said you as in the
I
I think all three of us do that. I don't have something like you. Oh my what do I
hate? What do I hate? What do I hate? You hate so many one thing mother fucker. I
dare you if I hate so many you hate so many. I'll say like, oh yeah, it's pretty
fun. You're like, oh, okay. So your example is this thing. I have multiple
examples that I cannot think of right then. You don't have multiple examples,
buddy. Nice try. I'm not a hater. You're a hater in the sense of you say
something is gay.
Yeah, I would never say the G word. But you don't say, you don't say, you
don't walk around being like, "I hate this," but if someone mentions something,
you'll call it gay. You know what else we'll do? Okay, perfect example. Okay,
now you have one. I can tell you have a really good one, 'cause you moved the
microphone away. Perfect example. To breathe.
Don't you say skateboarding. Three weeks ago, no, two weeks ago,
We're at the bar. It doesn't matter what I'm going to lie. I'm putting the
evidence out there. Okay. And there is receipts and people on your close
friends' Insta will know.
Two or three weeks ago, Neil's show or my old roommate, he has a show at
Revision Lounge. You can check it out.
He's on the bill. We're hanging out at the bar after the show. He says,
"I've been getting really into Pink Panther recently." Pink Panther is great.
That's the opposite. I like it.
You did used to hate Pink Panther. When he listened to Pink Panther, you made fun of it.
Yeah, I didn't hate her. I said I didn't want her to come to America, drop that bomb.
No.
Don't have a bomb.
And I still think that.
Because I was doing my DJ set last year and I put the song in there.
I was sure this was earlier than I'd ever been to one of your DJ sets.
I've avoided them at all costs.
You we did a show with Jacques that had a DJ set.
And I went to the bathroom.
You did. You stayed in the bathroom the whole time. Didn't want to hear me.
I don't want to hear that bullshit.
I actually think I left right after, but it was that the beginning of the show.
Oh well, I then I was definitely not there.
Well, there's one example you hated on it and then once it became a thing that
you found you liked it.
So this is not a good example. Check me is not a good. Yeah, I actually
thought of a bunch of examples that I can't say yeah, because they're all our
close friends.
Don't say that does everyone we know I do yeah, just like everyone we know I
hated and until just one day I was like actually or you think I still hate you
know people who you don't know who you hate like people you never met before
yep that you just are prejudice towards you're making me sound awful. I don't
have prejudice. This is now you're lying. I'll go with the pink panther thing,
but now you're lying and I don't like that at all and you know what I hate is
a lot of political figures that you really hate that you never met or given
a chance. I don't I was thinking about as well that people are shitting on
this lady, this old fucking raggedy bones bitch, Dianne Feinstein.
What's her deal?
Just some ancient lady who has no idea where she is.
Why are people like...
She is one million years old and she needs to give up her senate seat.
I literally do not give a fuck who is in any office on this planet.
I hate her.
Yeah, you do.
You hate the government.
No, I do not.
You hate the office of the government.
I don't hate it.
I'm indifferent.
Daryl?
If Daryl doesn't stay in that office, then I will completely blame him.
Well, yeah, because he moved up from the warehouse.
I Darrell is honestly one of the few things in this world that I'm pretty
sacred about. Yeah yeah. Darrell Philbin. Darrell Philbin from the office. That's
the one thing that I think the first time that I met you back in 2011 I think.
Yeah. Hey I'm Caleb you're wearing a shirt and there's a picture of Craig Robinson.
Let's do an impression of each other the day that we met. Okay here's my
my impression of you.
And then I really how I used to you literally, I remember I met you. I was
hanging. I met you. You were with Ben and you like got up on. I was like
talking to Ben and like you were his little brother. You got up on the
fountain. That was right next to and you like walked up and down the fountain.
I remember one of the first times that--
- Really tall guy, right?
- Yeah, you.
One of the first times that I hung out with Patrick,
what I remember is that he was,
we were in that little alleyway that led to a city place,
and you were on your skateboard.
- That wasn't mine, that was Shev's.
- Oh, excuse me.
- That was Shev's.
- You were on somebody else's skateboard,
that's an important detail.
And you were doing some tricks that you weren't landing,
and you were saying like,
man, I haven't skateboarded in a while,
and I was thinking, why is he doing this?
What's he doing? And that was a brick road also. That's tough to skate on.
Yeah. I think I hadn't skated... I think that day, honestly, was the day that I
was like, "I should start skating again." When did you? That's so crazy.
That is genuinely like... 'Cause I think I almost landed a kick flip and then
I was like, "Oh, fuck." I used to be good at that. Why did you stop?
fat one. Fat, but that's a grad. You don't get, you don't wake up one day and be
like, "Fuck me, I'm fat. Time to stop skating." No, I did that. I think I was
just like, I think I genuinely was like, "Oh, I don't know." Like, it's embarrassing
for like somebody my age to still be skateboarding. And you said that when you
were 19. Yeah, I said that when I was 19, I stopped skating for a really long
time. And then I met you guys when I was like 21. And now you're kind of going
into the OG, kind of old, older man. Yeah, yeah, really old man. Old head's spurning
wisdom of the children. Old head who, who,
old head who what? Who's cracking all of his single bones every single day.
Cracking them? Cracking all of them single bones. Breaking them or cracking them like a
knuckle? And he hangs out with the 16 year olds and says, man, I used to be able
to do that. Man, I used to be... It used to be different, man. Man, you used to not
be able to wear high ass pants, but now... You used to be able to say what you want
to. We used to wear high heels when we skated back in 2015. We used to get on our
our skateboards, we used to get on our-
Man, we used to wear polka dots.
Man, shit's just different out.
I used to wear a blue shirt with a big star on it.
Shit is just different.
We used to walk around-
I forgot about the star shirt.
I used to wear a dark blue shirt.
A navy blue shirt with a gold star.
A big yellow gold star.
Man, back in my day, when we skateboarded, we used to all wear
that Sriracha shirt.
Yep.
We used to walk around with the Sriracha shirt on.
All the skateboards used to be shaped like the Sriracha bottle.
What is up with men who wear the Sriracha shirt?
It's the new try for sure off of your body. The red Sriracha shirt with the
khaki cargoes. You do not need to be shopping at Marshalls. What's that type
of fabric? That's what I was a type of person who goes to Marshall's. The
polyester one or the like the all over print, the all over print one that's
kind of like a soccer jersey. I'm talking about the red shirt that is like,
yeah, it kind of has, it's like very stretchy. Yeah. It stretches over a fat
guy's belly. Well, that's a... And he wears a Sriracha thing because he's
he's like, oh, it's food. I think that's a sixty forty cotton polyester bland
shirt. I think the next shirt that's going to catch on because the sriracha
shirt that I mean,
I think the next one is going to be a mayonnaise shirt.
Helman's yeah, that's literally these guys would be wearing a man. I was
available, yeah, instead of the sriracha, where the sriracha shirt, because they
think it's exotic. That's the that's the fat guy equivalent of walking around
with a shirt. That's a movie poster that has Japanese characters. Yeah,
name of the movie there is like yeah. I like I like sauces, but I like exotic
there's this kid on my bus in middle school. It's a ratchet shirt kid. He
definitely was a Sir Roger shirt kid. He was a pretty big boy and the guy, this
kid in the back of the bus, Hunter was trying to get his attention and he's any
I think he was wearing headphones and somebody like tapped him on the shoulder
as soon as like Hunter was like hey fatty. There's a
in the back of the bus.
That's mean. He turned around immediately and then the name I would to the name,
the name mayonnaise stuck
because he dared to look at somebody who yelled at him, who was yelling at him
for calling it horrible. I just thought of any, then he embraced it and we were
just kind of like all right man, all right mayonnaise.
It is a cool nickname.
I don't like that. Yeah, that is pretty sick. That's a good one. I just came up
with a scenario that I want to lay out for you guys really quick. Go. So you see
a guy, he's wearing a Sriracha shirt. Yeah, he's like maybe, maybe, maybe he's
on your maybe
can't help myself. I pull it down right there in the middle of a bus stop. I'm
fucking sucking his cock. I pull down those khaki cargoes. I pull down his Bob
Ross underwear and I just I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm
on his fucking balls. I'm getting the whole thing down there. Maybe he's on,
maybe he's on your on your daily commute like he's on your bus or something,
and then I do it every day. I don't know him in a saran sure bus driver,
which
I don't care. I'll give him road head. Why drive the bus? All right, get up
here and you think okay, this is it's a saran shirt guy great like oh great.
He's wearing the saran shirt and then the next day you get on the bus. He's
wearing another shirt. Kikoman so sauce next day, Heinz Ketchup next day
Helman's man. You realize he's a full sauce. He's a
thought he was a Sirachus. No, just so is a full sauce ward. Wow! His name is
Jed Sossman. I do want I do want the perfect t shirt rotation is Monday.
Wake up Sirachus shirt Tuesday, wake up dark side of the moon shirt yeah and all
of these by the way, two sizes too small yeah like so spray, except in the arms
they're big in the arms. Somehow dark, when they know Wednesday, Dr Pepper
Wednesday is the Dr Pepper, the faded
Friday Friday, well, he's green try for a shirt gold. Well, yeah, I know, but
nothing on
Thursday. No sure day is a button down. That's a
print of oh with a vest. Yeah, there's days. Thursday is definitely a bright
button down. Yeah, like a really bright one, like a pink, a pink button down
with a pattern on it. Yeah, Saturday, it's the weekend. It's a try for shirt,
but he cut the sleeves off. Well, that's tough. Yeah, that is tough.
the triforce shirt and the khaki cargo Sunday, maybe a maybe a Sunday's going
to church. So it's a full suit, so it's the same as the same as Thursday, but I
want other shirts. I want a nirvana shirt in there. Yeah, a really, really
bad nirvana shirt would be good in there. Star Wars, Empire Strikes Back,
faces of Vader, the faces of expressions of Vader shirt is going to be here.
Yeah, see, but that's a little too like even those guys, but that's how he's
wearing it. He's wearing it. Ironically, yeah, okay, as he's like I would never
for this. I'll wear a fucking
Helman's mustard shirt, but I'm not wearing
fucking
Helman's Mayo T shirt. It would dare I say it would be a shirt that would go
hard. It would go hard. Yeah, wow,
I would wear that. I think shirts
the guy. It was like a genuine like do you think one day they asked it like who
was the first guy was like, let's put fucking Sirach on a shirt. People will
wear that. Yeah, I mean, it was you know, what happened in fourteen? Well,
actually, nobody what happened was any of them and then they got to marshals
and they went crazy. A guy was wearing a plain t shirt. Yeah, he was eating
food. He got Sirach on his shirt. His friend said, Hey man, you got Sirach on
your shirt. Why pull up above his head? Sirach shirt.
You know what it actually was. I think I do. I think they make no money off
shirts than they do the fucking tops.
So in 2014, like yeah, like everybody, like they had like the fucking Sriracha like key
chain and stuff that you could like keep that shit.
Why did they, who did that?
I don't know.
Why did Sriracha become a...
There has to be some like...
The company that makes Sriracha.
One ingenious marketing guy who did all this stuff.
It was Paul Rodriguez of the Permanent Skateboards.
The Power Rangers guy.
Paul Rodriguez did this collab with Sriracha.
No that is not the first thing he did.
No, it was huge. It was like a really big collab. They were making like Sriracha skateboards
and all the Sriracha shirts were gone through Primitive.
They would not go Sriracha skateboard first.
They did Kikkoman. They did the Kikkoman soy sauce too. They did a Kikkoman soy sauce cruiser
board that's shaped like the soy sauce bottle.
Oh, and our motherfuckers walking around with Kikkoman soy sauce shirts? Not that often.
They used to.
No, no, no, no.
The primitive Kikkoman soy sauce collab was also very big.
Who thinks soy sauce is primitive?
No, the skateboard company.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I don't know why I know all that, but I know it.
I know why you know all that.
Because you like skating.
Also their Naruto and Dragon Ball Z collabs are the only thing that's keeping them afloat.
Which is insane.
Oh wait, really?
Yeah.
I'm sorry. I didn't realize that.
That's why their team is so big.
I really hope nothing happens to those two collabs then.
They'll probably go under.
No, Tiago Lemons would not get a check.
Tiago Lemons?
Tiago Lemons would not get a check.
What a fucking normal name to have.
He's Brazilian.
Lemons?
He's Brazilian, that's why.
You know, have you ever heard of Brazilian...
Why is he not named Tiago Lime?
Have you seen the Brazilian lemonade thing?
Yeah, it looks like shit.
Dude, it's limes. They're calling it lemonade. It's all limes and it's milk.
In Spanish they call it the same thing. It's just a lemon.
Limon.
It's the same.
It's the same?
Yeah. Is it the same fruit? It's not the same fruit, but they just, it's just a,
it's a, they're both a, a, a Limon.
So they at least say Limon Amarillo? Limon Trotsky. Um, not really.
They just don't have, they don't even know how to tell the difference.
They just don't give a fuck. It's not that big of a deal.
It's like the difference between an, a red apple or a green apple.
We don't know how to,
I don't know how to differentiate between those two.
you the day that I found out I was allergic to raw apples is devastating.
I used to love to just you know, a big honey crisp and just take a big old
bite out of it. A honey what if you wait, where you were you not allergic to
apples and then you became allergic to apples, you know, like those allergies
that you get when you like like every seven years. So you didn't used to be
allergic and then you became allergic. I think so yeah, well, I wasn't alert. I
found out because I ate a big bag of cherries and then you thought these are
kind of like a full
stomach hurt and then my stomach was swollen. It's six hundred cherries
maraschino cherries
maraschino cherry and I threw a do maraschino other fruits. I agree a
maraschino banana sounds so
fucking good
where you can eat the peel. Oh,
Maraschino melon maraschino, you know, it actually would be good. Yeah, I
think it's just got sugar on it. Right there. She no, I don't even know
Maraschino Apple. Who's Maraschino? Maraschino is a former WNBA player.
I feel like we talked about this before, so tell me if we did, but I knew this before and I completely forgot about it,
but then I was talking about it with my family when I was back in Boston.
We already talked about this.
That Scally Bread is only in Boston.
Yeah, I was talking about Scally Bread last night.
Yeah, and it's called that because there was a family called the Scally family.
The Scally family in the North End, yeah.
I looked it up because I was looking when I first moved here. I was trying to buy
scally bread somewhere thinking about something. What I am trying to make
something work in my head. Okay,
all right, go ahead.
I'm still going to go. Now I was trying to do maybe a Terry Shivo cherry, but
then I got now I would have to be a vegetable. Well, that's what I was
thinking about how funny it would be to be talking about somebody who had a
brain injury in there in a coma and like you're it's like your dad telling
somebody and he's like, "Yeah, Chris, he fell off a ladder. He's stuck in the hospital. He's
a complete fruit now."
He's just getting confused. "Yeah, it's real sad. My cousin went to the hospital. He's
a fruitcake." Anyway, sorry. You guys talk about bread.
I do think a Terry Shivo cherry is good.
What about a maraschino human?
That would just be a wet guy. I mean, I turn into a maraschino human when I come out of
the fuck when I'm done playing basketball. I've told you guys about when I play basketball
that I get so sweaty that I thought I was really good at pick up basketball because
nobody would want to get close to me because I'd get so sweaty.
You told us about that.
I think that I have some kind of medical, I think it might be a superpower.
Did you get your cholesterol checked?
I don't even care.
Maybe that's it.
My cholesterol?
Maybe you drink so much coffee.
There's no anything in this.
Sodium.
sodium in coffee, are you crazy? You put sodium in there, you put sodium chloride
in there. You put salt in your coffee thinking it's sugar and you're like,
"Damn, this makes me taste good." Makes me taste good? Probably would make me
taste good. Yeah, it makes you taste good because you're brining your insides.
No, you would taste the best. You're like an olive wagyu cow. I would not taste
the best. You are. The stuff that I eat, Doritos, Mountain Dew. You're a turducken.
Actually, I think I would taste the best. You would probably taste normal. No. I
that I have taste. He would taste like chicken feet. I have a
Mediterranean diet. Yeah, yeah, I was told to go on the Mediterranean diet by
a doctor. What's the Mediterranean fucking doctor?
He recommended, you know what, you know, writes a prescription for his
family's restaurant. It's making it's making a lot of sense. Yeah, the doctor's
office was on top of a doctor. Coppelopolis. Yeah, yeah, you just go
right down the stairs. Yeah, I read and then he's like, yeah, and you're going
I'm going to have to worship some new gods. Yes, a whole pantheon and I'll say
is it cool if I change their fucking names?
I'm Roman, I'm Italian, yeah,
they nobody worships the Greek gods. I would piss me off. I do that would piss
me off. If some do you guys ever think that that's going to happen,
there are there are people who call themselves Apolloists or something, but I
don't think they actually worship Apollo. No, they just Richard Spencer says that
worships Apollo or something. Really? Isn't that funny? I didn't know that.
Yeah.
It was the first. I guess, yeah. He would ever saw the other Nazi guys
getting into Norse mythology and he's like, "I have to be a little different
here." I gotta be weird. Yeah. I'm sick of these alt Nazis. Just be a normal
one. Why do you have to be like, "No, I'm gonna be..." I like great stuff.
Yeah.
I'm gonna wear a suit. Just wear the outfit. It's already cool enough. They
They all wear suits. It's so crazy. They all wear suits and the suits look very
ill-fitting.
Yeah, because they look ill in them.
Damn, you look...
I'm not saying that.
And fit. Proper fit.
They're not looking...
Hey, you know what, Richard Spencer? You are not looking proper fit. You look like a proper
bitch.
Oops.
Joker gun. Oh, the bang gun.
It's a complete accident.
that actually is a sick. If you play those at the same time again, it sounds
really cool. Do you guys think that one day they'll change the gods of
Christianity like they did with Rome? Oh, absolutely. They're gonna be calling
Jesus Barack.
That's right.
They'll call Jesus Barack. They'll call God
fucking Billy Eilish.
Fucking. They may be, now I'm thinking about it, it would, back then when
everyone had a thousand gods and they all each had names and stuff, and then
and they were like we're going to have one God and we're not even give him a
name and if we do, you're not allowed to say it.
Do you think this religion stuff is all hocus pocus? Yeah, not me. I actually
starting to believe. Yeah,
I believe more and I'm more of a believer in aliens. I'm more of a
believer in thoughts and ideas. Yeah, the marketplace of ideas. I'm starting to
believe a whole new type of religion that I just thought of,
just who gives a fuck gives a fuck ism who gives a fuck ism Eric and Jack show
I DGAF ology is what you're thinking of. No, I'm thinking of my whole
ology is a science. Well, he believes in the science who cares about any of this
stuff. We're all going to die. Oh, this is actually damn somebody else already
made up this. It's nihilism absurdist absurdist nihilism that I have and I
I guess I have. I guess I have been kind of more into memes lately. Yeah, I'm
more of a believer in stuff that is not short. I send him all these amazing,
incredible. He sent me a good this morning. Did you write that one
customly? Well, I found that one really. I found that one and I copied and
pasted it because I didn't feel like crediting the author. Let me pull it up.
I saw somebody retweet it and I was like, damn, moving the mic away, like
Charlemagne because I've been watching a lot of that a lot of you said a lot of
breakfast club ass tits bro her shit posts.
These are all memes. I've been sending Cameron all these. I don't understand
that means and philosophical questions and ideas. I posited Cameron one of the
craziest philosophical ideas, which was would you rather do Sidney Sweeney? No,
no, no, that was a detective. Okay, Cameron say yours first and then I'll
they might wait yeah. This is actually a hard question okay or no it's not for me,
but for some
would you rather have sex with yeah, Sydney, Sweeney or a shaggy sheep?
Yeah, so
there's way no, no, no, there was a lot of added thing okay, so you need to
finish the whole thing yeah. I know I just wanted to make you look like a fool.
I am a fool, the shaggy sheep, which it is, it has to be shaggy, has a sheep STD
that none of humanity has ever contracted even once, but if it, but it
will, it will be contracted by you. It's a female sheep, not a male sheep, by
the way, okay, and you will get it and it will cause an outbreak of a new
disease. That is a sheep STD to everyone in the world, but I do I have to have
is actually a bunch of people to cause the outbreak or what? No, it's it
becomes I
yeah, it's like it's like emanating from you. Okay, yeah, so that's it's a it's
a bat soup situation. Yeah, exactly, and how many it's zoonotic. How many people
die from this? Oh quarter million. I was about to say twenty million. We can go
with that's the either one. I mean any if you even said if you said a millionth
of a million, that's still if it has a million in there, I'm, but you won't die.
you won't die, but you'll be sick, but everyone knows it was you and you're on
the new me for seven all right and your and the disease makes your penis turn
completely blue and hairs grow out of it and it can't be covered by your pants
and they put you on the news and then now the other side, the other side of
it, Sidney Sweeney. Yes, it's for she's four years old and it's Christmas
man. Yeah, see that's hard. See that's the kind of questions that me and
Cameron posit to each other all the time. That we develop. We have, we have
literally hard philosophical conversations like this. This is one of
those philosophical questions where I feel like you're, you need to ask a
mathematician or something. It's, it started, it started when I asked Patrick
just would you rather fuck Sidney Sweeney or a shaggy sheep, and then I
just kept adding details. You wanted to balance the scale a little bit. Yeah,
it turned into something horrible. Yeah. So then I asked him,
I asked him a question that I think is probably the same amount of hardness.
Okay.
Would you rather have $30 taken out of your bank account every single hour for the next
18 days or become a registered sex offender for the rest of your life?
No, you did not say registered.
You said be a pedophile is what you said.
You said be a pedophile.
It's the same thing.
No, it's not.
It's not the same thing at all.
it's not the thing at all to register to be a pedophile in society. You have to
register, but you're no, but pedophile means it is the there are a bunch of
underground pedophiles running around who are unregistered. You don't have to
it's not like say, oh, fuck, I just realized I'm a pedophile. I thought they
were all in a database. No, no, they're in the database. If they show off the
grid pedophiles, Jesus, by a big ranch. So you are so, so yeah, that's the
question is, would you rather lose thirty dollars right time every hour,
one times twenty four. It's not that much money times eighteen for eighteen days
eighteen days. Yeah, that's twelve thousand nine hundred and sixty dollars.
Yeah. So would you rather pay? I mean it's a lot of twelve thousand nine
hundred and sixty dollars or I don't have the money, but I think in eighteen
days, wait, I could easily come not easily, but I could, but I but also
explain your since you said bank account, you can get overdrafted right.
That's okay. Okay, wait, oh yeah, of course, so maybe so I would do that. If
just the fucking yeah zero dollars. The money isn't going anywhere. So
Saturday, I wait who gets the money yeah. Is it a I don't know I think I
think it's just the government, but here's another question that I asked.
Do I get tax thirteen K? This is a more important. The government is doing
this.
This is a more important question here. You want me to read it?
Saturday, five twenty four PM. I texted Cameron with a question that I knew
would blow his mind. Okay, as it took him two hours to reply because he was so
was pondering it. Would you nut in your cousin if a scientist told you it'd create the cure
for cancer, but you found out later it was a mad scientist who was lying to you?
And what did I answer?
You said, "I would do my own research first to confirm whether the scientist was telling
the truth or not."
And then would you real quickly just read what your next text was?
"Sunday at 11.21 a.m. I probably woke up an hour before that." Texted Cameron, picture
your old Greg with the quote it's attached to your rod mother licker.
Okay, wait, this is actually good. Would you rather drink Bailey's from a shoe
or fuck your cousin?
See, because that question like how dirty is the is it like a shoe? It's all
great shoe. It's all the bottom of the sea or the lake. Yeah,
Am I going to get a Greg a real cryptid? No, oh
he's not like a legend. He is a legend, but it is a proper. He's a proper
legend for the video, but
is he? Can you go and see like a like a place? What is all Greg up to? He
hasn't made a video in a minute. He I think he went to have an old Greg
reunion. I think he went like Kev Jumbo. He like went. He became a monk or
something. Did Kev Jumbo become a monk? Yeah, he became very religious and went
and became. Kev Jumbo was one of those YouTubers where I like as a kid, I saw
that he was like number one most subscribed or something and I was like, I
wonder what this is all about and I clicked on it. I was like, I don't
understand this at all. Why do people care about this? That's what all of them
are, right? But at least if like, I don't know, maybe I did. I don't actually
even know what Kev Jumbo really did. A lot of these, a lot of people who do
like streaming and YouTube stuff are so uninteresting, but because they are there
all the time people are held hostage by the like the only thing that they see
every single day. So then they're like, oh, I guess I kind of like that's
worrying about this person's life big now, Shane Dawson, but that's because he
did funny voice, Shane Dawson. Yeah, you can look at a guy like Jumbo and you're
like, I understand, yeah, yeah, I understand why why people are watching
this, because he's doing he's why people are watching this, because he's doing
videos that are he's doing skits, yeah, but kept jumbo just talked about his
life and was just like yeah, but he did the amazing race, though that's what it
was with his daddy. Yeah, it was pretty funny. Yeah, his dad was real name
jumper. His last name was Jumba. No, yeah, he's a Cajun fella. Yeah, I was a
Cajun man, Kev, John, yeah, Kev, John. I remember he's a monk now, Shane Dawson.
So somebody told me that at least he could be just a guy, but I don't think
he I think he quit every online thing and started doing monk like stuff. At the
least. I remember when I was 11 years old seeing a Shane Dawson video where he's supposed to be
Corbin Blue and he looks like he jumped in a vat of pudding and he is wearing an afro wig.
Kevjamba?
No, Shane Dawson. He's in full, he's in a black face.
You would say pudding face, I guess is what you're saying.
the shade of brown that he used for this black face looked like chocolate pudding.
And I wish Juvio is here to pull up a picture because it is extremely dark.
Chocolate pudding is not what I would... I mean, I feel like that's a normal skin tone to have.
That's not that like crazy.
No, but like the...
A normal skin tone to have as a white person?
Not as a white person, probably.
The sheen that the light...
I don't know. I mean, I'm scared. What do I say?
The sheen that the light would hit in the video.
I mean, I don't know.
the studio lights that he had in the video, they're shining on his face so crazy
that it looks like if it was in black and white it would probably be the scariest thing you'd ever see in a David Lynch movie.
I'd bite his head off.
Yeah.
Hey David Lynch.
He was really made out of pudding.
Be normal bitch!
Stop making weird flicks.
Yep.
I don't want to go to the, here's me at the movie theater, this is what I want to do.
Eat my popcorn.
Drink my soda.
I'll watch a couple minutes.
Look at my Insta.
so yeah look at my phone and then every once in a while I look up and I'd like
to see a fight scene. Yeah, I do not want to look at somebody who's shorter than
average
doing this being odd. I do not want to see any more zigzags. I do not want to
more zigzags people with dirt on them. I do not want to see a fast woman. I don't
want to see somebody talking like a weird bitch and I don't like that. I and
David Lynch, for the last time, I don't like sexual tones of voice.
Please stop with that. Also, ditch the close-ups.
Stop it.
I don't like close-ups.
Stop it now. No more close-ups and no more things about like your relationship with mommy.
Who's mommy?
Why is your mommy weird to you?
Hey, guess what? You're making me feel awk. I'm feeling awk when I watch these movies
because I'm sitting next to my mommy watching them.
Yeah.
And I'm saying, "Mommy, close your eyes."
Same goes to you.
Same goes to you, Ari Aster.
Ariester. I'm feeling awk. So please don't go see you Ariester your whole new movie
about mommy being meanie. Ariester you sorry. Sorry bastard. Don't you ever make
a motherfucking movie again. Mommy is mean. Quit it. Bo is afraid. Mommy is
meanie. Mia's afraid. Yeah. Mia's afraid of mommy. Mia's afraid. Mia's afraid.
Mia's watching his first two movies. Mia's afraid of his other movies. Mia's
fucking afraid. Also, you started your entire career making a movie that is so
disgustingly about
father having sex with his older brother. They should literally have called that
movie. There is something weird and wrong about Ari. You know what I would
have called it. That kid fucked his dad. That's what I would have called the
movie because then I wouldn't have watched it. I would have said, oh,
that's a pornographic. I don't want to do it. I named it but not watch it.
Father fucker. Well, that's the kind of
a perfect job. What name movies and movie namer? Yeah, like you like or the
guy who puts the but they don't you don't watch the movie. They just kind of
give you a post. You go there's something about Mary yeah.
It's a good idea. That is a good title for a movie yeah yeah one, but then
there's something, but then they have to go. They have to go and do the the
reshoots right, so they show you this fam this funny or this sweet family movie
about Ben Stiller, but you've had you haven't added your coffee today, so
you're mad and you're saying meet the Fockers yeah go ahead, make that
fucking movie. I dare you
that's a good idea yeah yeah, they would bring to me. They would bring the
avatar sequel to me and then be like we're like we wanted to be the way of
something. We're not really sure way of blue bitch. They're going to be swimming
around a lot. Yeah,
yeah, you say well, the people are made of water, so
way of water. There you go. They show you what if you call it avatar way to
water
and like I don't know if I saw the poster for child's play, I would
immediately call it child's play. Immediately you I call most movies
child's play. I would have called it to adult for them on doll yeah yeah
Chuckies play time normal child, normal child, weird doll yeah, no, I would
yeah. Oh my God, can you imagine so I'm assuming the movie name or he names
maybe he has like a quote. He does like maybe five movies a day or whatever
imagine that they bring you child's play and you're like a child, but I guess and
then the rest of the day so easy child's play to play three child's play your
naming, but there could give you're giving you movies. They're giving you
crap. Yeah, they're giving you like child's play three
pretty good. I mean I like this movie idea or this idea from a job. Yeah,
yeah, that is a good job. The namer, the namer, they would have an award. They
have different namers and then they would have an award for them at the academy.
How do you qualify for this job though?
It's kind of like it's like how editors have like A.C.E. at the end of their title.
You have to send in a packet where you name a bunch of... they're like, "What would you name a
movie that is about a guy fighting another guy?" And you'd be like, "Guy versus guy?"
Yeah.
Free guy.
Fight fuckers.
Fight club.
That's how they came up with that one?
Yeah.
I'd call a movie "Stupid Fucks."
What movie would you call stupid fucks jackass actually here? Wait, okay, let
me get it. I'll give you some log. I actually think you'd probably be best at
okay. Let me give you some log lines for some movies and you tell me what you
name them. Okay,
a
the an American epic about a
an Italian family involved in the mafia and a power vacuum is created. A big
movie Cowboys versus aliens, a big movie and Cowboys versus aliens. So that's
going to take some rewrites. Okay,
a
star crossed lovers who are star wars. Okay, star wars movie
okay,
what
Matthew McConaughey has to go to space to save the entire world. War scary
movie. Okay, well, it's kind of a scary movie when you're on. If you smoke, we
it is pretty scary.
Oh, a mysterious convict on death row
has mystical powers, superhero movie, Harry Potter
for okay,
a man's experience and a turn of the century, the experience, okay, the turn
of the experience
turn of the century turn of the century. Okay, in the title it's in the log.
That is good
Leonardo DiCaprio has to go into your dreams to Caprio
why I didn't finish Leo.
Those are the names Leo period Leo period, I think is better. I'm going to
give it okay now. It's a competition, okay, a
for an escaped slave has to has to the slave.
He has to hook up with a German guy to go get his wife Brumhilde from Leonardo
DiCaprio again.
slavery, the movie, DiCaprio, colon, the slave DiCaprio, the slave. Well, yeah,
but I'm going to give it to you. DiCaprio, the slaver. Well, but he you
don't know that, though, because I didn't say that in the log line room
Hilda's capture room. Hilda's capture. Okay, actually, I'm just going to do
Tarantino movies. Okay, seven funny looking businessmen go back into their
27 brothers, the funny farm, the funny farm is better.
Two
funny business guys have to hunt down some business. The fuckers goofballs,
the movie
is better. He's doing better than you. He's definitely gonna get this job.
Nazi Germany, 1931 Caleb's family. No, it's not.
Who's Caleb? That's people don't know who Caleb is. That's why you watch
watch a movie to find out who Caleb is okay wait to
two broadway producers produce a movie a a movie
box office bomb for insurance purposes, but it ends up being a critical hit the
bitches the bitches
the bitches. You can't steal his name the play okay. Well here okay, here's a
curveball okay
major league, a young lion is born and gifted the kingdom, but the king, I
thought when you said a curve hill,
oh, is this the name? I thought that you said a curve ball. That's the name of
the movie. Yeah, no, it is okay. That's actually pretty. What's the name of the
lion
king
I don't know
Mufasa Mufasa story. Actually, that's not his name. Is it now? Which one's
Mufasa Mufasa is the villain. Oh, no, he's the dad. No scars, the villas,
oh yeah, scar is not a dad's name scar. Oh, what about okay, wait, but it is a
name of a very touchy uncle scars attack scars. He doesn't attack him really,
though he just kind of lets him go. The menace of scar scarred hands, letting go
is kind of more of the image that you're the way that became the king.
He is kind of a wimp. It's good. I like that one. The wind who would be king
featuring featuring Zazu and Pumbaa and Timone.
With Zazu.
Okay,
a clown fish loses it,
his son. It is just, you can name any movie it.
Yeah, that's true. Finding Bitch. What the hell? His son is named Nemo. I
really don't know anymore. This has been going on too long. The Fantabulous
journey of one Nemo the fish. This has been going on too long. I think we've
this is an exhausting job. I think I can see you're just you're you're just
doing badly and you're holding his camera. I think well, I can see the
fucker that shit. You can't see I concede. Oh, I can see it in the job
that he was in. I couldn't see the best man one.
And I'm going to go for a movie. The best man one, the best man, one man,
one, and then they could do the best man to
Oh yeah, wait Jonah Hill has to go hang out with his wife's. See we were going
we were going to a movie.
They should call it. We should have just been going. We should have made the
movies for, we should have been coming up with movie ideas from the titles,
from the title. Give me a title then. Reservoir Dogs.
Reservoir Dogs,
it's about a group of mangy little pups who are stuck in the Los Angeles River
and they have to get out of it. Yeah. And there's seven of them and they're
well named. No, they don't rocky
Balboa
Benden Franklin
chrysanthemum. That's the girl. He's just trying to prove that he can name
stuff because he failed so badly, badly, wimpy, failed badly. Now, we'll end
that in the grinch
bye bye.