Alright, we're on this real quick. Hold up. Why did you give me this small? What do you
mean? There's no small chair. It's just your is a you are not we are you or me. You and
me are the same height. No, this is not our height. I'm taller than you. Clearly. Yeah.
What do you mean? You're sitting down in a higher chair. I'm in a chair. I'm in a normal
size chair. This is not acceptable. What do you mean this is not acceptable? Also I need
to get better mic stands because I keep having to lean down a little. Yeah. I don't think
that this is like a good mic stand at all. Maybe a little taller. Do you think we can
get ones that are a little taller? We complained about how tall these were. Does he have a
different one because that's like lined up to his face. This is perfect for me. This
this is perfect.
This is amazing. It is actually perfect. It is literally a pro setup. This is
what you guys need to be doing going all the way down on the chair, which is
what the position that I'm in right now. I'm going to go down on a chair, go
lower. How would you go down on a chair on a buddy? Wait till I'm on stage.
Okay, I'll show you go down on a chair. Show us how you would go down on a
go down on a chair chair right now.
Well, usually usually you know the comics hump the chair right, but you
go down on it. Like where would you go down?
Okay, where do you go down on a chair?
You fall, you fall. Oh shit, he's doing it. Oh my God.
Oh dude, stop.
Put it in your mouth and kind of swipe the lip of it like a credit card.
They put it goo on me, dude. Oh shit, dude, you made it. You made it bus.
made the work. Look at the
the grease. That's not I
that's nasty chair bus. Can I come back up? I'm going to go down. I guess we're
going to go down yeah. All right, let me see this
not that much of a difference. You guys are still higher up. Yeah, I'll meet you
in the middle.
Okay, this is a good radio.
It's very good. Really good radio. Yeah back for another one back for the
we're back. My girlfriend sent me a photo this morning and the caption just that
that never is the in beginning. We have stories explain this and I was like, oh
dear, what happened? Did I leave like a bunch of shit out in the kitchen?
Fucking sex that's so funny that kitchen completely gross and and every TV show
a movie someone gets a text from the girlfriend and says explain this and
they're like oh fuck. Oh, no and for pets like oh, no, I left a bunch of shit
Yeah, I probably left a bunch of shit out. I probably did something like that.
Literally, identical fear as your mom texting you, "What's this?"
She said, "Explain this." And I was like, "Okay."
I opened the phone, look at it. It's a photo of me completely asleep.
And somehow my cock has gone through the dickhole in my underwear.
While asleep.
While I'm asleep.
That happens.
I'm in my bed and I'm just rock hard in the morning.
Rock hard.
It's me in the bed and it's a really funny photo.
you had a rock show me all right.
It's really funny. I have to see this. We won't show the world. No, we can't
show the world. We can't show the world. This is not for the world. This is for
this is really three friends.
It looks like in my sleep.
You're jacking off. That's what it looks like.
It looks like you're good.
you did a thing where you were wet, you were jacking your shit and she walked in
and you're like I pretend to be dead. I was going to say you don't look like
you're asleep. You look like
you look like you're dead in the gutter. I always look dead whenever I'm asleep,
so for me to have like a yeah, it's like it's like when
like there's like a corner in a movie, it's like yeah, like one of the like if
a if a person dies when they're dead and they have a boner, they're going to
have the bone for the rest of their life. If a person dies when they're dead and
they have a boner, they're going to have the boner for the rest of their life.
You know what they say that in the movies. Well, how do they call him a
corner? Yeah
yeah yeah, wait a second. What is right? I think it's because that made Joe and
Alex leave yeah. They were asking that they did not like that at all. It's
okay, because core means body right yeah
now. Well, body means by a young little, little, little, little, and
in a
core. You're fucking blowing my mind right now. Yeah, sorry, learn a little
thing called etymology. Edamame. Oh yeah,
buddy, you have a lot to learn. I can teach you a thing or two about it. Well,
edamame make me grow breasts because of estrogenic. Does it have as I can even
think about that? Yeah, because of it's okay, but tell me that tell me at least
that the estrogen is on the shell and not on the bean inside, because I like
eating the bean inside and I'd I would honestly if I couldn't eat the shell on
that's that I wouldn't complain that much. Okay, all right, I admit it. It's
only the shell.
It's only the shell. I wouldn't be too mad if I couldn't eat the show. What's
the best shell? The best shell is the most tempting stuffed shell for show.
I'll say this, Tanny's shells, a sunflower seed shell. You can still eat
them. Sometimes I eat that. I eat that, too. It's just like you not every time,
but sometimes a little beaver. It tastes like wood, pistachio shell, pistachio
not a good one. Not good. It's too hard, but you can boil to suck on the shell.
Yeah, you can suck on it. Those are the show. Yeah, you suck on anything. Yeah,
but a pistachio shell is pistachio. I just suck on pennies. When I was a kid,
we all did. We talked about it. Ten thousand hundred. I'm pretty sure we've
all we all had Pica at some point. You are obsessed with Pica. My little I
thought my little brother had. That's like my mom always mentions Pica. You
thought you had your little brother at Pica because he was chewing on a
teething toy? No, he would eat my toys. I had these Star Wars micro machines and they came
with little action figures that you could put into the head. It was like a head of Chewbacca
or the head of Darth Vader. Wait, are you talking about the ones that flip the heads?
Yes. I missed those. And he would take them and pick them up and just eat them like they
they were M&M's. That's a funny thing to do. I lost all of them. Wow. That's funnier than
tearing the head off of your sister's Barbie or something is to eat it. You're never getting
this back. If you want this back, it will be poop. You have to look through my poop
to get it back. It's plastic, so it will be burned by my stomach. My poop stinks. My poop
is stinky because I eat ribs all day. I'm a baby that eats ribs. I eat ribs and toys.
those are the two things of a toy. Yeah, that's always like a Smokey Robinson song
ribs of a toy. Yeah, well, I mean there's tears of a clown and then so probably
of a sequel song ribs of a toy
sperms of a mime sperms.
That's probably the last bodily fluid. I want to see especially from a mime
specifically. I don't mind the thing. I wouldn't mind seeing a sperm from a
firefighter or someone who contributes to society, a police officer, but a mime,
a mime, you know that also is probably the first time I've ever done it. It's
probably black and also would act they would act like they don't know how to
jack off. You won't stay in there going like they would. They do it hands free.
They jack off far away from their body and then they squirt anyway, and if I'm
coming, if I'm if you're sitting looking the other way and I'm shooting a load
into the back of your head, you're going to hear
with a mime completely silent. Yeah, you're going to have no idea. Look,
you're going to look back in the mime. He's going to go
Yeah, you don't even get to join in laughing about because it's your head
and you know, by the way, the normal guy. I don't mind if you come on me. I'm
not made of sugar. All right, it's not a big deal, but a mime. I do not want
that. And you know that the mime is uncut because they like turtle neck
French French and turtle necks. Also, yeah, I guess. Yep, that makes sense.
Yeah, man, fucking mind is
these days, fucking sick, all this fucking mind is everywhere. Whose cup
is this
waffle house? Oh yeah, there's twenty two yeah,
made in China. Guys are starting to have to think about politics again. No,
we're starting. What about politics? We're getting back into politics, right?
We recently or just everybody, the world, the world or the United States.
Yeah, it's a whole we're in a move again. Earth United is despicable machine.
you know the gears are turning. You guys voting for the Santas yeah,
because I love Twitter.
He is awesome.
He is I feel like he's the first guy where maybe not the first guy,
you know, probably the 100th guy where I see people on Twitter talk about
him and say it's so funny how he's acting like this. I'm like I don't
care. Yeah, I don't know who this guy is and I don't think he's funny.
I think it's a guy who's walking around. I agree. He's he's great as
strikes me everyone. Mrs trump's so much he strikes me as a general manager of
like a restaurant. He's nothing he's not funny. No, he doesn't have the only
funny thing about him is his eyes. He would that's how you know somebody's
really evil as if they're not even funny. Yeah, so if he gets in that'll be
bad news trump again. We've already done that it was cool. Yeah, it was fine, but
him and vaccine yeah exactly stimulus check that was huge. That was beast and
they blamed it on biden uh-huh adderall plentiful yeah. We had always so oh my
there was so much. I was falling out of my ears. But as soon as we get
where you're not supposed to put in your ears,
this is the like, there's nothing really that funny about him. Like people keep
trying to post that picture of his face where he's like, yeah, and that's his
like,
laughing or whatever. Einstein. Oh, yeah. Oh my fucking God. Yeah. I thought
that I was like, it's happened. It's been so confusing because every single
time that I see a photo of who I thought was Ron DeSantis. I was like they only
had fucking black and white cameras. Yeah, well he's kind of you thought maybe
it was a style. That would actually if I was running for president I would only
let people take black and white photos of yeah yeah that would be a cool like
gimmick. And I'd dress up like Hitler. No I wouldn't. You would. What if a Democrat
what if Bernie Sanders dressed up like Hitler all the time? He wouldn't because of his
faith. He doesn't have any faith. He does. No I don't have any faith in him anymore.
He's an atheist. He's a fucking atheist. Why do you think he lost?
That's why he's got a bad back.
Yeah, exactly. He's been cursed by God.
Yeah, he's been carrying the weight of sin.
Yeah, his entire life. Hundreds and hundreds of sins.
Yeah, but there's that video of DeSantis at the Red Arrow Diner in Manchester.
Remember we went there?
I remember.
And he is completely robotic, but there's nothing really that funny about it.
That video of him at Red Arrow where the guy's like, "Hey, how's it going? I'm Mike."
and goes okay, not that funny see, but if you went okay, okay, a little john or
if you or if he went like okay, here's what we're doing now. We're going to
we're going to brainstorm ways to make we're the
campaign team. We're going to get it. We're going to get his memes up. We're
going to get his me or my way to make him funny like this is easy. Yeah,
this is fucking easy. First off, he should funny. Well, he needs yeah. He
needs something about his appearance is what I was going to say. So I was going
so either he has to get a crazy haircut or shave his eyebrows. Mohawk Mohawk bleach
the okay Rhonda sanders bleach the eyebrows get an undercut. Yeah, mesh
shirt, mesh shirt and underneath the shirt, another shirt that says real men
wear pink. Yep, and then we're going to get you in Daisy Dukes. Tell me rocker
tell me rocker. Tell me rocker. This is yeah. Oh my fuck the bullshit. Tell me
rocker. Fuck the bullshit way too many letters just around his stomach. It's on
three lines. So it goes all the way up to his neck. Basically, it's
what's on the fans tummy rocker. What's the fucking the car name or whatever
the yeah the kerning it's really close. So if you have to like re you know
you know what it is, it's one of those things where it's like the tall
letters and you have to look at the page. Oh my God, so you can only
you can only read it. If you're sucking his cock, it says fuck the
bullshit, but everybody else got running for office. Nobody can tell what it
says they're like. What is that and and he's an early say? What is that tattoo
saying? He says well, if you want to know better suck my day, yeah, you want
to know come to the bathroom and people are like well, you can't say that he's
like no. I literally stating a fact I got it so you can only get only really
if you're sucking my dick yeah wow okay. I've never even thought of that yeah
and I thought of fucking everything. If he does all of that actually, I just
realized you can also maybe read it. If you're doing going forehead to forehead
with him yeah well, no,
the fuck yeah that's true yeah yeah
yeah, so if the Santas does all of that, maybe he has a shot, maybe yeah, but
that's only a that's a that's literally just as a parents and I don't even
touch on his one. He's just he's just eye candy. He's not even
and he just looks like a hot slut. Yeah, he's everyone's going around sucking his
Dick and nobody even knows he's running for president right yeah, yeah,
fucked, but okay, politics it will be that would actually be ingenious right,
because people if you wanted to get his Dick sucked because it would be like
someone suck his dick and be like you know that tattoo. It actually says fuck
the bullshit people like this fuck the no, it doesn't there's no way that's
what it says he's running for president. I got I got a second, I can find out
for myself
and you know you need two hands for Ron. Oh yeah doing this yeah
crab claws yeah dude crab claws. That's new. You like go right
doing this
to the world's most medium missed violins yeah.
I think
he needs also he needs to he needs to
changed his politics become a liberal. No, not a little no, not something new
yeah, some new thing liberal when he gets when people hand a great fucking
reason. He just needs to be trying new shit. I would just encourage him like
whatever your first instinct is do it. If somebody hands you a baby to kiss,
throw it at the fucking just yeah, throw it as hard as come up with things that
maybe that people haven't just your whole platform should be things that
people haven't said yet. You should feel like you should be like your campaign
we expect the unexpected. Yeah, that should be the thing. His campaign right
now, his campaign right now is we're going to make America Florida, I think
is his slogan. Yeah, go all in, make it Florida, start doing meth, start doing
crazy shit. He should be doing mix and match stuff and he should be doing like,
he should be like, we're going to cancel the student debt, but we're going to
take all the, we're going to take all that money and we're going to give all
that money, we're going to take all that debt and we're going to transfer that
set to Ukraine and they yes, he should be walking around with a heroin needle
just stuck in his arm. He should have a right there. He should have an
alligator. He should have an alligator. He should become basically Joe. He
should outlaw animals. He should become a morton joe exotic. Yes, that is a
good one. Yeah, more can you say that again? A morton joe exotic
excellent edition, extremely
yeah, that's good.
I do like that
now the sound board now it's like complete. There used to be that little
spot there. Yeah, and just so you guys know, I will be cycling stuff out. Yeah,
I would think pretty soon. This is leaving. We never use this. I don't like
you know, we never use it and I have to, but I'm not just going to be doing it
willy nilly. I have to wait until I think of something that's at the level
of zombie nation. We need to keep, oh, maybe a whistle. Yeah, maybe like
the other thing is I'm not going to tell you guys. Yeah, maybe that whistle song
from White Chicks, though the one where Terry Crews is dancing, blow the
whistle
yeah, too short song, maybe I don't know. I haven't seen what it's going to
surprise you guys. I got to rewatch White Chicks. I was before fine to not
watch it. I didn't think it was that so funny when I saw it on TV. When did you
see it? Like probably in the last two years for the first time. Yeah. Yeah, I
guess that makes sense. I guess it is one of those movies. I was like this is
so we can on the other hand, this is raunchy. On the other hand, little man,
what are you saying? Little man holds up. I know little man does not hold up.
Little man holds up in a major way. Little man was a flop. Nah, little man
I flop. You're a little man and you flopped. I don't flop anymore. You flopped your wiener
out when you woke up. I did. Yeah. My wiener was flopped when I woke up this morning. Yeah.
You got flopped. Did that get picked up on the cameras, Jubio? Yeah. It did? Yeah. Yeah.
It fully got perfectly picked up. All right. My girlfriend's full name and... Yeah, that's
what you're worried about. My girlfriend's full name is on camera and a picture of my cock.
Is it tattooed on your cock? Why would it be on camera? My girlfriend's full name is on my cock.
really and she and I don't know that in she does a lot of property stuff about
me.
Look, would you date a bitch named Leonardo da Vinci? Yeah, yeah, sight
unseen yeah
no, she's dope girl Vinci. No, she's no, no, no, she's a girl named girl. I
probably would you come in and be like hey guys, I'm I have this. I'm doing
this new girl named girl named girl. Her name's girl. You would what was the
time that we were saying that it was like it Jeff is Jeff or Steve or a girl
named Steve. I'm dating girl.
I'd believe that
it's really funny that it's not that funny. It's funny. The idea you would
date a girl. It's not funny that it's not funny even to me and that you would,
but just the idea of you coming in and saying that and that being your life.
Yeah, I just like I'm going on a date with Steve later girl named Steve, who
like just normal hair boy named sue wow wow that was an abused kid it was
abused yeah right that's what that's about yeah he got abused he got abused
well actually I don't remember much about that song yeah it's a song boy
named sue yeah I don't know Johnny Cash what do you think it was I didn't know
I thought it was just a thing is it a book yeah it's like a book about a kid
who got so abused that they were able to write a book about it I think boy named
name. So maybe it's about the or maybe it's based off the Johnny Cash song. They named
it after that.
But Boy Name Sue is just about a guy. It's about a little boy who's like, my fucking
dad named me Sue. How fucked up is that? That's the whole song. That is abuse. It is. And that
is abuse to name your son Sue or your daughter Sue. That's a terrible name. Sue Bob. Have
you seen the Wild World of the Whites? That documentary about that family? They're like
a family where their dad was like a really good like Appalachian tap dancer or some shit.
And because he got a bunch of money from doing fucking tap dancing shows, they also, they
talk about it in the movie, how he taught their whole family how to fuck over the disability
checks and stuff.
So they live off of disability checks and just smoke pills all day.
They smoke Percocets and shit.
They smoke pills?
smoke percocets off of a
fucking tin foil. Oh wow, and then there's a there's a lady named Sue Bob
in it.
I'd like to Sue Bob. Her name is Sue Bob Bob's furniture. You ain't no
motherfucking cartoon. He's not a cartoon. He's a little about your thing
of little Bob to
fuck. They're different guys. Have you seen that, though? I'd like to speak to
the cartoon. No, we haven't seen it. You should check it out. Sounds interest
Jesco White. Who's Jesco? The older brother. And then Sue Bob, they're like, "They call
me the hot one." She talks like that. It's a human cigarette. You're a human cigarette.
I am not a human cigarette. You're a human fucking... I used to be. You're a human millipede.
Millipede? Yep. Because I got a million legs? A million fucking titties. Damn. Okay. All
All right, damn bitch ass. I'm not a bitch ass. I cooked you today. You didn't I
brought just broke your ankles. I showed you my penis and you're making fun. You
show me your hand covering your penis. It was hardly your penis unless that was
your been trying to make me show it to him for years. Yeah, that's why I was so
excited when you said you're going to show it to me. That was a little
disappointed by the photo. Yeah, because I was hoping that you disappointed. Yeah,
because you didn't show your whole fucking. I thought I was going to get
like great. I thought it was going to be like a yeah. I know. I know why my
girlfriend took the picture. There wasn't enough of she was disappointed.
It's not enough shaft because it was hiding between my briefs
obviously between yet two pairs of briefs on yes, in case I piss
obviously what's wrong with you. I'm sorry. Yeah, that's me being insensitive
about. I know how you guys are fighting and I think even though I don't really
want to talk about it. I think I need to bring up the elephant in the room on
what happened a couple of days ago. What happened a couple of days ago? Oh, we
I've already talked about this. I've already blocked it out of my mind, but
I'd like to talk to him. Okay, so you all right, right now we don't have to
talk about. So if you listen, no, no, I'd like to talk to him about it. So
if you listen to beers, we drink on Saturday or on Friday, this is a day
you will have heard you will have heard this already, but basically we did an
extreme betrayal and yeah, I'm going to say that it was one third me one third
Cameron one third Julio, because the only fair way to do it and it wasn't
even just to me. It was also to Rex, maybe like one half Caleb and one
or no, maybe one half Cameron because he's the one who said it first. No,
you say, do you know, no, no, no, no, no, hundred,
try and talk,
so it was Caleb who suggested it. He said, do you guys want to go to Fogo
to Chow? I said sure, and then he did a U turn like the mean
turn me up. I'd like to say this in my defense. I wasn't going to go,
that I put in Fogo to Chow just for S and G's and I was fucking three
hundred and eighty one feet away.
Well, how can I say no less than five hundred feet away from Fogo? You could
say hey,
hey, let me go for me, call you a car, let me call you a car, call yourself a
car. It was also also good to here's the other here's the other piece of
it. You be closing in. It was it was that he was coming to dispute
something. It was closing in
that you're coming in to defend yourself. It was closing in one hour,
so you guys physically was not got it was one hour. They close for lunch from
lunch to get ready for dinner. You would know if you remember watching those
videos about Fogo de Chal, I don't watch many of them. You've seen the I F with
Ryan video where he goes to Fogo de Chal. You know that you know that goes
for lunch. We talked about I F with Ryan. No, I don't. He's a special secret. Is
he a special? Yeah, well, we've just said his name. I guess we're going to
have to if you if you guys there's a guy that we've been obsessed with for
play a year now if you guys are, but just as a fitness guru and we really want to work
with him. So if you guys are into fitness, check out IF with Ryan.
If you want to learn how to intermittent fast.
Have you guys ever done a fast?
I do a fast most days by accident.
Have you ever done a multi-day fast?
My dad used to.
I guess the longest I've done is probably a little over 24 hours for like a doctor or
something.
24 hours you get you feel amazing. Yeah, and then I think you if you keep going
you feel really bad. My dad was doing juice cleanses and fasts and P90X and
Diamond Dallas Page yoga. I was doing orange juice cleansing like he's bathing
in it. Yeah. My dad looked good though. I saw an old picture of my dad when I was
like 16. And now he looks like a fucking piece of shit. No, he looks like the same.
No, he looks like I... Your dad honestly looks like a cartoon mountain. Yeah. Yeah, he
he looks like he looks like he should be on a run. It's like the Rock Titan from
Hercules. He does that's cool. That's what a dad should look like. Your dad
looks like a golem, not a golem. What are you talking about? My dad doesn't look
like a golem. Sorry, that's not okay to say about my dad. I have a good
relationship with my father. You can't just make fun of him like that. You do
have a good relationship with it's going to end today. I think it's a jealous
thing from the both of you. I don't give a fuck about your dad. You guys care
about my dad. You guys hung out with my dad. Yeah, I mean I care about him. We
young out. We got drinks with him that one night and then he drank like eight
beers. I've gotten drinks with millions of people in my life and I don't give a
shit about them. You don't care about how many beers my dad drinks really fast?
No, I actually do think, I think that drinking, you don't care about my dad's
burger with the onions in it. Drinking alcohol is so special, it almost makes me
want to cry thinking about it. Yeah. Did you watch that movie with Mads
Mickelson where he dances at the end? No, you should watch it. Is it about
drinking? It's about how drinking brings us together, but it also can kill us.
yeah, I don't care if I die from fucking good and that the end Mads Mikkelsen
amazing thing. I used to have a really bad problem with it. We've been getting
back. We've been getting back into having and do you know what the best?
Do you know what the best part of that movie is? What is that? Whatever
country it's from, whatever I think, sweeping Danish or something that
foreign title of breakfast is is I think I wish the American title. I assume
it's a translation. The American title is another round, but then the foreign
whatever it is title is drug. Yeah, okay, that's sick. You know, it's cool
I'm drunk about I'm drunk. I think it's a
poster is him drinking like champagne, so out of the bar.
It's
there's the Swedish title for every single Mel Brooks movie is spring time
for blank really. That's funny. It's like spring time for frankenstein. The
way the way they localize tiles is so fun. They do that with all the old
Godzilla movies when they were like that nobody like cared about them. There's
making them in Japan and they were like localizing them for Germany and stuff
like in Germany. Every Godzilla movie is called King Kong.
It's all stuff like that now in the poster that is put like a picture of
just like rain. I just mean the big monster, yeah, King Kong, yeah, King
Kong and Conan. Yeah, that's yeah, it's awesome. Yeah, all the put it's so
great. There's a there's a bunch of stuff like that. What do you think the
localization of this podcast is going to be podcast about who is King Kong?
King Kong, yeah, yeah, I wonder what we're going to start a podcast called
King Kong, it would be cool to get a name. I think you get in serious trouble.
The you're not making money.
We should get like a list. I don't want to do nothing. I'm not making every
single localization of the podcast name. Well, we're ready to hire some
translators. We should get like and also we want you to localize it in the
way that they localize Pokemon, where they're going to call that coffee.
You're going to say that he's drinking like sake or something. Yep, because
coffee is like when they said the only giri was donuts. Exactly. Is that what
they said yeah. They said jelly, this jelly donut and it's and clearly I'm
so hungry. I'm gonna eat this hot dog and it's a piece of sushi. That's so
awesome when they do the dub and then they like yeah. They what would these
fat Americans because there's no way the line was I'm going to eat this hot dog.
Yeah, he's probably saying something else, but they had to make it so clear
that it was awesome because the kid is watching that and if they're holding a
thing that looks like Onigiri and they don't know what it is that I have, I
needed it yeah. It will break their brain for they'll be like what Pokemon
with them exactly yeah. Why are they eating a Pokemon? Do you think they eat
the Pokemon in the show? No man, we've been talked about. We talked we've been
talking about this. We love talking about eating Pokemon is yeah. Which one
would you not eat? That's that's the opposite of the question we've done
before. Mr. Mime,
I wouldn't know that I would eat the fuck out of him. Are you kidding me? I
want to eat. I want to beat it up
jinx
drinks. I beat it up, which Pokemon is the most I'm beating that we did that to
fuck. We did a whole episode about that. We're looping around. You're a looper
right now. I'm looping. I'm loopy. Do you guys remember that movie looper where
yeah,
that movie so bad? Why we got amazing reviews when I came out movie was shit.
What's because everyone was impressed that they made that they look like
Bruce.
That was all they did. They
yeah. Why is that cool? Like shit? Yeah, I look terrible movies. The Anna was in
it, though right great. It's a great movie. Yeah, it's a great movie. I don't
know what to say. That's exactly what I think every time I see Paul Dan. I love
that yeah, you know, I can't be that bad. I saw when I was a kid, though,
Miss on I saw him in New York City walking down the street when I was a kid.
I visited New York City when I was thirteen. I saw you say to him my I just
looked at him and my entire and I told my family. Nobody believed me. Yeah,
they were like why would he be walking around on the street and I was like it's
That is such a fucking...
In New York City, they were like, "You're a liar."
That's so...
You fucked me up for years.
Why would a celebrity be walking around New York?
I know, dude.
Yeah.
Nowadays, I would love to run into him.
You ever walk with your girl down the street in New York City and she's like...
And they walk, somebody walks by and she's like, "That was Cody."
Yeah.
And you go, "What?"
And they're like, "That's Cody.
He's a musician."
Yeah.
And I'm like, "I don't know who the fuck that guy was."
I can't even doubt.
Uh-huh.
But I do, then I chase after him.
after my holding down take a picture of them. I did see my first celebrity on
the street. Who'd you see? It's not even that cool of a of a
seeing because it's probably just his every day. I saw Jim Jarmusch. Who's that?
I don't think I would recognize him if I saw him. Who's Jim Jarmusch? He's got a very
recognizable face. He's a director. Yeah he directed. He's got a camera in front of it.
uh-huh
that's so funny. It is the funniest thing we've done in so long. We did it years.
Me and Patrick. I think no, I think as a as a collective podcast right yeah, we
all did it together. So we actually put podcast collective podcast. We are if
when you're a podcast, not so much to New York in 2016. I saw I got dinner or
lunch. I don't remember you got dinner with it's the same with my dad at a
restaurant and at the table next to us, two guys were eating and guess who they
were. They were Laurel and Hardy, Ben Stiller and Martin Freeman. Wow, really?
That's actually crazy. That's fire right next to us. And I was like, New York,
probably you go here. You see celebrities every day and I've never seen
another celebrity here in my entire life. We should get men still have been
Ben Stiller did Hollywood handbook. He should do really yeah. Okay, you
don't get him big time in Hollywood, Florida. If you remember that show, he
did the Ben Stiller show, read our productions, read I production that I
we need to get Greg on this show. Greg, we know, and got Phil. No, we need to
go Greg. We do not need to
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
we're going to be the ones to bring him down. Yeah, you think so honey pot
well, we're going to say you were texting seventeen. You were texting at
to shoot yeah try working. Did you hear about that? No was telling me
get off your phone.
No is telling me that he's like
he's like a weird guy. He tries to pick up Nicholas Brown. He tries to know
literally everybody knows this. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
I literally will be like oh shit and fill my dog will see because he loves Noah
and he'll see girls on the street and try to walk up to them because he thinks
they're no. Yeah, yeah, messed up, messed up. Noah, cut your damn hair. No
man should have any hair. I'll say that look like men shouldn't have hair. It's
a feminine. I want to get Noah's haircut while he's sleeping. You want to get it
because I live next to him in a wall by a wall that separates us. I could go into
to his room. You could go through. I just had the most incredible vision of
Patrick in like ten years from now, teaching like an English one on one
course, like a two hundred person public university English class and how amazing
your lectures would be. Yeah, yeah, yeah, you'd be teaching them funny words. I'd
be teaching them how to talk in a style that is. What books would you put on the
I know, I know, I know what your first your first slide would be.
Screenshot of a drill tweet.
yeah, study this a lot of people would say this isn't this is the study. This
class is about the study of brevity. This is a text. You would say that this is
text. Yeah, this is text. This is and this is photos
and now this is yeah teaching an English class and is showing photos. This is a
photo photos. Now learn how to look at these. You think that texts that look at
this line of text thinking that they don't line of text six words. Look at
photo that accompanies it. One thousand and six. Wow. You would be such an amazing teacher.
I wish I had there was more professors like you in this world. I'd be such a good teacher
for people with adult ADHD. No normal people. Normal people. Good people. Completely normal
people. I could teach the syllabus one line. I wish I could. I wish. Fuck the bullshit.
I wish I could go back in time and make you older than me. I want to look up to you so
bad. Yeah. I want to look up to you in every way and I want you to teach me everything
thing that you've ever learned this. I showed him my penis and now he's being
very kind to me and I want to look up at it. I see you different is being very,
very yeah. I think you don't realize, but you completely changed your
relationship with us forever. I looked at the cock through the cracks in your
fingers and now I can't poetry. Oh, my God, the English teacher, I
right at the cock through the cracks in your fingers.
That is a rupee power poem, the most incredible line of poetry I've ever
someone say say it one more time. I've peered at your cock through the cracks
in your fingers.
I could listen to that forever. Keep going and what I've seen cannot be
undone.
That's not as good as no, but how can you beat that first line? That is truly
the best first line I've ever heard. That's an amazing line. That's
incredible. I'm kind of writerly in that way. Do you guys think I'll ever
write a book? No, no, no. You said yeah first, but I don't think I have. I
I don't think you're I think that is the hardest right. I could definitely write
a chapter. I think you could write a chapter. I don't think you're right. I
think I think a book is probably the hardest thing to do in the world is
write a book, but people do them all the time. I don't think that's true. I
think I think I think if you're actually trying, I think it's really hard, but I
think people I think it's really easy to write to just write all the way through
you write a chapter a day and you don't care and then you put it on Amazon and
rack up that money. Yeah, right up that five cents from an old lady who
I accidentally bought it because I was like trying and she's trying to jack
off. What would I write? What you guys are in works about when I was ten years
old, I tried to start writing a book. You would not believe how many books I
wrote as a kid. Yeah, you got sure you can guess and then thirteen knowing me.
Yeah, I halfway through just started listing all of the skateboard companies
that I knew about
your book would be a hero. You would make a coffee table book about
skateboarding. I guess with pictures, the worst that is. Yeah, that is such a
cheat code to make a coffee table book. Yeah, all you have to do is just hire
someone to license all the pictures for you. It's easy to like yeah, I wrote
that's a great idea for a cocktail book is just pictures. I like yeah, you just
license the photos from that's the future. Is that a fuck with just cool
ass pictures? Yeah, that's a great we should put out a coffee. That was what
David, we're just selling these ideas. David Beckham's kid did we're going to
have another NDA today and we're actually going to have a QR code on the
screen this time like we asked and like I generally a QR code for and did a lot
he had a QR code and you didn't put it in the show because he's he was to you
know. He told me you know what he told me. He told me he had the QR code file
downloaded. He had it on his computer. He had the thing up and then he was like I
just don't want to do a lot of editing. Fuck me. You put a picture. It's a
picture. He's on. He thinks that we don't know how to use premier. He's on
vacation. He's barely on big. It would take point five seconds and he's not on
vacation because he didn't get approved. Well, I thought of after effects never
And he's going to be putting in a cool slimy logo right here.
You wish he never just shook his head. No bastard.
Did you guys already talk about the police to what police basically burned all
the material stuff? Yeah, yeah. But we got, it's okay. That was, but that was,
what happened? I was there. I was the one who was there. Yeah.
But he was there twice.
So this is a thing that you talked about on beers. We drink already.
Yeah. So we can't even, I need to stop getting the scoops on beers. We drank.
Yeah. Yeah. It's not really the way. Yeah. I really should.
This matters a lot more. You know what I guess we can talk about. I guess there's
nothing. Yeah, why don't you bring up the next topic that you because we don't
know what you talked about. So just bring up something new. My favorite
vegetables. Okay, let me guess.
Coriander. Brussels sprouts. I know he loves Brussels sprouts, but I feel like
you would also like them. I definitely like them, but not your favorite. My
favorite vegetable is also cruciferous though. Cruciferous? Broccoli. Yes.
That's my favorite too. That's my favorite. Yeah. They're all
sons of mustard.
Bloody, what are you talking about?
The mustard plant. It's the father, the mother.
The broccoli is the son of a mustard plant?
Of Brussels sprouts.
Really?
The son of a mustard plant.
They're all sons of mustard.
But mustard just makes these little seeds.
Yeah.
With the angle in it, you can turn those seeds into different kinds of seeds through selective
breeding through millions of years.
Millions?
Brussels sprouts, broccoli, I think arugula. I don't remember.
you guys should as I call it, you guys, but there's a bunch of stuff that
mustard is responsible for speaking of millions of years, you guys should be
razzles, you guys should be watching prehistoric planet season two. Yeah, it's
coming out right now. It's so I don't understand how somebody could be so
irresponsible as to focus on pre history when we're living through some truly
know what the best part of the new post, open your eyes and watch the historic
planet, the new prehistoric planet season, which what's the guy's name
at and burrow? It's his first David David at and burrow. I have him narrating it
of course, and every episode starts it opens it's a it's black. It fades up to
him standing in a study and just the first word he said he just he just goes
nine. This
I
my phone
like you saw what now there's a pterodactyl coming into the room to
attack. So that's what every other starts and it makes me laugh every time,
and I have a video of it on my phone. Listen to this
I just believe
you're exaggerated. No, it's exactly what he fucking says. Holy shit! Oh my God,
so good
this is wow he's so he's lost it yeah he's so fucked up dude. He's past. He
does the thing he does the old guy thing where he moves his head too much to
compensate for the probably doesn't know what he's saying and he goes like the
t rex is a
noble animal and he's like wobbling all around. He rexes are not noble to their.
he doesn't say that it is made that up right now.
- The dexterity is mean.
- They have funny dinosaurs on this season.
They have one with a one horn that looks like a,
he's fat too and he's got--
- It's all made up.
- No, well actually one of them,
it was blind in one eye.
- It's all made up.
- So you're actually right.
It wasn't, it was red.
- They're all made up.
- Red, marooning.
The show is completely made up
'cause they don't know shit about these things.
- These are human bones.
These are human bones that they have been moving around.
- He was researching the one eyed one horn.
- Yeah.
- Not, don't even say it.
the fly. Okay, thank God. That's why we got an indoor office. They can show the
dinosaurs fuck a bunch and they show their things and their poop. There's
babies that eat their mom's poop and that's like, you can't know that they
did that. Yeah. There's, what do you, went into their stomach and you found...
We call them Dorans. You found...
Yeah. You went in these, you went into baby... I'm okay with it if it plays
the sound effect. You went into baby dinosaur's stomachs and you found their
mom's poop and I don't think so. There was not enough dinosaurs. There's no
way. I think they just made that up for the TV show to be gross and nasty.
they're doing these shows about dinosaurs, then yes, they should be
they should be also doing the show about big foots one on one horn flying purple
people. Yes, Loch Ness, I'm one hundred percent in agreement. Brownies,
Pajama Sam, Pajama Sam,
Freddy Fish, yeah, I Fox those games. I replayed all those about four years ago.
Yeah, I was in college. They hold up. It was fun as fuck. I is good. I played it
I was like we talked about the put put speed run. Have you seen that we are
yeah? Yeah,
well, they just click. It's just it's just a game of osu with no no circles.
You just click everywhere really fast and then the guy messes up and he was
fuck.
Those are fun, man. Those were my earliest gaming memories. Probably I
never played those. I they only they had those at the at the at the library, the
town library. I never had time to play a full one. I would just play whatever the screen
was up on when I got to the library for a little while. But I cared more about Adventure Quest.
We had a game on my computer. It was a Star Wars game where you put a Millennium Falcon
peripheral on to your keyboard and then you put your action figures in the thing and then
supposed to press the button through this like stupid peripheral, but we couldn't get it running
like an amiibo. No, it was like literally like it is the chair pushes down onto a key.
So you like the control key or something? Yeah, yeah, like it's like WASD. You could have just
sat there done this. You could have played it with the thing, but like, you know, it's like here is a
Millennium Falcon peripheral that you have to strap to your keyboard. Man, old like playing,
I think finding computer games actually ran on the family computer was such a
strong. They're always dude. I
can't play for two weeks. Surely Tempo
Nancy Drew. Oh yeah. I remember ordering games off ebay. That was like a used
disc that was like five dollars. I'd get it and be like oh, this is power PC.
You can't run it. I remember
man game I got on cd. I bought it somewhere on like a like a yard sale or
and it broke my heart. I crashed my computer. The biggest come up in my life was finding
a Half-Life game of the year that included Opposing Force. If I had had Half-Life, because
Half-Life was old enough that it would have ran on anybody's computer probably, right?
So I wish I'd had that. My parents wouldn't have let me play it. Oh, but my computer didn't
have a graphics card. This was before integrated graphics, too. Yeah. I found that at the Goodwill
and Derry, New Hampshire. Then I came home and then installed it on every single
computer in the house. Dude, two of the computers. Every single computer. My
computer. I think if I had been into... Do you ever hear people talk about stuff that
they were into at an age where you didn't even know what that was? And you're
like, "I would probably be a different person if I had that exposure to that
media." I think Half-Life is one of those things where that's... I don't think I
did I experience anything that could be considered a good piece of art or media
until I was probably fifteen years old? Oh, absolutely. Like I just had nothing
going on. It was all just YouTube videos and the worst music ever. Mine is
definitely anime. If I had actually figured out how to watch anime as a kid,
it would have been completely over for me. Thank God I was too ADHD to fucking
pay attention to the subtitles, because I got, I got, I watched the first season
of Gurren Lagann. Dude, that's exactly what I was about to say. I remember in
middle school hearing about Gurin Lagan like going to watch it and like big dog.
I don't even know if that's right. That's just how I always have. So just
keep going in Gloggin Gloggin. I think it's I don't even know to be honest. I
just said that yeah, but you could be completely right good and like that, but
I remember watching it and being like this girl's boobs are too big. I can't
watch this and she's thirty. Yeah, I think she's old. She's thirteen in that
show. I think the thing is she's an adult old adult and the kid is young and
it's like she has big boobies. Oh yeah, that she's yeah, that's like a
first, you know, she could be like eleven. I don't know the first scene in
the show is him like
see like they they do like a like a like a glint like a like a star shows up on
her boob. Yeah, they did. Turtles are insane. She had those are the most
insane. Have you never seen these? I never even heard of you would have gone
cray. I went for it. I went cray for sexy jitsu in Naruto. Yeah, I think
Naruto is the big thing where if my parents had let me watch that, I would be a completely
different person.
I got into Naruto in the third grade for the summer. I bought all the action figures on
my birthday and then stopped watching it completely because I was like, "This is the worst part."
As soon as they switched to being teenagers, it was too scary for me.
Shippuden?
Yeah. No, I didn't watch any of that.
I didn't even know there got to be teenagers.
I think Shippuden, they started airing it later on in the day or something because you
he wanted more blood and so I couldn't watch all that, but I had the headband.
I would walk around with a headband and my really I wanted the head. It was my
brother's friend, Sam Hacker, who played the slap. He slapped the bass guitar and
he left at our house one time and so I had the headband. Yeah, I saw I wanted a
Yu-Gi-Oh! dual disc. I had, though I had no you, your cards. I had things are
fucking expensive. Do you still have that you can see I did not I destroyed
that thing. Why do you those are because I was got in a jackass when I was nine
and I was don't make those anymore. I feel myself breaking it. You can sell
those for hundreds of dollars. Now I think I fucked up so many toys as a kid
that isn't that I'm not so funny and that you could everybody bet on the
wrong thing. You beg for a dual disc as a kid and your mom's like fucking fine.
Okay, whatever I need a little kid and then you grow up and you're like fuck
you mom. Somebody I know it's worth something. There's somebody that we all
know just recent. I talked to him yesterday. No, no, no, no, don't try to
guess what it is because I don't know if they want to have this publicly.
with their name. They got a bunch of calls from their home state and they were like about
like some taxing. They're like, "What the fuck is this?" And they looked at their like
first bank account they opened when they were like 15, and there was $6,000 in it. They
have no idea what it's from.
That's crazy.
Isn't that amazing? That would be the best. And it made me so jealous. Yeah, because I'm
a guy, every man sits around all day thinking about what they're going to do when they eventually
win the lottery.
That's enough for me. That's about what we're, that's pretty much. Yeah, $6,000.
That's what I imagine. I think that I forgot to close. They would cancel all of my medical and credit card debts.
I'm pretty sure that I have a, I still have my childhood bank account that I stopped using
because it was only in Massachusetts. Yeah. I think I forgot to close it, but I think
instead of $6,000 in there, I'm pretty sure it was like negative $150. Yeah, it's way overdrafted.
I think something, I don't want to ever think about it. That's right. You get a call from the bank,
you're like, holy fuck, this is my thing. They're like, yeah, you have $1 million in overdraft fees.
please it's possible shut down. I think I just turned off all the emails from
them and just never close the account. I don't know how much I left in there
when I was in when we were in college and I was like really broke. I would
always like optimistically open a savings account, but then it would get
overdrafted fifteen different times because I never put any money in it and
I had the fee. If you have less than three hundred bucks and then I would
just close it and I probably did that like six different times and I kept
letting me open. Yeah, I probably am really over. I should check that one. I
don't know. It doesn't matter. It's not going to do anything. It's kind of
got a dollars in my savings every month and then it takes it out really, but I
have six cents in there.
I have six cents in my savings. We need to get serious about our money guys. I'm
serious about money. You guys aren't you. I'm the move here with one million
dollars. Yeah, that's because you like cereal. Yeah, I can't do cereal. I need
champagne for breakfast every year. Cereal is fucking expensive. Now don't
even talk to me. I'm serious. Eggs are getting expensive. Everything's getting
so expensive eggs are when we when I lived in Boston eggs or one dollar fifty
nine cents. Now I get a six thing eggs. The cheapest one at the store is four
fifty when I lived with my parents, it was more expensive than that really
yeah eggs were free when I lived with my mom and dad and I don't buy that was
food and so is the roof over my head. We should just move back in with our
parents. I so much money man. I would love to move. We should move in with
each other's parents. We should do a rotation. I could hang out great idea.
Yeah, you're your dad and I would he would look through my record collection.
he'd say that's what I honestly think that I could show with either of your
parents. My dad's you guys could not chill at my parents houses. No, my
parents are, my parents are easy mode. Yeah, his is medium and then yours is
legendary. Yeah, I have the legendary difficulty home life.
No, it's fine to visit. They're good people. If you stay with my mom, it
would be a little easier, but also you have a 13 year old running around
hitting you with nerf bullets all day. That's why it's hard mode. That's why
legendary is that there's a child kicked out for saying shut the fuck up. Yeah.
And then my dad is just like,
my dad is just like kind of wandering around kind of asking you when you're
going to leave suddenly. Hey, so I'm leaving. What do you got going on today?
Oh, I think I'm just going to sit and watch TV. Okay. Cool. I'll be back later.
No plans. Okay, cool. You guys asking to borrow my dad's car all the time.
I can't fucking do it. I'm about to do it.
Yeah, I'd be asking your dad for rides everywhere. I'm about to just so you
guys know it's coming up this summer. I'm leaving the city revenge tour. I'm
leaving. Where are you going? I'm going home. What? Definitely okay, that's okay.
We'll make it. We're going home until I learn to drive. Wow wow that's actually
and you're making a documentary about it. Also sure I can do that. Yes, please
that's fine. I will have nothing because
I won't be able to drive when I go there and my mom does not live close to
anything. So I will have nothing to do all day.
I'm going to make a DMV appointment. I'm going to go and I'm just going to do
it until I'm doing the train spotting
thing where he tries to lock himself up to get himself off the heroin. I don't
give a fuck about that movie. I never seen it. Never will. Me neither. I don't
like, I don't like darkness. That is one of those things that you were talking
about earlier, like a thing that you see when you're younger and it fundamentally
like changes you that for me that was a matrix. I saw that when I was seven and
I or seventh grade and I thought this is the coolest thing in the world. You were
seven in seventh grade. I would believe that. Yeah, I was in seventh grade. I
they started doing some. They did they did testing on you and they're like this
kid needs to start in seventh grade. Yeah, and they're like actually we need
to hold you back. He's actually chill. He's actually a chill kid. You can hang
out with the twelve year olds. I saw that when I was twelve and I was like damn, I
want to listen to house music so bad. I want to listen to that. Is that what they do in there?
I still think house music is scary. Doesn't somebody shit on a baby?
So a baby dies of heroin. But whenever I hear someone listen, I... He deserved it.
I listen to electronic music. I feel superior to them. You don't like that song
"Born Slippy"?
Don't know it. That song is so good. Sing it.
Sing the drums.
I'm more into UK Garage and Dubstep myself.
But whatever burial
Was it called Kanye West?
Flashing lights drumstep remix remember that no oh that actually that's actually after my time in terms of music
I had that I had a Verizon blitz. It was like this little blue phone that slid up and I bet you had virgin mobile
For a long time really yeah, that's not even funny then yeah the virgin mobile oyster
virgin oyster
No, that's not funny.
But I had this little blue phone that slid up and it had like the keyboard and I found
out that you could put mp3s on it.
Not mp3s, it was its own proprietary file format.
So I converted all of my music to that and then I would listen to it on the bus and it
would be like.
Yeah.
I didn't know how to use mine.
I was like, yeah.
I didn't know how to download a ringtone.
Yeah.
And I wanted a ringtone.
I wanted numb, Linkin Park numb on my phone.
so I played Lincoln Park Num out of my clock radio and I recorded it with my
flip phone and I said it to my ring tone and it was like yeah. I was like
that's what I
speakers could not before set of speakers could handle. My brother did
line wire, but I did, but you guys remember playlist dot com now. Oh wait,
yeah, playlist dot com was you would put on your my space and the thing yeah
that you could just download songs from that, but I didn't do between those two.
I didn't know what to do, so I would
my dad's house. I would play a song on YouTube and record a video of the
speaker with his camera, and then I would download I would I would export it
into an MP three and windows movie maker. Wow yeah, it's probably sound amazing.
It sounded so so good yeah, yeah, so so I want to find an iPod sound. I
remember that numb sound recording, because I remember as soon as the guitar,
you know, it plays the synth thing and the synth rip and then the guitar hits
like as soon as the guitar hits the set like at the end of the ring tone,
there was just one like half second of just like
because it could. I remember that I had songs on my on my iPod that it would it
would be like DJ Khaled. All I do is win and you'd hear it. I was when and then
you hear my dad on the phone in the background,
and it was just to me. It was part of the song yeah yeah, but I was in I think
sixth grade I had this app on my computer called A-Tube Catcher and it could download anything
off of YouTube in any file format. It also had all these other things, you could convert
videos with it or whatever, do all that shit. But I would also use that to blame if I ever
accidentally downloaded something that my mom didn't want on the computer.
Oh no, like Pwn?
Yep.
Pwn?
It's Pwn!
it on the computer downstairs and I remember I didn't have my headphones
plugged in one time and I thought that it was really loud. I thought that they
could hear it upstairs but I realized I went ran upstairs and I was like what
the hell was that? I just tried to download an mp3 and then I think you
told that story like less than two weeks ago. Wow that's crazy. You are a looper. I
think that was your looping. Yeah I think that was the shortest time between
between stories told maybe ever on the show. That's insane. Well, we were
talking about files. Yeah, that's true. Yeah, I'm talking about files. I can't blame you.
Yeah, yeah. Man, files. I miss that shit. Miss files. What was the first time you
guys set your own desktop wallpaper? What was it? Ooh, ooh. Got my own like profile
on the computer. I figured out how to do that and then I made my wallpaper Rage
Against the Machine Evil Empire. I'm trying to remember. That big yellow Evil Empire.
I remember a few different. I don't know what the first one was. I definitely had
a binding of Isaac one at one point. I think I probably I think I had a doctor
who won sway at one point. I think I had the you know the one where the awesome
face isn't the me. Yes, I definitely had that one. I had that one. I want to say
I probably had some type of rage comic one at some point. I had one when I
first I want it. I was like teaching myself how to use a pirate at Photoshop
and I was like fourteen. I had a slender man and I made myself a bokeh like a
a bunch of like bubbles.
Oh my God.
And that was my background for like years.
Because I made it myself and I was like, "Man, this is amazing."
I just followed a YouTube tutorial.
Yeah, I did. When I got my first laptop,
I had a Windows XP refurbished laptop
that had 512 megabytes of RAM.
That's massive.
Really old computer.
Did it have the...
I could only play Fallout 2 on it.
Did it have the bubble?
All in the middle of the keyboard.
The clitoris.
in the middle. I bet you couldn't find it.
I'm trying to find my key. All right.
Where's my keyboard? I'm trying to find my computer.
But I tried, I learned how to like get custom themes
for the like the, what's it called?
Like the key, like the toolbar and all that stuff.
Oh yeah, Star Wars one. There's a million Star Wars ones.
Yeah. Yeah. I did all that shit.
And then I got like such a bad virus on that thing that it did.
I just couldn't use a computer anymore.
I bricked so many computers.
I bricked my mom's work computer because I was jacking off to Weeds.
Weeds?
The HBO show.
I was watching like a pirated version of Weeds, whacking my shit into all the sex scenes.
You bricked it somehow?
I just got a bad virus from one of the websites.
I tried to download After Effects onto that computer and I bricked it.
After Effects was the most common virus.
Dude, it was like Command Prompt and it was in Russian and I was like, "Oh, dude."
You're fucking done, man. You're done, man.
Yeah. Thank God I was like 12 and I didn't have a bank account, but that could have been
very bad.
Yeah. I never got a virus.
Yeah. You had a MacBook your whole life.
Not my whole life. I had a MacBook in high school.
I remember when my mom switched to Mac.
Yeah.
It was so weird.
Yeah. No, I was honestly, I was too scared because I did have, it was the family computer,
my family laptop and I was too nervous. I never really did anything crazy on
there. Yeah, my mom, because I knew how to like change the layout of the
computer, because I knew how to change like the tool bars and shit. My mom was
like he is a fucking computer. Yeah, I got all in the family computer days. I
got all my porn through Google images. Yeah, so say sir, pussy, pussy, hole,
pussy, hole, pussy, front part, girls, badge, girls, front, that jeaner. Yeah,
stuff like that vagina with coming it
was mostly that for me. It was that for me. Yeah, yeah, Google image search
vagina with lots of
the double vagina come falling out of a vagina. Come on your mark. Come come come
just come come come
searching. I told you guys about come white dick right. Is that your friend?
Yeah, my buddy let me borrow his iPad to play Temple Run in the lunchroom.
And we were arguing about something.
So I opened up Google on it.
And the first thing that showed up was come white dick.
Oh, and I was he winning white cum or white dick?
White dick with cum on it. Oh, shit.
And somebody come on or it's the dick's come.
The dick had to come. It's shot.
And I was like, why the hell are you looking up? Come white dick.
What the fuck are you doing?
Yeah. He's like, oh, I've been talking to this girl.
so I was sending her back a photo of my dick with how many times I was like
what do you what do you mean what do you mean he was like well she thinks that
I'm a white guy and I was like
wow he lied about being white lied about being white. He said by the way,
I'm white. I think it came. She said, Are you white by the way? Yeah, show me
prove it with your penis. This kid passed away a couple of years ago. That's
awful. How many kids sent just in middle school were just sending opposite
screenshots of the Pam and Tommy sex tape to each other being like yeah,
that's me, that's my dick, that's my boobs like that's like nothing. Nobody
was actually sending real nudity because every kid was that was too scary man.
Yeah, yeah, I remember taking a picture of my penis one time and just and about
to send it to my girlfriend in high school and just being like no, no, no,
This is last week?
Yeah.
No, that's, no.
You barely get anything for that.
Okay, I do like the song though.
I do like the song.
I just like the video.
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na.
Wait, Celtics are coming back.
Oh yeah.
Celtics are coming back.
And this song is going to be pumping in TD Garden.
Let's go Celtics reverse sweep on the Miami Heat.
That's me killing Jimmy Butler.
Yep.
up.
You know, as I get older, I've had this really sad realization of sports that I
have no. I think that I'd be really bad in war because I've no allegiance at all.
Yeah, I know I switch sides so often. I know if the Celtics are what means you'd
be really good in war, but you'd be dangerous pretty low. I'd be a spy. I
hate the Celtics when they're winning. I love them when they're losing, but then
as soon as they win, I'm going to be like oh, the Celtics won fuck. There'd
you'd be a good super soldier. You'd be a good. Thank you. So that's honestly
probably the kindest thing you've ever said to me. I would be a good
running experiments on yeah yeah. I should be a pig. They should be injecting
you with like a new steroid that makes like your penis. Do you ever see that
shit about like if you oh, we need to stop testing on animals perfumes. I
don't you can test perfumes on me. I don't care. That's not a big say that,
but you don't know the smell of their testing. What are they do on you onion
plus do onion plus do and that wouldn't rather by fart Jacobs fart. Jacob
doesn't have the capital. Are you doing here testing?
That's what that's what they're testing perfume for. It's not like to see if the
chemicals are like dangerous to put on your skin or something. They just
about they spray like a monkey with something. They smell like now that
smells like shit. Yeah, get rid of that. What would you fuck? It's like actual
poop. Yeah,
you want to
just based on smells now. Now it smells half like poop, but how do they so the
did that in my head. They test perfumes is yes. They sprayed on a monkey and
they put a monkey. They put it in a room with a blind person. They're like
would you fuck this person based on smells alone? They handcuff two monkeys
by their necks to each other. I'm a very cruel. They hold the chain in the
middle and then they have a big bucket that they got at a hardware store and
they dump them. It's filled with
and these are my flowers yeah. No, these are capuchins. They're pretty small.
they take the cutest monkey and they say let's go. It makes
yeah. I have a robot arm that looks it looks exactly like a human hand. It's
got skin on it and they have it as a full human body attached to it and it
just goes like when like when her son, but it is it as red eyes mice. They
take all of the they go around to every farm. They take all the cutest animals,
they take it back and they make the perfume and then they say let's see if
they if it makes the eyes smell better and they just say they write in their
sometimes. They use Homer Simpson's makeup shotgun. Yeah. That's how they
test all the Estee Lauder. Yeah. Estee Lauder. Yeah. They test all that way.
I only know what that is because of crosswords. Wow. There is a lot of
Estee. A lot of Estee. A lot of fashion. I assume means some kind of, it's a
good filler word. It's a clue, it's some kind of house of, some perfume
house or something. Yeah. It's a good filler word. It's S-T-E-E, you know,
you can fill up a lot of it, put it in the cross. Estee. Put it across, in
middle of the word. Do you think you could make a crossword? I made a lot of
crossword. That was really I
I used to make crosswords, but that should be a new segment. Do you think you
could make it hard up to snuff with the Sunday ones? That seems so hard. I could
I could make I've made several ones that I would say are probably Monday or
Tuesday. Maybe the twenty five. That's pretty easy. Twenty five dollar tier. You
get conference crossword. One month. I could do a one month crossword. That's a
great idea. Yeah. Yeah. It's all words that are like do. Well, that's the thing.
I do there's a bunch of fudge. I do think that there's a okay
what I'm going to say here,
but I'm going to say here is half a joke. Okay, you I think there's a space
in the crossword industry for some alt crosswords. I agree because I think
because here's literally literally to normie crossword. No, it's not nor
jupiter. The problem here's the problem it's either you get a really good
crossword, but it's all it's on New York Times, cultural, cultural ish, stay
there. I'm talking about authors like steward. I don't give a fuck about that
or the and then you look up across or it's like I want a movie themed
crossword, which may be something a guy might look up once in a while
no harm in that and you get it and it's all every every crossword like that is
kindergarten level. Yeah, they don't fill in the square. They have a word like
this and a word like this in New York and has so many things that are like
They're stupid. They're bad.
It's like cultural references that you or me, no normal person would ever get. It's
literally only for rich people.
And the thing is that just because they're in the New York Times doesn't make them good.
There are some crosswords I do in the New York Times and I'm like, if I was the editor
for this crossword, I would say no. I would yell at this person for this clue. This is
a bad clue. Even if it's not a cultural reference, this is just not a good clue.
Yeah. Going in there with your newspaper and just smacking the shit out of it.
I would go in there with a red pen. I'd stick it up their noses.
And then say, "You cross that out."
Yeah.
with that red pen. I would be so good as the crossword editor for the New York
Times. I think that you should. I have really strong feelings about crosswords.
I think maybe I've never thought I've had I've been having I've been having
kind of my dream job has been shifting. Okay. And I think this is my new dream
job. I think I just or the crossword. I was thinking first I was thinking
librarian then I was thinking mailman. I don't like Sudoku. I don't either. I
don't get it. It's not that good. No it's bad. It sucks. It's all math. Sudoku
for people who aren't smart enough to do crosswords. Yep. True. They can only
think in numbers. They can only think of nine things that is thing. I think
technically there's Sudoku that are way harder than cross. Oh for sure. Yeah.
Depending on how little you numbers are. It's completely true. That is
addicted to Sudoku, but the people who do Sudoku aren't doing those ones for
the most part. They're doing tried to step in, huh? With my dad. Yeah, I've
tried to. I've tried to stage the interventions for you. I do letter in
there every once in a while. I've made my I've made my girlfriend annoyed
before, because every time a crossword someone's doing a crossword in a tv show
or in a movie, I say that to be well. No, I say they're going to slow. Yeah,
that's on this person. This character is supposed to be smart and they're going
that slow. This is taking me out of the show. I've said that. I said that if
it's what if it's a very, very, very Mike Mike from and better call Saul. Yeah,
he's doing a crossword easy as crossword tiny. Yeah, but he's not a he's not
but smart pen to paper is a little smart. The paper is a little different.
he's from Philadelphia. He's not smart. Yeah, pen to paper. He's a smart guy.
He would be doing better than that. I'm talking in a sub Monday level crossword.
He was doing really. I'm talking like ten by ten, so tiny ass cross. Monday is
Sunday for Monday. Yeah, that's Sunday again. That's a hard ass one. No,
Sunday's easy.
What Sunday is like a Thursday level difficulty. It's just big
Thursday is the difficult day. No, Saturday is the difficult day. Saturday
is going on. They have to cross two extra lines on each. I don't know exactly.
It's bigger. It's much bigger, but it's easy. It takes a little longer. I got to
cross for you
that way that doesn't nobody can hear that. Nobody hears your fingers and also
I don't even like it. I just just by his cadence. I thought I should press the
button. I thought it was a slam. It wasn't much of a slam. Well, it was the
same because the audio was there. Um, do we have any info to give? Do we want to
pick the next? Well, we'll pick that another time. We'll do you want to come
I'm saying hi.
I'm eating.
Okay.
That's your deal corner.
Oh, there's coming a shout out.
Oh, deal corner. Wait, yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay, let me see what Serb has to say.
Do you actually have one?
It's from Serb. This is a deal sent to me from Serb.
Okay.
Serb said that there is, if you pre-purchase and pre-order Lord of the Rings, you will get...
Wait, show him the new sound. He didn't hear it.
Oh, yeah, you want to hear it?
Yeah.
It's a... the deal corner sucks dick.
like
like a CSGO sound. No, no, you're thinking of easy.
But it's and and and put that put that battle. Yeah, that's a good song. That's
the deal. I guess what's the deal? If you pre order and pre purchased Lord of
the Rings, you get Gollum. Great for you. I didn't pick it out. I was doing a
fan.
Bye bye.
Bye.
Easy money.
Easy.