I
think
that's
a
good
maybe
pat
once I
became the
clapper,
maybe his
first
good
clap.
What are you
talking about?
Maybe his
for you actually did get the
award of the day because you
found a cable that we needed.
So isn't that using creative
thinking really?
I mean honestly using like
everybody smarter than wanted to
throw out a bunch of you got it
in just and pardon the pun here.
You got it in just under the
And you got it in just under the wire because I was opening the bin that that was in when
you said it.
So I was opening it and you said it right as I saw the thing and my brain hadn't even
caught up yet and then I was like oh my god.
It was genius.
That was an amazing amazing moment.
I can just coast today and don't have to contribute at all.
It felt like you were narrating my life.
You have a Steve Jobs outfit on.
I do.
Yeah, I'm wearing that.
All black with pink socks.
It's summer buddy, look at me.
Show those shorts.
Show those socks.
Show those socks, bro.
The air forces are so fucking crazy.
These are so funny for you to own.
You're jealous.
I do like them, but it's so funny that these are the
New York City Air Force Ones.
Look at the bottoms.
got the five and the four train logos and then what's on that side. It's like the
six and the what
I don't know.
The six and nothing. The six and then the I think he knows everything about
what it really showed. Show me the bottom again. It doesn't say it just says
six and nothing. Okay, so it's just the four, five and six train. Yeah, we all
know them trains. Don't worry. I've never been on one of them. The single
time. Those are the six goes all the way to the Bronx. Those are I drive trains
to go to the IMAX. Yeah, I really do. I can't remember the six. You take a I just
follow the Google. The six takes you the Bronx Zoo going up and then going down.
It takes you to this one curb that I like. That's all black with pink socks.
You got the my Crocs. This is a funny ass. This is some bullshit dress for the
what this is honestly getting dressed for the Brockhampton show.
This is not getting dressed for the Brockhampton show type outfit. What are
All black with the pink socks and the camo crotch.
I didn't want to put on my shoes when I left the house today.
Yeah, right.
Did I tell you about the time I saw Brockhampton?
All of them?
Or do you think that's one guy?
No, I...
You saw a blue guy?
I spent my student loan refund from community college, the whole $300 that I got, I spent
on Boston Calling tickets and coincidentally that Boston Calling show was the week after
the Amir Van allegations dropped. So he was kicked out of the band and then...
So you saw that they did their weird stuff?
I saw them because I was like what is this show gonna be like?
Yeah, that was the reason you bought the ticket.
No, I went there, you know, it's more embarrassing because I went there to see Mac DeMarco.
Yeah, that's a little. I would say maybe that's a little less embarrassing than
going to see Brockhampton. Yeah, yeah, Mac DeMarco and Danny Brown were on that
year and then so like
their whole show, they cut their set halfway through because they all stood
up on stage and we're crying and hugging each other
because that we should do. We should pretend that we had a fourth guy that we
kicked out because he was a raper. Yeah, and we should do an episode. That could
we stand up, we all stand up. It feels like I like when I that I see on
Instagram people I knew in Boston who still live in Boston from like from high
school and stuff as they all go to Boston calling still every year and it's
crazy to me. It feels like an alternate universe that people are going to Boston
calling. It used to be cool. The crate that there used to be five. I don't
believe that I was in it was at government center. It was in the middle
know the city. Oh, that's oh really yeah. It was really cool. I moved into the
Harvard athletic Harvard athletic complex. You weren't allowed to smoke
cigarettes. Yeah, and it's all grass and mud and they have so bad bands now. But
back in the day, they were booking run the jewels.
I went the year that run the jewels played.
I went that year. That's fire. Yeah, that was the same.
White high schoolers dream that festival. White high schoolers dream got to see Hannibal
Burris perform gibberish rap live. No. No, dude. Holy shit. That was huge. You know he's
a full time rapper now. I think the funniest though, I think it was either someone I know
tried to book him on a show and he was like, I'll only do it if I can rap. Really? Yeah.
That's so funny. The funniest, I think it was either the year that Boston Calling switched
to the big field or the year after that that year was twenty seventeen
because that was the year I went. Okay, well, whatever year it was, it
was the one where
like I think the headliners were like Weezer and Major Lazer, I think,
but then the other, but then the other headliner was tool. That was the
one I like to. So the crowd was like half like, like sixteen year olds
going to their first concert ever and then half like forty five year old
guys who smelled so bad. I think it was the craziest crowd I've ever
I think the headliners were run the jewels and then no, it was chance the
rapper tool and then that's what it is. One of them one year was Weezer and
major laser dude that fucking I just remembered that. Okay. So is the chance
the rapper girl? Yeah, the chance the rapper show that all happened like the
week after the the Ariana Grande Manchester bombing. You remember that? I
forgot about that. So that happened like the week after I barely remember and I
I don't even remember what it is just besides it happening. Somebody
rapper said chance to rapper said in in like I don't know what, but he said
like do y'all want to see heaven tonight and then we heard like
and I was like oh my fucking God, he killed everyone in the
he's a young
tonight. I thought that chance the rapper was a terrorist. I thought that
I heard like to like what sounded like gunshots and I was like oh my God,
perfectly and then I was like oh no it's fine. I was just really drunk and I
thought that no no you thought chance the rapper was doing a ritual sacrifice.
He was no he was he was trying to get as many people to see heaven as possible.
No no no no other pieces unplugged. I'll plug that in okay. What are you guys
looking at you guys while I was talking about that you guys were all looking at
them and don't worry about something and I still don't know what it is they're
unloading it into a shop. I took my Adderall today. I've been extremely
I've been so focused on these stories I've been telling that I haven't let you guys get a word in edgewise.
What do you mean? We were talking about all the bus to Cologne. I've been talking up a damn storm all day. Shut up.
What'd you do this week? What'd I do this week? Did you do anything so fucking funny?
No, not really. Something so funny? Oh, me and Pat came up with something funny this week.
About surround sound. But we did something funny. We came up with something funny when we were walking.
owner. Why wait let me let me intro it basically it's a bit that we came up
with you fucking right. I think I'm sorry you know how excited I am. I think
you're actually going to I think you're actually going to like it, though. I
think it's actually funny all right, and it's the bit is Theo Vaughn, but he
grew up in a completely normal town. Yeah, okay, so I used to have this guy
coming into town. If your house is on fire, you give him one dollar. He put
that thing out. There used to be a place down in my town called the police
station all the cops hung out. I'll be cops there all the time man. We would go
down to the bus criminals. We would go down to this place man. It was me and a
couple of my friends. We'd go down to this place called the library and they
had every single book there. He was a borrow. He was a busy town. How about
that? Yeah, he's had his worm down there driving an apple and we had this worm.
He would drive an apple and all the caps all the cops were cats. See that's good
did okay. You guys did have a funny week. We were saying that to Jubio and he did not
get it. He listens to Theo Vaughn and he says yeah he lives in Mexico. Look at Caleb literally
trying to drift. I'll see you guys later. And then still got somehow out of the shot.
It's okay. Nobody cares. Nobody actually wants to see me. What? Don't say that. We did that
Hey, nobody even want we did that for the whole walk back to your apartment.
Good. It was funny. It was really making me laugh. It's been too hot.
I think it's cooking my brain. Yeah, cooking me toe all the way. I'm finally
dying y'all damn. It's really happening. It's confirmed. It's completely
confirmed. What way are you dying now?
I lost my vision again. You went blind. Yeah. How did you lose your
reiki beats me? It happened yesterday and I'm still scared of what you hear
they say it's happening again. That's what's happened. When were you and I was
sitting at the table, what do you get like a chronic migraine and then it just
well. So the usually I get a migraine. So also if any doctors are listening, I'd
really like you to tell me what this is. Do you wear glasses? No, maybe you have
macular immaculate, immaculate, immaculate, pregnant, but I do actually
want to know what this is. If you guys know you should tell me if I should go
to the doctor or not, but I usually get a mic. You know you get the don't ask a
the doctor they're going to say yes yeah. Do we have any anyone just a bunch of
everybody who listens to this message me and say yes or no, but no doctor, no
doctor, because you have a vested interest and you're trying to get you
have a doc. If what happened was you know usually you get a have you ever got a
migraine before you know how it's like a gradual kind of like visual halo that
like comes in, but this was like instant and it was like half, but the entire
upper half of my vision, just like it just was like it was just there and I
did you hit your head? Nothing app. I was literally sitting nothing, no, no
stimulus at all, something unplugged, something got unplugged in my brain. I
lost the upper half of my vision on one side. I stood up. I was walking around
saying I can't see I can't see what's happening. My girlfriend was very scared,
yeah, but I didn't feel I didn't my head didn't hurt. I didn't feel anything in
my body, my vision, and then it just faded away. I just some five minutes.
You only drink Gatorade. I don't this is the this is the first time I drink
Gatorade and probably over a month. Oh, then you probably not true. It's a
hundred percent sure I've been using the Gatorade water. It's completely true.
Do you know I went and you asked me to get you a Gatorade the other day and I
also was that Gatorade. When was that guys last week? That was not last. It
was. Let's be real. That was a hundred percent. It was not. I keep track of it.
Okay, I said you haven't had Gatorade this month is what you said. No, I'm in
at least a month in a thirty days. Okay, maybe I'll go to I'll go twenty days
then. Okay, I might give you, but it's been a while. It's been a minute. Okay,
I continue, though sorry I have nothing else to say. Do you think I mean it
probably nothing is probably just like a man, so it was the most scared I've
been. It's probably just a stroke yeah, that's what I was thinking. I thought I
was actively having a stroke. When it happened, it might have been a mini
stroke. Yeah, people have those all the time. There is a mean if you have a
mini stroke. It doesn't really mean I mean nothing really means anything.
It's not like
it's like I think it's like just your blood gets cut off to some part of your
brain for some very small amount of time. Oh, that makes sense. Got cut off to his
eyes. Maybe you have- I think it was my ocular nerve or whatever just got fucked
up in my brain. I honestly think just some little gremlin, some little mucinex
guy unplugged a part of your eye. Well, you know what else is? I think, as I did
have a headache in that morning. I didn't have one later in the day, but I feel
like maybe it was an aftershock. I think every headache I have is a- Did you hit
your head? I still didn't hit my head. You didn't hit your head? No. Did you hit
hit your head. I did hit my head. I did hit my head. You did hit your head. I
fell down. I hit my head on a door knob the other day, getting up from the
toilet.
I hit it so hard I had to lay down. You were sitting on the toilet and then you
got on hands and knees on the bath mat and then you stood up. No, I realize I
have a really bad habit of I get up really, really fast. I always go maximum
speed. That's when I hit my head on that. Yeah, so I keep hitting my head on
stuff because I get under something and I just try. I get so excited to get up
that I jump up and so I leaned over picking something off wall all while I
was taking a shit or something off wall. What are you saying?
You're picking up holy
you don't remember
what could you possibly
you know what you know what my you know the set up of my bathroom. I have the
toilet there, the doors in front of it, and if you open the door, which I shit
the door open when there's no one home for sure because I have the dog out.
I don't want the dog to get into mischief while I'm doing it.
So I'm shitting with the door.
Does he put his paw under the door?
No, the doors open like so if I bend over and then I get up, I might hit my
head on the doorknob and I bent over to like pick up my phone or something
while after I'd wiped my ass and I was lifting back up.
It's making a little more and I hit my head so hard.
I still have a red dot.
I see it.
I think it's like over here.
Oh, no, it's a little above that. Yeah, it's right there. I see it and that was
like ten days ago. Damn wow yeah, and I hit it really, really hard now and then
today
I was making meatballs in my air fryer and I spilled them onto the ground.
I opened up the air fryer and it, and the air fryer was tipping over the
counter. Something has been going on with us. You know what else? I had a
dream that a bee crawled in my ear. I had a dream that I just pissed blood and
that was it. I had a dream that I found. I had a dream that I pissed just straight
blood and I was like, Oh, my God, I was like, Oh, yeah, like like I in the dream,
I told myself like, Oh, yeah, this this is like a big problem, but let's just
wait it out. Oh, yeah, I mean, that's so fucking weird. That's what my sleep
apnea has been really bad recently, too. Yeah, and last night I had a dream that
I found an AR fifteen and I brought it to the police
because I was like, I don't want to get in trouble for having this. You guys can
kind of it and this morning I farted and the one sitting on the couch. Oh,
that's not that
girlfriend farting in her sleep last night and it smelled so bad that I left
the room for a little bit. I'm done. Oh, you can't say that. I think that men
need to take a stand, okay, because all three of us have lived in, we have
lived in, you're going to be in trouble. You're in trouble. She doesn't listen.
You're in huge trouble. She doesn't listen. All the girls listen to everyone
to see if we talk about them. They do. They do and they get together and they
listen while they do whatever. That's what they do.
that's what they do. I don't know. I'm thinking they do that. They do that
they do that because they hang out and I don't know she comes back and she's
laughing at me. She's laughing at you.
She comes back and she they show each other's pictures of our little sees me
as soon as she sees me. She does this and just so they can laugh and I go.
What are you laughing at and here nothing we need to take a stand here.
We are kicking every one of us. The girls from now on are sleeping on the
couches. Yeah, because I do not get a good night's sleep when I sleep with my
wife. I do not want to see her past eight o'clock. I want her to be gone.
You are a lunchtime only person in my life, lunch and breakfast. She's on my
bed. She is going diagonal while I'm trying to sleep. These women, they sleep
like I have a full bed. I have a full side. Can I tell you something else
going on in my life that this just reminded me? What there is a new baby
where in my building,
but it's only there some of the time, either that or it's really a polite
baby. That's good to be if you're a baby and you're polite yeah. My baby who
only screams and cries a little bit, but I was thinking that and also the
people have been fighting who has who were the baby in the baby. They could
be very could very I have no idea fighting like you're hearing like
I don't
but I'm thinking once they kill each other and the baby is gone, I've done
I care I can take the apartment that they're in and expand. It seems like
there's a lot of tension right now expansion expand and I was thinking this
is something I was I was thinking about okay. So if you get the apartment above
you, okay, tell me you're put in your inside your apartment, not in the lobby
or whatever. Are you going to put in a normal staircase, a ladder, a spiral
staircase or a jumping pad? What about the pole fire pole fire pole doesn't
goes down well unless you're very yeah, but I'm not that strong. I would say
tighter on your legs and climb up. Are you can choose that? Are you going to
want to do the jumping pad every day? That's my question. Yes, I mean it could
be fun. I was a jump. You mean trampoline? No, I mean like a jump or
like it shoots you up. No, we are. I already had this discussion with who
with me. Yeah, with you, I'm just saying it's not a trampoline. It's a jumping
red, like in a game like yeah, yeah, like a spring, a spring, that's what I'm
saying it's a spring. It's not a trampoline. No, I'm I'm just asking if it
was not
trampoline. That's ridiculous. Okay, well, then I think I choose ladder. I
think a jumping pad would really hurt my back. Yeah, I guess you're right. I
think I would go spiral staircase just because it saves space and you don't
decline. Ladders, the cheapest is the space cheapest and the best efficient of
space. Then old people can't go up. Yeah, exactly. No old people. No, I'm
I have my antelope spiral staircase looks cool. Yeah, if I think it amazing
a stick is a look good in your apartment yeah. My part would probably look good
with a jump pad. My apartment jump pad would fit in great in my apartment. No,
no, it would not yeah. Well, it actually no, I think if I'm from the eighteen
hundred that doesn't even make sense. Some some Nikola Tesla
well made out of it's made out of like sheep's intestines. That'd be cool.
one day you guys came in and I had that Nikola Tesla thing with electricity
just shooting it into my Xbox and shit. Yeah, but I one day I get all this
electricity. Why don't how come how come people who get completely obsessed with
interior design, all these girls who want to make all their spaces look a
certain way, look like a magazine, how come they always every time they say I
want to look like this is a one room school house in the old west, how come
none of them are like I want to make my house look like a science lab or like a
dinosaur jungle or have it look like I understand they wanted to look like a
little pretty inside of a car. My shit would look like a Sunday school, like
like it already does no, my no, no, like a new one where they have like like
yeah, half of a car coming out of a wall, yeah, and like a slide, a built in
slide to the wall where you walk in that's a wall. Yeah, no, that one of
these bikes,
these people who have such incredible attention to detail, they're buying
worn husks. No one is going buying wooden poles. No one is doing P.
Rods. Nobody's doing Peewee. Nobody's doing Death Star. Yes,
we need to take these these these colonial women to work yeah and make me
a house.
What set these colonial women to work? That's okay to say what's wrong with
that? Let's set them to work yeah and build me a nice house that looks like a
video game and also if you're going to do all this shit and make do all this
that you should also have to farm for me and make me different food and all that stuff.
You want a corn broom? Get those husks, dry out that shit yourself. And we should have
a goat. And we should have a goat. Or you should milk my dog or something. We already
have a goat. In my person we already have a goat. Yeah, that's it. Okay, that's enough
of it. That's too much. You're talking about that vision thing. I don't remember who it
was, but there's some skater that like hit their head falling off of a like a
big stair set so hard that their vision went
fucking skater hit their head really hard falling from really high. They fell
from really high and their vision went like completely black and white. It's
either Chris Cole forever Thomas, but no for like an hour can happen for an hour.
They went full artist. I didn't see him. I pissed my dad off so much. That's
funny. One of my dad talked about it for years. I don't even know what it was up
up against. It was up against 2011. It was up against 2012. The artist was up against
2012 and then from what I remember, my dad reacted to it like a sports game. He's like
Jesus fucking Christ! The artist, the black and white movie, and then I remember him looking
at me and being like, "Caleb, we should have made Moneyball." Oh yeah. The Tree of Life!
so mad because it won over Moneyball. That's so funny. Yeah, that's so fucking
funny. That's great. I was thinking of movies that I saw in 2011. It's like Toy
Story 3, The Sitter with Joe Mangielo. I remember my dad, he looked at me, he was
like, "You know what, Caleb? You know what we should have done this year? Made
a fucking black and white movie because we would have won an Oscar." He's so mad.
It's one of the maddest I've ever seen him.
Just a bit because Moneyball lost. The ultimate dad movie lost. It was, it was,
the ads have been waiting for the industry nod for decade. Dude, I went to
Kellogg Diner one time at like three in the morning. I was like hammered and I
sat down at the diner and next to me was just a dude like eating the biggest
breakfast plate I've ever seen just watching Moneyball
watching Moneyball on his phone.
What's up? A little breakfast right there just on that big Moneyball that
you have a plate you saved the most boring story ever by saying, but all
breakfast
as a guy watching money, you saw a guy watching a movie, a guy watch a movie on
his phone. That's your story. That was I've never thought to watch a whole
movie on. What are you crazy on my phone? No, why not everybody? You see that on
the train all the time. You're somebody if you're eating, what were you doing at
the diner? You on your phone watching a full he's probably stopped. He stopped
the movie and got up and left when he was done. So he didn't watch the whole
movie. He watched he was watching a good chunk of the movie.
I
like all the time on my phone. I saw a movie clip on YouTube.
The whole movie. And it did that like
it was the whole movie on his iTunes.
We have that movie clips part two of Eleven Moneyball. Yeah, that's what he
was watching. No, he's watching the whole movie. I don't believe it. It was
on his iTunes. Even if he was, it's not even interesting. It's not that
interesting. I can't believe you're fighting against it.
Is it now? It's not that interesting.
Don't get all inquisitive. Is it?
Yeah, wait, let's look a little deeper. Don't talk like that.
Talk like what?
It's part of a mystery.
Oh yeah, if that was the beginning of like a Knives Out style thing,
then I might as well... He was watching Moneyball, but then I saw him... Oh
my God, Pat, you would be maybe the best writer of all time to write the
beginning part of a mystery, where they, right before they cut to the detective,
like the beginning of like a Columbo episode or something. What would your
story be? Where like nothing's happening? Yeah, you would write like the first
four pages and then bring someone else in to write the page or something gets
killed.
All right, what do you do? What's this set up for your mystery? All right, all
right, so the
it's a
no, it's a library. I was going to say laundromat. It's a library that's next
to a laundromat. Whoa, that's already good and I already like this.
The lady who works at the laundromat closes up the closes up shop, puts a
shirt on a hanger and then walks out, walks into the library. So then she
walks up to the... It's clear that she has a rapport with the librarian. She's
talking, she walks in... I love that. Is the librarian girl or boy? Hey, Janice.
Oh, hey, Bernice. Hey, what have you... You clean a lot of clothes today?
No, just one shirt today.
And I hung it up before I left.
no, all right.
Are you here to get a book? No, I'm here to return my book. Okay, what book is
your
memoirs of a geisha? Oh wow, okay, no, no, no, because I said laundromat,
because then that could be racist coded.
So she's actually returning
she's actually retarded.
Okay, so I do now do one more one and she's returning memoirs of a
geisha. Yeah,
no fifty shades of gray. Okay, okay, now she's returning now.
And then Bernice picks it up and goes,
and she goes, yep, and then suddenly a man in a trench coat and a hat runs
in and slits her throat and she falls on the floor and screams and grabs
her throat, which one is Bernice or Janice? Both. Her name is not Bernice.
Burnet okay, Bernays, not like a no yeah, it's the laundromat lady gets killed
and then cut okay and then theme song and then the rest of the episode yeah
what in the what in the what is going on in this library? I heard of this
happen. I've heard of a bookish demeanor, but I've never seen something
he's madara madara,
but when it comes to this criminal, there's no one demeanor. This is
demeanors criminal
not even using book
did a bookish and he did it in a bookish room. Well, let me take a
look at this and then he walks up and he like and it is the guy from glass
or from knives out yeah and he opens us on you. He opens up her throat slit
ceiling up
puts his fingers in a hall. Oh there is a piece of paper in here. Let's see what
it reads. I did it. I did it. Well, criminal, the paper cut killer, take
this to the forensic lab and see if it's signed anywhere and then and then and
then get this here's. I'm going to add a wrinkle. Okay, the librarian. Can you do
the library? Go in the shirt? They're a library and says and that was the
motive. I'll take it to the to the lab. That's what the movie's called a wrinkle
the case, a wrinkle in the shirt, a wrinkle in the book,
a wrinkle in the book and also the shirt that was at the laundromat next door.
Wait, so what was the setup? And then the librarian says, I'll take this to
the lab. Why would you take it to the lab for me? I'll just take it. I like
doing things for you. Well, thank you so much for being helpful, Mrs. Janice.
And then the librarian walks off screen and we don't know where Cici go. Okay,
but we assume she goes to the lab. But we don't know. But here comes the
detective. That's where that's, kind of put a pin in there. A cyst,
sidekick. Sidekick. Hey!
My God! Why can't we dissolve this crime today? Oh my God, my canine sidekick is
speaking English.
Holy, the devil's got me. Oh my God, I think I, well, here. I guess I'm okay
with it. Yeah, I mean, I guess it's kind of cool. We need to find a murder
weapon. And you have the perfect nose to find smells of murder. I pull out.
Okay, now you need to shut up. I will pull, no, you need to.
There's a bee in this library.
That's the problem.
That's a problem with a canine.
Somebody get a book on bees and find out what they don't like
to get this bee out of here.
Okay, I'm going to swat the bee.
Oh, it's staying now because it was used to swat a bee.
Okay, wait, let me get the bee.
No, no, no, no, no.
so don't shoot at the be grab my
the jump pad. We have to get up to the second guys. I want to so I do want to
solve this mystery. Yeah, okay, okay, so it was the librarian's husband. Yeah,
it is a set up with Janice and his name and because I will say I want to expand
the library. Oh, my God, the the laundromat lady was taking out all the
books that were highest demand and keeping them for too long as well, and
it's also mighty curious that the killer, it was all erotic, does a murder
directly in front of Janice and yeah exactly, but not and she can't identify
and kill Janice and Janice, they asked they asked what they asked Janice like
what did the guy look like you did and she's like my husband. She's like no,
she's like well. I think he was about three inches tall and he had great so
you should go find a guy. It looks like that I'll be right on well based on the
security footage. He doesn't look like that at all. There's no such thing as a
that is green. Wait, who's that and you see him? He's looking he's checking out
a book yeah. How to get taller, how to get taller and less green. She's
friend again,
and she's framing
how to get taller and turn into a blue guy instead of a green guy. It would be
would you rather be blue or green in this world in this world that were this
movie world, the current world that we live in. I was in this world, then
in the
green. I would die up world. Would you rather be a blue motherfucker or a
green bastard? I would rather be a blue motherfucker. I guess I'd rather be
green. You'd be green. Why? 'Cause I could be an alien or a lizard. I think
I'd rather be blue because I like blue more than green. Yeah. I think green,
just when it comes to a green guy,
there's something special about it. A blue guy is like a blue guy, but a green
guy is almost like... Green is almost alien. It's almost like unbelievably
I think green would make it to a higher level of public office. A green guy, the
exact same guy with green skin or blue skin. Blue skin, oh my God. See, this is
like another... See, I think it would be blue maybe because I think green...
Racially coded question. I think green, it does, you think mutant, you think
alien, you think blue, you think I'm blue. Yeah, I think blue is literally like,
"Oh, this guy is a party animal. This is a big fat liar." But green, this is guys
from another world. This is a whole other planet of people. Or he's a... But a
blue person that we have blue people. There are people turn blue people eat
colloidal silver to make themselves and then blue, but people eat broccoli.
They turn green if they don't eat green, green candy. According to what
happens, that's what happens.
That's what happens if you eat a bunch of carrots. The can you turn orange
makes you orange. I think I had an orange and it makes you president. I
honestly think I was orange for about one year when I was in high school
because how many carrots I ate. There's some I think I'm also I could be blue
pretty easily. I think I could come blue. I think that happened on like an old
seven. My hands and feet turn blue. One of the I've never been blue and I've
never been green.
I bet you've been blue. I've been green and blue. I think we all three of us
have been blue for a video, but I've never been naturally blue. I think I've
been naturally both blue and green on parts of my body. I've seen you be green
yeah and I think I've seen you be blue and it's not my hands and feet turn
blue. Yeah, yeah, I've seen your blue feet. Yeah, but I would I think that you
have to go blue because you got to go blue is like you turn. You can be a DJ
green. People are going to mistake you for a plant. I think green and I've
it's happened to me. I think you go under the wrong lighting. Some people are
going to get very mad at you. Also people don't like Shrek. Yeah, people don't
like the Grinch. Well, they didn't like Shrek at first. Blue Grinch is worse
than the Green Grinch. Yeah, that's true, but yeah, but Blue Grinch also is not
widely known. It's true. It's completely true, but I think I like that. I think I
like the idea of being green precisely because it's so scary. You want to start
from the bottom. Yeah. I want to walk around and be like, 'That's right,
motherfucker, I'm green.' And then, 'What are you gonna do about it?' This guy
looks like a green apple. If I was blue or green, I think I would need to also
be in, like, the NBA or something. Yeah. What about hot pink? Hot pink? That
would, that would easily be the worst. Hot pink is the worst, 'cause then
everyone thinks that you just have high blood pressure from eating. Yeah, no,
I've seen, no, hot pink, not like, not like... Everyone thinks that you eat a
close enough to a shade of human person. Yeah, they're going to think that you
just this guy's fucking a part pig. Yeah, exactly. Yeah, and look, see right
there, like that shade of pink. That's not that's
yeah, I don't think that people are. I think that's going to have a similar
reaction to green or blue when it's that like look, look at this guy with the
with the with the ears here. Yeah, that's Mr. Pink. I don't know who that
is and there's all if you're telling me if you saw a guy who was this color,
would be like oh yeah. I guess that you could just have high boy. Can you click
that link, go to pink, go back,
click on that? Mr. Pink? Mr. Pink on mushroommagazine.com. Well yeah. And
here's all the info about him.
Mr. Pink? Who the fuck is this? Yes, I accept the cookies. This is art fashion.
Everybody at the big festivals knows Mr. Pink. He is half naked and painted in
pink and jumps out the crowd as if he emerged from another dimension. Okay.
tens of thousands of festival people have seen him. This is what you guys were
saying about the fucking like being a green person.
Your real name is Jovis and you are from the United States. Wait, his name is
Joe Visible? No, Jovis. Jovis. Wait, hold on. What was the funniest? Oh God,
he looks amazing. Wow. I wanna read this question. He says, "What is the
funniest experience you had when performing as Mr. Pink?" My God, there
have been literally hundreds. They are all so unique and precious. It would be
really hard for me. I thought he was going to tell a funny. No, that's
really that means that the experience was too funny and he doesn't want to
repeat it. I think he's done bad things. He asked then because it's twenty
sixteen. We haven't heard from him. Yeah, but anyway, that's my point right. A
guy who's this color of pink. He pops up at a festival. Hundreds of thousands of
people are paying attention to him or writing articles. It's not normal enough.
It's still a blue tear experience. Yeah, Patrick swatting him away. Yeah, I don't
I'm here. I think if he comes back, I'm going to slap the shit out of him again.
OK, what?
Color would you least want to be?
I think you've already been over this.
White. Yeah. Yeah.
I would rather be green or blue than the honky I am.
Yeah, honestly, because then at least like, you know, it's like telling people
like, you know, I just say half Italian.
I literally I'm actually fucking blue.
blue. Yeah, I'm blue, but I'm actually like some and I would get you know it
would be like it would be fun to be blue and then to get really mad at people
who play the song and be like yeah, very funny man. Yeah, what a great
while so original, huh? That's what I would say there is and it's by Ruka
Ruka Ali. Oh yeah,
yeah, yeah, and you can't play that. No, you'd be able to be the ultimate. Okay,
let's let's dig deeper. What's the worst two colors to be your half half and
we're upper body is completely one color lower body completely. I would say okay,
the best one yeah is perfectly black and white like a piano.
Whoa, what are you doing? He's playing with effects. Don't don't don't worry
about you be a perfectly black and white like a piano, especially if you can get
the cross section right down the hat like the I'm saying I'm saying top and
bottom and bottom. I was thinking strike because then you have to make a
conscious decision like left and right. It's like left and right,
whatever you could switch those, but top and bottom. That's you want to
see what color your ass is and what color your face is. I was thinking
just full stripes all over the body, like pink stripes with you'd be
Superman ice cream color. Yeah, yes, you would be red and I would be
like a bomb pop. Yeah, I think I think red and white is pretty good.
I guess I guess now that I'm thinking about it, we'd have to think about
what countries flags are two colors and maybe what? Oh yeah, because that's
gonna, 'cause red and white is what Poland? I would. Oh God no. That's Poland.
I would not wanna be red and white. So yeah.
The Philippines flag is
red and blue. Who's Philippines? I don't know. You said that like it was a
guy named Philippines. I know Philippines. I would... He's my barber.
I think green and... Okay guys, let's dig deeper. What would the worst 1000
colors to be probably the whole rainbow. Yeah, the rainbow is barely even it's
out of the color because if I tan, then it's going to get darker and darker
until it's like a
like a negative of a rainbow. Yeah, an opposite bow, but then in the winter, I
become pastel sunbow sunbow. Yeah, that's scary. Damn pastel pasty, pasty
white like I am right now.
Speaking of the rainbow, we finally got into...
That's barely white.
I think you're calling me Barry White.
We finally got into Pride Month.
Talk a little bit about that.
Me?
Yeah.
What does it mean to you, Pride Month?
It means that there's going to be some sales for...
You're going to start wearing that dog mask and walking around with the whip?
I don't know because my domino is not participating this year because of woke reasons.
Is piss going to enter the picture for you?
That's really, really funny to be like an anti-woke person who's also into all that
stuff.
Gayness?
Being gay?
Yeah, being a gay.
You think anti-woke people who are gay?
Or like being right wing?
right wing... So you don't like David Rubin? No.
Because now, it's like all the
right wing people now are just calling gay people pedophiles
and it's just like, alright, what are you...
It's your reflection in the headphones.
Can you, Jubio, can you really quickly make it look like
Patrick has put a Twitch chat up like he's doing a Hassan stream while he's talking about this?
God damn it.
just a bunch of people. I'm not going to talk about growing twitch chat. I'm not
going to talk about this. I love these right wing people are they gays or
got you. Yeah, pride month. Honestly, I think it's gone corporate. It is gone
corporate. I preferred it back when we were kids. Yeah, I like for I was a
little before I was walking around there before the chase bank got in dude.
Seriously, that chase bank is all over pride. My yeah, you know who else is
there. Black guys do nobody's complaining about.
Not kidding. Yeah, we should get a pride float that we could be that hard. I
almost I almost was a part of one last year, but then I decided not to do it.
I was like, wait, why'd you decide not to do it? Because it was gay. Wow. No,
you know what? I did instead was my friends. Wow. I did my friends fashion
show and I met that pit bull impersonator and then you were like I'm going to be on
a pride float. I was almost it was a it was Ben Ben Mora. You thought that you
were going to be on a pride float. They were not letting us anywhere near there
on the Snoopy.
The string
smiling
I think they got a Polaris slingshot for that, though I was kind of a Snoopy no
no for remember. We saw that like Polaris slingshot like meet up dude.
That was sick. There's a rental place about two blocks away from my apartment.
Yeah, it has like four of them out. I saw an old lady driving one the other day.
They're good car. I want to we need to get a three seat a
Polaris Slingshot. I think they're only two seater.
Well, they can make a special one for us. They should. We should get a double
decker. We get the pride float. Whoa, right? Three seater, double decker,
Polaris Slingshot that we have as our pride float. We go in to the pride
parade and we're like,
"How the hell did we get here?" What if... Yes, we dress up like The Hangover.
what the hell?
What? We're just trying to drive our three seated
Polaris.
What if- Where the hell are we right now? What if aliens finally detect the
Earth and they're coming down in their UFOs and they're coming down to make
contact and they're like, "We're gonna come down. We need to make contact with
these humans. We gotta come down to a place with high concentration of human
activity." And they come down in the middle of the pride parade and they land
their UFO and they come out and everyone's like taking pictures like, "Oh
my God, it's aliens!" And they take their pictures and they're all next to all
the guys sucking each other and with the pride flag and our first
our first pictures of ever of aliens. They're all people pissing on each
other and then forever
then the aliens are forever. No, the aliens. Can you imagine that situation
and people will be like I did not have this on my bingo card? Yes, yes, and the
aliens also would be so probably when they figured out what was actually
like. Oh, my God, we're getting out of here. Homophobic alien showing up
because they definitely aliens definitely are. That is I guess I never
the the first picture somebody ever takes of an alien is not going to be just an
alien against a white background. No, they're going to land somewhere.
They're going to be in front of like
or something. They're going to be in front of a guy. There's going to be a
crazy guy. They're literally going to show up at Burning Man. Yeah, they will
be in the middle of Burning Man. Yeah, women with giant hippie tits flying out
of their pants. What is Burning Man? Burning Man is a festival. It's
basically a, yeah, it's like a sex and
It's not really, I mean there is music there, but it's mostly like a, you go there, you do
drugs and you fuck people and you burn a big worker man.
That's why all the tech people go there?
Yeah.
Oh.
I thought it was a music festival.
No, it's like art and dance.
It's an experience.
The fire that burns the man should, somebody should lead a big trail of gasoline and burn
everyone else that's there.
You want to kill these, it's like a hundred thousand people, you want to kill all these
people?
They're going to burning man, yeah.
Yeah, they should all get it.
You didn't even know what it was.
You just learned, I just said that they have dancing and art.
You just have to kill them all, burn them to death.
Burn them all to death in the middle of the desert?
Burn all those motherfuckers that bring my big magnifying glass, put it over them.
Burning Man, I would go to Burning Man.
I would not.
That sounds fucking cringe.
I would go anywhere for the most part.
But I would go to Coachella though.
I'd go to Coachella.
I really want to go to the gathering of the juggalos and perform there.
I was performing that song. That's you performing. Yeah. You're doing your DJ
set at Coachella. I bring this over there. Only hitting that. Yeah. But I would go to
any, I'm trying to think if I've ever been to a music festival. Oh my god, we came
full circle. Guess what? All the way back to music festivals. I don't think I've ever been to one.
I've been to Boston Calling. Oh, me and Pat went to a... Oh, we went to FYA Fest. I lied.
I've been to Azalea Festival in Wilmington, North Carolina. Azalea Banks?
I've no no no I've been there twice. One time I saw Leonard
Skannard and one time I saw Snoop Dogg.
Nice, but those are the only people there.
Yeah, nice, but it's not really a music festival.
We went to the FYA in 2022, I think 2022, but I think that's
it. Yeah.
Yeah, I wanted to go to that one the stick new world or whatever.
No, the one that had him gay and had him in like gay Mr.
Bungle, your favorite band?
There were a bunch of bands I liked on that show, but I would not go to that festival.
But there was another, I wanted to go to Psycho Las Vegas, which is called Psycho Las Vegas,
and it was in Mandalay Bay.
Oh wow.
What was that?
It was like I Hate God and Emperor and a bunch of metal bands.
Psycho Las Vegas.
The poster said Psycho Las Vegas, Mandalay Bay.
Damn, that's tight.
I was like, God damn.
We went, what do, oh that was the first time you ever went to Applebee's.
The first of the first of three or four. Yeah, that's true. I there's the funniest Applebee's
ad that keeps coming on my to be all what happens in it. It is just a video of the food just
bouncing around it like you know how they do in a commercial where the food bounces
down on the plate and there's no talking in it at all and it just shows the food and shows
the name of the food and the prices and it's just I want to dance with somebody. Okay,
I want to feel the heat was it just plays that song and it doesn't make you want to
to go to Applebee's. It makes me laugh every time.
Hey, real quick.
Because it's just food on the screen and they're just playing that song.
As a comedian, I have something to say to you commercial writers.
Back the fuck off!
That's right.
Okay? Leave the funny shit to me!
Uh-huh.
I'm sick of you fucking making these little...
Leave Eric Wareheim out of it. I don't give a fuck.
You're basically doing an entire season of network comedy...
Tim and Eric.
In one... 30 seconds. Fuck that!
fact, Tim and Eric, get your ass back to adult swim. A T and T get your ass off
purple mattresses. I don't want to see no more little Caesars commercials. I
want commercials that are unintentionally funny, like from the old
days with puppets. I am. I am coordinating DDoS attacks and
electromagnetic pulses to take down the entire AT&T network. All the
McDonald's commercials. Stop taking my ideas. Yeah, I have a bunch of ideas
about commercials where people get McDonald's food and eat it and smile and
I've been using every single one. Most of my stand up is about people eating
different foods and going, "Mmm, that's good. How much does this cost?"
So please shut the fuck up. And Burger King, you stole my idea to make a
commercial for your burgers. Stop stealing my song, Burger King. When I saw
your menu, I thought, "I'm gonna make a commercial about these items." You did
it, but I had the idea first. I swear to God, I was walking around Burger King
headquarters in downtown New York City, Manhattan, and I was walking around just
going whopper, whopper, whopper, whopper, junior, junior, junior, junior.
(Laughter)
Yep.
Like I do every single day.
And they stole it and changed the fucking lyrics.
I know that they had one of those little guns that you can, with headphones on, that they
use in a spy movie.
The spy gun.
FBI.
And they stole that from me.
I know for a fact.
And do you guys remember what I used in my bit when I used to do in Boston about like
Arby's, what's their fucking thing, saying like, oh what, we have meat?
Yeah.
Boy, guess what their slogan is now.
no fucking way. We have the money. They stole that from you. They stole that.
They ripped that shit off of me. That is so fucked up that they do that to
Boston Open. My comics is stealer shit. Let me say something though. Most
vacation and travel ads, you keep doing what you're doing, 'cause I like seeing
the beaches and the TV. Yeah. Melissa McCarthy, you stay in that Travelocity
commercial or whatever. Melissa McCarthy, y'all, y'all pussies stay.
No, this is what you should be doing. You should not be doing funny commercials,
you guys, you should be doing dramatic commercials, scary commercials,
tears, a musical with food. I want to see every more of that surprisingly
human commercials. Here's an idea for a commercial Arby's.
Somebody's at an Arby's. They say, let me get a half pound roast beef. The
guy goes, yeah, of course he grabs like a
half pound roast beef sandwich. Okay, no pound of roast beef. Yeah, I thought
you were saying
he gets the you should be able to do that. It should be able. He gets the
sandwich right and he puts it in his pocket, his chest pocket for good luck,
like or just to put it there, that's the only pocket he has he's wearing a
uniclo pants with small pockets anyway.
So he's about to walk out okay, bam open the door, five foot, five white guy with
a bullet proof vest and an ar fifteen, who says I've been playing video games
my whole life and I'm ready to kill. Can I add a
mass shooting, killing every single person in the Arby's brain flying
everywhere?
He's double tapping the babies, he's killing everybody yeah, but and then
this guy he he's fully in shock, realize he's been shot and then he's down on
the floor. The guy finally does he kills himself or gets shot by the cops or
whatever, but then the guy goes oh my God wait pulls out the thing like a
Bible. There's so many layers of meat in a be sandwiched, completely block the
bullet from entering his heart eats it and then takes a bite and he says
doesn't taste like bullet at all. It doesn't actually
I was going to say I have a Patrick. I've had my hand raised okay, okay, and
We do not see that. We don't do this. We don't do that. We don't do that.
We don't do that here. I know that basically legacy and movie tie-ins is huge right now.
So as a marketing type of guy, let me tell you that this could be a tie-in for the new
legacy sequel. They're probably going to make for Falling Down.
Yep. The scene when he's in goes into the burger place and he shoots everything.
You could get him to come do that. Does he shoot in it?
Yeah. He shoots up a burger place. I was going to say he after he has the bullet in the
sandwich pulls out the sandwich right in the guy's face. I can't there's so much.
It's probably better if he's saying which is so juicy. Oh my God. There's so
much.
Or he just goes over to the guy. So that guy takes the AR 15. Yeah,
accidentally kills himself but shoots through his own head into the guy's head
and double suicide. No, I'm saying that the shooter kills himself. That's
because he can't handle that was cool though. And then at the end it's like
it's like Arby's. It's like a fuck, what the fuck just happened and every with
every sandwich get a chance to win a ticket to falling down to
the revenge, the revenge, Arby's, who the hell made this commercial? I just
had the best was a good idea. I said the best idea for a sequel to falling down
yeah, following up, falling down to society strikes back and it's all the
people he fucked with and they're kind of kill. Yeah, that's a good idea.
They're doing pitchforks in the street
that it's about cancel culture. You know that's a good idea. You got cancelled
because you went crazy and killed all these people
out a big as RPG on the highway and shot all basically all three of us just
learned about every single character and extra from the original. They're old
now yeah, I like they all have gone. They all have the same guns that Michael
Douglas has. I've never seen that movie, but I've seen every clip from that
movie. Yeah, it's a good movie. I've seen
that character parodied in Tony Hawk's American, I never really understand why
he does all that the
it's kind of a satire. He basically just fed up with modern and it's made by
Joel Schumacher, who made Batman. Oh really yeah, it's a good ass movie. You
should watch it. I bet you'd like it, because I bet you identify with the
character. I'm nothing, okay, I'm the furthest thing from violence. Why in my
head I just is to until
I do get pretty worried that one day I'll snap yeah, but I think that that's
probably eight or nine years away. I've driven you to the brink a few times. You've never
driven me to violence. I've driven you to violence many a time. You have instigated
violence and you have struck first. I will never ever strike first. There is not, no,
I have seen you, you have slapped me. When you wanted it. You have slapped me a lot on
this show. Shut up right now. There is now visual evidence of your slapping miss. Shut
up. You tried to put me in handcuffs one time. That was funny. You tried to handcuff me to
to you while we were recording. Why would you not want to be handcuffed to me for a day?
That is a perfect cartoon style. I think that you would be good in that. You know what I
had to do that day? Go to prison. No. What? Jerk it. I don't remember. I think it was
jerk it with the left. Jerk it with the left. Jerk it with my left hand. Jerk it with the
both. Jerk it with the both hand. I gave you, by the way, when I tried to handcuff you to
me. I gave you my right hand, which meant on your left, which meant that I was
giving you the, I'm, we're both right handed. Then I broke the handcuffs with
my strength and you threw, they were cheapo handcuffs, you threw that at my
knee and it did hurt. Really? Yeah, because it was a piece of metal at my
knee. Honestly man, so I've driven you to the brink of insanity and violence. I
I didn't even know that until right now. And that's another problem. Why can't we
communicate more? Yeah. Cause that's when we were not communicators. That's probably
two years ago. That is two years ago. And you couldn't just tell me. What a wild
ride it's been. You couldn't just tell me in the moment, "Hey, when you threw that
at my knee." It hurt my knee from the metal. I probably did tell you in the moment.
Metal on my knee hurts. Immediately, probably. I don't think you did. I think I
would have remembered that. Yeah. Because every single time that you tell me
anything really hurts you, I scratch it into my heart. I inscribe it on my heart
that fucking razor blade. Yeah, I did throw a can at your head one time.
That was wrong. That was wrong. And you I remember you throwing a shoe to you.
I remember that you're the hurt or you're the abusive one. You probably
you always throw stuff at you. You know, honestly, you always throw stuff at him
and then you probably do. Don't say that. Probably. Probably does just
based on the evidence. Yeah, based on how much stuff he throws at me, it's
always he throws stuff at you and then you fight back and then it's I get
I get scared exactly yeah and I remember every single incident and I fight back
well. I'm self to the only the only instigation from you that I can think of
right now
is when we were in Manchester and you tried to kill him. You tried to fight
you said let's have a fight club and then you cornered him.
I'm trying to find you would not let me in, but that was funny. That was let me
something in my defense. He had an alley that his apartment building led into
that was basically what I thought was a perfect either fighting or break
dancing club. I figured you'd be more into fighting than break dancing. So I
said, let's have a fight club and you were being such a sissy about it. Just
fight. I did not want to have a fight club with you because you work out and
stuff and also I was very, very, very fat at the time. I was probably in
in terrible shape that I was extremely big at the time. So you probably had
pounds on me. You could have destroyed me. Yeah, but I don't have arm strength.
What kind of strength do you have? I don't. I sumo him. I could assume you
could have plastered him the wall. You could have got a crazy. That was a crazy
look at the time, because I had all of this fat in my gut and waist, but then
these tiny arms. I remember that. I remember the first time I saw your tiny
arms. It really shocked me. Yeah, because I think I met you in the winter time.
Yeah, when you had burned all your fat reserves?
No, I was just wearing hoodies.
I was wearing those hoodies.
But the first time I saw him with a short sleeve shirt, I was like, "Holy, this guy's
got some mini skinny arms and a big ass body."
Big ass butt in the back.
But you...
I'd eat McDonald's every day.
But okay, so I admit that Fight Club is the only time I instigated.
I don't...
Do you remember Atlantic City?
What did we do there?
When you hit me in the elevator like Solange?
Yes, and then ran away. Yeah, and then he ran away. He fully Solange and me fully
Jay-Z. Don't give a fuck. I'm a billionaire. I'm not going to touch this
thing. No, you were you, but then I chased him. We had a chase. No, you did
the thing of like you calmly kind of walked out and then once you do the next
time that you guys were in the same space, you got him. I have to. I think I
only remember the times when both of you were fighting against each other
because I'm cowering. Yeah, one time I drank. I was like, damn, these truly's
these are eight ABV, that's crazy. And I had a six pack of them and I drank the
whole thing and then I slapped you.
Abusive dad.
I remember that.
Yeah.
Wait, when...
They say that when you're drunk, you're who you truly are when you're sober.
Yeah, you're a violent abuser.
I'm a completely violent person, yeah.
They say that getting more drunk actually makes you more sober when it
comes to your behavior.
When people say... That really terrifies me. If I'm actually who I am when I'm
drunk, that is the worst news ever.
Yeah, it's so funny.
Mostly when I drink, I have a good time.
You just blink a lot.
Yeah.
I blink a lot and I go, "Hmmm."
You go, "Hmmm."
And I like think it's funny to put like a new hat on.
Or if I find a jacket on the street, I'm going to put that on.
You drunk on the street is a scary sight.
Why?
Because you're going to pick something up.
Yeah.
Pick some trash up and keep it.
I'm going to pick something up. I'm going to keep it.
Yeah. I don't like that.
sometimes I sometimes I find money.
Oh, I found it. I found a dollar on the street the other day. I found a sheet of
dog stickers. Whoa! I was made to throw them away. By who? You can guess. Wow!
I hate her!
So wow! I've been having kind of a rough time at home. Yeah, I can imagine. Yeah,
you need him to come in.
Start throwing shit at her.
Oh, brother. Yeah, but you haven't you have not violently hurt me in some time.
Yeah. So I mean, I've got to stop doing it. There was a recent you threw a can
at him recently. I threw a can at you and no retaliation from me. And you said
and I was having a bad day. You looked at me and said you have bad instincts.
You do. You have no social. Yeah, completely true. That honestly that did
shake me to my core. It's saying you saying you have bad instincts. I was
I was clearly in a grumpy mood and you threw a can at my head.
Yeah.
And then we had to record a podcast.
Yeah, but then I gave you an apology poem.
I don't remember that.
So let's talk AI.
I said I remember exactly what it was.
Oh, it was AI.
It was not AI.
It was AI.
I came up with it on the spot.
Because I said throwing a can even in jest is not the best.
First run.
Patrick's first run.
After his worst crime.
I'm throw
do you guys? I don't know why I start first time you because you grew up with
with brothers. That's true. I was the little sibling, so you were the herder.
I was the instigator and then I would run away.
I you I treat you exact. I realize that day. I treat you exactly like I do. I
did my little brother because he would always like punch me or something yeah,
and I'll go
you don't realize if I fought back, I'd kill you.
If I fought back, if I let myself fight back, you would be fucking dead.
You'd be in the hospital, your neck would be broken.
That's what I used to tell him.
I was the instigator, then when I got older I stopped, but then my two older, my older
and my younger brother would fight and then I would use that as an excuse to shut off
their video game and then I would start playing.
I miss fighting my brothers, man.
That was fun shit.
Dude, you can't fight anybody anymore.
You can't fight your brothers anymore.
It's bullshit.
You can fight your brothers.
You can't fight your brothers.
I fight my brothers every time.
Then it gets sad.
And like sounds like that happened.
There's a hyena outside.
Yeah.
But yeah, you can fight your brother.
Anytime that we go back for Christmas, we get, we fight.
You fight your brother?
We wrestle over something.
I think my brothers, my older and younger brother have wrestled.
We smoke too much weed and we start wrestling.
At some point.
Watching TV.
But yeah, no, now I'm thinking about it.
I have like thrown shit at my brother and then run away.
At Christmas, yeah.
You're a coward archer.
Uh huh.
Yeah, I got a good aim. You should be on the back lines. Yeah. You're a sniper. I am. Bastard.
I'm real good at sniping. You're not willing to put your body in. Me, I'm the first person
to fucking die. I'd be like the John Daly. I'm like a spy. I'd be the John Daly of snipers.
I'd come in and disguise. Spy, sniper. Pyro. Pyro. Heavy. Yeah. Yeah. I walk in and I just
die as much as possible. There's a, every army is 5,000 me in the front. Do you think,
That makes sense. Like snipers don't really have to be in good physical condition. I mean
they have to run away.
I think they have to carry a bunch of sniper stuff.
Yeah, but John Daly...
I think every soldier has to be in physical condition, right?
John Daly would just... no, he had a caddy.
Doesn't everybody have to do all this stuff?
You're saying that snipers should have a caddy.
Snipers should have a caddy.
I agree.
And they can sit up there in their little nest and drink a bunch of high... oh, well
then it affects their aim.
They can't be drunk.
They can smoke a bunch of cigarettes, though.
I think you probably take some kind of crazy stimulant.
Yeah, Medgar Diazepam.
Yeah.
Shit.
I think that if you were the John Daly of snipers, that would be very cool.
Your aim is so good.
I guess it's more like a Dustin Dahlen, where your aim is so good, even though you're a million
beers deep.
Or you're like the drunken master.
Yeah.
You're only good at aiming when you're drunk.
You're doing drunken kung fu style stuff.
If you think about playing, you're better when you're playing a first person shooter game
if you're a little drunk. Yeah, that's true. That's actually a myth. Completely
true. Now that's a myth. It's completely true. That is true. That's an alcohol.
That's completely true. I am stone cold sober when I play FPS shooters.
That's because you play in a different style. Yeah, I do play tiger style. You
play with your keyboard all fucking stupid. I put my keyboard completely
sideways like this. Yeah, I don't really. I don't know why I just started doing
it one day. I think I saw some counter strike guy do that. Yeah, I play every
I saw you do that. I saw you do that. I started doing the weird controller grip. Oh, you do?
Yeah. Not for first person shooters, but for Dark Souls. I've been playing it like that.
I miss the custom controllers. My dad used to have one that was like all, every button
was on the back. Have you seen, I don't know if we talked, tell me if we talked about this
before, where the person who made the custom fight stick for the fighting game tournament
where it's every, it's like, it's, it's like a, they made it in a big shoe box and then
it's like, it has like a hundred buttons where they're all on a line so that you can do combos
goes by just like just pressing down the like it's like every button is just
like a different direction thing. So they brought it's like technically legal in
the turn of whatever and got pissed off. That's
it looks like shit. It's like it doesn't actual shoe box. It is a million
buttons and they just go
and just
because it makes it easier. It's so sick. I would use that. I would win every
single fighting and you can just build that nowadays. People is build their own
ish. I hate builders. Yeah, it's weird. I like out of here builders because where
did our inventions go? Yeah, it's true. Wow, that's true. That's actually, I'll just be
stuck in your head. Yeah. Yeah, if we had no builders, there would be no inventions.
If we had no inventions, we would have no uniqueness. There would be inventions, but
not prototypes. True. Prototypes are the mother of invention. No. They're the child of an
invention. Mother necessity. Oh. Invention prototypes are the mother of a blueprint.
Who was the mother of invention?
Necessity.
Zappa.
Frank Zappa.
He died from smoking too much.
You know that?
Really?
Yeah.
He's gotta be the only one.
He was also afraid of the human mouth.
Or the nose.
He had a bunch of nose surgery.
I do not give a fuck about Frank Zappa.
I used to love him so much and then when I got older I was like, "Oh this guy sucks."
I don't give a fuck about any old music that sounds weird and weird.
I like old music like Da Beus.
Were you kidding me? They got a song about a fucking yellow submarine.
You think that's normal?
I don't listen to the lyrics.
Yeah, you just listen to the music.
You're just there for the tunes.
You go to the Beatles rock band and turn the vocals down.
Mr. Beef, Captain Zappa.
I like one Captain Zappa.
There's a good couple of them.
But it's too much time.
It's hard. The only weird guys, the only weird guys who have ever made a good rock song are
Ween because they do Spongebob music. They are the inspiration for Spongebob. Most music
is just crap. I can't care about it. Here's what I like. I used to try to care about it,
I just can't care. It's too much of it. I just don't give a fuck. Too many movies. There's
too much tunes to pay attention to. It's like growing up and being like, "Oh yeah, I don't
I don't need to look at the new Pokemon game.
Yeah.
You need to choose, as you get older, you need to choose a hobby that is not one of the big
three of music, movies, and games.
Dinosaurs.
I picked dinosaurs.
You need to choose dinosaurs.
Something that's so, like, yeah, dinosaurs, crosswords, which is basically, it might as
well be fortune cookies.
Pendulums.
Huh?
Pendulums?
You could get into pendulums.
You said pendulum.
Pendulums.
Is that a hobby?
It's a hobby you can have.
Is that a hobby? It's a hobby you can have. You set up stuff and then you swing
your pendulum to make sure that it's fun. Yeah, I mean, honestly, any anything,
any literally imagine a hobby. I mean, if you're doing it in the garage,
truth, I think the true thing is that music, movies and video games, these are
not hobbies. Grandfather clocks. They're not how you need to have. You need to
have an actual hobby. People think they're not. They're not. No, they're and
they're not even they're barely even interests. They're a thing that everyone
and sees every day of their life. You know it's a nice water and yeah, it's
literally it's food. Yeah,
ebay's an okay hobby. Yeah, reset. That's a hobby. Anything where you actually do
something and you're not looking at something, anything that if you're doing
it in the garage or a separate room that's just for this and your wife walks
in, she's upset that you're in there. Yeah, that is a good hobby, because that
means that you don't give a fuck what anybody else thinks, including the person
who's supposed to be closest to you. Yeah, you're still going to do this.
exactly. You don't realize this is this is I do this so that I can spend time
with you because if it wasn't for this, I never see your
I'd be biting your ankles while you're making dinner.
Okay,
and cooking's not a hobby either. Nope and anything girls like
cooking is definitely not a hobby. No cooking is a necessity. Yes, you have
to do that's why people invent food. Yeah, that's why, like I have cooking
Yeah, cooking is not a hobby. You have to cut like a parchment paper and then put a
salmon in it and then twist it and stuff. This is what I say to my wife. I say,
I'm like,
"I see you're cooking," and I'm saying, "Just so you know, cooking's not a
hobby, so if you want to have a hobby, you better clean, too.
Wash the dishes after. That could be a hobby." Wash my food. Yeah. You better
wash this chicken. You better get home and wash the food. I need to, yeah,
put the plug in the sink drain, fill it up with Fabulo, so I want you to dunk
the chicken in yeah, and then I want you to dunk that I want you to put the
fabulous on the air fryer so we can get a nice a nice smell. Turn it into like
a fruit roll up yeah with the fabulous
fabulous. So put a little bit fabulous in gelatin powder. That would honestly
probably eat that and what are you doing? Don't throw away those chicken
bones. I'm making a diorama. I'm making a man of chicken bone man. I'm making
chicken bone man in my office. You know what he fucking times have I told you
not to throw away the bones, because I make mobiles and I make chicken man and
I've been working on this for the past six months. You've seen what he looks
like. I've got the face almost done. I just need fifteen
with glue. You can't vacuum in here. You can't vacuum. You can't back and take
one of the did you touch my bones? Did you move my bones? Because I didn't oh
it's in this drawer. I didn't put it there, though. I know for a fact that I
did not put this bone in my sweatshirt drawer.
I know that you did that. I did not forget this bone in my sweatshirt
pocket. I wouldn't do that. I wouldn't do stay the fuck out of my
sweat.
Those are my sweatshirts and you can't
top drawer, all bones, second drawer, all sweatshirts, bottom drawer is all
my glue. Guess what I'm doing? I'm making a sweatshirt made out of bones,
putting a padlock on all of your dresser.
How are my shirts? They're too big on you. What the hell you're wearing that
to bed. You're wearing that to bed. That's my crank. Yeah, put that back.
Here's the here. That's my crank. Yeah, what if I'm going to sell that? What
if somebody swatted us right now and called in and said that I was I was
holding somebody hostage? You're wearing my shirt. They'd come in. They kill you
I think you were me yeah. You fucking don't bitch a woman would not wear a
shirt that has Dane Cook's face on it. There's no world. Okay, listen if you're
gonna we'll compromise. You can wear that big shirt, but you gotta wear some
big pants too. Yep, yep, and a way it looks like you're not wearing anything
because the shirt's so long. You have to dress up like a mini baby. You need to
dress exactly like me or else I don't get turned on by you. Oh come on. You
need to wear my big pants and you need to wear my big shirt and my big way.
not the episode. I can't do this. Go pull up the website. Oh wait.
What website? The website. Pink Person? Yeah, pull this website up. Okay.
Why Pink Person? Are we... So we have a new live show coming up. Oh shit.
Coming up on July 14th. Go to swagproof.com/shows. July 14th, this is a
show featuring Pierce Campion, who you know from previous episodes. You also
know Alex Forrest and Joe Gleason from the planet.
Home planet.
What's their thing called?
This is world's biggest army port of call, Gowanus. We're doing a sketch show at Little
Field.
These are sketches that we are writing.
It's going to be a sketch show.
So imagine, think about this, think about all the crazy funny stuff we were saying about
are making a bone sweatshirt for a girlfriend. Imagine if that was all fleshed out and we
wrote stuff like that. And we wrote it and we performed it live on a stage. So go to swagpoop.com/shows
to buy tickets to it. It's in July. You better be there. I made a video for it and it flopped.
Big flop. It flopped immediately. A flopping video. We're going to have to promote this
way more. We're going to have to do another video.
Patrick had a giant flop.
Maybe we just post the poster.
The little video that I made.
Instead of making weird videos.
I thought that it was a good video.
You flopped a fucking ton.
And it fucking flopped.
Great.
A flopping win.
I flopped on the promo side. I thought that I knew how to promote and do marketing.
This is the other thing guys, we need to sell this show out because it's Patrick's first
time organizing a show.
Yep.
And he's doing a great job so far.
He's done an incredible job.
Except for the flopped video.
The flopped video was not even so bad.
It wasn't that bad.
I wouldn't really even call it a fly. He works hard, organized the whole thing.
He really myself. He actually did he completely did. He was on the email
chains saying
basically looking at these percentages and I was saying I was using a lot of
hello,
exclamation point, using a lot of
he was using a lot of hello. I was I was saying hello a lot, yeah, looking
over so much joy, writing an email. No, no, no use the hello, put some hello,
And you know what? You guys are going to think this is crazy of me. You guys are going to
think, "Damn, maybe this is how he got it." I did color by numbers with Patch's email
for the Union Hall show we did that one time because I was nervous about writing the email.
I didn't think we would get the show, so I used a previous email, switched all the nouns
around.
You mad-libs-ed it.
I mad-libs-ed it.
That was smart of you.
That was smart.
*Screaming*