and
hitchcock did not do
scooper to the side i think he did not know that is a very common in this fall
moves a very common that he did i think i read a list of spending a bit around
you know around is what i have talked made no they will make it and then
drowned
you're thinking of uh... of the third suicide is pretty lynchian
No, Squidward suicide was Hideo Nakata. Oh, okay. It's a Japanese film. Oh,
yeah, that makes sense. That makes sense because it has themes of suicide.
That shit honestly still scares me. Yeah, I rewatched. I'm not gonna. I can't
it been drowned. I will never revisit that. It's too scary, bro. Do you like
remember they made they made multiple people made multiple animated versions
of like what the description of the episode is? Yes, I watched I sat in bed.
and I had my girlfriend's laptop and I was watching every single one of them
and rating them to her. That sounds like something where you would come here. I
was watching them and like turning to her and going like that one wasn't as
good as the first one. What was the best one? Best one I saw was the one, I
think I took a picture of it. Please don't show it to me. Please do not show
me that. You're going to see it. Has Ben drowned the Legend of Zelda one? Yeah,
yeah, that's that one. He hacked the entire game. He did modifications. That
That one that one's so sick. That's impressive. There was a one. How is this
guy not? How is this guy not like a very famous?
Squidward suicide, lost episode 2005 by SpongeBob lost episodes. That's a good
one. Show me the picture. Whoa!
Oh, he's got poop in his eye.
Oh God, it actually looks like poop. You know what this close up camera is? This
is for Patrick to show his phone. Yeah, wow! That's genius. Yeah, my girlfriend's
mad because I ruined her YouTube algorithm. The girlfriends always get
they get mad when you fuck up their YouTube algorithm. I signed on to my
YouTube account on the TV. Now, this is all Jimmy High Roller NBA videos. Yeah,
she's pissed man. She's trying to watch house tours or some guy shows a town
remodeling. Yeah, all that shit. Fuck you. You know what's it called
Pretty Brothers.
It's called Rehe.
Rehe.
That, you just blew up so bad.
I know, holy shit.
My, today my heart hurts.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Because of what?
The air is doing bad things to everyone's lungs.
Not that.
I was fine with that.
I don't care.
I thought it was bad until I went outside and there was a bunch of Latino people playing
volleyball and I was like, "Oh yeah, it's not a big deal."
Everyone was outside all day.
Who gives a shit?
Yeah.
It's a nice out today.
more than I saw today. Is that video came out today. I don't recommend you watch
it of a man being eaten by a shark.
Where'd you see that? I saw it. How do you see all these videos? You're
searching them out. I don't search. You're like the biggest, you're the
biggest wimp when it comes to videos like that. Don't say wimp. And then... You
are a wimp. I am not. He's the biggest wimp when it comes to videos like that,
but then he's the one who sees every single one of them. I hate violence
because it's just so, it used to be so natural to me.
- Yeah, you have to watch those videos
when somebody sends you man eaten by shark.mpager
- It was just a daily dot or some shit.
- Daily dot is what they put in restaurant foods.
That is not a thing.
- What?
- That's what I, one time I got shrimp at the 99 restaurant
and they baked a daily dot into the bread.
what the fuck are you talking and the guy came over. I was like hey, I there's a
bunch of paper in my food. What the hell is this? And then the manager said, oh,
you found our daily dot that just means well. The good news is that means that
the shrimp is fresh and we cooked it today and I said I buddy, I don't want
paper. Give me my money back. They put paper in the food. They dropped a piece
paper into the breading of the shrimp. Oh, so it's like if somebody finds it,
they know that it's... It's like a quality... It's to get it away.
It's a quality thing. Also, it's probably on the bag. It's not like
paper goes bad, though. Paper goes bad.
No, it doesn't. I ate a bunch... Paper goes bad. Paper goes bad. It
yellows, yellows over time. I don't even think that's true. Yeah, it does.
Does paper go yellow over time? Yes, it does. I think paper just used
to be more yellow. Because of the pulp.
what know are you on about paper goes bad. It does not go over over a day
three month rule. Do not purchase more paper than you can use in three months
not a three monthly dot. The point is video. How long does paper expire? What
is the lifespan of photo paper three month rule? Wait what
five years five years yeah,
how does paper go back? Wait no way listen. What it says it says the first
lines of deterioration or loss of speed, huh? Oh,
that must be about photo paper yeah yeah on photography for yeah, no normal just
copy white paper does not go bad. Paper goes bad. Paper is yes. Paper does
expire. This again is photo. This is photo stuff. Okay, search does normal
paper go. There's no school that I was right there expired printer paper,
read it, our slash ebay zoom in wait. Somebody's trying to buy this shit on
day. I'm having a hard time finding any info about expired paper until recently.
I didn't even realize it had an expiration date. So does it really
expire? I have some that expired twenty years ago,
so, but I can't test it. This has got to be one of the comments here.
There's a gun. Oh, my God, the comments are deleted. Oh, my God, it's because
they're trying to suppress this information. Normal office paper will
absorb moisture from ambient humidity, unless it is sealed in an airtight
so paper can go bad if it is exposed to moisture, but that's only that you can't
print on it, because it might jam the printer from being wet, but just dry that
out, just dry that out, just dry that out, put that shit, a clothesline with
all paper. If you saw that, paper must go bad eventually. Paper, everything goes
bad, everything has an expiration date. Well, at the very least, it disintegrates.
Unless you freeze it. I mean, on a, yeah, that's why they have paper straws and
shit, but it doesn't go bad. It's not like you. It goes bad, but also a paper
straw even doesn't even they've recycled that. I mean, I think more if you leave a
slice of or a sheet of paper out, a slice of paper. I like that my fucking my weird
math teacher in sixth grade, the one who gave out deluxe hugs. I was wondering why
I remembered this. He would say, he would say, fresh slice of paper and then lick
his lips. He loved it. Fresh slice of paper. I said it by accident because I'm
addled. Speaking of paper, you guys saw what I sent you. The Dundee Mifflin was
under a scranton had the for some time the worst air quality in America,
scranton pennsylvania. Well, our heart goes out to jim and pam. I don't give a
fuck about jim and pam. Well, they I think they leave scranton for philly at
the end. So dwight and angela and andy, Angela's a whore. She's not a whore.
She's a christian. Oh wait, wait, bro. I forgot. Have you seen the fucking show?
She's a slut. What's out with andy bernard. She sluts out with everybody.
She sluts out with Dwight and then she's...
She marries Dwight.
She sluts out with the senator.
I never watched it.
The whole crew is hitting Angela.
Yeah.
And honestly she's mid.
She mid?
She's mid. I would rather have Kevin.
I would.
Close your eyes. Kevin.
The no teeth.
Whoa.
And you have to eat that chili after.
Kevin doesn't have teeth?
I think he's missing his front teeth.
He's not missing his front teeth.
his lip is just big. No, he's missing his he is missing his front top lip. I
believe that I just I don't know. I'm going to look wait. Look up Kevin the
office teeth right now. Kevin the office big teeth. No, not big teeth.
Look up with big big teeth without Kevin the office.
He's got some kind of just his lip. No, he has no front. He has no front teeth.
Are you crazy? His lip covers his teeth. Oh, whoa. Look at that. Well, I'm there,
but go down there was one where he's like me he's got tiny little chiclet teeth
yeah no he does not yeah his top lip his top lip covers it doesn't have any teeth
he has teeth we just saw the teeth those are flying in bomb Gartner is the grown
up version of Dayton yeah he doesn't have any teeth dog he looks at that
different he's gotten so much surgery since the show Kevin you can't be doing
that man you can't be dressed he's training for a bodybuilding competition
Oh yeah, that shit's so fun. The bronzer that they put on bodybuilders. I'm going
to join a bodybuilding competition. Yeah, yeah, I think I should join. I think I am
going to join. I found one that is a instead of doing a drug test, they do a
lie detector test. Oh really? Which is the funniest thing. Yeah, that you have
to go into and that you do a lie detector screening. That's so funny. And
they ask you, do you do drugs? Why not? Yeah, why not just do a drug test? What
other questions are they going to ask? It is really scary. I guess maybe it's
It's cheaper to it's a one-time purchase to buy a polygraph versus buying a bunch of drug
testing.
How would you, so many podcasts have done a polygraph.
I don't think we'll do it, but yeah, how would you beat it?
What's your strategy going into that?
Probably give myself a heart attack.
Yeah, just die.
Heart attack, sociopathy.
It is funny to imagine the bodybuilders like going in for that lie detector test and then
immediately just like they think that the lie detector is not passable at all.
So they just like are breaking down just like, yes, I smoked a little weed.
It's streaking the bronzer. Yeah. The bronzer is like going away.
It's like, actually, I don't think you do.
I smoked a cigarette before I came in here. I think you do only your face.
I think you do. You do your face.
What kind of you're going to face building competitions?
That would be cool. Just get the biggest, pointiest face possible.
Like doing the jaw training. I would beat a polygraph by having,
I did that because I have TMJ and it was affecting my sleepy.
I would be the polygraph. I would just use a prosthetic arm.
Yes.
Or whatever they connect it to.
Well, that's a hack, by the way.
Then they notice there's zombie flesh on it.
If anybody does bodybuilding competitions.
I would use zombie flesh.
Yeah.
Or I guess if anybody has an extra limb or is missing a limb or has an extra finger,
I think that that's -- you're almost a shoe-
Polydactyl.
Like a low-level bodybuilding competition.
Well, that's why the first question they always ask on the polygraph is, "Do you have a sixth
finger?"
a girl in my German class in high school who had two thumbs on one hand. I knew a kid with
an extra polydactyl. I never saw it in person. I only ever saw it online. She had a big thumb
that was going out like this. Two extra fingers. Going like this and she would wear those,
like her sweatshirt over it. I would too. I think on a first date that might be a deal
breaker. Extra finger? Not if you're in the smoke circle and you're like, here I got roach
switch clips right there. Oh snap, fucking blowing up to people, helping people out.
Oh fucking snap, putting the fucking two thumbs could be a game changer. Yes, if
there's any two fingers, if there's any finger you want two of, it's a thumb and
here's what this person should do. They should be a movie critic. Uh huh. Yes,
three thumbs up. Yeah, yeah. Oh my God, I mean, we're down, then they can just do
this. You see some crappy fucking Michael Bay movie. Yeah. Oh, four thumbs down.
don't say that about Michael Bay. I'm just joking. I actually like his movies
quite a lot. Yeah. What's that movie he made about the Transformers?
What's that movie Michael Bay made with the, with the rock, the robots and the-,
well, it's funny you say with the rock because, you know, he made movies with
the rock in it. Yeah. And then he made a movie called The Rock. That's true, he
made it. So it's kind of that, you kind of did a funny little-,
what's the movie he made, Pain and Gain? Yeah. I want to see that. That's The Rock,
that is the rock. I've only seen Kevin Hart. No, it's Mark Wahlberg.
Mark Wahlberg, yeah, yeah. Speaking of Mark Wahlberg, I started watching
Entourage. Yeah. I've seen a lot of similarities to our lives. Really?
Yeah. Is that show real? Jubio is turtle. It's real. Yeah, Jubio is
completely turtle.
I'm Ari. Okay. You are...
Vincent Chase. Vince, yeah. You're Vince for sure. And he's Johnny Drama.
who Johnny drama, Johnny drama, drama, you don't know drama
I'm one episode on whose turtle this is yeah, that's the way it's the first
picture. That's him
the first picture of the yeah. He's a turtle where they put a bunch of
hamburger ingredients
do dubious sent me the most fucked up picture of a hamburger
last night. He was eating with the burger. Yeah, he sent me the most
picked up picture out of burger. He said he was on to go look at that. He sent me
that to what kind of
a plastic for show the show the GoPro in his house.
In what world is this a hamburger? I'm sorry. I came to America. I started
complaining about every single food saying this is not a tent to go enough,
but that is not a tent to go. That does not look like an American burger.
There's nothing like a burger. I'm sorry. I'm not even looking up whose turtle
so funny, not even who's a turtle from we need to pop so hugely that then we do a
an entourage style produce a movie about or a show about our what is
entourage
based on mark. It's a reality show. No, no, no, it's a it's like a script. I
mean, it's a it's like a show. It's a show. It's a show. Show. It's a drama
show about it's a it's it's it's hooking up with Sasha Gray. Pretty funny.
She's in that. I don't know. I've only seen the first episode.
That was her big acting role.
That was the one when she made the jump over and now she is a Twitch streamer.
What a fucking loser. Just, I mean, just stick, just like,
I don't get that shit.
Just you do porn for like four months and just make enough money that you never
have to do. You don't make any money doing that though.
You don't think so. You get paid in pleasure.
You get paid in pleasure. Trust me. They did not pay me enough.
You wouldn't do porn. I did and
you can't tell it's me because I'm in a suit. I couldn't do porn man.
My penis is too small. I could do it, but I don't want to. I'm inflated.
I'm inflated. I could see you pulling up in the porn movie.
No, yeah, but you'd be the dead there. To be honest, you'd be the wimp that
they kick out. It's a little cringe. You'd be the makeup artist. I would
the makeup artist they fuck. Yeah, that would be you. Yeah, as a part of it. Do
they have like PAs and shit? Yeah, it's a full industry. Yeah, it's a whole, this
world is a whole ass thing. The whole thing is pretty crazy. I mean, they used
to, if I'm going by Boogie Nights rules, they used to have a whole thing. That's
true. Porn has really fallen off since Boogie Nights time. They don't really do
porn anymore, do they? They don't do it the same way. It's downscaled a lot.
They're not shooting it on a 1x, 3x, 8x or whatever CinemaScope.
They're not shooting it on IMAX.
I wish I was looking at you through a scope right now.
WakandaScope. I hope it's binoculars.
You say WakandaScope?
WakandaScope.
I guess probably a WakandaScope, yeah.
Some kind of laser beam shooting directly at your head.
You wouldn't do that.
I would.
Do they have laser beams in Wakanda?
You gotta assume.
Yeah.
Why would you assume they wouldn't?
because they mostly have little claws. What they are made out of I think
you're thinking of Black Panther.
Am I thinking of just one guy? They all have like his name is it what kind of
right? No, no, no, his name's not what kind of you racist,
then what was the movie about the movie is about the basically this it's like
isn't it? I don't know. It's like a town. Isn't it crazy? I got a job. Yeah,
they got a worm in an after the Black Panther, the second Black Panther movie
when Chadwick Boseman died and they're like we're going to do this movie in his
memory. This is dedicated to him and it's about Africa versus Mexico.
It was a cause very close to his heart.
Underwater
and try to destroy Africa.
Yeah, that is
yeah. If I was him, if I was trying to honor Chadwick Boseman, I would have
even his family, the budget for the movie, a hundred million dollars,
giving him that then fucking then make the most movies ever not made a fucking
sequel to Black Panther. I actually didn't even see it. I didn't see it
either. I just saw the trailer. I like the first one man. The first one was
cool. It's fun. I like when he jumps around. The ending was terrible.
Jumping the jumping is impressive. Yeah,
the jumping is a my God. I love that movie. The jumping and the stunts, the
stunts on the singing. Do they ever explain whether or not sharing all this
technology with the world? I think that gets solved in the end. Yeah, maybe I
don't know. I don't remember. They should have just put what kind of should
be a planet so that you don't have to answer that question. Yeah,
yeah, yeah, because there's I mean there's a lot of things. There's a lot
of things that take place at the early. I mean listen. I okay, I get it.
You don't want to share with us white people at least share it with the rest
of Africa. Yeah, exactly. Africa's in such bad sorts, bro, and you're
at least spreading it around the continent a little bit.
I'm not even saying I need to have all that shit. I don't need a flying thing.
Well, does any of that shit exist in that world? Does any of it exist in real
life? Does any of that shit exist in that world, like apartheid or the
Holocaust or anything that they could have stopped with their vibrate back
steely superhero? Well, yeah, because Magneto's a Holocaust survivor. Well,
I guess he's not part of it yet, is he? Did superheroes in some multiverse...
Is Marvel and DC and shit, where superheroes, have they always been around or was it just
like I think they've always been around?
I think it's in the 40s and onward.
I think that it just depends on, I think that there's no like overarching canon to any of
that stuff.
Because when does Superman come into play?
When is he his first kind of thing?
Well he's a little kid for a long time.
In the 40s, yeah.
So he should be the one.
That's the funny, they all started in the 40s because it's when they came up with all
the ideas.
I Need a Hero.
I need a hero, but they all were punching Hitler on the comic books and stuff
that's true. There is one. If you look at his burn, he burns those you burn
those I burn what
it off
a slide show of all the
the yeah. If you look on like every single like one of those like Superman
wiki, the flash wiki, any of those and you look up Hitler, there is always a
page yeah in the
There's always a...
Well, I mean, it's just a fact that there's always the coolest guy you can be fighting
as a Nazi.
They don't have the Punisher fighting him, though.
They're the best, most evilest.
They don't have the Punisher fighting Hitler, but I guess that makes sense because he came
out and said, well, I don't know, maybe they could do a what if.
I bet you $100 that the Punisher fought Nazis.
He fought Nazis, but the neo kind.
Yeah.
Maybe.
So I'm saying they all did.
Yeah.
All of them fought them.
I'm talking about the first ones.
talking about Hitler and that's gonna be so sad to be a Nazi. Yeah, that's gotta
be so fucking sad. Yeah, no representation whatsoever, because
you're you're also a dork.
You saying you get bullied by the other Nazis? Yeah. Oh, I see. Yeah, it's like
kind of like you're on the at the bottom of the barrel on both sides. Yeah,
you're right. Yeah, because you're not and I mean you're you gotta be the only
Nazi comic book nerd. I'm starting to feel bad for these guys. Honestly, I mean
It's just like, yeah, it's kind of sad.
It's very sad. His whole life is sad.
He should kill himself.
No, no, no, no, no.
If I was in that position, I wouldn't kill myself.
We don't want anyone to kill themselves.
What?
No, no, no.
Okay.
No, no, no, fuck no.
That's disgusting.
All right, all right.
I'm sorry that I brought up suicide.
He has a whole family.
What?
Yeah.
I know people who have committed suicide
and you're saying stuff like that to me.
Who?
Kurt Cobain.
That's disputed.
Who else? Oh, Anton Yeltsin.
Yeah.
Steve Jobs. Steve Jobs committed suicide.
In a way he kind of did.
He definitely did. He completely gave up.
He invented a computer. He knew about medicine.
He didn't even invent it, man.
Steve Jobs would a huckster. He was a huckster. He's a snake oil salesman.
Absolutely. You think computers don't even work would like he would be he
would have literally been Merlin the wizard back in English times
back in the English
do you guys ever
think that maybe you have the possibility of being a Steve Jobs style
change of the world kind of guy. I think I could get there. What do you think
would be what would be your your Avenue me? Yeah, I was not this. It could be
is
we could come up with an invention that actually that some scientist thinks yeah I guess probably
funny to make it and then he makes it and then he's like oh probably either like an
inventor or a dancer or a singer or novelist or an artist like painter type artist or an
artist with words not artist in a way for a no space graphic novelist or like a chef
or a construction worker there's no construction worker that has ever changed the world not
true no no no my friend Eiffel Tower Empire State Building Stonehenge I'm
thinking of a different that did change the world yep whoever invented Eiffel
towering that shit changed the world whoever thought up of that yeah not even
I mean I guess the name - yeah but what did they call it before that shit ring
around the Rosie the tower of gardens
Let's hanging gardens of Babylon this girl. Yeah, you know, it doesn't have a
Colossus of Rome. Does not have that good of a ring to it. Yeah, yeah, great wall.
Yeah, it's a great when a woman gets a great wall. That's when it's
like the like the 500 person gangbang. Yeah, how's that great line up? Because
they all lined up. Oh my does she I thought that they were the ones moving.
She's the one well, she doesn't she just time there on the great wall. That's why
That's the thing that would suck about doing the 500 person gangbang is just waiting in
line dude.
Yeah.
You should be able to fast pass.
They should have a guy going up and down the line selling food and concessions.
We need to break a world record.
We need to break a world record very soon.
We've maybe talked about this before.
What could we do?
We've definitely talked about breaking world records.
Any man worth his salt has done that.
has talked about it at the very least considered it.
But there, I mean we had this conversation.
Can we do longest podcast?
Can we podcast for two days?
We had a great plan that I wanted to do that just never shook out.
Oh yeah, that one.
But I think we can still do it.
We can definitely still do it.
We're going to do it.
Yeah, we have to.
We'll do it for some milestone.
But look up world's longest podcast.
I want to see what the record is.
It's probably held by Rogan or something.
Four hours?
You think that's the world's longest podcast?
Yeah.
for a fact they got longer ones because I listened to them before Mike Russell
thirty six hours. God fucking now that's hard. That's no that's easy to beat
yeah
fuck we'd have to hire. I think you'd have to pay like ten thousand dollars to
get the Guinness person to come yeah. Ten thousand something like that. That'd
be funny to pay the Guinness person to come and then just immediately. So
thirty six is so so beautiful. That is hard. Well, what's the exact time?
you can beat it by it was like if it was like forty eight hours and we had to go
past forty eight hours, I would be like no, I don't want to do that, but thirty
six hours is completely doable, but it's a day and a half yeah and you have to
what you have to you just have to go past that you do thirty seven, but it
doesn't matter over a hundred and fifty hours.
That's the longest, that's a lot of hours in one minute, fuck yeah, I'm not
doing that shit. You say fifty hours in one row. I literally and I do not want
you break a record. Why because you don't have four to somebody going to break my
record, the fame change you if you so I'd fame would change me. Somebody would
break my record. Is it audio only live stream? That's bullshit that that is not
at all. No, we're saying podcast. We're saying iTunes. It's in the feed. Rss
it's a full yeah. That's what always made me laugh about somebody opening it and
being it's a forty hour. It takes up all the storage on your phone, your phone
auto down. Yeah, it just check yeah. No, I think that's a good idea. I think it's
a really I think we can do that. We can also break some kind of food record,
probably not even eating probably some kind of we make the making make the
biggest make the tastiest
the world's tastiest make the world's the world's most unhealthiest salad. Okay,
oh that's good. So what would it be
poison nine? Yeah, no, it can't be point. It needs to be something that
somebody can take on health iceberg, lettuce and strict. That's it. That's
the only two ingredients. Oh my God, the world's least amount of ingredients in a
salad. I could be like the I could do the world's least interested in eating a
chocolate bar and I could just sit at the chocolate bar and not eat it. How
long do you have to sit? What's the right? It's not about how long somebody's
about how disinterested, how long is the way you measure that is how long is
somebody sat across the table from a chocolate bar and not touched it? Yeah,
I think I could break that record longest, but nails, but it is we need
to make that also Guinness. We would like to set the record for longest
sitting near a chocolate bar and not even thinking, but also yeah, you can't
also it has you have to be most disinterested. So you can't even be
like you can't even be like
thinking about it. You can't even it can't even register. So we oh that'll
be once we get the Neuralink technology, there will be a whole new
brand of world records. Yeah, 20 easy world records to break. Maybe I could
just try and break tallest guy. Yeah, there's no way. What do you 63 that?
Yeah, I could see there's no way you're not even in the top 100. I might as well
just submit to the record, but you won't get it. There's taller people everywhere,
but I might get it. Well, how you think you're gonna be if they've tried to get
the record or not? What if everybody is a little taller means like, oh, there's
probably a taller Robert Wadlow something. What's that guy? I think
that's what's his name is living guy. There's like a there's like an eight
foot guy and fucking yeah, but maybe he never called the Guinness Book of World
Records. He's famous. So he obviously was he saw it was they took a picture of
him. You don't know that I was that guy that the guy from Big Fish. Maybe I
The big guy like, oh I don't know. You don't remember that guy?
You're talking about the guy who played Jaws? No. The shark? No the guy in big the
Big Fish by Tim Burton. I never watched that movie. I never seen that. With Ewan McGregor.
Never seen it still. Oh. It's about a dad who's a liar. Oh. Yeah. You say it's a
you say it's a horror movie? No, it's just like a normal movie, but this guy
was in a lot of stuff. Oh, he's not even that tall. Seven to seven. There's
taller people in the NBA. Yeah, yeah. The number one pick. Maybe I can get
shortest guy. There's your why? Why is he having a conversation for sure? Oh,
oh, I was like, damn, why does he have an LAPD article? I was like, I was
because he was found dead. Oh, no. So so that's what I'm saying. Oh, you might
he has the largest feet. He had twenty nine and a half. I have bigger feet
than that hit twenty nine and a half feet yeah
shoes. Oh
that's not any height. That's a size where that's not even a size yeah.
Yeah, that's they don't. That's not a real. So they don't make. Why are you
even? Why are you even asking for the size right? Yeah, it's not like you're
getting you're getting your shoes custom. Yeah, now you don't go to the
store and say I'm twenty. I call a hundred thousand size a hundred. You
let's say I yeah. I have special feet yeah, just make them. They don't need to
be sized. They're not there's no stamping the vans on
size on the soul. They might not for this guy. No, I might they might step his
name big, big guy and you know he's not wearing vans either. Yeah, he's an
actor. He definitely has some kind of
orthopedic insole. He has to wear his knees are definitely over porinated.
What?
Pronated.
Over pronated.
Oh, okay.
Does that mean they're like this?
I think pronated is when your ankle bleeds out.
Oh, that hurts.
That has to hurt.
That would hurt so badly.
I actually don't know if it's out or in, but yeah, it's when you...
Well, I know about it from feet.
I don't know about knees.
He knows a lot about feet.
That's what he's telling us.
I don't think he does.
I just know about my own feet.
Tell me your feet facts.
What size shoe do you wear?
12 and a half.
11 and a half. I think I'm like 12. These are in 11 and a half. Mine are yeah. Okay. These
are 11 and a half, which means the last shoes I bought were made in Vietnam sample, not
for people. Oh, I thought it was people. I was like, get that shoe off your foot right
now. What are you doing? I thought you were trying it on. I don't want. Why would I try
I got your shoe on. I looked at the size of my shoe and said 11. I thought we were trying
them on. I thought that we were showing off that we all had the same shoe size. Mine are
some fucked up French size. So they say they're 38 or something. I have a bigger shoe. Does
it say 43? I don't know. What are you guessing? 48? I don't know. I'm telling you. 33? 43.
forty forty three. Whoa! Oh my God, you're smart. No, he's not. We are the
same shoe size and you wear a forty three in this. Let me see.
How did you know that?
Okay, so
he's putting the shoe on. You look like a girl. I feel like Cinderella.
Give me my shoe, bro.
You want to try mine on? No, dude. We're not. That's the worst radio of all
sometimes trying to their shoes on it's horrible. No, we need a topic to talk
about okay. Say something
fuck oh, I feel like I had something. Oh America's secret weapon against hearing
losses here, and you guys know that
I think it's not screaming.
I've been getting more and more and more of the alert from my phone that says the
volume needs to be turned down. You listen to your volume too loud. I did. I
I don't think I do. I don't think I do at all. Why we mean why I don't think I
don't think it's loud at whatsoever. I think that my headphones are quiet and
my and my computer for a long time. No hours, hours and hours and hours on end
on end. I never stop. I always have my always. I play speakers out instead. I
don't do my phone speaker. I find that to be annoying. I will. I don't I do it.
I'm usually alone even then. I think what if the name I don't also have an
embarrassing taste in music. I don't want people to hear this. Me too. I probably have
more embarrassing taste in music than you. I use my phone speaker. I use the sound bar
that Noah got. For some reason, I think using a speaker, a Bluetooth speaker, I think it
makes you a bad person. That's crazy. Wait, what do you, you listen out of your phone?
That's weird. That is weird. That is really weird. That is very weird. That's what I put
out of my pocket and I walk around to put it on. That's extremely weird.
You're muffling it. You're muffling the sound. No, I'm not muffling it 'cause I
put the speaker coming out of my pocket. That is still on. That means that you
have to wear at least chinos or some kind of slacks that have the side pocket.
If you wear, like, jeans, that's gonna muffle the shit. I don't wear jeans.
Okay. I didn't know you were, I didn't know you had it like that.
I didn't know you were wearing jeans. I usually wear shorts in my house anyway.
Damn. Damn. Damn. You got that warm house. I usually just actually don't wear pants in
my house. Yeah. Don't tell me this shit. We already talked about that. Don't fucking tell
me that though. That's true. No, he's told us about this. He walks around this house
half naked. You were the one who said it more than me. You go pooh bear in your house. You
like it even more. I made it all up. How about that? I lied. I don't lie. I made everything
up. That's why we call him Cameron Lincoln. Because he don't lie? Because he's incapable
Google of lying. I'm on his cherry tree. That was George Washington. Did he also
not lies at the story? He said I cannot. He's just said I cannot tell, but then he
probably did later on. It wasn't his overall quality. It was one thing he
did. So you can't be a war general and not lie right, because what if they call
you capture you and then yeah, they send you a carrier pigeon that says are you
guys going to attack us tonight? Yes, we're actually going to attack you at
eight o'clock shit, but that's noble. That is noble, but that's better. That's
better than this type of fucked up backstabbing, betraying type of war we
have nowadays. True. Where everything is on social media and so everyone is
doing it. All the soldiers are posting plans for attention. I kind of can't
believe that people used to fight wars by walking in a line at each other. I
just don't believe it. I don't believe the paintings. That just can't be true.
It has to all look like... There used to be chivalry. Yeah. It used to be. That
What was that movie, The Patriot, with Mel Gibson, where they're all walking in a fucking
line?
I don't fucking know.
I don't know either.
Had to watch that in school as a kid.
They used to, it used to be knights who would just run at each other on their horses.
And then so they thought, well...
You gotta do that with guns now.
Yeah, well we don't use horses anymore, because you can't aim a gun on a horse.
That's crazy to think that they were like, even both sides were like, we need this to,
I mean it has to at least be fair.
Like, no, you have to decimate them completely.
completely. No, it needs to be fair. I don't think it come. I think they need to
I think that the next step in warfare is we take all the drones and the planes
and we fly them in a line at each other. I said this forever that war should be
two robots fighting each other and you just sign a contract. This is whoever
yeah, whoever wins yeah, not we should be champion. You choose your champion
like a fantasy movie that literally nobody should be dying in war. We're so
past that it should be two planes flying at each other. The one that also saves
so much money, you just make one really good plane. Exactly. The instead of a
bunch of them, it can be so quick. Yeah. And whoever, obviously the bigger, just
like right now, the bigger countries have the bigger, better armies. The US is
gonna have the most tricked out fucking robot. Yeah, turned invisible. And that's
it. We need electrical robots. We need zords. Zords. We need zords. We need
huge. Yeah, zoids. Oh, zoids. Zoids. Zoids. Zoids. Zoids are power rangers. Yeah.
Yeah. No, we need zoids. We need zoids more than zords. We need robot bears and
have to run at each other and swipe each other. Oh my God, that would be so cool.
Have you guys ever seen that movie Robot Jocks? No, no, it sounds really funny.
That sounds like a death punk. They'd fight with big robots at each other. In
the entire war? I think it's a war. I can't really remember, but it's all
stop motion robots. Whoa, that's what I want to see. I want to see less people
passing away in foreign countries. And I want to see robots. I want to have the
a folded flag, the body, but a factory don't don't be crying for a slur when
your decision about war actually makes a I even angrier yeah. Why would it be
angry because AI and robots are the ones perishing, but I don't give a shit
about them. I'm saying don't come crying to me. Did you start giving a you guys
see the the footage is another video I saw of the
police officer responding to the UFO call where the people said that a UFO
in their backyard. I think my mom said it was two eight foot aliens walking around their
backyard. Yeah, I didn't see it's over. I don't think that's real. It's over. I think
that's all AI. I think that's an AI video that's being no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
AI to that's bullshit. I think that the aliens are AI and I think that it was all CG. It's
over where they've already won. I don't think that aliens an alien if an alien came here.
I think that we would have the wherewithal to beat the crap out of it with like by like
showing it different kinds of sodas and like showing it like that would beat the crap out
of it. I don't think an alien could ingest Diet Coke. I don't think an alien could ingest
think it would drink it. I think of an alien drink diet. Dr. Pepper is
something one of the chemicals in it would have a negative reaction. But you
think the alien would drink it when it got here? Yes, we would say we would
hand a diet. Dr. Pepper to the alien. We'd say, Hey, I think this is what we
drink every day. Only explanation for why we see so few aliens is that there
is probably only like 25 of them. Yeah. And they're from a very small, little,
big planet style planet. It's like Hawaii. Yeah. They're from like a Mario
Galaxy planet. And then they just come here. It's Delfino Plaza. Yeah. Yeah.
It's the guys from that. What are they called? I think they're called Delfinos.
Well, I jump on their head no matter what they're called. And they go...
Yeah. But basically, I think that the only explanation is only like 25. And
and they're not bringing it. They're not smart. They're not hitting us with any
kind of artillery. They know that yeah. Oh, no, they're eight feet tall, man.
They could live. We were just talking. You were like there's a hundred guys who
are eight feet tall. Yeah, you literally just said that earlier, but they look
do you think some people have gray alien DNA? I will say really tall people do
look bad. They look fucked up and not. There's people who here on earth who are
not human. 100%. Let's just go out, let's list them. I don't know them, but you see them
sometimes. You know one of them maybe. I don't think I know any of them. You don't know if
you know is the problem. That is the problem. Because a lot of them have used gene therapy
and they look a little more similar. They're doing gene therapy, they're wearing jeans
so you don't think they're a fucking alien.
- Exactly.
- Retail therapy.
- Yeah, you think what alien would be wearing this outfit?
- What are those, 501s?
- Anya Taylor-Joy.
- She's just ugly.
She's not an alien.
- That's what she wants you to think.
She wants you to think she's ugly.
- I think she's ugly.
- But in actuality, she's not.
- I watched this new HBO show, I watched the first episode.
- The Idol?
- I was mostly doing the crossword, but I had it on--
- The Idol, that one?
- Yeah.
the one with um, Lily Rose Depp. This show is pornography and it needs to be, it needs to
get out of here. That's the new Euphoria. It's by the same guy. It's worse than pornography.
It's the weekend and he's fingering her and stuff on the show. Weekend fingers, everybody's
fingering there's nipples abound. Oh my god there's too much fingering on the show. I
don't like it at all man. It really is just not, it should not be on TV. I saw a clip
and she is one of the worst actresses I think I've ever seen.
She's only around 'cause of Nep,
like literally, it's stupid to complain about it,
but genuinely, I think she's only around
because her dad is Jack Sparrow.
- I, yeah.
(dramatic music)
I agree, and I think if she wasn't around,
I think you'd be the star of that show.
- I would definitely be the star of that show.
Are you kidding me?
- I think The Weeknd--
- Oh my, wait, watch this, watch this.
The weekend would be braiding your hair. Watch this.
This is not that's the kind of faces she makes in the show. What's the type of
face? Describe it. It's a teeth out, teeth out, smile, smile like this.
That is not to that smile. I watch the show. She doesn't make that face and
she blew and she she winks her eyelashes at the weekend and it goes like don't
you guys think it's kind of fucked up and scary that when an actor is walking
around in his daily life or her daily life. They could, they literally have
been trained to do whatever and act like whatever person. So it's like we don't
know if they're acting right now, if they even need to be shopping.
Man, you just, you just, I mean, you see them at a red carpet and they're
flashing a smile, teeth out, and then you think, well hold on, I saw them do teeth
out smile on that one movie. Yeah. Are they even happy? Are they even enjoying
enjoying them. They are not enjoying it. At most actors, I think all the time,
what if you were married to an actor? Most actors do not enjoy their life.
They were crying. They go, "Shut the fuck up! I know you're fucking faking.
I saw you cry." You're researching a role. That was a Curb Your Enthusiasm
episode. You're researching a role. Exactly. So that's why you didn't do the
dishes. Well, that was actually, she was a paid crier. She was a paid crier.
That's even worse. That's even worse. I think that's the future of acting,
is we're not gonna, we're gonna specialize further. We're gonna have actors
you. It's not like one person who can act and play whatever role it's like yeah.
This is a laugher. This is a smiler. This is a sad actor and then when they
happy, when they cross over, they can get really, really good at it, so they
don't because like nowadays actors are bad because it's like well. I have to
learn to smile. I have to learn to act crazy. You don't know everything. I
have to learn how to make everything suffers. If you have to absolutely have
to learn how to make my smile into a frown exactly the transitions between
them, it's a lot of muscles, but a guy who just smiles and he's ten thousand
as as as hours of smiling yeah, ten thousand, how do you train for
something ten thousand hours, but then also the smiling guy moves over to
crying. It'll be like Adam Sandler doing a dramatic role, right, but that would
never have holy fucking shit. I would not let that happen. Yeah, true that
when this deal gets finished,
smilers will never cry. We need to get rid of every union on this planet. Oh
yeah, they ruined fucking everything. They ruined smiler, the smilers union
because you're right, every single thing would have a specialized union and
then all asked to be paid a million dollars a fucking minute. Yeah, I'm
fucking smiling.
You can't say anything sad when you're on the down union, the standing up. Yeah,
every oh my God, the smilers union. I'm imagining maybe this is the future of
movies where a character can be a group of actors and may and a character is
five people and they walk around together. There's one guy who sits down
when the character sits down. There's one guy who smiles when the character's
happy. More of the same crowds. More of the same crowds when the character is sad. I can't
tell people apart. I'm not going to notice. Yeah, but no, it's not that they're switching
them out. It's that they're always together and the group of them as one is the character.
Oh, well, we're probably headed that way with people too because people are going to do
monkey see, monkey do. They're smiling Steve, crying Steve. Yeah, well, it's just like they're
different. It's like Inside Out, but in real life. Yeah, the real life of a movie. Outside
inside. There's going to be Smilers East and Vomit. That's a bad union to be in.
Vomiters Union. But you know, that way a smiler will never have to vomit in a movie again.
That's true. That's the people who always want to be, I mean, Lord knows there are people who
like that type of thing. Can you imagine? I don't even want to bring it up, but the people who like
vomiting, that's all they have to do. Imagine having to pay your dues to the Vomiters Union.
I mean it probably just be like every other one hundred pukes a month. I
don't think you would pay in puke. I think you just probably pay money.
You would pay you. Why would you pay a puke and you're not in this word
envisioning a new world here. We don't have to be bound by the restrictions
that bind us right. We had a good idea and you guys are turning it into a
fucking bullshit. Okay, fuck a thought. It's not a bullshit fuck a thon to
think that come on.
A porn actor and a normal actor would almost never cross paths, so that's so
but basically it's already our idea is already true. You can make it you can
make their sexual actors and non sexual actors already can make the jump like
the lady from the never jump. They jump all the time. There was a jumper in
you in euphoria. There was a jumper in
I don't think Hayden Christiansen was a porn actor. I don't think he will. He
did a lot of CGI porn. What do you see? Oh, I think you're just talking about
jumping. No. Oh, well, that would be another. Yeah, that would be another
about a jumper's. There you go. Jumpers, jumpers. I didn't. I didn't realize that
the conversation was about jumping from. I've seen so many amazing videos this
week. I also saw the video of Tom Cruise doing his jump. Did you watch this? No,
yes, I've got to say it was so awesome. I see that video every few months. I
always watch it. It's one on one. Y'all you pull out that video. Did you see?
Did you see? Don't watch the video. Did you see that very long mission
impossible dead reckoning part one will only have one week in IMAX before it is
pushed out by Christopher Nolan's Oppenheimer, who gives a F about
Oppenheimer. Nobody even knows who that was, bro mission impossible at least
three weeks in IMAX, if not more. Here's the thing, Christopher Nolan,
IMAX more than Oppenheimer needs IMAX Nolan right now.
I need you. I need you to stop it. I need you to stop what you're
doing. Stop making this movie about nuclear war.
Okay, clear bore nuclear bore is what I'm calling it black and white black and
white and then
hey, hey, Christopher Nolan, you know who did that first Pleasantville, Toby
McGuire, Spider-Man, think about it. I don't think you're copying Spider-Man
and Wizard of Oz and any other movie that's gone from black and white. Well,
Wizard of Oz was sepia. So that's different. Shut the fuck up. That's a
sepia movie tour with color movie. I'm going to make you sepia. You're not
going to be or yeah, I'll make you sip you on some says are sip. I'm gonna get
you. I
sip your sperm sip your sperm on my sip your sperm. Your sperm up set my
I don't think I've ever heard that song. You've heard you've heard probably not
like my bitch. I don't think I have either. I've definitely I know these
I have it in my head. I've listened to it in my head hundreds of times.
I've never seen Charlie's Angels.
You've seen Charlie's Angels.
I used to love that movie.
Yeah, it's the fight scene between Crispin Glover and Lucy Liu. They play that song.
Tom Green is in that?
Mm-hmm.
And he falls in a tube.
See, that guy should not, in my vision of Hollywood, that guy would never be in an action
movie.
100%.
Tom Green?
Yeah.
He's in an action movie.
I don't like when comedians cross over and do any kind of...
my vision of Hollywood. What are you not understanding?
Freddie got fingered was an action movie. He did a lot of action.
Shut up. Shut up.
Well he does skateboarding. He did actions of violence towards his father.
There would be no skateboarding in any movies.
No, no, no. That would be strictly for YouTube videos.
And chimpanzees. And chimpanzees who go on a mini ramp.
And bulldogs also. Bulldogs and chimpanzees.
Viral. That would be only for viral Hollywood.
Hollywood. Yeah, they're making a new sector of Hollywood called viral wood to
try it because a lot of these viral videos nowadays are not as good as the
ones we used to have. So I'd like to maybe section off and divide get some of
these producers, directors, actors, get them out of movies, out of the movie
industry and just working on getting better viral videos. We get to see and
also there should be a union for us who like to make viral videos. Yeah, yeah. We
we get Newman, a guy we get Tays on day we, well, it would be like a
dramatic of the Union. Yeah, a monk has died many years ago.
You have to say it that meanly
years and years ago, they're like way before you saw the video.
That's a death.
You're saying it so flippantly
I'm so I don't that's a horrible. I mean, I guess you're right.
he's just finding this out right now and you said it like that
yeah. I mean there's nothing to be done for him. He's he's done and dusted he's
in the dirt.
Yeah,
he's gone man since when since probably one or something. I don't even know how
old that video is. It's older than the Internet, though,
what's that that dramatic chipmunk has passed. It says probably
and that's probably our thought and that was so that you're fine. That means he's
okay. A chipmunk doesn't live very well. I would guess it's not a chipmunk. It
wasn't even a chipmunk. He was a prairie dog. Dear God. Well, I got prairie dog
probably lives even less time than a chipmunk. No, it lives more.
I think he's still alive. I think there's a good chance he's still alive.
There's no chance. If there's one prairie dog in the world who's been alive,
it might be him because he has a reason to be preserved.
he's dead. He's not it says two thousand and also I hate to ruin this for you
guys. He wasn't even being dramatic. He probably just saw some food.
What he was not trying to be dramatic at he doesn't know what drama means. I
thought he was being funny. He doesn't know what being funny is. He's an
animal. He doesn't know what being funny is. He has no idea what that is to be
funny.
Well, you know people I just don't understand
and by the way, if you have a dog and it licks your face, it just wants to it
means you have a fucking salty face.
If you were wondering and if you have a cat that
sucks on your finger, I never had a cat.
It means you finger, you know, funny finger, your finger tastes, yeah, I don't
know. I don't know what it means. I'm not a veterinarian. Yeah. Yeah, you are a
veterinarian. I couldn't be a veterinarian. You have to kill, you have
to kill too many animals. You have to kill every single animal. It's so funny that
being a veterinarian, your entire job is just chop them all up. Even when you're
not killing them, when you save them, it's that you have to cut them apart.
Yeah, take their legs off and then you put them in that thing. It's always
someone who's like, "I love animals, I wanna be a veterinarian." You torture
animals all day. You go and be like the apprentice or whatever it's called.
Yeah, you're doing experiments on animals. You're like an intern or whatever.
I think at that point you just have to... That's literally what it is.
Yeah, I mean, I've told you that I had a friend who wanted to be...
Who became a veterinary assistant, first day killing dogs, second day killing
today like back in the 1800s or I mean honestly the 1950s like a veterinarian when they like
like they brought somebody brings their dog in and the dog dies they like like well you
know I don't might as well make it into lunch. No because you don't think they ate dogs in
the 1950s. You don't think you don't think that they dies of natural cause. You don't
think that they picked it up and just like threw it on a grill and the 1950s yeah. What
What do you think will the 1950s had refrigerators?
1950s was a backwards ass time, bro.
Not for animals.
It was actually better for animals.
It was in a factory farming.
Well, not in factory animals.
They didn't invent leashes much yet.
People were walking.
Really?
Dogs had their own houses and lives.
That's true.
They just go in.
There weren't really dogs in the cities.
Well, they'd run around.
That's what my dad always says.
That's one of the things he says.
you ever hang out with my dad, I'll say it at least one time, which is he says, you know,
dogs just used to roam around. They weren't fenced in or on leashes or anything. They just
go all over the place.
It's probably for the best.
He's just lying.
He's not lying.
I mean, back when, not when he was a kid, not in the 70s and 80s.
Yeah.
Nobody was...
In the 60s and 70s, yeah.
Your dad's that old?
Yeah.
Yeah, that was probably...
Whoa.
That was probably because he lived in like a small-ass neighborhood.
He lived in Cambridge.
Oh my God, that was not a small ass neighborhood.
Oh my God, it was actually a big ass neighborhood.
Oh my God, that was actually one of the biggest developing neighborhoods at that time.
They said kids would just get chased by dogs and you'd know which dogs lived where,
so at certain times of day you wouldn't walk by a certain house.
I don't believe it until I see it on a fucking cave wall.
You see it on TV shows.
Fuck you, I do.
That's always in a movie, a kid gets chased by a dog.
Yeah, they would show that in like Malcolm in the Middle and shit,
and it was like, oh, is that because he lives in a crazy neighborhood?
you know that's how you say
I say you know that's what it was like that back then here. It's like that
right now in India, so you know and in Mexico yeah, there are many places are
having a war in India between monkeys and dogs. There's dogs everywhere in
Mexico. I went and I saw you're tripping maybe not in your little you remember
that I guess you live you because you live you're gentrifying Mexico. You are
you live in a fancy neighborhood.
oh nothing to say now. Oh,
silence, because he's in the one percent.
He is in the one percent.
Always is. Silence.
But there was a
there was like a war between
yeah, the monkeys are throwing dogs off of towers.
Monkeys are throwing dogs off of towers
and then dogs are biting monkeys.
That sucks. I think all the time
about if my dog had
opposable thumbs and could articulate
fully articulating arms
that he would be doing
way to have a way different life. Yeah, if he had his brain in a monkey's body,
you're lucky you can't jump up on the can even if a ball goes on
table, he can't eat barks at it, because I have to come get it, because he can't
he can't do anything. If I had a dog and he learned to speak
and I would have to kill him instantly, I would be teaching because imagine you
come home to your dog and you open the door and he runs up and he goes. I love
you
where he walks in and you're whacking off. I love you. What are you doing in
there? What are you doing in there? That's all he knows. He would only say I
love you.
You're trying to
you would walk up to and you're you're jacking off and you'd say I love living
here.
I like my food shut up dog. My dog could speak. I'd be teaching it like if these
dogs could talk. If I'd be teaching him any young men joke, so we go on tour.
Yeah, he'd be I'd be given. I'd be holding him. I'd be holding him like
on stage and it'd be like, huh, like a little vintroquist that'd make him say, "Take my bone,
please."
Take my bone, please.
Take my leash, please.
I don't need that.
I think if my dog could talk, I'd fall in love with him.
Yeah.
I think I would get, you know.
You would immediately...
No, I think it would be...
I like my dog too much.
I can't...
Go to try and suck it off.
No, it wouldn't be sexual, but I think I would have an emotion...
I would emotionally cheat on my wife with my dog.
Yeah.
Or no, I wouldn't.
What does that mean?
Emotional cheating?
It's like when there's a girl at work and you go like I'm thinking of fucking you.
They're not fucking, but I would be like I am in love with you. I'm so is that and more in a way
that was different from it being a child. You'll be doing it romantically. It's hairy.
You got hair. That's what makes you. What if you like what if like your dog learned to speak
right and you're sitting there one day, you're just watching the news or
whatever and he walks up to you and he's like by the way. My name is not
Phil. Yeah, he would say that my name is not the first thing you would say. My
name is no, you know, you would say he would be like
I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you this whole time. My name is
my name is yeah. He would say my name cannot be pronounced in your language.
Yeah, it sounds like this. Yeah, I would be like whoa, I'm an M, M, M, you
name him? I would never tell you what his original name was when I got him. His
entire litter was named after the Encanto. Yeah. Oh, yeah. This was
Augustine. Yeah, that's cool. It's not cool. I'm so glad. What's the other
in contact? I don't know. That seems like maybe a good one. I mean, I haven't
either. I'll just into a dog. But what were the other dogs names? You must know
at least one or two of them. They all got changed. One of them's name is
flippy. But I just wanted to know, like, ruggy or some shit. Ruggy. I don't
way I can tell you I'm going to group chat with all the pretty close. I was
curious what if that's a good on conto name or a bad one, I guess, but I don't
think that I guess that doesn't matter and some of the group chat is called in
conto family.
There's Charlie. These are not the original names. These are what they got
changed. Yeah, these are these are new ones. There's Charlie. There's now now
there's Bruno Bruno Bruno Bruno stayed the same. There's Dugan. I think that
one is actually original Dugan Dugan Nash.
let's see Mel Dugan, Phil Rudy, this is the only people who are active. I
never post in this shit do that. Damn, can you send a pic right now? Tracy
send a picture? What if we have a play date? Can you say why? What do you
mean you play date? You do you think people would think it was weird to see
a picture of me? Yes, they're going to think wait. What if you put on a
picture? You say Phil is having an amazing day. Put the dog filter on
they sorry, no send a picture,
well, even just say something like he's taking care of Phil today, so excited
okay,
got this guy taking care of bill today. He's so excited.
My brother, I say my brother is
here of bill today.
He's so excited. These these pups are a blessing.
it.
These pups
are a blessing. That's just a heart emoji
and I was thinking
to this bro. I was thinking there's twenty people in this. There's no
way nobody's going to respond. Oh my God, somebody's somebody's going to
heart react it. Yeah, hopefully I'm going to leave it. Let's see someone's
not going to
two minutes. I said this
wait. They named it Charlie like Charlie XCX. I mean just no e. Oh my God, one
minute in no likes, no response. It's one minute. It's a face. People take
to
it was Facebook. No, it's text messages. Damn, I have all these people's number.
It's completely over. You should have put the dog filter on him and said,
look at how big Phil has gotten. Jubio wants me to send this photo. That would
be weird, though.
Phil, take a
go for
Why does he shit like that?
Oh my god.
Dude, he literally, I remember I told you what he looked like.
No fucking responses still dude.
You're making me look like a dickhead.
No, it's not me.
Phil looks like the night stalkers from New Vegas dude.
You wrote the message weird.
It's so funny.
You look weird.
No, you wrote the message weird.
I'm telling you, you should have put a filter on him.
That would have made no fucking sense.
and do it in black and white with like wish him luck or something like that,
then people be like OMG good luck. You should have you should have
you should have put it in black and white or something. You should have put
it in like a crazy. You should have sent the picture of me on all fours.
Now my wife's going to be so mad at me. I'm going to get a call.
Oh, I auto woke my phone, but I thought I got a notification.
I flop in the family group chat man.
I've never fucking flopped in there every fucking time. I send a message
heart react, smile, react, exclamation point. What the fuck you did this to me?
You made him a now I am bro. You should unsend it right. I am a pariah. You
are a fucking pariah bro. How do you unsend something? Don't don't teach him.
I don't know how he has to live with his flop more. You should send it an
invisible. I just delete it. No that just deletes it from your how do I do
it? I can't unsend it bro. You didn't update your phone. I shit yeah
that sucks for you man dude. I am going to get cooked. Just send another one
say jk. He took my phone. That's it's obvious somebody else took the photo.
He took my phone and took a selfie. Both your hands are out.
I'm not doing that man. You're ruining my reputation. My friend took my phone.
I just know the next plate. We have a snap. The next play that we have on just
say that we're going to be sitting there. Phil's going to be playing with
Ruby and or Dugan and Yuki and Charlie and one of the guys is going to be like
so you as your brother, how's your brother doing? How did he fare with Phil
and I'll just go what and he's like your brother. He took care of Phil go. Oh
man, it was amazing. Yeah, he did. Well, that means that would mean that he
remembered yeah and that was it was not a flop putting me in a in a situation
where I have to lie to some of the closest people in my life.
I didn't say that yeah, but you also aren't taking care of Phil. So you made
me lie. I've taken care of Phil before, but you're not today and also I can now
he has to
you. Oh my God, we go get no even cushioned. It was by saying these pups
are a blessing. Why'd you say that I thought that they would come across as
more because it's just kind of that honestly ruined it. That is not ruin it
that did ruined it a little bit. That's a weird thing to say. I just send
another message. Yeah, I say guys, I'm so sorry, I didn't mean to send
guys. I
I'm not doing that. I'm not sending another message. I'm just going to see
if people nobody's going to respond. It's going to be days and somebody's
going to be like
Yuki had an amazing play with a
that's the kind of thing they send in there. They just send when their dogs
to play with another dog pretty here. I'll then why do you care about
loving because I don't want to flop bro charlie did not want to go for a walk
last night and apparently she takes after me and the light was too bright
for her as she was trying to sleep.
So the what okay now I take it back and actually what you said is what you sent
is completely normal yeah do again loves the sprinkler yeah
you completely do it loves a sprinkler, never saw a dog play at a sprinkler
before. Wow, people are fucking morons.
I mean no, they're actually very sweet. They're your best friend, sweet enough
to throw a thumbs up. Yeah,
I think that maybe they think you're being facetious. Oh God, Rudy was
attacked by an off leash dog while out on a walk this past Friday. Oh my God,
could have been worse, but his gums were ripped off his jaw.
Oh, that's how you save it later tonight. So well, well later tonight,
later, so we are reacted Yep, that's right, who did it?
Oh, it was the lady who fostered them all nice. So here's how you save it
text from the wife. Stop
don't pray
fuck
it's over for me. No, no, here's how you save it. Here's how you salvage it
later tonight. Send a picture of yourself crying say OMG. Well, my
brother was watching film
brother died.
Just hands in my head a self timer photo sitting on the bed in my
underwear with my hands in my head.
My fucking brother died.
Phil ate him.
It's can't be.
Phil dragged him into the street.
Phil dragged him for miles by his neck.
All right.
I have to handle.
I need to make some calls.
I have to go.
I can't.
Wait, show the pic.
Show the pic first.
The pic of Cam?
Yeah, we have to get a close up of it.
Oh, and what day did we choose for the shareholder meeting?
Shareholder meeting is June.
This is one. The photo that is ruining my life right now. June 23rd is the
shareholder meeting and as always until the 14th, we will be plugging the
sketch show with
home planet and appears at Campion and it's camping. You may know him all of
us. Station station station station. Go watch that. Go watch it now. All right.
Bye. Motherfuckers. Bye. Bye.
Bye!
[BLANK_AUDIO]