[Music]
Play it?
Yeah, you pipe it in.
[Music]
Point it towards the mic.
What are you doing?
[Music]
He's doing audio and visual.
Oh, I see.
Cut to the Pat cam.
[Music]
This is basically the same experience as watching the video on YouTube now.
Uh-huh.
for people.
Stop before it gets stuck in my fucking head.
It's already stuck in your head, bro.
Yeah, it's too late for you.
What?
It's already stuck in your head.
What did, what?
Well, you know what we've not had in decades?
A meme like that?
Or a decade?
An infectious internet song that gets stuck in your head for days and days and days.
Double rainbow autotune?
Remember that one?
No, double rainbow, no schmoyoho.
No, you don't remember that?
Oh, I thought you were saying no as in, these are Patches headphones, I will hold onto them.
that you're saying no as in you mean that not that one. No, that one thing there
hasn't been one since then. Yeah, it was corn. That one was
that was a flash in the exactly the same. That's exactly the same as a flash in
the ones that's him. That's him. That's a schmoyoho. Yeah, but it's not the
same. It wasn't as good as for normies, but that's the only reason you're
discounting it is because it was for normies. I know the older one for the
weird yeah normies hated schmoyoho beat up every day because I had a schmoyoho
shirt a t shirt that I got it would happen and I would get this kick down
who my teeth fans schmoyoho we got get fucking brutalized. It was like yeah,
it was like when you when people find out you're a pedophile in prison people
they would kill it. I saw one time I saw a dude wearing a an auto tune the news
t-shirt. He was just walking down the street and this dude stops his car,
pulls around, throws him mouth first onto a curb and just
decks his head out with his foot. I thought you were gonna say throws a
splattering goo on him. No. Based on that sound.
That was the goo. The goo came out of his head. It was like a slime ball.
'Cause his head cracked in half. You're thinking of that movie. That didn't
happen.
I saw it in black and white when it happened to because it was scary long
ago. Yeah, that went in my head when I picture it, it is in black and white.
I've never seen that movie, man. I'm gonna be real with you. Probably. I
don't really care about that movie. No, I don't think that we should be making
movies about Nazis.
That's about a Nazi? I see enough... Speak on that. I see probably 40, 50
Nazis every single day when I walk down the street. I don't need... And nobody
say I'm passing by windows... Or the mirror store. And watching... Seeing my
No, no, no, don't say that. Because you go to the mirror store every day? Yeah,
because I'm beautiful.
Fuck yeah, I go to the mirror store. Okay. Does that make you mad? There's a
chandelier store around here. Yeah, I know that one. I think I almost went to
it. We should make a movie about it. It's so... Oh, your camera angle's so
messed up today. Look at that. What the hell did you do? Look at that angle.
It's kind of a European style. I like that. It's like we should just have a
video wall for Cameron to point at right here. I think that the the
chandelier show is kind of its hubris because it's like they have the lights
on 24/7 and they have the just it's just these gigantic glass and crystal
chandeliers that are just in there and they have the whole all the walls of the
entire building are glass. Yeah, and you can see in there every time of every day
and you know the only reason why they have one here is because there's no
earthquakes. Yep, because an earthquake in the chandelier store that could
first of all, can you imagine that now, but there's going to be an earthquake.
Can you imagine that that moment we know in movies when the chandelier starts
shaking? Yeah, if every chandelier in that store starts shaking around,
that'd be the worst. What the hell's going on? Owning a chandelier store in
San Francisco. See, we're not in trouble of earthquakes here. We're in trouble
of giant monsters. Yeah, this is the city that gets destroyed by a king kong.
Yes, that's where yeah, that's where a monster, a Hulk type monster would be
fighting someone in there. Yeah, bull. Hulk's not a monster, but I take your
point. He is a monster. He's a monster. He's a larger than life personality. He's
a monster. He's a monster. He's a monster and he's a piece of shit. Not a piece of
shit. He's a big a Bruce Banner. You're thinking of Bruce Banner. Bruce Banner is
a meek, fucking nerd. Nerd. Yeah. Right. The Hulk is a larger than life bomb.
monster is a bombastic kind of guy is bombastic. He's very bomb. I missed the
bombastic. He's not he's not a shaggy as Mr. Bean. He dances for that. He didn't
say Mr. Bombay. He is a
bombastic Mr. Bean couldn't string two words together. If you try to Pam yeah,
he does he says he says two words. Sometimes always not a word to is a word
he'll do a sound in a word. He's not even saying oh yeah, he's saying
that's a noise. You couldn't write down
That's a weird sound. Oh, what? That's not even Mr. Bean. This is me doing a new
sound. I think you need to be a Bean too. Yeah, you need to be Bean too back in
action. Bean too? Yeah, I think that you could be. Bean too is Johnny English.
Yeah. So I would be a spy. Y'all remember Johnny English? Not really. I get it
confused with that Steve Carell movie. You should check it out. I get that very
confused with the Steve Carell movie about being a spy. Get Smart, where there's
a bead curtain in that movie. Yeah, one yeah, we need a bead curtain for the
off that we should just replace the front door with a bead curtain. So these
riffraff can just walk in yeah. I think I need a bead curtain for my house.
Yeah, yeah, I need some price. I would fit yeah, no wouldn't that would fit. I
don't know wouldn't it. They're like a tiki hut white ivory beans, beans,
beans, you can make it out of you can make it out of canele beans. No, that
black. I he's saying what if it gets hot, what if it gets so humid, buddy, if it
gets hot, you got beans on a string and you can just sit there and eat them.
Yeah, I don't want it, but that's just one walking through just go
take a couple of beans. Yeah, I think anyone ever did that yeah, maybe like an
angry mom to alpha dog her son, what eat the bean, who had the bead curtains,
bean, I'm saying bean curtain. Why am I saying bean curtain? That sounds like a
vaginal euphemism yeah yeah, I'm sticking in your beans and I'm finding
being nice or being in your urban dictionary. Yes, yeah, hi baby. Can I
sneak in in your bean curtain? Speaking of being curtain, they're showing
Johnny Depp's kids bean curtain on HBO every single night at five o'clock. The
idol, what is going on with this show guys used to be the idol was just you'd
get like the idol used to be something that Indiana Jones stole out of a cave,
and now it's a woman with breast. It's a woman. I mean it used to be a Chinese
guy and we don't know if let me let me let me
point something out to you guys right now. This show it's pornographic. Okay,
this show it goes against our values, showing these things that we don't agree
with and you notice the show used to be called American Idol, but as soon as it
turned into this, what happened? What happened? They
that sex, the word American, it's not American. Oh yeah, it's not it's no
longer. This is fully a European idol that we have on our hands on television
and is the weekend Canadian people are finally people
he's a Canadian idol. There you go. People are finally starting to realize
how disgusting the weekend is. People are starting to realize what we knew
years ago. We were talking about
that damn pussy all the time. We were doing
we were on this before anybody even
take
will you let me take or not?
Will you take the tick off?
He's saying shit. I don't even know he's saying. It's so disgusting. He's
saying flick my
pop my bubble gum on my bubble gum and flick my take my ball
shit on my balls, my balls, my balls, my skin,
I'm bugging God blisters, pick them,
picking my book,
my
lick my tick. Will you let me flick my let me flick my tick or not
not
I want you to I'm not going to let you flick your tech weekend, please, but he
- I made a video in this. - Please girl, please, please.
- No, no. - Please let me flick my tick.
- No, we don't want you to. - I have a tick
that needs to flick.
- Please.
- We don't want him to flick his tick.
- Please let me flick my tick. - One verse of this.
Please, oh please.
- Please, please, please, please, please, please, please,
with a cherry on top.
(laughing)
Pretty please, pretty, pretty please,
with a cherry on top, let me flick my tick for you one time.
Please girl.
- Last night, I had a pretty please moment.
- Yeah?
- Wife needed to go to bed, work in the morning.
my dog ass wanted to play video games all fucking night. Yeah, I literally did a
please, please, please, please, please, please, please, like that and then
realize I had my my mic unmuted and I was talking into my game
with everybody that I was playing Valorant with. I was like, "What the
fuck are you doing?" I was like, "I'm begging my wife to let me play video
games for another ninety minutes. What are you doing, asshole?"
Yeah, so I pretty much got embarrassed. Wow! You know, that's shameful. We've
She's been saying bad news. I had a moment of shame. See, this is alright, go through
with it. Shame is good. I empowered me up for today. I'll say it. What else? This happened
to me a few days ago and I betrayed my trust in somebody. What'd you do? And then I was
set on the right path by the universe. What? What I betrayed. So basically, I was running
on the treadmill at the gym. No, I didn't betray Patrick. Oh. Not this time. I didn't
betray either of you. Okay. I betrayed somebody related to you. Thank God. I was on the treadmill
at the gym and they have the tv attachment. I was flipping through the
channels. I was like, I just need something to look at while I'm running.
What am I going to look at? I go to the travel channel. What's on the travel
channel? Ghost adventures. You know, you did not watch that fucking dildo. Zach
Bagans and we know and yeah, I feel really bad about this. We have a clean
about it. We have a by proxy beef with that mother. Zach Bagans because of my
uncle Matt, he doesn't like him. He doesn't like him and I shouldn't have
watched it. You shouldn't have done it. I watched. I just left it on. It was I
couldn't even hear the sound or anything. Did you at least watch it to make fun of
it? The captions were all the closed captions are doing that thing that closed
captions do all the time for some reason. Do you know what I mean? Where
they're just words on the screen. It just completely all it turns into symbols.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. I don't know why that happened, but so I was barely even
watched. So I shouldn't even even had it on. Okay, I but it's just on I'm
looking at it. Did you try at the end of the end of now? Listen at the end of
my run. I got off to go get the paper towels to wipe down the treadmill. I
left on the TV thing. Yeah, I come back and what is on the screen on go from
Ghost Adventures, but it's just cutting between a bunch of pictures of cake
and it looks like you're running. It looks like I was running on the
treadmill and watching a documentary
oh man, that's good. You're running on me. It taught you a lesson. I mean me
never to watch Ghost Adventures, because they are putting fucked up shit on the
screen. I just had all this bad boy. Okay, I'm sorry. I had the most
incredible idea on the treadmill. The TV should be behind you, and then you
can put on something like a KKK slideshow and you're running away from
it or a bear or a bear two options or yeah or something kind of scary or
a bear. A scary movie. Yeah, well, my my my fiance said that what you know
how they have the also the treadmills where they do like the video run where
that shows the screen and you're like running through like a street or
something. She said one of the ones at the gym has one where you run and you
run into the White House. Like, really? Like, January 6th. Oh, that's cool.
That is sick.
That's so awesome. Getting all dressed up to go do that.
But there is some incredible news this morning. What's coming out? I mean, I
just, I could not believe it when I saw my eyes. I look, I'm... You're sweet.
I'm here. How do you mirror store up so bad already? I did not even believe
you guys. I cannot believe this one. I even saw my eyes open up this morning
to see it.
I look down. I look down. I'm looking at my I'm looking at my phone black
screen. I see my eyes. Click open. Click open. What I'm expecting to see
is a notification from Apple News that says something like this bloody
the pandemic is in perpetuity. Global warming has accelerated. I'm expecting
some terribly bad news, but what do I see? A little red YouTube play button,
right?
You got 50 subscribers. No, even better. Notification, because I hit the bell for
this person.
Jake Novak is back. Oh, I saw this. Jake Novak is back as fuck. That was the
first thing I did when I woke up this morning, me to that I opened my eyes
and I took on my phone. I saw the text and I watched the whole video. It was a
man and he is a bang back in a camera work way. The guys are the best. I am so
I'm so happy he's back. I cannot wait for his next heater to come out. Hope
it's a song. I fucking hope it. I thought he was going to break in a song
the whole time and I was so fucking excited on the edge of my seat, but I
was so honestly the respect that I have for him just skyrocketed because he did
not do a song, mys and sen. Yes, Mermi's and cinematography, zoom
a zoom, a big zoom panning to show a food Spielberg vibes.
Definitely it was incredible. Yeah, the fable men ask for sure. Yeah, but it
was an amazing video. I was so impressed. We need to make something
that is a perfect masterpiece. Yeah, because we are, we are, Jake Novak's
couple years older than us I'd imagine because we have accomplished a half
year older than our average age.
I think that we were in college at the same time as him.
How old actually is he?
I think he was graduating during my freshman year.
So you were probably in high school.
Because you're young.
Cameron's a little boy.
I'm still in high school.
Yeah, I bet you were so hot in high school.
Bro, you have no idea.
high school pics you was even bad then. I bet you were. See look at you giggle.
You were hot. Admit it. You were hot as fuck.
I bet you wore sweatpants every day. Yep. I've told you that before. Adidas
sweatpants. No. Oh, I was so close. Really? You thought I wore Adidas? He
wore Nike Tech. Really, really tight ones. He wore Nike Tech every day to school.
I wore pyjama pants. And you had that pipe. That pipe. That pipe. He had that
pipe. Yeah, that pipe I would smoke. Yeah, no, yeah, that pipe in those shorts
walk around with that pipe. All your teachers are like this in class and
they're like you cannot smoke that and he's like there's nothing in it. Yeah,
it's a bubble pipe from Sponge Bob. Do you guys remember the first time you
saw a jewel? Yeah,
oh,
it was in a chest.
It was in a big red Ruby and it was glimmering.
I've even seen one now. Yeah, we've never seen one. I mean, maybe you've seen one.
That's not what I was talking about, but you've seen a jewel. Okay, I definitely
have, but I also and also that feels like something for the first one I saw
of those, but it feels like that's something that you should remember. It's
like kind of cool
the jewel. I remember a lot of different jewels that I've seen, but I don't
remember which one was first. Yeah, I don't remember the first time I saw a
jewel smoking device. Now yeah, I remember it because I it was so confusing
at me because I was in school and yeah, you were you and I had it. Yeah, it was
like and I fully thought it was a USB stick thing and I was like, what the
fuck? And he's like, it's a vape. Whoa, I was like, whoa, yeah, I don't it must
have been college when I saw one. It might have been you having one. It was
definitely I was my senior year of high school. Ain't no way because we were not
everybody in North Carolina had the had mods. Oh yeah, that makes a gas. The big
vapes that are like this. Yeah. The one. My first my roommate at community college had
one and he had a big pink Floyd tapestry on it. No, behind him. He had to just sit there
and he would like blow like that fucking picture. Chris Maggio took the fucking dude blowing
the smoke into the into the tapestry. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. He would basically do that
every day. That's cool. Yeah, it was sick. He had that. And then on the other side of
the wall big ass or like tapestry sized American flag. Can that affect your
tapestry? Yes. Are you kidding? It makes it trippy. It makes it come to life.
Yeah. The nicotine makes it come to life like Night at the Museum. Uh-huh. It makes all
of the the colors on the Pink Floyd triangle. It makes all of them move. Have
we already talked about what would be the best place to have Night at the Museum
happen? Yeah, I think so. I think we said the wax museum.
Fame. That doesn't sound like that. No, I wouldn't say that. I don't like celebrity. I don't like
fame and stuff. You don't like fame. It's not my kind of thing. I like my fame. I don't
like other people who are famous. I would get too jealous. I think yeah. I also think
the attitude of famous people can be sour at best. What if there was a night at the
museum situation at the wax museum though and see we never talked in the first idea
and it's a bad idea. The Queen of England starts coming on to you right. She starts trying
to kiss you with those big wax lips. You can't fucking hear, they're all one year old. You're
getting hot and heavy. No, because they're made of celebrities hair and stuff. They don't
use their real hair. They put their hair in them. No, they use. I thought it was a voodoo
thing. No, you did not think that. You didn't think that at all. I thought it was a voodoo
type scenario. No, you didn't. No. Home Depot. You must be on a voodoo fucking ranger because
you're acting drunk. Am I? Yeah. I don't believe that's so. You don't believe that is so? I
I believe that is so a wax museum. I don't think would be that good, because
I think that everybody's going to be in the middle of they're going to if they
cut the celebrities come to life, they're going to be in the middle of
whatever they were. They were like
well, it yeah, so it's going to be Bo Jackson do like running. That's also
your that's also just that's just night at the museum. Basically yeah, exactly
yeah, that's not it. I have that and I have I guess it is a wax without the
caveman yeah. I don't even get the caddy roosevelt it's it's a more boring night
at the museum yeah. What I got hang on the worst ever answer yeah yeah, maybe
the worst ever answer it's more it's more just the gram norton even any store
is a better answer. Yeah, I guess you could do the gram norton yeah. If you
didn't, I mean not a museum, he should have done the gram norton yeah, you
should just have been sitting in the lobby yeah, ask teddy roosevelt about
his favorite foods and chin and made him a sexual game yeah with squanto and
them. Teddy Roosevelt and Squanto. Oh, that's his Native American friend? No,
Squanto was from Thanksgiving. Yeah, he was one of the
the gods of Thanksgiving. He's one of the gods of Thanksgiving. Yeah. Oh, I
don't know anything about that story. Squanto and Samoset.
We didn't learn- The gods of Thanksgiving sounds incredible. You never
learned about Squanto and Samoset? I did
the- I was a Native American in a play, the Thanksgiving play when I was a
kid, and that was the last time I learned about Thanksgiving, because I
I learned that it was I was wrong yeah yeah. I had the feather head on and I
did a couple of these a couple of a couple of loud fast, you're bored by the
material yeah it's not that interesting.
Elementary yeah, I know it really seemed childish, so then I skipped four or five
grades, went back down to actually two grades under where I was because I
realized I had under you said underwear. You said two grades under where I was
see okay. Now you can't pack can't do that.
you can I'll accept it from you.
I'll accept that from you, but yeah, so I went up a couple grades down to under
the grade that I was in
and then two more down and then I kind of floated around there for four or five
years. The same kind of bumped up and down grades four or five years,
kind of haunting grades, yeah, walking around. I was getting a lot taller than
the other kids, so I grown breasts and then you can skip again and then you
I mean if you stay in one grade for like four grades, you can skip ahead and then
at that time at that point, it's time to get my driver's license and then I never
looked back didn't fly school. It is so funny. I just did not go to school at
all. Yeah, that's kind of what homeschooling is. If you if most people
who are homeschooled don't listen to them when they say that they almost did
normal, they did not do anything. No, yeah, it doesn't, but they just watch
you would ever be able to. I watch YouTube. I played video games. Yeah, I
did about 20 minutes of Khan Academy every day.
- Dude, I almost was homeschooled when I was like eight.
- You would have been a bad candidate.
- I would have been so bad if I like, if I did.
- Would you consider yourself--
- I think it's because my mom thought I was weird.
- Would you say you're a self starter?
- No, I don't know, it depends.
- What does that mean, you do stuff?
- It means literally do you do stuff or no.
- Okay, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Oh man, it depends.
- 'Cause I sure wasn't.
You know what I did, I made desktop backgrounds.
- Yo.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Me too.
- Yeah, you were talking about that a while ago.
- I would make a--
I made Bokeh, I made a bunch of different pictures of Master Chief.
Uh-huh, that's sick.
You know, an 8x8 Master Chief, different photos, because they're all low res.
Yeah, I would draw pictures of dragons on Photoshop that were 100 pixels by 100 pixels
and stretch it out to be my entire desktop.
Why does it look so bad?
Yeah, I learned how to use Photoshop and Adobe Premiere really, really badly.
Like, didn't learn how to use it.
I was obsessed with Photoshop.
Me too.
I still am obsessed with Photoshop.
I use Gimp a lot. Yeah, you get you get like portable versions of software and
you bring it to school on a thumb drive and then you just I'd be playing like
Cave Story off a thumb drive. I'd be doing all this other stuff. I never did
anything like that. That is cringe. Yeah, I was 13 years old. You're an otaku. You
are an otaku. I don't remember why I played that game. Admit it. It was free.
Say I am an otaku. Cave Story is a fun game, but it played off a thumb drive at
high school is cringe. It was the smallest game I could put on the thumb drive.
Now you can do tic tac toe or palm. You could have played cool math games. Yeah,
I did just like a normal kid and con. There is a cool that's the one where you
can like play with other people right. You're thinking of every game ever. No,
like there's a math game where you like send like the code or whatever and then
you have to do like the no, I don't know what you're talking about. Cool math
games was the one it was cool. We used to do cool math games and fun brain fun
brain was so full mass games was the one where it's had nothing to do with math.
Yeah, just called that we were talking about brain age the other day. Oh yeah,
how you guys are brain age academy brain age academy. No, was I talking to you
about this? Yeah, you accused me of playing it. Yeah, you seemed like a
brain ager. No, you seemed like you would have a hundred year old brain. No,
in the game. I didn't like stuff like that. What did you like growing up
spectrobes. What's a spectro? I don't remember spectrobes. I don't ever heard
that word in my life. Disney's JRPG for the DS.
Oh, I liked it. I thought that game was way bigger than it was. I like
DaVinci, I like swords and sandals gladiators, and I liked
I liked
I like the Sabbath feudalism to the Sabbath tour. Yeah, I like to have a
computer that could run that. It was on Xbox. I didn't. I liked all the
games that were flash games with shooting guns because I couldn't get I
wasn't allowed to have any of the actual. There was one that was called
something. There was one that was like top down and I can't remember what it
was called, but it was so sick and there were different levels and it was
like all like different countries that you go to and kill people. I wasn't
killing. It was kind of like Hotline Miami style. Oh nice, but it was like
an on addicting games. There was this one I was addicted to called Madness
combat that was so sick. It's like mortal combat. There was no it was like
you are. It was originally a flash game and it's a little gray guy and you're
supposed to like like shoot people and like throw your gun at them and then
grab their gun and so I do that. There was also there was a worms rip off
called territory war. Did you ever play that one? No, that one was fire
madness. Combine I played in those are some funny names of territory war
Madness Combat. I liked any flash game that had some funny shit like maybe Gary
Busey or Nicolas Cage. You know what there was? There was this flash game on
Newgrounds that would get DMCA'd all the time and then people would re-upload it,
but it was called... I've talked about this before for sure, but it was called
Bill Cosby's Funtime Adventure and the whole game was you taking a Kodak camera
and baiting women with jello pudding and new coke and hitting women in the head
and putting them in your cave.
Well, I guess I suppose that's age
kind of poorly. I don't know if it's aged poorly or very well.
Well, depends on it. I mean, I don't think that's admissible as evidence in
court. What if it is?
Oh, you think Bill Cosby made the game? What if Bill Cosby made the game as a
confession as a confession. You keep it in so I mean serial killers do that.
They make games. I mean a lot of probably a lot of these games were made
by serial killers who are admitting. I mean how do the people who make mortal
combat know what the inside of a guy looks like and also how do they sleep at
night? Yeah, well, how do you you know it's crazy bastards. It actually ruins
their life. The people who work on mortal combat, they're all like yeah. I
have PTSD. I can't sleep because I because they make us watch like gore
videos. Really, I have to watch like actual like anatomy videos to do the
it's the same as people working for Facebook and having a
manually. It's exactly that job. Oh my God, speaking of Facebook, my my
girlfriend was like looking at marketplace last night and then like
closes out of the window. I saw it on like on her laptop. She was looking for
a new boyfriend. Yeah, no, but she closes out and then the first thing on
her feet was a video to lions fucking. Oh, I would get that on instagram
every day. I would send them to I would send them to patches. There was this one
instagram page. It was called like beautiful Africa or something like that
on every other post. Every other post was either was lions fucking and like the
caption was like, oh, he likes it, but then there's also a bunch of like
elephants pooping on each other's heads and like animals peeing in their mouths
and stuff. Most of the time, every half of the posts are like a beautiful
picture of like the landscape and like a herd of zebras and then you're one and
trying to be a full lines, Dickin Balls, yeah, but she kept trying to play it. I
and immediately like somebody must have shared it or something or it like
showed up on her feet or whatever, but she looked at it, then looked at me and
went like what I hate Facebook, because it's always crap like this.
That's like a
scrolling through. It's just like Lion, Lion,
what the fuck is that?
the worst part about an out of here, the worst part about animals at their shaft
is hairy yeah yeah that ain't right. No, because they the
oh yeah, because then then the red thing comes the page is called Wow Africa
on Instagram Wow Africa, W.
Up there, don't look at
I'm looking at
hippo cleaning kindly. Please don't forget to follow at Snow Africa
adventures for more wild snow. Is that a tail waving away piss out of its
ass? Yeah,
Jim Carrey came out of there. I sent so many. I can find them all because I
sent them all to patches. Yeah, here's monkeys going at it. That was a picture
of Tom and Jerry. Look at this one. I don't even know.
Some kind of animal being born and the sack is attached. Here's rhinos fucking.
I saw two beetles having sex the other day.
- Whoa. - You get a pic?
- Congratulations. - No, no, I interrupted them.
I didn't realize.
I was walking on a, I was going on a hike upstate.
I'm walking down the trail,
and about a foot away from me, I see a giant beetle.
I go, "Holy shit, it's a giant beetle."
- How big?
- I mean, it was probably four or five feet wide.
And then I was like, I get a little closer,
and then I realize it's two beetles,
and they were having intercourse,
and they split like this.
So I broke up some kind of fuck session.
they break it up. Yeah, I break it up. Good. Come on. What are you doing out
here?
Yeah,
come on.
I would love to be a somebody who has a pet beetle feel. Yeah, beetle. I
think a beetle is the only, but I hate bugs. I do not like bugs. They gross
me out for whatever reason. A beetle does not gross me out. I would have a
beetle on a beetle is basically a mouse. Yeah, yeah, it's got that. You know
what it is? It's got that sheen. It's also it's solid. Yeah, a lot of other
bugs are have like are very wiggly and they're slow. They go like for the most
they go like they're all different parts of them going different angles, but a
beetle is just like I don't like speed a rock. I do not want to have some beetles
are fast, but a lot of them are the big ones are really big ones yeah, but it's
weird. It's also scary when a bug is heavy yeah in my head right now. That is
better to me than a big yeah and a big one that's light. I'm only picturing a
like a moth over right now. I don't like moss. I don't like butterflies. You see
those giant moths, you like butterflies, no, you don't like butterflies. I don't
like butterflies. I hate dragon flies. I'm scared of dragon. I have a dragon
yeah. My brother used to torture me by he would find dead dragon and show them
in my room. No, and they'd scare me because I thought they were nice to
come like that. Dragon flies bugs. I didn't I hated them. I thought I was
running. Why is it cool? I think they're disgusting. There's too big. I used to
try to get them to land on me weird. Oh yeah, you do that like yeah, you put the
finger out like yeah. They think you're that's why they never did. They never
landed on me because I was doing this yeah. See that's a
dragon fly. I thought that was a shoot up buddy. Hey land on this finger. You
dragon flies are beautiful, fat ass cream. If it landed on that finger, I
actually would that's what I'm saying. Their eyes are going different
directions. Oh, that's crazy to me. I don't care too much about bugs. I hate
bug. I there I definitely I feel like I have an okay tolerance for bugs, but I
also I'm not going to pretend I'm not if I see a spider or a scary bug, I'm
going to be scared of I used to have to I said babysit these kids at a bearded
dragon. I used to have to feed it cockroaches, just feed it worms. That's
what I think doesn't it live
I had to put three live cockroaches in its thing. Every that is crazy. It was
so disc. My and
fifth no third or fifth grade. I can't remember we had crayfish to do the
Crayfish unit. No. We took care of crayfish. Like we each had a yeah.
Crawdads. Yeah, but we call them crayfish in the Northeast. We did not do that.
Y'all are cray. Y'all are some cray ass fish. I've called them crawdads forever.
Crawfish. You're performative. You are being performative.
I actually call them crawdads forever. And he has the camo on. Yeah. Okay, nice try buddy.
Cringe. Yeah, it's not getting through me today. But we would keep, like everyone had their own pet
a crayfish that we would always take care of like it was like the like
butterfly type unit, you know, but it was crayfish. I don't know why we did
that. I don't know if that's that's a
thing or
really funded school, but I remember it really vividly that one kid, the
crayfish got away and it like
like everyone's cream, they got on the floor and it was zip just under the
door into the next class. It's a walk in my God,
it's one of the I was like
literally a walk in talking shrimp. Yeah, it's so it was so funny. It makes it
like
when it shoots its tail real fast. Awesome. They're disgusting man, but I
do like eating them. Yeah, speaking of eating bugs, I fucking saw my girlfriend
pick up the cat and make it swing at a fly.
She wanted to make sure I don't let him eat the bug. A fly is fine. Yeah, fuck
that. She was standing there. I saw her in the kitchen, holding him on to the
because you wanted to eat the fly. I wanted to eat the fucking thing. I was
I was on my lily pad all day. I
would not surprise me. It would surprise me a little bit, but I mean,
obviously a little bit, but not as much as with him. I guess if I was sitting
here in a fly, like landed on my eye, like it was the camera and you went,
your tongue came all the way out and grabbed the fly off my eye. Yeah, I
would not. I would I would be got a totally quality. There's something
frogly about you. Yeah, you're frogly. Yeah, probably because I
just
yeah, you are green right now. I guess and you also right now with your arms.
You kind of are having a frog like posture. You're kind of sinking your
head into your body. Well, you just riveted. I mean,
that alone makes you almost I want I've dude. I want to rib it so bad.
I want to have it and I want to be able to blow my cheeks up like a bullfrog
does. Did you guys have cat tails? Yeah,
the plant yeah yeah, I used to want to eat those me too, so bad. I thought that
it was a corn dog. Yeah, it looks exactly how fucked up is it that God
made as it makes a plant that looks exactly it looks exactly like a corn
dog. Yeah, well, I think I guess that we made the corn dog to look like a
cat tail.
Shut the fuck up,
shut up,
shut the foot right now. It was some for the prankster who invented the corn
dogs. I'm going to make it look exactly like a cat tail. That's just not right
dude and then you put and I put one in my mouth one time and it turns into
basically yeah, it goes yeah.
Is that the seed itself? Does that grow into something bigger? I think it grows
into another cat tail my friend.
Wow, it goes in it turns into a Christmas tree.
The Christmas tree seed wow, but I just don't I don't think that's right, but
there should be no food that looks like other looks like a plant. I don't think
that's right now, unless it's like a snowflake cookie or like a snow is not a
plant
for the last time. How many times have I to tell you that a snowflake is not a
snow. People eat snowflakes all the time. You catch it out of the air. People do
it. It's a movie thing. It's so common that they made it a movie trope. No,
like a snowflake plant, like the one the one that looks white as snow and it
looks like still think of a Christmas tree with snow on it. Am I thinking of a
Christmas tree with no
yeah with snow yeah with snow or you think of a paper snowflake because that's
not a plan either. People hang those up on a string. Actually, I beg to differ
yeah. What are you talking? It's made out of wood. It's made out of
which is made out of what Cameron wood, which is from what bread bread? No, not
from bread, dog and brain, not from bread. No, not from bread dog, not from
Bread dog
now dog
not from bread dog
bread dog bread dog could be cool looking dog
dog made out of red doing. I don't even know what he's bread. This this you
brought everything to a halt with bread dog. Yeah, yeah, I'm actually I'm
walking out. I'm protesting the podcast because you said bread dog. You said you
I'm ready to go on that. I'm coming in with this heat dude. The cat tails look
like hot or corn dogs, the night of the museum at the wax museum. We should get
corn dogs for lunch. We should order some on Uber. That would be amazing.
There is a corn dog spot by my old apartment. Yeah, I know that. Oh yeah,
the one on Knickerbocker, Korea, you've done it again. Yeah, Korea, you crazy
mother fucker. You crazy fuckers. You took a corn dog, one of the worst things
What are you? Well, hold on, hold the phone. I'm never in the mood for a corn dog. Then
why do you care about cattails? You're never in the mood for a corn dog. When I was a kid
I liked them. What about at the carnival? At the carnival I'm getting funnel cake and
that's it. El does not have carnival smarts. A corn dog is so delicious once a year. Yeah.
I haven't had a corn dog in many years. I had one. Well, actually I had a Korean corn
dog probably two years ago, but the sweet potato on it, the powdered sugar, this is
I had a really bad corn dog at that street fair thing. I'm sorry. It was really expensive,
too. That's just about the worst street food you can get nowadays. There's so many better
options. Guess how much this corn dog was? Five bucks. Seven. More than seven dollars
for a fucking burrito? How big was it? Eight dollars, normal corn dog. Are you fucking
for real? They already were handing it to me. They had made it and were handing it to
they're like okay, eight dollars and I was like you got bullied yeah, I got
completely fucked God damn. It was so horrible. I'm
sad. What am I going to do now? Walk away, throw it in their face. I had the
spirit of the street fair. Yeah, that's true. I mean when you're in a fair when
you're in a fair
and eight dollars is like six dollars anything good. I mean that's yeah
expensive for a corner. It's a three buck completely insane. Yeah, it should
be less than three bucks. Yeah, yeah, great, unless it has all the trimmings
completely absurd. The whole thing is trimming. That's what a hot dog is. What
the hot dog is like? No, like feet like like the sweet potato, like sweet
potatoes and the sneezing and is it true that eating a hot dog is the same? It
like takes the same amount of time off your life as like a pack of cigarettes.
I would imagine I would imagine that that's true about most food. Yeah,
yeah, anything that goes through a process. I don't think that a lot of
food is so healthy for you or in a hot. I feel like it's one of those things
sure it's probably not completely true, but it might as well be. I try most of
the other stuff you eat is probably going to do that anyway. Yeah, I think
hot dogs are probably I think I do think that per pound they're just about the
worst for you thing that you can eat. Why can't it ever in a hot dog in a long
time? That's that corn dog. Why can't it ever be the stuff that I don't want to
eat like my veggies, fruits that are bad for you? So why can't the only reason
that the only reason that you don't like veggies is because they're good for you.
I like veggies. I'm addicted to broccoli.
That means veggies are bad for you.
I did. I had a broccoli.
I like broccoli a lot.
Just broccoli with nothing else.
Have you guys noticed that women don't like broccoli?
Women like broccoli.
Women like broccoli a lot.
I haven't noticed this either.
The women in my life.
Women, no, women in my life do not like broccoli.
Two different women don't like broccoli.
You're saying this is a coincidence.
That is just a coincidence, yeah.
Well, fuck me then.
I guess I'm not making any sense.
No.
but basically I know two women that do not like broccoli and to me broccoli is
just about the most palatable vegetable on earth.
Yeah, I think that is the that's the number one broccoli. It's fibrous
cinnamon broccoli vegetable. I couldn't set it better myself. It's fibrous. It's
got all the vitamins you could ever ask for. Okay, they got different types of
what's going to do.
What's it's just a vitamin. I don't know.
way before my spinach heavily, heavily involved heavily
never heard of it. I thought it only went up to D. No, I know I know about
E. Now there's a K. There's a vitamin K. Does it go everywhere through up to? I
don't think there's a vitamin Zed. Z is basically just zinc. Well, that's not a
vitamin, though. That's a mineral. That's how they I guess it's just how they
brand.
What's it called AstraZeneca
all of it. You get every vitamin from A to Zinc.
Oh, okay. Yeah. I get it. Yeah. So for a long time, I thought vitamin Z was Zinc.
My aunt, my aunt had, she ate too much spinach and she had a vitamin K attack.
An overdose? She had to go to the hospital. Oh, a lot of vitamin overdoses
are really painful, right? Some of them are. She was in some of the greatest
pain you could ever imagine. Yeah. That's insane. Which vitamin? There's some
vitamin. Vitamin K. Yeah. Vitamin B sometimes... Maybe that's what the K is,
Vitamin K. I think is a dangerous vitamin to be having. There's another one that I was
seeing that I think that you can overdose on. Probably vitamin C. Cocaine. Maybe so.
If you have too many oranges. Yeah. What is it? It's keratin. If you eat too much, too
many carrots, your fucking skin turns all orange. Keratin is what your fingernails are
made out of. That happened to me. Yeah. I think I've told you this before. I think it's
a good thing. I think it's a good thing. I think it's a good thing. I think it's a good
what your fingernails are made out of.
That happened to me.
That, yeah. I think I've told you this before. I turned orange for one year.
Oh yeah.
When I was like 15, when I was vegan.
You said that very recently.
When I lost a bunch of weight when I was vegan, it was because I just filled myself up with
carrots all day.
If you eat too much chocolate, it turns your hands and mouth brown.
I, that is, I've noticed that.
I think, I don't know if it's a vitamin thing or not, but it's happened to me a few times.
Especially on a hot day.
Yeah.
You get a brown mouth.
And your hands get brown as well.
too many Jolly Ranchers, it can turn any color in your mouth. Yeah, turns your
tongue a different color. Yeah, and lollipops and if you eat too much
spaghetti, you're the ring around your mouth gets a red. I have been having
there's been too much spaghetti or you play too much Call of Duty in middle
school. You get a red ring around your mouth. I've been having a personal
epidemic of walking around with food, just food on your food, lipstick all the
time, and I don't even think to check before I leave the house and then I
I realized I walked around outside for hours and then came back and I had food
all over my face. Damn. And I was also look, I was winking at everybody.
You're winking? I'm a winker. Yeah, not a winker. I wink at everybody. You just
couldn't wink just now. He walks around like Spider-Man three. He's walking
around just going... Yeah, that is kind of how I walk around. Yeah.
You do that. I do see you. I do see you across the street sometimes and I
don't say hi because I don't think that... It's 'cause I got my pinstripes on.
you're in your seersucker suit. Yeah, leave me the fuck alone. You're in your
trilby hat. You're walking down the street. I'm in my summer suit. Uh-huh
walking around, winking at the girlies. Yeah, I think people should. I think
most people should have a flag popping out of my hat. I think most people
should have an arc like like Spider-Man does in Spider-Man three where they
find evil clothes and they turn evil. I agree. I agree. Yeah, which is
with their normal clothes. I agree, oh yeah, which is
that is basically what venom is is an evil sure he's his clothes that he
threw away that got mad. Evil shirts should yeah that should be a more
common trope yeah. The next venom movie should just be an evil. It should just
be a stinky old shirt shirt that was evil, a shirt with a face, the movie,
the shirt with a face, oh my God, and the shirt can talk like one of those
in the mountain t shirts that like is just a picture of like an apes face and
your shirt can talk. I have a shirt that is a picture. If these sure to talk, I'm
not sure that is a picture on it. Wait, you're wearing one right now.
Wait, I think it is a more picture. I have more. It has more picture than mine.
Yeah, you know what? The scariest thing about this shirt is you don't know if
there's a person lurking behind all these leaves.
I do. This is not real leaves. I'm not an idiot. You sure about that?
Me and our shirts versus your shirt,
our shirts would win.
Like if you personify them?
If the shirts became alive, yeah.
So you admit that a skater is a loser?
No, because that's a text.
So you admit that skaters would lose any fight?
No.
Because, okay, here's my beef with skaters, man.
It's never a fair fight.
Why?
Skaters don't fight fair.
They have a weapon.
They walk around on a weapon all day.
They do a truck smash.
One on one.
They do a truck slam, truck smash.
Truck smack.
Is that what it's called?
Uh-huh.
You can call it whatever you want.
I don't know.
Is that what it's called?
Uh huh.
You can call it whatever you want.
Hit with the truck.
Truck slapper.
That's, you can't walk around and, you can't ride a blade, I can't ride my blade all day.
You could.
No I can't.
Roller blades.
I can ride my blades.
Yeah.
But those are bad weapons.
Roller blades.
It takes a minute to take them off your feet.
You know what you can do?
Put a switchblade on the heel.
But then I'm going to prison.
You aren't going to prison for walking around with a skateboard.
Well that's because it becomes a weapon in the heat of battle.
As much as I think that you should.
There's no heat of battle because somebody told you to get up. Hey, stop skating on my
kids wheelchair. That's not a battle.
It's a little bit of a battle.
How's that a battle? No, there's no skater has ever all those videos where it's like
epic truck smack. Those kids.
There's no videos of truck smacks because that's an actual felony.
There's a video. I know a video of a truck smack.
You know a video of a truck smack?
Yeah, although now that I think about it, I think the guy was being really racist and
that's why he got truck smacked.
I know the video. Yeah. Yeah. That one makes sense.
But besides that, I haven't seen the only other time I've seen a video of
somebody get truck smacked is the movie kids.
I think that you're letting film sway your opinion.
I don't give a fuck about Harmony Koren movies. You don't? No.
I saw the spring breakers one and I thought that James Franco was doing an
offensive caricature of riff raff. Yeah. So I turned it off.
And I thought Selena Gomez was too skinny.
So I said, I'm not watching this movie.
I don't want to see this garbage.
I think the movie he made directly after that was Trash Humpers.
Old people.
Can we stop making these movies that are about the lowly dregs of society?
How come a guy like Harmony Corrine is allowed to make a movie
movie called Trash Humpers. Yeah, and we only have six or seven transformers
movies. The fuck is that? And I try to make a movie called The Bug Fucker
and you should be completely boxed out of the world. I agree. There should be
sent off world to a colony. There should be a colony of bug women. No, no, and
they're going to literally, they're going to tear you limb from limb. That's
exactly what the bug would not fuck you, my friend. You really scare it, and if
if you fucked a bug, it would be against the bugs wishes. A bug would scurry
bugs cannot consent. I don't know what yeah and you say you want to fuck one.
No, I'm saying it was a
change in his whole mind who can't consent a plant. That's your dream, a
planet of bug women who cannot consent. It's not true. That's your dream. It's
not my you made it up. I didn't make up a single word. I made up just now. Well,
okay, but I wasn't involved
whatever, unless there's royalties to be had. I was there's some royalty on the
bug planet. Well, I'd like to be the Queen, but just in a platonic way, I just
or a I would like to be christened. I think that
doesn't it suck that now you got to be christened by a guy yeah
kind of gay
next time someone is going to become a night. Oh, because I did I understand
yeah that you really isn't is put a champagne on a boat next. I really so
you have to be knighted by a king yeah
yeah he's got a touch. I'll fight for you yeah. I'll protect you. I'll protect
you, because your highness, why does these people get knighted for being
actors in the UK? Yeah, what's with that? How far have we fallen? Why is a we
have to kill six thousand people in the Middle East, so he became a night, sir
Pierce Brosnan, I guess that makes sense. He was James Bond. I guess if
you're a James Bond, no immediate, he was not he pretended to be James Bond.
The real James Bond should be nighted, not this.
He is not James Bond, no, not even a little. He's a slob. He dressed as
James Bond. Yeah, oh, I went for four or five movies. Who cares right? Yeah,
okay, you see what I mean. I see I don't even think he's knighted Pierce
thousand and I think I was just I think I'm thinking of somebody in the
Kellen is yeah, but he was Gandalf and that's one of their biggest again.
That's like they're not Gandalf. He pretended to be Gandalf and also that
was New Zealand. Oh yeah, do you get knighted in New Zealand? What do they
got down there? Not much. Yeah, I know they got some lambs not fucking
order the rings tour Lord of the Rings and then that puzzle world. It's cool
that that's like a puzzle world. Yeah, they got a whole they got a whole field
that is just like a
a bunch of statues that are like like a big chess piece, a checkers board.
Those aren't puzzles room that is small as you walk towards it. Are you
thinking of the Museum of Optical Illusions? You're saying no, there's
there's like a upside down building, a big a little be field in New Zealand.
It's basic. It's near the Hobbit holes and it's all their hobbles actually
puzzles and other things. They are their holes. They're hovels. They're holes. I
have to look that up because that's I had to do. I had to do a project on New
Zealand in high school and you found a puzzle world. There is a possible during
your investigation. There is a puzzle world. I think I was looking up
New Zealand landmarks. There's a bunch of mountains or cliffs or basically just
cliffs, not even mountains. Hobbit hole puzzle world. You know what? I don't mean
is an insult, but I could never see you going to Europe.
Yeah.
I just don't think you'd fit in.
I would not fit in at all.
Imagine him walking around like Paris.
Yeah.
That'd be kind of tough to imagine.
I don't even think I would want to go to Paris.
It's disgusting.
If you could go anywhere in the world, where would you go for a vacation?
I'd probably go to Syria.
I don't think you would.
I don't think you would enjoy it.
I don't think I would.
So you don't have it?
I didn't want to say Ireland because you knew that I would say it.
Well, except for Ireland.
Barring Ireland.
Okay, so barring Ireland.
Like what are the culturally interesting places in the world to you?
Yes, Germany.
Oh.
Because I...
Where in Germany?
Bergheim.
I want to go to the Scheisse room and see some crap.
No, you don't.
No, I don't.
What am I saying?
Me, I want to go to Italy.
I want to go to Greece.
I want to go to, but I don't want to have to travel through the country. So you
have to go to China.
Yeah, China would be cool. Maybe
I would basically honestly, I want to go to every country in the world and I'm
not even joking. I do. I do want to go to Europe for honeymoon vibes, but I am
looking at how to get from Italy to Greece. Yeah, and you do have to go
through every Balkan fucking country to get there, which does not sound that
fun to me. Yeah, you don't think it would be fun to go to like I don't want to go
to Serbia, bro.
Albania. I don't want to do any of that. What about Czech Republic? They got a
booming film industry there and you could probably make a movie while you're
out there.
Well, I do like movies. Yeah, but I why do they put the all the country? It
should be like the US where all the cool stuff is on the East Coast or the West
Coast and there's nothing in between. They should just you know what they
should do is just make a United States of Balkan countries and like all of Europe.
And then move the whole thing to Russia.
Move the whole thing.
Russia's way, way, way too big.
Yeah.
They need people in that eastern part of Russia.
They have to split that place up.
I think that's definitely a possibility for me if I flame out the United States.
Splitting up Russia?
Yeah, basically dividing it.
Yeah.
No, going and doing the homesteading act thing they have over there.
where they give you like 50k and send you to Siberia. I would do that.
You're going to have to do that in 50 years.
That'd be fun.
What is the only land left?
Is Siberia actually like a barren wasteland?
There's like nobody there. There's a couple of cities, but one of them is like the coldest city in the world.
Oh yeah, one of them is permafrost.
Oh Jesus.
Yeah.
How'd you live there?
Jesus, permafrost.
Oh Jesus.
Oh Christ.
a ton drop. I monsters there to Holy Yeti's actually the most beautiful
women of all time there, but they're all they're all frozen solid on yeah
there. It's probably it's probably why couple of ice queens up there in
Siberia, a couple of them all breaking your heart only a couple. Well, there's
only four or five people, so it's a really amazing rate. Yeah, beautiful
women, but I think that I could do very well in a Mongolia type situation.
Mongolia, Mongolia, I would do well in I think I think it would be amazing to
travel to to travel to over to Tibet and maybe do a Mount Everest thing. Yeah, I
think that I would write seven wonders. This is so I really would. I think I
would really like to live my life in kind in like rural China and be in a
Chinese village, but I wouldn't want to be the white guy who moves to rural
China and get the one white guy in the tiny village. So I China you ladder. So I
I think what I would maybe do is funnel some of my money into developing
basically the program from the Avatar movie and I would go into a Chinese
person's body to put you in over their body yeah and live in a village. So you
want to grow a Chinese peasant in your floors, you know, or I could just take
someone's body. Who's no we're not going to you can't take somebody's body.
That's yeah, that's insane. I take my body, they'd be they'd love to take your
body. Can I take your life in America to yeah? Yeah, what if it's just like a
freaky Friday situation where you just switch your bodies out yeah. You just
what you switch you body swap with like some like sixty five year old and then
Chinese farmer and you're just a little younger. I mean maybe the same my same
age.
You want to do you want to do an exchange student situation? Yeah, what if they
just what if everybody in China just wears glasses that show you as kind of
blending in
that would take a lot of convincing. I guess it just has to be my village.
Yeah, that does it and I just don't leave my village. I think you become some
kind of
Lord too quickly. Yeah, I didn't want to say that, but yeah, yeah, I think that
you just you have to I would completely be the Lord of a Chinese, you're too
magnetic to do anything like that
morally, because I think that pretty soon you'd be having
people bringing you around on wagons and stuff, and I don't think that that'd be
a good look for the podcast. Oh, you think we're doing the podcast? I hope so
what am I supposed to do in this situation? Yeah, I guess I'm doing I
guess you would be on a tour of Europe
that I exchanged with well. I mean that'd be yeah, it'd be a new market. I
guess
do we would pop on webo? No, why not? I don't understand that crap. It's the
name is everything else. It's just in a whole new language.
Yeah, but that would, it would suck going on. Oh yeah, I guess I could get a translator,
but it would suck going on there. You can choose AI. Not with the translator just going
like, what the hell are y'all saying? It'd be fun to go promote it on all the podcast,
all the Chinese, Chinese, your mom's house, Chinese, the Oman. That would be incredible.
Go and do all those shows. Chinese Bobby Lee. Yeah. Go do Tiger mom or whatever that show
is called. Tiger belly. Tiger belly. Tiger belly over there. That'd be cool, man. Yeah,
that would be pretty. I love to do that. We should do some. We should just do a
we should just do that. Yeah, on every podcast in the world, we I want to
become a promote insanely top level famous in a different country. Yeah, I
think that we are and then be forced to move.
Yeah, continue our life. Yeah, our like the fun, every like go we go there and
we become the first people to do
amazing next level alt comedy in the far east.
We are missing out not auto translating every single episode with AI to different languages.
That's what Mr. Beast does.
Is that what he actually does?
Well Mr. Beast has a channel for like 50 different languages translated.
Why aren't we doing that?
Because we don't have his kind of money man, he's the richest guy in the world.
I mean...
He's got more money than anybody.
We could figure it out.
This guy walks around in hands of homeless people with 10 million dollars.
He doesn't even notice it.
He doesn't even realize he's doing it.
He accidentally built a squid game.
He did?
It was an accident.
I thought it was on purpose.
It was a clerical error.
He was playing it off.
He was like, "Fuck, I guess I'll make a fucking video now."
He did that on accident.
He didn't even realize it. He just ordered all this shit.
He got a big statue that shoots a laser.
That's crazy.
It's fucking insane what he's doing.
that. 90% of those videos. He's just walking around getting filmed. I mean no, he orders
the stuff accidentally, he goes on a shopping spree on Amazon and then he's like, "Well,
I guess I could do a squid game with this." Is he a teetotattler? He's not a tattletale.
He's a teetotaller, is that how you say it? I've only seen that word written and never
heard. I think he's a tea totaler. I can't imagine Jimmy drinking. Yeah. Yeah.
Because I'm afraid of what Mr. Beast becomes when he drinks. Yeah, I know.
You hear the name. He's been training and losing weight. You hear the name
Mr. Beast and you think this guy must have gotten that nickname from pounding
them back, pounding back Coors Light every night. Mr. Beast. I don't really
think that. I think maybe he was like a feral animal. He was like kind of like
skinny fat like chubby. But he did post something where he said that he was 40%
body fat, which just can't be true. That is so fat. That is so much fatter than
he was. I feel like maybe he was fat before he was on YouTube or something,
or before he was famous. That could be true. I bet that's what it is. You know
that he's been grinding YouTube for like 15 years? Yeah, he made that video of him
saying every single word in the dictionary or something. Yeah, yeah, he
counted every single word, or not counted. No, he counted to one million. He
He counted to a million. And then he also, I think some, some podcasts,
I'm like, Hey, if you were going to make a video right now and you had nobody,
what would you do? And I think he said again, he was like,
I would count to 1 million. That's an amazing idea.
Like who will watch to this video? Yeah. Counting to a million.
I mean, I feel like that video is just him, like people just clicking on it.
That would take me so long. It'd be so fun.
It did you pull up the Mr. B's counting to 1 million video and it has the thing
and like over the like time bar where it shows like the most replayed and you
like click to see what the most replayed and he goes like a thousand
everyone going to find their favorite yeah yeah there. It is he said fifty
eight
that's my age. That's true. If yeah, if you're going to watch Mr. Beast, say
your your lucky number, there's probably pretty steep drop off after a hundred.
how many people are lucky numbers, my looking for seven thousand five
hundred and ninety six. I never see you. I see that number everywhere. Where do
people get these lucky numbers that they play in the lottery? Sometimes it's
grandma's birthday. Sometimes sometimes it's just a number that you feel is my
dad is a lucky number. What is it one like I'd say it publicly,
I'm not giving away the luck, not giving away the magic. I mean it has it
for him? Does he play the, has he ever won the lottery? He's never won the lottery, but
he he's still he's been using this lucky number for everything his whole life. But what is
there besides the lottery to use a lucky number for? Just anything where a number can be used.
What is another thing where you use a number? A password? Yeah, like phone number. You can't
choose your phone number. Yeah, you don't choose your phone number, but just like, you
know, just saying a number, pick a number. You can put your lucky number and you pick
like a six digit number. They want one and ten. It's not a six digit number.
This number is a five digit. It's a two digit number. You put your lucky number
in your password so that it logs. You make sure you log in every time. 69?
Wait, it says 69.
Was that close?
I'm never gonna tell you my dad's number. 23 Michael Jordan. No. 23 Lebron
James. No. 24 Kobe Bryant. No.
fucking what's another basketball player.
Forty-four already. Oh, no for I'm not even going to say yes. If you get it
forty-seven Andre Kalushnikov. No. Okay.
I'm not going to tell you
whatever do you're a bitch. No, I can't take. I'll tell you my lucky number
right now. Go ahead three. It's not three
- one
- three. So if you want to have a battle about it, we can't six six six.
That's the unluckiest number you can imagine. That's why you reclaim it.
You can't reclaim the 666. The devil has that on lock.
I bet that your dad's lucky number is like 13.
No. Come on.
Because it's ironically a lucky number.
People say lucky 13. It's not ironic.
That's a thing people say. People say that as an ironic thing because 13 is so unlucky.
52.
7 is a lucky number.
41.
14.
stop 15, 16, 17, 18,
22.
I can't jinx a lucky number for it's not jinxing. It is jinxing it. It's not
jinxing it to give away. If it were you just you guys, that's okay. So when the
camera, you have to keep in mind what's going on here, what we're doing right
now, this is not a safe place for me to share
to hundreds of thousands of people. I'll tell you my dad's lucky number. That's
really rude of you to do as I don't know what it is, but I'll text him and I'll
ask him see what it's like. Hey, what's your lucky number?
I haven't texted in six months. Hey, what is your lucky number?
That's not that bad to ask. That's what I'm saying. I don't think it's I think
you can get him a jersey. I'm just playing it safe or get like a hat for
him. It lives. What if I told you what if I said my dad's lucky number and he
died tomorrow? Well, I do think what if I don't say I think of us three, I think
easily the most superstitious one. You find synchronicities in almost everything.
I find all types of synchronicities. Patterns.
Patterns. When you told the story earlier about watching Ghost Hunters, I would not
have even thought of the betrayal that I was committing by watching that show.
It's Ghost Adventures.
See, I don't even know the name of it.
Ghost Hunters, Matt Schoolworth.
Oh really?
I don't even know if that's the show.
He said he knows them. Ghost Hunters was the first one on A&E.
I remember that show. So yeah, that's what I thought he was talking about.
See, I was I was so confused and
uneducated. I wouldn't even know when I was betraying him,
but you you were clear. You knew the betrayal and also as you were betraying
him, you knew that it was going to come back to bite you. I figured and then
when it did you were and you were looking for the bite. Also, yeah, the
bite you were you were on the hunt for a bite. Honestly, what I did not think
of the betrayal at all. And then I was not that I was just watching it and
and just my my complete honest reaction is I like was walking back to the trip
when I saw the screen and I saw the like KKK members of just my house. What the
hell
what the hell is this?
They change out loud,
it's like what the hell is this
jumping guy on the treadmill, hitting it at maximum speed and just running like
you never have before in your entire life.
yeah, but I did I did just fully of a what what is going on, but I didn't
think about it till afterwards. I think that every single machine at the gym
should have a TV on it. Yeah, most of the TVs don't work. There's one where it
works.
Thank you. Thank you. Let them know. Fix your damn TV. Fix your TV, man.
'Cause I go to the gym. You still go to that same gym. They play Impractical
Jokers. Yes. Yeah. And Practical Jokers friends and I will tell you that is the funniest show
I've ever seen in my life. In practical joke. I had never watched it before. I started going
to the gym here. That show is amazing. It is when they have been on that show for a
minute for a long time. When they make him work, when they make each other work at like
a Dunkin Donuts or whatever. It's funny. They have some really funny stuff in there. Tell
her you're going to kill yourself. He goes, I don't want to tell her that. That will be
That is amazing. Those guys have really done something special.
The Tenderloins.
That's a good idea for a show.
That's their name.
It's the best idea ever for a show.
They're a sketch troupe.
Really?
They're called the Tenderloins, yeah.
I didn't know that. I knew Sal was a stand-up.
When they go on that cruise, the cruise is them doing sketches.
Why are we not on the lineup for that cruise?
I have no idea why we aren't.
We should be on a cruise lineup.
I was talking to Eric the other day about us doing a Joy Tactics Potabelt list cruise.
On a canoe.
Not on a canoe.
We could fit more people on a canoe.
I think my uncle has a boat.
I mean we could get...
I don't know him that well, but also his boat is definitely not big enough to house all
of us.
We could get 100 people.
Not on that boat.
Not on that boat, but if we could get a boat that has 100 people and we could get everybody
eat something and we charge everybody $50,000, $40,000.
We could maybe eat something.
Yeah, that's how it would be.
just eat you eat you get on the boat on the boat, my corn dogs, hot dogs,
hamburgers, well the menu, just burger, basically every meal would be designed by
one. It's a six month cruise, yeah, yeah, we do the programming, it's a six month
cruise. How long are cruises? I mean, I think, depends on the cruise, yeah, yeah,
because I can't imagine being on a boat for like longer than a week and liking
it. Doesn't, might be ginants do a cruise? They do a cruise with the guy who did
still alive. John, no way. John, Jonathan, Jonathan, Colton, Colton, yeah, and
Paul and Storm. I don't know who that they all do a cruise. They do a big
cruise. 311 got a cruise with like did a cruise sugar ray and stuff and that
seems like the greatest cruise cruise. People die Natalie Holloway.
Often pretty often is that that's
who am I thinking of? Is that her Natalie Holloway? Your your even
Van der Sluyt or something killed her. He's in the news right now. What are you
talking about? Talking about that girl who got pushed off a cruise line or
something. I just saw the video of the kid who jumps off the cruise and just
dies instantly. Yeah, that's sad man. Yeah. Oh, I do. I keep I never watched
that one. I kept seeing it come up. I like why I don't want you to watch this.
What is this? I need to get this dirt off of my fucking screen man. Yeah, I
need to stop watching this HBO show. I need to stop watching the HBO show. What
happens in it. I've just been walking behind the couch while the girl watches. And I only
get for whatever reason walk into the most disgusting, I think the whole show is probably
disgusting because I only, when I walk in it's all the weekend saying show me your fucking
stinky, show me your butt from the back with your stinkiness. Your butthole is green. Put
honey on your butt. It's this kind of stuff. Put honey on your butt. Put grape jelly on
on your but please plant green, please, please,
so I think
put honey on your but if HBO wanted to give such a Maren Cohen that money and
he did that show and it was bore at instead of the weekend, be the funniest
show for the all amazing bore at on your but yeah, that sounds funny right if
they were playing it for laughs and not not like oh, we're making people wet at
their house. Yeah, that's like you for you make my wife wet
you for you guy. It's a you for you guy and he was like what if
I make the girl 18 this time and now he's like okay, and now
she can get all sexual, but they get a show on the
titty's and buttholes and you for you all and they're supposed
to be eleven years old. Yeah, it's a middle school. I'm gonna
kill you. It's supposed to be the spiritual successor your
I'm going to kill you. It's a spiritual successor to recess. No fucking way. I swear to God.
Spinelli's in it? Spinelli's in it. And she's all grown up. No, they're not even grown up.
They're supposed to be the same age. All grown same up. I'm going to take him out. Euphoria
the creator, I'm going to shoot you in the head. They got the kid with the backwards
hat? PJ. That kid was cool, man. I'm going to be real. I thought that that kid was cool
I copied most of my life off of them.
Yeah, I think that they should make recess again.
Oh really?
Oh, okay.
Alright, we'll end the podcast on that.
That's a banger to end on.
Yeah, they should make recess again.
Do we have info for anybody?
Yeah, we can get to the shareholder meetings next Friday, which would be the 23rd, I think,
6 p.m. June 23rd June 23rd mark your calendars make sure I come slash shows
world's biggest army port of call go on a sketch show with us home planet and
Pierce Campion and it's gonna be very fun and basically it's gonna be videos live
performance of sketches as well as other funny tidbits what else I will there
It will be a t-shirt cannon. I will be at the show watching TV tonight, maybe
watch an episode of Peep Show. Oh, might read a little of my book. Oh, will you?
And perhaps I'll have dinner.
Okay, bye.