I
okay,
you can't do that. I clap keep that in the
way. Okay, clap clap for real. I did clap. I heard you already. You didn't
miss the way
did you ever know how to do a turbo far with your leg with my leg where you put
you do that, but you put it under your knees and then you put your legs under
your knees and they could go.
That shit made me laugh in gym class.
Let's see.
My hands are too dry right now.
I've never been able to do that, man.
I've been able to do it a few times, but my hands don't get so wet, maybe.
Speaking of farts, I seriously think yesterday,
I think, and I already, Juby already heard this.
You had a turd blast?
No. Well, yes. But I think that I farted.
Go figure.
here. I think I farted and I think I genuinely ripped my asshole. Yeah, when I
was a lot fatter, I used to get that did nothing for you. No, you had to be at
this. I asshole's been hurting for two days. I think buddy, I think it means
you're getting it.
You think I'm getting fat fat people fart hard. I used to when I was when I was a
lot bigger when I was like two hundred thirty pounds. I
I think I had hemorrhoids, maybe when I was I never farted once when you were
three hundred and seventy pounds. Yeah, I kind of miss that's what I wait. I'm
just a big Cameron. Yeah, yes, you're going around like a balloon. We used to
play
yesterday. You say yesterday, yesterday, that's fire. Yeah, you do need to lose
some weight. You are disgusting to look at. It's like the whale when I come in
here. Yeah, as you'll be blowing my hole.
Damn,
Here's what me and Patrick were doing last night.
Every food has its taste, just like every drink has its ice.
Just like every...
(applause)
Pretty good.
Every taco has its hot, hot sauce.
No, that's not true. Not every taco has hot sauce, first of all.
Second of all, the funny thing is to make it really big in general.
in general. Okay, so maybe every food and drink just like this is just off the
top of my head, but
blanket every sauce has its cap. The one that was sticking in my head from the
other day that that's been stuck with me was was breaking bad better call. So
the wider and adventure time
watching TV
watching
oh yeah and is doing ten thousand verse
the office and peep show and also i'm watching what's a one glee. My
children are watching shows to they are watching veggie tales, cocoa, melon,
Daniel, tiger, G tails and sponge bob to
the big bang theory and also day
Cameron's angle is fucked up again.
Cameron angle, like camera angle.
Oh yeah, that's something for sure.
Now we each got our own camera. Wow.
Okay.
Yeah, I haven't been watching much TV recently.
I just have been watching TV.
I actually watched a few episodes this week,
last week, but honestly it feels wasteful because like I'm waste like
this could be going to someone who wants to watch it. Yes, and they're like I
always think this could be going to this electricity could be going to a
somebody in the dark in Africa, a dark. I don't think they have the I think
they all have electricity in Africa. Now you think they all have electricity in
Africa. We don't even have electricity in America. Well, I said it faster than
you. So I get you that one. I was trying to think well what I think most here
And then you said in America, so I changed to copy you. Most of Africa has
electricity. We need to do an Africa tour. Yeah, I need to be and I'm not
saying I'm not saying US. So I want to be in Africa, taking pictures, safari
photos of us with a dragon. When I was in or a lion, Mexico,
whatever they got in the Serengeti. When I was in a when I was in a Mexico,
and we were hanging out with this couple who was from Europe, and they were
tell they were like kind of like those world traveler types where they're
like yeah, I'm from Romania, but we were in like we how we went to Sweden last
like last month or whatever, but they're telling us that they went on a safari in
Africa and it sounds like actual hell. It's not like the worst trip you can
ever. It sounds like Africa, it just on a safari because you have to the animals
are awake at like only awake at like four AM. You have to you like wake up at
three AM and then you like have to go and you have to stay on the move,
because if you stay in any one place too long, like the lines and the hyenas will
come get you because you're like sleeping. You know, she was telling us
this thing. We're like she like got up and there was just like a hyena just
watching her and just slowly walking towards her and they gave her a
walkie-talkie to tell if like an animal is coming after them. She's like
there's a hyena coming after me and they're just like no respond. The whole
thing with the because hyenas love to laugh well, but so tigers and lions and
bears, oh my all of these creatures, if they're in a zoo or a some kind of
captivity. They're much more likely to attack people because on a safari, they
think that the car is a big thing. They think the car is one big monster.
They take the cars and they put like a big vinyl wrap. I don't know.
They put a big vinyl wrap over the car to make it look like it's some kind of
like dinosaur, like elephant or something. Because they still got that in
their brain.
yeah yeah, that's what they know. What you know the we do they take the red
nose. They take the red nose and there were the antlers and they put on the
car yeah
that's one reindeer that no animal would ever put a humans on board bumper
sticker. Yeah, a little white lines like oh, oh, I'm not going to I'm not going
to attack this thing yeah, because of the paperwork I'd have to do and like
insurance company. I think that any animal that attacks somebody. Oh, we
didn't talk about the monkey torture thing. Oh yeah, we've been talking about
that for years.
What do you talk about? We talked about the monkey, the
Facebook page. Yeah, oh, okay, wait, it was that guy from that Facebook. I
think so. I think that's well anyway. I think that I mean I don't know if it's
all if I assume that there's probably multiple like kind of splinters cells
and torture groups. Yeah, monkeys, yeah, they're all on telegram because you
but yeah, I imagine that this this torture monkey group maybe might not
also be the ones who are all on YouTube. It might not be the same. I didn't read
anything about it, but I did see a headline that was like monkey torture. I
didn't read all that much about chopping off fingers. Apparently, the guy got
started by tickling the yeah or no, not tickling sorry. He was and they call him
the torture king baiting him with which say monkey torture king yeah, yeah, he
probably wouldn't be that good at torturing a human. No, he could be
really good at torture. I'm not that hard to torture a human because you just
up off the fingers. It's the same thing. He's really good at torturing humans that love
monkeys. That's true. You don't really have to have a mini night system. You don't really
have to have like an imagine, you don't have to really be creative if you're torturing
someone. You just have to do, it's not like you're getting tortured like, "Wow, this guy's
really good at torturing me." He knows, he's coming up with wickedly clever ways to...
I'm going to be honest. Plus they're just copying Saw and Hostile the whole time. I'm
going to be completely honest. I do not understand torture at all. Me neither. And I don't know
why you would do that. Me neither. For information. Straight up. Well, but that's it. But what
you gonna this guy's looking for bananas why is he torturing these monkeys? In cases of
information and maybe power. I think it's about power. Yeah but you already have so much power
over a monkey. Wait not true, not true they got poop powers. No but you can put it in an outfit
you can dress up you can make a monkey look like Mr. Incredible. I think the reason you torture
a monkey is because you realize that you never have power over a monkey because they can just
go live in the woods. Yeah but you can do that. No not this. No you can't live in the woods. So
So you think that he tortured these poor little monkeys out of jealousy?
No I think he was a pedophile and that was the closest thing to a kid that he had in
his life.
They were probably jumping on his bed all night.
He had more monkeys in his life than kids?
Yeah I think so.
Said that in the article.
No it didn't.
I heard it.
I heard the article I read was that he was a doctor and a mommy kept calling him because
they were jumping on the bed.
So he was he's finally snapped.
A mommy monkey?
Yeah.
we call the doctor and the doctor said no more monkeys jumping on the bed and he
snapped. Oh, is that would actually be a fucking sick gritty movie to make yeah
the gritty reboot of no more monkeys jumping on the bed doctor coming in
and he's like he's like a fucked up like he's a fucked up. That Michael
villain doctor, Michael Shannon face, he has goggles or you can't see his eyes
and it's like let's say handle these monkeys. Let's go talk to these
that would be too scary
and all the monkeys are a g i andy circus down like like serial killer movie,
like they're making one of those like jeffrey dommer ted, but yeah and it's
like it's like it's the thing where like the neighbor knocks on like
jeffrey dommers doors like it's like it's my neighbor. I like shit near a
little weird in here and jeffy. I was like
I don't have a
funny buddy. I got oh okay. Hey my bad man. My bad. Hey me and the missus are
having a cookout next week. He's going to come through. Oh that's Smeagol's
voice.
Not really, it's just an evil voice. It was kind of Smeagol's voice. I could
have, I could have shmeaged it up.
Shmeaged it up. Did you guys play the Smeagol game? No, I want to. It looked
fun, but it should have been. It looked really funny. It should have been, they
put him in New York City, make it like Spider-Man. Yeah. That would be a much
better game. Tell him to make a sequel. If you- Every game should be the main
character in New York City. If you are a video game modder, if you mod video
games, if that's your thing, if that's your hobby, you get that Smeagol game
right now. You change the map to Times Square using Unity or Havoc or whatever
engine it was in. You change that map to Times Square. You put a full pedestrian
like walking stuff, pedestrian AI, hot dog vendors, Elmo, fucking everything
it's in Times Square and Smiegel has to walk up to them and go. I want a video
game where you play as the costume guys in Times Square. Yeah, that's a, oh,
it's a good idea. It'd be like that game with the Tokyo Jungle where, like, the
dog you play is like the different animals. Did I ever tell you guys what
happened to me with the postal and he snaps with the costume people in Times
Square when, when we were filming that video with Alex and Joe? Would they got
mad at you or something. They captured me yeah. I was that video. I was
wandering around New York yeah and we were in Times Square and we didn't use
it because I guess there wasn't good footage of it, but I was like going up
to the I was going up to the costume people and being like who are you? What
are you supposed to be and then they all immediately I did it. I said it to one
person. They all like got wind that I was talking to one of them and they all
encircled me literally like actually surrounded me. We're coming over like
picture picture picture, and then I was like I was trying to like get through,
and I like I saw they had that you know they have the big transformers yeah.
There was like a giant bumblebee guy and I was I was like walking towards him
and being like who are you and then he like went to like to like hug me like
he put his arms around and he like he like really lightly touched me, but it
like bump me forward and I like smacked my against his cost in the bumblebee
and I smacked my head against the bumblebees like torso and I went out and
man, all of the costume people and she was scattered.
Dude, they're so afraid of hurting somebody. They get sued a bunch, I've
heard. There's no way people are suing them. Don't they get sued? There's
always picture, there's like pictures I've seen of like Elmo getting arrested.
But that's not for being... I don't think it's... You don't get arrested
when you get sued. Yeah. He maybe got mad. Yeah, you do.
Don't, don't, don't. He maybe got mad at somebody. Come on. He maybe got
mad at somebody, tried to hit him or something. 'Cause that's how much else
He was arrested for allegedly groping a 14 year old.
Oh, okay.
Look at that fucking picture though!
Go back to the last one.
Yeah, that's a pretty poor, that's a piss poor Elmo costume.
I'm going to be completely honest with you.
His eyes are in two different directions and this lady doesn't even know that she's one
of the most famous women in the world right now.
This lady doesn't want to, doesn't want to look at him.
We could do that.
I think we I mean we always could use some extra money. I don't know you guys. I
could so what if we went what if we went and we dressed up as something easy like
characters from the office or yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah, we're famous enough. We
could just go as ourselves. That's real shit yeah, I just feel like I didn't
picture with us. I forgot how famous we are. Yeah, that were perfectly famous
to be amazing. Do you want a picture of yeah picture with on a picture with me?
Yeah, but we address as each other. I'm with the other two. You had to dress it
around here somewhere. That'd be the good trick. I don't want to dress up as you. Why?
Me neither. Gotta wear a funny hat. I don't want to dress up as either of you. I dress
modestly. I don't want to dress up as either of you. Really? I dress modest. Really slut?
Your clothes would be too small on me. I don't dress like a slut whatsoever. You do dress
like a slut. My clothes would be too small. I wear a large shirt. You're wearing a slut's
outfit. It's too small for me. I'm fully cut. You can't even see my wrists. You look a smalza
I'm a normal sized guy. I do think I'm shrinking. You're shrinking. It's just the chair, man.
I used to play, when I used to play basketball, I could grab the rim. Right. I was heavier
than I was then. I was heavier than I am now. Yeah. It was a little tight. Yeah. No, it
was in my front yard. Yeah. It was on your door. Yeah. I used to be able to palm the
ball too. Golf ball. You know what it is, is you're playing on real streetball courts
now. That's right. I hate street busy. These people are cooking me on the street ball court.
Actually no, I played basketball the other day and I was frying. You were playing against
Noah that's a different thing. No, I beat Noah really easily. But me and Sam went over
to a court in Williamsburg and I played against these. Where did you go? Reggaeton? I don't
know what the hell you're talking about. North Rodney Park. There's no skating at this park.
like two little ledges at this one basketball court, but it's off of Metropolitan. Yeah,
it's like near rocker.
Rola near rocker. Oh, okay. All right. Never mind. I think of a different place. Anyway,
I am glad we got that reggaeton chopped out. Yeah, I was it was amazing. It was my first
time playing basketball in like years and I just so happened to play against like four
like five foot Dominican guys. Yeah, it's always just blocking the shit out of them.
And I was talking shit too. I get mean when I play basketball.
You get mean when you play any game.
That's not true.
Yeah, it is true.
What game have you played with me that I get mean about?
I don't play with you anymore because of that.
What game do I make you...
Warzone during COVID. You would tell me how bad I suck.
Because you suck.
Yeah, I know.
You play on like a funny mouse pad that's this big with the highest sensitivity ever
and you just walk around, you look at the ground.
That's how you play shooters.
I like to take in my environment.
Do you think you're competitive?
No.
Are you competitive with skating?
No, not at all.
Yeah, how could you?
That's why I do it.
Because it's the least competitive thing to do.
Because it's not one versus one.
Well, unless you play skate.
It's one versus myself.
Unless you play skate.
It's man versus machine.
Man versus environment.
Oh yeah, MVE.
But I was asking about reggaeton because that's where I got my two clips in Blaine's video.
That's huge.
Those clips, man, those are just so fire.
Yeah, and they're at the park that Caleb was at.
He had a one second grind.
I almost can't believe that you guys were in the same place.
That trick is actually hard.
That's a front crook.
That's a front crook on a ledge that you had to pop out of.
I think he jumped.
Yeah, there was a crook in that video.
Yeah, yeah.
Somebody breaking the law.
Breaking the law.
Back crook.
If I was a mayor of New York, I would literally, I wouldn't even be arresting skaters.
He did.
There's a video of him at Borough Hall.
I would be distributing drugs to skaters.
As if they can't get it themselves.
But I would be flooding the streets.
Every skater, I would have Badger from Breaking Bad sitting in every skate park handing out
dime bags of whatever.
I would be distributing free boards and yeah, they're landmines and the wheels are black
bombs with fuses.
But there's a video of Eric Adams.
It's like the day after he just got the Brooklyn Banks back and it's a video of him just like
telling people to stop skating at Borough Hall.
And people were, "How dare he?"
what the fuck is wrong with this guy? He is doing too much. See, but the day that he
goes up like Obama announcing Osama's death and says, 'Every skater has been
killed in the, in the entire city, we kill every skater.' Or, 'We got Tony Hawk.'
Just for no reason, Tony Hawk lives in another state. Yeah. We got him. Don't
even try. This is, this is a message to you skaters. Tony Hawk is sitting in a
cell somewhere and we put the guy from the green mile in there. Michael Clark
Duncan, yeah, but this time he does not have powers. He's and he's angry. We put
his body in there, it's taking up the entire cell and they would go rose.
Well, I'm going to stop skating. Then the skaters, the graffiti artists, the
people who the music listener louders in the buildings, the people who yes, yes,
by the way, music listener louders and I have some amazing news. Yeah, my
Somebody's here for you.
For me?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's for you, Caleb.
Okay, I'll go get that.
And then I have amazing news, but continue.
What is this, mail?
Yeah, that's a mail.
What is he saying?
His shirt says Nalc.
Is he a Nalc Boys fan?
Is that a Nalc Boys shirt?
I wonder what this is.
I wonder.
I think it's just a letter for either us or the people who live in the store.
It's a letter?
Maybe it's an eviction notice.
Yeah, it's probably an eviction notice.
It could be funny.
It would be funny if it was an eviction notice.
Yeah, that's probably how we would find out is through the mail.
Yeah.
We would find out through the mail.
funny if it was an eviction notice. Yeah, that's probably how we would find out is through
the mail. Yeah, we would find out through the mail. What are you talking about? We would
our landlord would call. What are you doing? Do you know what that letter is? Probably
like an electric bill or something. Probably an eviction notice. Why would it be? Is it
an eviction notice? Caleb? No letter. It's for me. Letter for you. For you. A secret
secret admirer. That's not it is that was your secret admirer. I'll get it.
I'll read it to you right now. If you don't believe me, all right, go get it.
He got some water with him to bro. He got two different cups. He's got two. He's
using four cups. Look at for one drink of water, four cups. He's using four
fucking cups for one drink of one drink of water for putting his lips onto all
four. It is incredible how wasteful he is. Okay,
my letter from the secret admirer.
it's the con intervention. No, it's not.
Dearest Caleb,
your bill breakdown.
Dearest, dearest Caleb, your bill breakdown.
There is a turnoff notice on this bill.
Set up a payment agreement to pay your past due balance to
ensure your service is not turned off. Your down payment
can be as low as 15% and your balance can be paid off over 12
months. You know it's a turn off talking about these damn down payments.
Motherfucker. How's that? A letter from a secret admirer. You don't know what
you're talking about. Yeah, but they were saying they're telling you what
to do to not turn them off. Oh, true. So they were like, you need to pay up
and you need to pay me money. And you also need to start dressing less like
a slut. I need a sugar baby. I think you need a sugar baby. I have a wife.
I have to spoil your wife. You know what? A real sugar baby is a lot of
all these people. It's an animal. It's a baby. It's a food. Get a baby. You
cannot have a kid yet. Why? Because I would feed it booze. I would you would
be
you will not be you were going to try to be uncle Patrick. You will not be
uncle Pat. I honestly not to your day. I don't want you to take this the way
that it sounds, but you're dangerous to have around a child. I'm not dangerous
to have around a child. I have you are not in not in the way that you will hurt
them. I don't think I have no I do think that you will ruin them. Yeah, I think
that if I left my kid with you for a weekend, it would be I'd need a new
I may have talked about this before, but
my nephew did flip off his mom. Yeah, well, there it is, and it was a fight
between her and her baby daddy and
little did they know they know they deduced it pretty quick that I was the
one that taught him how to flip off. You taught him that because I've been
flipping them off since he was a baby. Kids know so much more than I did when I was a kid.
My little brother, there's a video of him when he was six years old. When I was six
years old, I didn't know how to cuss. There's a video of him.
Well, who was he around?
He was around me and my brother, and we were in the car, and my brother took a video of
him, and he looks in the camera and he says, "Fuck, fuck, fuck, bullshit, asshole."
What? How do you learn that at six years old?
I don't think I cussed around my parents until I was probably 22.
I'm here. Yeah, I didn't cuss until I was eighteen. I remember really my my mom
used to all the time. My mom and my stepdad, they used to do this move. My
dad, I don't I haven't heard him say anything above the B word. He's kind of
sticking in the PG range, but my mom and my stepdad when I was growing up, they
would say like instead of saying like fuck that, they'd be like that. Oh, they
just mouth it. I'm almost a sugar. Oh sugar. How's that a cuss? That's the
opposite of one saying that's and that's like a blessing. It's the complete
opposite of poop sugar yeah P. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, P is not the
opposite of poop. P and poop are synonymous or in the same family tree.
Here's what I was talking to my wife about last night. This is the kind of
conversations we have. Is a vagina the opposite of a penis? Oh, here's a
conversation I was having. No, they're in the same tree. Well, she said they
were like brother and sister, and I said,
I said no brother and sister you they shouldn't be having. They shouldn't be
having sex with each other. They should at least be fifth cousins. Here's what I
said. I said I what here's the conversation conversation that we were
having last night. I was asking if I
became paralyzed and I into the position where I was on all my all force hands and
knees. Would you take care of me for the rest of my life to a dog's position?
Yeah, I've told her so I've told my wife so many times if I'm paralyzed, she said
yes. She said yes, that's good. I've told my wife so many times if I lose an eye,
if I lose a toe, you're a you can leave you can at least cheat on me.
She lose it
your pinky toe yeah, you just hard for you to balance a little bit. You just
have to work in she's like move you come home. No, I'm trying to her with
if I lose all my train run on her
all these guys lined up out the door. Yeah, if I lose all my limbs and all my
senses and I'm
I'm literally a hair. Yeah, I exist as a hair, a piece of hair with a brain
stuck to it. She better stick with me and if I get long COVID or something and
I'm stuck in the hospital and I have the tubes in my mouth, I don't want the
photo of her holding my hand. I want to disappear. Yeah, I want no photos of
being in the hospital. Yes, I want to be gone. So yeah, I do not want any
photos like that, especially not because the thing is it's going to she's at a
blink on a concert next. Yeah, exactly. That's what I want. Exactly. I want.
She's gonna. Tom and Mark on stage. She
is playing the drums.
Jonah tits at Adam song.
No, I but I don't want to haunt the next the next husband. I do because I know
that I will die young. Yeah, this is I've known this my whole life. This is why I
I live so dangerously me too, but so I know that I'm not going to be here only
one, so I don't want to ruin it. You know
this isn't fully married man. What I'm not going to be the only one
I'm going to die one day and she's going to want to date some old guy. Even
if I even if I die, I want to be kept in a Tupperware in the fridge.
I want the I want to has been to open up the fridge, eat a slice of cold pizza on
Sunday morning and eat your nose.
It's a piece of
looking right at you to look at every single day. I want to be there. I don't
want to be there. I don't want to be there. I'll be there whether or not she
knows it.
If I'm going to be a ghost, you're going to haunt her. There's going to be like a
piece of like maybe my arm is going to be hidden in the apartment, but I'll be
on maybe my leg arm is hidden. My arm is I cut off my arm before I left, so
there leaves a pay a bread crumb leaves a bread crumb trail. We're not talking
about just leaving. No, I'm going to just leave. I think I think the best
argument against ghost existing yeah is that because if you were a ghost,
wouldn't you try all the time to just like watch TV or something to pass the
time? Yeah, unless I'll try to go in the TV. Here's what I think. Maybe ghost
can be real, but there is something so incredible in the ghost world that we
I can't even imagine that is so great that you get like you before you die
you're like okay. I'm going to I'm going to prove that that ghost exists. I'm
going to come back as a ghost. I'm going to haunt my family members. I'm going
to show them that I'm still alive and then you get there and they have some
new type of TV or something where you're it's so good that you don't even use
like I don't even need to contact the world living. I don't even want to turn
on or off any lights. I don't want to moan and drag chains. Yeah, I literally
I want to play this new ghost video game that they only have here for the rest of
eternity. Maybe they have some like contract that says that like if you
you right or a contract. If you try to contact the outside world, you are not
going to be able to play this ghost video game that we invented and check it out.
You get a limited point. And my kind of imagination, the good-, you don't even
need a contract, the game is just so incredible that it's all you want to do
forever. The afterlife. I thought it was like an ultimatum in my head. No, 'cause
I kind of have a positive, optimistic imagination. The afterlife is almost
certainly a dimensional shift, where you start off, you're in the first dimension,
second. We've both we've all been first and second. Now we're the third. The next
one is going to be the one where we're at first and second. We were we were
drawing this. We were drawing and then we were sperm. No, you can't even see
these dimensions, but we are in we were so these aren't the shapes dimensions.
These are just different types of dimensions, different types of
dimensions. And now the fourth one, the fourth one, we're going to be in. We're
in the third one right now. I thought we were in the fourth one. We're going to
be in the fifth one. No, no, no, no. The fourth one is is time. That's the fourth
dimension. What's the fifth dimension? They don't even know. Fifth dimension is
Ascension though. Ascension. No, see that's what I'm saying. I think you go ten and then
you prestige back to one like Call of Duty. I was back on those Facebook groups.
Yeah. Ascension, fifth dimension. Ascension Facebook groups and there's this lady. Who's that
dude? Oh the guy we used to love. Yeah. Desmaine Blu-Ray. Desmaine Blu-Ray. But there's
this lady who she she posts in this group all the time and it's actually
she really said, but
continue she it's also really funny. She like she has a basically. I think she
she has like her eight year old son. She always post her a picture like a
picture video of her eight year old son and like with a caption like OMG, my
eight year old son, just like just explain to me what God is and he just
told me how we're going to travel to the next dimension and it's always like
this really long thing and she posted one. I was like my eight year old son
has evolved past the need for food. I know I have to feed him, but he says
that he doesn't want food anymore because he's transitioning to become an
age
stuff like
Jesus so crazy and the and that she like I was at first. I thought she was
just crazy and she's just posting pictures of her son and then she post
videos where his son is like mom. God is that is energy mom. Don't you
understand and it's fully the kid who's like doing it to her yeah? Well, he's
he's going to be like he's a actual X files kid. That's going to be coached
saying it. There's no way he could be a star seed. He said that's true. What
did he say a sacred star child?
He said he was doing some crazy thing where he was making the word energy
turn into the word God or something whoa and he was like going through this
whole God's name is region. He was like oh no, you know he was saying he was
I was he was going like mom, mom, energy, enter, G, enter, God,
energy, inner God, what is sad or your energy? Yeah, enter, G, energy, yeah,
that's your energy. That's what I would be a thug child. Yeah, sacred,
child, sacred, thug, child, sacred thug is a sick name
for a guy to have sacred thug or like an album. I guys name an album cover
album name sacred thug okay sacred thug by Patrick yeah.
Imagine that album cover i'm like an angel and i'm wearing like my fooboo and
my echo shorts fab four angels by fab back yeah. Oh my God, a bad for angels
by a you got a fat echo location, you're wearing your you're a bat, you're
wearing your F F P B C for Patrick by Cameron
one of the two yeah, but this one is and it's that's right. You should just make
that shirt for yeah.
There's a white t shirt with with some sharpie on it. Yeah, P B C and it's got
like it's got like old English that is metallic, but also glittering and it's
a sacred fight. Honestly guys, if I knew how to make a shirt, I'd do that, but it
seems way too complicated. Yeah, shirt making is complicated. I am done doing merch. We don't
need to do any more merch. What we need to do is a full fashion brand. Yeah. And we need
to have a fashion show. That's a good idea. Okay. I have a ton of ideas for clothes. Well,
Noah has a screen printing at the apartment. Pants made of shirts, this kind of thing.
Shoes made of hats. Noah, we can do all this stuff at my apartment. Noah has all this. I
had an idea for clothes a week or two ago. What was it? Fishnet basketball shorts. Oh,
Oh damn, that's good right that that's high fashion. That is that would that
would literally go crazy. Wouldn't it go crazy on mulberry street, bro and also
is that is that in a fairy tale world?
Why don't also go crazy on mulberry street in the fairytale world? Isn't
that where the that's where shrek lived? Yeah, why don't more guys wear fish net
guys see through stuff with you? You can see your dick guys do that who go to
which guys bushwick dude. There's fucking guys guys. I've never seen guys
with fish nets. You've never seen guys with fish nets on their cock. I'm
saying like it. So for this, that would be really embarrassing for that guy to
dunk on you. Yeah, it's like his nuts are actually worse. You smell his nuts.
But normally it smells on a good
that's a good actually. That's a really good question. When Patrick Ewing got
dunked on by
I was so nervous I was going to get questioned about the smell of my penis.
When Patrick Ewing got dunked on by Scotty Pippen and he walks over his face, it's a big,
they call it a facial in the NBA.
That's what they call it when you get dunked on like that.
Yeah.
Does he smell his nuts?
He has to.
For sure.
There's no way he don't.
The guy's been running around for an hour and a half.
Have you ever smelled basketball shorts that got sweat in them?
Have you guys smelled other guys' nuts?
Yes.
Of course I do.
I've smelled them.
We've talked about that before.
Smelled another man's nuts?
We actually already had a long discussion about that.
We were in a van.
We were in a van together for a whole month.
We all smelled each other's nuts.
but that was like but like smelling that's like that's one thing that came
to get on smell. Yeah, I mean like singular someone's not person's nuts,
because I know exactly on my nut smell. I know I'm on smell. I can smell them. I
could smell them on the street. You know when you like like a pie on a window,
don't you like leave butter out?
No, no,
I don't think butter smells. I think that's the thing when it goes bad.
You've said, do you know when you leave food item out and we both said no, you
You just leave food out a lot, don't you?
No.
You do.
Yeah, I do.
You know when you leave pork out, that's what my nuts smell like, pork fat.
Pork fat doesn't smell.
When you leave pork out?
Pork fat, when you cook it in the air fryer.
I thought that I was making cracklings the other day, because I cut off the piece of
fat on the pork chop that I had, and I realized halfway through, I was like, "Oh, that wasn't
the skin.
That was just the fat."
Just fat.
You just melted fat in the air fryer?
Yeah.
Well, you know, like the really squishy stuff?
I'm over the air fryer. Me too. I'm over it. Me too. I made some chicken tenders in it last
night. I just warm stuff up in there now. It's a microwave. I don't have a microwave,
but I do have an air fryer. It's a microwave. I made last night. It's a better micro... I
have a microwave, but I'd rather warm something up in it. Salmon is the only thing I make
in the air fryer. Salmon and asparagus. Even that though. I haven't had a microwave for
a couple of years. I think that microwaves are probably hurting lots of people. I haven't
had a microwave. Because I've been feeling amazing. I haven't had a microwave since I
as I moved into my new place, I feel incredible all the time. It's the
microwave, man. It's hurting you. It really is. I feel so amazing. People get
microwave radia-, I don't know how it works at all. Me neither. Not two inches
ago. It can't, it can't, the pain of plastic can't, that can't be protecting
you. No. No, you're done. There's no way. Especially if you open the corner.
It's going into the thing you eat. Yeah. No. And the stuff that's in the
microwave is-, it's got plastic on it. Anything that, any kind of device where
you put your head into it, it explodes. Yeah, or your dog. Yeah, that's not a
good device to be eating the food from. Yeah. Well, I mean an oven would cook
it, but it wouldn't explode. It would cook your head. It wouldn't explode.
But it wouldn't explode the head. Which a microwave would. Yeah. A microwave
does. Haven't you seen Last House on the left? Yeah, and Kick-Ass. Yeah,
and Kick-House. Dare to be stupid. Dare to be stupid. Has that happened in
Last House on the left? I think the reboot. They blow up the... Oh, I
never saw the reboot. The Urban Legend, they blow up a dog.
What are you talking about?
A movie, Urban Legend.
I never heard of that.
I heard of that.
He knows it.
Is that about like Bigfoot?
It's about...
Car door.
It's a guy who, he's like a serial killer who's based on all...
Man door, hard car door.
Mandalorian.
The Mandalorian's in it.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
It was like one of those, it's like a Scream era ripoff.
It's a really bad ripoff.
It's like I Know What You Did Last Summer type vibe.
Oh, yeah.
Where instead of movies, he's obsessed with urban legends.
So he does like Paul Bunyan, Big, that kind of thing?
No, no, those are folk tales.
Oh, La Cucaracha.
No, that's a cockroach.
La Chupacabra.
Chihuahua.
The lady who tries to dry off her dog in the microwave.
Juvio, pull up the picture of the Mexican pet.
What's that?
Just Google Mexican pet.
You've definitely heard this urban legend before.
I've never heard of the Mexican pet.
Wait, what was that last one?
Hold on, type in Mexican again?
No, go to Mexican pet.
I don't care about Google auto complete. Well, the Mexican pet is the urban
anywhere. Wait, wait, wait, somebody somebody on this computer. This is
Caleb's computer. There it is, but second first one on the left. Yeah,
that's the
yes. I looked up big Mexican guys. As I tried to make it the background of the
computer.
Okay,
look, look,
it's in the auto complete
big
I was just seeing if it was I was just seeing if it was
the Mexican Pet Urban Legend is the one where a lady goes to buy a dog from
Mexico and they're like yeah, this is a special breed of dog. It's like a
chihuahua or whatever and she takes it home and it's acting weirdly and then
that she like takes it to the vet and the vet is like lady. This isn't a dog.
This is a rat. Yeah. Oh, well, how you never heard that before? No, but I also
that's not that crazy to me. It's pretty well. It's an urban legend. It's not
people have rats all the time true. Is this a barb and legend or wiki also
this lady is probably not that smart. I'm speaking of a lady. It's an urban
legend. Well, but I'm just saying she wasn't that smart. I have I heard an
amazing joke the other day from my father in law. Do you guys want to hear
it and this is this is for him are rated. So I was pretty impressed that he did
this okay. All right, a king is in his court and he has three nights and he
tells them by the end of the year, whoever brings me the most ping pong balls gets to
inherit the kingdom.
Where is this kingdom?
China.
So he says as many ping pong balls as you can get, you get to inherit the kingdom.
Eight months later, the first night comes back.
He says, "Sir King, I've brought you two million ping pong balls.
It took me the last eight months.
I've been working tirelessly.
million ping pong balls, right? The second night comes two months after that, and he
says, Sir, I have brought you five million ping pong balls. That's three million more
than the last guy. I definitely got this in the back. This was two months later. This
is two months. So did the first guy get to keep working or was he? No, he already turned
in his balls. He was too tired, so he stopped. All right. Yeah. So the so now it's the last
day of the year, December 31st, right? The 11th hour. Okay. The last night comes in, he's
on crutches, a full cast all the way up and down his entire body, right? He has a full
body cast and he limps into the court with a rucksack on his back, right? And the king
says, okay, night, you made it here. Finally, you must have been working even more tirelessly
than the last guys. How many ping pong balls did you bring me and the guy says
oh shit. I thought you said King Kong's balls.
Pretty fire had them on this. Why did the other two guys not wait till the end of
the year to get yeah? Why did they work smarter? Not harder man? Also, I'll just
like rest among the impressive part is two months later. This guy's got more
than double the guy who worked eight months. Yeah, more than yeah, I guess so
it's pretty impressive, but also the first guy just go back. Why did he turn
I mean, you know, I mean King Kong is basically a giant monkey. Is this a
joke that your, your father-in-law wants you to do on stage? No, he just was
telling me that and, and his, and here's the rest of the family. Oh, come on,
Dad. Here's me. Oh, my God.
My God, that is the funniest shit I've ever heard.
Holy shit. Yeah, that's funny. That's seriously fun, fucking funny. And they
got mad at you for swearing to know. Don't say fun King funny, funny, funny. Don't say
fun King funny in front of my father. I thought it was pretty good. Yeah, yeah, and he said
that he heard that joke. It was the first joke he ever heard the first one ever and
I yeah, I didn't even know that King Kong back then. I didn't know if sure, King Kong's
old. Surely I was like balls. Yeah, but you're thinking Donkey Kong. You freaking donkey
ass motherfucker. Donkey Kong is barely a monkey to me. Yeah, yeah, I think where's
a tie. Well, he's barely an ape then. Yeah, he wears a tie as a job. What did they ever
explain his name? Donkey Kong? I think it was a translation error. It was supposed to
be Donkey King. Autocorrect fail. Yeah, and he's 42 years old. It is apparently. Luigi
is 22. Donkey Kong needs to start dressing his age. Put some pants on. You're 40 years
old. Come on, you're 40 years old, man. Yeah, you fucking slut ass motherfucker. Okay, so
Luigi's 22 and then Donkey Kong Jr. is 41.
So it's, I mean, being a year younger than your dad is kind of weird.
Oh, here's a question that I had for you guys. I already asked Rex this.
Do you guys feel like Jubio is a little bit
our version of Yoshi?
[laughter]
A little bit?
Yeah, I think so. I think I could see that.
So we like kind of captured him. He's kind of like blood sworn to us.
Uh-huh. Yeah. If we jump on spikes, he dies first and we get another chance.
Yeah. And he tried to turn me into an egg. He came from it. He eats every fruit he sees.
He loves eggs. He does love eggs. He actually does love it. Huevos. Yeah. Huevos.
Yeah. That's the one thing I know about him for sure is he that motherfucka loves Huevos.
He's green. He's green. Well, he is today. He's green. He is green. He's green.
he won't yeah, he won't put it on. Oh, there is there is he is. He's got a
little bit Yoshi vibes. Yeah, his tongue is as long as it is wide. So
then who is Rex? Is he like Cameron's Waluigi? Rex is not involved in any
sort of Nintendo property. Is Yoshi just a normal Japanese name? Yoshi.
So yeah, there's people named Yoshi. There's a pro skater. So is it?
So Yoshi in
in Japan is just he just has a name. Yeah, it's like Fred or something.
Yeah, that's funny. There's a dude named Yoshi Tenenbaum.
That's cool. Is he Japanese? I guess he's I think he's half Japanese,
half Israeli or something. That's one of the most fire combos you can have in the
entire country. That's exactly the name you'd expect. Yeah, Yoshi Tenenbaum. I couldn't come up with that.
I don't remember if he was in the Olympics. He might have been.
Maybe he was skating for Israel in the Olympics. Get skating out of the Olympics.
You don't need it. Yeah. Skating and swimming. Trust me. These are not sports.
swimming is for much swimming. Swimming is like the number one in anything else.
Yeah, the fucking Olympia. What make it? Why is there no football in the world?
No, it's it's the same as like, why is there no billiards in the Olympics?
That's a good question. It's a, you know, it's basically the same as fucking
running. Swimming is the same as running, but you just added another element to it,
which is why people like because the when you boil the Olympics down to its
it's essential is it's just who is the fastest in the world or in every single
yeah, but it's probably like the runner guys could probably swim faster than the
swimmers, but they just chose the better sport yeah
and swimming. They have the jump in swimmers have to eat like a billion
pounds a day. That's because they swim all day. That's the thing with a lot of
these sports is like just stop.
You wouldn't have to do any of this shit. If you just knocked it off yeah,
just knock it off. What are you doing? Also you're in a vicious cycle, the
butterfly
The butterfly is crazy. That's barely a thing. What is that? That's this one. Where they
jump out of the water and do their arms. Yeah. Oh, that's, that one's sick. No, that one
is goofy. It is goofy AF. It's so hard to do. Every time I do it, I just sit in the
middle of the pool. It's like I'm drowning in a cartoon. Yeah. That's my version of the
butterfly. Yeah. I can't do the butterfly. No. They should put that in the Olympics.
How about this? I like doing the sea serpent. Here's some, here's some things that you could
put in the Olympics, the Olympic Committee, what philosophy,
velociraptor, philosophy, velociraptor, meme contest, meme contest. Good idea.
I mean, there's it's already subjective. They're already scored off. A
scored off is actually a good idea. Typing, maybe typing, maybe it's a
beacon style. I would actually be interested to see typing, typing typists
in the Olympics or art. Yeah, that's what I mean. You already do gymnastics,
which is God, the artlympics. Well, no, just be part of the no, just be no. We
don't want the legitimacy. We want the nod from the Olympic committee. It's
just in the Olympics. It wouldn't be a whole new. It's a whole different new
time. Back flipping olympics back. They do have back flipping in the as a part
of something else, but I don't care about anything except the back flips
and they do anything besides back flips on that. They just gymnastics flipping,
but they do front flips, which are not that impressive. I could do a front
flip. You couldn't do it now. I know front flip. Turn the camera. Let's let's
Yep, turn the cameras, we'll fucking test it.
I hurt my body.
ACL. No you didn't.
He pulled his ACL last night during D&D.
No I didn't.
You did.
I'm saving you, motherfucker.
I hurt the rest of my body.
No you didn't.
Yeah I did.
I think I could do a front flip.
I think I could do a back flip.
I hurt my back doing that cold open the other day.
Really?
I went home and I was like, "Oh, what the fuck did I do?"
Swinging the sword?
What did I do? And remembered that I was like doing jump kicks.
Oh yeah.
I got a bruise on my knee.
arms on my knee. I kind of want to get into some kind of should I do boxing
think boxing and be made for me. No, is that too much? I don't want to yeah.
It's a little too much. It's too much. You would become a monster. I think I
think it's just I just think it's I have a really short arms and I'm small and
I'm way over the weight class that I should be. I think it'd be a perfect
box. I think if you're the type of person who's already working out a bunch
and then you add boxing, I think that's when you cross the line and yes too
much into what I think if you're the type of person who's your workout is
boxing, then you're a girl, then you are a girl. It's true. Girls do boxing.
They do do as and a lot of them will be like yeah, it's good for self defence.
It's like I'll let me see you square up on the subway with the crazy homeless
guy right just straight up like all right, let's box about it. No rules, but
street rules. Yeah, exactly. That's why I do street rules when I books. Yeah,
women need to be what's the kind that you bite, bite, bite, quando. No, no,
there's a kind of martial arts where it's like you bite, you scratch your
guys out. I don't know that doesn't sound like a martial art. It sounds more
just like doing stuff. Well, it may be some there's a name for doing stuff
the
kinamutai that emphasizes biting
biting, pinching,
is what it's called
sick. Oh, my God, wait, I didn't do I'd be the master of this shit. Just
fighting. He just grabbed his nuts. Oh, this is look guys. I wear a helmet. See
okay. This is a real martial art fight in the world. That's what I mean. This
is what martial arts should be look he's well okay, but now he's definitely
going to grab this guy's nuts. Yeah, he punches him and then balls twice and
then it points his finger in his face. Whoa, I got you, you're gay
punches nuts. Two times smell my finger.
That's a good idea. That's I mean that's what martial arts should be. You stick
Stick your finger in your ass, and then you chase him with it.
That's a thing that if you do it in wrestling, it's an immediate disqualification.
Stick your finger in the guy's ass?
It's called checking the oil.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
That's kind of an Urban Dictionary meme thing, I think, maybe.
Yeah.
Well, that's a thing that --
There's a sex thing called a Cleveland Steamer, and a chili dog.
That's a real --
That's a thing that when my younger brother did wrestling in middle school,
that they told him it's the most illegal wrestling move.
They told him it was the most--
- I'm sure it is.
- Yeah, you know why it's the most illegal wrestling move?
- Because it's raping.
- Yeah, sexual assault.
(laughing)
- Yeah, that's why.
- Yeah.
- I guess that's not a really good thing to tell people
is a good self-defense mechanism.
- You know what they tell you to do though,
when a pit bull has got their teeth,
they like wrapped around a--
- You put it finger in the ass.
- Like a bichon frise, yeah.
you got to check the pit bulls oil.
Yeah.
Which I, trust me, I do not want to, I do not want to check the pit bulls oil.
What you're supposed to do with a pit bull attack series, you're supposed to have a little hammer and you knock out all its teeth.
Yeah.
Yeah, even if it gets you, it's like what?
That's literally, I read that you have to put like some kind of thing in there.
Yeah, a hammer.
*mimics hammer*
Yank it back.
That makes it, I mean, this is pretty much boiling down to hurt the dog at this point.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean that's the only way you're supposed to use a laser their bite for
strength. I had it. I had it. It's incredible. I saw a video that was a
very good explanation of it was two dogs in a fight in like Central Park or
something, and people are like trying to get the dogs off each other, and the guy
said, and this blew my mind, he said, how would you feel? Of course, they're
fighting. How would you feel if every time you walked by somebody, your
boyfriend or whoever he didn't say boyfriend, whoever you're with, wanted
you to shake the person's hand. Sometimes you're not going to like the guy.
Sometimes you're just going to fight and try and get him and sometimes you
he's saying this to two women screaming about their dogs fighting. No, he
basically did a green screen video where he's on top of the thing. He's pointing
up. You see this. You see this is basically like if you had to shake hands
with every single person in the world, I would do that. If I had to shake hands
with people too, that's yeah, exactly. If I had to do that, first of all, I
wouldn't leave my house, but if I was being dragged around by my neck and
having made to shake hands with every single person. I would lash out not
even because I don't like the people, but because I was bored. I don't want to
shake your hand. I'm done shaking hand. Also, if I was bred for combat yeah, if I
would that would so much worse pound the issue. If I was my jaw strength, if I
could bite through a wooden door, if I was blood and I wasn't and I was
punished for biting through a wooden door yeah, I'd be pissed yeah. I hate
pit bulls. I don't I don't mind them that much. I just don't like that. They
exist. There are a lot of times the sweetest dogs and the meanest dogs.
Yeah, I don't care. I don't care. I don't care enough to get to know a
people. Have you ever had somebody where you've made buddy meet somebody's pit
bull and they tell you something insane? They're like you're like, Oh, how's the
dog? You like the dog? They're like yeah, he's good. He's afraid of guns.
It's like what
what yeah. Also, when did you learn that like yeah, I can't say I ever had that
That happened to my brother's dog, I think. I was like, "How is he?" He's like, "Yeah,
he's afraid of guns." I would think so.
Yeah, I would hope.
Yeah.
My cat is afraid of trash bags. I don't know if that's because he's from the outside.
My dog's afraid of trash. Anytime I take the trash out, he gets...
I'm afraid of trash bags.
They're scary. They're white.
Yeah, they're loud. When you open them up...
Yeah.
Yeah, my mom freaks the fuck out, dude. I don't know if he just saw a guy change the
trash when he was living on the streets.
probably thought the guy was going to put him in a trash bag. That's probably where he was
going when I found him. He's probably going into a trash bag. He's going there again next
time. I'm over. Did you guys know you guys weren't there? You guys were there before
because I was on the stream and then I went home. We should start cat napping. Yeah, there's
somebody else. There's somebody lost cat posters around. Yeah, I know. Oh, it's perfect time
I'm to get it to the we should walk around with butterfly nets and just we
should be setting baited trap. I saw the craziest fucking cat on a stoop the
other day. It was like so it was like it looks like it was a white cat that
turned. I knew it was great, but I had to turn black, a white cat that turned
gray from dirt is what it looked like and it had the craziest green eyes
and I
weird. I know I know, but I let me
cat's eyes are. Let me show you this cat. That's like the stereotypical cat's
high color. Let me show you what this one looked like.
You took a picture? Yeah, 'cause it looked scary. It does look scary.
Look at how scary that thing was. That looks like a wolf. Yeah,
that looks like a wolf. Yeah, that's a scary looking cat. Yeah.
Now, you're completely right. The green eyes don't really bother me though.
The green eyes are the scariest part of the way he's looking. I think the
fact that he looks like a different animal is a weird... He's got snake eyes.
He's got cat eyes. No, he's got snake's eyes with a cat's face. It is funny
that the cat looked like that and you led by telling us just all the
different colors that were
yeah, it used to be white, but that was great and the eyes are green. That was a
that was a creepy cat, though it was a creepy cat. Yeah, I did want to I did
want to shake its paw. I think my next pet is going to be a skunk skunk. You
can feel croaks skunk
that you can do that. You can get remove their stink gland. It's not good for
them. It's illegal in America. Yeah, you could also get a raccoon. You can get it
done in the UK and then have shipped over here, but they also don't stink it up
unless they're like really afraid. Yeah. So you got to become it's good for
have you guys ever been skunked? Yeah, no, my uncle did, but then my house
skunk like skunk. I got skunked around, but I didn't get skunked. I didn't get
I ran. I ran. I saw a skunk. I ran. I was walking home one night and a skunk
walked like one foot in front of me across the sidewalk and I froze like a
cartoon. Yeah, and then I didn't skunk. It's not good. You have to bathe in
honey tomato sauce. Tomato sauce is always what I honey would be to
Yeah, my uncle who lived with me, one of them, one of my uncles that lived with me had his
dog, he was walking him at night and then he got too, he tried to get too friendly with
a skunk and he got sprayed so bad that we all heard him outside go like, "Ahh!"
The dog?
No, my uncle.
Oh, okay.
And then he came back inside and he was like, "I got fucking sprayed by a skunk!"
I kind of want to get, I saw a video of somebody getting pepper sprayed the other day and it
kind of, I think it's something you need to do before you die.
Yeah, get pepper sprayed.
Are you trying to build up an immunity?
up an immunity? No, I just think I have curiosity. I can spray you with my girlfriend's pepper
spray. The girl one won't work on me. Yeah, it never works. Trust me, I spray myself every
single day. I want the one where you go with your thumb. The police one? Yeah, the police
one. The video I saw was just a guy getting pulled over and he was like, "What are you
pulling me over for?" And the guy was like, "That's it!" Right in his face. It doesn't
don't look like it feels very I want to get I want to get tased. I want to
live in that's like opposite, though sugar spray sugar spray and so yeah,
tastes too good. Well, that's what I would do. It's a bunch of people
sitting in a line protesting WGA writer strike and the I walk up and I just
spray it into their mouth. What if it's a sour? What if it's just food spray
and it makes them full so they get lazy? If someone's chasing you, you spray
food on that's a pretty good idea mouth and then they're like they feel like
they decided Thanksgiving dinner. Yeah, you know, I just want to sit down.
They don't even Thanksgiving spray. Yeah, that's such a good basically
Christmas. I'm going to spray Thanksgiving spray. Yeah, so these are
all the same effect of filling your person. So this is Easter spread with
turkey. So good turkey deep fried turkey for Christmas. An Easter meal. Yeah,
I can't lamb and ham. I think you eat lamb on Easter. Isn't Jesus supposed to
be a lamb. I think that's why you're supposed to eat him. Yeah, you eat him
all the time. The guy's the most eating person ever live. Yeah, you know the
whole thing. Isn't it funny that Catholics the it's like Catholic canon
that when you eat the piece of bread, it becomes human flesh in your body. Yeah,
really yeah, I've never had the communion because I've never been you've
never taken communion. No, because I have never I've never been confirmed
communion. I wasn't allowed to do Catholic communion. I wasn't allowed to
do CCD
because my... Are you, what do they call it, confirmed? No. Wow. Hell. My whole... Hell
vibe. Are you baptized? I was baptized. Oh. That's weird. I wasn't confirmed because my
aunt was the CCD teacher at the church that we would go to. Uh-huh. And she said she did
not want me in her classroom. Whoa. They didn't want me in the classroom. She'd rather have
you in hell. We couldn't afford it. Yeah. She didn't like me. She didn't like me at
should rather have you in hell than in her classroom. That's crazy. We couldn't
afford this easy D classes, but also like I know you were crazy as kid. I was I
would have I would have said the same. I would sit in the back. I would have
either this. Can we transfer this kid to hell? Yeah, during my during my
cousin's, my cousins, like confirmation my my cousin, who I was my cousin Rob
same age as him. I'm in the back in the quiet room where all the old ladies sit
and I'm sitting there just turning to my mom just going. This is a fucking boring.
I was in saying fucking this is so boring. Do you remember the first time you
cussed in a church? I do know I never cussed in church. I cussed in church.
Would you say damn? I said fuck. That's the first thing I ever said. You just
said fuck. I just said fuck. My buddy Jordan said you're not allowed to cuss
in church and I was like fuck that
holy and then I immediately felt like a shock of electricity in my body and
knew I'm going to hell and it basically colored the rest of my life and then I
went outside and I climbed the tallest tree on the church grounds.
Well, that's just like youth camp stuff.
That's what I used to do.
That's what your counselor wants you to do.
I thought it was cool because I would go and I would climb the tree alone.
The tree climber kid.
Yeah, and then just sit up there and wait for somebody to look at me and be like, "Look
how high I am."
Yeah.
This is me.
"Look how high I am."
The other kids are fucking.
I remember the tree climber kid in school.
Yeah, that was me.
I loved climbing trees.
I had a phase of climbing trees.
And then I grew up in a cantry.
I had a tree climbing phase.
Never?
You don't like heights. No, I mean heights. I would get up on maybe a low
branch, but yeah, I never I also just wasn't I wasn't like strong. I would get
to the top of the tree and I would wave side to side in the wind. Wow. I also
hate heights. Now that I'm thinking, I don't think any human likes heights. I
think that's supposed to like heights. No, they're not good. I did like that. I
really don't like this. I don't like even being inside in heights. Yeah, yeah. I
went. If I'm in a building that's too big, I'd get scared. If I'm in a movie
theater and I have to take an escalator up and I know that I'm on the third
floor and I know that there's
floors below me, but the tall floors, I think that's probably a measure of your
intelligence that you are, because everybody else is too stupid to get
fooled into thinking they're on the ground. I was in a building once where
like my ears, we were on the fucking penthouse. It was like me and Tom,
whoa, show, we did the show that was in a penthouse bragging and bragging
and my ears were popping my ears popped one in the elevator in the elevator, my
ears, but on the elevator and then no, but we were on the balcony after and
you were so scared. I almost threw up because I was there to I looked I looked
down and I almost threw up because of the height.
It wasn't a rag that right yeah, you were in a penthouse. I've never been in
a penthouse. You could have come to the show, been a penthouse. I have you. I
invited you. I invited you guys to come to the show. I don't want to go to a
penthouse show. I want the first time I go into a penthouse, it's going to be my
penthouse yeah, that's the plan, but they got the people who ran the penthouse.
I'm gonna have that swan made out of towels. They weren't allowed to do shows
there anymore. I want to do that the doorman said that the doorman found out
it was a ticketed event
doorman also another job in the that the people's business yeah doorman your
entire job is to get a shitty Christmas gift and fucking shut the fuck up.
Phillips Norelco one blade. Here's actually that's a great Christmas gift.
Open the door, buddy. Yeah. Hey, why don't you do your job and open the door?
You're not an undercover cop. Oh, are you? Oh, is your what's your job title?
Are you a how was your day man? No, I don't think so. So shut your trap and
open my door. Press the button.
What but for the elevator or something? I don't know what they do. I don't like
I don't like any job where you're not a CEO and you wear a suit. I don't like
seeing people every day also. I don't want to see the same guy a bunch of times.
I would really appreciate it if the people in my apartment building would move
out after a month.
His Siri responded to him saying Santa.
He called Santa?
I guess so.
Hey Santa.
It didn't work this time.
Also, I would so much rather have a security guard with a Gatling gun or
maybe a sentry turret.
Literally, what's his name from Final Fantasy VII?
my God, but anyway, I just think that doorman get rid of them or everybody
should have one. How about that? Well, actually, we're talking we're talking
about doorman the week that you weren't here as I have had. I actually have a
doorman theory, which is I think that the reason that we don't have chivalry
anymore in this in our modern world yeah is because why would you hold the door
for somebody when you can get paid for it when it's an actual job you can have?
why would you do it for free? Miss the moneymaker symposium wow that's a
really good point right like it's capitalism is basically ruining fucking
shit for us. I wouldn't take it that far, but
slow your fucking roll, but yeah I'm like I'm not going to hold that. Oh,
I'm going to hold the door for you. Okay, where's my where's my salary?
Yeah, no, where's my salary? Yeah, also I think you get paid pretty well to be a
doorman, which is you have to I mean it's where you live in the building,
that is the most now boring job of all you don't live in the bill. They don't
give you a room fuck. No, what they're doing like the nicest apartments. You
think that they're going to give it some fucking doorman. It was
probably live in the in the Freddy Krueger basement. Yeah, yeah, you live
in the Freddy Krueger basement and you get a huge pay cut. That's why you get
a free. I've always thought a fun job. It has to be to be a super. I bet that
more than fifty percent of doorman are serial killers. It's got to be way more.
it's closer to a hundred. Yeah, I think it has to be a huge percent are doing
bad and bad, bad things. Yeah, bad. If I know that they also are like every
once in a while, they're like they say something to somebody and they're like,
"Whoa, how'd you know that?" And they're like, "Well, you know, I'm the
doorman. I'm the eyes and ears of this building." It's like that shit where
you're like, "Oh, I'm so embarrassed to
say this issue I'm having to my doctor, 'cause my doctor's gonna judge me."
And they're like, "No, doctors don't judge you." And then you find out that
that they all have a secret text group and they're all texting about you. They
have every job is it's always every single job in the world always judges
you and they all have their little things. They say about you to the
therefore, their other friends who work the same job. They're doctors are
definitely doctors where when some when you walk in, they go every doctor fuck
me every single day. It's a job. There are like nobody like yeah, nobody is
definitely a doctor group. Everybody gossips about you everywhere you go.
This you break your pelvis. They make sure they make your penis look smaller
and the door man sees who you come. I seen that happen to me and the door man
sees who you come home with yeah, who you have, who what kind of friends are
having over what kind of friends you're having over, so what kind of groceries
you're bringing in groceries. I was just going to say what kind of things you're
getting on Uber eats yeah. How often you're getting Uber eats, what packages
you're getting yeah, who was it? It was Samantha on sex in the city who had sex
with her door man. They have sex with you yeah, no it was a door knob. Oh yeah,
she fucked a door knob. Yeah, she was a complete slug. Such a slut. She fucked
a door. She fucked a door and then she fucked a boat and she fucked all this
other crap. Yeah, and now that's why she's not in and just like that. Look at
this salary, doorman salary, twenty to twenty seven dollars per hour. That's
not bad. That's too much full time employment, technology, information and
internet industry. You're trying to get paid to stand. Yeah, this is bullshit and
requirements, good communication skills, bilingual, have a can do whatever it
takes attitude for
whatever it takes to open this door.
Door fit is the tallest,
in the world,
the only reason you think that actually no, I think you'd be a good bell.
Whoa, my last name ability, ability to strip and wax floors as a plus bell
hops, your waxing floors as a door man, that's a janitor's job. Yeah, that
shouldn't be that's not the door man. Yeah, that's what I would say. This is my dorm
main anything beyond that exactly. Thank you. Scroll up, scroll up. They changed it
up more, up more. They changed it from bellhop to bell person. Oh my yeah.
Notice the rainbow on the logo for this hotel. Don't give these any clicks. Okay,
get off of get off of this. What's up was hop not gender neutral. You're not
going to become a bell person. Jubio maybe Jubio, but I'm a fucking bell hop.
yeah, what's a girl bell hop? Then if a boy bell hop is a bell hip yeah, a hip and
a hop, you know hip and a hop arm transport, oh my God, no arm transport
guard, yo I would become that way to have the brains logo. Does the brings
logo have the pride flag on it too? Probably that's actually dope. I want
that on a shirt to stuff like you know, LGBT stuff like Bank of America, yeah,
yeah, that seems like a pretty fun job, because you're the whole thing is like
it's it's hilarious how hard it is to rob you. Do you guys know you guys ever
walk by an armored truck that's parked somewhere and you think to yourself like
I hope they don't kill me. Hope they don't think I'm trying to steal from
because they're covered in guns. I got my I hope they don't mistake me for a
guy who's trying to get into the truck. I was walking home at like two in the
morning a couple months ago and they were like the guys were just sitting
looking the other way with like fifty thousand dollars and twenty dollars
bills there and they're just like smoking cigarettes waiting for their
dog break to be over. I was like this would be the easy, and you know me, I'm always looking
for a lick. I was like this would be the easiest lick. Kill these two guys, take this money.
Who's going to ever know?
They got cameras all over the truck. Every single part of the truck has a camera on it.
I have a camera? Fuck it.
But here's the thing, the Brinks truck has cameras on every single part of it. Couldn't
they make an amazing reality TV show about traffic with the same truck?
Well, that's what I was going to get at is that we should do a parks and rack
about two three guys in a brinks truck. That's actually a really good idea.
Parks and driving is what it could be called parking. That's actually driving.
That is actually such a good idea. And it's a brinks truck. It has all the
cameras all over it, and it's like those three sixty cameras, and they're going
into like into people's cars. Yeah, we just get it. We buy a brinks truck, an
old retired brinks truck, or we just steal one. We put some three sixty. We
leave all the money. We steal the truck, but leave all the money. The problem
is that people are going to think it's a real brinks truck and try to rob us and
all of our guns are they're funny guns. They don't do anything. They're props.
Exactly. And also we don't have any money. Yeah, there's no money at all.
Yeah, just us. Just our bodies. Well, that's what we could have. We could be
it could be like in a like a more like friends or how I met your mother or
something. It's like an apartment, apartment comedy. So like you bring over
a girl into the brinks. We all live there. We all live in a brink. You bring
going over the girl into the Brinks truck, you're shooting not on her face.
Oh, not on the money.
Come on, not on all the fucking money man. I wasn't aiming for the girl,
you're popping quarters in her ass. Shut up
stop man. You have the thing is coming on money. You have the
the like thing that slides like the like I slit the between the divider and
like the guys fucking the girl in the back and the two guys are in the cab and
just sitting there. It's like are you guys done like closet? He slides it
open, slides it open to the night comes
the guy having a
it's all about noting. This would be this would be the scene. I would bring
truck for a sperm bank. He would say, oh, that's a good idea. What are you
trying to look at the I'm looking for the applause, but he would say he would
say, Hey, I'm bringing a girl. You dropped your phone here. You go to the
applause, go to the applause thing real quick, though this is going to flop.
You you do your thing, you do your thing. So the whole thing it would be you and
you like I'm having a girl over night, be like to again man, because your
character gets pussy a lot. He's kind of a cool one and we'd be like whatever
Patrick, not you.
I wasn't giving you the thumbs up. Yeah, Patrick's like the cool one in the show,
but you'd be like yeah, I'm having a girl over tonight, like like the guy and
funny people, that kind of guy and then you would have the girl over and then it
cuts to you and me. We're listening to car talk, an old car talk episode,
armored car talk arm.
We're listening or actually we're recording our podcast armored car talk
yeah right and we just hear you railing this girl. You're both moaning in the
exact yeah, yes, be a big. Come on now, come on now, yeah, make me not make me
yeah you're doing that and then the thing slides open and you're like
can we have to get you a water? The waters of the front and then we can we
have to get out and go into the gas station to get by bottle water. Then
basically the guy from like dragged across concrete to gets in with the
fucking ski mask and he gets in and he's he's stealing the truck. He thinks
there's money in the back. He's trying to drive it to a secret base or
whatever. Yeah, he like turns and opens to the slot to see how much money he
stole. He sees him and the girl and they're going at it froggy style,
post coital and they're smoking cigarettes, lay on a bed of money. He
opens it and the smoke comes in.
This is what did I is this a decoy truck? There's there's a smoke bomb
we're trying to make an escape or we we bring in the water and he's like thank
you and then we like he like closes the thing and then we hear him go like oh
yeah, I'm pouring water on your ass,
not even drinking the water,
but then the the episode episode starts right. It's like you guys,
my uncle's coming over my uncle's coming over same exact episode, same exact
episode. This is how it starts out in the back. My uncle's coming over back of
the truck opens up
back of the truck opens up
uncle's head pops in. Hello, it's me, the president. It's Donald Trump. Damn it.
Wait, Warren Buffett. No, wait, Donald Trump's your uncle in the show. That's
why I get so much pussy. You're his dead brother's son. Yeah. So you're like
60. That was you were going to want applause for that. Yeah. For the Donald
Trump impression doing the Donald Trump. No, it's going to be him walking into
truck. So imagine it's like the the celebrity cameo on a sitcom. Oh, so
Trump. So it's not supposed to be applauding. No, no, no. Okay, then I
get the I get why you're saying it. I'll give you a plus for that. Okay, so
it's the his head pops in. Yeah. Hello. Yeah. Big applause break. He like start
tries to start his line a couple of times and he keeps getting cut off by
by the applause yeah, yeah, what what what where's all the money yeah, where's all
the where's all the money in the where's all the money in the trip, where's all
the money in the truck, where's all the money in the truck
now and then even then it gets robbed, but then he gets shot first left track
with air horns on it. Yeah, after every time I should do that
yeah, I can do that laugh tracks. Now people are so used to a point of a laugh
track, you know to get you to laugh and then warn you up or whatever everybody's
list of that by now that everything has a left track that you hear the laughter
and it's like it does. It doesn't even register to you that it's happening to
me, so you need something with a little more punch, maybe a machine gun.
Well, I think the drums are
that's enough of that yeah enough of the air horn.
All right, I need one more episode idea before the episode.
I need one more guys. The truck breaks down in the middle of nowhere and we eat
money have to eat the money and live in a forest or no in a day that oh that's a
great idea, because then it's this kind of lesson episode where it's like if
without all this city around us without the truck, you can't drive
the truck doesn't go without all the city around us. We you can be stuck there
with ten million dollars. It doesn't it doesn't even yeah yeah yeah it's
basically an episode that shows that money has no inherent value and it's
simply a societal.
Here's an idea for an episode. So we are short on rent for the truck this month.
We rent the truck.
We rent the truck. We're short on rent for the truck. We get the greatest idea in the
world.
Steal the money.
No, we don't touch the money. We turn the truck into...
Ice cream.
Ice cream truck.
Nice.
Yes.
But then we get into trouble because we accidentally serve like big wads of thousands of dollars
to kids on an ice cream cone.
but we're the heroes of the neighborhood. So it's between keeping our job. We're
like John God becoming the heroes of Astoria and it's in Astoria. Yeah, the
whole thing is in the store and it's called the Kings of and then we're about
to and then we're about we're about to make the decision that we want to be the
heroes. We don't want to keep our jobs and then we find out that every kid who
was coming up and ordering an ice cream cone that we thought we were
accidentally giving the money. Yeah, they were all paid actors by criminals who
knew that money was being given out. The kids are all working for a criminal
organization. Everyone that we interacted with was a criminal who was
stealing the money on purpose, and we realized that we have to do our job,
because there's no one else in the world who can do it. We go in and that's
another another sorry. Another little the nookie starts playing. We jump out
of the cars with the guns that are in there and we shoot all the kids. Also,
we play okey money yeah and we
we all not on the last guy has to go buy something with the money.
That's a great
the last kind of comments to go by
Minnesota
it has to be in your wallet.
It's just like
a good game. Yeah, you're just telling the guy like sometimes money does this.
I don't know. I don't know why. Yeah, I guess I had a piece of gum in my
wallet, but the guy knows it's an old weathered man.
I know you were playing Oki money. You piece of shit.
money. We used to play a guy never played Okie money. I was the game. I
invented Okie money. My name is Michael and he cleans the dollar off with his
slurping mouth. Yeah, well, it's dry by now. He's crazy. Yeah, you have to do
it immediately. So it's wet. Oh yeah, true. Yeah, right. Well, all right, we
can end on. Yeah, money's good. You guys, July fourteenth at Littlefield,
New York City.
Swagpoop.com/shows.
You always do the most long-winded vlog.
Yeah.
I'm just trying to...
July 14th Sketch Show in Brooklyn.
Go to swagpoop.com/shows.
There's the actress.
And who else is going to be there?
Special celebrity guest.
Dr. Dre.
Yeah.
He's going to do that.
Okay.
*thud*
*laughter*
Is that what happened?