I
get a lesson today and getting a laid back juveo yeah. You need to chill man
relax,
take a load off
just lie down on your
that's how you chill out. Surfers are so they got to be some of the
they are. Okay, we've talked about my
my hatred for skaters. I have the opposite feeling for surfboarders because
you are servers as I call them. I surfed like four times and I was like
surfers actually
listen. He's talking about surfing. Let me talk about surfing like he used to
do it all the time. Let me let me explain. Let me explain where let me
go a little psychological and I just explain the
the reasons for your feelings because it's because skateboarders they
pretend to take their lives in their hands every day. They go dude. Oh my
God, I'm skating. I'm going on to a box that is six inches tall. I could die.
I what if I guess right? I'm not wearing a motherfucking helmet bitch.
Whereas a surfer every single time he goes out there runs the risk of being
drawn and quartered by a shark. Yes, a shark sharks like to sharks a hundred
percent. There's sharks in the street there. No, shut the fuck up. That's a
cartoon and they're in the sewer. It's not true at all. Street sharks. They
don't live on the street. I saw one. You're literally, you're thinking of a
toy. I saw a shark the other day. No, I saw one. I saw one on the street. You're
a toy. You are a toy. I'm not a toy. You're a hella toy. I'm not a toy. I
don't write, so. Skateboarding is fried. Skate-- Whoa, chill. Chill. Chill on that.
Chill on that. Chill on that. Real quick. Dude, that's crazy. You're about to get
your jaw slicked. You can't say that. You cannot say that. You're about to get
your jaw slicked, bro. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. That's my boy, and I'm sorry. My
balloons are going to slide your jaw. I'll get him now. That's not even escape
talking. You're talking about balloons. I got balloons tower defense, bro. You
have balloons. I do have double. I would say there's almost no first find a
balloons when they surf. Skateboarders are lucky to find a penny with the
tail side up. That's our servers are weed addicted. Heroin
surfers are addicted to the beautiful vitamin D from the sun.
I'm addicted to one vitamin D and sunscreen.
You think surfers are gay?
Or girls I guess?
Surfers are gay girls.
Well okay, I will say that the most famous surfer
is named Kelly and he's a boy.
Yeah, which is a little strange.
He actually has some fucked up political opinions that I would not like to get into right now.
Does he really?
I don't know. I think I saw him commenting on some
one of those like public
rage bait videos that they post on like
what is it called?
Hood Clips or something.
something. You saw Kelly Slater on Hood Clips and he was saying, he was saying,
"I'm gonna kill every single one of my..." He's probably pro, you know what it is?
He's probably pro global warming because it's more... He wants more sea level,
yeah, exactly. Peach, higher waves. Higher waves, man. Higher waves, bro! He
wants the polar ice caps to melt so he can get one of those big Fiji waves.
'Cause what's he gonna do with the polar ice caps? You know what he wants?
He wants all of the... Nothing, nothing. He can't surf those. He wants all of
the planet to be covered in water so he can surf and Bradley Knowles corpse will go up
so he can use that, put it in his surfboard.
Who's that?
The guy from Sublime.
Why are you talking about Bradley Knowles corpse?
Why do you gotta get so far?
I mean his kids could listen to this show.
His kids do listen to this.
He didn't have kids.
He definitely had some kids.
He had Dalmatian.
I think the Dalmatian listened.
I think the Dalmatian would be passed away by now.
Yeah, probably.
They don't live very long.
surfing is a surfing is a moral is a moral dilemma. No, it's not a thing is
that surfing is about being at one with nature and the wild world. It is so
amazing, whereas skateboarding is about the concrete jungle, which is an
artificial about the light on the story of the planet, during the concrete
jungle. No, it's not. No, you guys build concrete ramps. You don't understand
so surfing is so serene like being out in the ocean. I served four times and
said that he's done it. Yeah, surfing is being out in the open ocean, 300 feet
from land. It's a mile out of the ocean surfing. I love I love the I want to I
want to try to serve. Actually, I have been I have been thinking about it.
Maybe I do that. I think you'd be fail at it, but I actually if it gets you off
of skating, I'm like a mom who's like kid wants to start like smoking weed
instead of doing pills like I find you should be. I should encourage maybe I
I don't know because I mean I can't flip tricks. I can't do flip tricks. People
don't flip all that much when they're surfing. Yeah, it's mostly just going
straight. Yeah, you go straight. Sometimes you go sideways and you will
do a handstand or they hang ten. You could get in a rip curl.
The biggest trick in surfing is hanging ten.
Has anyone actually ever hung ten? Yeah. The Tummy Hawk of surfing hung twenty
one time. Hanging ten, hanging ten's like a big deal. Hanging ten is not a
It's one of the only like five people in the world who have ever hung ten before.
No, dude. I've hung ten. Bro. No. You want to check me?
Speaking of hanging ten, there's a really, really crazy clip. You literally put your feet on either end
and you hang ten off, hang five on each side. That's my strat.
That's not, that's a monkey grab. That's hanging five and five. So you claim to be a
skateboarder and yet you know about monkey kind of language for surfing.
There's a lot of, a lot of the tricks are analogous to each other. They're the same
pretty much goofy came from all the word goofy. The goofy footed comes from the
animators in a Disney short about surfing, drawing goofy doing his foot like right
foot forward and then regular is like so it's actually about Disney goofy. It is
actually about Disney goofy. Yeah, that's awful. That just blew my mind. Meme style.
Do you ride goofy? Yeah, I'm riding a regular way. I bet he rides grimace style.
Oh, but hang ten.
You ride Ben 10.
There's a clip of fucking Tim Pool doing a hang ten inward heel.
That's cool.
It's crazy that he's hanging ten and then he does a flip with his two feet.
So he's kind of nice.
He's still wearing the fucking beanie bro.
He's kind of nice though.
He can skate.
He's yeah, he's better than me. Whoa. So you just admitted that yeah, Tim pool is better than me at skating, but they like
He's he cuz you're kind of the temple. You're like the leftist
Yeah, you won't take a hat off you I'll take it off right now damn it got stuck
Take us stuck
I'm down to go surfing this summer. The summer is upon us.
The summer is over. I'd be down to surf. Summer is over. Summer is barely getting started.
It's only 80 degrees. I'm so not excited for these 100 degree, 110, 120, 130 degrees days.
Apparently it's going to be jungle climate across the entire US.
Being born in July is a curse. Why? It's a cancer if
it's before the 23rd. Why? Because of the heat.
Right. Why the 23rd? It's the cusp of Leo.
on my birthday, the cusp of Leo, the cusp of shut up. Okay. Oh, you did get into
astrology for a little bit when you moved to New York because I was dating.
I had to know this shit. Oh, God, this is what you say. A girl asked you for your
astrological information. You say this fuck off. You could pretend like you're
you say you say really quietly manute bowl and you didn't you know they don't
- You know who Manic Bowler is?
- Bowl Ball?
- No, no, Bowl Ball is his son.
- I think his son went to...
- No, he didn't.
- His son went to school in New Hampshire, I think.
- Maybe.
Do you know who Manic Bowler is, though?
- Yeah.
- You know who they are?
- I know he has a son named Bowl Ball.
- He's like a seven foot seven guy from Africa.
And they just, he came to the US
and they made up a birthday for him
'cause they didn't know, he didn't know his birthday,
he didn't know how old he was.
But he apparently used to,
anytime that it would like,
the summer would come back around,
he would cut his head to mark like...
and he plays one of his teammates said that oh he is a sportsman yeah he was a
basketball player so one of his teammates said he could I think his
listed birthday was at the time he was like 28 years old and one of his
teammates asked him about the scars he was like yeah this is like how many
years old I am and he said that he had like over 50 scars and he was like 50
years old that's sick and then he died like five years after that so it makes
He died?
Yeah.
I thought he was alive.
No, no, he died.
They claimed he died at like 40, but he was probably in his 60s.
Oh.
Wow.
I would love to lie about my age.
I'm getting to the age where I'm feeling like I should be lying about it.
Yeah.
When people say...
I'm 15.
Yeah, you're young.
Dude, I look kind of indeterminate age, I think.
I don't think I look like a 25-year-old.
You look like one of those photos where they're like, "This is what a 25-year-old used to
look like."
I was like a twenty five year old in like nineteen seventy. Yeah, yeah, that's what high school
kids used to look like in two thousand and three. What the fuck? Yeah, I don't think
that's fair. Jesus Christ. Yeah, that guy's fifty. Yeah, I think I'm kind of blessed in
that way though, because I already look, I already look old. My parents look very young,
but maybe I, actually maybe I'm fucked. Why? Maybe I'm completely fucked. Do you think
you look older than your parents already? Probably. That's a fact. I look older than
my parents did in like photos. I'd rather look old than young. Yeah. I'm going to look like
a fucking raisin by the time I'm like 40. No, you have decent skin. I don't think you're
going to look like a raisin. I didn't get zits until my girlfriend started giving me
skin care stuff and then I was like, I can't do this anymore. I think that this whole skin
care thing that women are into. I think that that stuff gives you worse skin. Yeah, so
that you have to keep using it. Yeah, that's why. That's why they use it. Me wrong, L'Oreal.
I think it's probably true because they didn't have that back. They didn't have skin care
back in the caveman. No, no, no, no. Yeah, wait, have you ever seen a picture or a cave
great painting of a caveman with acne yeah never want no of course not no. I
mean they do it to the little blood dots yeah Simba. It's the easiest thing to
draw in the world yeah dots a dot. It's easier than a line and they didn't do
it dozens of lines. Imagine what caveman acne looked like the probably like
imagine how big imagine how big sure everything was bigger back then. No,
just like the just because all the oils and shit like they've never washed so
like imagine just like the doctor pimple pop of videos for caveman.
well, you know it would be do me like he does back then were sucking people dry
yeah and all the blood out land of the law land of the last. I never saw it
because it was too adult for me when it was released. It's too little for me
now man. There's some fucking inappropriate shiz in the show the movie
shut up.
What show the show that the movies based on you're trying to be old. You are to
Okay, you look old because you're spiritually a hundred. You love old
shit. Yeah. And you always know about old crap. Well, that show looks cool.
The reason is because you like your parents too much and you listen to what
they say. Well, they would... Me and him. That's right. Our parents blabbered
on all day about... That's right, I'm like, "Fuck you, Dad, I like Pokemon."
My parents wouldn't let me watch shit like that.
Like what? Like Pokemon because
there was... Well, there was like four kids in the house and they were like,
"No, we're gonna watch this instead." So they would put on their kids programs
from like when they were younger, he calls them programs. I do God damn you
man. Jesus. Okay, so here's how am I? How am I like this old and this young at
the same time? Me too son is a good thing. They're the same fucking thing.
Yeah, I think it's the electric company you want to watch. Yeah, you so to me
and Cameron Jeepers Creepers is a scary movie to you and to my mom. It's the
the song. It's the best song ever.
It's your ringtone man
that's your kind of thing. Yeah, scary movies you, you know, we need to put us
as a horror character. Yeah, who is attacking Christopher Robin and the
hundred acre wood because they abandoned him yeah right to you. He's some
cartoony. You probably only read the book and the poetry
I really I had a movie out of winning the that's new for me. I saw I still on the
Charles. I watched the trailer for that movie. That is got to be the biggest
whiff of a fine idea where you could have done something kind of fun ever. I
think well, it's all just it's money laundering. Yeah, I think so, do every
every every movie like every horror movie like that is is like that, but why
didn't they do it? They could have made him a big puppet. I think there was a
movie a couple years ago that was like also a similar thing. Banana splits.
Yeah, yeah. But that was kind of fun. They made a banana splits horror movie
where they like torture people. That's a show from the 70s. Yeah, yeah. So it
became public domain and they turned it into like they were torturing... They
were... How did it just become public domain? It was fun. How did that become
public domain? That was like made in the... Oh, okay. They probably... Yeah,
that makes sense. Yeah. But they also did that one with
Nicholas Cage, Willie's Wonderland. I didn't see that. They're all bad.
there was Willie's Wonderland. It's the same thing. It's another five. Is that
like a now they're making five nights at Freddy's movie, which I'm excited for.
I got a mother. I'm gonna wait. See, that's why that was my kid shows. Yeah,
five nights at Freddy's. Markiplier show. I think five nights at Freddy's is
literally the cut off point. One was the thing that was the first thing that I
didn't get. One of the actual shows that I love to watch when I was like a
five year old boy was this show called Lidsville, where a guy falls into a
magician's hat and he goes into a world of hats.
And the whole show is him interacting with hat people.
A world of hats? Shut the fuck up!
It's a real Lidsville. It's a Lidsville.
Search Lidsville right now.
This is a stop click.
Search Lidsville.
It's a Sid and Marty Kroft show.
I don't care about Lids.
Yep, Lidsville.
Oh, oh God, bro.
This is what you watch as a kid?
I watch I was a I was obsessed with say to Marty cross stuff as a kid. You are
an idiot. I'm not an idiot. It's just the shit that my mom would let me like
watch. I did this.
This is the VHS tapes I would have. I didn't fucking buy it. My mom did. I
had no money. I was a boy. This is something that you would you would in
2012 you would open an imager album that was called oddly terrifying shows
from the olden days and it would be this. Well, yeah, I didn't know that
that shit was scary until I started seeing. Why is she why is she she
they're blasting her ass? Why is he using electricity on her? And the
green guy, they portrayed the hats with costumes. Yeah,
the green guy, I forget his name. But then there's also the bug loose jam
and cartoon, but there's also the bug loose in the head, but need a bizarre
you thinking of the tootsies in the yeah, the hooters and tootsies
What was that? What that character's name? I think that's the boy. I don't
know. The person on the right. Oh, that's I don't remember. That's his
mom. This is literally you and your mom. Mrs. Hat, yeah.
That's what... The idea that I would be looking at this picture and asking,
"Who is that character?" I mean, the kid on the left. I don't remember that
much about Lidsville, but I do remember a good... You remember everything about
it. You said you loved it. I remember, I think I could tell you like maybe
storyline from HR Puff and Stuff. Here's why me and Cameron get along so well, better than
you do with us, is because we watched Cyberchase. Oh yes. I thought that shit sucked. Shut the
fuck up. I thought that shit sucked so bad. I didn't have a viewable, I just had an antenna.
When I was a kid I thought that shit sucked. Cyberchase was the best show of all time. I
thought that sucked and I thought HR Puff and Stuff was sick and I thought The Muppet Show
was sick. No man, you're just gay. The Muppets are so gay. The kid who liked The Muppets
still in middle school. Yeah, still like them a bitch in middle school. Yeah,
that was me. That's right. I'll go Mrs Piggy on it. Yep, yep. Slap the shit out
of them.
Why was she always hating on Kermit trying to get a little fat? She, she...
For real, though. Kermit would say... She did stay. I mean, okay, here's the
She did not let him.
They would have somebody on Elvira or something.
And she's rubbing her tits in Kermit's face.
Yeah.
And it's like, what is Kermit supposed to do?
He's the boss of the show.
He's supposed to scorn this beautiful woman.
It's also TV.
It's not real life.
So don't get mad.
She was always mad about that shit.
But you have somebody like Ricardo Maltaban on or something.
Yeah.
He's digging Miss Piggy out in the fucking dressing room.
that stage he's going all the way up in me yeah. I don't need to fuck my
pig. He's touching the part. They make the hot dogs out of he's up in there.
He's up in there. They got like he's like mum and shunts on there and she's
trying to get a train run on her by moment. Yeah, wait, deep way. He's
fucking with her patay. That's a really good point. Is there like pigs, pussy,
balls and dicks
it's funny to him. I that would be like we're going to make the hot dogs out of
the intestine and yeah we're going to use the butthole, but we're not touching
the post. Yeah, they definitely put the
we're sorting it all out, save the put
I'm going to take it home. Yeah, some guy, I'm going to save it. I'm going to
save it for later. There's one that is so nasty man.
You know hot dog and we talked about how hot dogs are technically as bad for you
as I always talk about. It's really recently. All right, dude yeah, if hot
dogs, that's probably why it looks so fucking old because of I got to change
my whole life. How often do you eat a hot dog? It used to be when we were in
college together, it used to be probably like
two every day.
No, I hear. No, that's a gross
estimation. It's gross, alright.
I think it was maybe, I think I would get like a 7-Eleven Big Bite probably
four times a week. That's a lot for a hot dog. But there's only like a $2
hot dog. That's not you know, I mean the price of it is not that it's not that
it's economical. Yeah, I'm just saying that. Yeah, I mean if obviously a hot
dog is the cheapest thing you can eat at any given time. No, that's not obvious.
You can get this. No a meal. Yeah, I would say people get a lot of peanuts
for the grind. I mean all I'm saying is that the price has nothing to do with
you get a problem with eating. That's a that's cheap. PB and J is more expensive
because you have to buy all the ingredients at once. True. Yeah. Well,
That's true. There was a I used to work at a restaurant that sold a $4 PB&J.
Still probably more expensive than a hot dog. You just said it was $2.
What restaurant are you working that sold a PB&J?
Clover.
They sold a PB&J? On that pita bread?
Yep.
Ugh.
And it was the tiniest little dollops of peanut butter and jelly.
Oh no.
And the tiniest peanut butter. We were ripping, dude, I was ripping people off. It was, it felt
like.
And you were getting all that cash.
I was like, I'm just following orders. I just got to keep doing this.
You're comparing...
Uh-huh. My time.
Your time working for a kind of expensive restaurant to be...
Yeah, a restaurant.
To working for the Wolfenstaffel.
Wolfen... Wolfensteppen. What was it?
Steppenwolf.
I like Disney! Fucking magic copyright!
That's got to be the worst song ever.
Yeah.
That's one of the songs where I'm...
There's a couple songs like that where I'm so surprised that they were not made.
They were not novelty songs.
Yeah, I always thought Steppenwolf was like a 90s band because the guy's voice is so stupid.
That's because you don't have the kind of knowledge that I have about 70s bands and stuff.
But your parents weren't even into like cool bands.
No, my parents, I got into Nirvana in middle school and my mom was like,
"That is the worst shit I've ever heard."
She doesn't like Nirvana?
She didn't like Nirvana.
Nirvana's fire.
Yeah, they were so good. My mom was like, "You didn't..."
You made fun of me for listening to Pink Floyd last week.
Pink Floyd sucks.
You are gay.
That's not gay.
Pink Floyd is awesome.
Pink Floyd sucks so bad.
There's some cool songs.
Pink Floyd is sick, dude.
They suck.
You don't like money.
You listen to songs that are like...
I like that song, actually.
It's a good song.
I really like that song.
It's in the Italian job.
Yeah.
Maybe I have to give them another chance.
You need to give Pink Floyd another chance.
Yeah, because I just got annoyed by them.
I don't know why.
When I was 15...
We walk into the office and you're listening to a song
and it sounds like it could be from a video game
that has a frog level.
- Absolutely.
You're listening to a Lily Pad song.
(imitating frog sounds)
- I was listening, okay, okay.
- That's the music you listen to.
- You guys come in, you guys came in,
I was listening to Sade the other day.
- That wasn't what we're talking about.
- No, it wasn't that.
- Not what we're talking about at all.
- No, I know the exact song that I was listening to
and it's gonna make me--
- Mario 64 underwater music.
- It looks even older,
it's gonna make me look like an old man,
but it's a song called the Elusive Butterfly.
Why how does it go
it's a good song? I bet you listen to the tent, the elusive butterfly of love
by Bob
I
listen to
I bet you used to listen to eight bit music. Yeah,
I talked about that. I talked about that before, but I was in middle school.
I really in the music because I made I made YouTube. You listen to the
eight bit stuff. Wow, I got I was listening to moon theme. Yeah,
you know what I you know what I had on my computer and I was in middle school
was
I had something called it was called it tracker like it tracker and so I could
listen to the files and higher sound quality.
It was like our mod plug track. It was a mod, like a midi player. No, it would play dot XM files or dot like it files and I don't even know what those files are. There are files on the old man files. I know. I think you listen to this is why I don't get along with anybody. My music dot O. G. G.
because you're so old. I think so. Due to your age. I like I'd like get along with you guys
enough. Yeah, we get along proper. Yeah, we get along well. It's just like I guess it's
kind of like you guys hanging out with me is kind of like when you got to hang out with
your uncle. It's like an uncle that I'm wiser than. Yeah, it's like having to take care
of an uncle. Yeah, it's like an uncle with an injury. With a hip problem. Yeah, not a
my hip problem. I'm that much of a burden on you guys. I'm going to take
care of an uncle. Yeah, I would say you're definitely taking care of your
kid. Yeah. Did you guys ever have an uncle live in an extra room in your
house or something? No. I've talked about, I've had every single one of my
uncles live in my house. Yeah, yeah, yeah, I forgot about that. Yeah. It's
fun. Yeah, well, it's kind of until, you know, you have
two other siblings and you want your own room. Yeah, but kids don't need to
have their own room. Two other siblings that still live there. Unless you're at
age where you also shouldn't have their own room. I agree. I should have shared a room.
Unless it's your sister and there's three other boys. I lived in a... I had a... I shared
a room for a long time and then I had my own room and it was a closet. I lived in a closet
under the stairs and my cousin Dudley. Every story Caleb has about me. It was so rude to
where he lived. Really? Yeah. I lived in a outhouse. I didn't live in an outhouse. I
lived in an outhouse for six months. I never lived in an outhouse. I did live in twenty
many houses growing up yeah. I lived in one rich cool, not at the same day
okay, great man money bags over here. What can I say? We just we move into a
house to get bored. We move buying an entire neighbor. Yep, but we did one
time we moved. We moved we lived in one house and then we moved four houses down
and then we moved next door to that house. Yeah, well yeah in like a year
I lived in the same place until I was in college.
But like I, for like, I don't remember how long.
I lived in the same place till after college.
What was it?
That's so fire, man.
My uncle, I don't know why, he had his own place,
but he got veneers. He got veneers done.
That's sick.
And then for some reason, my mom put a bed in the living room
that he could recover from the veneers.
- From veneers?
- He laid on the, maybe he got back surgery.
That makes a lot more sense.
- He just had veneers and you thought
that he was recovering from the white teeth?
- Yeah, I think that he got veneers at the same time
that he got a back, like a major back surgery.
So I, in my little kid brain, I was like,
oh, they must, that must fuck you up.
- That's honestly, I think the scariest part of getting older.
- I wouldn't be surprised if getting veneers fucked you up.
- Oh, it does, it fucks up your whole mouth.
No, it doesn't. Yeah, it does. They put little chicklets in there, Dennis the
Mastiff. Yeah, don't they do? They do Bobby Peru. Yeah, but then you have the
teeth, like it's not gonna... Yeah, but those teeth can rot on the inside of
the veneer. I bet it hurts like shit. Yeah. I don't think it hurts. After you
get them put in. I don't think so. You get a lot of good painkillers. My uncle
was asleep all the time.
I would get veneers. I would. I would, but I would not look good with them. My
teeth are pretty fucked up, too. Mine are, too. I've fucking cracked my... This
tooth is broken right now. Well, you have like five teeth that are rotting out
I have five cavities. How did you know? Because you told me. Yeah, I did tell you. Because
you're such a candy man. That's your tie to you. I got candy the other day. I'm so jealous.
I literally can't eat candy, bro. For the first time in probably over a year, I was
craving candy. Something's going on. I bought candy. I bought candy, too. What kind did
you buy? You're buying candy because I told you guys I have cavities and you want to rub
it in my face. I bought Nutella Bueno bars. That's terrible. I don't even know what that
That is a terrible choice. I got myself some Skittles.
I wanted some Skittles. What kind?
Skittles. Plain Skittles? Skittles.
Red bag. Red bag Skittles. I eat old lady candy. My favorite candy in the
world
Why don't you give me a side for that? A chocolate covered pomegranate bite.
Shut up. I love those. You know what's really good is those milk candies.
You've said this before and I don't know what you mean. Dove chocolate,
Magnum bars. Oh, Magnum bars are good. Yeah.
that dark chocolate that's real velvety and silky.
- Yeah, I like dark chocolate.
- That like all the ads are like,
it's like a woman in her like early 40s
and she like bites into the peppermint patty and nuts.
- You know these scumbag Europeans
think that Hershey's chocolate bars taste like vomit?
- Really?
- Yeah, because there's lactic acid in it or something.
- They got crazy candy over there.
- 'Cause it's not normal milk chocolate.
It's like, you know how Hershey's have like a weird
like kind of sourness to them?
- Yeah.
you know next time you try your buddy. All right, trust me. I know I know you
know next time I try her shoes, but I in my head buying a plane just Hershey's
bar and is helping it. No eating it and not like cutting it up and putting it
into like cookies or something is the mark of a psycho. I like a planer. It's
a psycho. If you don't get the one with the almonds, just the plane, you just
want one with extra flavors. Some people like simplicity. Yeah, but a Hershey's
is better chocolate.
I am refuge and there's way better chocolate that you can get a hustle and
chaos of modern life is a little too much for some Hershey's with almonds.
I just want one single bar with 600 ingredients. You literally want to live
in. So we want this factory. Meanwhile, I want to live on a chocolate farm. No,
I want to live in Lidz and I want to take care of the chocolate plants. I'm
gonna live in Lidsville and talk to all that. I don't want to live in Lidsville
and the chocolate animals and also I have a chocolate wife. Yeah, she doesn't
like when I call her that.
on the
oh man, the Lisville in troy on a crazy don't care week. I'll show you after
I don't care at all about I'll show you. I'll change the subject completely done.
I'd like to change the subject entirely. Yeah, you got it and actually we're
taking away points. We should have points on the show. Yo, that's a really
things made up in the point. Don't matter for the premium matter a lot.
Okay, all right, we're starting points. Now, okay, you're starting negative.
Yeah, can you put like a points board up? I'm starting negative to yeah, you just
lost. Why is it negative? You were the first person to have any kind of value
changed. You have to add three counters.
Search score counter instead of tally count. Tally count is gonna be one. Yeah,
tally count. It's not just me with the counter. Yeah, we'll just start with you
for this episode. So you're starting... Get a new, get more. Just search like a
score counter. Why are you doing this weird tabs thing? You're ruining
everything. I'm just joking, but you did just lose points. Yeah, Jubio, oh yeah,
yourself down for
okay. The guest is definitely Patrick. Okay, me and care, I guess is Patrick and
Jubio, me and cam. Oh yeah, then I guess it knocked down six points. Okay, and we
are six points. Yeah, why not? Yeah, because Jubio lost four. I just said
that I have to I can't walk it back and so me and Cameron are let's say we get
plus three for coming up to start. Yeah, this is a starter amount. Yeah, yeah,
and also yeah, a little bit, you know, yeah, because we need the edge.
You guys are so okay. This isn't going to work. A handio isn't accepting taking
away his own points. You need to take away. I will take away. I will. I will
gladly take that negative to negative four versus three. Okay, okay, yeah, yeah.
So now that now we have also some incentive to try to be to perform. Yeah,
exactly, because most of the time I'm like I don't even want to perform. Don't
zip your lips. No, that's your lips is bad. That's your only way that you can
lose because you're down. Yeah, that's true. Me and Cameron could zip our lips
and probably tie this thing up pretty easily. That's not true. We have a giant
lead and there's only nine
I would come up with something in nine minutes to talk about. Okay, so you guys
are going to be quiet. I'm going to talk for nine minutes. No, no, no, just I'm
just saying bring a bring a bring a topic and we can start talking. It can't
it can be Lidsville. It can't be Lidsville. Yeah, I already lost
points for Lidsville for bringing back Lidsville, bringing it back. So okay,
what is something? Oh, I found a thing in my notes at the other day,
and I don't know if we were trying to prepare a roast battle or something,
but it says Caleb is the type of guy who owns a dog because it's illegal for
him to own a slave.
that's a that's a negative point. I don't know it didn't work. It didn't work. So
that means it's that means it's no change, but yeah, but yeah, but that's
not really doing a roast battle. Don't think we were. I don't think we ever
viewed as a real
that's fucking rude. I think that was no. I think it was a roast of me for
no that I didn't ask for. I think it was for when you did the distrack
because I could the distrack can't rhyme and then I did something different.
When we were texting each other wraps last night, yours did not rhyme at all.
rhymed in my head. That's what I'm saying. They did not rhyme. I was proud
of mine. Yeah, I liked yours a lot. Yeah. Okay. Well, I'm getting into
rapping. I have a
I guess we've said it maybe every single episode for the past couple months,
but maybe that is our new thing. Is this rapping? Is just getting into
and being hip hopping. Well, that's the other thing. Yeah, I can't... Dude,
are you kidding me? I can't fucking rap. Have a little confidence in yourself.
The type of rap that my old ass would do. Do you think that Tupac
he got famous by saying I can't rap. I don't know who that is. I only got
famous by rapping. I only know Curtis Blow. I only know these guys.
Curtis Blow rapped. Oh wait, was it Curtis Blow that had that song
about going to prison? No. Oh wait, the breaks?
Yesterday? Is it the breaks where he says, he says... Yesterday? Yesterday,
I had, I just remember this is, this is related to rapping. I just had
sudden kind of urge from beyond and I just had I watched the whole the final
rap battle from 8 mile on YouTube. I just and I made my fiancee watch it with me.
She never saw it. Amazing and girls haven't seen it and she didn't get it.
That's one of my dad's favorite movies. Dude, I showed my wife. I showed my wife
the 8 mile rap battle. I know something about you. And she was like yeah, that
was actually really cool. It's so sick. Yeah, that's why I watched it every day
as a child. Of all time. Did you guys ever see that movie that Eminem made in
like 2017. He's funny and funny. No, no.
There's a movie that he made that is supposed to be the story of Slim Shady
where it's like a kid is writing of a mile. No, no, no, I'm not.
It's the kid from what's that fucking kid named?
The redhead kid with that crazy overbite. He looks super young.
He's always got braces.
Fragly. It's not Fragly, but if he was Fragly, he would be an amazing Fragly.
"Fuck, what is that kid in?"
He's got the greasy ass,
- I don't know this kid. - The greasy ass orange hair.
- Tell me about the movie. - But he's the star
and the whole thing is that he is writing his dissertation
on the use of the N-word in rap.
- This is not real. - This is real.
This is a real movie.
He's writing his dissertation
on the use of the N-word in rap
and then he becomes a battle rapper
because he just goes to like a battle rap
to see like what it's all about.
And then he becomes like,
It's like, "Damn, this boy boy can battle rap."
And the whole movie--
- I bet he's an English major.
- He's an English major, he is.
- He's an English major?
- And his dad is a professor, and he is battle rapping,
and then he makes the battle rap really personal
about his mentor, and he makes fun of his daughter
for having cystic fibrosis.
- Whoa.
- Yeah, that's too far.
- Even for Slim Shady, that's a lot.
- But you don't know it's Slim Shady
until the end of the movie,
where he's like sleeping on a park bench,
and he's like so he ruined his life for rap. He ruined his life rapping. He
ruins his life. That is modern day Moby Dick and then and then he's on the
bench and then his battle rap goes viral or something and then he's like,
I think I know what my new battle rap name is going to be and then needle
drop. Hi, my name is what and it's supposed to be. That's what happened to
Slim Shady. That's what it's I don't think so. I think some shady if you
you listen to the music. I think Slim Shady's alter ego was like he was an
escaped
elf,
mental convict from
and his gifts, he didn't want to rap.
Some awful things. He says that his stepfather fucked him in the butt.
Relapse, he says that really, and his brain fell out of his skull. My whole
fucking brain fell out of my skull. Who is this movie? But speaking of, is it
the breaks where Curtis Blow says that you go to prison and and like you,
these are the brave, maybe it's not the break. It's something about you,
you drop the soap and then no he and you look up say not the, but he says shut
up, but but no, but so what you going to do freaky deaky or what maybe the
sound is called freaky deaky or it could be something like what you're going to
do. So what you going to do a freaky deaky or what? Well, I guess I'll freak
you.
What's your decision? What's your decision? I'm waiting.
Are you going to freaky deaky this guy? I'm waiting.
He's waiting.
He's going to wait.
He's going to listen to that song all the time and really laugh until
that's one of those things where you get older
and you realize how dark it is.
That's true of a lot of Slim Shady lyrics.
That's the craziest part about that
is the beat of that song.
Do you like violence?
I always thought he was saying do you like Primus.
Hi kids,
do you like Primus?
But then I thought that the next line was like making fun. I thought it was
supposed to be making fun of nine inch nails. Yeah, nine inch nails and a new
metal crap. Oh, that new metal. This isn't the first time that I've misheard
an Eminem. That's really funny. Hi, kids. Do you like primus? Do you want to see
me stick nine inch nails into my eyelids through each one of each one of my
eyelids? Eminem has so many fire lines. He does crazy. The Eminem line that
made me laugh so hard in high school was in that song as the world turns when
and he says when he's in the song, he's saying he's mugging a woman, then he
says, plus I'm a rapist and a repeated prison escape
and I always make it lab really hard yeah yeah. What a funny thing to say
in your song. He has one song where he says he's raping his own mom. He is a
crazy guy, so now I'm oh and any the he says it from the perspective of
somebody listening to the song and the line is oh now he's raping his own
mother.
that's the line. Oh, now he's right. Oh, okay, now it's a to imagine like a
record executive being like yeah, yeah, yes, yeah, this is the stuff man, but
you know we're going to be the biggest white rapper in the world. We're going
to put a sticker on the thing so people know
that he says this kind of crap. Yeah, that's the the coolest shirt you can
wear is that sticker, the explicit sticker, I parental advisory, which can
we put that on our cover. It makes me oh yeah, we can we it makes me think that
you maybe have cuss words tattooed on your torso. Yep, maybe you have a big
F. U. C. K. On the middle of like two parts. I mean just when I read that
shirt, I'm like better watch out if you're gonna buy me. Yep, yep, I might be
a bad influence on your kids. Yeah, that's right. You don't want me in the
house. You do not want me around. I'm a bad bad. I'm a bad bad guy. That's what
they should do for sex offenders. Just have a shirt that they have to wear that
exactly warning warning crazy guy. No yeah, I don't think that's specific
express a person warning, explicit mother fucker, explicit content. That
would be a shirt. That's a Spencer's gift shirt for sure warning, explicit
mother fucker yeah, warning, explicit content with an arrow down to morning,
a
and then another one down to your ass. That what it's a bunch of arrows that go
all around. Oh yeah, all over my body for here's a shirt idea. It says on in
the front of it. It says my ass and then as an arrow down that goes around to the
back of the
your
so somebody sees the shirt and they follow the arrow. Okay, we get three
points for that. We get three points right now. That's an amazing, amazing
yeah, yep,
I work for the scoreboard. Yeah, the home team is up on a major way.
How much time is left on the clock? Twenty six. Oh my God, we'll restart it.
We'll do it for the whole episodes, whatever, but yeah, just pause the pause
the timer. We don't need the timer, but I think that you can even do one where
it's
warning, explicit cunt shirt. Yeah, I said that already stealing said cunt
stealing minus two points, minus two points, plus two for me. Yeah, I'm sorry.
Wait, minus two and plus two. That's a huge swing. That's a more crazy. Yeah,
we're still pretty. We got a comfortable. I'm fine with this. Yeah, we don't
He's got to play the foul game.
You guys, okay, it's two on one because Jubio doesn't say anything.
It's one on one, y'all.
He's not even contributing even a little bit.
He's just controlling the scoreboard.
I have no help here.
Blame his teammates.
That's points up.
Allen Iverson vibe.
Allen Iverson, one of the greatest of all time?
Yeah, one of the shortest of all time.
Good.
You probably would think that's good.
That's good.
That's good for basketball.
I'm tall.
He can't switch teams.
Yeah, he can.
you just switch teams. Yeah, you can switch teams with a sign and trade.
Okay, I'm going to switch the team to you can't know. We don't want you on
our team. Yeah, we're not buying your defensive liability, not a defensive
like you're a one way player, a one way player. Yeah, you only play offense.
That's true. You are offensive. Yeah, exactly and you're getting a warning
explicit mother fucker. You're catching technical fouls here and there. You're
going to get ejected man. I'm not going to get ejected. I think I'll probably
first day when I was at the hotel that I was at a week ago or less than a week
ago and the pool that we swam in the hotel pool. We were swimming in it and
then we noticed that there is a sign. So you know the sign that they have for the
rules of the pool next to it. There was a sheet of paper that was taped up on
the wall. Just a sheet of printer paper with printed out and it said it said it
said on it. It is prohibited
to it is prohibited to expel feces in the pool. Wow, I think that's
It should be an unwritten rule.
It was taped up next to, well that's what I'm saying.
We're currently swimming in the pool.
You notice that they had to put up a sign that said don't poop in this pool.
Somebody watched Air Bud before they made that pool.
How would that make sense?
There's no rule against it.
There's a dog named poop going in the pool.
Oh, there's no rule in the rule book that says you can't expel feces in the pool.
Yeah, exactly.
So they were like let's put it in the rule book.
Yeah.
That's a scary thing to see when you're swimming in a pool.
When I'm in the pool with my mouth open.
that's the rules. Is this a hotel? I just don't like the idea that they had to
put the the rule on their foot. Yeah, it was happening. It happens even one
time, because also let's be real. Also, how long is a piece of paper staying up
in a humid pool room? Yeah, right that had to be fresh true. Someone has it
wasn't laminated. It was not laminated. It was a piece of paper taped up man.
Probably should not have a thing to say him in that I was already swimming in
and then we were in the hot tub and an old man came over. He said mind if I
turn this thing up and he did and then he didn't get in.
That was a I think you encountered a witch.
I was kind of a
over
the jets and then he and then he just was spring of rosemary. He's looking
from behind one of those little trees that they have in there and he's like
all these
you don't even know that there's not water. That's all for us. Just a good
general guys in mind. If I turn this thing up pretty funny
one time, I think the first boob I ever saw in real life was in a hot tub yeah
and because some lady she like went under and out. It was like a lady and
her boyfriend. We were in Myrtle Beach, me and my little brother. Come on
come
on friendly fire. That's friendly fire. How do we decide that
plus two points minus two points?
you know a lady with she went under into the hot tub and then came back up and
her. Why would she go under? How far did she go? Yeah, she just like went under
real quick came up with enough force. I don't know. I made no sense, but both of
her boobs fell out and then me and my brother, we just looked away yeah and we
had been like talking to them and then they were like they were kind of like
weirded out that we were just looking away and they were still trying to talk
to me and then her boyfriend noticed that her both of her giant boobs were
out and then they just started laughing and I was like you're laughing. That's
funny you scar you think that's funny that I had to see your giant guard a
family
literally are never going to be
great same way. Ever we're both gay now. Thank you so so much. We're so
disgusting yeah and we're gay with each other, which is a legal yeah. So we're
brothers, we're a day with each other. I'm going to jail. We're going to jail,
but it was it was crazy man. That's pretty crazy. What yeah you who's going
under in a hot tub anyway, but I don't think I don't think I would. I think I
was eleven or twelve. I don't think I would do anything any differently. Now I
don't think I would feel ever comfortable. Are you can I be screaming
going like
excuse me? I'd be like your things, your whatever's are out
your balloons are out. Your thingies are floating. Hey lady, your balloons
just oh my God, they're huge. The worst part
shout to self, those things are gigantic. Oh, wow, huge. You know what I do hate
is when you, oh nothing, you're in the hot tub and like you just, you're already
in there, then two other like old people come in, they're just very friendly. I
love being in water with oldies. I don't. Being in the pool with the oldies,
being in the hot tub with the oldies. I'm spiritually so old, I just, I do not,
I don't fuck with old people. When I was a kid, I used to put my head under and
put it on top in front of one of the jets in the hot tub and just see how long I
could hold my breath and it felt like I was getting high. Yeah, yeah, you're
sucking in all that toe fungus. I just put my face directly into the jet. I was
letting my whole body when I was I was never somebody who put the jet on my
butt. I don't like that. I haven't done that before ever in my life. Once I did
it one time, I did it. I did it one time, but I did it a few times. The thing is
no matter how warm the water is, once it's in your body, it feels cold. Yeah,
so once it's in your asshole, the worst is when it goes. I will say after this
mysterious old man turned it up. These were some forceful jets. I think I would
I think I could have blasted my guts out my rib and the skin off yeah. I think I
could have ever had their whole intestine destroyed by a jacuzzi jet or
is that just a thousand way to die? A book yeah, it's a it's a Chuck Palah. I
thought that was a thousand to die guts probably also did it on a thousand ways
and yeah, I mean they don't think that those are real death. We've we've
definitely talked about how they aren't real desk because there's no way that
all of those people, I was actually just thinking about it. Did you guys ever
read the Darwin Awards? When yeah yeah, they had a Darwin Awards book in my
middle, so I didn't read it, but my mom would sometimes watch people on the
news. They are so I remember really the one that I read. I like read the book,
because it was somebody like it was in the classroom, and I would just read it,
and I read one that stuck in me forever that I fully under percent believed was
real when I was reading it in like fifth grade, and this is the craziest that
this is insane that they put this in a book, a Darwin Awards book, but there
was a story that this baby slept on his back
man and a woman were camping and they were having sex and then the lightning
bolt struck them and they got stuck together and then a bear ate the girl
and the guy had to crawl for help. While she was, they were attached together,
he believed this. I believed it a hundred percent. I was like I was like
either by like all the other things are like a guy was hang gliding and he fell
down to the ground and he died and I was like well, they wouldn't put this in the
book. If it wasn't real, these dark these Darwin Awards, I don't think any of
them are real. The committee is living the most boring life ever. They won't go
rock climbing. Yeah, they won't do anything. They won't even tie out zip tie
to their penis. They won't jaywalk. They won't have sex in a tent. Yeah, I would
hate to be one of the other one that I remember is because it was like you know
it's like oh either die or you make yourself unable to reproduce. Here's a
guy. I want to make his dick look big, so he tied a roll of quarters to it and it
cut off all the blood flow and they had to amputate it. Here's a Darwin award. I
would like all of quarters to it. Exactly. This stuff isn't real. It can't
be
Darwin from wild thorn berries. I'd like to see the words he gives out. We call
the bananas. He's the monkey. He's not a monkey. He's a human. He's a monkey.
Darwin's a monkey. Oh, there was a talking monkey human monkey. That's
that's his name like saying or something. Isn't that the wedgie dance? Yeah, I
know you're talking about in the Tarzan. Yeah, isn't he not even Donny Donny?
He's not even one of the he's not even like the he's a boy that this show this.
I hated the show and I felt it made me feel uncomfortable because of this
character Donny. This guy, if this guy should be killed, I knew a couple of
Donny's growing up to you that were uncomfortable by a boy who just lived
his life. No, they kidnap him from somewhere. They find him in the woods.
That's what I'm saying. He's already wearing. It's not a kidnap. That's a
that's a discovery. He's half naked and he licks his foot.
And this clearly has some kind of developmental
his developmental disability is that he was raised by
that's true and Z's, but I don't think chimpanzees lick their feet.
Chimpanzees lick their feet. Also, chimpanzees have have they have the
the freest life they do whatever the hell they want to kill each other. They
kill each other, kill each other, because they live others babies. This
guy, this guy, they're hanging with chimpanzee. There are some people who
kill each other and eat their babies. Do you guys think this guy wears pants
yeah because they wouldn't show a cartoon child penis on the show? Why
not because of the if it wants to be accurate to the chimpanzee, you want to
see a child's penis? No, but I'm interested in science. He's interested
accurate so that I don't mean this children don't think that chimpanzees
wear pants chimpanzees.
I'm thinking this is at least a point.
Chimpanzees don't wear pants on the show. Darwin wears pants on the show.
I think the other chimpanzees wear pants. I don't I don't think they had
chimpanzees other than Darwin. They'd had a million. I just think it's kind
of rude personally to the human race to be having a chimpanzee that can speak
English and a human that can't a human that there's way more. There's way
are humans and he says he had a buggy.
Okay, this is something you should Darwin after the guy who
discovered that he turned into himself. Yeah point.
I'm trying to puzzle this out.
They made him Darwin, which is the guy who said the monkeys
are humans and they need they named was Darwin supposed to be
the missing link.
We need a gritty reboot of where the wild thornberry.
Yeah, where Mr. Thornberry is he just straight up is kidnapping the kid.
Yeah, it's about colonialism.
Holy.
Yeah, exactly.
It takes place in like the like 1600s or something.
Yeah, and well, then how would they have a TV show?
The whole point of the wild Thornberry is that they have a TV show.
They're writing a play.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh, they're traveling play.
They're a traveling troop.
A mummer's troop.
Yeah, exactly.
And they mum.
What's a mummer's troop?
Somebody is not well-versed in the bard.
Yeah, minus one point.
my Marie no Bard info no Bard knowledge. I'm giving a shit about the low Bard
not I don't give a shit about the bar. You better chill okay. They are a
Bard.
I'm not going to even buzz you for that because you know what you did. I like I
like flipping you off. You like flipping off Bard. I like flipping off. He
doesn't even know who the bar. How many Shakespeare
yeah, that's who the Bard is
what
All right, point, I guess. You played the song.
I don't think Shakespeare was so much of it. Shakespeare was the bard.
Shakespeare didn't even... Shakespeare was the bard. No, he didn't even exist.
The name "the bard" means Shakespeare. No, what I'm saying is that he didn't
even exist. So he was not the bard. Oh, he was a group of people?
No, he didn't even exist, period. He was... He's... All that shit was written
by the pope. No. The pope. That's my theory. That's a minus point for you
for being religious. Conspiratorial thinking. That's kind of random. Yeah,
you're being random. No, no, no. Or somebody, I don't know who wrote it,
but it wasn't Shakespeare. He didn't exist. He existed. Did you ever read
that thing that was like every time Shakespeare signed his name, he signed it
differently? Have you ever seen that every time he signed his name? He signed
it differently, and one of the times that he signed his name, he wrote William
Shake Staff.
See, the guys didn't even know who they were. These guys didn't even know who
they were doing. Also, I love the
shake. What was it? I love the idea that if it was three guys, it would be any
less impressive that he that all these amazing plays.
I signed my name different every single time the barista turns one of those fucking iPads.
Oh, Shakespeare must have worked at Starbucks!
Yeah!
[applause]
Which yo bitch ass?
Shakespeare.
He worked at Starbucks.
He worked at Starbucks and he was writing people's names on them.
Yep, his own damn name.
And they flipped that thing over, that iPad, and I got a sign for using my card.
I'm straight line.
Yeah, 0% straight line. No tip. When I was, I was at the grocery store and I
had to sign my name after use my credit card and I signed it and the
the enter button wasn't working and I was like, oh, the enter button's not
working and she was like, okay, and she cleared it and then she signed it
and pressed enter. And I wanted to say, I'm calling the police. I saw what
you did. I'm not paying. Oh, you wanna pay for it? Yeah. Did she do it?
Did she try to report fraud right now? Yeah. Did she try to do a
her signature or did she just did she basically what I do it, which is just
as what if she wrote Cameron Fetter? What if she wrote your full that would be
scary because I don't know how she would know my name that quick from the card
info that can you get away with that by by claiming insurance for credit card
fraud? If you just sign something like bug or something, I think in the era
before CCTV, I bet people were doing that every day. Yeah, it makes sense.
That's what I that's also back in the day. You could go into a grocery store
you could be like put it on Kevin's tab. Yeah, five hundred dollars of
bring back tabs right now. They have we need to have the stores, though
they have everywhere you can. You can just like leave your card at a bar
and then just like
not with a card and also at stores. Okay, you should be able to start a
tab at a bar before credit cards, you leave and then just fucking see it.
It's not yeah, it's not like a tab you pay at the end of the
night. Yeah, because I want to say put it on my tab so bad,
but not have still say it, but there's like you're actually paying for yeah
you're paying for in the moment. Yeah, you know what there's a bar and if you
leave they charge twenty percent. Well, it used to be also that if you tried to
move towns, you would probably die in the process. Yeah, so that's kind of the
insurance against it. I guess if this guy wants to move and skip towns, he's
gonna be eaten by a snake. Yeah, there's a bar downtown, a bar downtown, not a
bard, a bard down under the ground, but I think many I think many of a bards
they have have
gotten drinks there. There's a bar where they didn't realize they still had
after pay
like you have to pay it. No, I think Ben did, though, but you think you bought
like two drinks and
why would they have it? I don't know. I don't know why they have it. Yeah, they
say after pay. They had after pay set up on the thing, so he's paying like a
$1.25 every two weeks for like drinks. He got one that's not that crazy because
you have no pants and stuff. That's not that true. I was after pay for sure
and sure in a pair of shoes that I'm wearing shoes.
You after paid for those yeah. Oh my God after pay, you know if you have your
base amazing, it's better because if you die, then you had more money when you
died exactly yeah, yeah,
take that when you die, the number that they print on your gravestone is a
little higher. Yeah, we should be after paying everything dude after pay is
incredible. You should be able to I think you can after pay groceries. I
think you can after pay basically everything. Yeah, well, I mean, I guess
a credit card is just after pay isn't it? Yeah, yeah, basically the same
thing you do you have to get approved for after pay now wow zero percent apr
wait, there's no interest. Yeah, it must that doesn't make any more or the
just paying like you're still paying the whole thing. It's just over the
course of there has to be, but it must go through their system. Maybe there's
some interest or something. I don't know. They have a PayPal style. Look, I
just saw the word zero percent APR and I was like, fuck it. I'll do that. And
you saw that little star next to zero percent APR. That means yay. Yes, I love
that little star star. Every single every single thing.
Deal paid every single thing. I've ever sparkling deal after paid or clarnoed
has been paid off. Klarna is another thing that you pay an installment. What
is that one of these new streaming services? No, it's one point. It's not a
point.
I know why he said it. Not you. Yeah, it was made me look fucking. We all left.
We all laughed so hard that we all left at that. It's not a streaming service.
We know that now. Okay, Mr. Okay, okay. What a service was. We are. I've
already explained the service. I think you might be a sociopath who hates fun
in the service. I don't point I don't impression. I don't hate fun. You hate
fun so much, which is you guys wear me seven points. You guys wear me down till
I would like to wear your skin point. Honestly, if I could crawl inside you
and live in there like a city, I would build the most glorious monument to my
love for you. I don't think you do what
he said. He didn't think I do. I was microscopic. I would build something out
of the plaque on your tongue. I would build a shrine to I would live inside of
and I would my job would be I would be one of the seven dwarves and I'd go into a
tunnel inside your kidney stone and I'd be mining in there. Yeah, and I get
beautiful gems and where okay point to where on his body you want to live 321.
What are you pointing to his elbow? I'm pointing to this inside his body in
general. I want to be in one of his organs that's in the stomach area. I'm
just I'm just letting this roll. I think his elbow it would be scraped by
I'm worried I got psoriasis. Yeah, my grandpa had it. Could be diet. No, it just happens.
Could be genetic, could be diet. I think my grandpa had psoriasis. Doesn't matter at all.
if I buddy if my skin starts flaking off like a like a that's happened in my head
yeah remember when I had a scale a reptilian I remember when you had a you
had a reptile thing going on for a little bit that's what I'm saying it
just happens then it doesn't have I still go to the reptile Expo in
Manchester yeah I still want to go to that they have it all over they probably
have one in New York yeah in fact I know for a fact they do and it's probably in
the next couple months true it's the best climate usually in August I think
sometimes I feel like I'm already in a wreck. I would love to go. A raccoon is
not a reptile. I didn't finish what I was saying because you said raccoon. I was
going to say I feel like I'm in a reptile exhibit sometimes when I'm with
you guys, because you're both fucking snakes backstabbing me and biting my
ankles. No, I'm a lizard more than a snake. Yeah, both of you Komodo dragon.
Both of you are spineless animals. Spines have snakes and on them. Yeah,
snakes. So you're something then you're in Octo. Maybe I can take an eel. You
you guys did not see this octopus video that me and you be a saw. I did what
happened to be a you pull up the octopus video. You showed me the octopus video.
What was in the you need to see this? I got a video sound everybody who is
listening. Pull this up. Don't tell me he goes into a quarter or something. No,
it's an I love when they do that. It's an octopus. Don't say anything about it.
That don't just let just seriously don't spoil his points because the way we
saw this video, this video fully caught us completely off guard. This is the most
the greatest video I've ever seen in my entire life. Amazing by young easy
amazing, I think some grazed back by someone else in that sashimi. Oh, no,
just no, just wait, just wait for this video giant octopus. Okay, and I think
it's around five minutes. Yeah, it's really good. Okay, all right, I'll watch
this. I mean the clip is so you're in charge of of describing what this is.
okay, so it's well the sound and this is really important. So honestly, I just
want everybody to hear the sound and I'll describe it afterwards. Okay, that
looks like all the way up all the way up. It looks like a butthole. Okay,
now watch here,
it's coming out of the computer to be it's coming out of the computer. Yeah,
wait, change the output
is a great
okay. This is here we go. Okay, now I can hear it all right. So he's got this
octopus, so he just boiled very large. He's about to cut it up. It's a giant
octopus. Oh, thank God of the aliens man. Look at that. That's his penis right
there under its head. No, that's it. That's his mouth. That's not his mouth.
You have never played
dad. Oh God. I hate when they get cut. Watch this part now. Watch silently.
what we just saw is a sushi chef cut an octopus and a jizzed into its own by
it's not jizz
directly into his own butthole yeah and then the chef puts his two fingers into
the but
my God
and then the but pro lapses a little piece of black squid. I do not like
the other said no. It
we were just watching a bunch of recipe videos and that just happened and none
of the comments mentioned at all. There's one comment that links the
timestamp and that's it no it's completely it's so insane. The craziest
thing I've ever seen in my life and I mean imagine if you got killed and
somebody made you your dead body jizz into your butt that happens. It doesn't
happen that happens. You release every single fluid in your body. I don't think
you release jizz yeah the way I'm going to die
David Carradine probably did. This guy made him do it. Oh, he was dead for a
while. This is honestly one of the worst videos I've ever seen.
This is the best octopus in Peter North. But his flesh is cut. Yeah. And he
probably still - an octopus never dies. Yeah. The thing of an elephant never
forgets. Ah, shit. Yeah. That's pretty cool, actually. Octopus can't be one of
God's creatures. No, the devil made that thing. Did you guys see the documentary
My Octopus Teacher? No. Is that the one where the guy fell in love with the octopus?
The guy fucks the octopus. He doesn't fuck him, he just thinks he's beautiful.
Octopuses are pretty insane. They're crazy. They're amazing. They're very
incredible. They really are. They're from another planet. Some people say that
they did come here on an asteroid. I believe that. I believe that. There's no
no way
no way in my favorite, my favorite like Facebook fake news type articles that
I've seen is like it was an article. It was an all capitalist. It scientists
confirm that octopuses are ninety eight percent aily. It's true, it's true, it's
got to be came here on a meteor yeah, that's what I heard. I heard they
landed in a ship. They probably had a hard time controlling it because their
arms go willy nilly. Yeah, it's a scientific. Did you know that I so I
lift up octopus jizz after I watched that video. I watch it about a hundred
times. Do you know the way that octopuses fuck? Yeah, a male has a
special arm. What is one of his arms? He's got eight of them, but he has one
special one that he just wait. That's his plus one or seven. No, it's a
seven. Okay, so it's well, it's just an arm, but it just also has this
function where he it's his penis arm, I guess, and he just sticks it inside of
the female's brain. That is what we should be doing. He just puts it.
There's a diagram of it and he just puts it up into her and then the sperms come
of his hand saluting him. He's doing he's doing Heil into his head. You're trying
to do this into your skull. You're not trying to do this. You were doing. I'm
trying to do this. Maybe that's where they got it. Maybe that's where they got
the arm from. That makes sense. They were fucking weird. They tried to find the
isn't that their logo. They should do a Monty Python and the Holy Grail thing
about the Nazis doing that. Yeah. Isn't that the Nazis logo, though? It's a
the rangers of the lost ark.
Red with black squid on it.
Yeah, it's a black squid.
Yeah.
That's their famous logo, is a red with a black squid.
All right, this thing made me have to pee.
We have to end.
We have to end?
We have to done?
Can we keep going?
You can go pee.
Okay, I'm going to go pee.
We're busy.
We're busy talking about octopuses.
Go, feel free.
I don't care.
Yeah, Caleb loses points for having to go pee.
That sucks that it wasn't individual points.
I also found this article about a squid that impregnated a woman's mouth.
his mouth. When she was eating it, it was cooked, but then it's a giant sperms got
embedded into her mouth. Wait, how did it? How did the mouth get pregnant? It
just has a living inquire, a story. No, it was on ABC News. Oh woman's mouth
falls pregnant to twelve square.
Oh, she was sixty three. She's already old and now she's got a fucking. She was
chewing sperm sacks, which forcefully shoot sperm. That was her first mistake
sperm in turn, try to embed themselves when they land, but yeah, she just ate
what is it look like? Did they show her mouth? They don't show it now. That's
the most interesting part. I don't think that I think that looks amazing, though
that does that's what she was eating that calamari. No, she was eating eastern
calamari, but it says western calamari fans need not worry. The things they do
in the east are a mystery to me.
See the comments here. How much did the meal cost her six squid? LL get it from
get a six squid. Oh, I get happy seven seven seven comments. That's
disgusting.
This is what people do in the UK. All the parasites from raw fish as well
sickening. What is what a load of rubbish from J B? What a load of
rubbish
yeah
the this, but this happens, I guess a squids and sperms live on after it's
been cooked. Oh man yeah, I don't fuck with squids. I think it's good to eat
them. I think it's very, very good. A very good is a delectable, maybe my favorite seafood.
Really? Honestly, I don't like a lot of them, right? You like, I like it all. I eat sushi.
I eat a lot of sushi. Actually, you know, rich ass motherfucker here. I eat the sushi sucks.
Cheap sushi. You've already tried to say this. You're just trying to tank your score. Sushi
is shit. You're trying to take your score. So I don't care. I've had all levels of sushi
at all level zero still up.
Still up by eight points. Patrick.
I do. She
levels and one to a hundred.
You're not had
level 100.
None of us have had love.
I have had I've had Harris Teeter sushi from the grocery store and I've had
sushi from some of the greatest master chefs in the right.
Have you ever had sushi from the gas station?
I've had sushi the other day.
I had sushi was a sumo.
the hell a wall green sushi bragging. I am bragging, Paul Green Sushi is
terrible. That is level two. I was level fifty. There was
there was a gas station in I think yeah around Laconia, where I or I went to
community college and my roommate would come home with sushi from there all the
time and he was like yeah, it's fine. It's like good sushi. It's not and I
know I don't know what they were doing with this gas station I think one of the
ingredients on it was like some I think there's one of the ingredients like to
keep the sushi red was like because it was like sushi with like a list of
ingredients that was way too long well they got all the station food yeah to
preserve that sushi there's no way that gas station sushi isn't cooked I do
think that sushi it doesn't I can't imagine it being safe to eat it depends
done, which I know it's completely safe to eat and I'm sure it depends, but it
just doesn't seem right. You know what I'm gonna think that's like. I think in
a way, if I didn't know about sushi existing sushi or fish is maybe the
little meat. I would not want to eat raw. Hold on. Hold on all of them. Let
me let me just say let me I meant that I got a I got a I forgot to apologize to
for something. What'd you do? I have to issue an apology to our producer
do you do if you want to get on screen
to accept this apology or deny it's kinda hard for me to uh... here okay uh...
so last night i was asking for uh... reference photos
for but the in the poster for pictures of our faces
and uh...
do you be o uh... let's let's just say
he uh...
i thought he was uh... trolling me
now now
and in a at the go pro cam to be a in a in a fit of rage
uh...
my my girlfriend was is kind enough to uh... draw this poster for us
and because i was getting trolled by jubilee last night i uh... commission
her with a snack
and said can you please draw this
uh... immediately
and come to my defense i'm being trolled
and uh... she drew this
wall
which is boobie oh
and I just want to say that I'm sorry. Do you be a why I'm apologizing? Why you
remove the points? Did he didn't even know you did that until right now you
didn't have this could have stayed between you and your girlfriend in the
group chat is in the group show. I don't I saw this. You sent a photo you sent a
reference for Joe. My Joe my way also if we're getting into this, I need my
photos to be shown and I need I need to get some I need to get some there's my
photo.
That's a nice photo. One of my best photos. So look at show the photo that I
sent my girlfriend said she needed a and now read what you said. No, no, no, no
explanation. Just I need a better photo with your hair cam with my hair. Okay.
Now what did Cameron send? I okay. I said that because my girlfriend told me
show the photo that Cameron said it's just a photo of his hair, but you know
why? Because he's following orders because my hair was already in the first
fucking photo and I'm not I'm not a model for you. Not a model for me. It's
a model for somebody who's who's drawing a picture of you and they're trying to
make you look amazing. So they were here looked great in that picture. It's
fine. Why are you being such a baby? I wasn't being the baby. You are a baby.
I wasn't being a baby. I was I was you think the person drawing it was being a
baby. No, I think that they were trying to be exact, and I think that they were
trying to be
they could have
exactly what the fucking photo was, which is he had his hair exactly in the
photo, exactly the way my hair is, and let me just say I don't want to. I'm not
I'm not going to bring this. I'm not going to bring this feud any further past
today because I think it's silly, but I was very offended. You were offended. I
was offended. Yeah. This was a horrible apology, Patrick. This is a horrible
apology. How is this a horrible apology? I was apologizing to Jubio. You only
made it worse. I was apologizing to Jubio and then somehow I've made it,
I've made Cameron upset. Because you think I don't have hair. It's not that I
think that you don't have hair. Just the question was, can you ask him for a
better photo where I can see all of his hair, all of his hair. You said Mo like
you were going to say Mohawk. Mo is my cat.
It's a different guy. I still am not allowed to get a Mohawk really divorce
divorce, divorce, take that ring back, instant divorce right now. Did I tell
you that I already tell the ring story? No, okay, this will be four point,
end point. This will close on this. So I got my girlfriend a ring that was, well my
fiancee a ring, that was from our family safe deposit box. It's like a family
heirloom and we had to go get it appraised so we could get it insured, you know, and it's
it's like an opal ring, not like a diamond ring, so nothing so fancy, but we
said we took, we had to take a picture of it, like we were making an appointment
with this this jeweler to get it appraised. We took a picture of it and
like emailed it to this person like, "Hey, can we come in and get this ring appraised?"
praise and this jeweler guy responded and he's like he said honestly just
looking at this ring. It's not even worth my time to appraise it. This ring
is a piece of shit. Do not email me again.
He said piece of shit. He said something along those. So you're not
going to get shirts for it. We took it to another place and they did it
completely. It was just a guy who was really
that's so
not even worth my time, not even worthless man. This guy's badass. So
sick. What a beast. Yeah, really was making me laugh quite a lot. So that's
a lesson. All you fellas out there spring for the diamond. Yeah, girls
don't care that your grandma wore the ring. Okay, they want the most
expensive bullshit in the world, especially at restaurants. Yeah, so
true. And at the store, I heard a story from my friend yesterday, me and
Juvio's friend. I won't say his name because I don't want to give out his
information and I don't want to tell you what country he lives in even, but
it's not America. He went on a first date to two days shut up on a first date two
days ago,
and he goes out to a bar and this guy's poor as dirt. He has no money, and they
go out to a bar on a date and they get a drink, you know, and there was no
expectation there was going to be food. It was after dinner time, and the
waitress asked you guys want any food. He says yeah, we'll get some chicken
bites to split. Oh right, chicken bites, chicken bites. That must be something I
in a different country. Yeah, I know. What the hell? What is this exotic cuisine?
Buffalo chicken bites, basically wingless,
jingless twinging.
Wingers, zingers. Wingsings. Wingsings. So he gets zingers, right? Yeah. And
this girl orders
ahi ahi tuna.
$25 on the first day.
Wait, wait, where are they from? 'Cause maybe it's... Canada. Okay.
Oh dear. Yeah, they definitely do that. I mean if they if she ordered like a tuna or something or the albacore tuna
Maybe I could see I could understand that he ah he ah he that's hey, that's far away from Canada
Yeah, what also I where is I he but I just wanted to say that's and I said to him
I was like buddy if you're into women get used to this kind of bullshit
they pull that into women. Stop. They're going to order. They're every single
time that you go to a restaurant with them. They're going to order the most
expensive thing. That is the smallest thing on the menu. Somehow they have a
they have a mathematical equation. They do in their head a formula. Yeah,
because and she's trying to test you. She's doing means testing, which by the
way should be illegal. Yep, she's doing means testing for you. So you need to
drop her. Yeah, yeah. So that's and if you're wondering about means testing,
it means testing facts. Honestly, all testing should be erratic. I shouldn't
be testing things. I owe it. Just do this. Thank you. Okay, do it all right
real quick before we end final score. Jubeo
it says it right there. It says to negative twelve, the negative twelve. It
doesn't matter. You will be what matters is on July. Fourteen. There's a live
negative. Wow, enough, don't say enough like that. That's what there is a live
show. There is a live show at Littlefield July. Fourteenth, it's going to be us.
It's going to be home planet. It's going to be Pierce Campion and we wrote the
most amazing sketch today.
The I think honestly the greatest sketch that we have ever written in our entire
life. Do you want to maybe now we're not going to spoil it? We can't spoil it.
Fuck no man. He wants to know that if it doesn't make it to the final show, we
we'll be doing it live on this podcast.
Yes, we will.
That's a good idea.
We'll be doing this sketch live on the podcast and it will be either a cold open or just
in the middle of the episode.
All right, thank you.
Goodbye.
Thank you so much.