Okay, this is recording too.
So, Patrick, why do you have a book in your bag?
Or rather, let's start, what's in your bag?
What's in your bag?
Okay, so, I didn't think I was going to have to talk about this, but
Now you do. You flashed it on purpose.
I've been reading.
You have not been reading the Rent-is-all World History.
I've been reading lately. I've been trying to brush up on some stuff that I already knew.
Name one thing that happens in this book, and without opening it, you can't open it to read it.
today in
nineteen forty five World War Two ends
cetera.
Can I say I was one of the chapters? This is the second time that I've noticed a
book in his in his bag and do you know what the first book was that I noticed?
I do this one is a world history textbook for people who aren't who aren't
watching the video. The first time I noticed a book in his bag was a couple
weeks ago and he had in his bag a copy of the outsiders. Wow, a bad news is
I graduated to world history. Bad news, there's conflicting forces in Japan.
Right now? No, this looks like it started in the 1920s. I think there's
conflicting forces in Japan, the different Pokemon. Yeah, I think it's
I actually think it's... I think it's whites versus Japanese right now. I
think it's tradition versus technology. Guys who keep moving, white guys who
move over there. You think Japan is whites versus Japanese? I think right
That's Japan.
In the dating pool.
The dating pool in Japan is whites versus...
It's lanky little white guys or big fat white guys versus big fat Japanese guys and lanky
little Japanese guys.
Why are you...
If they have the same body types, why are you specifying the body types?
Because of their different stats and skills.
Who do you think has better stats, the whites or the Japanese?
I think personally, and this is based on stuff I've read in here, this book, I think personally
on the whites team, I think that lanky wins most of the time, but on the Japanese side,
big fat juicy boy.
And who do you think should win in the dating pool in Japan, whites or Japanese?
Japanese.
You think Japanese should only date Japanese people?
I think that Japanese guys...
Japanese guys. You learn this after you read world history and you got to the
end of World War Two and you came to this conclusion. That Japanese guys should
date white ladies. That's not what you said. In Japan. Let's try to get him
today. You try to get me every single day. Let's try to get him. Okay, here's
what's worrying me about this development. Here's what's worrying me.
Napoleon falls from power or unless that's good, I don't
actually don't know. Was Napoleon a good man or a bad man? I think he was small.
he was book and certainly small. This book ends in the cold war. Yeah, I don't
know what the curriculum is. It's all on the it's on the back. I'm it seems like
it's all in the back. What this kind of worries me, because it means it means
that you think that the podcast is going to fail and you will need to go back to
school. I've already been going back to school for what for history you're
studying history at what college curry curry college yeah online.
you're doing online history classes at curry college. Yes, to finish your
degree and this is my text. Do you think? Oh, you know what I think is
you're a spilling Susan. We have hand towels now. Oh yeah, I bought a hand
towel.
Go get it. Don't just let it do that. Get a hand towel right now. Let it
spill. Go. He's mad that I called him a spilling. Go whatever. Holy shit.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute, Cameron, you're going to get excited. Okay,
what's this?
Pages one sixteen through one seventeen. Oh, those I like that. Guess who shows
up?
Yeah, geez, let me guess a little and he's from okay. I'll give you yeah.
Give me some money. Let me guess. Okay,
he's big and yellow Sponge Bob. No, no, but you're on the right path. Okay,
Larry the Lobster, who turned yellow, what is wrong with your brain? He's
bigger than Sponge Bob, a big yellow guy from history, a big yellow guy from
what a big yellow guy from a cartoon. He's not in the book. It says it right
here.
117 I'll give you a hint. Bart's father too big of a hint. I think it's Mo. He
doesn't know anything about Homer shows up. So I knew that one 17 and says what
he was pretty early in his that's earlier than I thought. I thought it was
That's page 117.
Wait, what's it?
What is it?
How is he on?
Oh, yeah, different Homer.
Yeah.
What?
It's a different Homer.
Let's check.
Some fucking Greek loser.
Let's consult the book.
How funny is it that we named Homer Simpson after Homer Homer after Homer from the Odyssey.
Did guys have one name back then?
I believe so.
Right?
So they were Homer.
You'd say you're Homer and then you'd say what Homer, what your address was basically.
Yeah, that is what was your name? What would your name be if you were in
ancient Greece? You would be Patrick of what of
what's your address? My address is 2060 Gates Avenue.
You live there? Yeah, you don't live there. You don't live. I live. You just
made that up. Currently, I live there. That's a pizza place because of a
problem. Yeah, that's a pizza place with the worst pizza ever. Don't go. Do not
go. Go there. It's the worst pizza I've ever had in my life.
But yeah, I am a little worried about you giving up on the podcast because you're not giving
up. I'm just trying to maybe make the conversations a little bit more interesting. Right. Okay.
I'm actually really good at cleaning. I just look at your puddle under your stand. Yeah,
you are. You are sloppy. Well, guess what? This is your belate with no sugar in it. So
it's not sticky. So it actually doesn't matter. What happened? Food is a weapon. Food is a
as a weapon in one thousand nine hundred and thirty two when peasants failed to
meet unrealistic crop quotas, Stalin retaliated by seizing all of their grain
to sell on the market. Hello to more yes, wow crap and people idolize. We don't
more people idolize this Stalin figure. He's using food as though he's having an
international food fight. How cool well no because how despicably evil give me
that book right now. Don't drop that book. How despicably evil do you have to
way to take food, one of God's greatest gifts and use it as a
as a complete. Well, I was thinking something about God
this morning that this is kind of off top. What if God was on
the bus? No, I was thinking that basically Tom Cruise would
be such a horrible father and his children, maybe because he
was in Scientology. So maybe his children would suffer and
they wouldn't like him very much as a father. And if God
was good, then what he would do would be would let a Tom Cruise
fan of Tom Cruise's movies reincarnate as Tom Cruise's kid
and keep their memories, because that's the only way you could have tom cruise
have a kid and that what is like the psycho? Why you thought about this
earlier? This is not in the hour. No, I was after the shower. That's when you
get your best ideas yeah after the show yeah after the show when I'm clean. I
was thinking about mission impossible and I then I was thinking about that.
What kind of thoughts do you sit there having about mission impossible standing
and I was thinking I'm excited for mission possible.
You are a simpleton. I'm not a sim. It's less than a week till I get your not
impossible to read world history. I already read all that shit. Really
watching movies here. Tell me something. Tell me about the instability in
Ireland. It was rough for the Irish. It was right for the Irish. Yeah, points
points. Cameron, did you know that there was actually absentee landlords who
owned large estates but did not live in them? Remind you of any city in
America? Uh huh. New York and New York City. New York City is a bunch of
Saudi Arabian guys that have $400 million apartments and they don't live in them. But I actually
think I read that that was not true.
Yeah, I thought that my landlord left the country, but then I saw him.
Yeah. In the country?
Yeah, outside my house.
I saw our landlord for this building whipping it on an e-bike with his little helmet.
Yeah, he was getting it.
He was like going at fucking...
I can't even believe that.
What's that motorcycle guy?
China was at the Cold War's wild card.
really yeah wow they were kind of a bonus game because of the the information
they could spread well basically they or their population of one billion the
communist basically triumphed sadly oh yeah in the cold war yeah and they made
a bunch of red photos yeah they made a bunch of red photos
wait for example red photo red painting of a guy with a gun
holy cow if you guys were in china would you have stood in front of that
that tank I will be in the yeah
follow whatever possible career path. I could to be in that tank. Please God put
me in that fucking well. Why do you need to be there right now? If I had
my
watching on TV, I'd be getting such fucking FOMO. I'd be like fuck and I
would not be doing that left right. I would be going for
yeah, exactly. I would put a cannon thing in the guy's mouth. Shoot it
Actually, I would just start. I wouldn't even shoot it. Why do you think? Why do
you think
that should have been fucking me? I'm a certain me stood in front of that tank
because he was like, stop, let me in. Let me in. I want to
he was on the lunch run. Yeah, he was supposed to be in the tank. He was
supposed to be in the tank. He was supposed to be hanging out with them.
He was supposed to be helping them out. That actually is me when I in 10
years travel back in time to try to get into the tank and then I find out
but I'm the tank man. That's an amazing story. I just wrote that is an amazing
story. The guy who wants to go back so he can be in the tank. He thinks tank man is
the man in the tank and he goes back and he is trying to and he's like well, let
me get a snack for all my new friends and also a couple of twenty four ounce
sodas. Yes, and then he has. Do you think they had those in communist China? I
don't think they even I don't think they even had water. If you ask me really
yeah, it's just because of the because they treat people like machines. Yeah,
exactly what you read in here. They put gasoline in people's ears. Yeah,
really? No, I don't know. A hundred percent. I mean, it probably says, I
mean, we can consult, we can consult this. It probably says what they, what
they drank in here. Yeah, I feel like this says that
this book, this is a New York Discovery School textbook, probably liberal. I
think, no, I think that maybe, I mean, we're in Queens, I think that maybe
this book is saying that in China, they used to make all students eat poop.
Do you think a book changes based on where you are? Yes.
Let's see what it says about our Lord and Savior.
That's what I'm interested in.
That's a good point.
How far back does it go?
Does it start in Mesopotamia?
I really hope.
Why does it say New York table of contents?
Oh,
ancient Rome and the rise of Christianity.
Yes.
That's a whole chapter.
Okay, let's see.
166.
Hold on.
Let's see what it says about God.
About the one.
Probably says nothing.
It probably says absolutely nothing.
It probably says something like.
Romana a new religion Christianity arose in a distant corner of the Roman Empire.
They're already trying to qualify it. Yeah. Oh, it was so far away from Rome.
It wasn't directly in the Coliseum. Shut up
with the culturally diverse Roman Empire various religious beliefs coexisted
Jupiter Mars Juno. That's two planets and a movie that is not any kind of
religion. Yeah, Juno is what was that one? That's June. No, that's June in
in Spanish, but what planet is Juno Juno's a moon of Saturn in the movie.
I don't know as big as a one of the planets have possibly a trillion moons.
You'll like this Patrick. You'll like this next part. A Jewish rebellion is
defeated. What do you mean that like that part? I just don't like that. Isn't
that what you strive for? No most of the time to defeat a Jewish. My look my
Jew, me and my Jewish rebels
we are a bell against undefeated. We are undefeated, you're on me and all my
rebelling against Judy, you know my J. You plus Jews are under the dogs.
They're my J. Dog, we got him again
a double G's double G
D, A, W, double G, D, W. If you oh my God, if you were in there, if you were
an ancient Christian, D, W, I don't get her ass out of there. I would like to be
walking up to everyone in history, just saying shit like it's my turn. Yeah,
tank man. She walks up to tank man saying get the hell out of the street.
It's my turn to stand here. Yeah. Oh, my God, and today it would probably be
blown up today would probably be Tesla man or something or Tesla woman,
Tesla in the square, Tesla, anion devil,
the Tesla anion devil. What's that a guy? It's a little guy. That's one of
the cars. He runs on a lithium ion battery. I think I want to buy an
electric car. The thing is about Tesla...
You should get rid of your car.
Shut up!
Your car is like...
My car is awesome.
Your car is on its last limbs.
It doesn't have limbs, it has wheels. It's on its last wheels.
Cars are... wheels are a car's limbs.
You watch too many cartoons.
I watch too much car... I've never actually seen cars.
Really? I've seen cars over a hundred times.
I think Pixar fell off.
Over a hundred times.
Easily. Easily a hundred. My little brother used to watch cars every single day and I
I had to watch him and I would watch Cars every single day.
At that point when Cars came out I was already watching like Jackass and like Naviva La Bam.
I thought Cars was gay. I thought liking Cars as in the vehicles was gay.
Whoa!
That too. That's what I thought as a kid.
As you get older though you realize that it's actually kind of cool.
Realize it's actually kind of gay.
It's not gay to like Cars.
I like El Caminos because that's what my name is Earl Drove.
Oh yeah he did.
did. He had a really busted El Camino that had a purple door, or a blue door. He had a
blue door on the side of it and he had a brother named Randy who was a fatso who was in love
with Catalina the maid. My name is Roman. If you were an ancient Roman and they pull up
up. My name would be played in my name is played in. If you were an ancient Roman
and the disciples pulled up on you and said yo mother fucker, yo played in hop
into chariot, we're going to Bethlehem. Would you go? Would you believe in
Christ? Because I like to say I like to think that I was going there to beat the
fuck out of pretty sure they're beating him. Okay, no, if I was there when he was
to doing stuff. I think there's a decent chance. I think that if you're if
somebody turns water to wine in front of you before you know about magic tricks,
you have to believe he's God. Yeah,
what I yeah. Do you think Jesus was just doing magic? What I want to know, I
think he was. I mean, could do you think that couldn't a Roman person wrote
there's not it's not like a Roman mythology didn't have some kind of
monster that could turn water into wine or something, but with Roman mythology,
I think they all knew it was not really when they were on their way to
Bethlehem. They were Roman because you could like if I was a Roman guy and I
was into and there was nobody up there. I was into Jupiter and Mars and
whatever. I would be like, Oh my God, this must guy must be Jupiter. I
wouldn't think this is a new type of God. I honestly also starts with J
completely new thing. I probably would be a little bit like well. We already
have cooler God. Yeah, yeah, eyes and shit like you want. I guess it would
kind of like Pokemon where I'd be like, I want to go back to the first game where there's
only like one or two. Yeah. You want me to like, there's too many. Now they have just
a normal guy. Yeah. The guy with long girly hair. He's really good at cooking. That's
his thing. He can make a bunch of food. He can make bread into fish. No. Right? No, he
can make bread and fish appear. Oh, okay. I thought he'd turn the bread into fish. I
thought it was a lot of, uh, what is it? Transmorphication. Thanks for the... He was doing... Transmorgifying
transifying what's trend, not trans modifying chair and that's a Calvary
Hobbs. Yeah, that's a thing. I thought that's what Christ was doing was with
the bread transubstantiation. You you you to you to you know who you to remind me
of goofus and gallant, who's who
this is goofus and you are gallant gallant was fire gallant. This was a
piece of shit about that. You don't think you're goof. I've never seen
Goofus so you didn't you didn't read highlights. Goofus would not
read Goofus and Gali. He did not know the difference between right and wrong.
Yeah,
he looks cool. He looks like actually wait, go back. You think Goofus is cool.
You're Goofus. Go back. You Goofus for real.
Go back to those. Go back to yeah. He looks like
Karen Carpenter
I didn't know the Carpenters had a song called Goof. It's not a very good name
song. I bet this song is probably pretty cutting for goofus. I bet he does not want to hear
that one. How incredibly dumb do you have to be as a parent to name your child goofus?
You don't know. That's like naming your kid Karen. You're putting them down the wrong
path instantly. I feel like if you named your kid goofus, I think that you had maybe the
epidural hit you a little too hard. The epidural. Oh, the thing that makes the pussy sound?
the pain. So I was a kid reading. Is that what it does? I thought it was a
painkiller. Yeah, dilates their vaginas. Oh, I thought that it was. I thought
that that was like the same as dilated. No, I think they get. I think they
get fentanyl. Now I heard a story. I want to get if I were real quick.
If I was a kid and I was reading goofus and gallant, I would be
reading it and I would be like, well, this is all very interesting,
but thank God my name isn't goofus or gallant and I can just be
a normal kid. Yeah, it must be really hard. If your last name was
goofish see that would be tough yeah. Mike goofus yeah. What if you only knew
Japanese and then you started reading goofus and gallant and you read gallant
and goofus and you thought that goofus was the good one. Oh, you're reading
right to left. Well, they still do the things they still translate it. Yeah,
so well they're still drawings. I'm doing this stuff yeah, but you think
that the last one's the good. They will be captioned. Oh, you can't think that
the last thing done is you can't yeah. You can't read even though it's called
gallant and goofus yeah, but you don't know what that means either
right you're thinking even read it. You're just looking at the pictures.
I said these are two things. The second guy would be the thing would be the
good one. If there was two and it's supposed to teach you a lesson. So all
of a sudden you're the one you're putting you're doing pranks, you're
putting salt in the sugar and you have no one to tell you. Otherwise,
we may be gallant could show up.
He's not real Patrick.
You didn't even know he existed until right now and you're already thinking
that there's a guy you're telling me about yeah. These are two people. I
you? Yeah. No, they're drawings. You, you, they're cartoon stories all the time.
Like, oh, and we, we used to, you're the one who would have friends,
Ben Gufus and Gallant. Yeah. I never said we used to, you are the
one with the Theo Vaughn stories. I do not say that I ate a
bullfrog. I never do anything like that. You, you, you told me, I used to
hit myself in the nuts. That's all I used to do. You told me,
that's the only crazy thing of my life. You said that you made a
kid in your neighborhood paint your fence white. That never happened, man.
You would say, you say, oh, I made this, when I, like,
growing up. We used to have this kid called fucking bullfrog and we there was
no you had a friend named chowder. We would really name different. We would
pay him. You had a buffet of friends. We did make him do stuff you that's what it
is. You would a friend. You were crazy and you had food friends. Admit it. You
were sitting in your house right now. I had this is my friend. Yeah, you say
mom, please catch a mustard come over later.
Your mom says ketchup can come over, but mustard is a bad and yeah, mustard is a
I must go everywhere together. I can't invite just one of them. Their best
friends. They live in that big white house in our kitchen. Oh my God, when
your mom is like you have to invite broccoli to your birthday party. I
fucking like mom. I want to invite crunch bar. Yeah, crunch bars. I want
crunch bar lolly. He's not a good cat. You guys remember any birthdays from
when you were growing up. I remember my brother's like
fifth birthday, because he tried to blow out the candles by spitting on them. No,
I remember my first birthday after I started being home. You don't remember
you're okay, not my first
I was going to say you say stuff like that all the time. Remember your first
you do say you remember your first I had remember my first birthday. I left
was your first memory, my first memory, the thing that's happening right now. I
can remember now. So you just tried to say I think he knows yeah
I can remember I claimed for a long time. I could remember my first steps.
I claim that to my mom. She's like no, you can't yeah. I was like you're
probably right. I used to say shit like that all the time. There was like
in kindergarten. They had like a thing in the back of the like kindergarten
yearbook. That was like kids say the darndest things and it was they would
just write down shit that kids in the classroom said and like a good chunk of
it was stuff that I would just like try to say to the teachers. So I would sound
cooler. What would you tell the teacher? I told my teacher that I saw the Statue
of Liberty when I moved to America from Boston.
And that's like that's back. Yeah, that is a darn thing. Yeah, it is a darn thing for
sure. My first birthday. Oh, my mom knew Christopher Columbus. Those are the most
wild lies I've ever heard. How old were you? I was five. Oh, I think I was like,
Oh, yeah, my mom knows that guy. I first day of first grade, I told everybody in
the class that I had been skydiving. Wow. The day before. Sick. Yeah, it's cool. And nobody
believed me, but it was true. It wasn't true. I remember my first birthday after I started
being homeschooled. I like left sixth grade and then over the summer didn't really see
anybody then I have my well, I guess it was the next year, but I had my first birthday
after that. I invited like all my middle school friends and they had all hit puberty and I
So I was just a little ass kid and just like eight grown men walked in and they all were
trying to have sex with my mom.
And I had to get in between them.
They, "No!"
Hey, if you want to have sex with my mom, you're going to have to go through me first.
And then they did.
That's what you did.
What's that?
I hissed at them.
You did the dog whisperer.
Oh, the Caesar Milan.
Yeah.
You should be able to train people like that.
Have you seen this guy Jackson Galaxy?
No.
He's like Caesar Milan for cats.
Cats do not need to be anything.
anything. Your cat needs to be put down. You like him, you just pretend like you don't like
him on the podcast. You like him, he cuddled up on you. He cuddled up on you and you were
holding him and you were like he's cool. He can sense it. Well, he still likes my cat
and he doesn't want to admit it. You like Phil and you don't want to admit it. I admit
that I like actually all the time. You don't feel and I are feeling our good
friends now. Phil likes you a lot more than like me. Clancy does not like me.
One Joe's dog Clancy hates Joe's dog. It's just every single time. It's the
nicest dog in the entire world until he sees Patrick. He turns into a complete
because I walked in with a skateboard one time and the wheels were still
spinning. It's also because every time I tried to show it to him so that he I
I didn't I don't know how to go socialize with dogs and I tried to show it to him
to show him that it wasn't a threat and then he ran over and tried to bite me.
You walk like a monster at him. You do when I have a heavy step and he doesn't
like loud noise directly towards him. I don't do that much that I don't know
what did I do and you inject him with things. I've still let me Joe Joe told
to feed him a Cheez-It so that he would stop barking at me.
And did it work?
Yes.
No, it didn't.
It did. It worked for a little while.
And then I moved a chair.
It was a spicy Cheez-It. It was a prank Cheez-It. I had one and it spiced me out.
Didn't spice you. You have a crazy low tolerance.
I used to have an extremely high tolerance and then as you know I was dosed.
You were dosed?
I've told you this before.
What happened?
My cousin, Nicholas, dosed me with pure capsaicin when I was 16 years old.
Oh.
he spent all year synthesizing pure capsaicin from a fucking Carolina Reaper.
No, that's what they just call like bell peppers down in Australia, down under.
A Carolina Reaper?
No, just they call capsaicin.
All peppers are called capsaicin down there.
They are so backwards and upside down.
They call it the name of the chemical?
Yep.
That's weird.
That's really weird.
Australia is... people don't talk about how fucking weird it is down there.
I think that they do pretty often.
Their toilets are weird.
often. What do you mean? I think there's an entire Simpsons episode actually.
What? Knifey Spoony. Yeah, but that's a Crocodile Dundee parody. I mean,
noping the fuck out when I see Australian wildlife. Crocodile Dundee is
like... You know what I've heard from people? He's Australian, but that's like
a parody or whatever. People who I know in Australia have literally gone home
with a girl,
a couple of drinks, right? I'm not gonna say they're sober. They go home with
a girl, they wake up the next day. She's a crocodile? It's a fucking spider.
it's a giant black spider. Oh, it's biting their finger. You I saw a picture
on Twitter. It's a sperm crawled into someone's shower. Oh, I saw that. Did
you see that? There a sperm and Australian wild sperm? Yeah, they got
they float in the air. It's called like a rat tailed bug or something.
No, it's not. Yeah, it is. It's called a rat tailed bug, Australian sperm,
wild sperm crawled in my ear.
wanted a few good. This is Jubio. You did not look up the right thing. I
wonder if I if I can look up a rat tail bug, look up rat tailed bug,
Australia. No, this is not. No, it's all sperm. Wait, have you guys? Sorry,
this whale thing just made me think of this. Have you guys heard that there
have been five shark attacks on Long Island in the last two days, but Long
Island on Long Island on the South Shore Long Island,
that can't be what it is. That is what it is. That's not that is a right to
bug. Yeah, a wild sperm crawled across their foot. It looks like a finger with
a long nail. Isn't it crazy? Yeah, that's disgusting. So get this you'll
like this Cameron yeah
five shark attacks in two days, but every single one of the people
was a whale. They did not see a shark and they didn't see what bit them. So
they're alleged shark attacks, but people, but they have been putting out
drones to like like out on the sea to see because you can see usually the
sharks and where they're where they're swimming. I have trackers too, but they
cannot find any sharks. That's crazy. Some kind of aquatic animal that is not
a shark has been biting people. I've been saying avatar two is coming. It's
coming out in real life. That's what it may be. I was like this is happening
now. I
okay, tell tell what you said about avatar being okay. So first of all,
there's the orca attacks. Yeah, that are orcas attacking ships that happens in
Avatar 2, Paya Khan, the rebel Tolkien sinks the ship. Yes, I remember this.
Yeah, a Tolkien. It's like a Pandora and whale, but they're highly intelligent.
Yeah, and also very emotional. And they sing and speak, and there's a musical
number. They can speak, but they don't sing, and there's no musical number. And
they love. There was also submarines. There's submarines in Avatar 2 that go
down.
The submarine was going down to... Oh, my God. To the Titanic in real life. James
Cameron's favourite movie. What happens in Avatar 2, a giant boat sinks, and
there's submarines involved. He did another boat sinking movie. It's so
sick. You didn't see it. No, I haven't seen Avatar to whoa. I don't go to the
movies. Blue people. Well, it's on Disney plus and a way of people where I can't
watch movies. I will be coming soon. That is the next thing. Yeah, so
just keep raspberry. Just keep an eye out. I can't think I can't remember
exactly any examples. I've definitely seen some blue people. I can't remember
specifically where when, but it is happening and you'll notice it when you
wait and now these a little silver people are eating colloidal silver as a
health thing because I haven't a long time ago because a new tropic I'm
talking about blue people goof and not people who turn blue but completely
blue when it's Paltrow has been selling colloidal so there's a big dunkley
osteos shark monster and avatar too and that's probably what's attacking these
don't go off on my island yeah dunkley osteos osteos osteos I do think that
it's probably it's probably has something to do with these UAPs that
we've had been having all of the time.
What's a UAP?
Unexplained Alien Phenomenon?
Ariel.
Yeah, this fucking guy.
But close, but close.
This fucking guy.
It's like he doesn't know that Marco Rubio, one of the most trusted people in all of America,
has been blowing the whistle on this.
Really?
They've been doing hearings in Congress.
Isn't Tom DeLonge there?
From the entire Congress.
Everything that Tom DeLonge said three years ago is coming true.
Tom DeLonge said three years ago, in three to five years you're going to have disclosure.
I just remembered that I saw a video a couple days ago. I can't believe I just
remember they were testing project blue beam in Dubai by making a bunch of
holograms of whales, blue line up into the sky, blue beam, what's blue beam?
That's the where they're going to end the world with holograms. Why would that
in the world? Well, they're basically going to use holograms to cause every
religious event like the second coming and all this stuff. Everything is
going to make it seem real. They're going to make it seem like aliens are
come in and contact us with holograms, so that we everything they're going to
rain. They're basically ramping up the world to the next level. Do you think
they're going to create a new world government? So there you're saying that
Jesus is going to come back, walk down from the stairway to heaven, simulate it
and say I am I'm the savior. I'm come again. By the way, do not touch me. Do
not touch anything that I'm on and also there's going to be a new government
and it's going to be fire. Yeah, the new government, you guys all got to get in
on it. You should all be ruled by this new government. That's basically what
probably getting pretty pretty close to the seven sisters of the Apocalypse.
Yeah, I think that all that I thought it was for horseman
whatever. What is the seven sisters? I don't it's my own thing. Your own thing
that you made up. I mean, I just said it's all like the twits. I like the
twins. I think I think it's all the famous twits, Mary Kate and Ashley T and
Tamara
sisters. That's for we go. We need so it's it's repair. Okay, we're going to
add Elizabeth Olsen. It's okay. And then a triplet is there any famous triplet.
Well, I'm saying you can add Elizabeth Olsen to get her to an odd. No, it's
two pairs of twins and three the Kardashian girls. Holy fuck. Yeah. So
there you go. Actually, I think that the four horse though, they've been
around a long time. Yeah, the seven sisters. The apocalypse started a while
ago. Yeah, it's a 30 year tribulation. So long to get ready.
That is the first one of the episodes.
That was fire.
It takes so long to get ready that you think that that apocalypse is going to start now?
They've been getting ready for it for years.
You're looking down at your watchers and saying, "We gotta go.
We gotta end the world."
Oh my God, the devil's having a hard time with these broads.
The devil is tapping his foot on the floor and he's going, "I'm not done yet.
I'm not done yet.
I'm still getting a blowout in my hair."
Me and Julio were on IMDb looking for movies for movie Mondays and I saw that
you can that you can put podcast episodes on IMDb and it was making me
laugh thinking about it, having this podcast on IMDb and going to the
soundtrack section. It says zombie nation
you got
to five hundred. I are on IMDb for a student film that has never or student
should have been censored. We I think
I just I don't I don't want that on my IMDB page. I want that gone. I don't
think you can take stuff off. Yeah, I know. I don't want it on there. Somebody
should make some I mean you can just put any movie on there, right? Yeah, so we
should make maybe a bunch of stuff, a bunch of awesome movies and put them on
there and send them to different producers. I see we've done a million
movies, nine point seven. I don't even know that. I don't know. We had a nine
What gave Patrick Goes to Jollibee like anything under a 10?
That's pretty funny. That's fucked up.
That is fucked up. Wait, what are the five user reviews?
Director Kayla Pitts. Director Kayla Pitts. That's a little...
Wonderful story of redemption, friendship, and a big, sexy, Filipino bee.
The director was Noah.
Wait, wait, there's spoilers for this one?
Can you see it? No, you can't. Oh, you can't.
I really like the scene where Patrick describes where he found out about
Jollibee, subtle brainwashing with the Patreon supporters part, but overall,
great film if you like food and want to see it. Stay away if you're a jellybee hater.
That's a pretty good review.
That's a good review.
So these are all 10 though.
Awesome movie. Touching story of friendship with laughs along the way. Patrick is my favorite.
Look at you buddy. Getting some props. Getting a nod.
Hopefully that's written by the Oscar, the Academy.
The Oscar Academy?
No, but it's Jay Haywood.
The Oscar Academy.
Jay Haywood.
Jay Wood.
It does not sound close enough to the Academy of Motion Pictures.
He's got wood like Hollywood. That's true. So yeah, but it's Haywood. That's a
worst town. I think that the four horsemen are already here. You want to
know who I think it is? Yeah, Bert Kreischer, Joe Rogan. Okay.
XQC, Hassan Habi, Aiden Ross, and Rice Gum. And Rice Gum. Yeah. I think it's
the streamers, man. Yeah, makes sense. Straight up. I think the streamers are in
charge of the apocalypse because I think they're screamers. I've been watching,
Well, these days you watch an excuse. I've been watching these all these
streamers 24 hours a day trying to study how to
take him down. You had to take them down. I've been studying excuse. It
turns out all you have to do the way you kill a streamers. You call the
police on them.
That's all you have to do. You call the cops and you say this guy is screaming
so loud into his microphone that you need to go kill them and they say we'll
be right over. I 40,000 people. It shouldn't it. It would be terrible. It
would be so bad. It's probably happened right excuse you getting swatted.
I think so. His reaction to that would be very funny. I think. And it would sound a
little like this. Oh my god, you guys, there's a bunch of cops at the door. You know I thought that he was from
Africa or something. Apparently he's Canadian. He's from like Quebec. He's some fucking Canadian guy.
He's a streamer that my girlfriend loves. Yeah and he goes, his whole thing is that he
goes really crazy on the stream.
Yeah. OK. He he watched I got
started watching it because he was
watching this thing where it's like
it's him reacting to the origin
of Jeff the Killer.
Like it's him watching one of these
like YouTube thing.
Cannot believe this guy has 50
million dollars.
That is so honestly that's so
100. He's made 100 million dollars
signing his little deal.
Yeah. That's what I think it is.
Well, he got banned from
or not banned, he got in trouble because he streamed the Dark Knight, right?
I have no fucking clue.
He streamed the Dark Knight on kick and then immediately he was like, okay, what my next
course of action is I'm going to start watching all of Breaking Bad.
Whoa, because there's just no rules on that website?
Well, no, there is rules and he is void, like, fucking up the terms of his own contract.
Oh, they won't let, he can't get in any trouble.
He's there.
No, absolutely not.
No, he's the number one.
Other guy they have on there is that guy that watched his wife get fucked or
something or his girlfriend.
Sneeko.
Sneeko, yeah.
I love Sneeko.
Yeah?
No.
You're a big fan of his?
I love Sneeko.
He's Andrew Tate's little friend?
He's just like--
Or no, that's Aiden Ross.
He's a kid who used to make Call of Duty videos where he would play Call of Duty
and then debate somebody about gay marriage.
And then now--
Jesus Christ, dude.
And now he makes videos where he gets beat up.
This is so stupid.
I think it's awesome, dude.
I think that this is what kids should be looking up to yeah and definitely on
podcasters. I'm so no, I think no, I think these kids should be watching all
these streamers. I think grown men should be watching us and they should be
adapting their lives to try and be like us more. I do think that our number,
we're about to experience a huge, a huge drop in numbers. Why is that? Because
Ian and Anthony bought Smosh. Oh yeah, that's going to affect us. I think a lot
of people are going to take their money out of this and put it into whatever
Absolutely. No. And Ian, if you're, Ian and Anthony, if you're watching, if you need a
third guy.
No.
If you need a third guy.
No, no, no, no, no.
Maybe could go like, maybe could be like your little like, like punching bag or like maybe
like a, like maybe you could put him in, maybe he's, maybe I'd be an apple or like a donut
or maybe I could be the food in food battle.
Why are you obsessed with this food being human food? This is all you care about now.
you could base me like a big turkey, put me in the oven, put me an apple in my
you want them to cook you know you could in and slow rose me put me in a in an
answer. Trager first of all surrender, surrender. This is directly addressing
Ian and Anthony Anthony stop wearing short shirts, yep, where a long or
large sleeves and wear gloves, where cover up those damn tattoos, Anthony
those damn tattoos, you're never going to get a job. You look crazy. Okay, we
don't know why you had to rejoin. I am bringing you to a Dominican barbershop
called the Sopranos, and we're getting you a haircut for real for real. I'm
getting you fitted for a tux, because you need to stop dressing like a baby.
Nice guy, though. Yeah, amazing guy. He's the creator of Smosh. He is an amazing
guy. He's going to create me into a big pork roast. But if you guys need a guy
who can come in and maybe be like, instant, I would say like instant sixth
six man off the bench production six man. How many guys are in Smosh? I think
a lot of guys. Yeah, no, no, no, there's a whole thing. I have like a whole
bunch of groups. It's a Smosh fan.
The apple in the video only
focused on Ian and Anthony and the also they were going to have with my just now
real. It just made me realize that you said you wanted to be a turkey with an
apple in your mouth. Yes, they put apple in a turkey. They're going to cook me
Sish one style. How small is this apple and how big is this turkey's fucking
mouth. One of them has to be bigger, small. What's going on? Why do they put
the apple in the pig's mouth? It's not making any flavor. It's last moment.
You can't tell me that you don't, that you look at that pig and you don't
think that looks incredible with the apple in its mouth. The apple levels. I
bet the apple with the apple a hundred percent level. I think I know what now
that I'm thinking about it, that apple tastes probably well. The apple doesn't
have any of the seasoning on it. I'm just talking about looking at the apple
looks awesome. If anything, if anything, that apple is going to taste like a
pig's mouth. You don't have to eat the apple necessarily. Here's why. The pig's
mouth probably tastes good if it's cooked. Here's why they do it. I know
exactly why they do it. I just figured this out. Why? The last thing that I
want to see when I'm about to eat something is its teeth. Or its tongue. Or
its disgusting tongue. Yeah, looking at me like Xs in the eyes, I don't want
that at all. Plug that shit up. An apple, I like apples. I would love to see an
apple. When I'm eating something, I usually prefer to see an apple. You know
I do suffer from oral allergy syndrome and the only way I can eat an apple is if it's
cooked. It's a big problem for me is that every time I want to eat an apple I do have
to go to a luau. You have to get it out of a pig's mouth. I have to get it from a cooked
pig's mouth. Do you guys know Napoleon was exiled to an island? Elba. No. He spent the
He spent the last 20 years of his life just sitting in a...
What are you doing?
He's wiping.
You don't need to wipe right now.
We're going to get spots and stuff all over the table.
I told you there's no sugar.
First of all, where the hell are our coasters?
Why don't we have coasters?
My coasters are right here. Cameron and Patrick.
That's pretty good.
What does that mean?
My coasters.
Co-hosters.
Oh, co-stars.
Yeah.
He said co-hosters. That's not what it was.
Co-hosters.
Yeah, Napoleon spent the last... He was owning for quite some time.
quite some time and he spent the last that's a great way to go out. I heard
that they sent him to
Idaho.
I think that he was probably on the island the whole time though and I think
he was probably just like fuck. They sent Napoleon to Idaho and then he did a
dance in front of his whole school and won Pedro the election is what I heard
through his shirt and dancing.
His shirt said vote for Pedro.
What I mean, what do you want me to what do you want me to say that I don't know
maybe you could talk more about the movie that I'm referencing. Yeah, and
his uncle played had a football. Yeah, there you are now you're getting it and
wait, wait, wait and his brother tried to do time or went. No, it didn't try to
do time travel. His brother had a girlfriend. Yeah, and what was her name?
Clifford. No, it wasn't. It was I don't know. It starts with an L. Come on. You
got this
fonda La Fonda. Her name was La Fonda and that's right. His grandma or aunt or
whoever that is. That's their aunt. She do you think that you could do something
bad enough in today's world that you get fully exiled to an island? I think you
just can you don't just go. Yeah, you don't either get killed or get sent to
jail that you what do you think you could do where now that you need to go
to an island. Now the people who are doing the bad stuff, now the people
that are doing the stuff that could get them exiled, actually like to have
their own little private islands where they can go do that shit. Wait,
holy fuck. Now the island is a prize. What they need to do,
they need to take... You have to live with a thousand other people.
Yeah, you gotta put these guys in a tiny home in the middle
of
Madison Square Park. You have to live in a brownstone with eight other people.
You have to have brothers and sisters. A co-op. You have to have...
sorry, cheaper by the dozen style. We're giving you we're making your parents
have sex. I'm a bunch of brothers and sisters.
You're watching the sex happen.
101, a bunch of little brothers and sisters and you have to, you have to
co parent also until they get older and then they do not respect you because
they're latchkey kids. Yeah, that's right. Your mom and dad work double
shifts at TGI Fridays. Dad's the manager, mom is a waitress and they met
while your dad had his other family. So your dad cheated on his wife with your
mom, then that split happened. His whole family is like wrecked. Now he has to
come live with this like lady. He knocked up and guess what he knocked her
up with octuplets and those are your brothers that you got to watch
you're cheating on your wife.
I have some bad news and I have some
try to keep it as a secret family and yeah, just like Holy like where's
ninety five percent of our
I don't know. Oh my God, you know what it is. I didn't use tap to pay at the
gas. Oh my God, somebody scammed my somebody to my credit card info yeah.
This is bullshit. Oh my God. I accidentally ordered eight of these little baby.
Well, I guess I'll just go. Somebody's hacked into our goddamn Amazon.
What the hell? Why do I have one of these buttons that keeps ordering diapers?
One of these Amazon buttons.
Too late to cancel it now. Yeah, honey.
I fell on the five tripped over my own shoelaces again.
I hit the fucking button eight times.
And yeah, I put the wrong address in so you won't even see it.
I got to go pick these up. No, because I don't know, because then you know what
like someone's just going to steal them anyway. I might as well just resell
them. Maybe I'll handle this. I'll resell them on the Facebook marketplace.
You imagine
I got this. You imagine how much of a nightmare it would be to if you had
octuplets and you lived in a I mean a bit. I guess I can't think of any town
that has eight different classes in a grade. I can think about this like
a big a big, but if you're a relatively small town where maybe there's three
classes of each grade, you just put them in different grades. You put the baby
in in fucking fifth grade to start. Yeah, and then it goes down. Yeah,
then it snaps back around. Yeah, so they're gonna be once they're mature
enough to be. Do you remember the case of the, it was called the Benjamin
family? No, the Turpin family, the case of the Turpin family, the case of
the Turpin family. Pray tell the Turpin family. They like it was this family
of like, I think it was like eight and they were all like, the parents would like lock
them up, like chain them to their beds and shit. So like a really, really sad story with
the, like they all had the same like bowl cut and there's like a bunch of photos of
them. Their parents would get remarried every year in Vegas. It's better with a loss, like
an Elvis impersonator. It's entirely sad. Well, the daughter like escaped. I know the story.
And now she's like a TikTok celeb.
And now she's a villain because of her backstory.
No, no, I know that it's like a police body camera footage and she's like...
What is medication?
Yeah, she's like, "I just escaped.
All of my brothers and sisters are tied up at my parents' house.
And if I was this cop, I'm going to be real.
I would have ignored it."
Kids make up shit all the time, dude.
You can't trust some kid.
It's just very like it's crazy that she's now like a like a tick tock influencer immediately
like she's doing like the like the dances with the it's like doing like sprite sponsorships
and shit right. You'd rather her be in the factory. That's good. She was still in the
bed. Yeah. That's good for her that she's got like you know leaves a fucking house and
now she gets all this free sprite all the time. I don't think that's going to make up
for what happened. You don't think so? You don't think a lifetime supply of sprite? It's
better than no free. I
is that not insulting if somebody's been if somebody's been a start some
if somebody's been abused for twenty years and had all their teeth taken out
like a prisoner of war. Yeah, if a prisoner of war comes back and you're
a can of president of one male, one can is great. Do you make a public
statement where you're like this prisoner of war is going to get I mean
a life of Chile? The truth is that you're just asking to get completely
unlogged. If you're like Sprite or Hormel or something and you do that and
then like you know and actually somebody's another company's like
actually we're going to give her a house in a car. Yeah, she can work here
as they have an email job. Yeah, what the fuck so yeah, it's got to start.
So I mean why don't you give them we're going to give her a big Sprite decal
that she can put in front of her new free house and get paid for that.
Yeah, living in this. Oh my God, she can live in a billboard. I've been
thinking about wrapping my car with some kind of like it would be so swag.
you get paid like 200 bucks a month. Really? Yeah. Whoa, that's sick. To wrap
the car, you can like pay for your car payment. You should ask just like a
small business around here, like one of these barber shops or something. I
would do that. One of these like old Polish guy barber shops. Wrapping your
car, it literally doesn't matter... Who gives a fuck? What the picture is,
just the fact that it is wrapped is cool. Yeah. It could be anything. Get
a big vinyl wrap around it that says subway or something. Yeah. Yeah. But it
could be anything. Oh, and then you paint the side, you make your whole
car look like the subway wrapping paper. But it could look like anything,
is what I'm saying. I would I would saying this is what I would do to get free subway.
Yeah, maybe even the police department would pay me to drive a cop car to advertise them.
Oh, that's actually a good idea. What it like a vinyl wrap that just says not a cop just
love him. No, it says police and oh, I'm a full cop. It's just a police car. It's just
a police car. It's a police car. I was driving around. I was thinking it's like his car that
says oh, yeah, his car specifically with that fucking hood. That's broken. It's not broken.
the latch doesn't work. It is held together with zip ties. It's because I'm pretty inventive
and zip ties are actually stronger than anything. You have the jalopy. Chill. Watch it, bro.
Chill the fuck out, bro. That is not cool. You can't say that to somebody. My car does
not go chugga-chugga-chugga and bounce up and down and blow black smoke out of the back.
That is not what my car is. It is a 2009 Ford Focus, which actually they resell for, if
it's under 100,000 miles, $2,800.
Really?
Yeah. If I fixed it up.
You know what? That is --
I'm sitting on three bands.
I think that is the exact price of two jalopies.
Mine's red, though. I have a red one.
Red cars are faster. Red cars are police targets.
Yeah, I think red car -- I think I'm a target for everything. I think having a red car has
maybe a massive, it's put a giant target on the back. You know what the reason is? It's
because the Wiggles made that fucking song. The Wiggles ruined a lot of stuff. The Wiggles
made that song about big red cars and now everyone's like, okay, this has to be the
fucking Wiggles car. I have to break into it. No. That's exactly what happened. I don't
even know what Wiggles song you're talking about. The Wiggles song, the big red car.
This is late period Wiggles must be. This is not late period Wiggles. This is from when
their first tapes. Oh yeah, so you're going in the deep cuts. I'm going hip-hop.
Yeah, no, it's a it's a rock and roll song. No, they used to be hip-hop. No,
it's a rock and roll song. It's like kid rock. Fruit salad is a hip-hop song. I
will say I will concede to that. That's some crack.com shit. Yep. I like that
fruit salad. When we sing that, can we pull up fruit salad karaoke? Do you
think we could start a Wiggles type thing? We I think because I mean, we
we could maybe do it. We could maybe do that, but I think it would end up like
being too famous. We'd end up being too famous and it would be like a blippy
style thing where like they show like old, you don't remember. We've never
done anything bad. They show all of our old clips. What clips could piss off a
parent? Him wearing the thing that says "I heart eating shit", a parent could
see that and they're like, "This is the guy that's singing to my kid about the
train." No, they wouldn't recognize him because they'd be like, "Oh, the guy
who sings to my kid about the train doesn't have a tattoo on his forehead."
That's true. That's a good point. But Blippi, he did a Harlem Shake video where he ate poop on Harlem Shake.
He diarrhea's all over his friend.
What are you? Who the fuck is Blippi?
Blippi was my nephew's favorite musician for years.
That's what he's known for? Yeah.
Well he's a kids like YouTube guy, but I only know him because of that pooping.
And he shit himself?
show. No, he's on to his friends. He's standing on a chair and he is
projectile diarrhea in into the other corner of the room and his friend is
sitting there like this like and it's a it's fake diarrhea. No, it's real. It's
real. He's a sweetest guy. He was trying to be jackass. Yeah. Oh, that's
nasty. Yeah, it's not. But he's saying that's what's gonna happen to us if
we're wiggles. But I'm saying what have we done that could be beyond that level
even possible. Yeah, show on camera. Who is the we've ever diarrhea on each
other? Who? I don't think so. Who are the other the jackass from Sweden dude
since God? Hey, I don't even want to think about that. Yeah, they did jump
or whatever dude. Those people were see what's his name. The big fat guy drew a
target on his belly and they threw darts at him. One of them broke like every
bone in his body and some never prank again. Really? Yeah, he had to retire
from prank. Their names were like Jaka and Joppa or something. They had the
most fucked up names ever and they just did not care if they lived or died on another level.
I think they cared if they lived. I think they wanted to survive every single one of them.
They didn't care.
So that they could go to the Swedish bars.
They did two spin-offs. They did the Dudesons and then they did Nitro Circus and those were the two,
no Nitro Circus was all of the boring parts of Jackass.
Nitro Circus was like Travis Pastrana.
Yeah and he was like, "Look I can jump something on my bike."
Shut up. That's what you're supposed to do. You're a BMX guy.
Nitro Circus, whose thing is that he's in a green wheelchair.
What if they made bike people ride a board and board people
ride a bike?
Whoa, that's a good idea for a new show.
Switchers.
We could call it switchers.
That's a crazy idea.
Every episode, it can't just be bike and boards.
Every episode, two things.
Two people, chefs and CEOs.
Oh my God.
Yep.
Chefs and prisoners.
No.
That would...
I'm thinking a lot of chef stuff. Maybe I got to switch it up anything.
Channing
and Wall Street bankers. He'd be they'd be like, Hey, we need to shred all
these documents that are the Panama paper. Oh yeah, then the guy he's doing
like nice
on the paper right. So then the CEO in the show, which are sweat. Welcome back
to switcher to Kobe. Shannix from Papa Roach and you're watching
good on switchers. He was the host discard and I think that's what he was
meant to do was host shows like this and then the chef or the CEO and the chef
thing, he would be like,
I mean, you know, probably what does a CEO do? CEO probably would be firing the
food. Yep,
he'd be putting it under the grill. Yeah, he'd be interviewing the food. Yeah,
yep. I had another TV show idea this morning. What was it? I was watching
catfish on the treadmill and I was thinking that I would like to do you
know how they people like email them to be like I think I'm being catfished.
Will you come and put me on the TV show? I would do I want to intercept those
emails and I want to go with my own crew and I go to the people who are being
catfish and I organize the meet up or whatever and we get there and then
they're about to meet them and then I say actually I just catfished you. I'm
not from catfish and I'm not even filming this and then I leave. You could
call it a different that's a great idea. That's an amazing idea, and then
another everybody's walking around doing a rocket power thing with their with
their hands as your film crew,
just making people meet. This is a new type of camera. Yeah, there's actually
such an amazing next level camera that it's invisible. I'm a transhumanist in
the
four different lenses in my fingertips. Yeah,
invented this. Yeah, so and now I'm zooming in. Yeah, you get right on.
I think there's a good idea. I think it's a yeah, you can fish the catfish.
Yeah, swordfish. I was also that's what I call it. Has there ever been a
catfish episode where both people think they're being catfished and then it's
beautiful because neither they both are so and the other person is so
incredible. That would be amazing. I feel like that has if that hasn't
happened yet. I feel like the that's the producers like white whale. They're
waiting for those. Yeah, cross reference every email. When did we we all watch
catfish together? Yeah, and it was the one it was it wasn't recently. I think
it was on tour. It was and it was it was that one episode where the lady
me. It was two people and they were in a relationship, but they called the
catfish people because they just wanted to be on TV yeah. That's right. Oh yeah,
catfish is such an evil show. It's I feel so bad for the I will get catfish
because they always the person comes out and they're like yeah. I did it
because I feel ugly and I hate myself and the person has to be like
yeah, you are like
I just on TV, though yeah and just seem like the bad guy yeah, it's so
horrible. You know it's a worst show I've been watching is Steve Wilkos.
What's that? I don't know what that is. It's the security guard from Jerry
Springer. Okay, his wife was like a producer and
they gave him a show where it's just like it's like Jerry Spring. It's like
if Jerry Springer was
on steroids, not like in the not like yeah, it's like Jerry Springer on
steroids. No, it's like an actual guy who is on steroids. He's a huge
act guy and like half the cases on that show were like, Conor was telling me about this
one where it's like the dude is like doing a polygraph for, doing a polygraph because
somebody accused him of molesting a kid.
Okay.
And.
Was it a kid?
No, no, no.
It was like a dad, like a dad who's like trying to get like this guy, like he hates his father-in-law.
so he's like saying that okay and
he told me that the like the polygraph comes back negative. Like he's like you
like are not a pedophile. Thank God and you know I just want to say sorry man.
I said a lot of things to you earlier because I thought maybe you were a
pedophile,
but let's be honest. You just kind of look the type and the guy goes the guy
goes yeah. I know I get
you're watching some show where it was like lot like the family members have to
guess if the people are lying or not. Oh, remember the show and there was one
that was like the last thing was like did you molest your daughter or
something? Yes,
that was the one it was one on Fox. It was called like it was our
something of truth. It was like yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's starting to be
like his favorite dinner is fish, yeah, be like I think it is and be like
and then we get to the final one. That one you molest your that one was there
is the one there was to we watch two of them. One of them was that guy and then
the other one was the girl who the host of the show comes out of the beginning,
and he says in all of my years of hosting television, I've never said that
I don't want to air an episode until this episode. I said we shouldn't do
this. The producers are making me do this without further ado. Here is the
worst episode of television ever and they do this show where you're hooked up
to a lie detector test and then they I think it's called to tell the truth.
is it yeah you have to answer every time you answer. You choose to answer or not
answer yeah. If you answer truthfully, you like earn more you earn more money.
If you just if you decide not to answer, you take the money that your whole
family is yeah, your entire everybody that you are lying everybody that you've
ever lied to is in a crowd of like a bunch of tourists who are like yeah. Oh,
I'm ready to go on to a TV show. I forgot about this is the crazy show of
all time. This girl says within like like twenty five minutes, she says her
my husband's right there. She says I cheated on my husband. I wish that I was
with my old boyfriend and not my husband. Then they bring out the old
boyfriend. I forgot about this. Do you still have feelings for him and she
says yes, and then she says she doesn't like her mom, her dad. She knows that
her dad embezzled money. It's like it ruins this person's life and then on the
lat the last the last fucking question is something so basic it's like it's
like yeah, it's like I have you ever thought that maybe you'd experiment
with girls, it's like something like that. Are you a total fucking lesbo and
she goes like or no no it oh no. I know what it is. It was. Do you think you're
a good person? Yeah, it's the last question. I forgot. She says fucking God,
she says yes, and then she loses a million dollars.
She fucked up her. It is the worst episode of TV. I ever see that was so
fucking crazy. I can't believe that they let that go. I mean it's amazing.
It's really unreal, but it is so hard to watch.
It does need to be out there, but for that person, no, it doesn't.
I mean, her life is fully on.
Yeah.
Like, you can never come back.
Honestly, I want to see the 10 years later.
Yeah.
They need to do an update on this girl.
She's definitely a nurse.
They might have.
They did the same thing.
What's that fucking, it was called like the Average Joe Show.
And it was just like they, everyone around the guy is an actor.
And jury duty.
No on free, it's on free, it's proto jury, ed monica, no jury duty. It is
not jury. You can watch it with free with ads. It was called it's the same
thing. It's the same thing who's a christian wig is in it.
They didn't know who christian wig was. This was like back in the day. Is it
the joe schmo show? Yeah, what do they do with joe the first season?
Yeah, I forget what they do. They just like make him do like I think he thinks
he's on a reality show and everyone else. He thinks he's on a reality show.
Everyone else around him knows that he's not or that he's not in on the joke,
and it was like Spike TV's like first like
thing. We need a reality show. So they brought it back. They brought it back on
TBS and Kat Daly is the host. Do you guys want to do like a keeping up with
the Kardashian style reality show about our lives as podcasters? I want to do a
the show. So this is an amazing idea. Has anyone done this? I mean you'd see my
episode, like every but not everything that would go like all the cameras would
go to me and it'd be me hanging out at a skate park or like drinking exactly in
my house. It would be but also we I mean we're going to have a producer. You
think we're doing drip drama into this?
Yeah, you know, I hang it would all be hanging. At least I'd be at least I'd be
like at a skate park and I could make like drama happen like it'd be like yo
that guy's talking shit about
we have to do this is an incredible a a a
and then you go to your house. What would we call it? Go to your house and
you're eating like keeping up with stone ground crackers, whatever Caleb and
stone ground crackers. You know the stone wheat crackers. You think I eat
stone wheat crackers at my house? This is what I do. Well, here's the first
drama. The fuck. Oh my God. Imagine I say that. Imagine. Okay, I wish we had
and I say that no, but I met the the sting the sting from kitchen nightmares.
You know the one that
Oh yeah, imagine I'm like yeah and Cameron's eating all these fucking
stone around. We do need I do talking. I have been getting a really he thinks
I'm so boring. I stone ground crackers. I've been having a super high incidence
of second hand smoke of real housewives. Yeah, I'm getting so much second hand
real housewives and I'm so ready to fucking do this. I think that you would
real podcasters of
perfect. I need a better name. That name is terrible.
That is such a bad name. What about
for
podcasters off the air?
This we can we do a full season of this? Yeah,
twenty four yeah, we get a camera and then we do the thing that real house
wives does where, like the next season, it's like two of us and then one other
random guy. Yeah, that's like a new one. Yeah, yeah, because they like the one
person got like kicked off. One person went to jail. Yeah, they always go to
jail or commit suicide. We could get what's that show that everyone is for
all of our Vanderpump rules. Yeah, well, that's the thing we need, but it needs
to be. It can be the same. It should be patterned off of Vanderpump rules
because we have a business that we share. Yeah, and so it's about oh my
God, they'd be stressing me on my computer playing skate. Yeah, exactly
session. Have you guys ever watched that show selling sunset? Yes, that show is
crazy. Yeah, that is a crazy. The craziest part of that show is that
they every single shot is so overexposed that it like lights up the
room. Yeah, it's like so white. It's a real estate reality show.
They have like a real estate company and there's these evil twins.
There is evil bald twins. Yeah, that's sick. Yeah, it's about them selling
giant mansions. Oh my God, we need a reality show. But this would just be
us arguing about us running the podcast. Yeah. You know what? This is so
good. Yeah, you know it's another sick reality show is the I think I've talked
about it before, but Kiss had a reality show because they wanted to bring back
arena football and they made a team called the L. A. Kiss and it was just
like Paul Stanley and Gene Simmons. It's like half the show is them in business
and marketing meetings where they're like, I mean, this logo just looks great.
This is just one of the greatest things I've ever seen. Then the other half of
of the show is like men who are like on the verge of like killing their whole
family from CTE being like, "I don't know if I'm gonna be able to play another
game." How do we round out the cast? 'Cause it's us three,
Jubio,
can do confessionals. Joe and Alex are like the people who are working kind of
near us, but yeah,
the once an episode kind of talking head where they say like, "Sometimes."
We'll be staying in it a little bit. It's like the thing on the reality
shows. Call him on the phone. Yeah, exactly. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Speaker phone
and he's telling us that we need to get the trash picked up and then it's
talking heads of all of us talking about the trash. Yeah, yeah, the thing trash
would be a full episode. The trash would be easily a full at least two episodes.
It would be the runaway. It's gotta be pierced right. He'd be like the runaway
star where it's like you know the show starts out where like the like this
main cast spin off and then he gets his own like he's like yeah. I think it
would be jubio. He's like the I love New York. Yeah, jubio would be like I love
York. Oh my God, wait. We're looking at this all wrong. We're looking at this all wrong.
We got to get like a bunch of people, right? It's kind of like Rock of Love, Flavor of
Love style show where we're trying to hire an intern.
That's maybe one episode.
No, no, that's a whole series.
You're saying that we do The Bachelor with a house full of people.
It's more, it's like The Bachelor and The Apprentice combined.
And it's all guys who wear funny graphic t-shirts.
But they could be on our bigger idea that encompasses that idea.
Okay, maybe one of the episodes is us writing that show and then it becomes the spin-off
show.
We could write the show in the episodes and it could be meta like Charlie Kaufman.
I don't like that guy's bullshit.
Charlie Kaufman, I'm done with you man.
yeah here's a here's a here's a get a Charlie. Come and be writing dialogue
like I am myself yeah, I am myself or am I I am myself or am I you so I'm
trapped in my own head shot is myself yourself. I think he did his best work on
the Dana Carvey show. Yep, he actually did
and spew e spewing me was that what are you taking a seat of medicine. My tooth
hurts
can't wait to keep this on you. Yeah,
it's in my bag. You guys didn't even go through my bag. Oh yeah. What else do
you have in here? Sorry, okay,
we're making this show by the way. I really want to. I'm not kidding. I
volunteer to edit it. If we get together, we film it. I need two camera
guys. We already have cameras. Yeah, we'll get to it. So we'll do
that was kind of cool. He has a tech deck. Yeah, yeah.
And then this is a this is gonna happen. I feel like I need one more one
more thing to get excited about this show.
deodorant. Yes, we can. Well, you know what? Actually, what we have to do, we
have to have some kind of big event that the show culminates on. Like the season
finale is always like somebody's wedding or somebody's opening a restaurant or
like, "Oh my God, somebody's doing a fashion runway." We need our sir.
What? You know too much reality TV shows. The Vanderpump thing. SUR Super
Unique Restaurant? Don't know. I've never watched Vanderpump. We need to
start a restaurant. No, I've heard... That show, I've heard... We'll actually
do sexy unique restaurant is, I think the name. What about a
what about a carnival with rides? That's too expensive and I would love
to do that, but I don't think we can afford that. Okay, well,
what if we just are throwing a party?
That's great. Yeah, the best party ever. Yeah, the office warming party.
The whole series is about the big party that we know that's the season for
that's what it's building up to. It's always it's yeah, yeah, it's but the
whole series isn't about it. It's our daily lives and then it's like that's
we're planning it as we go up, but that's like during the party. We're like I
just can't believe it's been such an amazing long road. Like I didn't realize
really how season two. Yeah, yeah, we could say that and then it doesn't get
picked up. Yeah, this will get picked up. It will get picked up. This will get
making one season for us and the rest are going on one for us, one for them
exactly. One of them. So this is going on network television.
Season hit us once. No, once we're going to make, we're going to make one season.
it's going to be incredible. Then we sell the idea to chapo trap house. Yes,
yes, and they do twelve seasons. I'm crackle
and we get
yeah,
all right, so
little field on July, four, July, fourteen, which is you already know
about this. You already know we have been talking non stop about this. It's
in six days from when this comes out. We made a video where everybody's on my
head to promote it. Watch that
Holy shit, well fire all right bye-bye.