I'm sorry that I just watched Anthony Jessel next second special Caligula.
You're not supposed to idolize just on Vimeo. You are not supposed to idolize
Jessel. Nick. Oh, I do if there's one thing I know him and the other devil.
You idolize Adolf Hitler. That's tired. No, that's tired. Y'all. Yep.
you
that's been done that's been the
they did that in the s. Oh yeah, Hitler, I don't even devil. I
back in the s. I mean I know no, I don't know. Hitler Hitler is too far. I like
the oh, you think you're being edgy by idolizing Hitler. I'll have you know an
entire country idolized him back in the day. They were so and also an entire
country idolizes the devil. Now we're in it yep
I wish we had that as a drop. We're going to we have been upset. Cameron doesn't
know about him. What's that? I showed from nowhere. I showed Noah, then Noah
showed youth and then you guys played Valorant and won every match. It
literally was a superpower. Let me read you. Let me show you this man. Okay,
this is Sean Stevens. His name's Sean Stevens. He shows yeah. He wears a green
hair, wears a vest, shows up on all these pictures are from the exact same
or maybe just showed the camera. Yeah, okay. This is Sean Stevens. This is the guy that showed up in
my Instagram reels. Okay. And I'm completely obsessed with him. So he did one photo shoot
and he got a lot of pictures. Yeah, he got a lot of pictures. He brought both of his guitars.
They're expensive. Here's the sick one. This one, this one's how you know he's a real rocker. Holy
shit. Yeah. Let me read you his bio. He's holding the guitar away from his body because it's too
loud. He's hitting star power in Guitar Hero. Let me read you his bio, Cam. Oh my god. Wait,
Hey, hold on. There's a different photo shoot. No, that's the same one. No,
that's got to be different. Look at this show. The this and this is this is
amazing. This looks like he's in Las Vegas and now he's got a green guitar as
well. Yeah, green. That one's different. Okay, read his bio. His bio CEO during
the day musician at night. Sean Stevens is once again venturing out. Whilst many
may know Sean for his various startups, volunteer work and direct a lineage to
Irish King. Whoa, really? They may know everyone knows him from that.
Sean now hopes you'll get to know him as an artist. A passionate guitarist and
singer, Sean dedicates his after hours to writing songs aiming to create
something meaningful and inspiring. Something that people can
relate to. His love for music comes from across in his charismatic
vocal style and a stage presence which can only be described as over-the-top in
the best way possible. Whether it's a live gig or rehearsal in the studio, Sean
Sean gives 100% to every performance written by Sean Stevens.
He doesn't have to say that.
You don't have to say that.
There's no legal reason.
Everybody do have to say this is the most beautiful song in the world.
Caleb is obsessed with this song right now.
Look at him.
He's crying.
beautiful it is. Yeah, a billion umbrellas.
Here's the drop.
and he's what are you doing? He's a CEO by day.
He's a CEO by day and at night. He's a rock star. What's he the CEO of?
Have you found out he's a CEO? It's called like leapfrog.
What?
He's the CEO of not leapfrog. Hold on.
Well, why did you say leapfrog? You got me all excited. That's crazy. I was
like, I like my frog. He's been with me my entire life. I didn't know tree frog
it's on your frogs tree frog. I think it's called tree frog. What is tree frog
do yeah that's
what do they do?
Show
yeah, that's definitely him warning a really long by. I was like huh, maybe
maybe this isn't him because I clicked on the web. It's like the first Google
result and I was like oh, maybe this isn't him and then it has a picture of
him. I know ain't no way that is not him right, because it's a picture of him.
Well I mean I have face blindness. I don't know if that could be him or not.
I've been taken I have face blindness recently. I've had face blindness since the day I was
born. I tried to remember what my wife looked like yesterday and I just couldn't picture
her at all. I can't picture anything in my head of a face. Holy shit this bio is crazy.
Wasn't he talking about Zimbabwe and stuff? What's the company do? I think they do tree
frog stuff. The switch to web is a big part of the bio. Holy fuck. Wait what do they do?
- Maybe not if I'm gonna patronize this business.
- They are based out of Canada.
They are the Swiss Army Knife of digital transformation.
- Oh, okay.
(laughing)
- So, if you were wondering what he's the CEO of.
- That song is so good, man.
♪ Calling all unicorns, unicorns ♪
- He records every single video
promoting it in his car, which is so sick.
- I have listened to that song in the last two months.
I have listened to that song driving my car.
It made me better drive my car.
playing video games made me incredible at video games. I did I tried to do a
squat to a one time and it didn't go very well. Yeah, we're here trying to
dance too hard. It was not a good. You were like you were kicking out your legs
and doing can can yeah, exactly stuff. Yeah, in the squat that would be on it.
We gotta look into the science behind that as a workout,
the science of moving your leg, no, the science of doing the can can while
you're doing a squat. Well, maybe not doing a squat, but if you had waited,
you know, there's like waited the leg things, the things that make you better
Yeah, exactly. I feel like people do that. That's like aerobics or something,
right? No, we'll do stuff like that and swinging their limbs around. That's not
a really so I think that can't be so far off. Is that aerobics? That's basically
aerobics. Okay. Yeah, I think speaking of using those to get higher jumping. I
think that I'm going to try to dunk by the end of this year. Yeah, I think that
is my new goal. It's it's crazy that I've never dunked. I know. No, it's just
that you talk about basketball the same way I talk about skateboarding.
I'm better at basketball than you are at skateboarding. No, that is not true at all.
Yes, I am. We are the same skill level. No, no, no. I'm way better at basketball than you are at skateboarding.
Not at all. I'm so much better. That's not true.
You've never, you don't know. I've watched you skate. You've never seen me play ball.
You've never seen me hoop. I have seen you play ball. I'm nice. I've seen you hoop.
I've seen you hoop in college. I was fat in college.
in college. I seen you hoop in college in the all comedy troop basketball tourney
tournament. And we only lost because they had a, they had a Terminator on their
team. They did. They had that big Swedish kid. This kid, they had this
fucking kid. It was all supposed to be, it was me and Joe and then one of us.
Did you guys set that up? Was that your doing? I think Joe did it. Yeah. That
is, it makes so much fucking sense that Joe set that up. It was like all of the,
all of the comedy people in, in college and it was a three V three basketball
tournament and the first year I think we destroyed and then the second year one
of the troops got this like Swedish kid who had been in the Swedish army and he
was like six foot four and insanely jacked and he was like twenty six years
old. He was like way older than he was. He was older than he was older school.
Yeah, he was way, way old. I was old as hell. His name was like everybody
called him like thunk. I think his name was third. Oh no, everyone called him.
I thought I remember him yeah yeah, because he looked like a cave man. He
looked like a like a complete game. That's why they called him that and he
obviously destroyed us. He and he had no it was one of those things were like it
was so sad because he was from Sweden. It was clear that he was never had it
was sad. He had never played basketball before, but the fact that he was bigger
and stronger, he just by default one yeah. Well, it was also the comedy troop
basketball team. I don't think they were sending. I think they were the only ones
you say that man, if you think he's strong, you should have seen the other
guy in the Swedish Army. Yeah, two guys,
yeah, yeah, I just don't think that that's right. He was he's basically like
you know, you should have been barred from going to school. One he was trying
to win. He was trying to win. He wasn't trying to be comedic in his basketball
playing in any way, like some of us were you. He tried to do. He thought that it
was he didn't realize it was a car. I thought it was a basketball, a basketball
comedy show. We were doing Globetrotters. Joe is in here right now.
Joe, we're talking about the basketball tournament.
Yeah. That Joe got really mad about it.
You got heated, I remember.
I was doing the Michael Phelps thing.
That's swimming. What is doing the Michael Phelps thing mean?
Come here. We can't hear you from over there. Talk into my mic.
Talk into Caleb's mic. Talk into Caleb's mic, I guess.
No, talk into everyone's mic. Yeah, just talk into one of them.
Michael Phelps did that thing where he was looking at the swimmer who was
who was like supposed to win the race in his last Olympics.
And he was doing like serious face and he was blasting music.
So I thought it was a funny joke if I could pretend I was like taking it super
seriously. I don't think you were pretending.
I don't think no, I think you're a psycho.
I think you just thought of that right now.
I think that the pretending of it was almost an excuse to take it really
seriously. OK, but I thought it was really funny and I was like kicking the
basketball. And yeah,
If there had been a ref, there would have been technical fouls ejected from the game.
It's also like, to set the scene, every other team was just like really tiny kids who clearly
have never touched a basketball before.
I was on a team and I thought we were supposed to do comedic basketball and I took, oh, the
actual basketball team of the school came in.
They started playing on the court with us.
On the other side.
On the other side, which they weren't supposed to do.
we were supposed to have the whole court to ourselves.
And their ball came into our game.
So I think I tried to shoot a basket
while somebody else was shooting a basket.
And I think that's what you're supposed to do.
- No, you were a dickhead, dude.
You ruined their game. - What do you mean?
- You ruined their game.
- Yeah, I ruined their game.
They weren't supposed to be there.
- We weren't supposed to be there.
- What are you talking about? - That's their domain.
- We had it reserved. - They weren't kind enough.
- We had the gym booked.
but we had the gym book. It's default that the basketball players get the
Hoopers to get the hoop. The Hoopers should have respected that day. We were
the Hoopers on that day. We were the Hoopers now and we were supposed to be
doing globe charter stuff and everyone was taking it too serious before I go
the
the one thing I remember really vividly is I walked. There's like a short kid
and I did a really low block like into the Julio's telling you to duck down
lower. I did a really emphatic block on this little kid little kid. He was a
senior in college and then I went to the crowd and I like you know really pound
on my chest and went I run this shit. This is my school. You are gay
and oh and then I also heard back that people who didn't know me thought I was
just like a really scary person after the yeah,
but I'm not I'm cool.
Yeah, Joe is a psycho. Anytime you play any any kind of sports with Joe. Yeah,
bye. You don't want to play.
When I used to live with him, dude, when he used to play baseball, he told me
that, like, he used to just try to hit people with the ball
when he was pitching. He was just trying to, like, set the tone for the game,
playing a fucking, you know, like a little league. Yeah. God damn, dude.
Trying to hit the batter with the ball. That's incredible. He said one time he
he played against two little person twins and he got like yelled at by the umpire
because he jumped over one of them.
(laughter)
He's so crazy.
Yeah, he's a very good dude. You play Mario Party with him, it's like, it's not even a party.
It's like Mario's, Mario's Detention.
It's like Mario's Funeral.
It's like Mario's Detention.
They should call it Mario's War.
Well, I watched the Mario movie.
was actually a blast. Yeah, I love you didn't like it. I didn't see it. I just
wanted to
you didn't see my nephew has become obsessed with Mario because of that to a
point that where like
my sister has sent me photos of him just on a weekday, dressed up like Mario.
He's wearing overalls now. He's got a red hat.
he's he's gone full Mario and how old is he he's like six, which is that's fine,
but it's like man. Yeah, I don't mean I don't have that low as a kid. I didn't
ask that in terms of like oh he's too old to be doing that, but more to said
would be funny to see a six year old kid walking does he looking exactly like
Mario? Yeah, he does he maybe think that you are Mario. He told me so much like
Mario. He told me I look like Mario. One time you look exact. You have the same
there the same like shape of your face, the same must the same little button
nose, you have the same like body to you move like yeah, you could jump and
you're not the only person that's my girlfriend has told me this that I look
like Mario. It takes a gamer's eye to recognize something like this.
That to this do this pose right now.
Yeah, that's Mario.
You are Mario yeah, that's a good person to look like I think yeah, it's better
been someone ugly and disgusting. I kind of look like one of the Goombas from the
the movie from the first movie that was Fisher Stevens. The what's his name from
a little little pencil neck motherfucker from succession that was him yeah. What
I thought it was a monster costume. No, no, his neck just looks like that man. I
think he had throat cancer. I've talked about it before. I think they removed a
bunch of muscle or something from his neck and I was, but I was like the time
you see somebody who looks just a little too crazy. Something is very wrong with
yeah, you gotta you gotta be kinder of a person, but you can think in your head.
You can think you can look at them and think in your head like you can think
whatever you want in your head. Nobody knows what your brain is. Nobody knows
what's going on, but
you can't say it. You can't say it out loud thoughts thoughts become feelings
yep feelings become actions. Actions become your character and your what is
your character, but your character defines your destiny. I can't as a
Mario thing. The only defines defines your destiny yeah, so I think a lot of
horrible stuff. What's the worst all you've ever had pussy?
If I see a guy wearing pink,
oh okay, I thought you were. Do you think we should bring back swag?
Speaking of guys wearing pink, bring back, bring back swag. You think that we
could start wearing like pink polos and like light wash jeans and ice creams and
Marty bringing that back already. Already. Yep. I had a thought today out of
fashion thought today. Yeah. You're gonna start wearing true ease. No. When you
should, I was driving around in my car and I saw a bunch of these construction
guys wearing all this high of is right. Yeah, but my first thought was not, oh,
they work in construction. My first thought was, oh, a couple of E. D. M.
the enjoyers right are plant doing doing stomp with a bunch of shovels and shit
over here on the side of you know your your actual first thought probably was
what oh my God. I can see them yeah. First thing I look at no no. So that's
the problem drawing attention to that okay. So now you guys these guys are
like this is my problem. This tree they were the second thing I looked at
because it was a bunch of hot girls going to a convention across the street,
but they were also wearing high vis. So yeah they were yeah, but all I think
Hi, this is not enough, because I if you are somebody there are people in this
world who they see somebody wearing neon clothes looking like they're going to
bar. I see what you're saying and they might even try to up you need an here
and what is going to catch your eye more maybe a helmet than a noise, only naked
body. Okay, so I think that construction workers should have to be naked. They
should have to be naked or wear a shirt that makes it look like they're naked. I
don't think because that would just you would think it was a funny shirt, though,
if they wear the pants to wear the big long white T shirt that has the bikini
by yes and that's got lights on all the polka dots on the bikini.
I don't think the or if they were just twenty feet tall yeah or they should
only hire
huge boobed humongous is twenty foot boobs humongous blue blur. Yeah,
humongously giant huge is on fifty feet.
there should be huge in the work place.
I agree there should be huge on the construction site. There should be huge
in the work place. There should be huge out of the out of this world huge.
There should be an asterisk on every dress code at every work place in
America. This is unless you have you need. Yeah, exactly. You need to cover
up, wear modest clothes, blah, blah, blah,
asterisk and unless you got a
gees you and the unless has to be in a special font. So you read it in your
head and you go unless you have huge is parenthesis. Let them fly. Let them
dang tang, let them thank you. Let them bring hang. Let them breathe man. Why
are we covering up these beautiful, beautiful things? The girls want to show
them the girls like to show their huge.
have you guys seen instagram recently? No, it's basically been what tell me
about it. What's on there right now? Been non stop hugies what's back to back
to back no hugies. What happened to the memes? It's huge. The memes are over my
friend done. They're done unless you play unless you play the algorithm
right,
because I basically just recipes it's recipes. Mine are all recipes. Mine is
whole memes yeah really means only mine. I open my instagram. It's three posts
that I already saw that are from a week ago from someone I follow and then
ten hundred thousand memes of raccoons about capitalism really because it's a
fairly it's a new ish instagram account and I'd have a really look at anything
on there. I found this. I think it just knows I like to funny shit. Summer ray
and look at her instagram five hundred times a day, and then you'll get a good
algorithm yeah.
if you if you let the reels just run, if you're just like swiping every other
video is like
if you do it right, every other video is just like an old man and he's made a
slide show of himself and it's like that's all fake his dinner and then like
a photo of him, then a photo of like his car and it's all set to like sweet
child of mine. It's great. That's a marketing department. I love I love
you're falling for it. How is that a marketing mark? Is that a marketing
that old man's old man's interns are putting together funny reels for you?
Yeah, and it's no, no, no, no. It's like I gotta, I gotta show you this one
guy. No, it's all fake. And the caption is if my boss said of this gets
5000 faves, I can get a raise. No, this these are videos that have like ten
like if I get less than 5000 face, I'll get erased. I'm getting I'll get
erased from the planet. I'm getting things with ten likes. It's an old man
showing off his dinner, showing off his car, showing off his puppy, just stuff like that.
And you don't think maybe this is an ad for puppies, cars, and food?
I think maybe it's an ad for Foster's Beer.
Why Foster's Beer?
There's a disproportionate amount of them drinking Foster's Beer.
I like Foster's. I don't know what these Australians are complaining about.
They make it too big.
Why would you...
The can is so big.
Okay, why would you claim Vegemite and shun Foster's? Foster's is a damn good beer and Vegemite...
That green can of Fosters tastes like dog shit. I like the blue can. The blue can's fine.
But that's a good beer. Why isn't every beer can that sized?
That's a good question. Why is it, why are all the other, it's just like, what is it? That's
a, that Fosters, is that a pint? Is that the blue can? Is that a pint? Have you ever seen
like a antique store, the old cans of beer that they're just like, they're, they're actual just
I found one the other day that was called like Africa beer or something and it had a bunch
of pictures of zebras on it.
That's cool.
Yeah and it looked really really cool.
That's like when Harley Davidson made cigarettes.
What?
Yeah there was a pack of Harley Davidson cigarettes and my uncle, my uncle lived with us, the
one who had like, I talked about him like two weeks ago, he had like back surgery and
was sleeping on a couch in, or like a bed in my living room.
he came back from like boot camp for the Air Force. He left his like locker out.
My brother, my brother and I unlocked it in, uh, with what?
I don't remember what, I think it was his key, but we knew he,
we knew he, my brother knew he had cigarettes in there.
And the first cigarettes he smoked was Harley Davidson brand cigarettes.
That's an honor. It was a black pack with the Harley logo.
I wonder who made the Harley Davidson cigarettes, because we stole that shit from him.
Oh, I'll tell you. Harley Davidson!
You think so? They think they got tobacco crops? You don't think they were like, "Hey,
Philip Morris, can we just put our logo on this?"
Dude, I don't know what the fuck you just said.
RJ Reynolds?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm talking about tobacco. I miss smoking cigarettes, bro.
Because you're just talking about which company's good, which one's...
No, I'm thinking about a pack of Camel Blues right now.
Why not just smoke them? You can smoke as much as you want until you turn 30 years old,
and then you have to think about it.
I did that early, 'cause I had the head start.
- You did have a head start, 'cause you started at 15, right?
- At 12.
(laughing)
- You are Tom Sawyer.
That is crazy.
Smoking cigarettes at 12 years old.
- Well, my mom smoked, so I would just steal them from her.
- See, my dad dipped, and I had no desire to have it dip.
- I had no, me neither.
My dad dips too.
I'm so worried about my parents getting cancer, it's crazy.
- I'll handle it.
yeah, you got it good. I got it you're going to take all their cancer. I got it
like that. You're going to suck all the cancer. I don't want you to worry about
that ever again. Yeah, buddy, you can do that. You came to the right guy. Great,
I'm glad
I got it man. You're like I'm working on it. God, I'm actively working.
I've just been sitting around my house just thinking of different things that
could cure cancer.
I've been giving treatments to many people. Do you guys think that cancer is
basically just because we drink out of plastic things? I think it could be.
You can get Alzheimer's from aluminum. Really? Yeah. Well, you like that's a
maybe that was just a rumor. I need to stop smoking crack. Yeah. With that
aluminum pipe. What was it? People would tell you like, oh, if you smoke weed out
of a Mountain Dew can, it'll give you Alzheimer's. I think everything we do as
human beings will give us cancer. Really yeah, we weren't built for this world.
We were made for another play. I think that's the biggest proof that we have
that we are from another son gives you cancer. Oh, there is no solid evidence
that aluminum is increased in the brains of people with alzheimer's shut up
jubio's mate jubio's correcting me. We don't need a fact of Pinocchio fact
checker on this show. We do have one, though we don't need that. We need
somebody to look up Mario and look at his phone. Most of the episode. Yeah,
Speaking of facts, can I read you guys a news story?
Yeah.
What are you looking at?
I have to find it, one second.
Click enter.
Click enter right now.
Do you be able to click enter?
Do you be able to click enter on that?
What was he going to search?
Naked guy.
Oh!
Click enter right now.
Don't do that.
Click enter on naked guy.
Don't search naked guy, please.
Please.
Okay, so this is a true story that I learned about this past week.
monkey foul creature haunting town captured by locals. So I don't know if
you guys have heard of a monkey foul. No, I've never heard of a bird monkey.
It is a monkey with
bird legs. It's a chicken monkey? It's alive, and it's alive.
It kicks around in the video. Do you have videos of the monkey foul? Yeah,
but I'm not gonna show them 'cause I think that actually they are some
horrific animal cruelty going on, but we can not think about that right now.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, what is, what is here? A monkey, let me read
you the news article. Okay, sorry. This is what really happened, and then
what these conspiracy theorists are saying is that probably these people
cut off a monkey's head and put it on a chicken for a video, but that's not
true. I don't believe
a monkey foul creature that has been terrorizing and haunting a French
township in Ivory Coast has finally been captured by locals after days of
tracking it. A French town. This is true from a viral video that has just
surfaced on social media as privy to us at occupied. G. H. Dot com in the video
the creature who has the face of a black monkey and the other body features of a
cowl was seen being held in front of a camera. The creature in a bid to escape
is seen flapping its feet in defense mode.
If it's a French township, I fully believe that they did. I fully believe
they chopped off the head. Are you kidding me? They eat snails,
but I think full snails. I think that this could be a real situation. I don't
think this is a real situation at all. There was another there was another
article that I found I have to search it again, but there's a lot of
information about this monkey foul. Apparently it was haunting the village
and there was days they took days to track it down before they captured it
in what world could a chicken bodied anything haunt anything yeah. The word
haunting is like hunting. Haunting is too broad. Haunting is a very strong
word and you should only use it when you're talking about ghosts. Yeah,
that's how I feel. Well, this this thing would you not say that you'd be haunted
if you saw a creature like this? I don't think I'd be haunted, but I would be
scared. I would be seeing it. I would certainly be seeing it, but I would
probably look at it and say, oh, that's an interesting one of God's many
creatures. I wonder I wonder what what is this please
that is definitely they've cut off a monkey's head.
Show the you don't have to show the video, but
they definitely put a monkey's head on yeah, that's so horrible. It's a monkey
now it's an animal. No, it's not a animal. They discovered in the ivory
coast. It was hunting villagers. It's a French township. Okay, if they cut off
a monkey's head and put it on a chicken, how are they able to track it?
They didn't track it. I don't think they're tracking it for days.
We have had to already put the monkey's head on it, but they were you know,
because the chicken can't see anything, so it was probably just running into a
fucking tree over and you cut off my head
sure if you cut off my my monkey's head and you put it on me and I I fucking I
would have no idea where to go. I'd have no vision. I would only have the
monkey's eyes in a video seen by docke's world. The young men could be
hers on docke's world speaking in French of the anomaly, which possessed a
chicken body and a monkey face discover related topics, a cap seller on his way
to market
capseller. A capseller. Let's check this article. Yeah, I need to know about the
capseller. Oh, it's just a Googled ad link. It doesn't actually even go to
anything. I wanted to read an article called A Capseller on His Way to Market.
There's this capseller I read about who had too damn many of them. He had plenty.
He had too damn many caps and he was walking around town trying to fucking
sell them to motherfuckers. Is this one of these nursery rhymes that only you
two know about and I never learned? You never heard of too many caps? You get to
always do this to me. You just read you when you were a kid, you would read the
Bible of you'd read the Bible and you would read the label on the Dr Pepper
can and that was the only two books you had read the label on the suave shampoo.
Oh yeah, that's right. You'd read Dr Bronner's. No, I didn't have doctor. We
did Dr. Browner's didn't exist related post can a has been around with six
fingers vagina and penis surfaces online as he begs for help. Who can a and boy
and six fingers vagina and penis surfaces online as he begs for help six each
hand or six total doesn't say yeah that's because maybe he's got like
maybe he's like fucking Oswald Cobblepot. He's got just three fingers on each
hand.
It looks in this picture like he just has an extra one on what news website is
this is this by gh dot com. Is this where you guys all your news from here
occupied G H G H, then for Ghana, probably our hero
occupies our hero six six six alert. Oh no six six six alert six six six alert
two brothers get bar code matching tattoos on their wrist netizens react.
What did the netizens say? Let's find out oh my God,
let's see here. Two young men brothers have gotten themselves beautiful bar
code matching tattoo on their wrist to mark their birthdays, respectively.
He also noted this was the first time they got a tattoo as expected netizens
reacted at you, Fexrix going to send this to my brother.
That's the reaction going to send this to my brother. The first reaction they
put in the article going to send this to my brother. Here's another one from
coolest sent this to my sister waiting for her to reply.
Here's why is this? Here's what a netizens here's a netizens reaction from
Mickey s okay, your brother is hairy, hairy and then two cute emojis. Why is
why is this a six six six alert to six six six alert because it's a mark of the
beast. The barcode is the mark of the beast. Yeah, obviously, yeah, mark of the
beast is on your left hand or wrist. It's something that it's basically like
an RFID chip or a barcode. You know, whatever you want, but these guys, it
seems like they gave it to themselves. What is RFID stands for really fire is
the devil. It's something like that yeah similar a viral video available to
occupy gh dot com captures the exact moment drake was bombarded with all
sizes of bras from his female fans or performing on stage. It's all a
blurtor. The Canadian rapper who was taken by surprise had to pause his
performance to attend to the pandemic flooding his stage at one point. He
ducks to save his face from being hit by the bras. He is enjoying the best of
moments, the best of his moments,
would you guys let your girlfriend go on Drake's tour bus and watch no yeah,
no, I would you would let her. I'd let her marry Drake. If you wanted to do, I
love I would not let my girlfriend marry Drake. Are you lying me,
but then you get to be to get in a was Drake to listen to his music. Yeah, no,
because then you'd have all these songs called like like I
wait. If Drake could write a song,
song with the beauty of Drake's lyrics and music and it's about the love of my
life. That's amazing yeah, but that's like all the other songs. There's like
that's three songs on the album. All the other songs about our how good he is it
having sex with your girlfriend. All the other all the other songs are about how
girl. How good is it having sex with your girlfriend and how much of a bitch
you are? Why would he why? Okay, he let him yeah
lease Drake releases a song. It's like the
the paper work. There's a cause on the paper work. You can't write a song
about how much of a bitch I am. I sign the permission slip. Okay, well, if
that's
she brought me a
back from the the concert yeah and I said yes, you are allowed to go on the
bus. Drake is having a wedding tomorrow. Can I go?
I said yeah, imagine, imagine you let that happen. Imagine you let drake have
sex with your wife or your girlfriend. You you sign the permission slip as we
we're saying just now this guy thinks he's in control of
to happen. I am in control
now, but imagine that happens right and then next drake album. All the songs
are like I don't want that root beer flow to get the get out of my tour bus.
Every single song is about how you're an overbearing weird guy, a root beer
flow like I'm walking in trying to give him a root beer yeah.
but I thought what I thought you were going to say the concept you said was a
so can that would have been funny. If you had told me what I jumped ahead, I
jumped ahead. I was what I what I thought you were saying is that the idea
of Drake writing a song about getting mad at me because I'm giving him too
many root beer. What I thought what I thought you were going, what I thought
you were meaning is like what if you let your girlfriend marry Drake and
they're together and then Drake releases an album and there's no songs about
love at all and it's just about to be a
floats of food and ran
that would break my heart. That would break my heart. Actually, you've been
waiting with bated breath for this album. You got every song is like my girl makes
me too many root beer float. He doesn't even say my girl. No, he doesn't talk
about her. I doing the way
so he's not even say yeah. He gave up on being cool at all. Drake Drake doing a
cover of salad. He's like okay, I'm ready to settle down yeah. Your
girlfriend's the only girl he has sex with for the rest of his life. That
would be so that would actually you have like a really long, hard conversation
with your girlfriend where it's like you know if this is what you want, you
want to leave me for Drake and live on his tour bus. I could tame Drake,
though it now if you if Drake, where every single song that comes out is
just like silly putty,
my favorite toy
is my favorite.
I can really putty. I can turn it into whatever
play with my leg.
Silly putty free play, make it whatever stick it to the wall. I got my own
custom mini figs stick it on the newspaper
free play. I got a
Whoa, you ever do that with silly putty. No, you can pick up. Oh yeah,
yeah, that would be a great song for drake to make drake. If you're
listening, because I know that you are, you should make sticky hand one
hundred one hundred song album about every single toy. You got at the
dentist, everything you to every single toy. You got from Dave and Buster's
white shirt covered in mustard.
I use the sticky hand to take tips off of people's tables.
What you take the sticky hand you go up to people's tables at David Buster's
when they're big and
they've been
even bastard
David Bastard sucks so bad, but the food is good, though. Nave Bastard, you got
tickets, you have parking tickets, yeah, Dave and Bastard's Dave. Honestly, when
I'm in Dave and Buster's the way that society degenerates in there. I feel
like I'm living in a medieval age full of knaves and bastards. I agree what's
a knave a fool. Oh, a just why it's called the naval, because when you're
no digging around in there, it's funny. Look like a fool. When you dig in your
navel, don't show me that I was I was disgusting body. I just came out. I
didn't do a porn. First of all, I didn't do a porn. Second of all, you called my
body discussed. You showed me your disgusting body. I didn't show you my
disgusting body. I was showing you what a naval it's covered in hair digging.
Yeah, you could save your belly before you show it. You could stand to do that.
I have so much hair, so shave it. I don't want to shave it. I literally I
think I need it. You know what I know? No, I'm not going to right now. Why I do
just by shaving material, I'm not going to go. Oh my God, Cameron, he's scared to
shave his entire body bald. I would never
I'm not going to shave my whole entire body bald, but I do think I do. I think
it would benefit me because I sweat pretty easy exactly and I'm starting. I
realize like I'll walk like you don't sweat you pant like a dog. You can't
sweat pant like a dog yeah. When you go, I you go police your teeth. Really it
comes off your tongue. Yeah friend my do I have a cud a cud yeah, and you true
cut do I is that not a part of the cow's body? No, no, it's gum cut is go. It's
gum. It's like the one is not call it gum. It's not gum. It's gum for cow.
No, it's a bunch of it's a
the stuff that comes back up from their stomachs. Yeah, I want it. Oh, so it
shoots back up, okay, and it turns in. It feels like gum. They chew it is
basically it's where the idea for it is going from
the original gum from God's green hand. It's normal world gum, and then we
natural. Have you seen that
have you seen that natural gum? No
have you seen that shit? The natural gum that's like pieces of like a crystal
and it's like yeah, usable gum. I've had that reusable gum sounds fire. I've had
that I run out of gum and I don't want to get more. Yeah, I've had the fancy
the real gum and it's not good. It's not good. It's not good. They put a flavor
with like honey and it's also like it's like five hundred calories a pack. Is it
reusable? Do you put in the flavor every time you're like you're maybe like you
chew it long enough, it loses flavor and then you put more honey in when you chew
it again, you can mix it up with another piece. You could just basically roll all
of them together into one big. I was a permanent. Here's my problem. Gum. Yeah,
gum
is no fun. No, I don't you can chew anything. I don't have to chew gum. Any
food that I like, I don't have to swallow it ever. I can just keep it in
my fucking mouth and chew it all I want. No, because it loses its texture. I
don't like textures. I like chewing. You can't chew it for so long. Yeah,
you can if you put baking soda in it.
What do you mean? Anything? You can just add baking soda into your mouth,
and it'll dry it out and make it a big ball again.
You can make your mouth a ball? You could do hamburger meat or something.
and then you could just keep adding baking soda when it dissolves.
This is a good idea. What are you talking about? You can just add baking
why not just have gum because gum doesn't take I don't like you like the
taste of baking soda and I don't that you just they have a natural gum that
tastes like baking soda. No, they don't. It tastes like honey. What are we
talking about gum? I thought we were talking about baking soda. No, I was
saying that you could add not just baking. You could add flour. You can add
any lower rubber gum glom glom is
gum is not rubber. What is it gum tree? Yes, it's tree. What is all of it tree
gum or some of I think only some of it is none of it is rubber Cameron. Some of
it is some of its plastic. Some of it is okay. No, I take gum and I is an
element. If I try to use it on a pencil,
is that an eraser? Yes, a racer gum it's called a racer gum. No, the content of
and a racer is called gum. They just call it that it's not gum. Then what is gum?
If you can call something gum and it's not gum is a more of a category right
so how is it? A go? Can you race is please like normal definition gum? No,
no, not gum definition. Look up what can you click around on this page? What is
gone? What is gum half naked man? What is go? Get guy back? What is guy? Wait
you guys got guys on the what is guy? What is what is gum? Okay, no go to the
all and no images yeah. We don't need that a viscous secretion of some trees
and shrubs that hardens on drying, but is soluble in water and from which
adhesives and other products are made. It's a race like say that again
gum. You sound beautiful today. You view gum, jubile, you have a beautiful
beautiful now is an eraser. What is gum made of right there first thing?
that's what we want to see tree, though we what is made of chewing gum made of it
consists thirty percent of the product, the remaining
thirty percent of it is seventy percent of it. Can you search is erasers gum
chewing gum contains plastic? Oh what the ingredient no as gum base in the
list of ingredients in chewing gum is largely made of poly vinyl acetate Jesus
gum. It's a plan rubber fuck dude gum is rubber is gum. Actually rubber. Most
modern gums are based on a synthetic equivalent, a rubbery material called
poly iso butylene. It's not rubber that's also used in the manufacture of
inner tubes rubber. Yeah, rubber comes from a rubber. It's plastic rubber, but
no you have to write chewing gum. I bet if you search that thing that it said
right there, you don't know what an inner tube is. I bet if you search that
thing that it said right there that chemical, I bet it'll say it's a type of
synthetic rubber.
you.
Fuck you, I bet it will. I don't like that. I thought I was gum plastic and
I was guessing I didn't even know that you have to know because that's like I
was guessing by the text.
That's like like like gum souls on a shoe, though
the class. No way that this is what chewing gum is made of. It's made of
this. They contain gummy solids.
They don't contain. It contains gummy. What is this? This is actually this is
you just hit me off to because this is not chewing gum. You have to look up
chewing. That was chewing gum. That's not chewing. It said it's a chewing gum
tube. Most modern gums. What is chewing gum made of
antioxidants? There he gets different. Okay, all right, it's antioxidants. Yeah,
it's completely does chewing gum rubber last emers has to be some kind of
plastic rubber thing. Yeah, most modern gums see a synthetic rubbery material
way all food. Oh my God, wait, it's actually rubber. That's what I'm saying
right about it. They put rubber because you're not even supposed to eat it. So
who cares they could put poisonous? Yeah, that's true. You're always going to
chew on it. They couldn't put spikes in. I when I was five years old, I ate a
whole thing of bubble tape, just pop the whole thing in my mouth and then I blew
a bubble and then I can't country. You've told us this story a hundred times.
No, I kept playing with the bubble because I was five and I know any
better kept playing with me. I supposed to play with the bubble. I was well,
no with my hands and fine. I got yeah. If you like being stick, I got a whole
thing of bubble tape in my hair and oh you were like putting it on your head.
Yeah, I was like like a home. I was like oh, there's a like a hat yeah. I
was doing shit like that and then I got it in my hair and my mom had to shave
my whole you literally were completely goofus. I was you had some kind of
divine guidance where you did all that you knew exactly the thing to do that
would be the most horrible thing to do yeah. Yeah, exactly how to how to mess
it up. I got my head stuck in a couch when I was a kid.
How do you get stuck in a couch? I got my head stuck in a recliner in between
the bars that recline so they just fucking on reclined it and put your
kids have to know what they're doing when they do that when they like stick
their head between the railing or something and they get it. They know
they're like they just want to see a fire. Yeah, they're like when you stick
your head in between the railing, it's because you want to see there's
manipulative calculus going on and that you want to think oh yeah, I fell in
well thinking I could I threw the remote at the TV. I didn't do that. I
would never do that, but when a kid does that I was really scared of falling in
a well. When I was a kid, I avoided wells at all costs. I never really saw
well me neither, but I saw a wishing well. I succeeded. If you fall in a
wishing well, it's not so deep. Pretty wells are deep main, a wishing well, a
wishing well, not that deep. If you fall in a wishing well, you can get out, but
you got to like get out over the wall of it. Yeah, where is that going with that?
It's going to be hard to climb out with all the damn pennies in my pocket. Yeah,
here's what I would wish for. Hey, I wish I was out of this well. I wish I was out
this world. I wish I was on a different world. Did you think when you were a kid,
did you have the thought in your head that one day you would go to space? I
still think I'm gonna go to space. I was too scared of space. I wouldn't even
look up at night. They're gonna do free space rides in 15 years.
That would be cool. The MTA is gonna give you a... You just do... 'Cause
we're all gonna die in 20 years, so in 15 years, they're gonna be like,
"Well, you can all just try going to space." You can tap to pay.
it's like a slide. Did you guys see that they're doing a simulation of a Mars
plant, not plantation of what do you call colony?
They're doing a simulated Mars colony, not colony, but like a, like a on the
computer. No, in a warehouse.
Can they do a bio dome 100 or something? That's a movie with Polly Shore.
but I think they didn't realize I think maybe that we should break into it and
pretend to be some kind of Mars. That would be a good idea. That's a pretty
good idea right. Yeah, I still think there could be aliens on the moon. I
agree. I don't think so. You know there's a face yeah. Well, there's a
face on Mars is what you're thinking on the Mars. Yeah, but I think that
between the moon and Mars, the moon is close. Mars is red and the moon is a
planet there. I don't think there's people who live on the moon. There's a
face okay. So you guys on you know that the face of face on Mars and the
other files episode about is also obelisks on Mars. Yeah, really there's a
super structure beneath the surface of the moon. To be honest with you,
basically what happened is fifty years ago. There was a huge, huge society on
Mars, fifty years ago or fifty something like either a thousand million billion.
I don't know, but some fifty years ago there was a a complete society on Mars,
and they built a giant face kind of structure that now the
NASA is saying that this is just this is just smoke and mirrors, but the truth
is that there was a society on Mars of alien life forms that was all wiped
out. There's a current society on the covered in water. Do you know this
pattern? Let me drop some knowledge on you. There is a they made a but there
when they invented remote viewing ESP being able to see using your imagination
you
they were able to this man named Ingo swan was able Ingo swan. I don't know
in I read his book. His book is his memoir is called penetration. Oh, by
Ingo swan, okay, and he
yeah, he goes one. He was able to imagine things across the world,
but what he saw about the moon when they were doing moon testing on him to
figure out what he could see that he was able to see an entire civilization and
structures under the surface of the moon, complete with water that are being
hidden from us by the surface of the moon that appears to be nothing, and
it's been hidden for a long time and it's all being covered up and there's
also aliens currently on the earth that are being disguised and you can tell
ingo swan said that you can that he was in the grocery store and he was picking
out produce at the grocery store and he saw a woman and he said this woman is so
beautiful that she cannot be human wow and that proved that she was from the
moon to so you're telling me that a pre Plaza is an alien. Yes, I look at the
it's in the it's a something else and something that you can tell from
community something you can tell about this guy. The reason you can tell this
guy's telling the truth and that he hasn't been corrupted by all these
three letter agencies is his book that I bought and the trace am penetration by
ingos one by ingos one
has a typo on the cover. Well, that's how you know nobody was getting their
fingers in there yeah, because the CIA, the FBI, they could they get in there,
they're going to change it. They're going to do your reading. You're right.
You know that it was all coming from his brain. Have you guys ever tried remote
viewing? Yes, yeah, dubious doing that right. Did you succeed? Yeah, I actually
can see my bedroom with my eyes closed at all times. I'm going to try it right
now. Okay, where are you going to go? Where should I go? I don't know you
let him go. You see where should I see okay the surface of the moon, okay
and usually you draw it. Well, I'm not very good at drawing Cameron. I'm my art
form is my words. Okay, then describe I see some seriously white ground
and I see a bunch of black crap out there, which is on my call space. Okay,
and wait what's that I'm oh God, I'm seeing a pale blue dot. Oh great dot of
pale
is very far away. I'm seeing some pale, but I didn't say which moon I was on. Oh,
oh, I guess you didn't say you were on a moon at all. Now, well about it now that
I think about it, I'm on a moon and I'm seeing a pale blue dot. Oh, but wait,
what am I seeing on the pill blue dot instead of love? I'm seeing hate and I'm
racial prejudice and sexism and worst of all misogyny and also kids being
unfairly treated by their parents. And also there's there's five or six green
monsters all around me and they are making something some kind of giant
weapon. A weapon? Yep and also I can tell that one of them is the most popular of
the six because the other ones are kind of just listening to what he's saying
and also he's the tallest one.
- But does he have like a special kind of hair?
- He has an Elvis hairdo.
(laughing)
Yeah, he has an Elvis greasy,
pomade hairdo. - That style?
- That slick back Elvis rock and roller style.
- That we all know and love?
- Oh my God, are the other ones bald
or do they all have their own distinct hairstyles
that define their personality?
- Well, basically, one of them has, okay,
so there's six of them, one of them has an Elvis hair.
- Okay.
- One of them has very long hair.
One of them has shorterish hair.
- But does he have glasses?
one of them is Bob very kind of cute. Okay, the bow and then three of them or
the remaining to
have no hair at all. Wait, let me go back
and they have a swimming pool, but instead of being blue, it's dust green.
Oh my God,
where were you? I was on
the moon. Holy, I told you there's water and structures and animals. What is
Literally all the things that I just saw what was that shit that?
Was it did Elon want to do it where he was gonna launch a nuke onto the two poles of Mars?
So that it creates water and ice I
Think that there are water from the ice that's there. I don't think anyone actually yeah
I don't think nobody no one wanted to do that, but it wasn't that like an actual like thing people talked about
That's like how you think so you would terraform Mars is with yeah, they're bombs
I don't know how that would work, but I also I don't know that much about nuclear bombs. I'm afraid that it might learn
How you buddy then I know in a couple weeks there will be a movie that teaches you everything
Does Mars have atmosphere when does that come? I don't know what that means
Atmosphere is not on Mars. He's on this planet. Yeah, he's a
Rapping the fuck out of some he's in Minneapolis, and he's rapping about his dad dying, huh?
Was that song from the fuck was that that was Cameron, but it actually did sound like some kind of interference
Yeah, I know. I thought you broke the computer or something.
When I was a kid, I tried to do, what you call that? Leave your body?
Transcendental projection.
That was the one that Jerry Seinfeld's obsessed with.
All of the Hollywood elites do TM, the David Lynch Foundation TM.
Thorough.
Bro, that shit.
Henry David Thorough.
But it pretty much works. I mean, these guys are really successful.
Yeah.
Yeah, you can do anything if you already are successful and it will make you
more successful. Do you know that in transit? Yeah, that's that's like the
one thing like Jerry Seinfeld and like David Lynch, like all the talking all
like yeah, this transit TM like change my life so much blah blah blah. It's
like yeah. What else do you have to do? All you do is just sit there. Stevie
wonder does it well. He does it all the time. Yeah, it's all he does. Yeah,
he's got his eyes closed every day.
Yeah,
It's amazing that he became so successful despite being I mean blonde blonde
blind
blind. Yeah, he was one of the first blonde guys to blow up in in Hollywood.
He used to be all Brunette. He thinks he's blonde.
He still thinks he's blonde.
He thinks he's a beautiful blonde woman. That's like the fucking like like
transcendental meditation. You just sit there and you just wait for like a you
like all your thoughts to go away. You can do that if you got a million dollars.
- No, you make them go away.
- No, no. Transcendental meditation is mantra based. So they give you,
you go take a class.
- I'm not thinking, I'm not thinking, I'm not thinking.
- They give you a mantra, which is usually some variation of like,
I am, or I will, I will, or some shit like that.
And you just say that over and over and over again. And it's supposed to be like,
- That's just the secret.
- You let thoughts fall away.
- You say it out loud.
- That is the secret.
- That's the secret.
that's manifestation. That's vision board. This stuff works dude. That's why we
are so fail. We are not fail. We don't do this shit. I do it. I
Cameron does it and he's fail. He is does not do transcendental meditation.
He you didn't even know what it was. I was tricking you. I was testing you
to see if you knew what it was. That is actually very advanced.
That is very advanced. They don't teach you that until later on in the
program. Yeah, most meditation you think of a leaf and watch it fly away. No,
you're thinking of falling asleep. They should make a meditation movies about
cool stuff instead of oh, you should be one meditate about whatever you want.
You should be one with nature. You should
I want to meditate and think that I am like a bulldozer or something and I'm
destroying millions of things. I'm I used to do a
orphanage is what I want to think I used to do. I'm a why I'm bulldozing an
orphanage. I mean you can think I'm the guy who's going in and bulldozing the old
Yankee Stadium. I'm just I'm making I'm going to say that to yourself. I'm going
to meditate to think that I'm making a million people. You're thinking of
imagining, imagining all you want. That's different from meditation. What is what
is meditation even meditation is is is sitting quietly with your thoughts. I'm
not doing that and noting them. I am not doing that. I used to do a meditation
where I had to imagine I was as big as the entire universe. That was the whole it
was a guided meditation. It was like you had to start off, you're in your room,
and then you're getting bigger and you're the size of your of your house.
No,
and it didn't. It's not how I grew. You tried to suicide by cop because of how
small he was. Yeah. You just had to make sure you're never going to do this
again. You need to figure big. When you were a kid, they called you sweet pea
because you were so small. If I was suicide by, if I was so small, I wouldn't
even have the cops involved. I would do suicide by foot. Suicide by thimble. I
the cops foot. You drink one symbol full of whiskey, yeah, that's what I would
do
brush shaved with a symbol
that doesn't even make how you shave with a thing is the little things on it.
You ever touched a symbol? No, because I'm not a girl. The only symbol I've
ever can't resist monopoly me to that's the only reason I know what a symbol is
yeah. Thimble was used in many stories. Thimble are history
that is true. Thimble thimbles are for sewing right there in fairy tales. It
protects your thumb.
Matt: Yeah.
Oh, then I've used one.
I've used one.
I never used one.
I never used one either, man.
I've simply touched it.
I've never even seen one in my life.
I took a home-ec class in 7th grade.
You thought you were going to make food, didn't you?
No, no.
It was like required.
You didn't get to choose the, you didn't get to choose, in 8th grade you got to choose
between cooking and woodshop and I should have chose cooking because my teacher, Mr.
Hill, hated my ass.
You did woodshop?
I did woodshop.
I made a little truck, yeah.
Dang, school sounded so cool, man.
I wish I went to school.
I always forget you were homeschooled, but...
Yeah, 'cause I'm so not kinda homeschooled.
When I was in seventh grade, I made a gym bag
and I got a C on it because my stitching was terrible.
So I had to use the thimble and I tried to fix it.
That's my thimble experience, y'all.
I made a gym sad.
There was a guy named Jim and we used to make fun of him.
Yeah.
He wore a suit.
my uncle Jim made him sad because I made fun of his elevator. You were a
scared of brief. He was a suit and briefcase kid yeah now see these kids
who we used to make fun of are the CEO. Unfortunately, their lives are worse
than ever before.
You'd love to think that their CEOs now, but unfortunately they're somehow below
the bottom strata of society. Yeah, they've fallen through the cracks
completely. They have started an ebay store that does not go row. They're
living in a in a
bower. Listen, I'd love for them to be the king of the health care industry or
something like that. They are the size of an ant. I do know one kid that was
like kind of a suit to class kind of kid who had told me that he was buying
Bitcoin in like two thousand and thirteen. Yeah, that kid is definitely
rich. Now he probably sold it in twenty fourteen probably, but even then he's
probably made some money off it yeah and I made no money and I said Bitcoin. What
the hell is that
Yeah. Bitcoin? And he told me that I should start mining it because I had a
graphics card. I was going to try to, when I heard about the concept of
Bitcoin when I was 14. I was like, I'm going to make my own. Me too. I thought
that I would get a Bitcoin miner. Well, I thought that I was going to get like a
Bitcoin miner on my computer and everything, but I was going to install
it on my laptop. I had a laptop from 2001 that was still running Windows XP.
It was a Dell with a little trackpad. You were going to grind coins on it? And I
thought that if I just ran that while I was at school, I would get free money.
I've watched probably thirty five YouTube videos trying to explain what the fuck
how that works and what that means. It means I just gave up means nothing. It
doesn't make any God damn sense. I thought that it was a cheat code for
unlimited free money. It kind of was for a couple of years. Yeah, and it probably
will be again. That's the thing. This is multiple times people. Everybody
bitcoins gone up and then down. It was C told you and then it just goes right back
up in a couple more years. It really makes no sense to me at all.
We need to have like Gary Vee on this show and have him explain that to us.
Bitcoin?
Yeah. We need to make a hard pivot. We need to do Gary Vee on here. Gary Vee, us three,
and then like the guys.
Two girls.
We need two girls.
Two girls who do OnlyFans and then those two guys who yell at them.
Not musical pop stars, great talents. Not women who sell their bodies for what, a buck?
paltry sense and dollars. I mean it's that those pictures are forever. You can
water mark them,
but what
well, what do you mean you and water mark them, but what but just what you
know your children are going to see that if they sign up.
Imagine imagine you that's the thing. If my mom had one, I would have signed up.
I just want to support her yeah. I would yeah. I'm trying to support. I would I
would sign up and say mom. I'm not looking, but
I want you to have a you think there's people who do that mom. You think I
have an allowance for ten ninety nine every single month
in a visa debit card
and she's a name that you don't know yeah
under name bits. What's the mom? What's the most attractive name in the world to
you
Sebastian Sebastian Sanchez has a
only fan
Yeah, but if I had an only fans, I wouldn't post any images. I would close
the account. Imagine my had one. If I had one, I'd immediately. I think we have
one for the podcast. I think you're right. I think we made one as a funny,
funny joke. You did a couple years ago. You did it and we had nothing to do with
it. No, because we have one photo on there and it's like you posted. It's
a picture you posted. I remember it's not a photo. It's a video. It's a video.
It's a video. Well, the title of the video. I mean, I don't think I think
it's not possible to sign up for it, because I don't think we ever finished
the account, but the video is titled Patrick changing
and I can tell you what it is, but it's it would be a spoiler for the video.
I think we should just say what it is because it was a video of Patrick
transforming into a werewolf yeah
okay, that's pretty funny yeah.
That is a funny
future change.
Wait, how do you transform into a werewolf? Oh, we had an app called
Monsterify.
Monsterify? Yeah. I think it was actually Face Story. Remember Face Story?
Face Story, yeah. I missed the first wave of facial apps. Me too. The facial
apps were amazing. Facial apps were a different thing. I had a phone. It's all
skin care and pornographic and gang banging. Yeah, exactly. I had a phone
that could run CamWow, if you remember CamWow from the iPod Touch.
And then I got a new phone, thought that it would be able to transfer over to this phone.
But it didn't.
It didn't.
Then you had the last surviving iPhone in my possession with CamWow on it and then you
needed a phone.
And then I gave you that phone and then you broke it.
And you bit down on it too hard and you crackled the screen up.
which I completely have destroyed every phone except for this one,
because this one has a case on it. Guys, you copied my case. So I didn't copy
it. I got the cheapest one on Amazon. Yeah, you copied me. That's what I did.
Millions did this. I did it for a hundred thousand reviews on Amazon. Yeah,
did you scroll to see what the first chronological review was? It wasn't you.
Oh, so you did check. What was it? Then I checked it was Ben David, Ben David,
Ben Davis, nope, Ben David, Ben David, yep, Ben Davis makes pretty good pants.
You can find him. Well, this isn't that person. This is some other guy. He's
got a gorilla logo.
You would wear those. I do yeah. You like animals.
Don't ever say that you like animals. Don't you ever say that? Oh, one more
thing about monkeys. Is it called aping? Because like you'll say, oh, I ate this
that aped me copy monkey see monkey do because monkeys copied humans. No,
it's because of monkey see monkey do.
So if you are have a monkey and you go like this,
the monkey will do that because it thinks that you like it when I think
copy, I thought it was monkeys copy humans by walking and creating tools.
That's the other way around. I don't think I've ever seen a monkey's. We
don't know that I was thinking about something the other day that I can't
remember.
that's a great place to end the show. You are useless, not useless. It was a guys.
If you love this high energy, amazing episode, yeah, you should travel back in
time to yesterday
and do what Patrick's about to say, or you could go see me in Austin on the
weekend of the 28th through the 29th through the 30th is when I take a flight
home. I'm going to be doing four shows. I'm opening for Dan Lakata, so Dan
La Costa. Go see me there. And then I'm also going to be on the bus later to
make a bunch of shit. Got a frittata, a culotta. A miata. I'm going to drive a
miata, drink a culotta with Dan Licata. I haven't had a culotta in a long time.
You guys want to get culottas after this? Okay. Joe Pera, that boy's scared of a
fucking... Do you guys know how to make the best smoothie in the world? How? No,
I'm asking. Oh. Oh, we can figure this out once the show's done. No, I actually,
I said I know I know you also also in if you're if you're in Brooklyn, New York,
you want to see me no no no. I know I okay, I got it instead of okay banana
yeah, no ice instead of an instead of ice use frozen
milk. No, you can't freeze milk. You can you can freeze milk. It's
you didn't even let me finish my recipe. You use a fresh banana and then you use
frozen berries. Yeah, I got those and you use I got those from my own. You can use
I think everyone knows the smoothie, but if you know I need to hear this, if
you're going for taste, though, here's my recommendation instead of milk, orange
juice, orange juice, orange. Okay, that's a good that's and that's it and that's
pretty three ingredients. Maybe a little honey if you need it right on protein
powder. I'm going to try that also if you live in Brooklyn, New York, and you
would like to see me at a bar show hosted by Pitbull impersonator, Stephen Vega
that is on the twenty-sixth. And if you want to see me doing my laundry, come to
my laundromat. I only go there for a short amount of time, because I just drop my
clothes in the washing machine, then I go home and I come back to change it over,
and I just come back to pick it up. So it's a small window, but I'll be there
three times, one to bring it to the washer, one to switch it between the
washer/dryer, and then one to pick up the clothes. And I will be in Morro Bay,
California, visiting my family at the end of the month. Oh, yeah, and I'll be
leaving the country as well. I'll probably be walking around. He's gonna be in some
another part of the world. I can't reveal what I'll be out of the country at the
end of the month. I'm doing none of us are going to be here to hold the office
down. Somebody could break in. I'm doing the break in. You want to break into our
office. The address is I'm going abroad to report on some issues going down
and other parts of the world. I think you'd be an amazing war reporter. I'm
going to send you guys some videos of your pressure. Okay, we will see
Cameron's report when he doesn't be reporting. All right, wear the helmet.
what helmet Caleb? Yes, sir. Let's record your vertical for your dunking goal.
My vertical. Okay. Okay.
Well, we're on the on this
stand. Wait, stand next to Patrick. Go, go move the chair that way and stand
next to Pat. Pat will be the match. So Pat sitting here. This is about two
feet tall right here. This is not running. This is just my my yeah,
straight vertical. I would get a higher vertical, right? But that's not really
how we're measuring this.
Oh, I heard that crack. That was a huge crack. Yeah, you have a huge crack.
Jump. Okay, so you didn't even really bend your knees at all. So if you bend
your knees, you can get a little more air. Well, you're just your feet could be a
little higher up. See, like that doesn't make your yes, it does. You can go over a
hurdle better like that. We're not hurtling. I'm trying to dunk that doesn't
No, no, keep your feet straight at the bottom.
You brought them up.
- Well, it's just about the height of the vertical, right?
We're not dunking, there's no hoop.
- But your vertical is not how far your feet up
are from the ground. - But for right now.
- We need a hoop.
We gotta get a hoop for the office.
- We'll just see who can touch higher on the wall.
That makes way more sense. - Okay, that's better.
But that can't be seen by the camera.
- Yeah, that, let's, what are we doing?
We gotta end this.
- I got higher.
- Okay, bye.
Can we get one eye?