So explain what you did to your body and the reason why and give us one reason,
but you can't get three good reasons. Give it yeah. Okay. There's one more.
There's one reason and I can't really talk about it just yet,
but
I give us two other reasons because I know that you wouldn't do such a
drastic for only this one reason. I did it for just this one
No, you wouldn't. You're not that dedicated.
No, I'm more dedicated than ever now.
I'd put too much effort into something the other day.
I screamed so loud on set of a movie.
Whoa! Oh my God!
Why are you buzzing it?
Because you just humble bragged.
That's the humble brag buzzer.
I was not humble bragging.
I was getting...
I screamed so much on the set of a movie.
I'm actually giving it. I gave it my all on the set of a movie. I was too
dedicated.
I got to
generating hype for the movie right. So let me guess you weren't even so he was
a man, a scene with the extra. You did go on a date with you. It's nice. I
wanted to get his info before we left, but they they hustle. He left
immediately. I wanted to use. I wanted to use him as an extra and something
was his name. I don't even remember. Damn, that's what I wanted to use him
an extra where you film him and you watching TV at your house.
Yeah, that's fine.
That's what I'm just saying.
You guys would have liked him. You guys would have liked him a lot.
I liked him. I talked to him the least out of all of us.
I don't care about extras, man. They don't matter to me.
Me neither, but he proved himself. He showed something. He showed he had what was necessary
to be a star.
He's got star power. I have a photo of them on a date if you want to see it.
Yeah, but we don't have the GoPro today, so you're going to have to go.
Damn it.
I'll show it. I'll go. I'll walk. Yeah, you'll walk. It's pretty important to
see. I would say. Yeah. He was a really nice guy. They genuinely look like
they're in love. And you had such a connection with this guy that you were
surrounded by people that you knew, and every time I looked over, you were just
talking to this guy. I was, but they told me to sit there. I could, what am
I supposed to do? Just saying, man. Get out of my seat? He's an extra, bro.
Ignore him. Look at those two. Holy fuck, they're in love. I made such a
connection with him. You guys would not get it. That's the thing.
Immediate on on screen chemistry. You would on screen. Can I show you the
type of thing we were doing in our scene? Yes,
wow, and this is what he was doing.
He was miming. He was miming too much. One of the extras was had to sign had
to
had to sign a check or had like a restaurant check in his part, and I saw
in between takes. He was taking out like a note and practicing
and so he had this like it was like it wasn't a note. It was like an old
receipt that he had in his wallet and he practiced signing it like a hundred
times. It was just covered in his signature over and over and over again.
That's so funny. Wait, who had to who had to sign stuff? I thought it was
just him and the other guy. This voice. Dude, it's so bad. It's because I was
doing fine yesterday and then I had to scream at you for the scene. But why are
you also it's not just light on my voice. I'm trying not to like raise it at all
like even laughing hurt. You weren't doing this ten minutes ago when we were
setting up. You sounded normal. I I you're playing it up fine. I don't know. I
just need some water honestly. Okay you want this. Yeah. This one. Yeah it'll fix
it.
You better now? Yeah, I'm completely better now. I'm so much better now.
But yeah, I...
I never wanna see another extra again. I'm sick of them. I was running into
them, I was bumping into them. They're rude people. You fell into a woman. I
fell onto a woman. You fell onto a woman who almost broke her clavicle. She
acted like it was a big deal.
It was. You broke a plate.
I broke a plate on the other side of the room and then I ran into
we're very, very fastly. That's true. That's not a crime. We're describing too
much of the plot. We can't. We signed an NDA. No, we didn't. Yeah, we didn't. No,
we didn't. I'm not. The movie is about I'll tell everything I don't give a
fuck. They didn't pay me. It was Barbie. It's Barbie. Oh my God. Did you hear?
Wait, I actually did hear something. Apparently, in addition this weekend, in
addition to Barbie coming out and and I know what you think. I know what you're
thinking I'm going to say here, but and in addition to Oppenheimer coming out
okay, there is a new
episode of podcast about list dropping and it's this episode
wait and this is coming out the day after Barbie and Oppenheimer, so it's
kind of same opening weekend, potty potty, barb,
hardland,
barb, barb, barb, barb, barb, barb, barb, barb, barb, barb, barb, barb, barb, barb,
barb and liner. I just about barb.
Potty potty lines, potty liner, potty liner, op and potty pot barp, op and
pardon me, barb cast pod op, leisten barb.
There we go. Hard cast, hard cast, our arbit bop and our barb and limon. Yeah,
holy fuck, dude. Look, I've been seeing the memes. People are excited. Look for
And we pulled out all the stops.
Look, people are doing a triple feature.
That's a practical gun effect that we have right here.
This is not CGI.
I've seen the memes on Instagram that people are buying.
They're buying a ticket to Barbie in the morning, and then they sit in the lobby of the theater for an hour to listen to this episode, and then they bought a ticket for whatever the other one is.
And you know what? Here's the best part.
Here's the best part.
What does a movie ticket cost nowadays?
Fifty bucks?
Sixty bucks?
I don't know.
fifty bucks and that's not even including popcorn right. That's for half
a seat. That's right to
five. One one
Patreon sub to part about list. If you want to go bare bones, that's only
five dollars.
If you want to go bear, a really sad thing about someone going bare, but
that's a dead guy. Yeah, that is scary. They want to if you want to go dry
bones.
I don't want to play as dry bones. I don't want to play as you're too scared
of barb and lepon hind hind in the wire, but the time or bart class the
bartender bark there. We go. We fixed it bartender bark, bark, bark, bark,
bark. It's honestly, I still feel like we haven't gotten it. I think it's
pardon, hyphen, pardon, my in my in my garden, my guard, Lee this clock this
class, okay, oh, is in oh, parvin, oh, parvin cast bow, barb and parvin cast
Barb Bautenheimer list three listory listering there we go. We got it again.
We found a barb and barb open
bar bout
bar bar, bop and bouton yeah, Barb cast about
that's good. This timer bar bop and bop out, tell you, tell you what our
bopping out bout list barb. I want to I want to barb my list of ops. Yes, yeah,
this with the Oppenheimer. Yeah, I want to find my ops.
Here's what I don't want to do. We're him them,
take him out to a nice dinner.
That's to go to food.
That's what I'm doing.
You'd say that in a warehouse.
I'm not taking I'm not taking my ops to a delicious food restaurant. No, you're
not. Oh, my God, I bet somebody that's the poison restaurant.
What are you doing?
Jimmy is watching. Are you playing watching old? Are you playing an old
episode? Why are you playing an old episode? He's doing his thing. He's
making an alias for this because we move to the Mac.
You know, why don't you play? Why don't you play the episode while we're while
we're talking play the previous episode while we're talking because it will
sync up. We'll talk about the same thing at one point. Last night when we were,
there's something about having to be doing something for so long it makes you
go so, so crazy, but. Maybe that's why I did this. Me and Patrick and Alex did
come up with a movie idea. Oh, I heard about this already. Mr. Toilet, yeah,
you were there, you were listening. It was on, it's Toilet Man. Toilet Man. Yeah.
And he's a superhero.
so we were we were we were pitching an idea and no one on set was listening to
us, not the director Joe sound the sound. Let me tell you because what you what
you what you're thinking here is I hear what you're saying. Can I tell you the
truth? Tell me the truth. The truth is that the room was completely and
utterly silent.
All the extras are sitting, boiling alive, miserable, sitting silent, waiting
the forty five minutes for them to set up the cameras and every everybody in
the entire room hard. You go toilet man's like oh yeah
and you guys are giggling on the ground. I was lying on his back on the ground.
Alex and Patrick were crouched over him. We couldn't see so it sounded like
they were tickling you because they were laughing so hard that you did not
actually hear the actually what happened, because I tell you what man
doesn't say. Oh yeah, toilet man is a superhero where something's going on.
Say there's a new kind of nine eleven or something. The bridge is on fire
bridges on fire
I'll save you, but I gotta go really really quickly here. I'll be right back
and then he goes to the bathroom and he gets
oh wait, wait. I thought that the toilet was the one and he doesn't say oh yeah,
no, the toilet, the toilet says oh
so yeah, that's a
super hero is a guy who any time that they call on him. He says okay, I'm
I'm going to go handle it and then he runs the nearest bathroom in the
you don't like this idea. I like it. I'm telling you what I'm telling you how
everybody in the room felt about it. They liked it even more. There was a
lot really dead. So
quite a firm I've ever heard in my life
they're hearing is good. You hear a say with joan and johnny everybody were so
stressed out like trying to set up all the shot. They were like moving all the
around the white people were moving everything. That's why I don't hear
anything like this. Did you guys hear that? So did you guys hear about when
toilet man saves the guy and what he does? No, he says
hold on here. I got to bring you somewhere and then he brings his other.
He brings that guy to the toilet, the bathroom and the toilet says, Oh, you
bought a friend
and then he toilet. I don't even know how the toilet. I didn't we didn't get
Our brains were fucking boiling alive in that restaurant.
There was no AC in there.
It was just like shut down.
This restaurant's been closed since COVID.
There's just like, like, I was, dude, I was looking around at that place.
They had like things up that like I haven't seen since like, it was like.
Explain what you mean by things you haven't seen.
Yeah, what are you talking about?
I was looking around this restaurant and there were things I haven't seen.
Such as?
It was just a, it was a program for March of 2020 and they had so many jams.
the year twenty twenty
something. I haven't seen since twenty twenty, which is a date that says
twenty twenty on yeah and then a bunch of bottles of Aperol.
I haven't seen that since twenty twenty. No, that's all I've seen.
I've seen that often, often, very early and often yeah. We need to make a
movie now. Yeah, we need to make do I know we don't need to make a movie at
all. That was so stressful. Shut up bitch. It seems easy thing in the world.
that seems it's a way to
would say that the extra would say it was easy. The guys who have to run into
women really, really fast. The guy had to roller skate all day. The guy had to
scream
had to scream.
And what you have to do count on your fingers silently. No, that was what the
other guys ideas from the floor. No, I got to hang out with my best friend.
Yeah, exactly. You would think it's easy. Yeah, when your your job was hanging
out with your best friend. Our job was to pretend that we hate each other,
yeah, which is hard and to go on the floor. He had to spit in my face fifty
times. I spit I do. There's so much spit on your face. I know yeah, so sorry.
He did something where he screamed at me and I was I was drenched in spit. By
the end of it, he was completely filled with so you guys feel on the strike
then. Well,
as we were saying yesterday as future SAG, after a future SAG, WGA and
directors, guild members, as future triple threats and future Oscars,
Oscars pending, Oscars pending kind of style guys. Yeah man, this strike is
killing me. This strike is I explain the whole strike to the my extra friend. He
was like so what's going on? You don't explain it. He would have walked out.
Yeah, well he didn't because he loved his company. Oh you're right. If it was
anybody but you, he would have walked out. Yeah, he was also the only person at
our table group who got paid.
no, you get paid thirty nope, didn't get paid anything.
They walked over, they handed him a lot of money and then they walked away a
lot for yeah. I mean I couldn't see how much it was. I just saw him hand of
money. It was four of us. What would you call it? Two bills? I couldn't see how
many it was. It wasn't it was a five on the outside, so I knew it was a small
amount because they wouldn't have a five in it, but it was it was out. It was a
it look like it was. It was a put to they put put three tens in a rubber band,
but no, I did not get paid at all. So well, think about that whenever you're
watching that thing, you have drops on Vimeo. Do you have any interest in
watching or in
pursuing the extra life from now on? Honestly, do you think you could be an
extra? I think I'm going to career. I think I'm going to lead an extra strike
just for the extras. Yeah, that makes sense of the injustice. I face a silent
strike yep to show you're also because we're we just stand in the background of
the actors strike
we hold signs and we go.
This is an amazing idea of my die. You guys can add the whole the whole sag
straight. You guys can sit in the back, but no, I would never do that again. I
wish I didn't do it. It's so well. It sucked. It was that bad. I was there
sitting for five hours. I didn't get paid. Of course it sucked. You got
like being around my friend. I didn't eat any of pizza. I ate before. I
you have the option to eat. I'm going to eat there's a hot room for five hours.
There's pizza, there's chips, I ate some rose, got paid in trail, my
trail mix and you made your money back. You made your money back and you got
trail mix. They didn't even compensate for me for my train fair. Can you
believe that? No, they compensated you with cookies and pizza and trail mix and
you everything the money was on the table and you just decided not to take
the money was on the table in front of a different guy. I didn't get it. The
pizza was on the table and you said no, no, no, no, no. I'm already so full of probably
peanut butter and jelly.
Well, there's only it was four people that we knew and then a bunch of Craigslist extras
so that it didn't look like it was a restaurant full of young people.
Which what's the problem with that? Why can't you have a restaurant filled with young? Well,
you got to have old people in a restaurant. I haven't seen an old person at a restaurant
in years.
Yeah, that's true. They don't go out much anymore because of COVID and the current pandemic.
I need to stop going to restaurants and eating. I'm getting as fat as a balloon.
You think you're getting fat? Look at me. I look disgusting.
That's your own choice because of your hair, your head shave.
I look like a complete cow.
No, you do look like an animal though. I've been trying to figure out what animal you look like with no beard.
I've never had a beard. I've always just had the mustache.
You had a beard.
I did have a beard. There was that time.
I was, I grew, I forgot that I had like a huge beard when I first met you guys.
Yeah, your beard turns orange.
It wasn't so huge.
No, a big Santa Claus beard, I remember.
No, there is, yeah, I had like, like young Santa from like year without a Santa Claus.
It's what I looked like for a little bit.
I would say a beard.
I wouldn't say huge beard.
It was, no, there's a photo I have where it was poking out the sides.
It's a type of sriracha out of sriracha ramen.
That's what I think of when I think of huge beard.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Yeah.
You just have...
I mean you guys met... when you guys met me I either had like a beard or just was clean-shaven.
I didn't have a mustache for...
Either an air on your face or you didn't, straight up.
No, beard is different from mustache.
But the beard got a mustache.
The beard is 75... or mustache is like 25%.
Mutton chops is 25.
And then if you do some weird goatee, that's 50.
But then a beard is 100.
beard, mustache, and mutton chops, that's 50. One mutton chop and then that's 33.
That's 33.
You're the only one of us who can grow like a really full, thick beard. Have you done
all the different combinations? Have you done... Has anyone ever tried just this?
I had chin strap.
Just the cheeks?
No.
No, that's a good idea.
Right? That's a good idea.
Maybe I'll grow that out.
That is a good idea.
Just the cheeks. No sideburns.
No sideburns. Yeah, exactly.
no side, no side burns. Yeah, exactly make it just two circles, beards, just
the cheeks beard. That's a good idea.
You see nobody nobody's done this. You can't even find this shit exist on
Google. Yeah, this is a new style that I just came up with. It's just the
cheeks beard.
Yeah, but you could try that. I think it could be called. It could be here's a
new style. I bet somebody locks. I bet somebody has done this style before
Maybe so it's like you grow a really thick mustache and then you shave a
bunch of lines into it. Yeah. So it's like a bunch of I'm not I'll say Charlie
Chaplin, a bunch of Charlie Chaplin mustaches next to each other.
Mini Hitlers. Well I wasn't going to say that but yeah.
You could get that. Like five for a little bit. Five Hitlers stacked back to back to back.
Back to back to back. Five Hitlers stacked and then back to back to back. I did have the
wharf for a little like when I had shaved it. The wharf? I did keep the wharf. I think
I think the whole thing's a war between the beard and the mustache.
That's how I understand it.
But I had just right here, like how Worf has his fish.
I don't know who Worf is.
Worf from Star Trek.
He's a Klingon.
You had scars on your face?
No.
Like a seal?
Is he a Klingon?
Pfft.
You cannot say that.
Why?
He's got all this stuff on his face.
The scars.
Klingons don't have scars.
They just have a ridged head.
They have gills or something.
They don't have gills.
Oh.
Excuse you.
have gills. They're fishes. They are not fishes. They look like they have gills
to me.
What? I don't know anything about Star Trek. I have no interest in Star Trek.
Me neither. Yeah. I watched Star Trek and I was like, "Oh, I guess I could
probably get into this, but I'm not going to." It's all of the worst parts
of sci-fi of like, you have to... What? You're supposed to recycle? That's why
you watch this show? I just like any show where it's a hundred episodes and
it's from the 70s. I think that's the best, always the best TV show. But you
gotta watch Deep Space Nine. I feel like you could get into that. I'm not
watch any of it. I'm sure I would like it but it's not going to happen. It could have happened
years ago. You've got to get into it when you're like 6 years old. I just don't have
the mental gumption anymore to watch that many episodes of anything. It's too much man.
When it was on Netflix I tried to do a Deep Space Nine rewatch and I think I got to like
halfway through season 3 and I was like Jesus Christ this is a slog. This is just so hard
to get through this. They didn't even get, Worf wasn't even there yet.
They used to make 50 episodes every fucking season of every show.
Now it's like, oh, we can make 8 piece of shit episodes.
Uh huh. But it used to be 25 bangers.
25 huge bangers.
25 almost bangers.
25 of the best episodes you've ever seen.
I remember watching X-Files.
Really?
That show was so fire.
There's a lot of episodes. I've never watched the whole thing.
I've only seen the movie.
The nice thing about X-Files, that's one of the nice things about a show where there's
a million episodes is there's usually...
of the movie a point where it gets really, really bad. Yeah, everyone says
you're allowed to stop and you know you can stop twin peaks like episode one
never seen twin peaks either. I mean even like the the Simpsons, it's like
there's a lot of good stuff, but I know that there's an end in sight. Yeah, I
know that there's a point where I just want to make it will make me want to
stop. Yeah, it's not even like I'm gonna be like okay. I have to tear myself
away. It's like I'll keep watching. I'm really like this. I can't do this.
This is really sneaks up on you too, because like yeah, it's not there's not
say consensus. This is where you should stop watching some people. I feel like
people say it's season nine. Some people stop it like season twelve or whatever it
really is. So it somewhere in there you go. Oh yeah, I'm done. I'm going to go
to the first season ten and you watch like a season four episode and you're
like oh my God yeah. I didn't even notice this was happening. Yeah, there
really is a great that occurs with that show when you're watching a creep side
show Bob he's far from a creep. He's a complete yeah. I would say Mo is the
creep of the Simpsons man.
He is a creep.
Moe is the one who's always trying to look at Marge's panties.
Moe is not suicidal.
If Moe was suicidal, there's no such thing as suicidal.
There's no such thing?
No, if you were suicidal you would kill yourself.
And Moe's still alive.
For now.
Doesn't he try to kill himself every episode?
No.
Yeah, that's the Easter egg isn't it?
No, that's not the movie detail.
The Easter egg is they have one big scar right there on Moe's wrists.
Oh, it's very sad. What would a Simpson scar even look like
Harry Potter?
That's actually a good that's the that's the exact way to find it. Did he leave?
I think maybe he left. Oh, that's okay. He left and he left just the cheeks
beard up.
Oh, he's here. He's alive. Oh, can you search Simpson's Harry Potter and see
just what color the scar is?
Simpson's Harry Potter. I mean it'll be red, but I just want to see what it
looks like. Oh, it's well on the pig. Well, that's not he's not yellow.
I need to see a yellow fell like a Simpson right here. The second, but
yeah, so there you go. That's basically not even anything that look like
little easy words. That's a it does catch up. Yeah, that is a catch up scar.
That's that's there is what is it? Simpsons do better with the guy, the guy,
the what Nelson's dad snake or was that his name? Is it snake? It is snake is the criminal
guy. Yeah, he is. Yeah, I think he's Nelson's dad. I didn't know that. I didn't know that
an Easter egg. Isn't it like an implied thing that he's Nelson's dad? I have no idea. I
don't follow the Easter eggs on most shows. Yeah. I'm going to say here's what we need
to make a movie. Guys, hop you don't follow the Easter eggs in hop. Don't even know what
you're talking about. It's the Russell Brand movie where he's a rabbit.
Peter Rabbit. Here's what we need to make a movie guys. It's about Easter.
We need to make a movie so that we can add movie details
to the movie. Yes. We need to do that. I've been trying. I've been working
on the movie details for the podcast, adding all sorts of background
stuff. Like what? For instance, in this episode people may
not have noticed the entire run time I'm holding a gun.
That is actually a movie detail. Here's an Easter egg. I set this up for Cameron's
birthday present. And it stayed up. And it stayed up. And we haven't touched it
for some reason. I think that that's probably why, you know, between Barbie and
Oppenheimer, me, I'm gonna go for the movie detail movie. I'm gonna go see
Oppenheimer. Yeah. Because there are going to be so many details in that fucking
movie, you won't even believe it. It's historical. They're gonna hide.
died. Do you think that they're going to put Hitler in the movie straight? Yes,
who plays him? I don't think they will. That person right now should be
blackballed from Hollywood for playing him in 2023.
If he's in it, I do you think that is Hitler? Hitler's kind of the same role
as Santa in movies. Do you know what I mean? Where like you just have to look
fifty percent like him yeah and then you don't really say much yeah. It's
what it's it's yeah. You have the very recognizable costume. Yeah, you don't
even really have to look like him. It's just like the Santa impersonators to
where it's like half a year. You're not working. Taiko, a tt barely. I mean
probably he's again. Well, I guess he is at the probably the fifty percent he's
fifty percent yeah. He looked fifty percent like he's halfway between
looking like Hitler and not looking like Hitler. Yeah, he's a man at the time.
So it was pretty much most men look like Adolf Hitler. You could definitely be young Indiana
Jones versus young Hitler right now. And it yeah is not good for me. Why? That's a role.
Yeah, that is a role. What was that? What was the song we were making up about acting?
You can tone out. Oh, you can tone out extra. Oh, even though I was the one who was making
up this song in the first place? I ain't afraid to no roll. Was that you made that up? We were
all singing that together. Yeah, it was Ghostbusters. I came up with I ain't afraid to no roll.
Acting makes me feel good. Acting makes me feel good. But then I came up with I ain't
afraid to no roll. I ain't afraid to no roll. Being an actor has got to be the blessing
of my entire life at this point. It has changed a lot about me. It's hard. Change your voice,
change your face. When I go home, when I go home, can you get me a coffee right now? Change
I open my door.
Well, that's empty.
That's what I think of actors.
I get them empty coffees.
I want to be an actor so much.
That's exactly what I wanted.
That I want to live in a trailer.
Yeah.
I would want to live in a trailer.
I want to live with all the actors and with all the trailers.
Brendan Fraser is one of them.
Yeah, he's in a trailer.
He's in a trailer.
If you're a real actor, you're sitting in a trailer park.
Your home is your trailer.
You guys are going to think it's all fun and games being an actor until I Me Too you.
you will. I hate as an actor,
me too. I do not like me to
or I don't like the stuff. How do you even say that I don't like the I don't
like that comes before I don't like the movement happen. No, not the movement. I
don't like I like that. No, you're supposed to you like the movement. I
love the movement before it. I hate I love the players hate the game,
which which team or maybe reverse. I don't know. I just don't scratch that
okay. I don't like speaking. Okay, I don't like the scratching that goes on
in me too and the what's on changing what is me to I don't know. Are you
talking about? I don't know what that is man. I'm a new actor. I missed all
this shit. I just started acting yesterday.
I don't know anything about any of that. I know TMZ Entertainment Weekly.
That's kind of Mario Lopez, Mario Lopez tonight, Lopez tonight,
These are the only things that I know. Okay. I don't know anything about anything that happened
in 2017. I do know one thing happened in 2017. What's that? Dunkirk. Exactly. Christopher
Nolan. I have a movie mind. I never saw that movie. Me neither. You know what I forgot?
Let's watch it right now. We were talking about the Christopher Nolan movies. A movie
I just remembered this morning that he made was Insomnia. Have you seen that? You mean
Inception? No, we were just talking about this, but I don't remember. Insomnie's Al Pacino
and Robin Williams is a serial killer? I had never heard of it. Pierce told me about it
for the first time like two days before you talked about it. It's so good. It's an amazing
movie. I gotta check it out. It's like 50 or 60 hours long. It's very, very long, which
is I think good. I like long ones. Robin Williams? Yeah, Robin Williams is a bad guy. He's a
great bad guy. Yeah. Yeah, he was a pretty bad guy. No, that's not what I'm saying. I'm
I'm saying that he was a good actor when he acted as a bad fella.
Uh-huh.
You know.
Not so much anymore.
I think he was great.
Mrs. Doubtfire, that's a villain role.
That's an easy role.
Anyone can play that.
Have you ever...
That's a layup.
Have you ever considered that he would go to fucking jail if he did that in real life?
Those are the actions of a psychotic man.
If he did what?
If he did all that Mr. Doubtfire.
Somebody should...
And if it was called Mr. Doubtfire, there would be a changing scene where the sun walks in
in. Wow. Wait, why? If it was called Mr. Doubtfire? If it was called Mr. Doubtfire and the roles
were reversed, it would be ultimately so sexualized. They probably do want to do a gender-swapped
Mrs. Doubtfire. Honestly, they're probably going to have a new Doubtfire movie where
it's a they/them parent turning into a they/them man. Wow! And it's called just Doubtfire.
Wow. That's the stupidest way to figure out your name for your fake maid.
Mrs. Doubtfire. He saw the word Doubtfire on a newspaper.
What? That's not where is that surname even come from? Doubtfire? I've never
seen that movie on either. Yeah, that's how he gets the last name. Doubtfire. He
just reads it somewhere. He read. That's how everybody came up with names. He
he sees the word doubt fire in the eighties and nineties, the
people named Michael went up like seven thousand percent because of Michael
Jackson, Michael Jordan and Michael Tyson, Michael Bublé and Michael Bublé
later on in the decade, but there's no everybody just steals and speaking of
gender swaps, unless you make a Michael Bublé, Santa buddy, the way to
the way to get out of this name cycle where everyone just takes all the
copies all the names. You just got to come up with a brand new name that no
one's ever been named before. Yeah, exactly. Let's put a bunch of letters
down. Hebe. Yeah. I can name my kid that.
Craig. Pay LeBron. Name your kid Pay LeBron.
Pay Patrick, Caleb, Cameron. Oh, okay. Pay LeBron. Pay LeBron. Pay LeBron. Pay
LeBron no money to name your kid.
and he's not getting a red cent for your that kid's name. You're going to have
the people are like, oh, pay LeBron. Was that like a like what you combined
like Patrick and LeBron? No, it's for three guys. Actually, instead of oh
wait, that's our names combined is pay LeBron. Whoa. Yeah, I just realized that
you and me could be LeBron. If you mixed our names together. Yeah, I don't care
about the first part, but you and me being LeBron is actually so it's the
the last the letters of three of both spells LeBron, but what's the first
came care
came to
LeBron comecca LeBron comecca. This is an amazing revelation yeah.
Okay, we could definitely do a name of a name. Combine
LeBron comecca is a perfect name yeah, and if we added Patrick, I mean Rick is
already in there. Yeah, but I just be the middle name LeBron comecca LeBron
Patrick comecca
If you add all of our names together, we already have that.
You are getting so many phone calls today.
It's my credit card company.
Well, answer them.
They're trying to give you a new line of credit.
They're trying to give me more credit?
You think that's why?
I think so.
Not because I didn't pay?
I want to have a...
Everybody I know has a credit card has like a $15,000 limit.
I have a $2,000 limit.
I have a $1,500 limit.
I think mine is $6,000.
$6,000?
How do you get up there, man?
Mine was a student credit card.
get up there man. Mine was a student credit card. You have to pay your credit card? Yeah.
What? That sucks man. That sucks. I fucking hate it. In college I just maxed out two credit
cards and I still haven't paid them. I just left them alone. Yeah. But my credit is not
that bad. It's like $680 or something. Oh that's good. Yeah it's okay. I don't know
how that happened. Mine is $597. Really? Yeah. I'm honestly surprised it's that high. Yeah.
I thought that you'd be in the 400. No, no, no, no. I have 10,000 credit. You don't have
10,000 credit. 10,000. Your FICO is 10,000. I don't believe you. I looked it up. You can't
look it up. I googled it. You can't google your own. I googled Cameron's credit score.
And the info box popped up and it said 10,000. Hey FICO, throw me a damn bone, you dog. Because
so it sounds like leave me alone. Oh, because it sounds like Fido bones
throw me a freaking bone.
It's because it's one letter off from Fido and dogs throw bones. That's why
saying that if you had two dogs with each other, Fico and Fido, well, it
doesn't matter what their names are. If you had two dogs with each other, if
they what does that mean if they were in the same area? Okay, they
hypothetically fetch each other forever. No, no, that's called Fido's paradox and
you've proven it to be false. Really? But if you had a cat and a dog, the cat could put
a ball on the counter top and the cat would swat it off and it was a bouncy ball so it
could go down like maybe you got a railway style apartment, you go down the hallway,
the dog could bring it back to the, well then the dog would have to put the ball back on
the counter top. Well then you put peanut butter on the counter, easy. Yeah. I've been
watching. Peanut butter is the name of the cat though. Oh well that doesn't change too
much. Yeah, it's kind of the same. It doesn't affect anything. I've been
watching a bunch of videos of people having pet. What am I doing?
Now you, sorry, hold on. Let me think about. You've been watching videos? I've
been watching videos. Let me try this one more time. You just chill on me. I've
been watching videos of people who have pet raccoons. Oh yeah, me too. Really?
Yeah. The, well, there's the people with the pet raccoons, the pet raccoons
like open up like the bathrooms and the bathroom door and stuff. Because they're
they open the sink and then yeah. They have monkey hands. They have opposable thumbs.
And then there's the guy who feeds like, what is he fed 200 hot dogs to a bunch of raccoons
that live in his backyard. I didn't see that one. That one's good. He sits in a chair and
is holding like a Kirkland signature thing of hot dogs. Here you go. It made me wonder
why we. That raccoon on the Instagram account called raccoon Obama. Why have we not fully
domesticated the raccoon. People are trying to it's like the skunk where it's
too much of a hassle, but a rat, but it's not because a skunk has a bomb,
but we're going to make ten hundred different dogs that can look like
raccoons are like smarter than dogs. They're like somewhere between a dog
and a cat. Kind of they can be. I don't think you want a smarter one. What
like part like our raccoons like a type of like I want to play. Are they part
of the canid family? Are they part of like the feline? I think if I had to
guess I would say they're a mustelid.
A mustelid?
But that's a complete guess. Those are weasels and that type of thing.
Oh that makes sense. Yeah but you could have a weasel and a ferret as a pet. I heard that
ferrets are disgusting to own.
Ferrets are mean and horrible and disgusting and they kill themselves.
And they jump.
Yeah.
I hate jumpers.
They're snakes. They're part of the snake family.
I want to pet a mongoose.
No you don't.
I don't really even know what a mongoose is.
Mongoose are snake eaters.
I know, I've seen videos of mongoose do stuff.
know what kind of mongoose I want? The bicycle that I had as a kid.
It's a terrible bike. It is. It's the worst. Yeah, those are not good. Yeah.
But a raccoon you can like, they really are just like little monkeys, but they're
cheaper than monkeys. And they're not as dangerous because they can be, I don't
even think they have claws. I think they just have hands. I saw this video of this
guy. He's got a pet raccoon and it's somebody filming him. He's like at a
Dollar General or something. And he's holding onto the raccoon by its scruff.
and then he goes, "Watch this," puts it down
and then runs away and the raccoon runs towards him.
Then he walks back to the car and the raccoon
is like right behind him, like his companion,
like his follower.
- Are raccoons more like predisposed to rabies
or is it just 'cause they're a wild animal?
- I think it's just 'cause they're a wild animal.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
I don't think they can just get it from chilling out.
- Yeah.
How does an animal get, it's only if you just get bitten
by something with rabies still?
Or what's the original source?
Yeah, I don't know, but I think I think it's just you got to be bitten. Yeah, I
am scratched or whatever some shit like that. I found out yesterday that mad cow
disease. It comes from
they were feeding cows. Yeah, yeah, pre on disease. Oh, it's the same thing as
like as Kuru. Yeah, yeah, it's cow Kuru and you love. You didn't know that you
talk. I didn't know that's how they I knew it was a pre on disease, but I
thought that it was I thought it was a pre on disease in humans. He's a
obsessed with eating it, but it's originally when's the last time I said
the word Kuru. I only know I only know about it because of you one okay, and I
think we've talked about it multiple times and that makes me obsessed great
okay. So he wants now is so bad now it's completely abnormal for a doctor to know
about diseases. You didn't scared now you're talking about getting given
people Kuru and talk about giving you dry firing this gun. Yeah, I'm not
shooting at his gun at anybody dry firing a revolver at me and talking about
who don't know what you're. I think he's a mad doctor. I think that your new
name is big iron.
That's what I'll call you from now on big iron yeah. That'd be cool. What if
he puts the gun away? He's still but he still had it yeah. That's true. Yeah,
you know just because Batman takes the mask off doesn't well yeah. I become
the first one. Okay, well
there could have been a better example. I just not that smart just a nickname
just basically just because Michael Phelps gets out of the pool. Don't make
him not Michael Phelps. Don't make him a swimmer or he is. Don't not make him a
swimmer. Don't yeah,
yeah,
that's a good one. That's a good
turn. Crazy that any any mad chef could sprinkle brain into your food and give
you a day is crazy. If you do die, if you eat brain, well, if you're a human
brain, you could get a pre on disease. It's very unsafe. That's why it's not
safe to eat human flesh is because all the diseases in human flesh or human
disease. Yeah, because most humans eat like Twizzlers and stuff and I've been
saying it's more because I've been saying it. Y'all the same shit. Wash
your brain. Yeah, wash your brain before you wash the brain and these these
people take not seasoning. If you're eating brain, you need to wash that shit
you know, wash soap with soap. Get the get the Kuru out of that scrub. You get
the scrub brush. Didn't somebody do the temple of doom monkey brain thing in
real life. No, I was watching a movie. Never mind the temple of doom. Yeah, he
was watching temple of doom debunked. No, it's from that movie faces of death.
Oh yeah, I don't I have no interest in eating a brain. Yeah, I don't think
brain looks like the worst thing to eat.
It can't be good. I mean, it looks like it looks like anything that grows in a
body and looks like a vegetable. I don't want to eat that. You think a brain
looks like cauliflower. It looks like cauliflower. I don't want that. I
especially when you cut it. I feel like the texture is probably just gross.
Yeah, probably jello-ish. Yeah, I feel like it's... No, because I feel like... I
was going to say it's probably like eating an eel, but I feel like... I mean,
British people eat eels all the time. I've eaten... Is a nerve microscopic?
Yes. I don't know. 'Cause a brain is just a bunch of nerves, right? So would
it be like stringy? I don't think it's stringy. A brain is just a bunch of
nerds, the smartest part of the body. A nerd is a bunch of brains. Yep, you
I mean, that's what I meant. Oh, a brief history of people eating brain that
actually looks kind of good, though, because it's got fried KFC seasoning on
yeah. I guess I would eat. I guess I would eat a fried eat that brain
nuggets. Yeah, I mean, I'd eat anything in a nugget. Yeah, they're probably
probably you probably do eat. My God, thinking about eating it out of
somebody's head. That doesn't sound very good. That is the scariest thing I've
ever seen in my life. A brain eating a burger. Yes. Why
think
look up what I want to buy this in it like it's called 16 by 20 printed it's
called in my home go up eat delicious fast-food burger human brain by Roger
stuck holy crap Roger I am so it's all burger eating type yeah what else does
Roger stuck have on here probably all burger stuff I hope it's all burger
stuff are we not even showing this is a picture that just says hello well it's
not even it doesn't matter to see his portfolio oh yeah oh it is a lot of
got fast food stuff. Oh, fast food consumption. Oh God, that burger looks
too juicy. Is this fetish material? The burger, the seeds are flying off the
sesame bun. What are you doing? Eating a burger so vigorously that the seeds fly
off. God damn, that's insane. The seeds go everywhere. Oh my God, this one is
supposed to be Trump. A massive man in a suit and red tie screams. That's
definitely Trump. Guys, DeSantis is finished. Yeah, is he done? Is that Hungry
video. We already talked about it on the very last episode. Yeah, so we talked
about it and then, but since then, his approval rating has plummeted. It's
plummeted. It's been plummeting, man. It's sad because I thought we were about
to see, well, it's not that sad because... I thought politics was above this,
to be honest. Above, above, like, just the most base,
pointless ad hominem, just dragging people down for videos that aren't even
hate your dragging people through the mud. I hate that you're saying you
mean campaigns. You know we move past this as a civilization. You're saying
you think people are opposed to things that are base. Meanwhile, everyone is
calling people like De Santis and Trump. They're saying based when nobody is
anymore. The no one's talking about it anymore, but they're using the word
crazy cringe. I now it is cringe nowadays. Nowadays base is good.
I tried listening to an interview with RFK Jr. I'd never heard him really talk that much
before. Does he talk like a Kennedy? No. Really? No. He has some fucked up voice. He's like
"I'm a J.D." He's got the worst voice I've ever heard in my life. I don't care. I don't
know anything about his policies. I don't know what he believes. He truly cannot be
the president. There's no way that anybody would ever take anyone seriously who's like
happy. I don't think there's any risk of anyone taking him seriously. Even
he doesn't even have that fucked up stupid Kennedy voice that everyone
loves. He stole Cheryl Hines from Larry David
in
is going to be so remember that Cheryl Hines was rightfully Larry David's wife
based on the TV show. They should have been married in real life. He owned her.
he only you're like you are doing a job as a wife. The man gets first right of
first refusal and absolutely to anybody you want to marry and that's keep
talking about this and keep pointing the gun at the camp and if you are playing a
wife in a movie during the day, you can't divorce him when you go home at
night. You're still the wife. Yep, yep, yep, yep, until that movie wraps, you're
so I and if you're playing a husband,
you can have a second job where you're not the husband and turn that shit
sideways and that job can be sitting on the couch and watching your shows.
Yep, and if I'm ever as a new actor, if I am ever in some kind of role where
I have a wife, she is making me all sorts of delicious meals. You are making
me crème brûlée and when I need an Epsom salt bath, guess who's drawing
huh my wife. If you're my wife and when I need an Epson printer ink cartridge
type sixty seven guess who's retrieving that is going to staples because I
don't want to talk to the lady who works at the weird ink kiosk. I think
she has a crush on me yeah and I don't want to see her again and you're my
wife you and you know you know I am easily tempted. You don't know how I
know. I have a temptation. You know how I am. You know that that if the
the staple, the ink lady at staples. If she looks at me and says I'm going to
fold, I'm going to make an ink down here and I need you to clean it up. I'm
going to go to the back room of staples. You got to get you got to be not even
see a girl and a reflection of glass. I have to kill myself. Yeah, I'll fuck a
man again. I'll fuck a man again again. No yeah, I will. I'll fuck him. I don't
please me. If you don't go back to being gay, that's so funny. That's that's an
ultimatum in the in the sixties. That was a definitely an ultimatum or threat in
the sixties for show is if you don't if you if you don't be my good wife, then
I'm going to I'm going back to the old me. I'm going back to the old me. I'm
switching it up on him. I'm going to show the world. I'm reversing all of that
conversion therapy. Yeah, I'm converting the conversion. Should we make a
documentary where we all go through conversion therapy and see what happens
to us? Yeah, like yeah, just for fun. I mean for for a document, journalism,
yeah, but if you think journalism is fun now, then you've obviously never been a
journalist. But that that would just be that would just be a documentary of us
where we like go into the clockwork orange room where they're showing us
porn. They don't show you porn in conversion. There they show you God.
yeah, they show you God yeah. The whole thing is that you with electrical
impulse. Oh, they show you gay porn and then zap you. I think yeah, they show
I think that's probably what it is.
That's how I would design it. If I was the guy, you know, I'm realizing now that
I genuinely did believe that that was I think that I don't know you gave that
was part of conversion. I think I don't think they zap you as a punishment. I
think they try to zap your brain. I think they do like the electroshock
shock therapy type of thing. It is terrible. Oh, I thought that's what
electroshock therapy was. Was they show you gays to affect your brain chemical?
They do that for people with like severe depression and stuff. They use magnets
and electricity. It's like a type of... Oh wait, magnets isn't... Magnets is
electroshock therapy? No, it's... I've heard about the magnets before. I think
it's two different things. But it could... But magnetism, get this, science, blow
your mind, magnetism is electricity. I said that too. Oh God. It's the same thing.
It's the same. That's technical. So when you people say electro shock therapy,
they're kind of I don't know. I have no idea. Okay. I know that. I would imagine
I would imagine a big deal. I would imagine it's not magnet because they say
shock. Big iron is saying it's really, it's really not a point. He's pointing
it at himself. What's wrong with that? He's been talking about conversion
therapy and pointing the gun at himself. I'm excited. Right. It doesn't make you
want to die hearing about what they do to these fucking people. I don't. I was
I was just focused on you pointing that right. You can't even think about it.
No, no, I need to get converted to you need to let a big iron worry about big
iron. You need to be big
headphones right now. Okay, and you need to listen because I'm telling you I'm
giving you some
yo big
we I've definitely caught so many big headphones before. It was a walking
around with those big head. Get some ear plugs or ear buds.
you got these big headphones walking around with these big headphones? I know
Lou Reed got shock therapy because he was a little gay. Just a little bit?
That's what it said on his Wikipedia. It said he was a little bit gay? Honestly, he probably
he probably did that on purpose to himself to seem more rock and roll.
That's true. What's more rock and roll than getting electrified? Yeah. Yeah.
Getting electrified by your guitar. That's cool. Getting electrified by the
mic stand. I have shown you the video of Frankie Palmieri from Amir getting
been electrocuted by the you can get a oh I've been a
like
well, not to death. He's playing this dog and there it's like right before
break down and he goes like he's like screaming into the mic and then he goes
like this
goes completely stiff, like shake a die. No he was fine, but he fainted like and
then he like completely like wooden board falls over and the band keeps
like thirty seconds. Have you guys? I thought last night I first every time
we've you've corrected me on this before did Wayne static from static X die from
touching a microphone and it electrocuted him. No, he died from a
horrible life of drugs and sadness. Okay in
first you're thinking of his hair, but just sticks up
and his electric theme to be
you
you to correct me on it before, and I know that you did, but then we started
talking about this. I mean you look at him. You have to imagine he's yeah. Of
course, every time I touch yeah every time he touches that Mike stand his
hair. Let me yeah you you got you. You look at him from the from the forehead
up. You think oh my God, this guy he was a like you and he does and then you
look at the rest of his body. You're like oh no, it was he over to it was
producing on drugs.
Then they replaced him with a robot.
Have you all ever been electrified?
Yes.
Yeah, a little bit.
I, my science teacher in sixth grade taught us how to make a hot dog cooker, which was
a wooden plank, like a two by four, two carpenter screws, electrical tape, and then a frayed
wire.
And it was like, you just put the hot dog on the two, like, nails.
that is not a safe experiment to be doing with kids.
No, but then I touched it and I
shocked my fucking hand.
He told me not to touch it too. I touched plugs coming out of an
outlet before and that type of thing. Yeah. I once heard... Put your finger in the light bulb.
We had one. My dad had... I didn't do that. No, that's an actual way to
kill yourself in a cartoon. I did that by accident when I was younger.
Really? I was plugged in. Put your finger in the light bulb socket? That can't be
an accident. No, it wasn't an accident. That's not an accident at all. It was an
accident. Don't lie. I put my finger in to see what would happen like in the
cartoons when I was a young boy. That doesn't count as an accident. No. To see
what would happen is not an accident. Getting electrocuted, I will say,
getting electrocuted does feel kind of good to me. It doesn't feel like pain.
Yeah. It's this weird thing where you're shaking and you can't move. Yeah. But
until... It would feel nice if you could do it in a controlled way. Yeah, I do
kind of like it, like maybe you're watching some sort of porn. Yeah,
exactly. What's better than watching porn and getting electrocuted while you
do it? Damn, that actually sounds sick, but I did it. What my dad had a
outlet that was out of the it like had no cover on it, and it was just hanging
loose out of the wall, and it never really was a problem, but we never put
the three dollar cover on it, and then one time I was plugging in a laptop and
I didn't understand how it worked at all, and I grabbed the back of it.
Oh my God.
And plugged it.
And I just sat there like, "No!"
Like looking at it, and my brother was like, "Are you okay?"
And then I just let go and took a deep breath.
And I think that it changed me forever.
I almost, I'm pretty sure I almost started an electrical fire at our college, because
I remember I had that big gaming laptop.
I would lug everywhere, but I bought an aftermarket.
Wait, what?
Yeah, I had like that.
You lugged it everywhere?
Yeah, it was heavy.
It was really heavy. I remember this laptop. It was like this thick.
For a second, when you said laptop, my brain heard desktop.
Oh, no, no, no. But now I understand.
I had this aftermarket, like, because the charger,
I was like a broke college kid and I broke my charger somehow.
I bought this same charger off of like
fucking Panda Buy or something. It was like this
market like charger and every single time that I would plug it in, I would see like, I looked
at the plug one time and it was just all like chipped and I was like, "Oh, that's weird."
And I plugged it into the outlet at the library and I just heard like a "pfff."
I was like, "Oh, fuck."
You popped the outlet.
I popped the outlet, yeah.
Holy shit.
I would pop the outlet probably every other time that I plugged it in.
It was so fucked.
I don't like, I could have burned the whole library down.
shoot out of all my outlets all the time and shoot into my house and fly around.
Yeah. Wouldn't it suck if you go-- They shoot into my water that's on the ground.
You plug-- It's like, "Hey, buddy, that's my water."
You go to plug something in.
Knock that off. That's all my water on the ground. Stop putting your sparks in it.
You're not allowed to touch-- Don't touch my puddle, buddy.
That's my tons of puddles all around right at my feet where I sit at the couch.
That's my little oasis I made. That is the dream setup. Oh, my God.
Water on the floor.
a ripped up lazy boy with a giant puddle
all around it.
With a spring coming out the back.
Yeah, and a wire that's hanging from the ceiling
and just like one inch away from just touching the water.
I love leaving water on the floor.
Yeah, me too.
I spilled some water on the floor.
Oh, watch out, I spilled some water on the floor right there.
I've never ever wiped up water.
It goes away.
You don't wipe up anything.
You don't wipe up coffee or soda or anything.
There's stains everywhere here.
all the stains on this table are from you. Yeah, that's because I didn't do
that. It was about to be a stain. I wiped it during an episode, but that's
because our old table was covered in sugar. Yeah, sugar, as you drink your
sugary drinks. I don't have any. I was always zero sugar coffee. Okay, you're
synthetic. We should be destroyed big iron. It's time for you to turn in your
gun. I don't think so. Imagine you go to plug something into an outlet, though.
It sparks up right. You're plugging your computer and I'm like, damn, I light a
one
Water guy comes out of the outlet and he has all the data from your computer.
Wait, why?
Because you plug your computer in the outlet, it's sparked up, hit the puddle, it comes
up.
And the reason that water guy comes out of the outlet is because I have a bunch of data
about water guy from my old group chats in my computer?
Yes.
And that comes to life?
Uh huh.
What if you talked shit about water guy?
I never have talked shit about water guy.
No, but your boy talks shit about water guy.
Nobody talked, I promise you, nobody talked shit about water guy.
you guys have a group chat where you guys just talk shit about me all the time.
No, we touch it about water guy. He doesn't know, but there's I'm not
entertaining anything, any lies about the water guy situation.
No, see I'm not. I'm why I don't water guy is a code for somebody here. It's
not even true. That's not true. I would not be water guy. I would be the red
pig.
you text each other when you're lit. It was like the red pig is landing at the
nest
is in the for
the red pig is thirty minutes late to the barn. I don't know why I say you
look like a pig all the
really right now I'm red because I have sat in a blood that's blue rushing
blood is said blood is rushing to my head to block the tears.
I don't look like a pig and I'm not that right. You're a to have a to have a more
pig ish pig ish to have a
you can't be mad when I say pig pig ish pigly. It's so funny to have a have a
code name for one person be like yeah yeah, we're we're going to hang up
hang out with Alex and Joe and the red pig.
no,
I'm not the
we're all getting new nicknames today, big iron red,
I okay if it's a nickname, I'll take it because I do like having a nickname.
I don't know if I like the red pig that much I'd rather go by a Mike. It's so
funny. We can't do middle. I know we can't do middle names because we have
the same middle name yeah, but I can be Mike, though. No, you can't. We can't.
what if I did what if I did a late twenties shift from where I do the
little kid thing and I start going by my middle name? Yes,
I can't tell I can't. That's a good that's good. Yeah, see Michael Pit.
That is pretty good. Thomas Howell, though, I don't know who that's
completely copy Thomas Howell is I can't. I can't fully tell this, but I
was thinking of you'll understand when I say this, but I was thinking of
changing my last name when I get married and you think about what my
name would be and that would be pretty funny. Wouldn't it? I would be funny
yeah, wouldn't that be a pretty funny thing to have that name?
Actually, yeah, I did. I don't think that I think that you're I don't want to
say it, but I did text your fiancee. Well, a photo of you on said last night.
How did I find out about it?
She told
after I told her, I was going to her. She confronted you, huh? She confronted
you about your date with. She said, What the fuck is this? She did. She asked
I was there was it and then I said it was fun. She said, well, I know what you're
really doing.
I told her yeah, I like
I liked him.
You liked him. Did you like it was nothing? It was not nothing and I'm
ready to admit that
not going to lie to myself or to others. I think you might be taking this guy's
last name. What was his last name? You remember? I don't even remember his
first name. Yeah, oh shit. I'm going to guess his name just because he was on
set.
Mr. Movies. I really, maybe I might get, I might get, find, I might try and find his
name. You could ask, yeah, I might ask the AD. I'm probably gonna do that because I
think we should give him some work. Yeah, maybe he could just sit in as an extra
on the episodes. Yeah, that's what I was thinking. Yeah, I mean he would be a good
guest. We're chopping it up. He would not be a good guest, man. He would not be a good guest.
I think a pad are going to have a mom on your vacation. Yeah, that would be
that I was actually a good idea. You guys are both gone at the same time
right. You guys are both going to be leaving me alone. You're going to
abandon me soon at the same time. You're both abandoning. We're not
abandoning you. You're bending me, making me feel like shit. I don't know
if we're going to make I mean that's on you. I was I was thinking of doing an
episode where it's just me and two people from craigslist that I don't know,
but I don't know how to work the roadcaster.
I think I just don't.
Pretty easy to work.
I don't trust you as security to protect our equipment.
Yeah, that's true actually.
If random people come in.
I could get the two construction guys who helped the...
You want them to sit in the front?
That helped put the wall up.
Helps do their job?
You want them to be security or you want them to be on the show?
It's going to be me and those two guys on the show.
Oh, those guys are cool.
That's fine.
They're nice, yeah.
One of those guys told me he did a misty flip at Brooklyn Banks.
Oh yeah, one of them was a skater.
I remember he's a rollerblader. He said he did a misty. Holy. I don't know what a
misty misty flip is a five forty back when you turn into mist.
That constricts you guys that he did a five forty back flip on roller blade.
That is fucking awesome.
I was waiting for you guys to to come here one day and I was playing. What do
you even say that you just go like, oh, I did. Yeah, I was just like, oh, really?
Wow. What's he going to like, you know, I'm not going to challenge him on that.
That's the coolest thing I've ever heard. I really hope it's true. But I was
just playing session on the computer. I was waiting for you guys to come in here
one day when we like first had the whole place set up and he recognized the
Brooklyn Banks in the game and he was like, I did a misty flip there. That's so crazy.
It's so it's like I was like yeah. No you did man. I but I honestly I fully 100
have no choice but to believe this. Believe that you did that
Oh man.
We have no show to plug. I do. I have stuff to oh God. I have stand-up dates.
I guess I have I'm going to be in Austin. I'm going to be in Austin.
You remember when I was going out on the road and he would he would say that I
had to plug and I would say no no. No. Yeah, I was trying to help you out.
Yeah, I didn't. It's how did those shows sell? It's cringe, bro. It's cringe, bro. I hate
it too, but how did those shows sell? Don't sell any tickets for anything. How did those
shows sell? You're being so cringe right now. Just get like 10 people, 15 people in the
audience. That is all you need. Okay. It's based to have nobody show up. In the cave,
I'm going to do four. I'm doing four shows opening for Dan Licata. I'm going to put half
your body in a creek and half of it in a cave. Okay. And then I'm going to be at Pitbull's
this show on the twenty-sixth. You're just going to be at it. Just look. I
don't know this guy. I look at my Instagram stories. I got all my my shows
that I plug. You're plugging your Instagram now to follow me on Instagram.
So you tried to plug the poster for the show. Really? He said, and we have a
really nice poster.
That's funny. Wait, the poster for that poster. Okay, the poster, the poster for
you and the cottage show is very funny that it's Dan Lakata and you're opening
and you are the ninety percent. Yeah, well, yeah, but the poster that it's
parodying
is the CKY poster. So Dan is bam in that poster. You guys parodied a poster.
You're some crazy ass motherfucker. Y'all ripped off. You're gonna get
soon. We ripped off bam. I thought you were talking about the Pitbull poster
because I didn't see that. I don't even know what you're talking about. I'm
doing a show with Steven Vega, the Pitbull impersonator. Oh, okay. Reunited
Yeah, he's hosting a show that he's hosting a show with our friends Charlie Sosnick and Michael Kandel and
It's gonna be at house of yes. Oh
Nice, this is gonna be a really crazy show. Yeah
Kobo was saying last night we were doing like what's that thing called?
The knife game on the untitled knife game. Yeah, I don't knife hand knife game
But he was saying it'd be really like imagining a guy with a gun me. Let me show you oh
Yeah, shooting between is shooting between the fingers instead you do it. Then we'll get it. We'll get an insert
I know you didn't just try to touch this you try
Because it's gonna be you tried to try to touch the big iron
Don't do that man. That's like me touching your headphones or me touching your curly tail
Okay, bye.
Stop.
Now we'll edit that part out.
Oh, it's 101.
Yep, perfect timing.
(laughing)