This is my camera, right? Yeah. Hi
It's me Pierce friend of the show. I'm going on tour with Matthew Golden J Wine Garden and Brian Fitteman
We're gonna be in Pittsburgh, Detroit
Baltimore and
Brooklyn and Boston
Just go to link dot T link tree
Traveling with humor to find the dates in a city near you and
We have not we haven't sold enough tickets yet
it if you come all of these things will be yours.
And then blow out the candle.
Beautiful.
Okay, put the voice back on.
My favorite food is birthday cake.
Mmm.
Oh.
That's my favorite flavor.
[CHEWING]
Yum.
Mmm.
Oh.
[LAUGHTER]
Oh, it's good.
Mmm.
I actually like it.
Sandwich.
[LAUGHTER]
A nice smell.
and that's how you start the episode.
Yeah, yeah, it's Pierce week, Pio sweet. Oh yeah, that's right, two episodes in a
- I hope you're-- - Two episodes in a row.
That's how I do it.
I do a normal one and a premium one no matter where I go.
- This feels so weird being on this side of the table,
honestly.
- Do you wanna switch?
It was very generous of you to give me the seat
with the GoPro close up.
- Oh, I put the GoPro.
The GoPro's, actually it could be centered
and I don't know.
- Yeah, we can't see the video at all.
- I don't know.
I don't know anymore.
The setup is all, we have to change the setup.
We changed the camera angles.
- Yeah, we had-- - After we got our feedback.
Uh-huh. Useful feedback. Yeah. Thank you. Hey, you're helping facilitate that.
Man.
Are you guys gonna make a overhaul to the set? We will soon. Yeah. It's just a
matter of doing it. Yeah. Right. That's the only obstacle. That's really the
only thing on the to do list.
The problem with doing it is once you do it, the podcast is over because there's
nothing left on the to do list. There's not much else to do after that is there.
it gives you it gives us like something to look forward to and then once the set
is made, it's just like okay. Now it's just a fucking job new office after that
yeah, right, yeah, I have to get another new office. Yeah, it'll be nice to have
two offices at once. We did for a little bit. No, we didn't yeah. We did no. I
had two apartments at once.
That's no, I had two bathrooms actually way that goes. I always had no way. I
there's two pillows on my bed. When we were thinking of when we were moving
out of the first office, no, when I was moving into my apartment, I still had
like a month where I like I could move into my new place early and then like
where I could have to go off winds. If I wanted to, I had two apartments. It was
cool yeah. That is always cool. I had to apartment. I mean that's kind of the way
to do it, because if you go from one apartment to the other, then there's
that tricky period with no apartment, yeah, or almost even the scary period
where one day you have one and the next day you also have one, but it's
different yeah yeah. That is a scary moment. I don't like that when things
I guess I technically had to a man's too, but they were in different cities,
so I couldn't even go between them. He's a
damn
camera and I had that for twelve months.
Yeah, I had three years of having two apartments yeah in different cities.
Yeah, a summer apartment in Boston. That's really wag yeah. No, it's not
true to holidays. Yeah, it's true. You do get to fourth of July's to
Christmases. No, because there's a tree at both houses. That's actually okay.
There is two trees, two turkeys in both ovens. Oh my God, and it's
two turkeys in each oven, y'all, because you have to drive back and forth,
and it does take four hours each way.
Yeah.
sitting outside of the sitting outside of a restaurant and smelling that they
have turkey and like walking in like a dog, like a blood out my son waking up
my wife would be like mom. I hear Santa Claus, that's me out there.
Pleas
wrapped up to her.
Here's me walking around sniffing the ground
mystery pine needles. I wonder how many kids just smelled the smelled the cookie
plate was like this was like Dad's fingers.
The heck
yeah, the smartest kid in the world yeah, but the best knows really yeah. I mean
honestly the best part of the brain. No, the better your nose, the absolute
Jupiter you are. I think yeah, I guess that's probably true. Yeah, that means
you have like bloodhound characteristics, you have big floppy ears. My old
landlord, my old landlord with one tooth and long, greasy hair and a pot belly
that was like sixty pounds. Nanny McPhee. Yeah, Nanny McPhee vibes.
Former 300 pound heroin addict, this guy, legendary Pokemon type guy. He
would smell dead animals in the backyard because he would attract them. He would
feed pigeons with a big pigeon feeder every day, and then rats would die back
there all the time, because they try to get the pigeon feed and then they like
can't get out of the backyard or whatever, and so when you weren't, didn't
you have like a basement apartment that like had the backyard, so you were just
dealing with pigeons every single fucking day? Yeah, and he would go out
there and try to find rats, and he would literally just go,
"Where is that fucking rat? I smell it." And then he would knock on our door
and be like, "Hey, you wanna see how I find a rat?" He was like, "Watch me
find it.
It's over here somewhere.
I can't fucking find it."
I mean that that is smart, because what that is is that's a beautiful
deception where he's looking around, but he's acting like he's smelling.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, just looking to see if you can see a rat while also going
yeah,
it's like it's he's like trying to like make it look like he has like
heightened senses. Yeah, just like the like he's like oh my nose is so good
watch that is like a very easy bit to do if you're at home and you're not
funny. You can't make your relatives or your girlfriend laugh if you're looking
to the remote just like sniff while you're looking for it yeah. That's
it's easy laugh yeah echo location is funny to yeah. If you can click or
I'm making the sound the remote makes yeah, that's good. I'm acting like a
TV. I'm trying to learn the remote to me
just start reciting the office quote yeah, yeah, this is the same. This is
the same landlord that would make you
give give him your car yeah. He would borrow my car
you'd borrow my car in exchange for a hundred dollars off the right, he would
just go to the beach and shit. Well, he would just go to Manhattan to like
process his compost and then it would take him like a
composting
the back seat that he's driving like like what like in the past thirty
minutes yeah,
and then he would he would not pay for gas. He would come back with an empty
tank and then I would just be like. Can you please fill up the tank if you're
I drive the car and he was like that was never part of the air.
But yeah, he would drive my car all day and then he would come back and then he
would bring my car key up to his apartment. He lived on the top floor and
then I would message him. Could you please bring my keys to me and he would
say you'll come up and get him
and then one time I did go up to get him in the inside of his apartment was so
horrifying. He just had plastic bags filled of like rotting fruit that was
ready to go to the compost just nailed to the wall. Oh my God, just filthy
clothes all over the floor. Yeah, this guy definitely has a strong sense of
smell. He really does yeah, he's training, he's training his nose. That's
why he has the bags on the wall right. There's no better way to train your
nose than to completely obliterate it. Yeah, I would run your if you're a
hungry junkie so much sense around you that when you go outside and there's
like no gross smells, it's like yeah, it's a hundred percent drop in the
weights. You're talking about this on monster crazy. How I think it's so
ridiculous that human beings just can't turn themselves into dogs by
concentrating, but I think if you're a hair a fat heroin addict, that means
that you have transformed into a dog. You just walk around and you eat
everything all the time, just smelling around, just smelling around like a
junkyard dog. Yeah, yeah, I remember you like
this guy is so I'm so fascinated by this old landlord. I just remember this one
time you were telling me that like he
they like arguing with them news like you hurt my feel.
Oh yeah, I told him hey man you're kind of hurting my feel because our place
flooded and then he starts yelling at me that I'm weird and I was like look man
you're kind of hurting my feelings. I think you should leave and he goes you
hurt my feelings, tell me that the apartment flooded when it never has
this is the first time it's flooded. So you you hurt my feelings.
That's the go to tag.
yeah
because I told him that the place
just anybody pulling that oh yeah. Well, you're hurting my
you're hurting my you're asking him like hey man like yeah, there's like like I
lost like my x box or whatever, like there's so much water in my apartment.
It's like
you would always cry. It was so or if I man you just talk to me and just like
oh, I got an annulment for my wife, which is good. Listen to me. You want an
annulment, but oh my God, her mother, her mother made the best spaghetti. I
miss it so much. That is the
keystone phrase for a guy like that is, but oh my God, my God, God yeah talking
about your ex wife's mother's spaghetti.
Man, yeah,
well,
so I'm fleeing the country. You're fleeing the country, yeah. Oh yeah,
you're going to Ireland. Yeah, I'm fleeing the country and leaving. Maybe
the most jealous I've ever been of you. Yeah, you've drawn his iron. Iron,
yeah. Ironically, when I land there, he'll be filled with iron. Yeah, when
you land there, St. Patrick's gonna chase you out. No, dude. Fucking snake.
no, no, no, don't land in Ireland at four AM or what you want to get stuck in
that you stuck in a wepacon
stuck in a pot of wepacon gold,
which actually sounds kind of good. I visited Ireland at three AM and became a
saint. Wow, that is so slick, a camera there, a saint Cameron, probably Google
it. Maybe there may be a saint Cameron. That sounds like that seems like there
probably would be yeah. That seems like I wonder. I wonder if there's saints for
all of us there at there is a Cameron or camera Cameronis. Oh was murdered in
three or three under three or three three or three. Is he Roman? What's
going on? Does it say anything about the Saint? Can you click who was Saint
Cameron there on the info box? He was a Scottish nobleman, so this is a
nobleman. No, that's a musician.
Well, he sings the Hussie. This is pretty uninteresting. Unfortunately,
yeah, yeah, even a single quality given to the same. He has no animal
super power. He was Scottish. Yeah, he didn't even chase any snakes away or
anything.
Oh well, yeah, but that's okay. I'll just become the new Saint Cameron. I'll
come up with a good thing to be a sense of well, then what's your what's going
to be your thing when you go over there and you Saint of intelligence? Yeah,
yeah, that's good. Saint of concentration,
the saint of sitting still. You see you're sitting on one of those like
cobblestone fences they have over there, just doing this with your mind.
You're the same. I'm going to get a painting done of me when I'm there.
Yeah, nice. I think I'll get a painting done every day, like an oil painting
every day. Yeah, I'm thinking I'm going to do that because there must be
people around to do that. You can probably just walk into a pub and get
somebody to do a painting of you and you can get a pie if you're American
enough things and paintings. I bet that's what they have instead of the
wine night, the wine paint by numbers nights they do for moms.
It's the same thing but with beer and men.
Yeah.
Yeah, and you're painting boobs.
With ale.
You're painting boobs.
You're painting big old tits.
And rugby balls.
And portraits of landed gentry.
Yeah.
[Laughter]
The two best things.
Landed gentry, that's like,
that's like,
like how Christopher Guest is like a member of the royal family.
Landed gentry means you're the upper class and you own land.
Oh, okay.
That's, I didn't know that.
Yeah, well it's landed, I think, I mean, I think so.
it's what they call. Well, he technically is technically a landed gentry. It
means to be Irish, because there's so much less land over there, and if you
own any land at all, you're considered a billionaire. Yeah, everyone there is
basically Elon Musk, who owns land totally so many so many of the Irish
working class are getting pushed off the cliffs because there's literally
they're running out of way. You can't walk here. That's my land. Yeah, it's an
Irish accent. You can't walk. You can't touch my land. You can't touch my land.
yeah, you've got to five feet on my line.
That's pretty good. How's that you sound like Liam Neeson and I was doing the
demo man voice right yeah. There's no Irish team Fortress to mercenary. There
will be soon. They're going to add it to the expansion bag yeah. They already
added. They added a Chinese Irish guy. You've heard of a black Scottish guy.
Wow right yeah, this and what would his ability be? What is his weapon? What's
is a skill. What's a skill class, the only member of the TF two team with
melee weapons. Wow, besides only melee weapons, nope he's they're going to
remove the frying pan, the fists and he's going to be able to use them all.
Wow, I heard that he's going to be the only one that when you kill when you get
killed by him, it forces you to log out of the game. That's his ability. He has
no weapons, but if he does kill you, it deletes your account. You lose all your
hats. Oh my God, he steals your hats. I used to be so obsessed with the there
was like a
community made tenth
fighter that was going to be the guard dog. Do you guys ever look at this? The
guard dog up? I was definitely obsessed with this type of thing. Yeah, me too.
He he had ninety five HP and he would run around and he had two big galling
turrets on his back. Was he a dog? He was a literal dog and he could bite you and
he could shoot you with the galling guns and he could piss on you, which was the
time attack is the Gerati attack that sniper has, but he could fill up the
Gerati sniper attack with his piss. Nice pretty cool yeah, that's not a bad. I
would add that he was small. I don't know how that would work in the source
and
he can't he can't jump over any. Let he can't go upstairs or anything yeah, I
don't think it would maybe there's a mechanic where he gets too scared. If he
goes too far away, oh my God, yeah, because they got fireworks and stuff
true yeah and all the explosions, the explosions force your character to run
away
the coward. That's the
scary coward. I was talking to Brian last night about how scaredy cat is not
it's like a misnomer. A scared cat will just leave the room and not fuck with
you, but a scared dog like this is what a scared dog does.
a complete scared. That's like you're freaking out you're going to kill
some they show their teeth at you. They go like yeah.
They also just they run in circles and stuff yeah.
It's so weird. Why wouldn't you just like leave? That is so funny yeah.
Their eyes are really wide and they stick all day
and then also I'm going to bite you is such a strange fury action yeah yeah
what what stupid animal. I mean if right, because if if some kind of if
okay, say that an alien is coming to me right and I wouldn't want the alien.
No, I was scared right. Do they know fear? Yeah, aliens, yeah, yeah, they
know they know fear. They have well, they know fear. If I go like this,
what do they think that's like? What if they think that's a greeting or like a
mating? These are aliens from earth, okay, so they know all the same.
All right, the ones from under the ocean, so the they actually know all
the stuff that animals do the atlantis actually. They would even know that when
the chimpanzee shows its teeth. It's not smiling. They would know that too okay,
because they made they made them that see that's another stupid fear reaction.
My smile yep yeah jing jing smiling supposed to be happy when you smile yeah
chuckle scared animals, no happiness. I think every animal is more happiness
than as the other animal. See that some of these monkeys do look scared. I
don't know why doing that because it's scared.
they're scared of being a stock photo when they're really angry. They do
kind of
so weird. I try to look up things like this sometimes, like monkey with
painted nails. Yeah, this is one of the first clip art things that I've ever
seen of a monkey with painted nails. I feel like it's a pretty rare
monkey with tattoos monkey with piercings and monkey with painted nails.
Sometimes I look those up, but there's a really good picture of a monkey with
facial piercings in a Mohawk. Whoa,
that's
yeah, but this is going to be
to use of monkey. That first one is kind of dope. Yeah,
actually, what's cool? Look at monkey finds peace after a
lifetime of suffering monkey piercings Mohawk. That's such a
crazy headline. Yeah, it's a chimp with Mohawk, but it's so
good. I bet it'll come up. Yeah, that guy.
It's so swag. So it's got gauges to
It looks like it works a damn hot topic monkey see monkey do get pierced today
We don't have a Facebook account. That's too bad. We should get a Facebook account for the podcast
It should be named to Caleb Cameron Patrick
That's a good idea and everyone can write on our wall and say happy birthday to us
And poke us. Do they still do poke?
Poke to every other social network. Yeah. Yeah, you didn't a poke war. Yeah
I thought that there was something recently that was like you can shake some
someone
you can grip or shake someone or so that's what they should now. Once we get
once we get all the implants and whatever all our chips in our fiber
optic contact, yeah, or whatever you know it's got an X chip yeah, the
vaccine fuck me with Elon Musk and but that's that that's what they should
bring back poking and they should make it have haptic feedback. So when someone
pokes you, it shakes your entire body. Yeah, you can feel it physically when
someone pokes you
right in your belly, but yeah, I like in your belly, but
that's your you're at work. You're like a barista or something yeah. You just
say
you're pretty, whatever, whatever I was the guy. I would love to be able to
poke a barista from far away
and then you're trying to voice message to whisper into their ear and say I
need more coffee.
You're my girlfriend.
You could yeah. You could put in a series of pokes on the back of their
older and then a whisper sound yeah. I would love to change my relationship
status with a barista yeah using have to
imagine how horrifying it would be to see if you're working as a barista and
you had your your ex contact lenses, glasses in and you and you just see a
little on your hud. You see a little notification that pops up and it says
anonymous has changed his relationship status to include you and as a picture
your face and then you look over and you're saying across the room, you
just wave and then there's a bunch of pokes that happen after a bunch of
pokes. Hey, then the whispers are like you're my girlfriend, my girlfriend,
then the periscope like start yeah, yeah, everyone in the everyone in the
coffee shop is approving
all their love. It would be so funny. If you get the X contacts lenses, it's
just crap with people like
instead of cat calling just beautiful women can't see because there's to
another accident today. I walked in a traffic was blinded by like it by too
many likes. It would be so incredible if you could set your if you could set it
like your status to be like a bit moji type thing, but it's like when someone
looks at you like on the street or something and you have the thing and it
just shows over your face the expression of the status. You want to walk down
the street, you're looking everyone and most people have like a smile on some
people have like doing a funny face. Yeah, some people are sad yeah, some
people have their heads blown or like a text status that comes up above their
head. That would be incredible to be able to do. Yeah, it's happening sooner
than you think it probably happened right now. Yeah, it's already in trials.
It's dark future that's ahead of us. Google glass was supposed to be like
that, right? Google s was supposed to be like that. And then it was. I mean,
nobody, I don't think anyone has one. I think it was mostly for taking videos
and pictures without using your hands. Yeah. What everyone always says is that
all these things that yeah they failed because they look ugly yeah, but I feel
like that can't be true because I
have to be there has to be a line that you cross where it's like okay. This is
this technology is insane enough that I'll wear it even it's ugly, but Google
Glass wasn't even like that. It was just like a like a bar with a little thing.
I think yeah there was a promo where it was like if you focus on something for
three seconds, then it does that it's like clicking on it. So, like if you
wanted to take a picture, you would go like this and then the camera would be
like today, and then if you wanted to look at a calculator app, you would go
like this and then you would pick each number
to a genius. So wait, I can figure this out. Let me think about this one
hundred yeah
one hundred that's one zero
equals.
do you think you think like you could maybe buy a Google glass on ebane like
now right they think they don't ever made it. I don't think they ever made a
prayer eyes. Also, I thought they had them because I think people were getting
like bullied for where I think they remember reading a news story that
people were getting bullied in the streets of San Francisco for wearing
Google glass. I feel see I think that that I'm saying that has to be the
thing where that can't be true. That has to be a thing that people like to say
you only feature of these is that they automatically dial nine one one when
your head is dipped into a toilet.
Oh yeah, you could actually well. So what I'm thinking right is like because
your eyes moved all the time all over the place. Unconsciously, you have the
cicadas or whatever, we're looking back and forth constantly. So what you I
mean, I guess you have to focus on something for a certain amount of, but
I'm imagining like it's constantly imagine you're opening up a pedia
version of the the Google glass version of the DJ academics computer glitch
where everything all the programs are opening and the screen readers going to
stuff. Just that happening in your real life world. You have to blink to close
yeah. You actually looked at something for too long and your entire world
starts going to
what's the DJ academics computer. You haven't seen that video. Pull it up. I
actually I need to see this really. This is the best video of all time.
He got like a got a virus or no. He spilled something on his keyboard. Oh
Jesus. Well, Pierce's Secret Service call came up on podcast about this
highlights. I don't even know what that is. That's when I talked about getting
call right now.
Mike, come on, you got this.
Oh, my.
I love how he has no idea that it's
it's so incredible.
Just wait.
What the fuck?
*laughter*
Yeah, I don't know what the fuck this is.
Holy shit!
What happened? He spilled something on his computer?
He said...
How the fuck does that happen?
What the fuck?
*laughter*
Exiting Nereus.
like
imagine this this happening to your to your real world,
yeah,
it's so fucking just in because you know, because you know, holy you, they have to
have a zoom function on the Google glass or else, yeah, that's the point of
having something like that yeah, so it could do that yeah, just accidentally
clicking so many click bait things, because you go out in the rain and yeah
the rain hits your glasses and that's our gun. Yeah, everything I think maybe
maybe one of the ideas was to click by blinking, but then you blink on
no way to actually verify that you want to advance. There's no way, because if
you look at something too long, then you're just your human attention is just
a click, and if you blink, then your brain is a click. They had those
snapchat glasses.
No, they just Google glasses. No, they were just like glasses that were they
like Ray-Bans, like Wayfarers that had like little cameras on each side.
And I think they were like 360 cameras, but that was like a whole thing.
It was like snap lens or something. And you could, uh, like tap,
like the side of it. If you wanted to like show your POV,
it would automatically like add it to your snap story.
But like the whole,
I think the whole problem with the snap glasses was that every single person was
was using them for like up skirting or just like going to the be definitely
just like
doing that. The thing is that there's no there's literally zero function at all
that that you need glasses like that for because you have a phone already yeah.
The only reason yeah, the only reason you would get them is if you're up to
something nefarious yeah yeah. I mean what are you doing on the app for
children?
What are you doing on the africa? I mean even on the like new like the apple
ones that they're making or whatever the vision. What are you going to do?
You're going to put a dragon on the train that
you're going to watch a video that's overlaid over a guy's face yeah. What
that is possibly needs to be a dragon on the train right now
talking to fuck
aren't the apple vision, though those can't leave the home right. They have
stay plugged in the know they can't they they don't need to stay plugged into the
wall, but what they do need to stay plugged into your pocket. They have a
battery pack that you like clip really about that as a cable that runs that
show for a big ass battery. A big cancer emitter that goes right on your test.
It's so crazy, it's whack yeah, well that's another vision of the dark
future yeah, but speaking of this, speaking of the dark future and the
dystopia, we have a dark. Yeah, do you want to introduce what this is so okay?
How do I introduce this? Because it is part of the shareholders meeting.
Today we're joining the Illuminati. I just wanted to tell you about this guy you found.
So yesterday for the shareholders meeting, I didn't know what to do.
And I was on Facebook. I was messaging all these different groups that I'm already in.
And you know how they like Cameron talked about the new feature that they have that every
single like community on Facebook now has its own group.
Right.
And I mean how it should have always been.
Yeah.
I'm in all these groups, you know, like the Ascension Fifth Dimension.
I mean, it's like like I found one that was like buy and sell underwear retail or something.
I'm trying to get information out of them.
I was going to the big the big thing, though, the big news drop I want to get before we
you. Oh yeah, that's right. There's some that well there's yeah, but there's some
huge news about what's going on on Facebook groups right now and all the
community chats and stuff right now. I'm really sorry to say that anybody who's
fan a fan of this group, the exo politics Israel Facebook group has been
completely, which is about that's about that means UFO politics Israel. It's
been completely taken over by by bots selling shoes, so I get a notification
every day. There's ten new posts. They're like these shoes are so comfortable, and
really scroll through is just all shoe like videos of shoes and then there's
like one guy mixed in that's right, just posting videos of aliens and stuff.
Yeah, the kidney stone understanding and supporting group got completely
overhauled by Snoopy shirts, but it was about Snoopy being a stone former. Oh
wow, that's crazy. Yeah, it says you can't hurt me. I'm a stone for
but then I found this one group and I didn't think that they were going to
reply. I honest
it was a group on Facebook called Illuminati Dark Brotherhood, and I got a
response almost immediately
from
I guess one of I mean the master can only contact you on whatsapp yeah, the
master rodney. So yeah, rodney, the leader of the Illuminati is named
rodney bruce
and he only communicates through whatsapp. You can't speak to him over
Facebook. No, I tried to I tried to really hard. I was I was saying only
contact you over. I was saying I have a problem with WhatsApp. I was just banned
because of the really not so voice number. No, he's not sympathetic at all.
He's you if you want to talk to the Illuminati master, you need to talk to
him on WhatsApp, right? Which so me and Patrick already have done so we've
already done. We've already entered the Illuminati. We're already in the
Illuminati. Now it's time for Pierce to join. I know Pat showed some of his
his conversation in the shareholders meeting. If you want to see that, you can
upgrade your tier and look at that. But I have some screenshots of just so you
know what to expect. Yeah. Yeah. Why don't we pull these up right now?
So this is me. So first I just tried to call him out right before I sent a text.
He wouldn't pick up. I said, "Sir, pick up. You joined my friend, Patrick Caleb
Fetter." That's what Patrick said his name was. Nice. "Into your organization."
He said, "How are you?" I said, "I'm good, my friend." He said, "Yada yada." I said,
"Does the health care plan cover prion diseases such as Kuru?" He said, "Yes,
my son. I said, "Thank you, Master." He said, "You're welcome."
Oh, yeah. I was trying to join the Illuminati for the healthcare.
Yeah, we were talking a lot about healthcare with Tim.
Because SAG is on strike.
So then I tried to ask him, "Is Barbie or Oppenheimer better, Master?" And he just responded
by sending the form I have to fill out, which I did eventually fill out. But basically,
the point here is that I just kept asking him over and over, "Master, do you know
Barbenheimer? Master, are you familiar with Barbenheimer?" He completely refused to respond.
he would just ignore me. He would send dot dots until I filled all the form, so I
filled it out and I was able to actually get an answer about Barbenheimer
eventually. Oh yeah, I asked if I could fill out the form over the phone,
because my phone was running low and he said no,
so he was still refusing to pick up here. I filled out the form here,
twenty one years old, male writer, you know, etcetera, etcetera. There's my
self, my initiation self, so that I said interesting thing.
and I had to take I had to take a video as well. That was like pledging my
allegiance to the Illuminati. Did he give you a script? Yeah, what was do you
remember what it was something like like the light or so I don't remember it
yeah, the light I'm going to go forward and backward into it or something or
out of the
I'm going to go backward and forward and like that yeah. So now Cameron, but he
never asked me to send videos. He only wanted me to send the selfies, which I
think I stunned. I think I think I served. I think you slayed. I think I
slayed
those are my and he said they were great. He said okay, my son, that's great. I
can I send that's he asked me if I was sure I said thank you, master. He also
asked me to send him a video of me writing down my desires. Well,
over a candle light, well, he didn't ask Cameron to do any of this. No, he
didn't, but I got some answers from well, I guess, because you probably
released the wheel for Cameron. He was like yeah, I did everything. I was also
kind of misdirecting him by asking about Barbenheimer a bunch of times. I think
he was kind of didn't was maybe a little annoyed with me yeah, you're just
trying to get you over with yeah
you know. He also eventually told me I asked which is better barbier
Oppenheimer and he said son. I can't reveal to you information. I can't
reveal this information until you join and then so I asked
past. Are you familiar with barb and I were master? He said yes, my son, why
are you so concerned about barb and Imer? I said Master, I need guidance on
which is better and he immediately said Barbie is better. It's so fucking
awesome and that was where I left the conversation great. So you got what you
needed from him yeah exactly. I got the guidance information yeah, the guidance
the Illuminati is on the side of Barbie team Barbie yeah, yes, you would think it
would be team up and I was expected, but it shows that the the nuclear bombs that
they want to drop or bad. Yeah true. All right, so let's pull up what's up here
and let's get
let's get this new account all signed up. Let's get Pierce into the Illuminati.
Do I have to do anything? No, no, I think we can do it up. We can we have
it all up on screen. I can just type here. Yeah, here we go. So okay, so
Pierce already started the conversation here. Yeah. What did you say here? Pierce?
You said, sir. Hello. I am hoping to join up. He says, how are you? He says,
I am calm, but alert. How are you? So now we have to fill out the form. Yeah,
So go ahead and copy and paste this into the text box for me, Julio, and then we can just
fill it out.
Yeah, we'll fill it out together.
All right, so number one, we gotta go full name.
And I'll control it from here, Julio, I got it.
All right, full name, we'll say maybe...
Pierce?
That's great.
Yeah, and then maybe we'll say maybe Pierce Pitts.
Yeah, Pierce Pitts is good.
Age?
What do you want to be?
Can I be 14?
I think maybe you have to go at least 21. Okay, let's do 64 then. Yeah, I'm just
worried that he won't he won't accept you. Okay, do do 26. Okay. Yeah, do
something sweet. 26 your sex. Yes, please. Yeah, we'll say no. No, come on.
Come on. Please. J. K. Mail. Okay, dot dot mail. Nice period. Okay. Occupation.
I guess I would love to be a locksmith. Maybe he can use me in that way. That's
a good yeah. That is true state
Ohio, Ohio,
most normal locksmith in Ohio.
Most normal locksmith marital status.
Let's say single. Okay.
That's funny.
Monthly income.
I think a locksmith is going to make about three thousand a month. Yeah
depends on the law. I said eighteen thousand. He did not bad and I
purpose of joining
need purpose
and answers.
There we go, okay, then we got plans after achieving which I don't really
know what that means plans after achieving that membership joining yeah
maybe a public suicide.
you
this one country will like to settle when you become a member.
Yeah, where do you want to go? Once you remember of these, I mean, I go
anyway, I conquer, I guess I said China yeah.
I don't know. I don't know.
What do you guys think? Maybe just say I don't know, and then just like a like a
drug suggestions question mark. Yeah, so you have a successor. Will you like to
be rewarded with a position in the organization? I skipped ahead. I would
like to be awarded. Yes, yes. Do you have a successor?
Maybe say yes. I don't know. Yes, I said soon
explain a little about you.
So can you just say yes? I know a child
I know a child who will be strong.
Okay, explain a little about you the same thing. I know a child who will be I
know
all right, let's send in the form all right and now we're just going to wait
for Rodney Bruce. So yeah message us back
it's a very prompt reply. Oh yeah, I think I think that
yes, please, J K does not fit with anything else that we've. It's kind of
strange that he is like the master of the Illuminati and he also oversees like
all the forms. Yeah, yeah,
you think maybe he'd have like an intern or some kind of yeah, definitely like I
mean, I guess the Illuminati, I guess, I'm kind of servant. The Illuminati is
more about like
violating norms right and it's not exactly normal for a master to look at
the form. Is it no it's almost like the order of the world is turned on its
head. I don't know if the
with violating norms. I would have thought that there, I guess they are
in charge of norms. Yeah, now that I think about it, you're right right, but
the once you're once you break through that membrane, once you're through the
rabbit hole, everything is topsy turvy yeah. Can you just put I would be
willing to process these applications in the future. Yeah,
that's good. That's good. Yeah, maybe maybe like okay. I can
master master. I will fill I will be willing to I will be
willing to initiative master if I am accepted.
I will help you out. I will help you out.
And then send maybe just a smile. Why not?
that might get the ball rolling yeah
okay, all right, so it looks like maybe
so we'll just wait for him to respond here and in the meantime we will just
we'll just gab yeah. We should have got actually got started on this
completely silent.
Well, he responded instantly to us every other time, so maybe he's just
rising up busy. I what could he be possibly be busy with? I don't know
he's I mean he's the leader. He's the master. Maybe he's getting a massage
yeah. I mean he responded to you instantly with the other stuff right.
Yeah, I think I kind of left him on right a little bit. Maybe he doesn't
take me so seriously anymore. That's true. Well, that's okay. Oh, can we
pull up the the Illuminati's website? I don't remember the link. Does he
don't want to click that link? There's a line that the guy sent over Facebook
that was like dot online dot. I click it. I clicked it to get the phone
number. It was safe.
Why not click it? Why not click the pick?
just click the link here. I can I can open it up for I can say the name of
the website here. Does the two check marks on whatsapp mean seen
or does it mean delivered? That means delivered. Oh yeah. So the website name
for Illuminati Brotherhood organization was
Illuminati - Brotherhood - USA Business site. Why not go?
I feel like that's awesome to check it out. It's trusted.
it's trusted. Yeah, that's a trust. That's huge. So you look at this. You
go straight there. Welcome to the pyramid Illuminati official network.
Join Illuminati today. Join the famous, powerful, wealthy and so
it's a celebs club. The Illuminati is an elite organization of world leaders,
business, business authorities, innovators, artists and other influential
members of this planet. Our coalition unites influencers of all political,
religious and geographical backgrounds to further the prosperity of the human
species as a whole. Okay, join the Illuminati family. See they spell it
wrong there. Are you a pastor? You can't google the website? Yeah, anti seo yeah.
Are you a pastor, politician, businessman or woman, or are you a
musician, musician or an artist? Do you want to be famous or do you want to
become rich or powerful? Is better you become a member of the Illuminati and
make your own dream come through? This is the chance you for now to become a
member and get what you seek from us like money. If you are ready to become a
member and realize your dream, then
okay, that's the only thing on the website. No, there's also a gallery. So I
went ahead and I think the gmail. I went ahead and I just I just texted him.
Good afternoon, master, just to see if he'd respond to me. Maybe you went to
sleep. Yeah, maybe he's just not too keen on this application. Yeah, maybe
we filled it out wrong. You know what's crazy is that guys hours. Look, what's
their business hours. They okay, maybe that's oh no, because it says they're
open twenty four hours. Every single yeah, it's not worth putting it on and
it says open twenty four hours looking at the pictures. It's like the guys
decided that they wanted to be pedophiles, even though they don't have
any sexual attraction to children.
They want all the glory of
yeah, there's really only three sections of the website. They're like the guys
they're like the guys in a band who don't play the who just are the hype
men. Yeah, yeah, yeah, they're like bez from happy Monday run sound for the
yeah.
They're the guys who drum on kegs for slipknot yeah for sure.
Well, I don't know. I guess I didn't. I guess I didn't hit him with a nice
song. Maybe he went to sleep or something. I didn't respond to me
either. I mean you like to just keep sending him messages say master, please
so disappointing. He was responding instantly all yesterday. He's caught on.
I don't know.
Yeah, let's send him.
Okay, well you know if he never responds, that's okay, yeah yeah. I
guess that is okay right yeah. It doesn't even bother me. It is a bummer.
I thought that we were going to buy one. It doesn't bother me that yeah peers
won't get to join the Illuminati and be with me and Patrick in it yeah. It
doesn't make me sad at all. I am in the yeah now thanks for allowing me to even
try to be friends with you guys in a new context, but this is something Caleb
will never get right yeah yeah unless yeah, you guys are doing this again
unless we try this out one more time. I don't know well. What else yeah? What
else is going on? Did you hear there's five men currently trapped in a
submersible? Oh underwater yeah yeah, I heard they were in the air. I heard
they were high in the atmosphere in a satellite. I've gotten bad information
had been trapped in a satellite. I heard they went on an expedition to find the
titanic and they went far up into the like too far in the air. It goes to show
that some of these billionaires are dim witted yeah, yep, that they actually
think that the titanic is up there. No, no, my friend, that is a ship that sank.
It did not float yeah and if it did float, it would only float to the top of
the water.
Go any higher than that that's as high as something can float yeah. It just goes
the show that people like Elon Musk will always you can count on them to do the
exact wrong thing in any context, and I heard that he's now calling his website
X videos or X hamster or X X and X God. He had a good idea of putting chips
into monkey brains and now he's going to completely fuck it up by removing the
chips from the monkey
buddy. They don't work after you take them out, but there's no money in that
people don't want you to do that. They want you to keep them in yeah.
wonder how far along did he get into those monkey brain chips. I think every
week he says okay, we're finally going to do it for yeah. We're finally going
to do this with a human baby. Yeah, they're going to start with a baby
imagine like being the person who like like
options off their baby to do that. He probably will start with a baby.
That's the yeah options off. I know that's like a auction off auction off
yes option office is with it. I don't even think they say option off. I think
first option, but I think yeah you would have to
that's interesting. I think you have to start with a baby fresh out the womb.
It's crying because then you get the clearest results like it's crying and
it goes to plus two. You know like it works. It's a miracle. Is that what the
chips are supposed to do? I think they're supposed to make you. I think
they let you go online. Yeah, I think they enhance you huh actually so I'm
actually I'm actually pretty sure that Rodney went to sleep because right now
I'm calling him and it's just ringing, ringing and usually declines my calls
after one ring. Yeah, so I think that he's maybe he thinks his phone was
compromised. Yeah, that's a good maybe a drop. Maybe we should or something
yeah hit. Okay, well we'll try to call him right now. Yeah, I think it's just
going to ring. Unfortunately, I look at this camera.
This is definitely going to turn him off. Yeah, it's just my computer. He's
looking at it. So he didn't get turned off at all when I called him like five
times. Yeah, he kept talking to me. I do think I truly do think he's probably
asleep and we probably just have to wake him up yeah by texting yeah. I think we
are going to keep
just call him on his normal cell, maybe if you want to yeah, that's not such a
bad idea yeah. Rodney definitely fell asleep yeah or I think the Illuminati
number is compromised. Maybe he knows what if I got a being surveilled right
now yeah. I think they're listening in and that's why hang that up hang that up.
They're not only listening in oh fuck. What have we got ourselves in that's
okay? I'm just going to call my
phone.
Google Voice
Illuminati.
OK, OK, so when did that become a Google
voice number?
OK, so when did that be?
What's that?
Oh, he's probably got a Google phone.
I mean, this guy.
No, it's still winging.
Yeah, I think he I think he put his phone
under his bed yeah
god that's so disappointing. It's horrible all right. Well, I'll leave a
voicemail if I can does Google voice even let you do
here we go.
You've made a huge mistake.
Okay, so here's that is what the number one thing you don't want to say the
Illuminati
you said you threatened them. I don't care the Illuminati and we're here with
you. I
guessed on the episode and you do this. This is my care. I don't care. I don't
even care. This is completely messed up. I'm not scared of them. I think
they're stupid. I honestly don't even think this guy's all you already.
We honestly I was watching this video yesterday about like deep ocean stuff
yeah and there's this part where it was about this guy who went down in a bath
Bathysphere and like I want to say the twenties or the thirties. What's a
Bathysphere? It's like
it's like a metal sphere that has like a glass window. It's like a really early
submarine that they just yeah, it's like that. They just like drop it down. You
always see it in movies and stuff. He's co opted this for the diving helmet.
Yeah, that's a bathyscaphe, I think,
but we should do trivia. Yeah, we should do trivia. This guy, what he would they
lower him down on like a cable and he would just be in there and just looking
at the window and he would just write down and draw whatever fish he saw and
then he'd come back up and be like guys. You won't believe what kind of weird
fish I saw down there and there's one instance where he saw he went down there
and he said that he saw a fish that straight up doesn't exist and that no
one's ever seen since so it clearly was that he just wanted like they were like
they were like yeah. I guess it could have existed and then somehow gone
extinct since then, but what's more likely is he doesn't like wanted more
attention, so he made up a six foot long fish that had two tentacles.
I bet he saw a colossal squid or so yeah, it's just like, but he drew a very
but he was like it was a six foot long fish. It had a glowing light, it has
glowing light. I saw two of them. It had glowing lights along the side and they
each had like two tentacles that also had glowing lights like it was something
that yeah doesn't sound so ridiculous. No, I mean, but the funny thing is
that no one has ever seen it since and there was no one else in the or no. You
so I think it was that there was two guys in there and one of them wasn't
paying attention. What
like oh my God, wait, look at this. Oh, you missed it.
Luckily, I just drew it glue
that's like most of oh my God, we get I think I just heard a noise. I heard
a what's that notification. Can you click
I okay my son that's great okay click back in the in the field. What question
do we want to ask?
Let's ask a question about the fish. Is there any fish living in the deep ocean?
Yeah, that's a good question. Is there any hello master? Is there any fish
living in the deep ocean?
Yeah, same master master. Is there any fish living in the deep ocean that is
six foot long with two tentacles
in the
deep ocean that is six feet long with two tentacles?
Can you say the national the real NASA and then in parentheses aquatic is
lying about fish again?
The real NASA
aquatic
is lying about fish again dot dot dot question mark
all right. Let's see what Rodney says back because I personally don't believe
in this fish yeah. I don't either part of the Illuminati says that this fish
exists. I will believe in it. I will totally believe in this fish, long with
not specific
oh my God. He just responded to me saying a mistake. How
oh he's typing right now. I just saw the typing. I love this guy. This guy's so
knowledgeable. He's truly my master is the master of the Illuminati. Also, when
I texted him knowledgeable good afternoon master. He said greetings my
son. Oh my God, great. I wonder if he knows that it's the same person that
is
maybe he's freaked out right now. Maybe he doesn't want to answer anything.
No, he said, are you sure you're ready to take this great step in life and
achieve all your dreams and heart desires? Yeah answer about the fish.
I'll say yes, yes, but I need an answer about the fish.
okay, we'll say yes dot dot dot, but I need an answer about the fish yeah
that's good. Okay, I just really I
was feeling crazy about it, though I'm at that. Can you just a fish that's
only one person ever saw
ever yeah, he definitely made that fish up sometimes that happens, but that can
happen in the deep underwaters yeah wow. What if it was an eel? I guess it was a
strange deal. What if it was an eel with an alien tentacles a strange
glowing eel that was maybe two of them swimming together. Maybe yeah, yeah,
I think so hard to believe school of eels, but you'll still live deep
underwater. Do they there are some maybe eels live in I don't know. I
think there's some meals that live. The eels live in mud. There are
definitely some meals that live in mud. I think worms live in dirt. You
know who loves eating eels is the fucking British people. You've seen
that video or it's like the oldest fast food restaurant in the world and
it's like they like jelly deals, a jellied eels in the in the pie bar or
whatever
really jelly,
jelly, jelly. I went to I went to I mean I sent it to you guys immediately, but I
went to a restaurant earlier today. Jelly J. I got the guy behind the counter
was named Jelly J. That is such a good name. A or it was like a are jelly J. A
are jelly J.
okay. Now that I'm thinking about it, maybe a jelly as a nickname in between
the R and the J yeah, but his are a are jelly jelly j
jelly jam, jelly, jelly, jam, jelly, j that's such a good name. What do you
say? There's jelly. Yes, I know we're just going to hit him with no worries
wrong number. No worries. That was I thought yeah. I thought you were
I'm really so curious about this guy. Yeah, I want to know like well. First of
all, he's not answering about the fish. Yeah, he will he will he will. I hope
maybe he's maybe he's too concerned about this mistake. Yeah, he'll answer
about the ash. Are you sure you're going to take this great step in life and
achieve all your dreams and hearts desires? Yes,
but I need to know about the fish. My friends and I are don't believe that I
What's the first change in the world you guys would make if you were the master
if I was the master first change I would make
fix Apple pay on my phone is broken right now.
I can't tap the subway.
It's hard.
Oh my God.
I can't tap to get into the subway.
It used to be so easy.
Now I got to take my whole card out.
I'd just fix stuff probably.
Fix all the problems.
I would do stuff for good.
You should be able to Apple sell.
You should just be able to put your phone up to something and get money.
Can't you do that?
Can't you put two phones together?
here. That's kind of that's always my fear when I'm using. I mean it can't be
so hard for some genius.
Hacker is the smartest in the world. Yeah, to when I'm reaching out to tap my
phone on the turnstile that they can just pull the money out of the air.
Yeah, can't they do that with the the the dolphin thing? Have you seen those
little yellow or orange? No, I don't know what that is. It's this this RFID like
spoofer that you can get. It was like you can like there's like a frequency
sooner thing. I know you can use it to like open up other people's garage
doors yeah unless unless I or or or or copy library books labels.
We're just talking on text instead of on
his
let's get to it. Let's get to it master.
Maybe I was just following I also I of it, but it like it was showing videos
people. I mean, you can do that. You can use it to spoof amiibos. You can put
amiibos into your you can get all of them put. I used to be. I used to be so
obsessed with that in like middle school and high school. The idea of of yeah,
copying or erasing RFIDs and stuff and that you but not that I ever was able to
do any of that stuff, but it's so crazy that that's something you can do. I knew
somebody who had like a DRM stripper or something and they knew how to like
remove the DRM off of iTunes gift cards and that's how they got all their me.
that's so swag. I used to crack the DRM on e books from the library. Oh yeah,
that's the that's the most fun thing. What I used to do is I had a you would
do that in the Illuminati yeah. What I was before I joined the Illuminati
that's why they want me yeah. They reached out to me first. Actually, they
said I saw what you did with library
the most returning institution yeah. I had to pull over hoodie and then with
the big pocket and you can fit a nerds rope in there.
not so hard. It's the hardest thing to steal, but not with a pull over hoodie.
Yeah,
what was that? Can you focus the what's up again? I just want to ping him yeah
well. No, he's talking to get back to me on what's at my son as if he's not
okay. Yeah, I'll get him yeah master the fish.
I just wrote yeah, let's get to it master. I am ready for abilities and he
Okay, get back to me on what's okay. I said no, my son knows I knew it. Am I
say am I not ready yet? No, because I'm ready. Well, I know, but I know, but
maybe he has to do like I think he's answering your question about the fish.
Oh, that's a good point. I think he's saying there is no fish like that. Well,
he's typing. Well, then maybe this will clarify. Let me know I'm ready. Yeah,
see I told you I told you he I told you it was going to be the question of being
ready. I'm
Is that not his name? He changed it right? No, that's what we said at the
top. I thought it was Alan something now Rodney Bruce. I want to run an
Allen. Alan is the guy from the focus group. It was on it was on the set of
the non union production that we did not scab stop calling us scabs. It was
scabless. It was completely scabless. You scabbed hard. I've been scabbing
recently. Oh yeah, yeah, I've been just writing all the movies that have been
of coming up. That's
any movie they need made. I just he said I'm not here to be asked a relevant
questions, which is out of the organization. You are on the wrong foot
with him. Okay, sorry, okay,
okay, sorry. I thought you knew everything.
I thought you would know about the fish.
I will ask someone else.
I'll ask someone else about the fish, but for now I need to join.
but I'm ready dot dot for Illuminati. I love you.
Oh man, well, how are we ever going to find it? Who are the else? Are we going
to ask about this fucking fish? Do we know? I honestly don't even give a fuck
about this fish. You know what you're totally right. I don't give a fuck about
the fish. I'm over it. I'm over that yeah on it. We should say honestly I'm
I'm honestly I don't care about the fish.
Honestly, I'm over the fish and don't care about always typing. I only care
about puppeteering.
He's typing again. Okay, I think right now he's going to tell you to send the
selfies or the video. Yeah,
So we have those ready, right? You have all the photos. I have the photos.
All right. Okay, good. All right. I think the organization is not a place for
jokes or relevant questions. My son, damn, he's really cracking down. Yeah,
I know. What the hell should I tell him? You just made a huge mistake.
No, not yet. No, say, say, master. I am ready.
I am ready to become a member. I am brimming with excitement and
trying to make a good impression. These are not jokes and I'm sorry that I made
a bad first impression.
I'm not funny in real life.
He's going to like that yeah. This is going to win him over. I hopefully
Rodney Bruce
yeah
I'm called
the master
I'm called Master Rodney Bruce
the master of the Illuminati being do you think he's lying on his bed right
now with his feet up against the wall? No, I think he's lying on his back. I
think he's just he's holding his phone right now. I want to know about him
every detail of his life. Okay, my son. Now we got to send the selfies. Let's
go. Okay, let's go. I'll forward you these
forward you these selfies. I'm going to type to him while I do that. Okay. Say,
do you want them in HD?
Do you want the...
Excellent. I knew this moment was coming.
Do you want the photos in high definition?
All right, Julio, I just forwarded the selfies to you on discord so we can throw
with them in here and get Pierce all signed up. Yeah,
now the hand signs, you might have to take the video with the way that this
has been going.
I think that might be a little extra from you. He might notice the CIA
that's embroidered on the
well, that's okay, because the Illuminati probably controls the CIA.
Yeah, I mean, so you're probably already probably in a good position.
Yeah, yeah,
Okay, great, then the photos are high definition. Yeah,
these are good photos.
So huge,
but that's okay. I love the hand signs that Rodney Bruce makes you do to join
the Illuminati. He does a it's a rock on sign, a spider man sign and a and a
high five.
Please forgive my cuticles,
my heart harassers have
augmenting
fingers at night. He said okay, my son, that's great.
I'm brimming
and yeah, I buy every everybody who's watching or listening to this. You
should join the Illuminati. We get all hang out and I think we should all join
it. Yeah, I should all join together. We should all join because this is a yeah
it's only fun. If all your friends are in it, yeah, if we all troll this guy, if
we have a discord, we figure out exactly how we're going to call him. I wonder
going me going to the Illuminati meeting texting first me like yo who all is
there yeah wait. I really do understand.
I really wonder what his end game with this is though, because it's definitely
like some kind of credit card scam right like I think we're going to have to
send gift cards soon. Yeah, I can't that's cool. I do think that he might
just be cos playing. I think he might be having fun yeah. It's a really good. I
don't know which is that like what's worse is it's worse that he's just doing
this for fun or is it like I would do this for fun. We're already doing it.
Yeah, it's true.
You are the point of my life
because there's no way that there's like an Illuminati
thing like this and it doesn't end with like you need to send me
to join. You need to send me five hundred dollars in Amazon, but he said
that we're joined yeah and now he's texting me. I said he said greetings my
son. How are you? I'm just going to tell him now go and get a good handle of the
videos coming. Yeah, that's okay. We'll tell him I say I already had one. I
already have one yeah. Okay, say I have a candle and then we'll just we'll just
bait him here.
(Laughter)
Because we don't already have one in my hand.
I use it to channel.
Oh jeez.
I use it to channel purposes.
Okay.
Yeah.
Is there a candle?
We might have candles. Yeah.
Oh okay. Do we have a lighter?
Yeah we have a lighter over there.
My son don't rush. Okay.
Okay.
No rush here.
I have mastered patience due to gastric bubbles.
We do have a million patients.
Where's the lighters over there?
Lighters over there next to that pack of cigarettes.
These smell amazing.
They smell like apples and they last for four hours.
What do I do with these candies?
You must be aware of the path you have chosen in life.
That's so true.
Honestly, that is a good mantra to have.
Yeah, I am aware of the path I have chosen in life.
I am so certain
take a clean piece of paper, a piece of paper that's a night. Okay, now I gotta
get a clean piece of paper. Yeah, hold on. Okay, the candle is lit
and there's three wicks on this candle, which represents the three of us
currently in the room.
perfect. I told him I am lighting the candy. I am grasping my sheet right all
what you seek
desire from the organization on okay. What are we? What are we seeking desire?
We're seeking answers about the fish yeah, but we gave that up yeah. No, I
say no longer seeking answers about the fish. I'm just right different amounts
of money. I said don't like the can't oh
blew it
don't get the candle is so funny. I'm going to write dinosaur
okay,
just that
yeah, that's good. What else okay,
I'll say I wrote I wrote down my desire.
When do I like the candle master white? I'll say it right now
dinosaur sciences,
anything else international money
internet. He said no. Okay, say okay.
When are we going to like yeah? When do you when do I when are we being
informed? I'm just going to write bubble girl,
bubble girl, girl with a girl with a bubble body
at the bubble girl and bubble realm. Yeah, okay,
now what now what that's good.
Yeah, I can't he's just taking his sweet. I know come on man. You're leaving us
hanging here. Okay, he's typing now.
Okay, now what let's go Rodney Brews. He's probably gonna tell us to what did
he he asked you to do this right Patrick? Yeah, but I told him I had to
ago. Okay, so we're getting pretty where we've gotten. I wonder if he's gonna ask
us to burn it. That will be oh yeah wag. Have you ever tried becoming a member
before? No,
he wants new members.
Okay, so if if we had said yes there, I wonder what he would have said. Don't
like the candle Patrick. You didn't inform us. I just like the smell. These
candles are so fly. I love the way they make me smell. They make you smell
Wow, these are making me smell. I can't help but smell
bro. He's being so annoying. He is master. You're being a no master. I'm
annoyed with your actions.
Master, what's
what shit?
What's the next step? Master? What's the next step? Yeah, I can hear garage
door.
It's coming. Okay, my son, okay,
okay, kind of stalling their master, making it up all on the spot. Now he's
typing a here. We go okay. I hope it doesn't say to kill somebody.
Please tell me to burn the paper to take a nude picture. Yeah, I don't want to
do anything. If he tells us for the paper, we all just scream like I said,
be patient, no rushing my son. Okay, I'm on a time constraint.
I mean I'm at work.
I'm on a job right now. I'm supposed to be I'm supposed to be fixing a lock.
I'm in the bathroom pretending
no that's too jokey yeah he's going to catch wind. No he doesn't he doesn't
know what we're doing. The Illuminati doesn't know anything about us yeah,
except for what we tell them. We got to get a closer. We are kind of well. I'm
like the Illuminati's friend yeah
Yeah, I think we should need to think of one really good final question to ask
him if he's not going to go. I just want to send in this video. I feel like
that's the swaggiest thing is for him to go. Well, we wrote down. We wrote down
all the desires right okay, okay, at what
I'm home. It's my lock.
I'm home yeah.
He's completely stringing us along here. Yeah, I'm just going to be, but I'll
back and forth. Okay, Rodney needs to to really, really, really. Do you think
that Rodney Bruce is a code name? Maybe it's an anagram for something. Julio,
can you look up anagram for Rodney Bruce?
I bet that it broad broad news broad
broad news it free anagrams.
Okay, this isn't right at all. I think there's an anagram name getter. Let me
if I can find it on my phone.
Anagram solver.
He just responded, though.
If you have any questions or doubts
about the organization, you can ask
before I proceed.
OK, do we have any questions?
Wait, wait, wait.
Go to that.
What is this website?
This website doesn't matter.
OK, we need to get we need to finish
this chat here.
Yeah.
What do you have?
Do we have any doubts or questions?
I feel like I mean, I guess the
question is, I'm the question
is, are you ready for me?
Are you ready for me to join up doing ranks? I'm so ready. The
question is, are you ready for me to join? Are you ready for
me?
The paper is hurting my hand.
Paper is hurting my hand. Please tell me what to do.
The paper is hurting my
the bubble realm bubble realm
God,
you're giving Pierce conniption. He's having conniptions. He's having a
connection. Wait is that what he looks like? I don't know. He does have a
profile picture. Yeah, that's a picture does look like him, though. Let me see
oh that's him in his gear and his garb. That's him. No yeah yeah wait. Surely
that's it is
maybe he's in phoby. That looks like him family of Bruce International family of
like Bruce international work wait click that's got to be him. No that is not
what
is
that's got to be him. Can you click about on this family of Bruce go to
phobia and games calendar
non profit.
Okay, this looks like the photos used on the website. He's a cult leader. Oh my
God,
games calendar. No games. This isn't a cult.
I don't know. I think if it's a cult of Bruce and Bruce is the
leader. What's Bruce leadership? Did we already go there? No, we
haven't clicked any of this stuff yet members only area the
fit. Well, I think we've uncovered something. What's
what's Syrian keen?
Syrian King Kingi
page left blank for two-sided printing
chief of the name. What is this? Yeah, what is this family of
Bruce international? I think this is some kind of
family. It is a it is definitely a family.
What's Bruce leadership? Could you go up to the leadership? Yeah,
well, this is so swag. Well, he's a guy who says he was
king of Scots.
Okay,
Lord Bruce.
Oh my God, Lord. So I bet he joined this community because
he's obsessed with societies and then he was awarded the title of Bruce
maybe Bruce
go back to Rodney
yeah, he's typing
whoa, he's sending whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, okay, play the video, play
the video,
the
are these the same sent us videos
(Batman theme song)
- That's the same garb that he was wearing.
- Is that the same?
- Oh my God.
Halo classic fashion.
- No, that's not the same.
- What are you talking about, Patrick?
He's the family of Bruce.
Wow.
What's the next thing he said?
What is this he's unfolded and said okay, he's sending a screenshot of
someone else's come yeah with him, then he's sending his rings. He's what's
that number is garb
a passport,
Exorcist thing.
This is like a sound alike.
This is like an audio jungle.
No!
Kevin MacLeod.
You should say this is scary.
The ring fell down.
Oh my God.
Master Passport.
Oh my God!
The plan of illumination.
Oh my God.
This is crazy.
Yeah.
He's just all.
together.
There's no way there's no I'm telling you now he's going to make us send him
gift cards or something.
The music is so swag dude, it's so fucking and my ring
wait a minute. I didn't know you were in the free mason's.
Let the candle place the paper beside let the writings be visible on it and
a short video and send it to me while saying all hails to the light.
Okay.
Here, let me take the video so that, take it on my phone so I can send it directly to
Julio.
Okay, and we can't get any of the mic cables or anything in the shot, right?
Yeah.
Here, you can hold it and take the video.
Okay.
You're putting it right above the candle.
I should just accidentally light it up.
No, you should not.
Here, wait, bring it closer here because I don't want the cords in the shot.
Okay.
All right, this is it, guys.
This is it.
We're about to get-
face and say all hails to the light. He's the farthest. I'm going to turn it to me.
Yeah.
Make a short video and send it to me while saying all hails to the light.
I don't think you need to show your face.
All hails to the light.
OK, now let me send this over to Julio, he'll send it over and we're good.
I think we're in guys.
Yeah, I think you think we'll be next in line to be masters.
I hope so.
Wait, do you guys think we could be I think Rodney Bruce would let us become
master. I can't believe the videos that he sent.
They are so awesome.
I think here this is the most exciting time before before you send.
I'm just going to text him.
Yeah, go ahead.
Just say like I just shared the video with you Julio to once he
once he types this delicious.
These videos are deliciously horrifying not horrifying.
You can't you can't say that you're scared are deliciously
not frightening deliciously cryptic.
I think they are scary.
I think that's the point.
No, no, no.
Okay.
Yeah, powerful is a good word deliciously powerful.
I cannot wait to have how these would scare children or layman yeah and then
send that and then Julio can send your video right after that, because I send
it to him.
Okay, you have to stop typing to do it, I D, I D, I D.
This is going to be kind of go down in history as investigative journalism.
Yes, I think. Here comes my video.
Okay, here comes a video Rodney.
I hope it sends.
Okay,
Dinosaur Sciences, International Money,
Bubble Girl, Bubble Realm.
All hails to the light.
This is a good video.
Yeah.
ID. It still says ID. That's fine. Yeah, it seems cryptic and okay. Yeah, I guess
Rodney's going to watch the whole thing. So we have to fill 20 seconds here. Yeah,
maybe we talk about our favorite foods. I like shrimp. Yeah, I love swim. I can't
wait to eat lunch after this. I am hungry lunch hungry. I'm ready to you
guys want to get no. I already had Burger City. Where's Burger City? That's
where Jelly J is.
Oh
it's where jelly day works. That's where it is for our daily day works.
We're silly J
Rodney all hails to the light. I'll need you Rodney. Do you think that maybe all
hills to the light is a phrase that's picked so that he can he can cut it up
and rearrange it and it can get into a voice password system? Maybe and it's
like you saying like I am me yeah
I think that that's definitely maybe message him right now and say no. I'm
on a time crunch. He's watching the video. He's busy. Maybe he's pounding
off to the International Money Bubble Girl bubble. I don't understand. Maybe
he has to look up bubble girl. Yeah, he probably is looking up. What happens
when you yeah, let's try to see what he's Googling bubble girl bubble girl
in quotes or yeah, just he doesn't know how to do quotes. Yeah, definitely
doesn't okay, bubble girl. Oh, so I hear so this makes sense. So it does make
sense and what about bubble realm bubble realm is a good good search to we need
to know what bubble realm will will will will show yeah
okay,
enter
but to enter shadow realm shadow room is different from bubble realm. Yeah, it
is pretty different. I really am so excited. I want to get
Okay, should we ping him?
Yeah, we should ping him.
Alright, let me go ahead and say...
Do you like my video?
Is it...
Um...
Is it Satisfactory Master?
Yeah, is it Satisfactory Master?
This candle smells good.
What is this? This is a...
This is lime, basil, and mandarin.
the
twenty five hours. Really? Yeah. Well, he's going to actually read the I
wonder if he reads the documents that people send. Yeah, I think he does. He
must. I really am so curious about the end game of this. Yeah, it's gotta be
gift cards, right? It's gotta be. I don't know. I feel like he already would
have said something. No, no, because they're gonna string you along. Yeah, I
think they do have to develop a relationship with you for. Yeah, yeah,
like he's promising you membership to the Illuminati. That is a pretty big
promise. He didn't say anything about public suicide. Yeah, that's
yeah. He lets a lot of stuff slide. Yeah, maybe try to call him. You go hit
call. I do like I like debasing him dragging him down enough to ask him
about Barbenheimer enough times that he'll he responds to it. Let's see is it
calling
okay
okay and the call because he just replied
Okay, my son, that's great. All else to the light. What is next master? We need
I we need to go with a bang here yeah
okay. Can I be the leader?
Two unread messages, what's the second one?
Is it before
I don't know. I don't know doesn't matter yeah,
Okay, all right, oh he said not yet,
okay,
wait, he's typing, he's typing.
What is he going to say to see what he says, and then I will send this message,
depending on what he said,
okay, wait, yeah, where do I get this? Where do I get the suit? Here's the
scam
heals the scam. You know you sound like a idiot. Here's the scam here. It is
he's going to ask for money yeah.
If you think that's a scam, you've never really been scammed because I would
like a suit that's true, yeah, but what you don't know is he's going to take
your money and not send you the suit. Okay, that is that's the scam. That is
actually a scam. Yeah,
dinosaur science, a hurry
money and
yeah, what do you think this like because he's showing the suit right in
those videos with the money and stuff yeah, wait go back and you scroll up. I
need to I need to lose it. I was typing this is too much man. Yeah, this is
I'm just going to send him a picture of me with my shirt off. Okay.
No, we're almost there. What do you mean? Almost there? I will inform you on what to do.
Okay.
I told you it's a okay. Excellent. Half six six six.
Do shirtless pic. Do shirtless pic.
Can I get a discount? Can I get a discount?
And look really sexy with my hands out like this.
Hold on, my camera is not working.
Oh, come on, Cam.
It's completely not working.
Close it and reopen it there.
Do a seductive face.
Oh, wait. Yes, my son.
Oh, he's smart. He knows math.
Alright, I'll send this to you right now.
Ask him, say I have $333.
No, send him this pic and say, "Can I get a discount?"
All right, I just sent it and this will be our this is our closer here.
Can I receive a discount master?
Ask if the uniform will fit on my body. Will the uniform fit this
so wait let's just wait for discount. I bet that's going to be a quicker answer.
Oh, the suspense kills me really does yeah and it's like is this even a
podcast is waiting for a weird. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know if this
episode will be great or bad or too far gone. Yeah, the first part of it is
something yeah, I'm having fun. I don't know anyone else. Yeah, it demands an
edit. It demands a cut
now it's fine.
no, it's good to go just upload all yeah. I hope he's not ignoring. I think he's
ignoring
janks
hurry.
I got unclicked
sending hurry two times every time
Judge Judy. Yeah. All right. Yeah. All right. Well, I think it's time for my
lunch. Yeah. Oh, he's typing. Oh, he's typing. Oh my God. No. Damn. Fuck.
What are the final message?
I want to keep talking to. I know. Yeah. Don't say that. We'll when this
episode drops, we'll post the follow up. Yeah. Everyone in the organization did
same before they officially became members. OK. Oh, so this is the script.
this is the scam script because everyone wants a discount. Yeah, all right.
All right, we'll end it here and then we'll post the follow up once that's
done. Yeah, okay, okay. Thank you for listening. Yeah, you're ahead and plug
your stuff. Yeah, we'll move that. We'll move the plug to the beginning. Yeah,
hi,
wait, which camera should I look in? Does it matter? Well, wait, he said,
once you officially become an organ, a member of the organization, $900,000 USD
will be given to you as your new membership benefits. Oh my God. Can we
subtract. I mean obviously we could talk to him all day, but yeah yeah all right
and then or you can look into this. Okay episodes over