*outro music*
You don't have to clap.
Yep. That's right. We still don't have an SD card in the thing.
Cameron leaves and now all of our shit is so fucked up.
Everything's ruined man. Yeah.
This is how it is.
It's completely fucked.
You and me, we are two of the least competent people in the world I would say.
Yeah. I mean you haven't, you haven't scheduled trash pickup at all.
Nope.
have a fruit fly problem because of Caleb's actions.
Not because of my actions, you're the fruit.
I'm not the fruit.
You're the fruit that's being attractively attractive to a fly.
I had to become fly Hitler and make a...
You did not have to.
You wanted to become fly Hitler.
I made a... it's soap and apple cider vinegar.
I hate being an animal Hitler.
Me too.
way too many times as a man. As a man, there are 40 to 50 times in your life,
when I'm probably at time 15, where you have to be a Hitler to a group of
animals. You know, ants, flies, cockroaches, wasps, mice.
Mice is a bad one. Yeah, you had a lot of mice. I had the Hitler mice for a long time.
That's why when I got Moe, Mouse Problem, my old place, the fucking
building that was constantly falling apart and covered in rats. I
remember that. Rats weren't a problem though. He did play with a, Alex sent me a video one
time of Moe just playing a little floor hockey with a cockroach. He just sent you a video?
Sent me a video of Moe playing floor hockey with a cockroach and I was like, did you get
the cockroach out of his hand? He said no. And he said no, I wasn't going to touch it.
Dude, Phil will, anytime that there's like, you know sometimes there's a bunch of dead
worms on the ground somewhere. No, but go on. We live in different neighborhoods. We live
We live in the same neighborhood.
Well, I live 10 blocks away from you.
Sometimes there are a bundle of worms that have all spontaneously died and been smashed
at the exact same time and Phil will walk up to them and he rolls in it trying to, like
he's putting on cologne.
Yeah, he wants to make himself smell better than other dogs.
I do not like that at all.
Yeah, I get that.
I don't like that.
Speaking of bugs, Mo eats a lot of bugs. Pet talk. We should have a new theme song. I don't
even understand how to put my pet on. What if it's just a popular song but it's done
with meows and woofs. And that's our theme song for pet talk. Meow meow woof woof woof.
good. Yeah, that'll work. But so when Mo was a baby, like two months in, he was never a
baby. He was a kitten. Well, he was still a kitten. He's he's turns one this month. But
he was like, maybe the size of my palms. Yep. And he ate a spotted lanternfly and was like
acting really sick for a couple of minutes. And I was like, oh, shit. This is like when
after I had to like watch him for I had to like monitor him and make sure he didn't die
of panleukopenia and then he threw up a bunch of red stuff and I was like, "Oh God, this
is it. This is it. I have to take him to the emergency vet." And then I looked at it closer,
whole spotted lanternfly. He caught it and then ate it and then it was sitting in his
stomach and he was just going like...
Which by the way, these emergency vets, it's not... You think based on the name, you think
that it's going to be a scene in the Godfather where someone gets shot and they're rushed
down a big long hallway and they have tubes all in them. It's just a vet that's open 24
hours a day.
Most of the time all the animals in there it's just like, "Oh, my dog ate a bee."
Yeah, exactly. And you still have to wait two hours sometimes.
Yeah, there's really no rush.
And that's Shoe.
That's Shoe?
Yeah, you haven't heard this?
you ever heard this? Is it one of your notes that you said you had? No, just something
that I heard. Yeah? Yeah. What's shoe? It's like the op, you know cap is like lie. Shoe
is like the truth. Oh yeah, because it's so true that you'll stand your ground on it.
Exactly. Wow. So you can say, like instead of saying like, you could even say, like if
somebody says the truth, you say like that's shoe. But if someone says a lie, instead of
saying that's cap, you say that's reverse shoe. No shoes. No, that's no shoe. Shoeless.
Shoeless Joe Jackson. That's shoeless. Exactly. So yeah, and I mean, Jubio knows about this.
Yeah. He also has been hearing about it recently. Did you come up with this? Is this something
that you... No, somebody, some random kids that I heard on the street came up with this
and people were talking about it and I just kinda, I keep my ear low to the ground. I
keep my head on a swivel.
Well, it's like near the shoes.
Near the shoes, and that's shoe, you know?
I'm getting a text from Jubio.
What's he saying?
Is he saying shoe?
Maybe.
He says his power went out.
His power went out right now?
Yeah, I don't know if he's still...
Well, I mean, it's recording on...
Yeah, it doesn't matter.
He'll come back when he gets a chance.
Yeah, well...
But that does mean that I do not have any backup.
Yeah, well, I wasn't gonna...
I'm not even...
You're not even a little bit skeptical about shoe.
No, I think that maybe you made it up and this is you trying to plant the seeds.
That is no shoe. That is reverse shoe that you're saying. I did not make it up and that's
shoe.
Maybe Jubio or Rex made it up?
Nobody that I know made it up, man. I'm telling you, I was just walking by.
You're planting the seeds?
I was walking by a perfect kind of like Taco Bell commercial group of people, you know,
who were like all sitting there having a fun time, fourth meal style. And they were saying,
Oh, this is complete shoe.
Maybe they're saying bull shoe.
No, no, no.
Bull shoe.
Maybe they're saying shoot.
No, that doesn't make any sense.
I think it was shoe because it makes sense.
Cap is lie.
Shoe is the truth.
It's a bottom up system.
What would be like pants or belt?
Pants or belt is like a half truth.
So it's like if you misremember something, you would say like...
And then when something's above belt.
Yes.
That's like being above board.
You know, when people say above belt.
Above your belt.
I've heard that in my life.
Yes, people have said that.
Now that I think about it, I've heard that too.
I've heard that maybe more than cap and shoe.
Yeah, people say that's above belt.
Because that's more than half the truth.
Or below the belt.
Below the belt means more than half a lie.
But when someone says something's below the belt, that means that it's like, oh, that's
a cheap shot. Yeah, but that's in a different context. Yeah, if you're talking about truths
and lies, as many many men in America often are, you say, Oh, that's that's more than
below the belt. That's it. That's knee pads. And then if you go up, you say, that's a cummerbund.
You know, that's like above the belt kind of mid riff area, you know, or that's a bra
that's a sports bra. That's a necklace, you know, so it's all it's kind of a gradient.
But shoe and cap are the two ends of it, I would say.
Okay, so it's a full spectrum.
Yeah, of truths and lies.
Because I'm sick of, or not I'm sick of,
these random people that I heard say this,
this amazingly diverse group of people
of all different ages,
and races, and religions, creeds, and well...
You know what? I'm fine with every race,
fine with every religion,
but I'm not fine with every creed.
Creeds are, you know,
it's a slippery slope once you start
letting people with different creeds...
different creeds. There are certain creeds that I do not want in this country. No, absolutely
samurai. I would want them for our army. Samurai do not want to be a part of an army that is
not completely 100% samurai. Yeah, samurai want a fully samurai. They want to see every
they want to open their eyes and see all they don't want to do. They don't want like a like,
you know, like really extremely diverse army. No assassins. That's a creed that I don't want
Yeah, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Because I mean, look what happened.
We'll get to happen to our president, McKinley.
Look what happened to Bethlehem in the in the year like 100.
Yeah, that was not going so well.
There's some crazy lunatic walking around with a knife hand. Yeah.
That's not bad. Huh?
Which I thought the assassins created that this took place in Italy.
Not the one of them is like Bible times.
Yeah, if I remember correctly, it's kind of cool.
It is kind of cool. Those games are fun.
I didn't play the pirate one, though, but I really know my brother.
my brother's really into those games. The Black Pearl. The Black Sails or something. The Black
Pearl. It's not called the Black Pearl. If you were on... You're conflating Pirates of
the Caribbean. Caribbean. Yeah, why do people say Caribbean? Why don't people say Caribbean?
They say Caribbean unless it's Pirates. Yeah, and then they say Caribbean. That used to
really bother me when I was a child. I kind of grew out of that. Because then people would
like, you know, like your uncle reads the DVD case and he's like, oh, Pirates of the
the Caribbean, you're like, "It's not Caribbean, it's Caribbean."
It's actually the Caribbean now for this one movie, asshole.
Yeah.
That's cool that they made that movie and then were like, "Oh, then we should start
making the other rides."
Oh, yeah, they made...
Haunted Mansion.
Haunted Mansion, and then they just remade it.
Yeah.
With...
LaKeith Stanfield and Danny DeVito.
I almost went and saw it, but I saw Talk to Me.
Talk to Me.
But I wish that I'd seen a hundred man she gives that actually looks funny as fuck you think it looks amazing
It's got a son menage in it. Oh, yeah, whoa. Yeah, and he plays a
Sarcastic asshole damn
So it's basically my kind of movie. Yeah, yeah, it's got movies. I like I was reading I was reading online
Something that's gone viral on the Twitter verse what?
Something that's gone viral on X. What's gone viral on X's?
was
people complaining that there's too much product placement in the movie.
Of Haunted Mansion?
Yeah.
There's like a scene where...
For a ghostly specter?
Well, if there was product placement for maybe like ghost busting services,
I don't think that that would be a problem.
That would not be a problem at all.
But I guess there's a scene where Lakeith Stanfield is describing
the way his wife passed away.
And he's talking, he's got this big long speech,
speech and he's like, she wanted to stop it. Baskin Robbins.
And it's so clear that it was an ADR.
Like they threw like Baskin Robbins in.
Just so they'd be like, yeah. That's awesome.
But also like that's the funniest fucking product placement.
Like, I guess it makes a little bit of sense. Like,
I don't care too much when they like talk about like,
there's like product placement in a movie. Cause it's like, yeah, like it's like,
like when you talk in like conversations, like, Oh,
I'm going to go to fucking McDonald's or something.
Yeah.
You know, like that's normal.
That's realistic.
But like, I don't know.
Like when a scene takes,
like when somebody works at like Baskin Robbins
or something like an Ant-Man,
I think that's kind of egregious.
But like saying it in conversation like that,
I don't think that's too bad.
I think that these brands need to realize
that the only way that you can do a product placement
in a movie and get away with it
is that you need to be subtly poking fun at your brand in a hilarious manner.
So if they work at Baskin Robbins...
Well, that's what, yeah, I mean that's how it is in the movie.
In Ant-Man?
Yeah, and Greg Turkington is the manager.
Where, at where?
Baskin Robbins.
It is a Baskin Robbins?
Yeah.
So does he...
Ant-Man works at Baskin Robbins and he gets fired for not being a good employee.
Does he say, so because he's not a good employee, does he say something, he looks at, let me
guess, he looks at the Rocky Road and he says like, "What's this, poop ice cream?"
Yeah.
Something like that?
Basically it's stuff like that.
And he goes through every single, all 32.
And he says, "This looks like jizz. This looks like piss."
The white one is jizz, the lemon one is piss, the chocolate is poop, chocolate chip is jizz with poop in it.
Pistachio is a vitamin B piss.
Rocky Road, again, that's poop with chunks of poop.
That's chili poop.
Chili poop.
Okay, and then what is...
Strawberry is a period jizz.
(laughing)
Okay, and what about Superman?
Superman, what's that?
Is that a Baskin?
I've really never been to Baskin Robbins.
Did you just say, "What is Superman ice cream?"
Superman ice cream.
I'm realizing now, I've been to, I'm a Dairy Queen.
Wait, you'll see this when you see it
when you show a photo of it right now.
I'm a Dairy Queen boy.
Superman ice cream is this.
What would Ant-Man say about this shit?
Oh, buddy.
I mean, he'd have endless quips about this.
This looks like period jizz with pee and blue.
- Oh, God. - Blue crap.
- So let me guess, Greg Turkington fires him.
- Yeah.
- Wow.
Does he fire him in kind of a dry way?
- Yes, a very dry way.
- Oh, I love that.
Or does he do his guy?
- He does his guy.
- His character guy.
- Not Neil Hamburger.
- He doesn't do Neil Hamburger?
- That would have taken me out of the movie.
- Get out of my ice cream store.
Why? Why are you such a bad employee?
Yeah, and then he told him...
Because you called the ice cream period more of just vitamin BP.
That would... they should have done that.
Yeah, they should have had Neil Hamburger in it.
But he already had a movie, Entertain Me.
Where I hear that it actually has emotions.
It does. I actually love that movie so much.
I've never seen that movie.
Yeah, it's really good.
I saw the comedy.
Comedy is also so good.
I thought it was really good, yeah.
It was a little weird.
But as I get older, I'm starting to like strange stuff.
It's a little weird, but I expect that from Heidecker.
Yeah, you know what I called it?
You know what I said?
I watched it with my wife, and you know what I said right afterwards?
I said, "That was Heideckercore."
Yeah.
This is giving me Tim and Eric vibes.
This is Heideckercore.
Yeah.
And then, turns out I was right.
He's in the movie.
You didn't even know that while I was watching it.
I thought that it was just kind of...
I couldn't recognize him because he's got a beard.
I thought it was Ryan Reynolds.
Yeah.
But apparently it was.
He does.
He looks so good in that movie.
Tim Heidecker.
He's a really good looking guy.
Yeah.
He's like skinny as hell now though.
I'm worried he's on the Aussie.
You think he's on Aussie?
Yeah.
Should we get on Ozympic?
I don't think that people would like me if I was skinny.
You think people wouldn't like you?
If you were skinny?
Really?
No, I think I would just look so...
too threatening because you're good looking?
I think it is.
If you were like shredded it would be a really big problem?
Maybe.
And people would be like fuck.
Like you know when you see the pictures of Post Malone where it's like clear that he's
been doing Aussie.
Oh and he's scratching his arms.
Yeah.
It's clear.
I don't know.
I think it would change me too much.
You think it would change you too much?
Yeah.
To be skinny?
I used to be rail thin.
It'd make you good at skateboarding though.
Yeah.
You'd be able to do ollies and nollies higher.
I think... What's better, an Ollie or a Nollie? A Nollie is a bit more impressive. Wow. Speaking
of, Tim Pool. Oh yeah. I already got... You got flamed for this. And I agree. I agree with
the flamers. I... You... Okay, for people who don't know, Patrick went after Tim Pool in
what can only be called kind of an Aspergic rage that you kind of dipped into. Yeah. Where
you all you could think about was how this was not an impressive trick that he was doing.
It's not that it's not that it's not impressive. It's just like shut up. It's it's the type
of trick that like you do if you're the guy trying to like you're like the old guy trying
to impress young kids at the skate. So it's like the thing where you do the you put one
foot under one foot over on an upside down skateboard and then you flip it and you end
No, no, it's not a strawberry milkshake.
Is that what that's called?
Yeah, that's what that's called.
It's not like that.
It's like, I don't know, it's just one of those fucking stupid,
like technical tricks.
The reason that I fucking hate that thing,
the full name of that trick that he does is a hang ten pressure
inward, inward heel flip.
OK. Late flip.
Why is that? Hang ten pressure, inward heel flip, late flip.
That sounds like it would be an amazing combo on Tony Hawk's Pro Skater.
Well, that's no. Why? Because it would have it should have a cooler name. One.
All right. The Tim flip about the Tim flip. Yeah, I guess it's the Tim flip
the pull drop. Yeah, but I don't know. That was just like it's like what?
Like somebody who's never seen skateboarding.
That's amazing. No.
What is making you so mad, bro?
You don't like him because he's bald.
Look, he even does the thing that skaters do where they bitch and moan
because they fell over.
It's just so fucking kooky, dude.
I there's no way that I could.
The thing that I was like mad about is like I can't explain why that sucks to
people.
Then it doesn't suck.
I can't explain why that that why that is the fucking worst thing that you can do.
It's not the worst thing you can do.
It's the worst thing you can do on a skateboard.
You can't do that.
No, I wouldn't want to.
Yeah, that shit, those, it's like a thing that like a YouTuber does.
It's not like... He's a YouTuber.
Yeah. You know what... What are you expecting from fucking Tim Pool, man?
Dude, if he posted literally just like
Kickflip 50/50, something like that, something simple.
Uh-huh. It would show that he has an actual like
understanding of like what makes skateboarding like good,
what people like, like about it.
But people like that. I like that.
I don't even know what this guy...
I just know he's a classical liberal.
I don't know anything about this fucking guy.
Right. And this made you a big fan of his?
Dude, he's the man.
The best game wearer I've ever seen.
Are you kidding me?
I don't know.
Even if he just posted just like him doing a fucking like wall ride or something,
that's like way cooler.
That's way, that's way sicker.
It's about it's about looking cool.
I mean, I will say, you would rather like.
Like what it's like, how fucking like Michael Jordan is like really good at
like what's the thing that everyone talks about him for?
Basketball, he's really good at basketball.
It's not that he like, it's just like the way that he did like dunks and stuff.
He's a high flying acrobatic finisher, greatest finisher of all time.
Exactly, so that's like the equivalent of just doing like one really good like lofty kickflip.
Okay, and so what's the basket, make me understand.
So the basketball equivalent of that is just like just being really good at like
sinking like a free throws all the time.
So if you can do a bunch of tricks
and you can't figure out a way to like make them look good.
Uh huh. There's no fucking point of that.
There's like no point like like the tricks are like, yeah, cool.
You like you can do fucking tricks like you can do tricks in your mom's backyard.
So you're saying that was not you can't take it to the streets
or the parks or whatever.
It's fucking bullshit.
Okay, so this is the equivalent of like maybe shoot like shooting half court
shots or something. And okay, all right, that's what it is. It's a half court
shot. Yeah, because guys will go to the white guys will go to the basketball
court when there's nobody there and shoot half court shots and make one out
of five and be like exactly and post a video of it. You know, Tommy, Tommy
Bear, Tommy Bear did that.
Tommy, we got your fucking ass.
But then if you go and you're playing 5 on 5
He also skates
Yeah, so he should understand this
And yet here he is posting half court shot videos
But anyway, it's the difference between doing that and then going and playing a game
And you have to do real stuff
Alright, I kind of understand that
That's why it sucks so much shit
Alright, you convinced me
I mean I'm still going to have to do a little more research
and watch maybe 40 or 50 ten pool videos
and kind of see what else you got going on.
I hear he's a rocker too.
- Yeah, he is a complete rocker.
- He looks like a rocker.
He's got a rock star hair.
I like that.
He looks good, man.
- Yeah, I'm gonna look like that in a couple years.
Yeah, I'm gonna look like that in a couple years.
- You kind of have the same eyes.
- We kind of have the same thing.
It is making me think.
- It kind of looks just like him, the more I look at it.
- It's kind of making me think
that I maybe should start hitting the gym or something.
You have a little better of a beard than he does though.
Yeah, he's got a shit beard.
Yeah, he's got a really bad one.
Shaving this off is maybe the worst decision I've ever made.
Shaving the mustache off.
It grew back in like four days.
Yeah, but it wasn't as... I looked at a photo of it from like...
the... like two weeks before I shaved it.
Dude, I had like... I almost was able to... I could have done the twirls.
You need to do a mustache competition.
Mm-hmm.
You need to do that.
We gotta do Movemba.
We need to do Movemba.
Hopefully it'll be back to where it was by then.
I'll do Movember this year. I won't shave my head or my face.
Yeah.
See what happens.
Well, I'm not going to shave. This is like, I think that that's an institution on my face now.
Wow.
I think that it's...
I do agree. I think that you, your face works much better with a mustache.
Oh, absolutely. It matches my eyebrows.
They're the same.
It's symmetry down here and there.
It's not really symmetry.
It's symmetrical if I have it like this.
You're, if you, this is not any, this is not anything.
I get surgery to look like this?
You kind of look like animalistic muskrat like.
So yeah, that'd be good.
Would you ever get those surgeries that that Mormon guy gets?
The blood boy?
He has a blood boy?
Does he get surgery?
gets like, well he's taking Brian, Brian, fuck, Callan.
No. Yeah, I would get surgery to look exactly like Brian. Yeah.
Yeah. Just walking into a fighter and the kid trying to just like
can convince them to start it up again. Yeah. Hey, well, he works
for Steven Crowder now. Oh, really? Yeah, yeah. Oh my god.
Shob or Callan? Callan works for Steven Crow. Oh, wow. Pretty awesome, right? Yeah. You remember
it was Brian Callan, Will Sasso, and Chris D'Elia had a podcast. I remember. Yeah. I never
watched it. They were all big on Vine. Chris D'Elia's Vine account was just him filming
people in public and going, "Um, excuse me, sir. You look weird." Yeah. And that, dude,
he blew up from that. Didn't he make that one that was like him on the stairs and someone
walks by and he records it. I don't even remember what he says but it's like some lady on the
phone. I think that's Chris D'Elia. Oh the guy on the stairs and the lady says they were
roommates? No that's not Chris D'Elia. Who's that? He was like some photographer. His Vine
account was crazy. He was like... Oh yeah that's not him. It kind of looked like him though.
Kind of could have been crystal. Yeah, I can see that. But that dude's vine account was
just all videos of him like giving like little kids tasers and shit. That's funny. Yeah. He's
a photographer. Yeah, he's just like a terrorist more than a think he maybe was a terrorist.
Well, he maybe wasn't me. I think now that I'm thinking about it, I think he was an active
member of ISIL. It was ISIL at the time. I remember this when they turned ISIS to ISIL
and I had an English teacher. It was my freshman year of college.
I'm still calling him Isis.
Not English? Yeah, dude. Fuck it.
I had an English 103 teacher.
Yeah.
Because I was in advanced English, just so you guys know.
Place 10 to it.
Yeah, it's pretty awesome.
A plus, by the way.
But I was in advanced English.
Got an amazing grade, right?
What is the point of the story?
What was I talking about?
ISIL. ISIL.
ISIL versus ISIS.
So amazing grades, great writer.
and then we had this professor who was it was like the day where they were like
it's called ISIL now and he basically cried. No, he was like he was like
the one teacher who was obsessed with ISIL.
He was like
first of all, I remember him saying like
this is like when Jefferson Airplane turned to Jefferson Starship and I was
like that's that's fire. I'll remember that for the rest of my life.
But then he also said that ISIL means in some language, I don't know what the language mostly.
I think you should, I think you should, I leave.
I sink, I sink, I leave.
There we go.
That's me on the pool table.
But he basically explained that the word ISIL sounds like a word in their language.
No, it sounds like a word in English, the asshole.
Well, yes, but he explained that it sounds like a word in their language that basically
means like gay bastard.
So that was, it was done as a way to kind of clown them and it worked.
You don't hear much about ISIL anymore.
No, the CIA stopped them.
Really?
Yeah, they were like, uh.
I don't really know what they became.
Yeah.
Well, there's people who believe that the CIA created ISIS.
I don't know.
I don't care.
I don't know if I, yeah.
is if the CIA controls fucking everything, I can't do anything about that, man. I'm not
even going to try to think about it.
We're going to podcast so people know the truth. No, we don't. Who's listening to us?
The people who are obsessed with that kind of stuff are basically the same people who
make four-hour YouTube videos about Warhammer 40,000 lore. It doesn't matter. Who gives
a shit?
That's exactly they are making too lazy to try videos about like Epstein.
You've been obsessed with too lazy to try huh?
Oh yeah.
That guy makes great videos.
Dude that Jay Moore Bert Kreischer beef video.
So funny dude.
So good.
That whole fucking story is so...
It's so funny to make up a story and then have it stolen from you and be like well...
I was lying the whole time.
It's actually my story.
Making up a story about Tracy Morgan too.
Who is just another guy who is also in your same line of work that you're going to run
and then two all the time and make up a story that makes him seem fucking crazy.
And he smoked PCP.
Whoa.
Yeah, okay, you're just telling everyone that fucking Tracy Morgan smokes PCP at a strip
club.
Burt Crusher.
Burt Crusher, this you burn notice.
We're gonna take you out, fool.
I've been saying this for fucking years.
I've been stealing the machine from you.
He literally has.
I'm not kidding, he's been doing the machine on stage.
I have been doing the machine on stage.
It doesn't do very well.
It bombs every time.
It bombs.
Nobody knows what he's talking about.
No one knows what I'm talking about. I'm doing the machine and it's not working.
You pay your audience to make that work.
And also, you should have come up with a better story.
If you're going to make up a story, put a dragon in it, asshole.
Well, he put a machine.
The best thing you can come up with is that you hung out in Russia on a train.
You know who hangs out in Russia on trains? Upskirters.
That's right.
Yeah. You know what the real story of the machine was, Bert? You were on a train. You had mirrors
on your shoes. And the lady or whoever, the train conductor or somebody was like, "Blah
blah blah." And he said, "I'm in the mafia!" "I'm a machine! I'm a machine! He's covered
in mirrors." "I'm a machine mafia!" "He's covered in mirrors." He's trying to say he
He is the Tin Man.
Yeah, he's trying to say he's the Tin Man so that he stops getting caught upskirting.
So they're like, "Oh, he has no sexual desire because he's a machine.
He's a robot.
Robots think in the only ones and zeros.
And that's not the penis and vaginas."
When they think of ones and zeros, they're not thinking about putting a one in the zero
in the hole.
That might be if Andy Warhol was still with us, may he rest in peace.
I think that's maybe an art piece he would do.
Yeah.
A penis, a vagina.
A one going into a zero.
Well no, just a bunch of, like a line of code.
Uh huh.
Or a line of binary.
A line of code that looks like sex.
That's all ones and zeros.
Yeah.
But it's penises and maybe even, I mean he would probably do asshole.
And then there's two ones touching and then two zeros touching to represent gays and lesbians
and then other people who have those parts or whatever.
And then a zero with a one strapped to it.
(laughter)
- Yeah, that's a good idea.
That's an amazing idea.
Maybe a one with two zeros underneath.
- Yeah. - Balls style.
- Dick and balls.
- Balls style is what they would call that.
That's pretty much all the permutations.
- Yeah, that's all you could do.
I mean, yeah, 'cause it's all numbers.
You can't really represent every single person.
I'm thinking about the zero with the one strapped onto it.
And this is becoming one of the best ideas I've ever heard.
And I think that you need to draw this.
- Yeah, I could draw it right.
I got a pencil.
I'll draw it on the table.
- That's only half the battle, buddy.
- I'll draw it on the table.
- The table is not paper.
No, you don't need to draw.
- I can get a piece of paper.
- No, no, no, you're leaving me?
Just fucking do it later.
I wanna see like an Adobe Illustrator version of this.
- I gotta make the sketch first.
So it's just.
- So it's a zero, okay.
And the zero is pink. It's going to be pink.
See, that's just got to be like a, that kind of just looks like Rick and Morty.
There's another zero here.
Wait, why? Oh, okay. And then I guess you need like a belt buckle strap.
Yeah. It's going to go up the zero. Okay.
And then the strap underneath to support. Uh-huh. And there we go.
What was it called again?
I don't even remember how we got here.
We were talking about ones and zeros, it would be penises.
Oh yeah, this is a zero with a one strapped to it.
Hey, I have a question for you.
I've been asking everybody this question.
I think you might have a pretty insightful answer.
Okay.
Here's the hypothetical.
Got it.
Okay.
You are, you die, right?
Oh.
Just let that sit.
That's pretty powerful stuff already.
You die.
You go to heaven.
Actually, I have two.
Okay.
I'll tell you the one that I just thought of now.
Okay, well tell me after the first one, because then I can see how you got to the second one.
No, no, I'll tell you this one first, because I realize the other one doesn't have anything
to do with dying or what happened.
But this is also not a hypothetical, this is a what if.
A what if is our hypothetical.
I like trap, but it's not a question, it's just a what if.
What if you got to, my cousin told me this, my cousin Matthew that you met, he brought
this up one day.
He wrote Vanilla Ice Cream.
He's also a Vanilla Ice Cream guy.
He said, "What if you got to heaven," this blew my mind, "What if you got to heaven
and the clouds part to reveal God, and instead of God being a human man, a big human man,
God is like a Ford F-150, and God reveals to you that actually cars were the people
the whole time and people were just cars, and they just needed us to turn them on to
get them around. But in reality, we don't have any souls. We don't even barely exist.
We're just a vessel to make cars move.
We are just vessels that need to get gas and put gas in the cars and we need to make the
cars.
We need to invent the car.
So that's the other thing. It's an alternate history. Well, before cars...
This is Transformers.
No, but no. No. Before cars were people, horses were people.
And then before horses, it didn't even exist. The world wasn't even, it's all made up.
Yeah.
But really cars were just people.
Before horses it was fish with legs.
Yeah, we'll say that. Yeah, before horses it was fish with legs.
And so on and so forth.
But so, is that not, does that not make you think about this, all this global warming
bullshit a little differently?
Well, I don't drive. I don't know how to drive.
Yeah, so you are like basically the bottom, most useless kind of thing.
I'm not going to heaven.
Yeah, I'm not going to heaven at all.
Because cars, you have never helped a car.
I've turned my mom's car on when I was younger to get the AC started.
Okay, that's actually fine then.
Yeah.
That's actually, that's a helpful good deed.
I mean, I know how to turn a car on.
I know how to back it up, but I mean, once you get me on the road, I don't, I can't.
You know how to back up a car but not make it go forward?
No.
You need to be driving in backwards, reverse vision.
Maybe I gotta get a reverse car.
It's just an idea.
Yeah.
But that's the first what if.
hypothetical is this, would you rather be a hand or a foot, but you don't get to pick
whose hand or foot you are. So you don't get to be like Dua Lipa's foot. You have to say,
I'm going to be a hand or I'm going to be a foot. I just made up a name. Is that a person?
Yeah.
Well, I didn't fucking know.
From what I know, from what I don't know much about her, I think that she is maybe like the
prime minister of Albania. Let's see who's this? Dua Lipa's feet. Yeah, those are pretty
ugly I'm going to be honest. Her feet kind of look like she has, they look like a very
overweight person's feet. Does that make sense? Can you lose weight in your feet? You know
You know how people say your face is the last thing that gets skinny when you lose weight?
You know what, when I was like, I mean maybe I just, no, you know what I'm thinking?
I think maybe I just grew.
But I was a size 10 and a half in shoes until I got to college and I gained a bunch of weight.
Now I'm up to like an 11, 11 and a half.
Ok, back to my question.
Would you rather be a foot or a hand?
No choice on who's hand or foot.
Probably a hand because I could pick up pencils. I could get all up in them guys.
Here's the thing, you are just sitting there. It's basically you're a face where everything
just gets shoved into your face.
Like I'm a vegetable.
You are not in control.
So it's like I'm completely awake.
Yes, you're a sentient hand attached to a person.
the person controls my every move. So if you're a hand, you already chose hands so you're locked
in. Yeah, but feet, feet you're in. You're a wiping ass and buddy, I've wiped my asshole
before and I've missed, the toilet paper's in the wrong place, poop on my finger. I've
picked up every disgusting fucking thing in the world. Yeah, that's true. I've touched
the tongues of tons of animals at zoos that have been eating disgusting slop. Yeah. Right?
I jack my off. I jack my off. Every other day I jack my off. I touch my bees. I touch them.
I touch my bees and I jack my off. Every other day at least. I sit on the couch, right? I
sit on the couch, I rewatch Girls, I hold my bees.
So you just front of the pants?
I grab them from the back. I go around. So here's the problem, if you're my height, I
go through.
but you're not you're not just touching you're touching the the tea as well as
the bees. I credit card through my cheeks
above my tea,
grab the bees.
No pee. No pee, can't even reach the pee. I don't have enough arm slack to
reach the pee at that point, but I've credit carded all the way through my
bee and my tea to grab my double bees. Yeah. So that's the argument against
the hand. Okay, but then shoe
is a big part of the equation.
What kind of shoe is it?
What's the thing?
What's the job?
Sometimes it's work shoes.
Sometimes you get a real uncomfortable pair of loafers.
Most people just immediately say hand,
but you start thinking about this.
Yeah.
And it's a really hard fucking question.
At least with shoes,
you know,
I mean, have you ever broken a toe?
The thing is about breaking a toe
is that I think I've broken my toe,
but it's I feel like
If you go to the hospital for a broken toe, you're a baby.
- Yeah.
- So I don't actually know.
- Did I ever show you, I broke my toe skating.
I was out like skating all day.
Was like, oh, that's weird.
It's weird that my like toe hurts.
Walked around on it all day, was kind of limping.
And then went to a party,
like an event for the Jenkum magazine.
I was on a dance floor, people were stepping on my feet.
- Okay.
- I went home, my toe was completely purple.
- You had a purple toe.
- Do you remember my purple toe?
- No.
- Do you remember I was limping for a while?
- You have been limping at various,
probably every six months you limp for a couple weeks.
- Yeah.
- Since I've known you.
- Yeah, that's true.
- You hurt yourself pretty often.
- Yeah.
But usually it's minor hurts.
- I was thinking of it, like since I lost my healthcare,
I've been thinking about my mortality a lot more.
- Yeah.
- I've been thinking about just like--
- It's so scary to die.
- Dude, I have been going through life with just like,
like, oh, fuck it, I got healthcare, I'll fucking, yeah,
I'll just go to the doctor.
I can't go to the doctor now.
- You can't, you also, the doctor can't save you.
- No, I can't do shit.
I used to, I fucking, I fall down,
sprain my wrist or something.
I go to a doctor, pay them $600 to say, put ice on it.
Put it above your head.
So the swelling goes down.
I used to pay them $600 even after co-pay.
Even after the--
- And now it'd be a couple grand at least.
- Yeah, they're already covering,
the insurance is already covering
the $3,000 of the $36,000.
I haven't had insurance in a very long time.
Yeah.
I had it for six months and then I lost it again.
I used to have a very bad healthcare plan.
Really?
My very bad dental plan.
That's why my teeth are so fucked up.
I think I'm going to get on Obamacare.
But the problem with the ACA is you Google Obamacare and every single page is just like
Trying to get an old person to click on it.
So that you go...
It's like Obamacare free iPhone.
And I'm not smart, so I say, "Oh, you get a free iPhone for signing up."
"Oh my God, an iPhone 3G!"
One of these Obama phones.
Yeah, exactly. And then I sign up and now I...
I have two emails that I can't even use them anymore.
Because there's so many Obamacare things.
Obamacare things and they're also sending you free Sony camcorder.
Yeah, exactly.
It's like, "Oh my God, this Obamacare..."
I'm going to buy every single time. I'm going to buy every fucking time.
I had an old email when I was younger that I used specifically to try and sign up for
those things because I thought like, well, what if it goes through? What if I do get
my free Sony HD camcorder that shoots in 720p?
Oh my God, Sony Handycam? Dream.
if I do get it, then I can start my YouTube career.
You're right man. I really wish now that I had been a probably a famous YouTuber.
Yeah. Like a Ryan Higa?
Could have been Ryan Higa, could have been Kev Jumba.
Could have been Timothy DeLaGhetto.
Wasn't motivated enough to be Timothy DeLaGhetto.
Yeah.
As a kid I would film videos and never edit them. They would just sit there on my computer
forever raw footage of me and my little brother making fart noises or whatever. And that was
it man.
I got a couple of the old YouTube sketches I made when I was like 15.
Yes, I've seen these actually.
Yeah, I got a couple of old ones sitting around.
Yeah, you got to get those off the computer. Yeah, they come up when you search your name.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh no.
They have comments from people who listen to the podcast.
Oh, I haven't looked at it. I don't look at it ever.
It's pretty funny.
Yeah, yeah, how which ones the one where you are running for president? Oh Jesus that one has some
That one has some
Pretty good. Hey pretty good editing for a 17 year old
Actually, I was yeah, 17 year old is one year away from being a full-grown adult. So yeah, it's fine
There it is at the year ahead with dr. Patrick Doran and Gary Wilson Gary Wilson this singer
I don't think so. I would imagine not the singer this guy looks nothing like me
Okay, final answer, hand or foot?
Probably foot because I'm into that.
Okay, would you rather be... that's fine, that's a completely okay answer.
Would you rather be hair?
Would I rather be hair and then the rest of my body is a person?
No, we're not doing reverse person.
Would you rather be hair or food?
Hair.
Okay, would you rather be hair?
Well, because even if you shave, they're still like, like if I'm like hair on like
I would, I would be the hair above the ear because unless the person,
oh, so every, my whole body is hair.
Whole body hair.
Okay. Then yeah, because I mean, you can, you, it's not like they're the person
who...
But you go through it, but...
You go through a lot of changes.
You experience great pain.
Yeah. But food, you get food, you're around for like, you have the life cycle of a
fly. You're around for a week.
Yeah, so this is the argument for food.
Food, you have a short life, but you're beautiful,
you're appreciated.
Hair--
- Hair, you're also appreciated.
- You're getting constantly,
depends on the person.
Hair, you're getting constantly--
- Oh wait, a woman's hair.
And not like a--
- And a woman's food.
- Okay, I'm a woman's hair versus a woman's food.
- So they only eat half of it.
- Yeah.
So I'm like a can of sardines.
- Yeah, something like that.
Some almonds, four or five almonds.
Four or five almonds, a can of sardines, some of these like...
But with hair you experience intense, great pain.
Yeah.
Off... Okay, here's another one.
Would you rather be food or a human?
What kind of human?
Just any... I mean you, yourself.
Yeah. Would I rather be food or myself?
Would you rather be food or would you want nothing to change in your life at all right now?
What kind of food?
It's random.
Is that like a type of fish?
It is random.
Okay.
So you could be Indian food.
So okay, if I was, okay, yeah, so I'm a meal.
Would you rather be Indian food or you?
What dish?
Am I like a chicken dildar?
Am I like a...
Don't go for a deep cut when you're...
Don't say chicken dildar.
Say chicken tikka masala, say butter chicken.
That's all you can say.
can say. Okay, I like Chicken Dildar the best though. That's my favorite Indian dish. Fuck
you. It's got pineapples in it. Sounds good. Yeah, it's actually. Is there pineapples in
India? Well, I think this is maybe an American dish. Oh, God. An Indian-American dish. I
hate Americanized things. Ah, some of them. General Tso. Okay, here's the thing that I
learned. What? About. Apparently, well, I've been calling it General Gow's my whole life.
Oh, it's grown abundantly. I've been calling it General Gow's my whole life. I call it
General Joes. General Joes, okay. Shout out Trader. General Gow, apparently local to, like,
that's a thing people in New England say because I was like, oh yeah, can I, I was talking to
my girlfriend, I was like, oh can I just get like a, we were doing an Uber Eats, can I
just get like a thing of General Gows? Yeah, I've never heard of General Gows. She was
like, what the fuck are you saying? Everyone else calls it General So's. Yeah. Do you know
why it's called General Gows? No, and I looked it up, the only answer was, you're probably
some fucking idiot from New England who says that. And I was like, huh, let me get one
of those.
Last one. My lucky. You can't take my luckies in.
I know, I'm not taking your luckies in. But yeah, I didn't know that that's a regional
thing. Also, it's just the stupidest regional thing because it's... I don't even think that's
pronounced that way.
What, General Gal?
Yeah. T-S-O?
ESO? No, it's definitely, no, no, no. This means that some,
there's gotta be some chain. My guess is some chain in New England.
Maybe Kowloon? Maybe Kowloon or something like that.
Cause my dad's called it that his whole life. My mom's called it that his whole life.
And I've heard... My mom works at a Chinese restaurant. They call it that.
Yeah. I've, I've definitely heard that before. Uh,
but I've never ordered it and I always assumed it was a different thing.
But my guess is that there was some chain that was,
they called it General Gow's.
- Yeah, like back in the 50s when Chinese food
was starting to pop off.
- Yeah, it was probably called like Mr. Gow's or whatever,
so they named it after the mascot.
- Yeah.
- And then everybody just started calling it that shit.
- In New England only.
- In New England only, yeah.
- But I've like said, like, oh, can I get General Gow's
at like places around here?
And they still give it to me.
- Wait, maybe you're more authentic.
Maybe it actually is originally General Gow's.
maybe the rest of the world got tricked
and New England is the only bastion of hope for the truth here.
New England is the only bastion of hope for Chinese people.
Especially Boston. Boston is one of the most Chinese friendly places in the world.
Oh yeah, people in Boston, are you kidding me? The most open and accepting people.
They actually are. Yeah, they did have gay marriage first.
Yeah, Boston is kind of, for better or for worse, become essentially the woke capital
of America.
Yeah.
Tied with San Francisco, of course.
Two cities that I do like.
I was a block away.
You like San Francisco?
Well, I went back after, the first time we went there, we were only there for 24 hours.
I went to visit my girlfriend when she was out there.
And it was actually fucking sick.
Yeah, it's beautiful.
It's so...
It's very great.
why those tech people really wanted to fucking destroy that city with their stupid little
like self-driving cars and shit. I almost got hit by one of those.
Yeah, it was the tech people and not the drug addicts, Patrick.
I support drug addicts.
What?
And I support graffiti and skateboarding.
What? The fuck are you talking about? No, a city should be grey buildings with big,
big...
Brutalist architecture?
Big windows.
Uh-uh.
little windows. Yeah, little window, big gray concrete buildings, little tiny
windows, central air, right? Okay. I think that we can both agree on that.
Central air is amazing. Central air, so good. There should be, and I don't want
to have a key for my door. I want the entire... I want an RFID chip in my wrist
that I go, "Peep!" Or I want a code that if I forget, I have to move. Yeah. This
is not my house anymore because I forgot my code. And you can't ask the landlord
for the code. I don't he doesn't know it. Because yeah you made the code. Yeah exactly. And you
were like I'm going to make it. I lost my password wallet. I'm going to make it funny.
I'm going to make a funny number. Yep I made it funny. I made it funny because when you
look at the code upside down. Which you can't because you'd have to turn the entire door
upside down or the world upside down. Do you ever sit and look at the stars? No I don't
do that. Never. No. Not my thing. Have you ever done that? I honestly. You ever lay down
in the grass and looked up at the stars?
I like the city more. I like to look at a building.
You'd rather look at a building than the stars?
Yeah.
Well here, I'm about to change your mind.
Okay.
I'm about to blow your mind.
Stars are the buildings of the sky?
Well, just next time you should go lay down on the ground and look up at the stars and
think about how the world, the entire earth is moving so fast through space and it's kind
of like you're on the front of it, right? And you're like kind of holding on and you
be like, "Ahhhh!" and you're like shooting through. Is that kind of fun?
It is fun. It is good.
Huh? Well, I can't do it. Yeah, do it right now. Pretend that you're like looking, like
you're holding on to the front of a semi-truck in a Mad Max movie. "Ahhhh!" Yeah, so you
go and you do that.
That's pretty good.
And it's kind of fun.
Yeah.
I would highly recommend that.
Yeah, it's not bad. That's not a bad thing to do.
You're not a stargazer.
No.
Hmm.
I like to look at, I don't know.
I don't know what I, there's...
What's the most beautiful nature you've ever seen?
Have you ever seen anything beautiful?
I did.
Have you ever been touched?
You know what it was?
The Grand Canyon, yeah.
That was like a...
We just talked last week about how you didn't care about it.
Well, no.
I saw, like seeing the people, like enjoy it, made me enjoy it.
Yeah.
a really tall part of San Francisco and I like that too.
The tall part of San Francisco?
The tall part.
There was this one spot we went to that overlooked the whole city and I was like oh shit that's
cool.
Yeah.
I was touched by that.
You were touched by that?
That's still a city right?
It makes me mad thinking about how I could never live there.
In San Francisco?
It's so nice there.
Dude, it's not nice.
It's really nice.
It's insanely expensive.
expensive. Well, that's the thing. If it was cheap, they have the craziest homeless people
in America. Yeah, I could get along with them. You could not get along with them. I get it.
Remember when we were in Portland and there was the guy walking down the street swinging
chains? Yes. That's like every and we went we crossed the street. But the guy who said
you ever seen someone get fucked up by a machete. That was a different guy. That's what I mean.
Oh yeah. Those are two different guys. I don't remember the chain man. There's a guy walking
down the bridge swinging chains like this.
Was he walking towards us?
Yeah, and then we crossed the street and we thought it would be kind of funny if he was
like, "Whoa dude, you guys crossed the street?"
What the fuck is that?
Kind of racist.
I forgot about the chain, man.
Yeah, he was like swinging chains, shirtless guy, tattered clothes.
Battered bros.
Yeah, swinging chains.
That's what every day, as far as I know.
I mean I've been watching my favorite skateboarder Tim Pool talking about San Francisco.
The thing that I remember the most about Portland was, I mean we were just day drunk the whole
time we were there.
Oh yeah, I'm doing, people who listen to beers we drink know that I'm doing groggless ogless.
Oh, ok.
No grog.
No grog at all?
No grog at all this og.
Uh huh.
That's why I didn't go to the bar last night, no grog.
Wow.
They have an A, they have a hoppy refresher there.
I love that thing!
That's my favorite thing to drink.
When I was sober for six months, that's what I would drink all the time.
Poppy refresher, that thing's good.
I would be drinking, I was still drinking like the same amount of beer.
You're binge drinking NA beers.
That's what I was doing, yeah.
And I was...
I'll have a six pack of NA beers, it's like 500 calories.
What are they putting in Heineken Zero?
They're putting just X-Lax in that.
That does make you, well that means...
It makes you shit like green...
Does normal beer make you shit green goo?
Depends.
Depends on the type.
I mean if I have like a bunch of Narragansetts, yeah.
I would love to get to become a part of your gut microbiome.
Yeah?
You want to see what goes on in there?
I bet it looks like the day after tomorrow.
In the city that is your gut, everything's on fire, tornadoes are ripping everything
out of the place.
You need to do an elimination diet.
that where you eliminate all food.
Oh, and I just do juice like, uh, no.
Remember when 50 Cent did that?
He went on a completely liquid diet for that movie about that dude with cancer.
He got really skinny and nobody liked the fucking movie.
Yeah.
The movie was bad.
That would suck so bad.
You're sitting there.
That photo, imagine you gained 300 pounds to play a part.
And then you're just like sitting there watching the reviews come in.
It's like, you're wearing a CPAP machine while you're awake.
in every review. It's got a 44 on Rotten Tomatoes. It's just like...
Well, that's kind of good.
Three out of ten, three out of ten, three out of ten, five out of ten.
That's just remarkably average.
See, but then you don't even get the fun.
I'm saying like a two and a half.
But if you get one of the greatest bombs of all time, that even has a novelty to it.
Yeah, that's true.
I'm like, "Oh, that's funny."
Or just like the most mid movie.
Yeah, just a shitty movie.
And you're like, "Oh, I gained like a bajillion pounds."
Yeah, that's got to suck, man.
I gained a bajillion pounds so that I could play Norbit's brother.
You see the thing that Mack from Always Sunny did where he would drink ice cream to gain
weight?
You were doing something like that.
Well I do that already.
Something that ruins ice cream for you?
You drink ice cream?
I drink ice cream.
I will say when I get a bowl of ice cream, I swirl it around and make it melt a little
bit.
Not all the way.
Yeah, it's got to be a little soft.
Yeah, I don't want hard ice cream dude.
I'm not a penguin.
I don't like ice like that.
Penguins I don't think eat ice.
What do penguins eat?
Do you know anything about animals?
Do I know anything about it?
Do you know anything about penguins specifically?
Because I had a very important question.
Ask me a question.
What do penguins eat?
Fish.
Oh, they do.
Yeah. You know what?
They can fucking swim.
And they sit and they do the they feed their kids like
they vomit into their kids mouths.
Hmm. And they eat little silver fish.
Yeah. All right.
Well, that answers that question.
Any other animal facts that you'd like to know?
But I'm more, I know about raccoons.
Yeah.
And possums.
They like hot dogs.
Raccoons like hot dogs.
According to one video I've seen.
They have weird opposable thumbs.
Possums.
I think, I mean you can own, how long do raccoons live?
I think they live.
They live like pretty long.
They live much longer.
Possums only live about 18 months.
Yeah, possums are born to die.
Yeah.
That's kind of sick.
It's kind of crazy 'cause they're so,
rats are like that too, they die really young.
Raccoons, I'm going to guess, oh, three years, that's it?
Oh, in the wild.
In captivity, a raccoon can live up to 20 years.
Wow.
Why does anything have to die?
That's a good question.
What about why can't we just live forever?
Wait, wait, wait, go back.
How long has Pinch Raccoon been around?
How old is this one?
How old is this raccoon?
When were they?
I think this raccoon is maybe pretty young.
Well, she's the same age as Jelly Otter.
OK, well, how old is Jelly Otter, I guess?
That's a good. It is so crazy how Oh, Universal Orlando. You're not buying
tickets to Orlando. Well, hold on now. Listen, do I want to go? Yes, it is
crazy that if you want to go on like the Disney wiki or like any of these
wiki is just just a billion ads. Yeah, they should. They should be running the
same. If you have a wiki, you have a wiki about one on one. If you have a
wiki,
Same operation as Jimmy Wales.
You got to be asking for donations.
Why does Wikipedia not?
I would rather have fucking ads on Wikipedia
than have this fucking big sob story every three months.
Yeah. Shut the fuck up.
Jimmy Wales. Shut up, bro.
I don't care. Yeah.
You have backed.
I'm sorry that you backed yourself into this corner
where everybody depends on your website so, so much.
You can't even keep it up that you can't keep it up.
like there's so much traffic going to it that you can't keep it up, you can't pay for it.
That's not my fucking problem, right? I want to read about...
I'm taking my ass to Encyclopedia if you don't knock it off.
Exactly, yeah. I'm trying to read the behind the scenes section of the Brown Bunny Wikipedia.
I don't care about you need me to pay you $2. And also why is... the options go way too
high.
Uh-huh.
The options go down...
One thousand?
Yeah. Who's giving $1,000 to Wikipedia?
Probably the editors.
Because they work there?
Would you give a thousand dollars to your job?
No.
No, I would not give this fucking place a thousand dollars.
I don't want to do that.
Me neither.
No.
There's no world where I'd do that.
I was reading the director of Brown Bunny, Vincent Gallo, held such a grudge over Roger
Ebert saying that Buffalo 66 or Brown Bunny...
But they secretly liked each other, I heard.
Yeah?
Yeah.
They had a mutual respect.
but when he died he said some crazy shit. I wish I remembered exactly what it was.
But that was just him being funny.
Yeah.
Well that's nice.
It's actually nice.
It's nice that he said that you died with no jaw you gay bitch or something.
It was something along those lines.
Yeah.
I will say...
That's what Bam Margera... when Roger Ebert died, Bam Margera went crazy on him.
Dude, if I just...
A lot of people! A lot of people went crazy on Ebert once he died.
Tough talk once a man's dead.
Yeah.
Because I bet you couldn't look him in the face and say that.
You'd laugh.
but yeah, you look, you look Roger Ebert in his face. He looked back at you like
this,
like, "Oh my God, he's so surprised at what I said." At least close his mouth,
bro.
Like, just fucking, why does it have to be fucking open? I don't understand.
Why do you have to... He's got this little jelly jaw, just fucking sit
there just like...
He doesn't need to be in a permanent state of awe. Yeah. You do not need to
have him be... They could have put a piece of tape that...
like, you know, connected his bottom lip to the top one.
Just do that, man.
Just tape it.
Don't let that motherfucker hang like that.
That is disgusting.
If I, yeah, man, if I'm ever in that situation, man.
If I lose my whole jaw to cancer.
I just want to die.
Just, yeah, it's a flat, or at least do that so it'll look, I can go like this.
Yeah.
And it'll look funny.
Give me a permanently, don't make me look scary, man.
Yeah, make me look funny.
Oh God, they really, I mean that must have been some kind of experimental surgery.
He would wear turtlenecks all the time too.
That's not helping.
Yeah, it doesn't help at all.
You ever seen that show, Spitting Image?
Uh-uh.
Oh yes, yeah.
The British thing, yeah.
No, fucking, God damn it dude.
What, British comedy?
Leo made fun of me so hard for that.
Because you're an Anglo comedy fan?
Yeah.
Yeah, you do know all the Anglo comedy.
You made fun of me because I know the co-creator of Mr. Bean's name.
That is crazy. That is actually crazy.
What? It's like, you know, like Mr. Bean's funny.
You'll know this. What was the one special they did where it was like a ghost thing and they pretended it was real?
What are you talking about? Mr. Bean?
No, not Mr. Bean, man.
It was like a channel 4 or whatever.
They did like a real ghost investigation special and pretended it was live.
Back in the day?
Yeah.
How long ago?
In like 2000, late 90s.
Probably don't know it.
But it was actually really scary as fuck.
And they got like a bunch of people calling the police and saying ghosts were real.
Was it a comedy program?
No.
Then I don't know it.
It was supposed to be mildly satirical.
Have you ever seen any, you know how they do those,
they do like the mentalist specials in the UK?
Where they'll have a guy who like,
- Who points at something and is like,
"I know your father."
- It's kind of stuff like that.
- "Your father's trying to talk to you."
- They do stuff like that, but then they also do like,
there's one where a guy plays Russian roulette on live TV.
- No way.
- It's cool.
They do way cooler TV in the UK, man,
because they don't have any money.
- Well, all they have is fucking quiz programs.
Yeah, they don't have the big mouth writers.
It must be so easy to be a fucking comedian in England.
OK, that must be so that's that's absurd.
Why do you say this?
There's four TV channels.
Right. If you don't get your show on one, that's the other three.
But that there's no programs.
There's nothing going on.
That is kind of true.
Yeah, it's not like that.
You don't have the TV real estate being taken up by shows that have been on the air for 40
seasons, because they only ever do three.
Yeah.
Six episodes, three seasons.
It's mostly specials and stuff.
Stuart Lee, old Stuart Lee.
Oh, well he's Scottish, isn't he?
No.
He made fun of Scottish people.
Isn't Scotland part of the UK?
Well, it is, but they don't want to be.
What?
Stuart?
That's Stuart Little.
You're thinking of Stuart Little.
We're talking about Stuart Lee. He's a dry comedian from a different foreign land.
He does a lot of crowd work.
Yeah, so he'll look at somebody and say...
He's exactly like Matt Rife.
He's basically Matt Rife in the UK.
This is not him, man. He's not this fucking...
No, you're thinking of a different...
I know that you're thinking of Stuart Little.
Here's a fun fact. The dad was on A Bit of Fry and Laurie.
Really?
Because he was Hugh Laurie.
British comedy program. It was a program that ran for a couple of seasons. It was a good
show. I've actually never seen it. It's one of those things where it's probably good at
the time but I watch it now and it's like, I don't fucking get it. What are they talking
about? The Chuckle Brothers. Oh a pensioner. Shut up. We watched the Chuckle Brothers and
none of that made any sense. They were saying shit that just made no sense at all. To me,
you. What is that man? I don't know. Those are beloved characters over there. You could
not you would be you'd be castrated if you if you try that shit down on. Well yeah that
but if you talk down on the Chuckle Brothers you go you talk shit about the Chuckle Brothers
over there they're fucking they are they are dragging you through the street. The Bobbies
are going to look away. The Bobbies are the people you the only you want to get a red
head coat guard at the palace to break. Don't try to tell them, "Hickory dickory dock,"
the whatever. Don't do dice clay jokes to them. Say, "The Chuckle Brothers aren't funny."
"The Chuckle Brothers are a couple of nonces." They're going to hit you with the bayonet.
Stab, stab, stab. Shoot you while the bayonet's in your body.
Gears of War style.
Gears of War, they're going to do Gears of War fatalities.
They're going to sneak up behind you, Modern Warfare,
the new Modern Warfare game.
MI6, if you even think, they know,
they, like, as soon as you go over to the UK,
MI6 is like, they have your phone tapped,
you have a new SIM card they put in,
you have to get a SIM card at the airport once you get over there.
On that SIM card, there's a program
that if you even text somebody and say like,
"I'm going to go say that the Chuckle Brothers are..."
I'm going to go say the Chuckle Brothers aren't funny.
Your phone explodes.
It'll blow up in your hand.
Blow your hand off.
Like that movie...
Agent Cody Banks with the Mentos.
The movie with Jamie Foxx and the guy from 300.
That I don't remember what it's called.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
The one where...
real gritty movies. Yeah. Remember that era of like 2006 to 2011 where every
every movie was about a guy in prison. Yeah. Trying to get like like he's
talking to a cop who's like, you need to tell us where the bodies are. And he's
like, well, I'm not I'm not telling you where it's not. Gamer is an amazing
movie, but it's not. Gamer has that Bollywood style dance at the end. Gamer
has boobs in it, too. Oh, snap. But every movie it was like a smoke smoke and
Smokin' Aces. Yeah, Smokin' Aces. Every movie in 2007 had that grainy, brownish tinge to
them. It looks like shit. Yeah, they all look really bad. Color grading back then was fucking
insane. It was like bad digital cameras they were shooting on. Yeah, everything looks terrible.
Smokin' Aces, Lucky Number Slevin. Yes, Lucky Number Slevin, exactly. We've talked about
this before. It's like movies that we watched at that age because we were like, "Oh, I watched
like adult movies. I get to watch R-rated movies. I watch R-rated movies. And they were just
fucking terrible. And it's just, yeah, just the most blank, kind of boring, I mean some
of them are sick. My Bloody Valentine 3D. Yeah, like that one. Slither. Slither. Stuff
like that. Fucking, what's the, Smokin' 8, no it was 21 is the one with Kevin Spacey
and that dude from across the universe. It's color graded terribly. It looks bad. All of
those movies look so bad. They put the poop filter on it. Yeah. 2007 they were putting
poop filters on everything because guess what? The recession. The world was going to shit.
They couldn't afford it. That's why the Hurt Locker is so brown. Yeah. Well it's brown because
of the desert. It's actually quite a bright movie. They were outside for most of it. Well
I didn't see it, I'm going to be honest.
I just saw stuff making fun of it.
My elbow done.
Is that Jeremy Renner?
Yes.
Well, good luck to him.
Good luck.
He's been hurt.
He has been in a completely catatonic, vegetative state.
It's actually sad.
He's on, Jeremy Renner, we know that you are on life support right now.
Yep.
You're hooked up.
You're barely holding on, buddy.
You're barely, I mean, I'm worried because there was supposed to be a Hawkeye series and
now I don't think that that is ever going to happen.
I think that Jeremy Renner is not currently knocking on death's door.
Not long for this world.
Same with Jamie Foxx.
They tried to weaken at Bernie's Jamie Foxx and put out a video of him singing, but I'm
not falling for it.
He's dead.
He is dead.
He has passed away.
The fucking conspiracy theories about that though, where it's like his face shape has
totally changed and they're showing like red carpet photos where like the camera is like
really far away.
He's bigger.
His head is way smaller there.
And they put chemicals in his head to make his head big.
Look at how big his head is.
I believe this.
It's like the phone is right here.
It's like, "Hey guys, I'm doing completely okay."
His head is fucking huge here.
And look at this.
I got him, man.
This is him in The Amazing Spider-Man 2.
He's got a weird comb over there.
They changed his hair.
They changed Jamie Foxx's hair.
I believe this shit.
Look at him in Jango, he's wearing a blue suit.
Uh-huh, where's his blue suit now?
Wait, he changed clothes too?
I'm starting to stop believing that he's passed on.
He's dead, they cloned him like Gucci Mane.
They didn't even clone him. They barely made an effort.
Wait, did they clone Gucci Mane?
No, no, Jamie Foxx. They definitely did clone Gucci Mane.
Yeah, Gucci Mane was cloned.
They cloned him in prison.
Yeah.
The real Gucci is stuck in a vat somewhere.
They put him in a vat like Snoke.
There's no doubt in my mind.
Put him in a vat like Snoke.
Well guys, at the end of the month I'm going to be in DC with old Adam Friedland.
And I mean old.
Yeah, he's very old.
This guy is pushing 50.
He is.
It is crazy how old he is.
No one talks about it.
He is 50 or 60 years old.
He looks young, he acts young, don't fall for it.
Good for him how young he looks because he is like fucking decrepit.
He's literally, his fingers fall off sometimes.
Yeah.
Yeah, when we're sitting in the hotel.
August 24th through the 26th, we're going to be in DC.
Go to his website for some details.
- Do you have any other,
oh, we haven't planned the shareholders meeting.
- We'll figure that out.
- Yeah, I have no standup dates.
- Big surprise.
- Well, last month I did.
- Last month you did.
- Mm-hmm.
I'm going to start, you can see me at the skate park.
I'm getting back into it.
- What skate park's you going to?
- Probably Blue Park.
You can see me at Blue Park.
What days do you usually go?
Pretty much every day in the week.
Are you going to go today?
Maybe, no it's going to rain.
It's going to be 10% rain all day, you can skate through that.
Maybe, but I don't want to get my new board wet.
I also bought new bearings.
Pussy.
Buy you a waterproof board.
That's a good idea.
Get a surfboard.
That's a good idea, I should be doing that.
Not a problem.
Alright, bye.
Bye.