(upbeat music)
- All right, we're on.
- This is feeling weird, man.
- We haven't done it just this way in maybe,
I mean, honestly, what is it, two years now?
- Guys, every--
- One year. - Two years.
- One year, it's felt like two years.
- This guy-- - You see that thing
yesterday where it was like one year ago,
that's when Ice Spice's song came out?
- Yeah.
felt like five years ago. What ice by song to me, honestly, ice spices fame
feels like the blink of an eye. Maybe it's because I'm interested in geology.
The how rivers are formed geology and not rocks are formed through water, the
history of prehistoric life. But to me, the prehistory of fame is like it's
less than this. Wow. Well, when you zoom out, when you zoom out of most things,
The universe is what? 10 million years old?
Yeah.
10,000.
So it's 10,000 years old.
Ice Spice's being around for one year is basically the blink of an eye, the flash in a pan.
Wow.
So that's when people say one hit wonder, it's like, yeah, I wonder why.
I wonder if they're going to have another Big Bang.
Exactly.
Wow.
Yeah.
Because again,
And that's rocks and geology and dinosaurs.
Yeah.
Let me, that's if there was a science, maybe the science equivalent of a youth pastor, he
you'd be like, "You guys are all obsessed with these one-hit wonders. Let me tell you
about the real one-hit wonder."
The Big Bang.
Jesus Christ.
There is a science teacher, I think, is it?
Well, this would be more of a guy...
Middle school science teacher.
Yeah, but he was kind of exactly analogous to a youth pastor in that he's at a science
church and he's dressed up as a Christian science teacher.
So what you're proposing is...
And he's sitting on the chair backwards. And you can imagine maybe even just the way that
every youth pastor looks in a meme or video.
So what you're proposing is a, I like this idea, a science church with a science youth
pastor.
Yeah.
And he does all the youth pastor joke meme stuff, but it's for science.
How's everyone doing tonight?
Wow.
Yeah, but they don't have like, they don't have like science class, like they have Sunday
school.
And what's going on?
It's actually...
Let's actually check in, what's going on in everyone's week?
It'd be called the SSS Science Sunday School.
It's less, there's less danger that he would be able...
Saturday because they're not observing the day of the Lord.
The youth science pastor wouldn't be molesting the kids because he has an intimate knowledge
of the human body and he knows how to pleasure himself with the help of another.
Maybe he would have a wife or a husband.
He could be touching and playing with the little frogs.
They're even smaller than a kid.
He feels even more power over us.
Or he's poly too, which is weirder because maybe he's just like...
Poly people are not scientific.
He would be, instead of molesting the kids...
so emotional. They're not doing experiments on the kids. You'd be
doing two experiments on twins psychologically. Yeah, seeing and
physically physically cutting them open, seeing if they have joining them
stuff, conjoining them, joining them, taking them apart, conjoining them
apart, joining every combination, joining them at different parts of the
body, like the foot or the ankle or the hand. If you were joined to your
twin at the bottoms of your feet, that would suck. That would suck. And you
you had to walk on your hands like a long dog, bro. You just invented cat.
Yeah, you just invented girl boy
girl boy, girl,
another one of the difference between this and cat dog is that since the
bottoms of their feet, they would have a huge hole in the middle of their body
with the legs. Well, that's where you could put and you could play basketball
or their
there could be a new sport yeah, but with a moving basket. Oh my God, you
It runs away from you.
This is a great, well, base, it barely runs.
Although you'd probably get pretty good if you were doing that.
They would get really good.
I've seen videos of guys with no arms or legs doing some incredible things.
Yeah, Felipe Nunez got no legs.
I saw a video.
He jumped down the stairs.
I saw a video of a man with no arms breaking a swimming record.
Wow.
And I was like, I would be so...
What was his name, Bob?
I don't think his name was Bob I believe he was Chinese.
Oh a Chinese guy can't be named Bob?
I knew a Chinese guy named Bob.
Me too.
I'm lying.
(sad horn music)
(laughing)
- I feel like when we don't have video,
we're more irresponsible.
- Oh, absolutely.
- You get away with a lot more.
- Get away with 10 times more.
- Right, 'cause there's no, nobody can post a video of it
and say, "Look what this guy said."
- Exactly, yeah.
And nobody's gonna click on a screen recording
of an audio from a podcast.
- Of a Windows Media Player visualizer.
Exactly. Nobody's going to do that shit.
So you can say whatever you want, Pat.
And there's no proof that it's that it's you.
It could be any of us.
Yeah, that's true.
Maybe if we change all of our voices.
That's what I was about to say.
I can pitch you up and you can say whatever.
That's true.
Look what the chipmunk said.
This fucking chipmunk went on this podcast, said something crazy.
You know what I'd like?
This chipmunk said motherfucker.
Chipmunk said motherfucker on this podcast. He's not allowed to do that.
What were you saying?
Um, I have a new, I have a movie for the movie club.
What's the movie club?
There's a new thing.
The movie club is a new thing?
It's free on YouTube.
It's called The Wrong Guy with Dave Foley.
The movie club is free on...
What the fuck is a movie club?
You're just saying, what's the movie club?
You gotta watch it if you wanna be in the movie club.
I don't wanna be in the movie club.
movie club you need to start with this. I'm starting a movie club. Here's the first movie.
Thank you. He said it exactly. He does everything I say. The Wrong Guy, 1997. That is one of
the best movies I've ever seen. We don't have these mid-budget comedies anymore. Yeah, we
do. No, we don't. Yeah, we do. What movie? Blades of Glory. Oh, alright. That was the
last one. Barbon Stargo to Vista Del Mar. That's yeah, I guess that's the second to last one.
No, I'm feeling say Barbon Stargon. What? Barbonheimer. Barbie. Barbonheimer be like.
No, explosion. Explosion. I don't want to be part of your movie club. You don't want
to be part of the movie club. You're kind of you're kind of normie. That's not normie.
That was really Normie. That was hella Normie humor. That was cringe. That was Normie and
cringe? That was not Normie and cringe. That was not Normie and cringe at me. It was Normie
and cringe of you to do a Barbenheimer joke bro. That was so fucking... That was literally
three weeks ago. That's okay. Barbenheimer opening weekend called, they want their joke
back. That actually makes it funnier because it's tragedy plus time. There was no tragedy
That's why Oppenheimer was so funny.
You think there was no tragedy involved with Oppenheimer?
Wait, Cameron just said that. There was no tragedy with nuclear bombs,
the big one and the little man.
This is the episode that's going to send us to prison.
Here's hoping that we don't.
I don't want to go to jail.
No, I don't think I would fare very well in prison.
Because all the crap that we've said so far, in this seven minutes.
I am going to I have to today I have to go pay $2,000 to get my fucking car out of the
pound and then I have to ride dirty as certain rap villains would say from
what does that mean because they're taking my license plate off oh so you
I'm gonna tell them that I live at Eric's house cuz he's a driveway they're
gonna drop the car off there and then I'm gonna go move it to somewhere that
is not his house. Yeah, but I have to drive from there. But you wouldn't why
not just tell them the place you want to go in the first place? Yeah, because I
have to basically walk into this parking lot and be like, hey, here, can you can
I pay to have this car park? There's no license plate, right? So you have to you
can't be like, go find a parking spot in this general area. Yeah, yeah. So I have
to do some deception. I have to buy a new license plate. This is gonna be really,
really tough. I have to outsmart a tow truck driver today. That's hard, which I
don't know if you know tow truck drivers. They're pretty smart guys. The
bar for tow truck drivers, like the bar exam.
It's the actual bar. Yeah. It's the actual bar and then there's
also the CDL license that you got to get and then you got to take a class
called trickery 101 at the community college and it's taught by a magician.
They're bastards.
They are real bastards.
They're like mosquitoes.
I'm really not looking forward.
This is going to be, I already know.
Do you ever wake up and you know what is going to be the worst part of your day?
Yeah.
I hate that.
That's when I go to the dentist.
I'm going to the doctor today.
That's how I know that's going to be the worst part of my day.
That's going to be easily the worst part of your day.
You're going to get some, I can already tell you're going to get some tragic news.
Something bad is going to happen.
You're getting a prostate exam.
Yeah, I'm getting a prostate exam.
That's not tragic.
From a doctor with, who's an arm wrestling champion.
From Wolverine.
You're going to get the top of the world.
That's not tragic. From a doctor who's an arm wrestling champion.
From Wolverine. You're going to get the prostate exam from the cartoon with the doctor with
the big hands. Yeah. You're going to get that. That's going to be your doctor. They're going
to put chemicals up to my body. It's going to be a foam finger. Honestly, they're not
even going to do anything to me, but I just hate my doctor so much that I'm suffering
just thinking about going there. You hate your doctor? I literally, I can say this because
there's no video and we're all behind a paywall. I want to kill my doctor. Okay. You and I
You want to kill him or her?
Her.
Whoa!
Wow, okay.
What the fuck?
A little too far.
You can't say you're going to kill a woman.
I said it's not on video.
The hell is that?
She's an elevated woman.
She passed schools.
That's true.
Once she passes schools, she becomes a man.
You're saying women doctors are acting like men.
That's what you're saying.
They're at the level of a man who's a tow truck driver.
They've reached that level.
And you want her dead.
Yeah.
crimes for crimes against me and my body. Yeah, crimes against your body because you
made you breathe in that cube that one. Yeah, and it charged me a whole lot of money. Yeah,
I do not like doctors. I fucking hate my dog, but I know I know dentists the most. I know
that the worst part of my day is to dentists are terrible. I liked my dentist in Boston,
but I will never go to a dentist again. I do like that flavor they put in your mouth
fluoride that orange flavor. Oh yeah, they don't do that since you're eight. I've always
been afraid of dentists because my little brother almost died at the dentist. He went into anaphylaxis
when they put the...
B in his mouth.
They put a B, yeah. And they take that B to numb your mouth.
Sting it on each tooth.
They have a B on a toothpick that they stick in your mouth and they put it right in your
gums.
Applying honey all over, it makes no sense.
Honey on his gums.
That is scary that you can die from a...
A B.
I've never been stung by a bee. I'm convinced that when I get stung by a bee I will die.
I got bit by a wasp. I got stung by a bee. I got bit by a wasp or stung by a bee. I got
stung by a bee and I went. Is it a hand on something and there was a wasp? Are you allergic
to wasps and bees? If you're allergic to one it goes to both? Maybe. They're in the same
family. Is it the same venom? I actually don't think so. But I got stung by a bee and my
mom is super allergic to bees. She like dies every time she's been stung by a bee. She
dies and then comes back. Or she's been like, dies. She's like rolled around on the floor
because there was nobody home and had to like crawl to an EpiPen. Oh Jesus. Yeah, she's
like super allergic. So I thought that I was too. I don't even have an EpiPen. Yeah, you
need an EpiPen. I know I need one. I'd have to get an EpiPen every time I need a carrot.
I got stung and I freaked out and I was like my throat is closing. I'm dying and I went
to the emergency room and I walked in and I was like I got stung by a bee and they were
like who gives a fuck. Yeah. And I wasn't allergic at all. I'm so scared of anaphylaxis.
Yeah, that's maybe the most scary thing on the planet to me.
They had this shit, the laughing gas distributor or whatever it's called, the latex thing.
My little brother is like so allergic to latex that they put that on him.
He was laughing so hard he couldn't tell them that he was in trouble.
He's like, "I'm in trouble!"
I think that's what happened.
I think he just started like choking really hard.
He was like four years old, so he also doesn't, he can't say.
He can't even say I'm going into anaphylaxis. He doesn't know what that is.
Anaphylaxis, what's that? A damn Pokemon? I would be really upset to find out that I was allergic to a shark bite or something.
Because then you get bit by the shark and you lose your arm.
And you're like, "Oh, well at least I escaped with my life."
Wait, my throat is closing up. I'm also itchy.
I can't itch because the other arm gets the spot better.
Exactly, yeah. Or you're walking around and you're holding your arm that he bit off and
itching it.
Yeah.
I'm really scared of phantom limb syndrome.
I have phantom limb sometimes.
For what?
My other legs.
Your back legs?
My back legs.
That would suck if you had a full centaur phantom limb.
I start walking backwards sometimes and I'm like, "Oh, it's because of my back legs."
That would suck if you were a centaur and they took off your horse part and they let
you just do normal legs.
They give you this big hairy ass.
Yeah, now you're walking around and you think you're bumping into people with a big hairy
ass.
Or you're trying to grind on a girl, but you're actually...
You're ten feet away.
Because you grind on a girl.
so
well, they would because their dicks are in the back yeah,
a sitar with phantom limb syndrome. He's doing every every
yeah,
girls like trying to to eat his ass out, but she's like don't don't don't come
to close. You're walking
stop to stay right there ten feet away. Okay, now just like
Oh
true. If you had a phantom,
woman just going like,
playing peekaboo
arm amputated, you could phantom limb jack off anywhere. Oh yeah, nobody be
able to see what you're doing. You're just that's true. You see you doing
making a face and going
Jack off. I have a phantom limb. I'm just scared of the pain that comes with having a phantom
limb. I'm scared of almost every medical possibility there is known to man.
You get shot in your phantom limb?
That would suck.
You lose your phantom limb.
And then you get shot into it.
Oh, you get shot. I thought you said you get a shot.
No, you get shot in your phantom limb and it's like, "Oh my God! No!"
Yeah, because there's no way to get that bullet out.
Yeah, you need to go to the phantom doctor.
Exactly. He's miming all this stuff.
You know the stuff where it's like,
they like, have you ever seen the experiments
or the studies or whatever they do
where like, so you know how some people get phantom limb
and they get like an itch on it that they can't scratch?
And then they do a thing where they like,
they have like mirrors.
So you look into the mirror
and it reflects your other arm or whatever.
So it looks like you have an arm
and then you just scratch that arm
and then their itch goes away.
Oh that video of the dude getting hit in the hand
with the hammer.
Yeah.
Yeah. I've seen that one.
They hit him in the hand?
Yeah, there's a fake arm
and they hit the fake arm with a hammer really hard
and he like screams.
- Yeah. - Oh.
- He screams like a banshee.
- Well, maybe he's just scared of--
- Yeah. - Loud noise.
- I'd be scared if that happened.
- Yeah, you would, I mean, we should do that to you
'cause that would be a funny reaction.
(laughs)
- You just wanna have a funny reaction.
- We have a fake arm in here and a hammer in here.
- And we do have a panel that we can put--
- The one episode that we don't have--
- I know. - Video of every component
to fully realize this. - We can actually do it.
- We literally have two fake arms and a hammer.
The fake arm that we have is covered in like fake scabs.
It would work. It would work on me. I'm not that smart.
No, even if we have the panel up to make it look like it's your arm and everything.
Just put it in my head. It would work on me.
The sound would scare the shit out of you. Just going like that.
Yeah. And to see the gold.
It's funny that you got like Luigi stuff going on.
What does that mean?
Like Luigi's like afraid of every... I'm thinking of his mansion.
ghosts. Yeah, that's a scary Luigi Luigi Luigi Luigi Luigi Luigi Luigi Luigi
for being scared of everything. He screams whenever he sees a ghost or a
monster. He screams that he sees 600 ghosts that are running towards him.
His whole thing in Smash though is like he runs towards you like he run his
fighting style is a scared style. I don't know anything about Smash.
Scared style? Virgin. You know his kung fu? You think it's a virgin? You don't
know anything about smashing. Okay, buddy, if you're talking about smash
bros, that's the type of virginity you're taking away is that of a three
year old boy.
And that's based on what I've read about the smash brothers scene. What
what's what? There's a bunch of pedophiles in the in the in the in the
competitive smells and all the thing. Probably. Yeah, I think I read about
that a while ago. I mean, yeah, they're playing competitive smash. I mean,
I play smash bros when my friends come over. Yeah, so you're a competitive
I don't even know you in the same group.
No.
When my young buddies come over.
You know who's really competitive with it?
Joe.
With a video game?
Joe is competitive.
Competitive as in he gets mad or competitive like he's good.
When I lived with Joe and Neil, Joe and Neil would play Smash on the Switch in the living
room and I would hear it from my bedroom and all I would hear is like, "Ness is a fucking
bullshit character!"
And then Neil was just like, "Well no, you shouldn't."
I don't like fighting games. I don't understand them at all.
They're fun for an hour.
I don't get why anyone would want to play a video game competitively.
A lot of the fighting games have sexual women characters.
Okay, I'm back on.
Yeah.
I just talked about this on beers we drank, but there was a very funny clip that came out.
No, you don't get to censor this.
No, what are you doing?
I could have told the whole story by now.
Well, you didn't have to tell the whole story.
There was a guy...
How does it feel getting buzzed?
I don't think you've ever been buzzed.
He can't get buzzed, that's the worst problem.
I can buzz myself.
I can't.
No, you can't because you know you're doing it.
You know you're getting buzzed.
Basically a guy who had a nude mod on for a Street Fighter tournament.
I saw that.
Oh you did?
That was a funny clip.
I gotta check that out.
That was a funny fucking clip.
You gotta check it out because you gotta see Chun Li's big floppy boobs.
Whoa.
They flop.
Yeah.
They put the jiggle physics.
What's the game?
Were those dead or alive?
Dead or alive is what you just asked me.
I literally would probably say.
What's a game where those dead are alive?
I woke up one hour ago.
That means you should be,
that's not a long,
that's not, how long does it take to recover from waking up?
Is that a short time to you?
I'm still waking up.
You're still waking up from an hour ago?
It takes me two hours to wake up.
I think I have chronic Lyme.
You won't survive in this world.
I won't.
I've been waking up so early. It's been so nice. It's been so goated. My time difference.
I woke up at 8 o'clock and then I went biking for 2 hours 2 days ago. And that was, I felt
good.
I've been waking up at like 7, 7, 7.30 naturally every day. And I've been getting so tired
that I can't stay awake by like 9.30. It's incredible. It's so nice.
I've been biking from Ridgewood to the end of Williamsburg and then back.
It's real nice.
Sometimes I'll stop at Blue Park and go skate.
I'm getting my steps in. I'm getting my exercise on.
That's not steps, that's pedals.
When I was flying back from Ireland...
One step is equal to four pedals.
No, four steps is equal to one pedal.
What kind of bike has one pedal?
You're on a unicycle.
Half of a unicycle.
My pedal got stolen.
That's a bad situation.
That's not going to be a very good vehicle for you.
You could still ride it, but it's just not going to be ideal.
No, it's going to be bad.
When I was on the plane back from Ireland, because it's like a seven-hour flight but a five-hour time difference,
I watched six hours straight of movies.
I watched the Avenue Avatar again, and then I watched that new...
What's the Avenue Avatar?
The new Avatar, and I watched the new Guardians of the Galaxy.
Bro said the Avenue Avatar.
six hours of movie straight and got off the plane. It was basically the same
time that I got on the plan. Isn't that crazy? It felt I felt so insane. I felt
like I was in a pocket dimension. Yeah, that were only movies. You were a movie
world. I was in movie were six hours and I got if you watch more than one movie,
you get on the plane, you eat lunch, you watch six hours of movies, you get off
the plane, you eat lunch again at the same
the day of
that is definitely laugh so hard that to think about yeah that I went into a
special time world time pocket to watch movies and eat an extra
time traveled, but all I got was an extra lunch
to live a day that's 30 hours long and just use it to watch movies and eat an
extra lunch, but you miss out on lunch on the way there. I know yeah, the way
there is horrible. And the movies are basically taking double the time. Which is the scariest
thing ever. Isn't that horrifying? Yeah, you leave at 8 and you get there at 8 and it's
all and you watch two movies in that time. And you only ate one meal. But you might as
well have watched four movies. Yeah, I'd be watching four. If you watch more than one
movie on a plane, when you land it does feel like insane. Dude, I watched those two movies
and I had like an hour and a half left in the flight. It felt crazy. You didn't watch
any other movies? No, I watched too many. I don't like two movies and I couldn't watch
three long ass movies. I watched Casino. I watched Casino that took the whole flight
from Austin to New York on the way back. But on the way there, I watched the Social Network
and then the movie Overboard with Kurt Russell and Colby Hahn. I don't know what Overboard
is. It's just like a very mid like 80s like comedy where Kurt Russell essentially, Kurt
Art Russell tricks a woman into thinking that he is married to her and then she has to take
care of her three or I think it's four little piece of shit kids.
Does she have brain damage?
She has amnesia because she fell off of her yacht.
Well fuck her then, she has a yacht.
And she's rude to him at first.
To her husband?
It's not her real husband.
He was building her walk-in closet on her yacht.
And he's trying to hit a lick on a cumbo.
He was just trying to get $600 so that he could father his children.
And then the whole movie is just like him training her like a dog to get him beer and make the
kids learn how to read.
That's cool.
And then they fall in love from that somehow.
Because that's what girls actually secretly want.
They want to be trained like dogs to get you beer.
I love watching two movies on a plane.
It's so awesome.
time when I was flying back from Mexico, I watched Men in Black and 8 Mile and that
was a good double feature. Yeah, I watched it. Getting to the end of 8 Mile as we
were about to land was the first time ever in my life I was like, "Please don't
land yet. I don't want the plane to land." Yeah, I think I have... Let me finish this
let's see. We need to do one more loop real quick. Yeah, just loop around real quick.
I have ten minutes left of overboard. I don't know how it ends. That's the worst
feeling, man. I don't know how it ends at all. When the plane lands and there's ten
minutes left? Uh-huh. What about, "I'm never gonna watch this movie off a plane"?
I'm not finishing Chinatown. I'm not finishing. You just go to the flight tracker and you're
like, here's it. I was playing one of those games. You know, those games they have. Oh
yeah. Here's a trivia question. I want to see if you guys know the answer to this. I
definitely do. So this is a, you know how they have all their trivia games and whatever
on the flight. Let me find this picture I took. This was, I opened up this game that
was called, I can't remember what it's called. It was called like world. There were two different
trivia games. That's why I remember pop culture in the world. Something wise.
I can just see that it cut off something wise on my picture. Sam, this
was question one of ten. Okay, see if
question one of ten. What gift should you not give to your Chinese colleague?
What are the good of the most cigarettes, tea or time pieces? I'm
gonna say time pieces. I think it was time pieces. If I remember correctly,
It seems like the kind of thing that would be bad luck, because I know Chinese people
love cigarettes and tea, obviously.
So that doesn't seem like the most bad luck thing.
Yeah, probably.
Oh, it's just the first trivia question.
You just press the game and that's the first thing that pops up.
Speaking of Chinese colleagues, I watched Police Story the other day.
That movie is so good.
Dude, what's Police Story?
The Jackie Chan movie?
You got to watch it.
You haven't seen that?
I haven't seen any.
Only Jackie Chan I've seen is Rush Hour.
You gotta watch the old Jackie Chan movies.
He was so goaded.
Yeah.
Dude, that movie.
He got hit by cars.
Yeah.
He does the most insane stunts.
The one where he slides down.
Yeah.
Dude, the stunt is so sick.
Because those movies, you're just watching them to watch the stunts or whatever.
They do a triple, they show every single angle, one in slow-mo and then the two other angles
at the end of the movie.
he slides down this pole that's covered in lights and then everything around him is like
blasting sparks.
Exploding and shattering, yeah.
Dude, it's so crazy.
It's so good.
Those movies are so...
He hangs off a fucking car, he hangs off the bus and then he's fighting the dudes.
I've seen that clip.
That's a police story?
Yeah.
Police story is like...
It's so good.
I saw the clip.
It's so funny too.
I love all that stupid shit where it's just about him and the girl.
Just all the...
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
With all the phones and stuff.
All that stuff is so good, man.
is it Jackie Chan is completely go to did you see the interview with him about that bus
scene where he was like yeah the bus was going way too fast and the guy can tell the guys
like really all the guys who fell off the bus got really badly hurt yeah yeah there's
like so many the I forget what moves oh he was in cannonball run and then after I watched
the movie I just like when I just right in cannonball run yeah he's in there for like
a little bit and then he said that the the blooper reel at the end of the movie was very
inspiring to him so then he employed that in every single one of his movies after that.
I didn't even know that Cannonball Run was a real thing people do.
Really?
Yeah.
I've never seen Cannonball Run.
It's about who can, the Cannonball Run is a...
So you go from one side to the other, right?
It's a route from, there's a specific diner or some shit in either New York or LA where
you drive from one to the other, you try to do it as fast as possible.
And somebody's done it in like 20 hours, like something crazy.
they go like 130 miles an hour the whole time.
Yeah. Jesus Christ.
Yeah. I think I would like to do something like that.
I'd like to break some record.
I'm going to try to do something.
Some shit they did on Jackass.
I'm going to do something that's along those lines,
but from the earth to the moon.
Yeah.
That's going to be...
Fastest earth to the moon.
I think that that'd be a pretty easy record to break, honestly.
If you throw caution to the wind when it comes to space travel...
The cannibal run, do you have to be alive once you get there?
[laughter]
Yeah, I think the car just has to go there. Yeah, I think you have to if my
dead body is still in the car. Well, but how did it so explain how you think
that it would keep going with a dead body in the car? Well, it will be
self-driving using technology and artificial intelligence because it's
going so fast that the g-force I can't survive. I can't because you can't if
you're not in the car in the first place. There's no way it counts, right?
If it's just a car that goes there by itself, you get to the other car the
whole time. You get to the other diner and all of your skin is in the back seat. And
I'm driving it until I die and then the self-driving takes over. But I'm just going so fast there's
no way I can survive beyond 10 minutes. How fast would you have to be for that G-Force
to kill you? Probably a thousand miles an hour? Yeah, I guess it's also how fast it speeds
up. It's more about G-Force than the speed itself. Yeah, so it needs to have some serious
torque. How far, so it's one diner to the other, how many miles is that? I think it's
It's 10 miles?
It's 10,000 miles to from here to Austin.
Or 1,000.
No, it's definitely not 1,000.
1,050.
No, it's like 1,000 miles.
1,050 going from 1,000 to 1,050.
No, it's way more than 1,000 miles from here to Austin.
Probably if I had to guess, 3,500 miles.
Let me see how many...
I couldn't even hazard a guess.
I have no clue.
Could be 100.
From here to the comedy mothership that is...
You have transit selected.
Oh, that would take two days.
Only two days?
Yeah.
To walk, walking directions are not available.
Just click on the...
Drive.
Just look at the distance.
One day.
How many miles?
One day worth of miles.
It's 1700 miles.
1700 miles.
1748.
So, yeah, it's probably close to 4000 miles between here and LA.
So that's how long, okay, so if you're going a thousand miles an hour, that's only four
hours.
Yeah, but the tough part I think there is designing a car that goes that fast.
That's not so hard.
That's not that hard.
You just get a rocket ship to put on top of your car.
Rocket boosters.
Yeah, rocket boosters and nitrous.
Don't know that.
Laser bastards.
Nitrous might work.
Laser bastard.
And flying car.
I don't even know, is that your bodyguard?
What's a laser bastard?
Laser bastard.
Oh, okay.
I thought maybe you were going to have a guy who like fights the police when they chase
you called your laser bastard.
Laser, Laser Bastard is the name of a...
Or can you use wormholes?
Wormholes are strictly disallowed.
Okay.
Laser Bastard is a German Jewish guy.
Fly by car, pass Jupiter, go to a wormhole and appear in LA.
That would be way, that would take way longer.
I had a landlord named Laser.
You did?
You just remembered that.
My first landlord was named Laser and then I learned that that is apparently
like a Hasidic name.
Laser Wolf.
I think that was his name.
What? Fiddler on the Roof or something?
Probably. Oh yeah. That's the only...
That's the only Jewish piece of media I can think of.
His name was Laser something. I just remember I was like...
The last name doesn't matter if your first name is Laser.
Well if it doesn't, it's Wolf.
Or Bastard.
That's true. Bastard too. Laser, Bastard.
Laser, Wolf, you're thinking of Star Fox.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, Star Fox from Fiddler on the Roof.
when the song that Slippy Toad does.
Slippy Toad is definitely Jewish also.
Yeah.
Right?
Because he's nervous?
Come on.
Because he's a frog, a green reptilian?
What are you guys talking about?
No.
You are being anti-Semitic.
They say he's Jewish in the game.
They don't say he's Jewish in the game.
I don't know.
(Laughter)
They do.
Peppy says, and by the way, Slippy...
Frog.
Is Frog a Jewish last name?
Maybe.
I don't know.
it could be actually i don't know i don't know what actually then
it could be
because it's all good be a little jewish lessons i don't know that any last name
yes in with the any other i was not yet by the jewish lessons confuse me
because sometimes people are you think they have a jewish last name but the
just like russian or something and you're thinking very hard about this
type of stuff like walberg
not thinking that hard about this kind of stuff now
is that i wonder if you have a mccain jewish rightness and i'll let him is
clement of
which i was uh... just assumed it is jewish
uh... but he's just running into
i would assume he's some kind of citrus
as a beat those in the
as a buzz man
now you don't get the song for that
you'll get a song for that
you can get a lot of that's a lot of the song you get how it was that was that is
a good song to
This is not a song.
This is a cricket.
That's a song in the terms of modern ideas of music.
That's true.
Something that...
Somebody who enjoys IDM might like that.
Yeah.
That's my...
That's the best name for a genre.
433 Remastered.
Bringing new elements forward in the mix that could never have been heard before.
They do need to make more intelligent genres.
Remastered versions with crickets.
How about some intelligent mumble rap, huh?
We need IDR, intelligent damn rap.
Now what do we got?
We just got IDM.
I hate IDM.
Intelligent damn music.
I've never listened to an ounce of it in my life.
Me neither, but I just know I hate it.
I just know I don't like it.
Yeah, you've listened to, what's his name?
Intelligent dance music, that's IDM. Same with Better Off Alone.
Oh, Planet of the Bass. That's IDM. Certainly that's IDM.
Full version dropping y'all! That's ACDM. Wait, what's today?
Alternative comedy dance music. That comes out in four days.
For real? Yeah. But I don't know where it's getting released,
be in line at GameStop in four days. I'm going to, um, no, I was, I got to go to the Apple
store. I'm going to, I'm going to do, I am tomorrow's my last day with Apple care for
my AirPods and they keep connecting while they're in my pocket. So I'm going to try
and get them replaced before I lose Apple care. Okay. So after this, you guys, I've
got a very, very important mission. I think I'm going to convince them that my
shit's broken when it's not. See, this is tough. I have to outsmart a tow truck
driver. You have to outsmart a genius. Yep. They put it in the name to scare
you. Uh huh. And look at me, the old goof is over here. I got to go in there.
Genius. I have to go in this Apple store and say, Oh, you have to act as
stupid as possible. Yeah, no, no, no. What you have to do is you have to act.
I go in and I act like... You act really, really smart. Okay. This is my Apple store trick that
I've always done. Okay. I go in and I just hit them with every piece of possible tech
jargon I can think of that maybe relates even a little bit to how my computer is broken.
Yeah. That's completely wrong. Yeah. And they will completely cut the bullshit every time.
You just go in and say, "Yeah, I think it's a problem with the BIOS," and they will immediately
will just take your computer and... I think the firmware won't update. Literally just
say that and they will help you. Otherwise, they just assume that you're a stupid person
and they just are going to ask you to turn it off and on.
Yeah.
That's what I've always done.
It's always worked for me.
Because they assume you've already turned it off and on.
Exactly.
They assumed that I'm more of a genius than them.
Because none of them know any of that crap.
They all just give it.
They all just, they just know how to use their little restaurant card scanner
and type in the issue and put it in the back for the goblins
and the gnomes who actually fix the Apple computers.
The smart gnomes and the smart goblins.
I was thinking of going in there like,
Ed, you're telling me to go in there like Double D.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, maybe even like Jimmy Neutron.
Yeah, who was not from that universe, but similar one.
You were thinking Sheen.
You got to go Jimmy, buddy.
Yeah, yep.
Sheen Estevez.
And keep Carl out of it.
Keep Carl.
No Carl.
No, you should never be going into any stores, Carl.
Carl is going to...
My laptop broke because I was looking at Jimmy's mom.
They're going to say that'll be $40,000 because you were looking...
Oh, yeah, sometimes it breaks when you look at Jimmy's mom.
Yeah. If you look at Jimmy's mom on your MacBook at 3 a.m. you're gonna get a
porno virus. No. You're gonna get a porno virus. No, no. You're gonna get a fucking porno virus.
What are you talking about, man? Your computer is gonna get hacked from pornos. Okay, so we're gonna
cleanse from that and here's like something that I was thinking about. Here's something that's a
little silly that I was thinking about. Okay. You guys could weigh in on it. It better be very silly. I was waiting. I thought of this
weeks ago and I was waiting to discuss it with you guys. I really wish that animals, every
type of animal could, of their own volition, with no humans involved at all, go out and
get their hair cut. Because here, I'm going to lay out my reasoning here. You know when
you're walking around and you see a person and you see they have some kind of crazy haircut
or even just a normal haircut that looks a little weird and you're kind of like, "Oh,
that's interesting. This person has decided to cut their hair. I wonder if they like that
haircut. That must be what they think looks good on them. They must think that looks cool.
Can you imagine if you got to experience what your dog thought that it would look cool like?
And you have no input at all. It goes out, it comes back, and it's like, "Check me out."
You see a bird fly by with a mohawk, you're like, "That bird is feeling it. That bird
wanted a mohawk. Every bird would look like bubble yum or whatever.
Double bubble. The blowout haircut? Yeah. Every bird would look like the bubble gum
bird, the bubble gum duck. Why is it a duck? What type of, what types of birds
would want this haircut? What types would want another?
You know, it's just, it would be so fascinating. Some birds naturally have
crazy hair like an emperor penguin. Exactly. So would a crazy haired emperor
penguin, would he go out and get a haircut and get it completely shaved?
I can hear it. I consider birds hair to be feathers. I call them feathers. Yeah,
I don't. I consider it to be a
hair. It's an interesting theory. You're positing. I it's an interesting theory,
but it will find no quarter here. Okay, well, that's fine. I saw I saw a guy,
a dog guy with an insane haircut the other day with a haircut that he maybe
gave himself the dog. I can't even believe I saw this. This dog at the dog
park had it was full. It was like a schnauzer and it was fully shaved front
legs, fully shaved body, back legs shaved just so that it looked like it had
pants
and the owner was like like there was some other people there who like had
seen this dog before and they were like, oh, we like his new haircut. It looks
like pants and the owner was like yep.
so the owner went to a groomer and was like put pants on my dog. I need to put
pants on this dog. My friend in high school, his mom would get the cat to-
she had the cat to look like a lion. Cats already look like lions. Well, she
had like a big- They give it a mane and then like the rest of the body would be
like really like short and then they would like kind of like fade the boots
in, so it looks like big paws. That's what I mean, man. Yeah. Oh my God, which
dog at the dog park, if it was given the chance, would dress in fully Balenciaga.
Uh-huh. That'd be like an Italian greyhound. They'd be wearing a Balenciaga.
Some dogs would be. Which dogs would be the New Balance dogs?
You know, that's what I'm thinking about. I'm walking around.
I wish they could express themselves so I could feel cute about them.
Every single dog breed, let's think about it.
Yorkie, Yorkshire Terriers, they're going to be wearing little baby gap clothes.
I think that Bill is cool in streetwear, so he'd be wearing full Diamond Supply Co. with
a Diamond Supply Co. backpack.
I think so.
Diamond Supply Co.
I think he would be dressed like he was homeless.
Huff jeans.
Huff jeans, Huff socks.
Huff socks with the weed on them.
With the weed on them.
Huff shoes from 2014.
Yeah.
Doesn't exist anymore.
Then he'd have like a Benny Gold snapback.
A snack pack.
A snack pack too.
He'd be wearing snack pack merch.
(laughter)
- He'd be telling you all of his weird Twitter poems.
- Yep.
- Uh-huh.
That's what Phil would be like.
Phil would be exactly like that guy, Snack Pack,
who's still around apparently.
- Yeah.
- Pushing 50 probably.
- Pushing 50 years old still going.
- Hi!
It's so nice to be nice.
- Is that what he does?
- Yeah.
- I don't even know who this is.
- You don't know who Snack Pack is?
- Not really.
- Noah told me the other day that he had Snack Pack merch.
- Yeah, I believe that.
Noah was like, I used to have a bunch of Snack Pack merch.
- Yeah, Snack Pack used to be lit on Facebook in 2013.
- And Noah is, I need to find these photos of him in this,
in this merch.
I need to find these photos of Noah wearing Snack Pack merch.
- I kind of have a vague remembery of this.
- Yeah.
- But I don't, I don't remember the shirt though.
- He had the merch too.
- I did not have the merch.
- He's pretending not to remember.
- I was friends with Snack Pack on Facebook though.
- Yeah.
- I fucked with him on Facebook.
I did not. I hated that guy immediately.
You've just always been just a skateboarding cool cat, man.
I've always been sick as fuck.
Do you hang out with the skateboarders who are the Twitter skateboarders?
What does that mean?
I don't know.
We can just move on then.
That's fine. We can just go to the next topic.
What's the next topic on the list?
I don't know. I brought the...
The Twitter skaters?
I've made friends.
Is there skateboarders who are the Twitter skateboarders?
What do you mean the Twitter skateboarders?
Are they like hella toy but they act like they not though?
(Laughter)
Yep.
Or like skateboarders who don't like comedy?
Are there skateboarders who are like
I don't like the skateboarders who like comedy?
Are there drama skateboarders?
There's drama skaters for sure.
Is there drama in the skating world ever?
Some skaters just really hate comedy. It's really funny.
Is there drama in the skating world?
Yeah. Really?
I've told you guys about this before, but the best beef ever, it was a one-sided beef.
This guy who owned this company called Team Burrito.
Funny.
Yeah, and the logo is like bootleg Supreme box logo.
It says Burrito.
I was obsessed with this when it happened.
He also owns this shoe company called Footprint.
Funny name for shoe.
He got wasted, he had too many white claws at a Wu-Tang concert.
His footprint was doing a Wu-Tang collab.
Got too many white claws there.
Goes on Instagram live and then just starts saying, "Fuck you Jason Dill and your fake
ass company.
Fucking poser piece of shit.
Your fucking shoes don't even pass the rebound test."
Which is a test he made up.
Jason Dill is the Grillo's mascot?
Jason Dill is the Gorillaz mascot, yeah.
He's the guy who wears the shirt that says "Fuckin' Pickles."
Mm-hmm.
Now, Jason Dill owns Fuckin' Awesome.
Oh.
By the way, Fuckin' Awesome, if you're listening to this, man...
Change your name.
Change your name. It's got a...
I don't know if you noticed,
you accidentally did a mistype of a cuss inside of the name.
But also, my wife bought some shoes of yours.
Those shoes... Okay.
And she didn't know that it had the fuckin' name on it.
She bought the shoes that I own.
She copied me.
She completely copied you.
Your wife is a copycat.
Yes, dude.
Damn.
Your wife copycatted you.
She copies pirates every single day in the way that she buys purchases for our house and
wears her clothes.
Yeah, but she bought the FA Experiment 1s which have the logo on them.
And they look like shit.
I don't know what that logo looks like.
Shit.
Which one?
It says fucking awesome.
That's the Hulk Hogan font too.
Oh, it's the Hulkamania font.
That is so hella toy.
is toy to switch to play with funny fonts. Fucking awesome is toy as fuck. Their other
gear is pretty sick, or it used to be very sick but now it's kind of insisting upon itself.
Alright, we're starting Escape Brand, you and me. Okay. What about me though? You get
to come up with the name. You are the receptionist. Team Rider. Team Rider, that's what it's called?
team rider. That's the name of our team. Rocket. No, that's not the name of the team. And we
are making, okay, here's what we're making. We're going to start out. We're going to start
out. We should start small. We should start small. We should start at the hardware. We
should start at the boards. You're ruining my idea right now. No, I'm see how not fun
it is to start a skate company with him. You're ruining my idea. You're, well, okay. What
do you want to start at boards immediately? Oh dude, I don't even want to do boards. I
don't want to do shirts. What do you want to do? I don't want to do shorts. I want to
stickers, knee pads, elbow pads, helmets, shin guards. This is what we're making.
Special cell phones that have one button to call 911 and your mom. Yes. In case you fall.
And they're attached to the knee pads, so if you fall and hit me, it automatically calls your mom.
This is Team Rider. We make the biggest helmets on the fucking market. We make knee pads. You
will never get hurt wearing Team Rider. That's a guarantee. If you walk into the break and
We make skateboards that go on a rail like a roller coaster.
We make a full Michelin man foam suit that is protecting you from falling over.
That's also what this guy who owned Team Burrito does.
He has socks that have shin guards built in.
Really?
Yeah.
See this is the kind of shit we're making.
Yeah, we're going up against Team Burrito.
We're going to be way safer. We're being way safer. We're team safety.
Team safety. That's what we are. Yeah. We are team safety.
Everything is also full black and yellow. It's high viz.
You will never get hit by a car. It's all only made out of high viz.
There's no material involved that is not high viz. It's full high viz.
The wheels are high viz. I don't think we can make wheels yet.
We don't want to make wheels. We don't want to make any of the parts of the
skateboard. It's just skateboard stuff to make sure that safety is happening.
but the next phase is skateboards that are safer than the average skateboard.
Yeah. Skateboard made out of styrofoam.
Okay, because here we go. We sell these big puffy shoes,
skate shoes. On the bottom of them, they have magnets.
You're like, "What the hell? Why are there magnets on the bottom of the shoe?"
Metal bowed.
Year later, metal bowed.
If you have any kind of separation between you and the board,
that is what we call a gap of danger.
Mind the gap.
that's a classic shirt. So this shit is if there is any space between you and the board,
that's space that a spike could go through or a spider or a spider could spider especially.
Also, it's the everything is everything is pre-sprayed with industrial level raid. And
we're yeah, we've got deep. Yeah, there's a lot of the thing that the that they say that's
the one that they said that you can't use in bug spray anymore. That's why you also
So that is why we also have gloves and respirators because you have to because
the stuff is so toxic. So imagine this right helmet big as fuck big padding
around you basically it basically looks like a mushroom top on your head. You
look like toad respirator on your face goggles and then a Glock and then Glock
Glock in your case you get someone tries to rob you in case a security guard
tries to touch you. With a blade in it. Lead blanket vest in case someone tries
just to x-ray you. In case you're skating next to a hospital and the x-rays come out the window.
Yeah, the x-rays thing start swiveling around and they shoot it at the window.
Wrist guards. Or if a nuclear bomb goes off. Wrist guards. Turtle shell. Wrist guards that
are made out of turtles. A little pill that you swallow and when it goes into your stomach
it puffs up and becomes very big and it stops any of your internal organs from moving around
being jostled. Yes. Basically one of those foam dinosaurs that you put in the
bathtub. Yeah. And it makes your insides feel like jelly. And this is
team safety. This is team safety stuff. Yeah. And that's what... oh it's just some
team safety shit. Pants with knee pads built in. And we're gonna sponsor
rappers. And a backpack that comes with a giant flashing LCD screen on the back
that shows your face, all your allergies, all your pre-existing medical conditions.
And also a parachute, just in case you fall from something high.
A parachute that has a helicopter attached so you can go back up if you're falling down
a bottomless pit.
Yes.
This is all amazing ideas.
Because a parachute only saves you if there's ground beneath you.
Yeah, if it's a bottomless pit, the parachute is just going to make it more agonizing.
It's going to make it worse.
Or if you're going down over water, you could go sideways until you get out of the water.
And also everything is made of the, it's the same thing as the inflatable vest on a plane
where you just pull it and it's going to, you're going to puff up, it's a life jacket.
Yeah, you're going to look like Bubble Buddy once you're done wearing all this team safety
gear.
And all this gear, it's free for the good of society.
It's paid for by taxpayers.
So tell me.
And that's why, and this is also, this is, we're not going to clue Patrick in on this,
but this whole thing is a way to sow discord in the skating community.
But also in the larger community because we want people who are walking around
with no pads on and stuff. We want people to be like, "Fuck you, man!
My tax money is going to have to pay for your exploding limbs."
And then your team safety sunglasses,
they scan that person's face who's yelling at you,
send it to a database up in the sky.
The one thing server.
The one thing I will say that later.
The one thing I will say is if you do that, you will
be removing
Kobe Shadix from employment because then
SCARDA is not going to exist anymore.
He can fall back.
It'll be like tiny.
It'll be like we're using we're using a
microscope to find
injuries, to find like tiny microscopic
stapled his finger to a paper by accident.
No, we can still do skating, but it'll be like
the mother fucker poked himself with a mechanical
so I was he didn't draw blood, but it was red. I was a piece of lead was in
his finger for three years and
I don't know just one day I went to write something down and missed the
paper and it went into the back of my finger.
Oh no, he stubbed his heel on the corner of the door
with his because he was walking backwards
Office scarred. He hit his head off his hand. Office scarred. Office scarred, yeah.
Workplace scarred. He was sad. Oh, that would actually... He got too hungry. Wait. That would be sick.
Where it's like, it's scarred but instead of extreme sports, it's all like OSHA violations,
all like, like that OSHA shit we read. I'm surprised that's not, well that's because I think it's...
Jacobi Shattuck just watching... Legally it has to be anonymous. Yeah, that's true.
If it wasn't, that would be a great show.
Yeah, it's just like dudes getting into forklift accidents.
Yeah.
Dudes doing that video where the guy is putting the pallets on the dolly
and then all the pallets fall forward.
I got in a forklift accident.
And then he flies forward.
Yeah, I lifted my fork and I accidentally ate a bite of salad.
Fat ass.
Fat fuck.
Well, no, it's like, "Ugh, veggies, ew."
You're fat.
Well, it's not even about-- I guess I'm fat, but it's not.
You were in the whale, did they?
(laughs)
Did they have to use AI technology to slim you down at all
to play that part?
When I was in the whale, I escaped like Jonah
by the grace of God.
No, you were more of a Pinocchio.
I watched Sodom and Gomorrah
get wiped off the face of the planet Earth.
You were Brendan Frazier's stunt double.
No, you were in a whale 'cause you were a Pinocchio
'cause you ain't a real boy.
I'm a man.
No, you're a puppet.
You a donkey.
I'm not a puppet, I'm not a donkey.
Then who's my puppet master, pray tell?
the U.S. government.
Geppetto.
The U.S. government.
And Geppetto.
Who works for the U.S.
Geppetto is still there.
You can't get rid of Geppetto.
I could get rid of him.
He's old.
One punch.
You wouldn't get rid of Geppetto.
Break all his teeth.
That's your father.
You guys are confusing me with another guy.
You're a fat puppet.
He's not a puppet.
He's a marionette.
Marionettes are puppets.
Marionette is a type of puppet.
No.
And you're a big fat one.
You're a 400-foot puppet.
They have to use chains on you instead of strings.
405 pounds is not that heavy. I can deadlift that.
No, that's pretty heavy for a human puppet.
I wish I was 405 pounds.
You do?
I think I'm going to get, I think I'm going to try to be 250 pounds in one year.
Yeah.
I think I'm going to try to gain 70 pounds.
That's all right.
That's fine.
Do you think I could do that?
I mean, I don't want you to because,
Why?
Like, because I know, I know you're going to have to do like some kind of crazy diet to do that and we're going to have to sit
here in the office and you're going to be walking in here eating like two whole rotisserie
chickens and just like just stinking up the place with your fat.
Do you think rotisserie chickens stink?
I'm not going to get fat.
No, I'm not getting fat.
I'm going to get really strong.
Yeah, but you're still going to be eating like crazy.
You're going to be eating like Taco Bell wrapped in McDonald's.
I did.
Oh shit.
Wait, that is...
Taco Bell wrapped in McDonald's?
Stoner meal.
I think that...
Uber Eats should have a...
Stoner option.
No, it should have, they should do a promotion.
Do you want to stoner-fy it for $2?
Where you mix and match any two fast foods.
Uh-huh.
You can do two orders.
No, no, no, no, no.
You can.
You can, it's just morally wrong.
No, no, no, no.
They wrap it, they combine it together.
Uh-huh.
They put all the food, it's not like you're getting a Taco Bell and a Big Mac, a Taco Bell,
you know what they sell.
What do you mean wrap it?
Do you want them to put it in a ball?
They put it, they combine it all.
They may, if you get...
The cost would go way up.
They'd have to hire chefs.
So here's what you get.
It's expensive.
okay, it's a promotion. Here's what you get right and this is this. You order
it's a it's a DNA combination, but it doesn't have DNA. It's just a
combination. You get a crunch wrap and a big Mac. They put the crunch wrap into
the big man. Here's my idea.
Okay, okay, this is so it all goes in it all goes to the Uber eats like
there's a like you know how they have like the getter building and like the
like stuff like that. I live in a
jet G. T. T. I. R. like that where they have like the it's basically like they
are open building. They open they open these grocery stores just so the riders
can go there. Yeah, it's like snacks only. So it's one of those right. One of
those where the person goes to both Taco Bell and McDonald's. They take the
their bike back to that spot and scientists combine it and then the chefs
and the scientists see here's the foods already made. So the job of the
you guys are just inventing a restaurant at this point, but
it's a restaurant that only uses your Uber Eats order. One restaurant takes food that's already made by a
chef and uses scientists to combine it. Exactly. Make one restaurant that does that. Well, here's the question.
Do you consider God a chef? Yes. I would consider him more of a
Lord. Okay, so if the Lord or the chef takes...
Or if he makes fruits and he makes animals, these are already foods,
y'all. So here's my... You think scientists are combining them? Okay, I think the
I just want to throw this out there. I want to throw this out. We're saying Taco Bell
and McDonald's, right? Yeah. So you get the ground beef from Taco Bell. McChicken Bell
Grande. That's pretty good. Take the beef from Taco Bell, the seasoned beef. Uh-huh.
The cheese and the buns from McDonald's. Yeah, keep going. The McSloppy Joe. Yup. They already
did a bell beafer. What's a bell beafer? You don't know about the bell beafer? I don't know
about the bell beafer. You don't know about the bell beafer? This is a real food item
that my dad talks about every Thanksgiving. It was a Taco Bell sloppy joe? It was a Taco
Bell sloppy joe. Oh my god. It was a Taco Bell meat sandwich. Wow. The bell beafer. The bell
beafer. And they took it away and they also took away my dad's precious enchiladas. Well
that would make sense. They're trying to slim the menu down. Trying to streamline it. Well
with my science restaurant, you could make the Bell beef for custom with ingredients from
different restaurants.
You can already just get the Taco Bell meat.
Oh, but are you guys going to join the class action lawsuit?
Where?
With Taco Bell?
I, buddy, I have a whole case.
There is a class action lawsuit that has been filed against Taco Bell because they misrepresent
the amount of meat that is in a Crunchwrap Supreme.
Oh, I got to get that on that.
I ate a Crunchwrap Supreme the day that I found this shit out. No meat at all.
Yeah.
What did you order with beans?
One corner of meat.
Oh.
I was going to say, yeah.
Single corner. Hey, sour cream lovers, come on down to Taco Bell, get a Crunchwrap Supreme.
I do love sour cream.
Lettuce lovers, knock yourselves out.
I do love lettuce.
And if you don't like the sour cream, replace it with a different ingredient from a different
restaurant.
So now at Science Deluxe.
It should be called...
That's a terrible name.
so science deluxe. It should be called like uber deluxe uber super deluxe
uber experiment ubers x uber experience. You can't suggest that. No, you're out
of this. You didn't want to be a part of this venture like businesses, but okay,
so it's it starts with it goes to the has to start with an x. What about just
x.com uber experiment that would have worked a month ago, uber experimental
experiment. It's experiment. Uber eats experiment. It doesn't have to be
combinations, it could be anything you want to experiment with your food.
You can order something and ask... So you get grocery store...
Can you make it glow in the dark? You get grocery store ingredients,
you get like Uber Eats, it's like, "Okay, I want like a porterhouse."
Okay. And potatoes and asparagus. Yeah, see now we're... There's a private
chef. Yeah. What I'm thinking of even... Well, that's a different business,
that's Uber private chef. Okay, maybe this will fix the idea for you.
maybe it's like a slot machine and it spins three food items from
the wheel, but you already pay for it. It's like a get what you get. It's
a flat rate. Yeah, it's like you pay $15 and whatever comes up. I know
this is not a
but it's the novelty of it. It's supposed to be a novelty thing. I
think this is a great idea.
I'm fine if they rig it. If it's $15 and they rig it... You can pay extra
choose the item. If they rig it so that it's $20 to choose it. I think that even if you
I think that they should add something to Uber Eats that is like you gamble you pay 15 bucks
or whatever the price is that makes it like makes sense for them where they get a house
edge you pay 15 bucks and you get an entree from a list of of restaurant and sometimes
it's Taco Bell but sometimes it's it's a it's a Wolfgang Peter Luger Wolfgang Puck Wolfgang
puck, salt bays restaurant. I might go to Fogo de Chao tomorrow. Solo? Solo Fogo? You
might dolo Fogo? I was thinking about it. How are you going to get there, Blood? Bus?
Wow. The Fogo bus? Here's something I found out. Take an hour and a half bus ride to Fogo
de Chao. If you take the Q58 bus. I know how to get there. You take the Q58 bus all the
way to the Queen Center Mall. I've taken the bus there before. They got an Olive Garden.
They got a Chick-fil-A, they got an Olive Garden, they got a Fogarty Chow all right there.
Is it an hour and a half really? No. It's less than an hour. I mean you could take the
Q58 from here. There's a bus that goes straight from Central Park to my house. Oh yeah. It's
amazing. I've seen that bus. Anytime I'm even close to there I just get on that shit. It's
like a coach bus too. It's all comfortable and shit. I like the buses here. The buses
here have chargers. Yeah, it's pretty cool. Hey, the rest of the country. Get on the level
up Nashua, New Hampshire. You've got like five buses. Dice made a leap of logic in my
brain, but Dunkin Donuts is releasing spiked coffee. Yeah. Did you see this? Like in a
can in the store? They're doing the raspberry refresher, the iced tea, the cold brew, and
then I would think like a regular Duncan. No, it's hot. They're all hot. They're all hot.
you got to heat them up. I mean you have to get them from the they have to keep
them in the rotisserie chicken area. Yeah, the history chicken area of
Duncan is a grocery store. I mean, it's a, you know what? I think it rose
history chicken from Duncan would be pretty good. I trust. I like all the
food from Duncan. Yeah, Duncan's got good stuff for the disgust. Browns
make me shit immediately. I think I'll get some Duncan Donuts in two weeks.
Yeah,
You're really planning out your meal. You're doing meal prep.
So you're doing FOGO tomorrow.
You're just gonna make dinner at home.
These are all just lunches you're gonna get.
You're getting FOGO.
Duncan breakfast.
OK.
And I'm going to get it in Massachusetts.
Oh, you're going to Massachusetts.
That's why I said that.
I haven't been home in probably since March.
I haven't been back in a minute.
Yeah, I've not been back since March.
I haven't been back in North Carolina.
I got to go to New Hampshire soon.
Yeah, I'm going to be going to New Hampshire.
I'm going to go to Manchester, Vegas, bro.
I'm going to go to...
I'm going to hit Plastow.
I'm going to hit the Savers.
I'm going to hit the Shoe Barn.
The Plastow Savers is so good.
Fire.
I have to pee so bad.
I saw a Tabuska shirt there.
Pat, you're going to plug my dates while I pee.
Okay.
So on August 24th, Caleb will be going to prison.
He'll be on Mars doing the Martian showcase.
He'll be doing the Martian talent show.
Just for Laughs Mars.
Just for Laughs Mars trial.
Yeah.
And then he will be going to then.
Yeah, I think it's just the 24th through the 26th.
He will be in DC and he's going to go.
No, he's not going to do that.
No, you will not do that anymore.
I am gonna do some stand up.
It's going to sing that on stage.
Y'all bring the memes back.
Y'all, if you, okay, if you go to see Caleb open for Adam Friedland in DC, you got to do WWE style printouts of memes.
And you got to hold them up and show him while he's performing.
Tell him that you liked his funny tweet about dying and you can't believe he's alive.
You can't believe he's alive. Print out photos of his tweets and show them to him while he's on stage.
on stage.
He's a meme and do right shit on your forehead.
I heart laughing at live comedy on your forehead.
I heart Caleb's set.
If you're bald and you do that, Cameron and I will send you $25 each.
I'll commit to that.
I'll commit to that too.
If you're a bald guy, we will give you 50 bucks.
But unless you actually do it, and then I'm going to wiggle my way out of it.
And then we will figure out a legal way to not have to pay you.
I'm not paying you $25 for anything.
Because, okay, you have to be naturally bald.
What time is it?
It's probably time for you to go to the doctor.
It's 1219.
I gotta go.
Okay.
Alright, bye everybody.
You can, I'll just, I'll keep going.
Okay, what else can we, okay, so if you're, you have to be naturally bald.
You can't like shave your head the week before.
Like you got to like prove that there was like you were on the Norwood scale at some point.
You got to prove that your like hair is like thinning as fuck and like stuff like that.
And I guess maybe like there could be, no it still has to say I heart Caleb's set.
I guess I'll just I'll come right out and say it. We started a law firm.
we did fetter and doran and pits international
crazy bitch by buck jerry
You got a lovely face, going to your place, you got to freak me out, sleep so loud, get
fucking laid, you want me to stay, but I got to make my way.
Hey, you're crazy bitch, what you want so good, I'm lost out the way, I'm with you all night,
I'm doing you all night, since you don't have no back to you at all.
You're a crazy bitch, let your fucks feel good and let's talk a game now.
Take it all, keep it in your game, you should've been there for fame.
I'm the one you're paying for, and that's so fine.
I'm being lost, catching in the rocks,
but you can get your face to face.
Hey, you're a crazy bitch, but your fuck's so good,
I'm out of town for bed when I dream.
I'm giving you all night, can't do some damn of that to you at all.
Hey, you're a crazy bitch, but your fuck's so good,
I'm proud of being an artist, you know,
I'm with you all night,
'cause you're some damn, the best beat ever.
[music]
I like the video,
it's so good.
Good video,
Crazy bitch.
Crazy bitch, crazy bitch, crazy bitch, hey
You're a crazy bitch like a fuck soaked m on top of bed when I dream
Dreaming you all night, slippin' down my back and you're out
Dreaming you all night, slipping down my back and you're out
You think you know, you want it all
So take a shot, you're gonna have to go down
Take it all, but leave it's on
You're crazy but I like the way you fuck me
You're crazy bitch but you fuck so good in my trap
I've been in a dream, been in you all night
Touches on them are better than your own
Your face is based like your thoughts so good on my sky
But they are not me, I'm doing you wrong now
Stretch your thumb down my left
Keep it right on, keep it right on
Go crazy but I like the way you fuck me
[BLANK_AUDIO]