It seems we've forgotten where we came from. It seems that we've also blown up to a proportion
where we get fancy water sent to us now. You know when people on mic do a, they open a
beer. Yes, I'm very familiar. I'm sure you're familiar.
Wow.
There's a crack on this.
Icelandic glacial water, natural spring water from Iceland.
Yeah, we basically got sent an entire case of this by somebody on Instagram.
So and no, it's not like how you might get a case sent to you through a transaction.
We did not win some kind of, we did not win a water sweepstakes and get a one month supply
of water.
No, we didn't.
We kind of won a water sweepstakes.
by being famous artists.
We're completely famous actors now.
No, not actors.
Celebs.
Celebs who have radio host.
Yeah, water sent to them.
Listen to this.
Over 5,000 years ago, long before the first humans reached remote Iceland,
a massive volcanic eruption created a unique underground spring
complete with its own natural filtration system, pristine lava rock.
Now known as the Ulfhus Spring, this is the origin of Icelandic glacial TM
TM the natural spring water which is the source of an epic life and you know
this tastes like what is that last part mean pure which is the source of an epic
life water is a source of an epic life and y'all I'm halfway through this thing
we're a minute into the episode no this expired addicted this expired in June 23rd
1907 what no way water doesn't expect wait really where does it say that no it
actually expires on the 1st of June 2025 but above that it does say June 23rd
1907. Well, that's the date that the spring was discovered. Probably. But it's printed
like an expiration date. And you know what? This is just the tip of the iceberg. Wow. We
are going to sell out like crazy now. All different types of waters. If you work for
a company and you want to send us crap, anything for free, we will endorse it. We will supply
of anything. I don't care if your CEO was racial or something. We already got roaded
out with all sorts of road equipment. Now we have Icelandic water. What's next? Clothes.
If somebody works for jewelry, if somebody works for Audemars Piguet, if somebody works
for Audemars Piguet, if somebody works for Audemars Piguet, it's a company that makes
watches. All of Mars Pikmin. That's what I was thinking. You were saying if somebody
works for Patek Philippe, if somebody works for Rolex, ice me out dog. Trax NYC. I'll
wear whatever. I'll wear girl stuff. I'll wear wigs. I'll wear a complete girl dress
and say this fits men really well. I'll make it seem like I'm giving a measured and honest
review by at the beginning saying, "though it's not without its flaws," but then I'll
do
What happened with him? I saw that he confided in XQC, which why would you do that?
He, a woman accused his company of making her cut her own leg off so she could go home from work early.
What?
Or something.
(Laughter)
I think she, I think that's...
What?
I guess the work, I mean we have a pretty grinding work environment that I think is pretty hard
to escape. We all get pretty caught up in it. Anybody who joins who wasn't here from
the beginning kind of gets chewed up and spit out. But I think they took it to another level
and they were having these long, long hours and nobody could get any time off and she
wanted to leave work and so she tried to cut her leg off.
In the bathroom or outside?
I don't know where, but then she was like, did she have a desk?
How are you going to, it's just tech reviews.
Right?
Buddy, somebody doesn't know what goes into YouTube.
Yeah.
You do not realize there's editing and filming as well.
Most of these popular YouTubers have teams of up to 150 people that are working on their
different videos in different types of ways.
I think that this is an amazing opportunity for, there's a vacuum.
There's a spot.
a spot in tech review YouTube that maybe we might be able to sneak ourselves into.
The Logitech...
Yeah, okay, give us an example of a tech review.
So what is the exact model number of this?
I think I need to...
This is a wireless presenter.
A Logitech wireless presenter...
What is it?
No, that's the laser.
So far you will lose all...
That's okay, but there's a lot of editing that could be done.
You don't even know which way...
Well, yeah, a new word did appear.
The Logitech R400 is a sleek, tiny little device that comes with a laser pointer.
If it's switched on.
But you didn't even say what it does.
The laser pointer can be used when it's turned on.
And a laser pointer that can be used when it's turned on.
And you can do funny things like this with it.
You can put a crosshair on my head.
See, I would go more like, "Oh."
Apple has done it again with their wired headphones.
They have included a lightning jack that only works on iPhone plus two little earbuds on
the side that fit perfectly in your ears if they're big enough.
They also have this little switch here that controls volumes but doubles as a microphone.
Overall, I give this five stars out of five.
Apple, please send us more products to review.
Okay, you can't be going around doling out five-star reviews.
And you can't say, "Please give me more products for me to review for free."
No, you have to do something like this, right?
Okay, expert, why don't you show me how to do it?
Expert. It's funny you say expert because here I have an Expo marker,
the only marker for experts.
Now, this is a marker that does two functions.
It's a combination of dry erase and you can use it as a chisel,
as you can see is labeled on its sleek, colorful chassis here.
It's also a low odor marker, so if you have issues...
Use it as a chisel.
It's chisel right here and it has an image of a chisel.
So I actually did try using it as a chisel and it worked pretty well on sand and air.
This marker also conforms to ASTM D4236 and it's from the USA.
Made in America.
Now let's test it out.
That's the straightest line I've ever seen.
And I was trying to draw a circle.
It straightens the line when you draw it.
Wow. We could even do stuff other than tech. We could do...
Like markers?
We could do... No, that's tech. I guess this is technology too.
This is technology.
Guys...
Everything's technology.
Next time you're outside and you want to shit your pants when you're in the bathroom at
the gym, you need to grab yourself a Zen 3, the chill flavor, a slight hint of menthol.
Guys, you can collect, track, and redeem at zen.com/rewards.
And this one expired in January.
- That expired?
- Yep.
06 Jan, 2023.
Did not get this from a smoke shop, got this from a deli.
And it seems that this one was best.
- I put that in my mouth.
- I got spit for this.
Wait, this is so good, I can only imagine how good it was
before January 6, 2023.
Yeah, and there is a January 6, 2020.
Wait, January 6?
Yeah.
Well, I think that a lot of people,
a lot of people should have expired.
That a lot of people should have been.
They should have just killed them.
Yeah, a lot of people
should have taken some of these and chilled.
Yeah.
Oh, that's actually really smart.
That everybody who was at January 6
was all hopped up on cigarettes and cigars.
Yeah, they should have chilled out with Zin-Chill.
They should have put a Zin in their mouth
and Ashley Babbitt would still be alive
She had a protective zen layer that blocked all bullets from entering her entire body.
She would have lived to be over 40 years old.
I can guarantee that.
Now, I put one of these in my mouth before we recorded just because I saw that Caleb
had them and I said, "Give me that."
And honestly, I did Candyman.
You have a case of the gimme's.
And I'm going to be honest, I was not ready.
was not ready for the amount of nicotine
that's in my system.
I knew that this was going to happen
because last time you talked about having one of these
you said that this exact thing happened.
Yeah.
And you kind of left it to me.
Well, the last time that I took one of these
I was very drunk.
Right.
And now you're not very,
well, maybe you might be drunk on
delicious Icelandic water.
Can I tell you guys some scary stuff
that's been happening in my life?
Where do I put this?
I'm done.
It goes in the can.
It goes in the can of C4 performance energy.
The only energy with a...
Have you guys ever gotten a voicemail on your phone without having a missed call?
Nobody called you but a voicemail disappears on your phone?
Fuck no, I haven't had that happen.
That happened to me this morning and it was completely in Chinese.
Wow.
The voicemail.
Do you have Google Voice on your phone?
No, I don't think so.
You got hacked into by...
It just went right into my voicemail.
Wow.
Automatic.
A Chinese white hat hacker?
Yeah, I mean, I don't know what it said because I can't speak Chinese.
Oh, I actually don't know if he was a white hat or a black hat.
Why don't you play it and then somebody who listens can translate.
I could play it.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't know if any people out here know.
That would be even scarier if you play it now and it's in English.
Oh my god, I can't even imagine.
All right, here's what I got this morning at 11.03am.
Is this the speaker or not?
I think you're...
Maybe they said you won something.
Wait, so you got this voicemail and you did not get a phone call?
No, no phone call.
Are you familiar?
Unable to transcribe this message.
I'm sorry.
Are you familiar with a movie called The Grudge?
Yes.
It's not a Chinese movie.
It's a Japanese movie.
Japanese movie.
Well, they kind of sent it.
But here's, this is the second, this is the second thing that's happened.
The first thing that happened, and listen, people aren't, people maybe are going to be
skeptical on this.
I'm ready to be, I'm ready for people to attack me.
Okay.
Because I know that this is also the type of thing people like this do, to discredit
people like me when they say things like this.
Survivors.
But I know for a fact that the TSA went through my bag when I went on the airplane.
And when they go through your bag, they're supposed to put in a thing in your bag that
says "We went through your bag," but they didn't.
Wait, how do you know they went through your bag?
Because I have a duffel bag that has clips.
It has a zipper, and then it's got clips all the way around.
And whenever I check it, I put all the clips on.
And when I got my bag back from baggage claim, all the clips were off.
Maybe they just took the clips off.
No, they wouldn't have done that because that would have made it a hazard to have in the
airplane because the clips would fly around.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
Were your things out of order?
No, because they weren't folded or anything.
They were just in there.
Okay.
So there wasn't really a way to tell.
So there's no way to tell.
But it was just clothed.
So they probably were pretty mad when they discovered that I wasn't.
So my phone was not in my checked bag.
No.
Interesting.
Yeah.
It's maybe, I mean, maybe you forgot about it and it actually was and they
planted the voice mail on it.
And they put it into my pocket.
You put your phone in your pocket.
Yeah.
But anyway, the reason...
And you're playing with someone else's phone on the plane.
Listen, I'm saying this stuff because things like these, they always come in
threes and that's two.
So if I'm gone soon or I get put somewhere or someone that you can't contact me, something
happened.
It was the third thing.
Well, I feel like kind of the water appearing at our door might be the third thing.
That was somebody messaged us.
Patrick's doing.
It didn't really disappear.
Does everything come in threes or is it just bad stuff?
All types of things.
Anything that you...
Sneezes, deaths in the families, courses of a meal, meals of a day.
Oh, true.
between meals and after dinner.
- How many almonds you can eat without getting full?
- Yeah.
- Three almonds?
- Three times.
- They fill me up.
- You eat three and then you wait a little bit
and then you eat three more.
- I bought a lottery scratcher ticket on the way here.
- Oh, and you put three numbers in.
- And I scratched off three times three numbers.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause there was nine total numbers
and I didn't get a single thing.
I did not get a single fucking thing.
- That's true, yeah, bad things come in threes.
- So that could be the third thing.
- Well, it happened to you.
- Yeah.
But if I had won millions of dollars, you know, I would have given you some.
That would have been the third thing for me.
That would have been...
I would have given you money.
That I didn't win it.
I don't think you would be in here right now if you won a million dollars.
You'd go away.
You would go away instantly.
No, no. I've thought about this a lot.
Here's what I would do.
If I ever win a lottery...
There'd be a cloud of dust that we see and it's the shape of your outline.
Just because you have money doesn't mean you run fast.
If I had...
If you... you would run to go cash that thing out.
I don't think you can do that. If I think you go to the guy, I mean, you go to the
convenience store,
a billion dollars. I think if I won the lottery, I would not tell anybody, maybe
not even my wife, and I would just start blessing everybody in my life to an
amazing degree. You don't tell anybody. I would hire an actor to play a
billionaire guy who would set he who would give us an email, right? And he'd
like I should have expected you would do something so Nathan Fielder esque. No, I
should have expected an old comedian like you would be running a kind of the
rehearsal type scheme. If you're in the lottery, more and more I'm trying to
okay, well, you just got cut out. The billionaire guy is just gonna say, I
think this is the I really like Patrick and Caleb and I do not like Cameron at
all. And I'd like to give you guys $100 million. But I would put you both on
payroll, you both be my assistants, you'd be my chain carrier and you'd be my
you'd warm up my chains before I put them on.
Chains?
My chains, my jewelry.
Yeah, okay.
You'd hold them and you'd warm them up on your body so they're not cold when they hit my body.
So I get to wear them?
You know what I would do?
You get to wear them but not publicly.
So I get to wear them?
Not publicly. You can only wear them in.
Well, it's warmer outside than inside.
You can only wear them in your house.
Right now.
See, this is why I hired you.
Because you're so smart.
But also I'd keep you in a sauna 24 hours a day so that the chains get really, really hot.
You know what actually the warmest place is?
What?
It's on stage at a rock concert.
Yeah.
So I think I'm going to have to go do that wearing your chain with KISS, with those loud lights and those bright speakers.
I guess yeah, you could do that. Anything in the interest of keeping the chains warm is fine by me.
Going off of your idea of hiring a billionaire guy, right?
Well, it's just an actor.
Well, okay, you're hiring an actor to play a billionaire guy.
Carlos Large.
What I would do, Carlos Large is a good name. What I would do...
Melvin Dollar.
(laughs)
You get an email from Melvin Dollar?
Melvin DeNiro.
Oh, that'd be good. Melvin DeNiro.
So instead of that, maybe I would stage a situation, right?
So it's like, okay, we're going to go to this restaurant at this time of day.
It's going to be me and my two friends.
This is what you would do?
So you need to sit there at this restaurant within, I don't lie, we can see you.
You need to choke on your food.
I'm going to get up. I'm going to give you the Heimlich.
I'm going to get all the food out of you.
and then you're gonna say, "Thank you for saving my life.
Here's one million dollars."
So everyone thinks that I'm a hero and now I also get a million dollars for my heroism.
Okay, so then we get it in its double...
I feel like saving somebody from choking is not an act of heroism that will be remembered for that.
Yeah, but the millionaire gives me one million dollars and that would be the thing.
It would be more impressive to win the lottery.
It would be more impressive that I save this guy's life so good that he gives me a million
dollars.
How much money do you need to end world hunger?
Probably not that much.
It's like 20 bucks I think.
Fucking Elon has enough to do it.
And guess what he's doing?
Playing on his damn phone.
Well he is writing some jokes on his phone.
He is taking that sink in, or letting that sink in.
What?
He let that sink in.
Oh.
Oh I see now.
And that was funny as fuck. If you want to come on the show and let us sink into our studio.
That would be funny as fuck. But I do think that there is a way to make all of your friends
heroes like if you win the lottery, most people disappear. Most people you'll never hear from
again. They move to Singapore or some place where they don't have to pay taxes on it.
Yeah.
Like Eduardo Savarin.
But I think you have an opportunity to make everybody around you, I mean basically make
them heroes to the entire world.
But it's got to be more than choking.
You need to do like a...
Choking on a peanut that he's allergic to.
So you give him a lot of it and then stab him with an epi pen.
Choking is not...
Nobody cares about choking.
Nobody's amazed that somebody survived choking.
Okay, bringing a dead billionaire back to life and he gives you a million dollars.
but why are you choking it on the floor in the restaurant? Bring somebody back to
life. Yes, you would be famous. You brought somebody back to life, bringing
them back to life through prayer. You're swinging too wildly here, though.
That's over the line. You're gonna... How is this over the line? I'm bringing
a millionaire back to life through prayer. If you bring somebody back to life,
they're going to study you like an alien. You're never gonna know a moment
of peace. You need somewhere in between those two goal posts. That's called
celebrity status. If you want your friends to be famous, you have to do
stuff like, one of your friends needs to be a nine-toe mom, one more than
to mom. We need to create a nine to mom. You need to do a real balloon boy where he's actually
in the balloon. Yeah, you need to do a chocolate rain, a golden radio voice homeless guy. Like
this is how people get famous. Now. Nobody is is famous for doing Schindler's List stuff
anymore that happens every day or the what do you mean like saving a bunch of people
that doesn't know nobody gets famous for saving people's lives anymore. Nobody gives a fuck
about lives, lives don't matter. You need to be or you need to knock out Francis Ngannou.
The only guy that I know who's from the MMA, UFC. The only guy I can think of famously
who saved any lives at any time in the past 30 or 40 years is that kid who saved his sister
from a pitbull who you see on Facebook every time you open Facebook. No, I've never seen
that. And he has his face all fucked up. It's the little penguin Pokemon. Oh, those are scary.
I wouldn't want to fuck with a Pokemon at all.
No.
It saves his sister from a Pokemon attack.
So that's another, or you could create a real Pokemon.
You could become a meme.
You could do some kind of, well that's already what I was saying, you could become a meme.
Like that guy from the Amberlamps video, remember that?
The old guy that just beat up a black guy and everyone was like, he's a hero.
Amberlamps, you'd be that guy.
You'd be, what's his name?
If I won the lottery, I would build a Coliseum in the desert.
Would you make people fight in it?
No, I would live there.
I would have amazing concerts.
You'd live in a Coliseum?
It's open air.
Yeah, well there's parts of it that are inside.
You'd live in a fortified Coliseum?
Barely.
Well, I'm building it.
I can put in whatever I want.
I'm not going to do an exact replica of the Coliseum.
I'm going to build a Coliseum.
What is the Coliseum for a reason?
Well, it's the one because it's that one.
Why would you want to live in a Coliseum?
This would not be a good place to live.
Again, another thing, another great place to put a real life Pokemon.
a coliseum. Yeah.
Yeah.
And have them battle it out.
I wished for Pokemon to become real on every
birthday candle and fortune cookie for my entire life.
I wish that I had code name kid next door in my backyard.
And I wished that this one tree stump that was in my backyard would turn into an elevator.
The tube elevator specifically.
And I would be sucked into it through drama.
Does anyone have a tube elevator in real life?
I want to go in a tube elevator.
Like one, not one with angles I don't believe.
No.
They can do one that goes straight up and down.
straight up and down yeah but do they? There's some hotels that have them. Really? Is that
true? The glass tubes? Yeah see right there vacuum elevator. Vacuum sucks you up. Yeah
it does. Is that Dr. Oz in that fourth one? I would not trust this shit. I almost don't
trust elevators to begin with. I don't trust elevators at all. I am anti elevator, anti
escalator. That is not Dr. Oz. How are you anti escalator? I hate escalators even more
than elevators. My cousin got afraid of escalators. Do you walk around in flippy flops all day?
No. What about long gowns? No. Well then why are you scared? Because if you fall in you
will get ground up by gears. What's his name? If you fall down. One of the stairs or some
of the stairs disappear. The bass player from Anal Cunt was doing elevator pranks, killed
himself that way, or escalator pranks. He killed himself on an escalator. I didn't even
know people could die on an escalator. He was holding onto the side of it at this mall
I know the video of the escalator collapsing and the guy gets ground up.
This happened in Boston fairly recently. I don't think anybody actually died.
If somebody gets caught, say it's an escalator going up or down.
I've heard of that.
If someone gets caught at the bottom, then everyone else is going to bunch up and they're all going to get pushed down
and get fucked up and hurt by the thing moving.
If you're going up, everyone will fall down.
In Boston that happened.
Where in Boston?
In an escalator.
In the Prudential?
I don't know.
I don't remember.
Why did you just guess the Prudential?
He just wants to prove he knows a building in Boston.
No, I just want to know about escalators.
You don't know anything.
You don't...
My Uncle Jimmy was an elevator repairman and my cousin James got afraid of, he got scared
of the escalator at the Museum of Science and when I was a kid I thought that was why.
I thought that he didn't want to betray his father.
Wow, that's actually cool. That would have been cool.
That's sweet.
Yeah, no, he was just like young.
I think somebody's selling drugs outside of my apartment.
Yeah.
I saw an old, old man and a young, young man sitting on the bench right outside my apartment.
There's a bench right up front.
It could be father and son.
But a third man of an age in between the two men came by and sat down and the young man
reached into a plastic grocery bag, brought something out, and slid it very slyly, breaking
bad into me.
Was it drugs?
I have to assume it was drugs or a rare baseball card.
It could be a rare baseball card.
And they looked at me, and I broke eye contact, and then I've been scared for two days that
they're going to try to kill me.
No.
Because I know.
They don't know that you know.
I mean, I was walking around, I was acting really weird.
You had your newspaper and a camera.
Let me rewind time for you. Here's how you should have handled that. You see him slipping
the thing into his bag. You in your brain, you know you've just seen a drug deal. Maybe
you're going to get killed for knowing what's going on here. So here's what you say. You
look at these guys on the bench. Here's what you say. "Geez, you guys are always sitting
here doing completely nothing. Why don't you find a hobby? You're not even doing anything.
You're just sitting there." Get a job, you lazy bones. "Exactly. You haven't even moved
in the past 10 minutes. You've been sitting completely still there doing nothing." You've
been sitting here for hours talking to your friends, giving them gifts.
Stop loitering. No, not... No, no, no, no.
So now you're gonna give... That's what I'm saying. Doing completely nothing.
Why don't you at least give... Yeah, you should say, "Why don't you take
up a hobby like drug dealing or something?"
I wish you guys would sell fucking drugs 'cause at least I could buy
some. Yeah. Yeah, they know that you don't know that they're doing anything.
That's how you repair the thing is like, "If you're selling drugs,
I would like some." Right. I think you're not dealing drugs, so you
shouldn't kill me, but if you were, I would be okay with me.
That's what I was wondering. Is it better if they think that I'm a
police officer because I kind of have a police officer's head and
build? Or is it better if they think that I'm just a just a
waste? OID? Yeah, because who are they least? Who are they
less likely to kill? Probably a cop? No, but a cop would is
there is their real enemy? Yeah, me. I could also be a waste or
a drug addict. I think they would probably prefer a waste
enjoyed. Yeah, but they also would kill him if they had to. This is a this is a blade
that I've been I've been teetering on. I just don't know which side to go on. I don't know
if I just start dressing like a cop when I leave my house. Start. You think I dress like
a cop? Like a undercover cop right now with the Dankirk shirt that I stole from Patrick
that I got a coffee stain on, don't tell them.
I see it. I saw it. I noticed it.
I don't know what that is.
Is this your skin?
Hey, I'm looking for some drugs.
This is a piece of Caleb's skin.
No, that's a pepita.
That's a pepita that I was eating earlier.
It got stuck to my shirt.
That's from his head.
It's lizard skin.
It's literally a pumpkin seed skin.
The heat is making him shed.
I don't wait. You think that I look like an undercover cop
with this hat on?
You think this Bud Light snapback makes me look like an undercover cop?
Hey buddy, let's drink some beers and some brown paper bags.
What's up?
Or not, actually, let's not use the brown paper bags.
Let's drink them and expose the label.
Let's drink beers out in the open.
Yo, y'all wanna hop this turnstile and come watch a Matt Rife video with me?
I think I would be an amazing undercover police officer.
Yeah.
'cause I think I am very, I'd be good with disguises.
- Maybe.
- But they would never put me on any big case.
They'd put me on parking and stuff.
- No, they would know you from your videos.
- You'd be a desk jockey.
- They would see guys who were getting caught
by undercover cops are like,
"Damn, Caleb, when's that new video dropping?"
- No, they would not care about my videos.
- "When's that new Twitter video dropping, Caleb?"
(laughing)
You haven't posted one in a minute.
- They would not do that.
and then I would say, "Check my TikTok, y'all." You'd be arresting a guy and he'd
be like, "I put new ones on my TikTok, y'all." You'd be arresting a guy and he'd
be like, "I'm gonna fucking kill you. Yo, wait."
No, you would not say, "Yo, wait." I need to point at you. And he'd be like,
"Everyone, come here. Yo, he loves eating shit."
Every day I am punished for being an artist.
Every day my friends punish me. Oh, you wish. We all are. Notice how we never
go, "Oh, man.
Patrick, you're so...
What's a video you've made?
None of them have been good.
Bingo.
See, that's the difference.
They might go, "Oh, Patrick, you did a stand-up thing with an alert in it."
And they go, "Remember that?"
No.
No one remembers that.
My videos, hundreds of billions, literally legend forever.
Know your meme status.
I don't think I have a know your meme page, but I could.
I don't have one.
I'm sure you do. No, no, Caleb. It's know your meme right now. I don't have one.
Why are you going to Google? I would
I would bet ten dollars. I don't have one.
I might be referenced. No, I bet you as a person don't have a page, but
I bet that your memes do. There's no know your meme, y'all.
What? Somebody posted one of my videos
retard in it? What is this? What is okay buddy retard? It's a little kids subreddit. Oh okay
for memes. Well okay so I don't have a know your meme page so you guys just got destroyed.
Maybe but maybe I could be. Why does it say Caleb Pitts the 1975? What did you do with
the 1975.
Caleb Pitts of the 1975.
That's not me.
No, that's you.
That is your from your appearance on
Raisin Man Arena.
Oh, OK.
Yeah. Yeah, that probably.
There's our friend Ben Loftus.
This is awesome, guys.
Yeah, I think we can.
Yeah, I think you could have stopped this.
Maybe we're done looking at all these
pictures.
Yeah, well.
We will find your know your meme page.
I don't have one, bro.
You might have one.
No, I do not. I haven't, I seldom made it to that. That is truly a mortal status.
Yeah, that is truly a mortal status.
If you get a know your meme page.
Didn't you get a know your meme?
I did get know your meme for Great Peppers.
Whoa!
Real ones remember that.
Damn.
Yeah.
That's actually fire.
One result. Jingling keys.
And it's about the Tim Pool thing again, huh?
again huh? Oh look at you! See that's what people if you were an undercover cop people
would be like wait. I'd be good at it because I know the streets. I know you're not a cop
you hated on Tim Pooles. There's no way you're a police officer. You were shitting on him.
They wouldn't put me on undercover duty as a cop because I would be too obviously a cop
just from looking at me people would know. That's true because you got that mustache.
Yeah I got that look I wear those type of clothes. You do dress like a cop more than
any of us three. And when I see crime I go...
Just like a cop does. You could probably be a cop in New York City. Cops in New York City
are all built like Oompa Loompas. Yeah. You're saying he's built like an Oompa Loompa? You're
saying he's short and round? No, I'm saying they can be. You're saying Cameron is short
and stout? I don't think I've ever seen a cop that looks like me. I've never seen representation
I've seen a million cops that look like me.
I, have I ever told you the time, like when I was like 16 years old.
It's because guys who look like me become actors.
There's a lot of guys that look like me.
This is a beat cop over here.
I'm a beat cop police chief.
You look like a police chief.
You know what I could actually be?
I could actually be a detective.
You could definitely be a detective.
Yeah, I could see you in a trench coat.
Maybe a detective for cybercrimes.
There was, there was this, uh, there was this like student, it wasn't the resource officer,
He was like the detective that was assigned to the school for some reason.
He was trying to make sure that kids weren't dealing...
He was a school detective?
Dude, it was so weird.
He worked for the...
You did not go to a normal school, man.
No, I did not.
But, like, they had nothing to do...
You don't dismiss a school police officer.
My hometown had a SWAT team...
I feel like it was a normal school police officer.
Well, no, he was saying that he would walk around in a fucking trench coat and everyone
knew he was a cop.
but he was there. It wasn't a detective. Did he have a magnifying glass on some
days?
On some days, he had to use a detective. Yeah, I don't believe he would hang out
with the resource officer. He would hang out with the resource officer and he
had a like a full like tan trench coat. A fashion. That's what you're describing.
Maybe that's what I don't think a detective wears a tan trench coat. No,
No, they don't. A detective is just a piece of clothing.
You're thinking like L.A. Noire. A detective is just a higher level cop.
The school, my hometown had a SWAT team because the airport in Manchester,
New Hampshire was technically in Londonderry.
So they had a huge police budget.
So there was cops right next to the police station.
They had enough of a police budget to do period accurate costumes for the cops?
I wonder why this guy would walk around the school in a trench coat. He probably just wore that.
Cops are weird. They like to wear strange clothes. No, because my uncle knew of him.
He thought he looked cool. He did look cool. He knew of him. And then they found a bunch of blood
in the parking lot in front of the- hold on, hold on. They found a bunch of blood in the parking lot
of this plaza that they had, the pizza place everyone went to, Prosciutto's Pizza. They found
a bunch of blood and the detective went on a full investigation. He was like, "We are
not ruling out homicide. There's no way that this is like... Somebody was shot here." And
I think he was on the news in his little trench coat, fully created this fake homicide investigation
because somebody hit a deer and it ran in the woods and died.
This was animal blood.
This was animal blood. And he immediately...
So whatever. So this was...
immediately went for fucking like this. This was a detective who came to your
school to investigate something. I think that there was this was not a school
detective. This was kids selling drugs and he was in the school sometimes as a
detective. This was a detective who was at your school. It's not your school
detective. No, I think that my wording there was very bad, but he would chill
in the school sometimes and so I thought he was a school detective. Investigating
stuff. I don't think he was chilling there. He was he was dude, cause he wasn't doing
shit. He was just standing there thinking detectives get paid. He's probably reasoning.
He's reasoning. He's probably reasoning. He's probably deducting stuff. Yeah, exactly. Yeah.
But that fucking that deer thing was so crazy. Did he ever like say what's up to you and
be like, he never, he didn't talk to me. He was afraid of me. But he wasn't afraid of you.
No detective would be afraid of you. You were the most easily detected person. That's so
So funny to show up in a big...
Why is he wearing the detective thing?
Why is he wearing a detective outfit?
Again, bro.
It's the same reason that
any person wears a trench coat.
Because they think for some reason
that they look cool doing it.
Well, I thought he maybe could have been a school shooter.
It's the same reason a firefighter wears...
An old school shooter with a badge.
He shows up in the trench coat and is like, "Man..."
It's the same reason a firefighter wears
that big hat
hat and all that reflective stuff. They don't need that. They don't need that. Farmer doesn't
need that. A farmer could dress in full fucking V-Loan and it would make no difference to the
vegetable. The vegetable is going to come out still bright orange. People with different
jobs dress like that so that children see them and know what job they are. It's to help
civilization. Exactly. It's rich and scary. Yeah. I guess, I mean, if he didn't want us
to know he was a detective, we knew immediately.
Because everybody looks the same.
All people look, I cannot tell the difference between any two people.
Unless they have different clothes on, then I might be able to say what job they have.
Yeah.
So that's why I knew that these guys were drug dealers.
One of them was wearing Crocs, the other one was wearing like slacks and like nice dress shoes.
Yeah.
Oh, he's the dealer.
What is the only...
The two tights.
These two...
He's the kingpin.
He's wearing loafers.
Exactly.
That's what I was saying.
I was like, this has to be deeper than just a normal coroner deal.
This is mafia.
Because otherwise, why would a schlubby guy in a Rick and Morty shirt and Crocs be hanging
out with this Don Dada?
Well, you live near a pizza place, right?
That could be he could be.
I've always wanted to stumble into a mafia thing and then get away.
I've been thinking about it so much.
There's a pork store down the street.
I want to go into a store and see a bunch of guys in suits and be like, "Whoa, sorry!"
and walk out.
There's a pork store down the street that's never, I've never seen it open.
I always thought it was just always closed. Today, I saw two guys unpack or
like putting giant boxes into a van out of the pork store and the pork store had
like lights on and stuff. I was like, wait, these guys are moving something
other than a dead animal. Yeah, there's a pizza place over and if I was a police
officer, I would have said, guys, I'm getting a box cutter. I'm opening these
boxes. I'm putting you on citizens arrest. There's a pizza place that way
that always has, they always have folding tables outside with a ton of guys just
sitting there hanging out. Yeah. And I, that's always my imagination. I always
like, Oh, I think I know the one you're talking about. Yeah. I always, I think
it's just a family who lives there, but I always look at them like I want it to
be a different type of family. Any, any, like if a bunch of old white guys are
are hanging out and they all have really tiny tucked in white t-shirts. Yeah.
It's the mafia. Yeah. They're all in weird lounge wear. I've also, I've
I looked it up. There is an active Polish mafia in Bridgewood, Queens.
Oh yeah.
That's so swag dude.
And we might be stumbling into their crosshairs.
Somebody that I know lives close enough to the office.
You?
No.
Oh.
There's somebody that I know that lives close to the office.
When we were first moving in and shit, they live across the street or something.
I think they would see us going in and out all the time.
And they were like, "What the fuck is going on?"
They thought that we were...
Because the gate is closed sometimes, the gate is open.
Oh.
It was like this whole...
I talked to them, they were like, "Oh, so you live around here, blah, blah, blah."
I was like, "Oh yeah, our studio is over there."
They're like, "Oh my God, that's you guys."
They thought that we were mobbed up.
I thought somebody was going...
I thought that it was like fucking mafia or some shit.
I do always think it's funny to imagine,
especially when I come in here just to do like,
not even to record, but just to like grab something
or do something.
I have just people who live here.
It must be very funny to see someone opening the gate
and going in for 30 minutes and then coming in
and like locking everything up with bed locks.
- I think, I do think the day is coming
where we get a knock on that door right over there
and an old, old man says,
this is a pretty rough and tumble dangerous neighborhood.
You need protection.
- You need protection.
- Yeah.
to shell out probably some of these waters. I would be like, "Oh, that's kind of nice,
but no, thank you." No, actually, no, Tai Chi. Yeah, I think we're going to be okay.
Yeah. We have the locks on the door. We have the prop gun that we have. See, I would love
to put that in somebody's face, jam the stick in someone's face, up the pole. Yeah. I want
to up the pole into a Polish guy's face and say, "Get the f..." Up the pole is a... What
does that mean? It means put the blicky in their face. Because, buddy, where I'm from,
does not mean gun. Does it mean penis? Peca. What? Peca. Sucking on a pole? Sucking on
some pole. Sucking on pole. That's what you think. If you go up the pole, you zesty. You
think it's zesty to go up the pole. But we should do some decoy stuff in here because
I don't want people to automatically know exactly what this is. So we should have
that big sticker on the window. We should have like a big with our logo.
We should have like a brewers vat. Yeah. You know, so it makes it look like we're
maybe right. Something that from outside looks completely illegal. Yeah. Yeah.
Something that a moonshine still. Yeah. That's what we should have in here. We
should have a full moonshine still. Something to draw even way more
attention. Yeah. Yeah. Or we should put the word for sale on the door. I do want
to put a I think that this might draw suspicion put in a sticker on it and it
would stop people from walking in that says not open to the public yeah that
would be exclusive as fuck yeah oh yeah easy or be ready to present your
credentials yeah yeah members only yeah there's a supper club yes members only
supper club that's the other reason why there's definitely mafia yeah yeah what
need a members only club buddy? What is it? Is it ROTC? Can I become a member? I've never
felt more FOMO in my entire life than when I walk by a members club or like a supper
club or like a members only bar or something like that and I see somebody walking out and
I see just the I see the crack of the door. I see the velvet. I see steamed hams of old
guys hanging out and I'm like, oh I need to go in. I want to be there. I want to be there
I want to be in there so fucking bad.
I want to be their gopher.
I want them to...
I need you to buy me a pack of fucking misty lights.
I need to be fucking wedding crashers in there.
I need you to buy me unfiltered cigarettes.
Go get 'em, boy.
I need to try and juggle two different guys who I'm telling each of them that I'm there as a guest of the other guy.
Do you think that we could blend in?
You keep changing your outfits in the bathroom?
Oh my god.
The thing is, I would probably let three white guys in.
Yeah, that's a good point.
I think that's the whole point of those members only thing.
only thing. I don't want to say what it is or what it's called because I might get assassinated.
It's right by my house, but there's one that I want us all to join. Yeah, I'll join one.
Yeah. Is it? Is it? Okay, it's not that close to my house. I'll say what it is. It's the
Italian Americans Club. No, they had one of those in in one of those water towns. I want
I want to get into a, what do they call it?
This one is called the Soccer and Folklore Club.
Whoa!
And I've seen the door open one time and it's a bar.
Yeah.
But it's a members only.
It's a bar where they have soccer and they talk about that course.
It looks like a VFW inside.
I want to go to, I've never been to a VFW.
We should go to a VFW.
Can you get into one?
There's one in Londonderry that I used to go to.
Don't you have to be a veteran of a foreign war?
I don't know, I think because my grandpa was a veteran of a foreign war.
in the meme wars of 2016. Walking in with a meme war veteran hat, trying to talk to some
fucking decrepit old man who has Agent Orange burns all over his face. Oh man, I want to
belong to something. Is that what Agent Orange does? It burns you. It sticks to your skin
and burns you. And if you have kids it makes them odd. Yeah, it makes them orange. That's
That's why they call it Agent Orange.
Oh, that makes sense.
And they call it Agent because it was secret.
Yeah.
I think there's a members only club down the street that I saw on the way walking over
here today.
I'd never noticed it before.
And it has an Italiano flag on it.
So I think I might be able to get into that one.
Also the door was open.
It was just wide open.
They leave it open to air out.
We should apply to every single one in the area.
I need to get into a members only.
Can you just apply?
We could just turn this into a members only club.
Yeah.
A speakeasy.
But a speakeasy, like, we could go to jail for being a speakeasy.
No, because it's donation based.
Is that true?
You can just say that we're an art gallery and you are donating and the donation gets
you a free beer.
Oh, okay.
Pretty smart.
We could do that.
Yeah.
What would our art be, though?
I mean, I could make some stuff.
This is a good piece of art right here.
Photoshop.
Right behind us.
No, you can't do Photoshop art.
We don't do that new age bullshit.
but it could be new age bullshit so that the cops can't figure that shit out.
We're looking to bring a pinch of the old world across the pond.
So we have to learn like renaissance paintings and stuff?
Yes.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I watched a video the other day.
Or at the very least get some.
Okay.
They're pretty expensive man.
I didn't say buy some, but I won't put any more details into the recording.
There's a video that I saw yesterday of a bunch of people, speaking of the old world,
the old world, a bunch of people in Ireland walking down the street and they get asked
if they know how to speak Irish and then they start speaking Irish. That is not a human language.
Crazy language. Unfair, I guess I have it. Why do they speak that? That means man and
woman. They have it. Unfair, I guess I have it. Unfair and a woman. August is and. So
So fair August fair would be man and man.
Is that where fairy comes from?
Maybe as a homophobic slur?
I think fairy is fair folk, right?
Yeah, but I mean like fairy like, oh, he's a bit of a fairy.
He's a manny.
I don't know.
You have to ask the Irish.
Yeah, I guess we'd have to ask the Irish.
But no wonder they can't stop fighting each other up there.
Yeah, it's on every sign they have it.
have it's like bilingual. So they have yeah.
Is there any people who don't speak English and they only speak Irish?
No, the last of those people I think are dead, but there are people who speak Irish as a first
language or I yeah it's everyone in Ireland is taught Irish in school I guess and then
it's I think there was a population of people who only spoke Irish and there might be like
a couple left but I think for the most part everyone speaks English now.
I really hate heritage.
Yeah.
I think that nobody needs to have any heritage at all.
And we just need to have a full reset.
So that's basically how it is now.
That's what I mean. I think it's pretty good right now.
Yeah.
The fuck are you doing on there?
Sorry.
You just Patrick'd.
I did. He was flashing these.
So yeah, my peripherals.
You know, he didn't even mention it.
Patrick.
Okay.
And I didn't look at it.
He didn't even notice it.
But yeah, I think that everybody, and it doesn't have to be English, but everybody should just
be speaking one language.
That's barren.
Because where is, yes.
I think we should go back to the Adamic tongue.
What's that?
The pre-Tower of Babel language of God.
What is that?
How do you speak it?
It's lost.
Nobody knows.
Mormonism says it's going to come back.
Yeah.
We just need to reverse.
They also say that everyone gets their own planet.
Yeah, well, they also say, well, only the men.
also say that if you wear a special Mormon underwear, you're protected from gunshots
and car crashes.
That's true.
To be fair, I've never heard of a Mormon being shot to death. I don't think that happens.
They definitely have something figured out. I think Utah probably has the lowest rate of
homicide of any state.
Well, that's because all their beer is like 3%.
They don't drink, they don't even do caffeine.
If you're, if, well, I mean, they do caffeine.
They don't swear, so there's no way for it to get tempers rising.
That's what they do at the Brigham Young parties, is like, they drink a lot of like diet coke
or like coke and they go like, "Oh!"
No, they don't, they're not allowed to have caffeine.
No, they drink a lot of soda.
They do stuff they're not allowed to because they're in college.
Caffeine-free soda.
In college, you think they're popping out the caffeine.
I think they probably are, but yeah, the thing of Mormonism is you're not supposed to.
Yeah, that's the thing is like, well, in college I drank soda and now because I feel so bad
bad I'm devoting my life to our God.
That's what they instead of having coffee shops in Utah they have soda shops.
Yeah.
Where you go and you get they make a...
They have a barista?
I'm serious.
Really?
Yeah there's like a bunch of chains of soda shops where people go in the morning and they'll
get a soda with cream in it like it's a coffee and put whipped cream and sprinkles on the
top.
Yeah.
It's their uh...
Fuckin what is it?
It's like it's their like mocha frappuccino or something.
The soda shop is a sip of Utah culture.
Yeah, it's all like...
Look how disgusting that is.
They're the weirdest,
the weirdest fucking people in the world.
But it's all branded like crumble cookie and shit.
Like that kind of new kind of business that will fail.
These are all caffeine free sodas.
Oh yeah, they're just putting the syrups in the...
I wish Mormonism wasn't so evil
because they have so much crazy cool stuff
just built into their shit.
You know the white horse prophecy?
No.
That's that the Mormons believe that at some point the U.S.
Constitution will be brought to its knees and the only people that can save it
will be the Mormons.
How are you going to bring a piece of paper to its knees?
And they call it the White Horse Prophecy.
There is this old...
What does that mean, brought to its knees?
Like it'll be hanging by a thread.
But what does that mean in regards to the Constitution?
It's a prophecy, it's not supposed to make sense.
There's this old Mormon like tape, like this old like thing.
I saw it recently, it's like something they show in their Sunday schools where it's like
how they taught the gospel of Joseph Smith to the natives and the way that they represent
them going to the light is that they turn white.
They turn white.
People turn white in the afterlife.
Well, you know what the curse of Cain is in Mormonism?
So in the Bible it says when Cain kills Abel, God gives Cain the mark of Cain, like he curses
So the mark of Cain in Mormonism, they interpret that as meaning that God
turned Cain black and that all black people are descendants of Cain and
they're cursed because of that.
Okay, wait, I didn't hear about this.
They also have a thing called the curse of Ham, where there's another
biblical guy named Ham and his lineage gets cursed to become slaves.
So they believe that black people are descendants of Cain and Ham, and that's
why they are black and that's why they were slaves, because they were cursed by God.
There's a bake shop in Utah.
they only like renounced this and like I think it was like the 70s, late 70s that
they were like okay or no it was it was I think it was like the late 70s were
like maybe this isn't true and they didn't officially contradict it until
like 2015 or something. There was a bake shop in Utah that made a bunch of cookies
that were like like the name of them was like cane something yeah it was like
fucking crazy there was like a double chocolate cookie. It's so nice. Did you guys know that the Catholic
Catholic Church raped like five million kids.
(laughter)
You know, I think they're all...
But they don't have as many cool
things, ideas, prophecies to counterbalance.
The Catholic Church has so much cool shit
going on. Yeah. You know, you see,
you're playing devil's advocate here,
because I know you hate Catholicism.
I love Catholicism. You grew up...
I've never heard you talk positively about Catholicism
until I just said that. I don't like...
ever touched shit. But it is cool that they have.
It's been held away into my mind forever.
I'm not letting you get away with it.
It is cool that they have so many...
They have a lot of cool secret stuff.
I like the secret stuff. You like the secret boy touching?
Not that secret stuff.
That's that secret stuff.
No dude, they have the
Ark of the Covenant, all that kind of stuff.
The relics? Yeah, all the old relics
are cool. It's cool that they have them and they
say, "We don't know where this shit is, but it's all
under the Vatican. I've learned this."
Yeah, well, I think they don't have the three Nephites. Yeah, what's the Nephites? Those
are three immortal guys that help Mormonism. Yeah, yeah, they're are they still around?
Yeah, they were doing dude, they were doing this shit in 2012. So they do like proxy Mormon
baptisms for like, people who I do know the Mormons believe this is so cool. The Mormons
believed that the great flood was the baptism of the earth. That's so smart. That's crazy.
Isn't that awesome? That's so smart. But they did a proxy baptism in 2012 for Anne Frank.
I think you've told me that before. So what? I mean, someone had to do it. No, if no one's
going to do this, I guess we'll step up. I mean, it's been a while. If anyone was going
to do this, they would have done it by now. The honest truth is, if you are a Mormon,
is the right thing to do. If you fully believe that you're saving her immortal soul, then
fucking do it. You should be baptized. Baptize everyone, dude.
That's what they do. They just put little Mormon kids in a tub.
Do they think that normal Christians are going to heaven?
No. I think they only think Mormons are going to heaven.
Really? I think it's only Mormons.
Who had that? Our friend Tom had that joke.
Believe that, yeah. There was something I was reading. I was reading a lot about Mormonism
recently and I think it's something like they believe modern, or they think the Roman
Catholic Church is the great enemy. I think that's the biggest enemy to Mormons. I think
they said that modern Christianity has less in common with the truth than like some...
Yeah, it was something where I think they don't like...
You know there's a famous Mormon, Napoleon Dynamite, creator.
Wasn't that whole squad?
Whole squad Mormons.
That's crazy.
And the Killers.
Really?
The Killers is a Mormon.
That's not a very Mormon name for your band.
No.
But that's why it's rock and roll.
But I think a lot of their songs are...
They were thinking of the darkest name they could possibly think of.
All of their songs are like Mormon stuff.
What?
Pretty much all of them.
What's a killer song?
Mr. Brightside.
That's not Mormon.
Mr. White Guy.
Nazis Violinist Lead.
I Got Soul.
I'm Not A Soldier.
Now She's Drinking Soda.
And I'm Drinking Caffeine.
That is not Mormon.
Mr. Brightside is not a Mormon song dude.
I think it is.
I think they're all Mormon.
I mean I believe they are all Mormon.
Brandon Flowers is a Mormon.
That's just one.
And his name is fucking Brandon Flowers.
Is Gene Simmons?
No, he's Jewish.
Gene Simmons is completely Jewish.
Yeah.
He is Jewish, isn't he?
His real name is Chaim Witz.
Really?
Yeah.
Wow.
That's cool.
That's a cooler name than Gene.
Gene Simmons, yeah.
I like that.
That's the coolest name he could come up with for a stage name.
Well, I mean, it was the 70s.
You know, you go up dressed up like a demon and your name is Chaim Witz.
I think a lot of people are going to...
I guess he was always sticking his tongue out because he needed the Heimlich maneuver.
Do you think the Heimlich maneuver is you get your tongue out of your throat?
Well how else are you going to signal that you're choking?
You can't say anything.
Well you go like this.
Yeah I guess you're right.
True.
You go ahhhh.
Man Kiss is like one of the worst bands ever.
The worst band of all time.
I remember being so disappointed because I thought my entire life growing up I was like
Kiss is like badass hardcore metal probably right?
I'd never heard a Kiss song, but just based on how they looked.
And then I played Guitar Hero,
and it was like the wackest song I've ever heard
in my entire life.
♪ Everybody says you're looking good ♪
It's like not, it doesn't fit the look, man.
No, no.
You can't have metal shoulder pads
and sing about how you're everything,
but in your entire song, it's about staying up past midnight.
They have that song, God of Thunder,
which like, that makes sense with their whole image,
but it's like, if you're gonna do that,
if you're gonna dress like that and be like,
"I love rock and roll, baby!"
It's like, what the fuck?
Like, why are you dressed up like a demon to do that?
You could...
Yeah.
Their marketing is so fucking crazy.
They've like only stayed relevant because of like how much merch they put up.
If you look up like the Kiss website, it's like a fucking like, it's like SkyMall.
Like they have every single thing with the Kiss logo on it.
Probably.
Like, they like, what they tried to...
Yeah, they had that arena football team.
We like, we watched that show, right?
what was it called? Like they had the, it was on, it was on Tubi.
Remember we would, we would watch this together.
I never have seen this with them.
They had a reality show where like half of the show,
I've definitely talked about it before, but the LA kiss,
they bought an arena football team, tried to bring back arena football. Uh,
the whole show is them creating the LA kiss and half the show is just Gene
Simmons and Paul Stanley in business meetings. And they're like,
this logo looks really good. I love that so much.
And then the other half of the show is men who tried to get into the NFL and have been
playing football and doing MMA and shit their whole life.
They have so much CTE that if I get another concussion during training, I will go completely
blind.
And they're doing that for fucking the LA Kiss.
I mean, they're doing it for a bag, dude.
They don't care who they're...
They're mercenaries.
Yeah, that's true.
that's true that would be a better name the LA mercenaries than the LA Kiss.
Well these days you'd probably have a real mercenaries complaining about the
name mm-hmm and you probably would have real people who kiss complaining about
the kiss name too. Yeah I think it should all just be football team. Their name
should be football team. The Panthers the North Carolina football team it should
all just be that. Yeah that was that was the coolest. That's how they used to name baseball
teams. What do you mean? Like the red socks were like the team that wore red socks, the
white socks wore white socks, there was the black socks. Like most baseball teams were
just named after like the shit that they were wearing. What about the Astros? Well they're
a later team. Oh. They came later. Well what are we, okay so we all have socks, but what
else? Athletics? They wore what? Athletic clothes when they played fucking baseball?
I mean it was like, there was probably like 8 teams in the MLB I think. That's another
sport that it's been around long enough you guys that we get it you all the pictures that
you have of the sport are from 1905. Yeah, stop it. It's not enough. Nobody needs that
sport now. We can get rid of baseball. We don't need it. It sucks. You know, the hats
were almost completely like the baseball hat as we know it was almost completely different.
We were almost this one and this would have been like a like one of those fucking flat
caps. But because this is like the like the kind of like the baseball hat that they have
now is like the Brooklyn style hat. Are you telling me all the teams had different style
hats? Pretty much, yeah. That is cool. That's why the Pirates had like pillbox hats for
like ever. That's so cool, man. Pillbox hats look terrible though. On my head, I can't wear
that shit. Wait, what's a pillbox hat? The square hat. Oh, I thought you were talking
about a pirate hat. No, no, no. You're thinking of a tri-corner hat. That's what they should
have been wearing. That's what they should have been wearing. A tri-corner hat with a
They should have all had different hats, you're right.
But there's a thing that I saw the other day,
and I think it was one of the first new era pamphlets
or styles of baseball hats teams could get.
And there's like eight of them.
There's like eight different hats that they could have chose from.
Did you guys know that the old real pirates
are basically like bloodscrips of their kind of era?
I knew that.
I thought they were heroes.
You thought they were heroes?
I thought heroes were cowboys and pirates, but it turns out these guys were not good.
They were criminals.
They were bad guys.
Cowboys were called cowboys because they were boys that stole cows.
And pirates would steal.
Pirates would get drunk all day on grog and pickles.
There's jeans called rustlers.
Probably named after rustlers.
That's like having a pair of pants named Latin Kings.
You're right.
I guess it is.
I guess.
I would wear it. I would imagine him.
Some LKs.
Imagine the bedazzling on the back.
It would be amazing.
Oh my god. Imagine what those look like.
Bedazzled AK-47 on one side, Mickey Mouse on the other.
Speaking of clothes, yesterday I was with my friend Henry. I was trying to show him
those shoes that Sam has, the Subway.
Yeah.
The Subway like Jordan 7s. Have you seen those? Has he shown you them?
He has Subway shoes.
Yeah, it's the shoes with the Subway logo on them. They're so sick. But I was trying
to show him what they look like. I found this website called I love my family forever and
it's just all just like they're putting different like brand logos into like these 3D shirts.
You know the type I'm talking about?
What?
Hold on, I have some photos.
I love my family forever?
The website is called I love my family forever and yeah it's like this. You can get like
custom, oh here it is.
Are you doing an ad?
No, I wish.
Whoa.
I wish they would send us some shit.
Look at these.
These are like soccer jerseys basically.
Yeah, pretty much.
Dude, those look like Assassin's Creed.
Yeah.
This one, this hat right here, the Hormel chili.
Nice.
Damn.
The Frank logo.
These are expensive, man.
That is.
Zoomies shoes.
Oh my God, that is fire.
Wow.
These Zoomies shoes are fucking sick.
Oh, you can get custom printed.
You get your name on the front and Walmart on the back.
This is the one that I think Cameron would love the most.
day. Halloween Arby's. Whoa, that is tight on that. But they have all these fucking Halloween
graphics like they got like pictures of like the Grinch with like the Patriots logo. Oh
yeah, the Punisher. Henry sent me the Dunkin Donuts. The Punisher Papa John's shirt. Punisher
Home Depot is really sick. These are sick, man. I mean, I guess this is if you are. Oh,
you could also get it on a polo shirt. This graphic. This is kind of what's it called?
malicious compliance. If you are trying to fit with your work uniform. You wear one of
these things.
Yeah, these are, dude, this Pepsi logo is so fucking sick. This is the coolest shit I've
ever seen.
The thing is, man, none of these clothes ever fit a normal human.
No, no, no.
They don't, these are not meant for normal people to wear. This is like peewee football
coach body. It's the only thing that can fit into this kind of hoodie.
Oh yeah, they're made out of like 100% like...
When I was in Ireland and I was in the tourist shops, I was trying to find a nice sweater.
Every sweater I put on that was my size, it's so funny, they're all completely made for guys
with the biggest bellies of all time. They all looked so insane and horrible on me because
they're all built, they're all like knit together to like stretch like three times only in the
stomach. It was so horrible.
Yeah, I mean we have plenty of fatties here, and I love them because they're here, but in any other country
Do not like the fatties in other countries
Make some clothes for the skinnies because again we turn mostly he's over in Europe because they don't have sugar in their food
They have they have
You don't have any sugar in there for they have nothing that makes it
There is an entire country that eats a pastry every morning where France?
They eat pastry every morning.
I know, actually I do that too.
They may not have sugar bloating up their belly, but I think that everybody in Europe has some
kind of gas bubble that's been in their stomach like a baby for nine months straight.
Guilt from World War II.
They eat beans for breakfast.
They're walking around pregnant with guilt.
I don't think beans for breakfast is that crazy.
It's not.
That's because they do that in New Hampshire.
It's not that crazy.
That's true, yeah.
I'm not that good. I ate it that one time when we went to that red arrow diner.
The red arrow. Yeah, we got takeaway and we brought it to your apartment and it
was not very good. There's no reason to eat beans for breakfast. The beans
weren't good or the red arrow food. Just well both. But why would you eat? Yeah,
just is not a breakfast food. It's not right. I mean, I don't know. I do like
beans on toast. That is the British in me speaking. It's not good. You're not.
We were. Oh, he just admitted he was British because he's 100% Irish and it's
the same thing. No, you just said that shit. 100% British and Irish. I just don't like to
talk about it. Oh, really? You're not 100% Irish. What if you were like 95% British?
Do you probably are? You probably are. Well, again, it's the same thing. I don't even care.
I'm not going to get into this. You're not going to get into this. No, no. You know what?
I'm being a bigger person. I'm being a bigger person than Caleb today. No, you're not guys.
Jake and Logan Paul are beefing. They're brothers. That's what I said. I bet it's a, uh, is it
over the licensing of what's it called? No. What's it called when you have anything to
do with Prime? An investment. No, when you do something, a trick. Yeah, but it's for
attention. A magic trick. Oh, it's a publicity stunt. Publicity stunt. Yeah, it's definitely
a publicity stunt. It's a publicity stunt. I don't think so. I think Jake's serious this
time y'all. He said Logan is accusing Jake of not letting him bring a Prime bottle into
to
that guy is serious black. He's supposed to be his godfather.
They named him serious black.
Serious black. That's a Netflix special, dude.
You got to be really glad that JK Rowling named Dumbledore before she
decided that he was gay. Yeah. Yeah. Oh my God. Could you imagine? You
imagine Dumbledore's name if she was like you're gay from the get go?
it would have been like stretchy hole.
It would have been yeah, but like it's so she's so like twinkle fairy. She
wanted to be so subtle
she would have named him like underwear or something yeah or she's like she
would have named him like like Barnabas jock strap yeah
professor anal puke.
I mean, those names are just crazy man. Professor Pervious. Yeah, it would have
been Pervious. Yeah, because she named it in the 90s.
The only one that is not like that is McGonagall. Pervious Indoctrinatio.
Snape. That would be his spell. Severus Snape is a name for an evil guy.
It is so fucking funny, Severus Snape. She sucks so bad, dude. I've never
liked those Harry Potter things. I'm glad that the public opinion... I so love
Harry Potter. I'm so glad the public opinion is like I stopped
looking at Potter on the fifth book. I was like never never
read all of them. I read all of them too, but they were
basically hate those little fucking wizards. Then do
something about it. I'm gonna kill her Daniel Radcliffe.
Look the fuck out. You stole my birthday. He's goaded.
He fucked a horse on stage. He played weird. Ellen a funny
ass movie. That was almost two and a half hours. I forgot
about the weirdo movie really movie of all time. That makes
me so sad. I couldn't finish it. I thought it was alright. I thought it was so, I thought
it was the most, it's made by Funny or Die and you can tell that it's made by Funny or
Die. It's based off a Funny or Die skit from like 10 years ago. Oh god. And it's a skit,
not even a sketch. Did Daniel crush? Daniel was okay. Did he suck a horse's penis? You
know what Daniel Radcliffe, I rescind my threat. I'm threatening now Harry Potter and Ron Weasley.
We've seen the bugs, the invasive bugs. You've seen them?
The red lanternflies.
I've been thinking about this so, so much.
I'd like to issue a warning to science. We've seen these bugs. If you pull up a picture of
one on the screen to search lanternfly, these are invasive bugs that are attacking from,
let's just say China.
They're not attacking.
Let's say they're coming from China. We'll say that they are because they're from...
They're from...
Oh, it is native to China.
got these bugs. You'll see you've probably seen them around if you're in this area in
New York. I don't know where else in the United States they're coming, but I know they're a
big deal here right now. These bugs, they've got a larval stage that looks like that little
spotted red thing right there. You see that? And then they've got the big adult ones. Now
I'd like to issue a warning to China, I mean to the US government, but a warning to China
also, but separate from this. The US government, beware because if there's any knowledge I've
gained from my life as a video gamer. Phase one, phase two, there's always going to be
a third evolution. Okay, we have not seen the Charizard of these bugs yet. You're right
in the Charmander. We've seen the Charmeleon. Watch the fuck out. That's why we're killing
him now. Get ready. You're anticipating legs that could have pants. I'm think that I think
that we're going to be seeing a large new type of bug with my powers and an added type that
really scares me spotted as a type spot is a type I I was thinking that for those who
were more poetically inclined than I am maybe a great poem would be from the perspective
of one of these spotter lantern flies about someone's looking in how you have I thought
it was maybe a package for us but he just looked in and went and then he's just interested
that's fine, well he heard me.
But--
- He's a poet.
- Well, I'm gonna give him this idea.
Guys, if I was a spotter lanternfly,
I'm looking around--
- Do you have a poem at the ready?
- I'm seeing, no shut the fuck up.
I'm seeing a butterfly descend from a tree
and land on a child's finger.
I'm seeing everybody around the child
look in awe at this beautiful creature
and people clap and people kiss
and people celebrate, they're popping champagne.
I see a ladybug crawling on the ground,
somebody's foot about to step on it,
then they realize, "Oh, that's a ladybug.
I'll allow it onto my body to piss and shit on me."
- Yep.
- Me, a spotted lanternfly,
the perfect combination of a ladybug and a butterfly,
is being massacred.
Literally, people are trying to do a complete genocide
on these bugs,
even though they're just as beautiful as every other bug,
or even as the most beautiful bugs,
the bugs that we allow to be in our homes.
People let butterflies...
I'm personally, I'm scared of butterflies. A butterfly landed on my head the other day
and I screamed and a little kid laughed at me. I was at the dog park. A spotted lanternfly
is just as beautiful and scary as a butterfly. Stop the hate. Why are we killing these things?
My cat ate one.
But what is the problem? People say it's an invasive species. I don't give a fuck. It's
a bug. It's not taking up that much space. It's little. I don't care.
One of them landed on my headphone.
If there was so many of them, well, okay. I'll say this much.
The spotted lanternflies do not know how to act.
No, they don't.
That's why they're making us kill them.
They do not know how to act.
They're too much.
They act, they're wiling out.
You can tell they're new bugs.
Yeah.
They're new bugs.
They don't know how to act yet.
They are acting brand fucking new.
They're walking around like they own this place.
They fly up and land on you.
You are a guest in America.
You're originated from China and Vietnam.
I've been seeing, can you go back to that lanternfly thing?
My girlfriend has been letting,
she's saying that she's been finding ladybugs
in the apartment and letting them free.
They've been looking a lot like that motherfucker
on the top right.
Yeah, this top right, that's the nymph,
I think it's called, form of the lanternfly.
She has been making me open the window for her
so she can free them.
Wow.
I should be I should be smacking the crap out of those bugs. I was seeing those bugs around
before before the this the second wave because they come in the summer. Yeah. Before the
second wave was going on, I was seeing these little guys around and I fully was 100% convinced
I discovered a new bug and I was ready to let everybody know I've been seeing this new
type of bug. I've never seen it before, but I'm seeing it all over. They're going to make
an announcement soon that a new bug has been discovered in New York City. Wow. I go to
Google red bug with white spots. It's the same bug all along. Wow.
Has been here. Oh my God. I was ready to go public with.
I felt like that when I first saw a silverfish. Yeah. You know, those like we,
they're, they like crawl on your walls.
One of them scared me so bad one time that I was silverfish completely paralyzed.
The ones that look like cockroaches? No, no, it's like a centipede with giant
antenna. Oh yeah. Kind of like a house centipede, but not really.
When I was in, when I was in Austin.
We don't have that in North Carolina. We just have giant ass roaches.
You know those water bugs? Those really big ones that look like cockroaches?
Those are like the big pest in North Carolina.
The Toad Biters?
Yeah. Well, I don't know if it's a water bug. I don't know what it was, but there's a bug that looks like a cockroach that isn't a cockroach.
Can it fly?
It flies, yeah.
And it's giant?
Yeah. So, when I was in Austin, I was on stage, I got three phone calls, and it was weird.
I was like, "Oh my God, okay."
Did you let that shit buzz while you were on stage?
while I was on stage didn't check it.
That's a bad look.
Uh-huh.
People in the audience can feel that you're getting a call from a collections agency.
So, well, it's not a collections agency.
Oh, OK.
I was getting a call from my girlfriend
because she said that a cockroach flew in the apartment and landed on her face.
It was a...
Break up with her.
Big ass water bug.
I am never kissing you again if a cockroach has landed on your face.
You better scrub the shit out of your face.
Yeah.
She called me and I was like, I'm in Austin, Texas.
I cannot do anything.
So she locked it in a room with Moe and let him.
- Let him eat it?
- Let him fuck it up, yeah.
- Phil's been eating the spotted, why can't I say that?
I keep saying spotted, spotted lanternfly.
He's been eating them and then getting really sick.
- Yeah.
- The other day he ate like three of them at the park
and then I tried to walk him home
and he just laid on the concrete.
- Just threw up?
- He didn't throw up, but he laid on the concrete
for like 15 full minutes.
- You should have induced vomiting.
You should have put your finger into his...
I'm probably sure he ate a zen the other day.
He ate a zen?
Yeah, but it was used.
Oh.
And I looked it up and they were like, "It's fine."
I probably already talked about this, but yeah, Moe, when he was that big, a week after
I had to keep monitoring him to see whether or not he got panleukopenia or not, and he
threw up a bunch of red and I was like, "Oh, that's it.
He threw up his heart.
He's dying.
I have to take him to the hospital."
How would he throw his heart up?
He was a tiny little fucker.
He was so small.
he was all the stuff was in one spot and he had there was a possibility that he
had a disease that is like a 95% mortality rate and I looked at the
looked at it as a little red piece on the ground and it was just full spotted
lantern fly so then you're like I was like oh he's fucking stupid yeah well
he's pretty smart actually to be catching a fly because this is a new bug
cats don't have this in their ancestral memory exactly they don't know much
Only a Chinese tiger would be able to know how to deal with a lantern.
Only one of these cats that does this with its hand and sits on a windowsill, that one
might be able to catch a spotted lanternfly.
You put some glue on that hand?
Yeah, exactly.
You're going to be catching spotted lanternflies all day.
Is that why those are there?
To catch flies?
To swat flies away?
I think it's to wave hello as you walk into your home.
I think almost everything in China is for good luck.
Pretty much everything.
I think everything is about auspicious things.
They eat food because it's lucky.
And the way they eat it is lucky.
Yep, they eat in a lucky way.
And that's why they are dominating the world right now.
They've been generating luck for thousands of years.
They have like an overflow of luck.
They have like a sieve of luck pool.
They have a surplus of luck.
And they've been drawing,
but they have not used maximum.
They have so much left in the tank when it comes to luck.
Pretty much everything in American culture is something that generates bad luck.
We have mirror stores.
Oh, yeah.
And there are clean up on aisle three.
Pretty often in the mirror store.
The only two, it's the Irish and China.
They are the ones that care the most about the luck.
And Ireland's not doing that well.
That's because what they do is not lucky.
Also, they gave up on luck.
Their luck was all fake and stupid.
Yeah.
They tried to copy China.
Their luck, they tried to get luck by having rainbows, but the reason they have rainbows
is because it rains so fucking much.
The rainbow even then.
So they tried to turn their terrible climate into a...
The rainbow belongs to the world.
It's not even yours.
Exactly.
That's what I'm saying.
They took the reason their country sucks and they tried to say, "Yeah, actually this means
we're lucky."
It's actually very lucky to have giant tornadoes.
tornadoes. They're actually a sign of good luck. Shut the fuck up you fucking Irish bitch.
They have every single natural disaster. It's the only place on earth that has all major
natural disasters. They get hurricanes and typhoons. In Ireland? There's puffins. Really?
In one of those black rock beaches? That's cool as fuck. I think of that as a cereal.
No snakes though.
Nope.
No snakes in Ireland?
No, it's too cold.
Ohhhh.
That's why they have their little story.
They ain't got no gators either.
Their little story they tell themselves about who this guy who got rid of the snakes.
Well wait, how did they even know what a snake was when they came up with this story?
Well, St. Patrick was supposed to them interacting with other people I would imagine.
Once the Catholicism got brought over.
Yeah, because they weren't Catholic to start with.
No, they were all doing spells and rituals and shit.
They were like blocks.
Yeah.
They had the fucking, what's it called, the Tain or whatever.
The Tam?
No, that...
The Tain?
They believed in all types of weird guys with strange names.
Oh yeah.
Plape and Tain.
Yeah.
They had that.
Alright.
Yeah.
Alright, I have to go pee pee.
Me too.
Because this Icelandic water really runs through you, man.
This Icelandic water is so good.
The pH balance, it goes down so easy that I drank the whole thing in the first 10 seconds.
That's enough for me. I'll give this an 8.4 out of 10. Thank you to Icelandic Glacial,
Natural Spring Water from Iceland.
I give this an 8.4 out of 14 on the pH scale.
Carbon neutral product too. And I'm going to go throw it in the trash can.
Alright.