(upbeat music)
- How far you have come as the sync clapper on this show.
You used to be a piece of shit when it came to the clap.
- No, I was good at it.
- No, you might as well be drunk.
- I wish I was.
- Might as well have been, I mean in the past.
- You might as well have been drunk in the past
and now you are--
- When you clap.
my sober go. I wish I was completely drunk right now. Me too. Have we ever done a
really drunk kind of? Yeah, we have. Yes. We've done them a lot. That was the
entire first two years. Yeah. I'm pretty sure there's one episode where I went
and we all visited. Oh, and we recorded at my countertop. Recorded at your
countertop as soon as we got home. But even before that, we were, there were
somewhere we're going pretty hard. It's good to get drunk at your job. There is
one episode where I'm just completely blasted. Oh, that was one that we did
with Thomas, yeah, and you, did you put an onion in your mouth? I bit an onion.
You bit an onion. We've talked about this. I remember that now. I'm trying to
think. There's a lot of D&Ds that I've done where I'm pretty hammered. Well,
that's a different thing. That's a completely different thing. That's what
you're supposed to do. You're supposed to get drunk in a new D&D. Drinking, yeah,
Exactly drinking and drunk drunking. I've done so much stand up where I'm like
completely hammered. I don't do that back in the day back in the day. I was doing a
lot of like I used to do. I used to watch movies and play video games while drunk
back in the day, but really different now. Yeah, I'm never going to hurt us on
the remember I was on the crackers and the pretzels recently. I would get a
whole pitcher before I would host that open mic and I would drink out of the
pitcher liquid courage stage fright. Yeah, it was it was bad for a long time.
Yeah. Recently I've been wanting to get back to smoking weed again, but I don't
think I'm going to.
Disgusting.
It is disgusting.
Gross.
Oh God, I want to every single day. I get home and I go, "Oh my God, weed would be
so amazing right now to watch Goodfellas and smoke weed as a toy."
I'm pretty purified from it, but every once in a while I get such a strong desire.
Weed is OD toy.
It is not OD.
It's OD toy.
Is OD good or is OD bad?
OD is depending on the context. It's like okay. OD means overdoing it. Like if you
say if someone's OD is like okay where it's in the middle where like for
example if you ask someone they want to do something and say okay that's good,
but if so you ask someone how was this and I say it was okay. I mean it's bad. I
think I finally I think I hit this is my year where I am just at a different
stage in life than young people and I cannot understand things like OD anymore.
you grew up.
OD is an old man thing.
No, I think this is, we hit the generational line.
Where I don't have any clue what anybody younger than me is talking about.
The generational line for me, I can tell you exactly what it is.
Tell me.
What?
Five Nights at Freddy's.
Oh yeah.
See, I like Five Nights at Freddy's.
I like it.
I like Five Nights at Freddy's so much.
I remember so vividly that being the first thing where it would conceivably be something
I was interested in.
Oh, okay, this guy's too old to get scared.
yeah, but then afraid of horror. Oh, this is for kids. It's not for kids and
being being still a kid saying that it's for grown up. There's a lower that that
it goes back years. There's a years. Well, the game's been out for I don't
even know how long it's been out. The game's been out for ten years. Yeah, it
came out when we were like we were in high school. Yeah, I was in
probably probably fifteen when that came out. Yeah, I feel like I remember seven.
I feel like I remember that being the thing where I was like this. I this is
for children, even though I was still liking all the other stuff that was for
kids, but that was the first thing where I was like I'm too old. He liked all the
other stuff that was for kids like here comes the airplane.
You can still that's okay. It's still like a piece every night. Everyone you're
gonna not gonna do here comes the airplane. How else is it gonna get your
mouth? You still do uppies. How else am I gonna fucking get up? What are you
talking about? You are being an asshole. You sound crazy. Yeah, you're saying so
you're too old for you to get a plan of peace. I'm a little bit. So let me get
the straight. I don't you bring your face to the plate. You don't bring the
food to your mouth. Yeah, this makes no say don't like a pig. If I don't hear
I don't use a fork, I just use my fingers and I grab so here I grab a
piece of corn like this. I
or here comes a comet. Here comes comment and asteroid or you could say
here comes Santa and his reindeer. Any of this works, but instead you decide to
I'm too grown for that. You're not grown at all. You are not grown. I'm grown.
You are not grown yet. You're not grown. I'm completely grown. Guys, we had,
and I didn't want to talk about this, but they're making me.
We had an office drama this morning. We did have an office drama.
We had an office drama this morning. I
had to put in a ticket. I had to put in a ticket in our work.
At the poop factory. Our work zen desk. He had to clock into the poop factory.
because I did not have any toilet paper and I was trying to bust a nut at work,
but I could not. I had no where to put it. That bathroom is so dirty right now.
It's pretty bad. Yeah, it's got paint all in it. Yeah, it looks like a
squatter's home right now. I cleaned the last paint bathroom, so I'm off to
clean this one. Don't worry. Don't worry. Patrick won't clean anything,
so I'll have to do it. Me and Patrick, as a result of having to go buy
toilet paper for Caleb, me and Patrick actually came up with something rather
it's funny yeah, which will save this situation from being purely negative
intense. So basically going to buy toilet paper and you go up to the to the
cashier to the register and you're so and you're like oh my God, I feel so
awkward buying this and you go up and you're you're buying the toilet paper.
You go. I'm actually buying this for a friend. I'm buying this for somebody
like tapping someone on the shoulder. I can you buy this for me? I've thought
that I gave it. I gave him the rolls of toilet paper like the big going to I ran
way and hid behind the makeup counter. Well, that's even more embarrassing.
Now, that's way more embarrassing. I've had that thought before where I was
checking out at Walgreens and it is funny to buy. It is honestly funny to
buy toilet paper. There's like a pretty cashier and she just knows that this is
going to touch your poop. Yeah, yeah, well, that's how I say you buy it and
you're like, honestly, I don't even know what this stuff is. I just thought it
looks cool. First time trying it. Yeah.
Have you ever used it before? Is it good? Is it bad? Is this one good? You had so
many of them over there. I'm just buying this stuff just in case. Yeah. I don't
need it. Yeah. I don't need this at all. I'm doing a... This is for my
bug out bag. Yeah. This is for my neighbor. And six rolls of toilet
paper. Okay. Alright. I'll make sure to get that. Sounds good. Beep. Wait, you
want six rolls? How much shitting are you doing? You're doing so much crap.
Sorry. My friend is basically addicted to shit. Yeah. My friend's so fucking
weird. And I'm the one... He made me come here to buy this. But then they...
but here's the one who has to buy it for him, because he's banned from buying it.
Yeah, if you could buy so much, what I thought this was just paper, my thumb
was covering the word. What the fuck I thought it was let paper. What the hell
is this? E T paper, where would this even go in the toilet? I thought it was
weird back. E T weird alien paper. You put this in the back of the toilet and
it collects all the water. Here's the world we're heading towards the all
you walk in to the Walgreens, you put twelve rolls, you think, "Oh, I'm going to stock
up." You put twelve rolls and they say, "ID, please."
Damn.
Yep.
Eighteen plus.
Yeah, like Benadryl.
To make sure that they aren't going into a gender neutral bathroom.
Another of my cultural predictions here. I think it's time to watch out. I think a new
disease is spreading because today when we went to buy toilet paper, there was barely
any toilet paper on the shelves.
In the right aid.
run on toilet paper, people are buying it up. Something is going on. People are
going to be stuck in their houses that usually most of the I mean the drinks in
the back are usually barren. You know it's kind of it's a right aid where they
constantly are low on items, but the fact that they had low stock on toilet paper
today, yep, it's predicting Cameron's future. It is pretty it's a prediction of
his future leaves my prediction of the world. His future, that's even my future
because I'm part of the world, but I just want to be clear. This is going to happen to everyone.
And it's probably based on either my bug prediction I made about insects or a new prediction I've
been working on that I think there's a new disease that you get for one night and it
only happens when it's dark out. Oh, okay. It just gave me chills. Yeah, that's going
to be one symptom of the disease. My prediction, I know it's been making me so unbelievably
mad that it's come on, bro. Stop playing with your white cover. Don't make it up. It's really
you get dude don't twirl it bro. This is hurting. You know what that looks like
you know what that looks like right now. What do they call it?
Don't talk like that either.
What does it look like? No don't
you're acting crazy. You're acting crazy today. You have to see it from the
side.
Yeah, it does look
it does look crazy like a penis.
it's the same kind of color difference to yeah, exactly the shaft in the shaft is
that was honestly that was the gayest thing I've ever seen you to do you
helping it and you kissing it. That was so disgusting,
disgusting or not disgusting because it's
disgusting to do that. It's going to be sexual at work is what I'm saying.
okay, well we're not at work. We're still you literally violated that when you
made me come into the bathroom with you and wipe your butt. Did not okay,
here's what was weird is that you open the door to hand me the toilet paper and
you looked right at me. You're supposed to do a courtesy. No, I want to see what
you're doing in there. I'm taking a shit. Well, you should be he opened the
door. He opened the door and started going.
You did you. I was trying to hold the first. I saw your I saw the tip of your
those come through every single crack in the door before you opened it and sniff
it.
You doing that like a truffle pig is trying to find out if he's trying to find
out if you had any mushrooms in your poop.
Could be.
I get excited about stuff. Sue me. Okay. I'm not gonna hurt you. That's like the
thing we were talking about. That trait of mine is why I'm one of the most fun
people to go to an arcade roller coaster concert with. So I'm not gonna apologize
or how I act around my friends at a bath.
You go to a roller coaster.
You go to a place that has a roller coaster.
I don't agree with him right now.
I don't agree with his actions.
I don't agree with his attitude today.
I don't agree with his actions or his attitude.
He had to be my toilet paper slave and now he's got a whole bat.
I'm sorry, but I do agree that you go to a roller coaster.
Can I come clean really quick?
Yeah.
I have been acting out lately because a few nights ago I had a dream where I got struck
by lightning and I haven't recovered.
That is really...
you got struck by lightning and survived or you woke up?
Yeah, here's what happened in the dream. I was outside, there was lightning striking
all around. I thought I should go inside so lightning doesn't strike me. So I start to
run inside. Then lightning strikes near me. I think, "Oh, I'm safe. It only struck near
way that was lucky, but then it goes into the ground and it goes and it goes
across the ground like a video game area of effect. What if you woke up? It goes
into my body and then it goes up my body like and I shake around and I fall to
the ground and then my heart stops and then I was survived and then I got up
and I said and my dream I said, well, I thought I was going to die, but it
actually just felt weird. What if you woke up from that? That's how you in
real life you'd say like well, that's a dream. If you woke up from that dream
and your finger is just in your the outlet in your
you're doing sleep. You woke up and it's like you're like your nightstand is
here, your bed, your bed is here and just everything out of the way the I'm
chewing on my phone charging cable down it perfectly in the outlet on the wall.
My outlet shaped, pulled shaped finger shaped. Well, you have it yeah, you
got because we have a whole gel finger in your mouth. Yeah, I know you doesn't
sleep with your finger in your mouth and then you scratch your balls, put your
finger in your mouth.
I wonder if I ever done that myself. You know when you it's your bud and then
you stick your fingers
we all do it. I don't do we all do it man. It's not you don't have to be
afraid to admit it. Okay, I do it you're right. I do that shit.
I stick it in my mouth.
What is up with you? Do you
the mall
while you're like looking or
your Christmas shopping your Christmas shopping for your girlfriend, you're in
the middle of Victoria's Secret, the woman's about to walk up to you and
you're just going
I was like about like a
sound is an apple. When you put your
your
I don't like this idea. This is
well, I'm just doing an absent mind and I'm doing it in the way of like I
forget I'm not on my couch. Yeah, yeah, this is something I do regularly.
Oh, oops, I did it on the end
middle of Brandy Melville
getting which one's the stinky finger, damn the stinky finger. Oh, I think that
I
honestly eating, eating my own shit. We've talked about this. No, we
Yeah, we never talked about that. We've never talked about eating shit. No, I
think that it would be, it's either
I think it would ruin my life, 'cause I would be so ashamed or it might end up
being the highest form of artistic expression that you can do. Those people
who are into scat are not ashamed of it. They don't eat the shit, though,
right? No, they eat the shit. I thought they just cover their butts and their
penises on it. They cover their butts and their penises, and then they suck
the shit off the penises.
So gross.
(laughter)
- They suck the shit off the penis.
- You're like eight years old.
- That's what I've seen.
- And then they fucking fart diarrhea
and they suck the penis off the shit.
- That's the worst thing you can send to somebody.
- I used to, I'm--
- People think it's like, oh, you sent me a photo of that--
- I was thinking maybe when Cameron opened the door
I was gonna show him my poopy butthole.
- Yeah.
- I decided that I was hoping--
- I thought I was ruining our friendship.
- I used to be immature,
I used to think stuff was funny like Patrick said. I used to find scat funny, but now I've
grown up a little and now I find skak funny. I'm a fan of all comedy.
Yeah, skak backpack. I'm a fan of Pierce Campion and Will Duncan.
Yeah, no doubt.
Man, what the fuck is going on this week in the news?
What's going on in the world?
I mean, what is there even?
Well, I told you about night disease.
Yeah, night disease.
What's night disease?
It's the disease you only get for one night in the dark.
Can you explain night disease?
You, you what?
for one night in the dark. I was just talking about the symptoms congestion
chills, bad dreams. Oh wait, I've had this disease before you get it for about
eight to ten hours. I can if I if I have something I have to do and I don't
want to do it, I get I get sick for two hours. You don't even get it before
you lie, but you lie down in bed. You instantly get it. The second that you're
horizontal, you get it. You when you wake up in the morning, it's completely
gone. Yeah, it's not a it's night disease. Yeah, it's really gonna take
all over the world in a pandemic. I've had night disease before it's coming.
It's coming, it's coming. That's why the toilet paper is gone. Yeah, that's what I
was saying. That's all along what I was saying. That's even the context I
brought up night disease and in fact really a dream about a dream about
toilet paper.
What you had a dream about toilet paper going on?
I didn't have a dream about toilet paper. I had a real life experience of
toilet paper being gone. Have you ever have you ever had a dream that you're
pooping. No, you wake up and you're already going. I think I almost every
single time I wake up in the middle of night or I'm really tired and I sit down
to shit. I get really scared that I'm dreaming and I'm either shitting my
pants or I have slept walked to the toilet and I'm shitting on top of the
toilet. It's such a crazy. I don't think that anyone I've ever seen anyone do it
I've never done it myself. I've never met a baby. I don't think I've ever woken up and
had to go shit really bad. Yeah, definitely always have to go pee really bad when I wake
up. Sometimes I wake up in the morning and I don't think that's ever happened. You're
gonna run to the bathroom. I gotta get up. I mean, I gotta walk to the bathroom. It's
not that urgent. Sure. But yeah, I guess I don't even think I need to go until I'm up
and awake. When I had food poisoning, when I had food poisoning in like 2016, food poisoning
doesn't count. Well that's the craziest feeling though is I would have these like fever dreams
and then like wake up and have to go shit and waking up having to shit like waking up
and having to pee is like okay like I can I know how to hold this but like waking up
and having to poop. You don't know how to hold your poop. You're like holding your like
stomach so that like you think that you're holding the poop in your hands. How far away
is your bathroom? What are you talking about? How long does it take you to get from your
your bed to your toilet sometime well in my parents old house. It was a little
hallway. Yeah, they lived in a hallway. They're very railway, a railway style
hallway, a railway on a real when the bathroom when you have a station,
you're really long way. I was just really weak and just like having to like
get up and run because I like I'm about to shit your pants man. You're sick. Oh,
I'm not shitting my you're allowed to shit your pants. If you're sick, I
I only think that's your chance man. I don't even like that. Come on man. I
don't even like shitting my pants. What the hell are you doing? This is your
only excuse. Make your girlfriend clean it up bro. I don't even like shitting
my pants. I can't clean it up. I'm so sick. I don't know about, I think you
two like that, but I, me personally. Shitting your damn pants. I hate shitting
my pants. I love it man. Every time I get a chance, I'm, I'm dropping a,
dropping a shotgun blast at chili in my shorts. No, it is true freedom. I
crap, there's shotgun blasted chili in my primark jeans. I think if I and the
spandex expanded around the poop, I think the only thing that keeps me from not
ending my life is maybe the thought that it's that I could never be sick ever
again because of every single time that I'm really sick. I'm like I have food
poisoning. Anytime you get food poisoning, you're like, "If I could press
a button and die right now, I would do it." There are many, many people in this
world who turn a billion forty years old and they never are sick again for the
rest of their life. Really? Yeah, unless they get like it. They're called
they're called immune, immunions, immunions, where they where they hail
from. My dad is one of them. Your dad's an immunion. I guess my dad might be
too. My dad, my dad got covid and he played golf with all his buddies. They
just some people just don't get sick. That's sick. My mom, I think, is one of
had COVID early, like my dad had COVID June 2020. So both of these are not ringing true
as immunians to me because both of these stories are about people who got sick. No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, my mom, my dad got COVID, my dad got COVID and then my mom like was
in the same room as him. She didn't give a shit. I was sucking his dong. Why'd you say
that Pat? Yeah, did you talk about your own mom? She was, she was, she had teeth with
with his ball sack hair and spitting on it. She didn't get COVID, though. You
can't get COVID from eating cum.
That's the only contact I had. He came into a law, into a bank tube, a delivery
directly to her mouth every single day. Yeah, you can't get COVID from that.
That's gross. Who the fuck is calling me? Probably my mom to tell you to stop
talking about her like that. I knew it. I knew it. He's calling me. Oh, my God.
pick it up, just got a word at him, pick it up, and he just got screened. I don't
want to pick it up and have him on speaker phone so he can blast his ass
for ruining our job. He'll say something so fucking out of pocket, bro. He will.
I don't want to fuck with that right now. We'd have to edit out him saying some
shit. He's gonna say, guess who met Taylor Swift last night? Dude, I was
backstage. Oh, I don't know, bro.
I met Taylor Swift. Yeah, dude, she was chill. She was chill.
awful. I got awesome bro. Thank you for calling me. Did you buy our plane tickets
that we for tomorrow morning yet?
Yeah, he's a good guy. Yeah, yeah. He at Funny Mom, Chappell's son was there.
I feel like this is a bit of a too much inside bit. Probably shouldn't say it,
but he got so excited that he was like, can I can I tell everyone who you are?
that is so sick. Do you guys wish that you were would it be good or bad to be a
celebrity's child?
I've probably my theories about celebrity children and you guys stomped all over
it. What was your theory? I told you that God should reward fans of Tom Cruise by
reincarnating them as Tom Cruise's children and you guys said that's crazy.
I never let it go. We said that it was crazy. We said it was not crazy. He said
that that's what you were thinking about in the shower would have been would be an
abusive father because he's a Scientologist. So the only way that
somebody could enjoy and have a happy life as a child of Tom Cruise is having
a remembrance of a past life where they loved him.
That seems just... I just don't know...
You're just changing the subject, I think, because what I'm talking about
is what it would be like to be a celebrity child and you're doing this
whole... It would be bad. Unless you were in a past life a fan of
that celebrity. I don't get the reincarnation aspect of it. I
know why that's I do think you're going to be a fan of them in a past life if
you're not reincarnated would stink to be this the child of one of the greatest
artists. Yeah, because you'd have no ability to enjoy their work. The
sliding or the I don't like the fucking I don't like my dad's the whatever
no, I think you're stuck. Oh, my dad does. I don't give a fuck about that.
The spectrum here is you're either like when you're a celebrity skid, you're
either a Robert Downey Jr. Or like a fucking not even like a Chet Hanks
but just like somebody you're like the son of like Dan Schneider or something
would weird example.
Interesting choice.
Just like a celebrity that everybody hates.
That feels like a good experience to be a child around Dan Schneider.
The son of Dan Schneider feels like a big heart.
The middle ground here is just being like fucking Fisher Stevens kid.
I'm going to blow this out of the water.
Okay.
It would be all these people's kids, you know, would be incredible.
Any of these people except Dan Schneider as your uncle.
No, she would be right with him as a
greatest. That would be so incredible. I'm
getting excited about it. I treat Matt
like he's a celebrity. Yeah, uncles are
so the celebrities of your life. There's
no question. Everything that they do is
cool to you. Yeah, you get you keep up
with them on Instagram. Yeah, exactly.
Like you see the news stories where it's
like look what look what he was doing.
He was hiking. I still think there's
time for Matt to become a celebrity. My
My nephews fully believe that I met Spongebob.
Really?
My nephews fully.
Did you say that or they said that?
I told them that I met him in New York at a party and because they were watching some
YouTuber.
That would be so fucking awesome.
They were watching some YouTuber play Battle of Bikini Bottom and I said, "Oh, do you guys
know I met him once?"
They turned around and they went, "Really?"
So did you tell them that you met Spongebob? Not Tom Chimney. You said that you met Spongebob.
I said I met Spongebob and we got drinks together. You hit it off so well at this party that
you guys, did you go to a second location that night? Or did you? Yeah, no I was telling
them that like you know I met Spongebob, we're like pretty good friends now, and they think
that I know Spongebob and they think that I'm neighbors with Spider-Man. I mean you might
be. I could be. I live in Queens. I think Spongebob might be. I feel like we don't know enough
about his personal life to the point where I know somebody's protecting him. He might
be like an NDA guy. Yeah. Oh yeah. Well I hung out with him and he was amazing. Really?
We got drinks at what's that bar downtown? I heard that 169 bar. Spongebob makes girls
sign NDAs and he also won't fuck or date any girl above the age of two. In sponge years.
In sponge years, which is 46. But for him it's two. But for everybody, that's why nobody
really cares because he's a sponge so he pretty much lives forever. And he also will only
fuck small women that are the size of sponges. So he has a really hard time in the dating
scene. Yeah, except for in the sea. The dating sea he does very well. Hey, there's plenty
at fish there. He doesn't fuck fish. He fucks human women there to the size of a
sponge. He doesn't like plenty of fish in the sea like the... No, no, I got it.
Like the old idiom. Old idiom? I don't think people say that all the time. I
don't even know if that one's that old. That one's pretty old. I bet that one
came from like a rom-com in the 90s. They haven't figured out that they were
rom-com in the 90s. That fish lived in the sea since like... About a sailor. They didn't
know that. Yeah. I found out about a... 1573. Oh! He was so right again.
we doubted him again and he was right again. Well, I do actually know
Spongebob, so you are a genius man and I never have a fish come from
comes from the sea. Plenty of fish come from the sea and they learned that in
fifteen seventy three. Yeah, no shit, no fucking shit.
I think people who use idioms might be idiots. Maybe that's where you use
from uh, idioids. Yeah, idioids. Using those idioms. It's crazy that you think that as a
person from the south. That's all that you guys speak in. I don't, dude. All you guys
speak in is idioms. There was a video this week of that girl talking in a southern accent
and people were hating on her. What video? It was a video of some girl and she's saying
like "You don't want to mess with me y'all, cause I'm from the south and women from the
south are crazy." They are. And people were like "This bitch is fucked, this bitch." Bro,
They are. She was so beautiful and her voice was, she had the voice of an angel.
Why do people hate the southern accent? It's great. I don't know.
Is it because we're stupider?
It's probably because of the civil war.
If you think about it, there's a historical reason why.
You think it was fought over the voices?
It was fought over their accents because people up north were saying like,
you guys are retarded. You guys are no fucking piece of crap.
Stop with the slaves, kid.
Stop with the fucking slaves, kid.
It's a fucking nightmare.
Bro, what are you doing?
What the fuck are you doing with these slaves?
What the fuck are you doing, bro?
That's a human being!
Whoa!
Not at all!
What are you doing?
And we were...
Put him back!
Or not we, but they.
We?
Not we.
My whole family, nobody in my family ever had slaves.
I'd like to say that.
If I, I mean...
Have you done ancestry?
Do you know that that's true?
It's 100% true.
Yeah?
family was like like fucking dust farmers in Oklahoma. They would farm dust or
some shit. I don't know why would they farm dust? What is that even gonna? I
don't know anything about them. I just know for sure they didn't have slaves.
That's the only thing it said. You see, you think that they don't have slaves
and then you like look up your family on ancestry and you see them and in their
field there's all these dust people. Yeah, I'm driving by the pits plantations
left and right all through North Carolina. It's all clouds of dust that are
like picking corn off of corn stalks and shit. You have all these dust people.
I have toured one plantation and one historical home. Have we talked about
this? How funny it is that any time you go to any kind of historical thing
where they had slaves, they always say,
"And unlike a lot of people in the area, the slaves were actually treated very
smell here. That's why they keep the building up. And they sometimes ate the
leftover food,
the leftover...
They didn't have to eat kibble all the time, like a lot of the other slaves in
the area. Yeah. Yeah.
Man. Yeah. But those places are, I mean, they're beautiful homes. I gotta give
it to them. Yeah. They had good taste. Those plantations look pretty good.
Once you get rid of all the history, it's a pretty nice building. Once you get rid
of all the ghosts, it's actually a pretty nice place. I haven't been to,
a historical thing in a long time. There's not as many of those kind of things.
Buddy, you see a historical building every single day in this beautiful melting pot of
a city.
The historical buildings in New York suck fucking dick.
Yeah, they're not as good.
This is the worst city for history of all time. Worse than a city that was built in
1990.
Yeah. What cities were built in 1990?
If there was one, this would be a worse city for history than that one is what I'm saying.
Probably like Game Boy Nevada or something.
What is it? It's in Nevada. They have the Simpsons house, the one to one replica of the
Simpsons home.
That state is so unbelievably fucked up.
Yeah. Well, it's dude, it's like legal gambling and then like also Mormons and shit.
Yeah. Do they have the...
Imagine how fucked up it would be.
The nuclear uroam.
You would be fucked up too if you were shaped like an exacto knife blade.
That is true.
You would be emo as fuck.
That is real shit.
They have a I think the nuclear testing has destroyed that. You stay forever. You have
Reno. New Mexico. I thought I don't care. It's still it. It travels. It does travel.
Yeah, you're right. But I think New Mexico is where they all have all those beads. New
Mexico is fine. New Mexico is fine. I like all Mexico. They dropped the bombs in New
New Mexico. They dropped bombs in Roswell. No, they had an alien there,
which I've been... They dropped a bomb on that one. ...international media...
Am I... When they announced the alien... Am I confusing this? I don't know.
What are you... They tested the bombs in... They tested the bombs in... Los
Alamos. In New Mexico? Yeah. Okay, and is that on the border of Nevada?
Probably not. I don't know. Where did they...
Were they testing nukes on aliens to see if they were resilient to them?
Yes, I would do that. I think that's settled science. Yeah, yeah, Nevada test
site. Oh my God. Oh, yeah, you're right. Oh, yeah, I was the most lady.
Significant. I was getting a lady in Roswell, so I in the Nevada test site
Roswell is nothing to do with any of this. I know I went to Roswell for
no reason. I thought that's where all that stuff went on. I thought area 51
was like we tested bombs here. That's where aliens landed. Well, they got a
lot. I just think that whole area of the country has just too much fucked up
stuff coming out of it. Yeah, I've never met anybody from any of those places,
except for fucking Adams from Las Vegas, I guess. Yeah, but look at him. Yeah,
exactly, but like I think people who go to those places who move there to live
there too are crazy. Yeah, why would you people retire to escape your family and
move to somewhere where it's a hundred and thirty degrees in the summer? Why
would you go there, man? And there's no like water. They have animals called
monsters. Yeah, I think that's true. They do. There's also there's also people
that retire in the north. I'm just thinking of that in general area. Oh
damn, those I didn't even know those were in America. Yeah, people who retire
in like New Hampshire. What's up? Fucked up. There's people that are going up
and retiring. Retiring in the northeast is goaded. You think so? Yeah, 100%.
Waterfront. Yeah, I guess you do get seasons. Mountains, waterfront, forest. You
know exactly when, like a big thing with when you're getting older. The desert
It's fucking not a place to retire in.
Yeah, that's true.
Life cannot live there.
No.
Unless you like cactus and prickly pear.
Well, if those are your two favorite things, then I think you should retire in them.
You could just buy one of those and put it in your house.
Damn right.
Yeah, you could get them Instacarted.
What are these people doing?
They're going there to, I think they're gambling, I'm going to be honest.
They're probably going there to shrivel up like a raisin.
I think they're gambling with their lives every single summer.
Can you guys, do you guys think it's going to suck when you get older and all your friends
start to die?
Yeah.
I can't wait.
I think about that constantly because everyone, everyone I know is dropping like flies.
You've had friends pass away recently?
I've had every single one of my friends die.
And I'm stuck with you and Cameron.
So that makes me and Cameron feel like shit.
Yeah, that's not great.
And I'm stuck with you guys.
Because we're not your friends, we're your brothers.
My close personal friends are dead.
Who?
And I'm stuck with just these two business partners that I'm stuck with.
King von King von past hard my good friend King von yeah, I think I'm
probably going to slide for him pretty soon. Yeah, who else just who else of my
friends just passed away?
Some kind of musical artist. Yeah, Avicii my close personal. That was over
a decade. You should be over that feels it. Honestly, if you're not over a
friend's death by 10 years, it's over for you and that wasn't your friend.
That was your boyfriend, bro.
they should be still thinking about
I agree,
bro move on. You should be done shot. Oh, you're wasting years. I
work time. Absolutely, absolutely, and that's if you're mentally ill yeah.
Why are you going to the grave plot? You friggin jerk douche bag you do
actually like a douche bag you're hogging all the flowers for your dead
friend. He's not going to smell him get out of the cemetery. I want to walk
around there. Yeah, you're making me uncomfortable. I'm trying to use the
bathroom and all of a sudden you're putting a bunch of flowers underneath my
leg. I want to listen to my iPod and I want to smoke a fat cigarette. I have an
iPod touch and I'm taking photos of me and my friends in here. I'm trying to
sneak in and be scary. I'm listening to Crystal and Ritz in here. This guy's
name was Jeff fucking. Yeah, Jeff fucking and Dick Riblet are buried next to each
other. Can I please take a photo of them? Oh, that's your friend? Your friend with
Dick Riblet? Yeah, nice try buddy. Oh yeah. Oh, I'm putting flowers on Dick
riblets grave. Hey buddy, how about you put some flour on some riblets? Let's
get a fucking barbecue going in here.
Let's get a grill in this cemetery. You're gonna flour, you're gonna bread
ribs. We're gonna bread riblets and we're gonna deep fry them over a thing
of oil and a grill. Okay, so you're gonna take a Traeger, put a pot in it.
Do you think I thought this through? And then you're gonna heat, somehow use
the smoker to heat up the oil to 400 degrees, and then we're gonna bread
riblets riblets cover the flour and then we're going to throw them in that
into those actually look insane. Yeah,
those look really good. I'm not sure if the technique was followed in the way
that you said, no, but it is. I can tell that these probably I don't like that. I
don't like that barbecue has become this whole thing man. You like to become a
line bar with it. You like you. Oh my God, this place in red hook. That's like
the only good barbecue place in the city.
Yeah.
And it's like $70 for a plate of barbecue.
Oh, that's bullshit.
And people line around the block for this fucking place.
Well, that's because you can't get it here.
You can't get it here. You can't get good barbecue in New York.
This place is honestly pretty good. I was pretty surprised.
I've been wanting some barbecue lately.
Oh my god.
I was going to say...
I want to go back to that place upstate.
You definitely like that barbecue is becoming a huge thing
because you can be a snob about which barbecue is the best.
I'm not a snob about it at all.
You're a southern guy.
No, I don't give a fuck about it. I like North Carolina barbecue. I don't really like the
South Carolina style.
Snob. You just said he doesn't like a style.
Do you like every style of...
I like every style of everything.
What is a New Hampshire... a turkey sandwich?
Don't even start on turkey sandwiches.
Okay, you are a snob.
Back off, man. Back the fuck up.
Back the fuck up.
I'm sorry.
You don't know a single thing about Thanksgiving sandwiches.
Let me pop off about barbecue real quick. Y'all, I do not want to eat brisket anymore.
Stop making so much fucking brisket. I want ribs. I don't like beef ribs. I like pork
ribs. Pork ribs are the best. And also, I think that a hamburger should be a barbecue
food. You eat it at a barbecue. That's not a bad idea. There should be hamburgers at
barbecue should have a burger fest soon. I burger fest. I'm gonna have a
I'm eating a burger fest tonight. Okay. I already planned it yesterday. I
don't care. What did you have? What kind of burgers? You're the one who
brought up a burger. We could go to Brian's house before I even brought
I'm doing a blind mate home made, but it's not for me that I don't care.
What burgers are you making? I'm gonna do. I actually don't even want to
tell you. Are they deluxe? Are they? They're kind of the opposite of
the Deluxe, but you're going to make fun of me.
They're smash burgers, but I use 93% lean ground beef and I put it on a piece
of lettuce instead of a bun.
I didn't want to tell you. I didn't want to tell you.
I didn't want to tell you what I was doing, dude.
You were so excited. So, Cameron. You're having a burger fest tonight?
Cameron, it's...
I'm having a burger fest. So, it's my kind of a burger fest. I can't... No,
man. No, you were having you're having a burger play date. You're having a
burger, a burger nap, take the headphones off Cameron. He cannot fucking come to
our burger. No, absolutely not. He does not get what it's about. He cannot come
to the burger. No, no, no, I might have a burger fest in one and a half weeks.
That's a good idea. Okay, his headphones are back on.
It's a it's still a burger just because there's no, I don't want to hear about
and I don't want to hear about that. That thing you made
you've been planning that thing
I plan all my meals out.
Is that such a crime and Wednesday? I mean I'm a burger, no bun
honey,
I won't need the buns, but they give me diarrhea. I'm going to the grocery
store. You think yeah, don't buy buns, do not
I need a bib of lettuce
Or four of them actually, because I'll eat two burgers.
And one for the top and one for the bottom because they are nature's bun.
You know what, you're going to, I think that I may, well okay, at least I'm not, I'm using
buns on these, but my girlfriend wanted turkey burgers the other day and I made some pretty
dope ass turkey burgers.
I don't like turkey burgers, man.
I get it.
Just get a lean ground beef instead of a turkey burger.
I get it, I get it.
She just doesn't eat red meat.
Just make her eat it though.
I was just making, I should have just said.
I should have said, I should have said, I should have said, I should have said, I should have
said, I should have said, I should have said, I should have said, I should have said, I
should have said, I should have said, I should have said, I should have said, I should have
asshole. I think it's not real, but yeah, that is a if that's real, I don't think
any of that stuff is ever real. Right. Oh yeah. You want your wife to go into the
bathroom and just fucking shit her brains out? Nah, it won't do that. What are you
talking about? When you're like vegetarian for a while and then you eat
like meat? This is a complete myth. What do you do? I did that. You were
vegetarian for like two months? I was pescatarian for a year. Did you just eat
something else? And then I went and ate a bunch of ribs. Actually, you know what? I
went to Kowloon and saw Gus Madsen and I ate a bunch of spare ribs.
A beef tallow is not enough to make you sick.
That's true, yeah.
It's just oil.
It just violates your values and ruins your world view.
Yeah, exactly.
Values don't matter.
I think that's what made me shit was the fact that my values were gone.
Yeah, that is satisfying.
The body reacts when its ethics are violated.
Maybe I'll start being vegan again.
Well, speaking of the turkey burgers, I made a very good cranberry mayo for the turkey
burgers and I forgot how good that is.
Nobody needs to be eating cranberry with their turkey. I don't like this shit.
You are, this is why I said do not even talk about the Thanksgiving sandwich.
I don't like the Thanksgiving sandwich.
Thanksgiving sandwich is goaded for the days after Thanksgiving.
Yes.
You really think that?
You really think that, you know what?
Making a little Thanksgiving burger, no stuffing.
Tell me, do you like Thanksgiving food?
The stuffing is in the turkey patty.
Yeah, the stuffing is part of it.
I would say that you basically put all the stuffing ingredients in the
turkey patty. I would say that Thanksgiving food, you think it's just
turkey and cranberry? No, my burger. Thanksgiving food is the fourth best
holiday food. I don't like Thanksgiving food that much, but Halloween, yeah,
those are the... Wait, how are you having any difference between... Christmas,
what's the difference? We eat lasagna and meatballs. Is it 'cause you get
coffee cake in the morning? Oh, alright. Well, that's your Christmas,
that's not... Yeah, that is weird. I would not call that Christmas. If you
look up Christmas dinner right now. You're going to see like a goose or
like
cooked goose or
exactly. That's what I was going to or like or like or like porridge and now
what the fuck are you talking Christmas? There a cooked goose. Who the hell
eats a turkey for Christmas? A lot of people. That's what Christmas dinner is.
If you say Christmas dinner, that's what it means. Christmas dinner,
olive and mother fucking who will Christmas dinner and thanksgiving and
this, but this is what it means. What do you mean? We live? No, you don't
to live in a bill to eat roast be. This dinner is look at me, balls,
meatballs, cheesecake,
yes, he's got bread sauce,
that's Christmas dinner. Yeah, we make it every Christmas. You just have a
family fun. You're just a tally.
That's like you're talking about. Do you guys like Monday dinner or do you
guys like
Friday is pizza Friday is pizza, but thanksgiving the only universal.
fourth. It's Christmas, the lasagna, the meatballs, Halloween, the candy, fourth
of July, the hot dogs and the hamburgers, and then Thanksgiving rounding out the
bottom. Wait, you're forgetting the birthday cake on fourth of July, man.
Valentine's Day. We have that every fourth of July in my family.
Okay, then I'll include it. I'm not such a snob. I'm not so... I like July 23rd
dinner the best. Why don't we just all adopt the best family traditions of each
of our families? You guys can take the meatball and the... Do you guys want to
you watch my uncle's meat balls. If we're doing all the family traditions of
Christmas from when we were growing up, do you guys want to watch my uncle's
fight? Yes, and I want your grandpa's leg. Oh yeah, fake leg. We should have
the leg.
I talked about
we got presents every year. I have not tried that, but I'll take it just to
the remind the leg thing. My great my mom's grandpa was like diabetic or
something and lost his leg. And then when he died every Christmas, they would wrap
his leg up in Christmas ornaments and tinsel and stuff, and they would make us
take photos with it. That's just a reminder.
A fake leg.
How high up did it go? Did it go past the knee?
Yeah, dude. It was like...
Whoa!
It's like the... It would connect to the knee. So that's where like the strap.
Oh, yeah. The hinge?
Yeah, the strap and the hinge. So with that leg, cornucopia style.
you could just connect one of those to your foot and have a three jointed long
leg.
That's also true. We could do a race. Yeah, still exactly. If we're combining
all the traditions, we still have to have the leg in there. I was thinking
cornucopia. A long legged race. A long legged race. We could do a long legged
race with one person. Yeah. Yeah.
All of everyone versus the one guy with a leg attached to his leg.
Kind of a cybernetics experiment. Yeah.
And then what other ones? So we got to watch my uncle's fight. Watch him
with toys. The leg, playing with toys is good. We go get a tour of my Uncle Matt's new audio
equipment. You guys ever do a Yankee swap? That's actually sick. You ever do a Yankee
swap, Pat? No. What's that? That's like a game where everyone puts a small present into
a pool and then it's like you go in an order and it's like the first person, and then you
can either take a present or you can switch with someone else. Isn't that what White Elephant
is? I don't know. Is it the same thing? We call it Yankee swap probably because we're
We're a couple of Yankees.
You guys are Yankees.
Well that's our accent when we say that.
You kind of have a southern accent for some reason.
I don't have a southern accent.
You say like ain't.
I don't say ain't.
Yeah you do.
You add in a southern accent.
You're a faker.
That's the thing.
The south taking over.
The south is third coast baby.
the third coast. I fully second for a split second. I was like no, I say aunt.
I fully submit to the south. I'm ready to I bow down to China and I bow down to
the American south. I'm fully ready to be assimilated. I'll be their slave.
Imagine that barbecue. Oh my God, that would be a man in a world where those
two are the are I have dual citizenship in those two countries. Yeah, yes, that
the in a no it's not the confetti all right, not anymore. The south is going
to have a second civil war where the north is the bad guys. Yeah, I would oh
I gotta be so amazing
that would be so just to even if it just lasted for one day, we could just call
it square and stop doing all this stuff in school yeah right. I just think this
is a good idea. Let's just if you guys could just fake it for just one day man.
It would really connect the country. I think
you fake what? Fake a civil war just for one day. Just for one day be like, we need to
get slaves up north. And then we'll just be like, what the hell? What are you talking
about? And then the civil war will be over. We're taking you down. Yeah. And then we surrender.
Yeah, exactly. See this would instantly wheel our country. That would completely wheel the
country actually. Every division we have would be over. You're on team south. Yeah, I'd be
team south. Of course. You're pro slaves? You're joining the north for this? What are
what are you doing? What are you talking about? I thought you were saying that
the slay, okay, I thought you were saying that it was the same team. See,
this is perfect. The confusion would make it actually go a lot smoother,
'cause if both sides think that they're good, this would completely cleanse
America and everyone would be happy. Yeah, are the American person would ever
be able to say, no person would ever be able to say that they have never seen
racism in person, 'cause they live in Boston. Exactly, yeah. They'd never be
able to make that excuse to try and crazy.
People say that I said that people always say that people are not Boston,
but the northeast people are always like yeah, like the south is racist as fuck
yeah, that you hear that London, New Hampshire is the whitest place in the
world. Every place in the northeast is extremely like yeah, of course it was
very racist. Everyone there is fucking honky. I don't see racism because
there's no black people in my city. Yeah, we need to make we need to do like
in Atlanta, Maine. Yeah, that would be a good idea. Oh my God.
Could you imagine lobster fishermen getting off their boats and going to like
magic city in the middle of like Bar Harbor? I could see that. That would be
amazing. Yeah, just a bunch of like Mainers just walking in like, oh, look at
a boobs.
Oh, this is awesome.
Oh my God, a strip club with fucking lobster rolls like Atlanta. This is a
great idea. Oh my God.
If the southeast and the northeast could link up, we could change the world forever.
In the most northeast states, the strip clubs have to keep their clothes on if they sell alcohol.
The Gold Club in Manchester, Bedford actually.
Why do they do it? What's the point of that?
I don't know.
Fun fact, the Gold Club is where they shot that scene in Mystery Team.
I guess it's better to a horny pervert to go there than to not go anywhere at all.
small yeah, but it's hard to not go anywhere. If you're complete pretty
easy for some of these guys, you're complete horny degenerate pervert.
Yeah, it's probably
trip club type of guy that goes to a strip club, greasy horny pervert. Yeah
works glasses. It's full going to a trip club on a day. Yeah, you're going to a
strip club on a Tuesday in Bedford, New Hampshire.
It's like all right.
We should I don't they should spray them with pesticides.
I
you should have to go through like a like
like an international space station, like cleaning routine. There's an air
lock. If you're if you're in the north, if you're in like again, Bedford, New
Hampshire or something like that, and you were going to like a strip club on a
Tuesday, they should remember when they were doing the drive through strip clubs
when everything was locked down. No, I always thought that was a good idea.
Window tent, who knows it was in that car, right? Maybe it's me. Maybe it's me
I'm fifteen yeah. I got my learn permit. My mom's got to be in the car because I
can't drive by myself. Yeah, I go. Oh Mom, I think I took a wrong turn. I might
as well pay. I as well. We already your your you're pulling the fucking hand
brake. So the car stalls yeah.
My God, I just broke broke the whole car. You just here in the
fucking engine putting Drano and the oil. Oh, Reservoir, what the hell? How
did we even get this far? There's a bunch of drain. Oh, the car broke down in the
combination strip club movie theatre. Well, what that's what they were doing
them. I don't know. Oh, probably not. I don't think I've ever drive through a
movie. I don't think I've ever heard of a drive. That's a better idea than a
drive in movie theatre, a drive through movie. Yeah, play every frame is on the
is on a billboard. Yeah, you drive really fast and it animates it smart. Yeah, or
it's a combination car wash, and so the movie plays while your car gets washed.
It plays in the soap.
The soap goes around your car and it's all the frames of the movie.
Wait, that's actually genius. What do you mean? It drops down.
So when the car gets covered in soap. It drops down like frames of soap.
Because you know how the soap is different colors. Right.
Like an oddly satisfying TikTok where they throw rice in the air and it makes a
picture. Yeah. So it would be every frame is a layer of soap that is dropped
down here, which it's like a New York playing all over your car. Yeah, it's a
long, long drive through, but at the end and the rotating brushes do vibrations of
the sound and their credits. This is the credits would still be in the on the
tassels. The credits are the spaghetti that okay, that works the car at the end.
I like
yeah,
there's a good idea. There's a really good idea. Yeah, you do have a lot of
potential to get final destination in a three hour car wash, though. Oh,
absolutely. I mean, at some point, you're going to want to smoke a cigarette
because you're in your car. Yeah, what about how are you handling? You just go
open the window. If your car doesn't have a bathroom in it, buddy, it's
twenty, twenty, what the hell is wrong with you? What are you doing, bro?
Yeah, you are not going to make it. That's another amazing business idea for
us to start car bathroom, a car. Well, no, not a bathroom. A car bathroom might
work, too. Well, they sell them at like right aid. You can just get like a
You can get a portable urinal.
You mean a bucket?
No, no, no, no. It's a little tube and it fits both penises and vaginers.
What are you talking about?
How do you find the hole for a vagina to do a catheter?
Basically, you just drop it out.
You just let all the pee flop out.
That's what happens. It comes out of both sides.
Are you being real? They sell this at Rite Aid?
What are you talking about?
A portable urinal.
How do girls pee so fast?
It's basically, have you ever cut an orange in half and then squeezed it?
(laughter)
That is so true. That is crazy.
That's what it looks like.
How did you lighten that so lighteningly fast?
That's what it looks like when a girl pees.
It looks like.
Because it comes out of all the parts of it.
squeezing orange on your face. It's like that
oh my God. No it does come out like that. They it takes them like two seconds to
pee yeah and I'll just yeah. Did you
make oh my
that's the sound it makes when it's better. It takes me forever to fucking
pee. I'm getting worried. My dog, Phil, male dog, peas like a girl dog. Wow girl
dogs and male dogs, P and random type sometimes, but he some dogs even with
flip upside down to P.
My kind of dog you have seen my child. They do they walk on their front legs
and they bring their back legs up over their head. My childhood dog feel
that's not true
dog.
You've never seen this before. No, I've never seen this crazy weirdo dog. P
dog. There's so many never seen this video. No, I've seen this video
probably 300 times. What the fuck? Why is he drinking the dog's pee? No, this is an
adverse.
Smoothie. Oh, an ad bro. Come on my bad. I'm going to a smoothie king in a while.
I don't think they have them. I don't even know what that is. I thought it was
Chick-fil-a based on the colors. And yes, I'm cup. You never been to smoothie
king. No, that's a southern thing. I don't is it so the smoothie king is like
this is like Jamba juice. I'd say about 60% of dogs pee this way. That can't be
future. I've never seen this once in my life and I hang around dogs all day.
Wow,
it's not it's not a stupid dog. It's not a remarkable. They should put they
should put another head on the dog.
Remarkable, they should put another head on that dog, but and then you don't
think this is a little bit interesting. This is completely don't find this
unique. This is mundane. Why'd they take the video then?
It's probably just one of those accounts that take videos or whatever
they see.
I guess it could be one of the other videos on here. It's probably going to
be like sandwich. I saw yeah, maybe the fire works at the fair sign. I saw when
I drove next to the road or I drove on the road. I mean there my my mom and my
mom and dad's old dog, Charlie.
He got bullied into being normal by the by our older dog. What does that mean?
How did he pee before he would pee sitting down and then I well, I guess he
just I guess he wasn't bullied, but I guess he just saw the how the other dog
peed some male dogs peed with the squat and some female dogs lift the leg. He
was peeing with the squat forever and then he saw another dog. Pee P's with the
squat. It's he's a very self conscious dog.
I think the squat is really funny because it's like trying to get their P as
close as possible to the ground and shoot it straight forward. It's still
sply. This morning. I was I was just really tired and I took the dog out to
pee and he peed on the ground and I had my Crocs on no socks. By the way, peed
in your shoes, no socks, piss all in my shoes,
everywhere on me, getting in your shoes. He pissed up in my my kicks,
getting an animal in your shoes, excrement on you is not good. I think
it's normal. I'll say it happens all the time. I'm not a fan of it,
but I don't care. Sometimes I pick up the poop and I like it and
I get a little poop on my finger and I have to just hold
my finger up like this until I get to the park. You can
go through the plastic of a dog bag as well. The glove technique,
it's giving you dog germs that will turn you into a dog. I hate the dog bag
technique. What technique would you use? I hate, I don't wanna own a dog because
I don't wanna pick up poop. You could have an animal poop in your house.
You could put the... I'd rather have an animal poop in a thing where I
can scoop it up. No, I like touching the dog's poop through plastic to
experiment with the texture. Sometimes it's unhealthy and you have to call the
vet. It's crazy the different textures that you can feel. It makes me imagine
what it would feel like if I picked up my different poops every day.
and I think about an issue. Well, that's the thing. Sometimes you get happy to
pick one up because it's so simple. Do you think all poop feels like that or do
you think that because we drop it into water, it changes the texture? That's a
good question. That is a really good question. Have you guys ever done an
outside poop? Yeah. Probably once or twice, but I can't remember any specific
instances. When I was a kid, when I was six years old, I thought that I was
hiding it, but I went, I was out playing and then I had to shit so bad.
that I just like drop trow and pooped in the middle of the woods and then wiped
with a leaf and looked up at my cousin Megan was watching the whole thing.
Dude.
And she was like, "Did you just fucking poop?" And I went, "Yeah."
I was obsessed with shitting outside when I was a kid. I had a...
Oh, we know.
There's a tree behind my house.
Oh, you told us about this.
where I would go, I called it my fort,
but it was just a branch that I took shits off of.
(laughing)
It's cool.
- Yeah.
- It was so cool.
And then I would tell people like, yeah, that's my fort.
And like friends would come over
and there'd just be a big pile of my shit
right under the branch.
(laughing)
It was cool, man.
- Yeah.
- I wish that I had had a tree house growing up.
- Me too, man.
- I thought that I had a tree house,
but my neighbor just drilled a plank of wood to the tree.
- That is a tree house.
- Well, I guess it, I mean, I don't know.
- If you could stand on it.
You could go up into it.
It was a treehouse.
You could go, yeah, you could stand on it.
So I guess that is a treehouse.
My treehouse was that there were two knots in the tree that were, in the tree in my yard
that were about six inches off the ground that I would stand in like they were footholds.
Ah, whoa.
And I would imagine I was in a treehouse.
My, there's, we had two, then the other one, I mean, you've all seen the video of my little
brother breaking his arm on the swing.
That was our other treehouse, was just a...
Just a swing on a tree?
a swing on a tree that had like, I think he put like a another plank of wood there.
I only went on a tire swing I think one time at my grandparents house and then the branch
broke and it hit me in the head and I got a concussion.
Damn.
Because I was too fat.
You know what would have been goaded to have as a kid in my yard?
Tether ball.
Tether ball would have been dope.
Real shit.
Yep.
Because that's a game you can play by yourself.
Yeah, you just got to get the ball and the tether.
I would have been out there playing tether ball all day.
Excuse me. What the fuck? Two burps in a row is crazy. Do you remember, no you guys were
long gone by then. I think I've talked to you guys about this. I had that house warming
party that one time and then I was trying to kick everyone out of my house because I
got really tired.
Long gone means 30 minutes by the way.
Yeah. Well, yeah. But I was trying to kick everyone out and then while I was kicking everyone
right now. Tommy says that he's he's told a million people about this, but I was
trying to kick people out. I was hammered and I just had a burp attack that was in
the middle of your talking in the middle. I was like, hey, thank you, thank you
everyone for
hey guys, when I
and like Rick,
you raked on a Rick dude, I was raking like crazy. I literally, I couldn't talk
for like, like
20 seconds. If I was there, I'd be like, "Jeez, Rick, I don't know if I want to leave your party."
I would have made fun of you for raking. I would have gotten so many fucking laughs.
I would have crushed the party. I think that I was about to throw up and I didn't realize it.
Because I was getting crazy.
I got crazy on him. Are you guys going to, when the strike's over, you guys going to go out for the Rick voice?
Yes. Have they not already found anybody?
We got to go to space, Murdy. Murdy?
sounds like Rick. No, well, I would try and take the voice back to the roots of
the character, and I would think, well, this guy's supposed to be a scientist,
so I'd do something along the lines. Morty, it seems that we have to do an
experiment today. Here's what I would do, actually, now that I'm remembering.
Indubitably, Morty. Now that I'm remembering, he's a scientist and not
just a drunk uncle.
I would probably...
Hey, Morty. That's not a scientist voice at all. I would change it to be...
It's according to my calculations, Morty. I feel like that show has become a
little bit to kind of roll. I was going to say a little too boomer, so I would
bring like a new, younger, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Marty, we got to go on
instagram live, Morty, yeah, instead of burping, I go yeah, yeah,
more you hit your vape inside of burping, Morty, we need to watch the aid
and Ross stream tonight, Morty
Morty, Morty, we got to go back in that's actually good. We got to go back
in time and let every time in every time that Rick burps he moans after
Yeah.
Morty, we gotta go.
We gotta go to the Logan Paul Dylan Daniels fight, Morty.
Morty, we gotta, we've gotta, we gotta go back and we gotta,
we gotta save Jake and Logan's relationship, Morty.
We gotta save their relationship.
They're two brothers.
They're two brothers and they're fighting.
Whoa, two brothers.
They're beefing Morty.
They're two brothers and they're beefing Morty.
They're beefing brothers. They're beefing brothers and they're beefing way too hard.
You have an insanely good sexual moan.
Yeah?
I would have sex with you if you made that noise. It doesn't matter what you look like.
Okay.
Even if you were as ugly as you are right now, I would still have sex with you and that
moan would stay there.
You don't think the prisoner outfit that I'm still in is doing anything?
I said you looked good in the prison outfit and you immediately went and got changed into
it.
I got changed into it because I thought we were going to make a joke up top about how
I'm the only one still in prison.
That's your joke to make.
That was my joke to make and I guess I kind of let it steamroll, huh?
Let it steamroll.
Ow, ow.
That does sound like some early like parliament funkadelic title.
Let it steamroll.
Guys, I'd just like to say this before we leave.
I'm sick of the hate that my wife is giving me
for playing Red Hot Chili Peppers in the house.
- I would give you the same hate.
I don't like that band that much.
- You just said that much,
so there is two songs that you like.
- Yep, it's the one from Power Rangers
and it's the one from, actually there's four songs.
♪ How low, how low ♪
- What's that one?
♪ Was like ♪
- What's that one where he's like,
"I got a baby named Adino"?
- That is, you're thinking of the Weird Al version
of that song.
- What?
Yeah, well, I got I got a baby named a Dino. Yeah, that's the Flintstones.
I feel like that's two different songs.
Bedrock. No, this is you're doing. This is a weird out song that you think is a
it's a cover. Not really by the peppers. No, no, no.
Weird out. Interesting. That's why it's funny. It's about the Flintstones.
I thought that they just like the Flintstones.
I mean, they probably do. Who doesn't like the Flintstones?
Well, I don't like the Flintstones. I'm playing one of them.
y'all that I get you my impression of a guy doesn't exist on the patron
episode. Did I get you? Did you believe that I didn't like the Flintstones?
When I said that I think you're going to be surprised that you will have to
crown me as a master troll.
I think what this comes out this Saturday, so then I guess on this comes
out last Saturday, the twenty eighth and the thirty first I'm in Pittsburgh and
Baltimore. Bodymore Murderland. Baltimore.
That was sick. That was actually sick.
I heard Jack say that one time.
I'm going to be in Cashington
Da Coin.
Cashington Da Coin.
I'm going to be in Cashington Da Coin
doing some stand up at Summer.
Cashington Da Coin.
Tonight. Come on through.
And then I'll be here.
Speaking of Jack, he just texted me.
Smoke he said come smoke at my house. That's beast all right. Bye. Bye. Bye
I'm gonna be in da burg
[laughs]