Okay, well, well, well, okay, well, I guess this is a how it is now. This is a
giant you and me. Yeah, we're in. We're gonna take it to the finish line. We're
doing hard time, right? Uh-huh. Hard, hard time. Patrick's out here in random
some cities. I've never even heard of yeah doing shows television right.
Okay, here's my joke that I told you I was going to have a joke about this. I
thought of this, so doing the news and he knows I love the news. Yeah, me too,
and I would be on the news. A great news. Yeah, here's what here's my joke
about Patrick being on the news. Oh, so Patrick thinks he's so cool
being Patrick thinks he's so cool that he's on the news right. Well, watch out
Patrick. Thanks for the way you've made me feel.
you're not the only one I'm going to be on the news very soon. That's right ten to
fifteen times. Yes,
yes, that's my little joke. I thought attacking women yeah doing horrible
thing. Let my feelings out yeah and Patrick because Patrick beat you to the
news. I'm going to be someone else on the news. I've always wanted to do a
funny comedian morning news thing. Fuck dude we can do it. I mean I was going to
walk out and pretend to blow the weather man. Just get down there and yeah
unzipping his pan, I would be like I would probably just act awkward.
Oh okay here wait. Let's do it. No, this is a good. It's a good pat.
We could do the news. Okay, you be the news anchor.
Welcome back to Fox fifty four serving
Los Angeles.
We're here with comedian and podcaster Cameron Fetter Cameron. How are you
doing today?
I'm supposed to answer, so I would do stuff like that. Yeah, I would maybe I
probably like a few hundred hours of Michael Sarah to train myself like an
a that's good learn his man. You know what I you just the thing is about if
you do the new, if you do one of these news shows, I'm not saying yes, unless
it's one of the episodes where they bring a monkey out
yeah. Why is every one of the for a bring me a listen listen, listen,
listen, okay, listen, listen,
first of all, that's why I should be on the news yeah. I'm going to make a clip
go viral. I'm going to give you your D D Mega do do do do do what was the
der hap of what was that other one where the lady had a stroke on the
there? She said she had some kind of a throwing up on himself in an Xbox
and an Xbox video. How small is this guy
video video? I can render things of any size. That's a good, but listen put me
there every they're bringing they they're bringing these guys on the day
news right bring the days on the get guy news. Yeah, they've got listen.
They've got Patrick talking about how he's allergic to carrots. They're
talking by the way, talking about Pat. You smash that one out of the park. I
was incredible, beautiful, the one thing that said when he was on the news, he
said, well, I'm allergic carrots. I can't eat raw carrots, which is very it
reminded me of those old clips of norm doing morning radio. No, it really was
perfect. Listen, they're bringing they're bringing on these comedians.
I bring on girl God to talk about
tanning tanning hacks and all this this daytime bullshit man bring me on for the
breaking news yeah. You call me up when when there's a killer loose when terror
straight there in thirty seconds, not a problem. I will I will camp out outside
of your new studio for something real till some kind until something really
really bad happening happens. Get me in there and then I show up and I go. I
I mean I'm doing the bits yeah yeah exactly bits man yeah yeah I'm acting
Michael,
hey who am I hey here's my present at fifteen year old kid who's walking down
the highway at the wrong time.
We're both on there and I've yeah this is the guy come we're going to kill a
kid.
We're going to kill a fifteen year old kid
and here's me what
those two comedians on the nerves.
so fun.
Yeah, they bring you on to talk about maybe China's invading somewhere.
You're like, "Well, that's very interesting. Here's what I think that
Doug from the show... Doug would have to say about that."
It's a good idea, dude. Comedians are very good people. Yeah, yeah, and
they're funny. Better than most, funnier than most. Funnier than almost everybody
in the world these days. Dude, I would hate to be a non comedian. We call
call them civilians. Yeah, I don't like civilians. I would hate. Oh, my God, if I
were a civilian,
I mean, what do you even do? What do you do all day? The spark that- How do you
not have- what do you do with your, with your overflowing abundance of creative
energy? I guess doodle. So, you just draw- I guess you either doodle or jack off.
See, I don't do any of those. I retain my, my- Right. I do- So, a civilian would
have- Doodling is jacking off, by the way, because it's not actually creating
anything. That's how I thought of jacking off, is because of the word doodle. And
you're thinking of your doodle. Yeah, doodle. No, but I mean like when I'm do I
mean like doodling is the same thing as jacking off because you're wasting your
your your less creative spark. Yeah, in the same way that you spill your seed
like yeah into a toilet. That's so fucking true. I mean, I guess yeah, when
I think about me versus a civilian, when both of us might have that idea in our
head of a naked woman. Yeah, the civilian probably sits down and cranks one out on
the toilet gets it all over the bath mat. Yeah, that's hanging on the side of the
tub. Yeah, and it drips down into the that you painted a target on
the corner, the space between the tub and the ground.
But me, the grout, that's the word I was looking for. Yeah, me, I'm thinking of
a joke about it. Yeah, two boobs.
Why not three? Yeah, two boobs. Wait, what is one the mom boob and one's the
dad boob? This is just the kind of shit a comedian comes up with that you guys
you could never even think of yeah. You see two things, one's a mom, one's a dad,
oh or maybe they're both dad. So where's the baby? Yeah, wait, so where's the
baby? Is that the baby? Yeah, pointing to the belly button. The belly button.
Wait, that's a reverse boob. And this must be the baby, and then I guess what's
under it is probably a similar looking sibling to the belly button. This is my
Edinburgh Fringe show. Yeah. Where I bring a naked woman on stage and I go,
"Okay, so let's break this down." Yeah. Hair,
hair
and and her feet also yeah do something like that there was there when I went to
Edinburgh fringe years ago. We need to do years and we need to do I remember when
you went and I was water. You think we would slaughter you think we
I thought that was an evil villains laugh. Is it not? No, it was a dog. Oh my
God, that completely sounded like a human. That was insane crazy.
So nuts. What the fuck, man? Oh, here comes a package. Oh, get ready. It's FedEx. Oh,
they're about to knock on our door. I'm really nervous. They're literally walking right up.
Oh my God. Please, no. Please, no. Please don't do it. Please don't do it. Please. They're
coming. They're going to knock on that door. They're going to come here. I swear to God.
It's this Goodfellas diner scene right now. Yeah, no, I think Fringe would be the worst
experience of your life. I can't believe it. Everybody who does it is like, "Oh, it changed
my life. It's like yeah man. You did Molly. Yeah, you put you drank for thirty
nights in a row. You chilled yeah. I don't think it's and then you ask like
how are the shows. It's for people came to every single one. The only people
who sell out the shows are this guy, Stuart Lee, Stuart Little, Stuart Little,
who's a very huge across the pond. He's a very and he does kind of sardonic kind
of dry British wit. The only the only joke I remember from from from the friend.
I went to two fringes actually. Wow. Yeah, because my friend went to school over there.
I could I should get a friend in the front of your head. Yeah. I obviously I remember
seeing a bunch like there are a bunch of people that I wanted to see that I like. There's
like oh like I'll go see this person because I know of yeah whatever, but the only like
the fun part is to walk into random stuff that you don't you don't even know something's
happening. I just walk into a bar and there will just be a show happening and you sit
and watch and the only thing that I remember from any of those was this guy who we like
just walked into this random show and he's doing stand up and the only joke I
remember is he was talking about Millennials and he was saying that they
don't he was doing literally like what you would like a he was saying that
Millennials don't look at sunrises anymore because they look to spend too
much time looking at their apps. He was saying he was fully honest like
earnestly like probably middle it like two young middle ages middle ages 600
thirty years old. I would guess like forties fifties, like two to not in the
right window for this type of thing. I feel like barely not a millennial yeah
and then the only thing I remember it a really strong accent. He kept being
like yeah and you'll see millennials in the in the park doing toy chi. Oh my
boy, she and then he didn't act out of toy toy toy, toy, toy, toy, and you just
go
and I've never seen anybody do Taiji in my life and this guy got a thirty day
thirty shows. Oh yeah. Well that's cool. Was it like, do they do shows in the middle of
the day in the morning and stuff? Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Sounds like hell man. I hate shows.
Well yeah, that's, it's, I mean, it is, it's the, it's the Mystery Science Theater 3000
style comedy fans delight. Yeah. It is the, it's the lol cow comedy fans. Yeah. Paradise
Playground. Yeah. You get to see one, you buy, you buy an expensive ticket to see like
Dan Soder one day or whatever, and then every other day you see people
wallowing in the filth
of their own brain. Here's what we do man,
you, me,
Patrick, okay,
right, Pete, I'm okay, Pete, Pete Holmes,
we run that town. We should do a play, we got to do a four person show.
We gonna run this town tonight. The other thing is, the other thing as far
as I can tell, if you get, if you get the like
official. I don't know how the whole thing works. I've know I knew some
people who did some shows and I don't know how you like get it. I think you
have to like get it and assert, but like I think that if you get a friend show
like they newspapers will send people to review your show. That's so awesome,
like no matter what like it's you can you can be you can just have the worst
show of all time and they'll send somebody to write a review of a show.
It's the worst show I've ever seen. It's one star. See if we can get like all
one star reviews. I really think we could do the worst show ever.
that's a great idea. That's a really good and try to get like to try to get
every day. I one star review in a different newspaper, make make truly the
worst show of all time. That is really genius. No, I mean what will we be?
What we even do? What is I mean we wouldn't have to try. We already did a
full fucking episode. How do you eat, but how do you even repulse Europeans?
Yeah, what repulses these sick animals? I would say, oh, we can take a shower.
we could take a shower on stage. We can any TV show or video game that has
colors in it. Yeah, we could brush our teeth. We could
we could listen to loud music, vegetables, rock and roll, that's great,
leafy greens,
cruciferous vegetables, toothbrushes, toothbrushes for sure. That's what we
could do. We could do just the whole thing. We could design the entire thing
to discuss, to discuss the European. Individuality. Individuality, yeah,
yeah, maybe entrepreneurship. Yeah, definitely. We could do an entire show
about an entrepreneur with the most amazing teeth in the world who eats six
small meals every single day or maybe he does intermittent fasting and he's in
really good shape. Did you see what the top joke of the fringe was? You see the
number one top J top number one joke of the fringe. What was the number one joke
of the friend? Let me look it up so I can read it verbatim. But it was a pun.
And who is the bard that this joke?
Let's lips.
This is not a joke of French 2023.
Okay, so comedy do people do drama drama? Yeah. Yeah, it's
like plays and all the drama.
They do. There's a bunch of one-person shows.
I hate it's everything from one man shows to one woman.
Yeah, a solo show. No, it's over there. It's a one-man show
or a one woman show.
They don't call it solo shows.
Like God,
let's see. Okay,
The top joke was written or told by Lorna Rose Treen. So shout out to Lorna Rose Treen.
Lorna.
Here it is. I started dating, oh hold on.
Yeah, get it ready.
I started dating a zookeeper, but it turned out he was a cheetah. That was the best joke
I've ever heard.
That was the top joke of the 2023 Fringe Festival.
it doesn't even make any sense. He was a cheetah. You thought he was a zoo. You
dated a large wild animal and he thought he was a zookeeper because he was at the
no, you don't understand this woman just has a heavy accent. You're saying I
started dating a zookeeper and it turns out he was a cheater. It's a dead joke
and the joke is that the joke is about how unfaithful people are nowadays.
That is so sad. Actually, here's the here's the
is there a runner up?
so it's just this web. This web page I pulled up has all of them for the like
every year. I need to hear all these are all the exact same. Okay, give me one.
This is insane me twenty twenty two twenty twenty two. So I see what
happened in twenty twenty two. What was like a big news story in twenty twenty
two
the podcast about list podcast our list at a united states tour. So this is how
this is the year that this happened. Okay, give me the joke. I tried to steal
spaghetti from the shop, but the female guard saw me and I couldn't get pasta.
Oh wait, it's it's UK, so and I couldn't get pasta.
It works better in the UK, and I'm going to be honest yeah yeah pasta. It
doesn't make yeah. I went pasta, but I couldn't get pasta. That's funny. Yeah,
that's okay. So these are all going to be the female guard saw me. Well, you
had to say it's that I was wondering why the female guard, but there's no
there's not it's not called past him. Yeah, you have to say otherwise. It's a
yeah.
okay, give me the I couldn't get anti pasta yeah. See that I could be good in
an opposite kind of universe. I went to the I tried to steal. I went to the
opposite spaghetti store and the female guard tried to stop me and I couldn't
get anti pasta.
Okay, it skips a toy. Anti anti pasta already exists, though
yeah yeah, that's why I said it wouldn't be an opposite. It would just be a yeah.
Well, an appetizer store yeah. Yeah, I went to the appetizer. That's a better
joke. I went to the appetizer store and the female guard told me told me I
wouldn't be able to get an tp it yeah. I couldn't steal from and she and she was
an anti guard also yeah. So this is
this is from twenty nineteen, because I guess they took a couple years off for
cove it probably, but blow me yeah. So it's one and I think about here. This is
basically cove. It is brewing in this in the during this French, the nervousness
the guys, the it's on the influence of or you know years and this is co vid years
or they're in they're intersecting, but this is maybe the last carefree joke.
Oh wow right, so last the last vestige of happiness for everything was so yeah
way. I need to know what it was like because these these last two have been
very dark yeah. So this one is is by olaf falafel. No, yeah, it's by olaf
falafel. That can't be the name of a him. It must be okay. Here's the joke. I
I keep randomly shouting out. That's all that's a great start to a joke. That's a
good set up. I keep randomly really, really good. That's a really strong
every every every comedian has at least one. I keep read. I keep randomly
shouting out.
I keep randomly shouting out broccoli and cauliflower. I think I might have
florets
all right, yeah, all right, that's my Olaf Olaf. Olaf Olaf. This guy just
your check out all a falafel on instagram, a bit as real or he crushes
the reels
yeah okay. Now we have the first real joke in twenty eighteen. This is the
first one that's not a pun that I'm going back
Adam row working at the job center has to be a tense job, knowing that if you
get fired, you still have to come in the next day
because you have to you have to get a job at the job center. They mean the
unemployment office. I think yeah they must have a different. They must call
the job center, the job center, the job, be
gotta go down to the job. Yeah, we can stop it man. This goes all the way, but
okay, give me the oldest. We go two thousand and nine Dan and to Polsky
okay, I'm anti Polsky hedgehogs. Why can't they just share the hedge?
I kind of like that one.
I kind of like that one a little bit. Hey hedgehogs,
I'm okay. That's like a joke man when I was a first starting stand up.
When I was like a type of joke, I would yeah, when I was like sixteen, I had a
joke that was like
I sucked so bad. I was so bad for so long. I know man. It's I had a they
shouldn't you shouldn't be allowed to try to stand up in high school. Yeah,
and it sucks that if you're not like the only people who are really good at that
age are like like Dave Chappelle. Dave Chappelle was like fifteen years old and
was like really good. Yeah. And like if you know that if you do it one time and you're
16, you don't do well, you're like, well, okay. So I know that I have my ceiling is
way, way lower than I was hoping. But I think my first joke I ever told on stage was like,
it was like, hey, man, these ant eaters, that was the beginning. Yeah, again, another classic
thing of animals. These ant eaters, you ever think they get a little bit tired of eating
That's the kind of joke I think of now. It's kind of funny. That's all I can think of.
But then I remember my first time doing stand-up, I was at this hookah bar in Wilmington. Yeah.
And my mom dropped me off and she wanted to watch and I said, "No, you must leave." Right.
And I made friends with these like hippies who were there to like watch their friend
do like a DJ set at the open mic. And it took him like 15 minutes to set up and he went right
after me, but they were all they were drug addicts. Yeah, for sure. And the guy one of
the guys had like track marks all up and down his arm and I was just a little kid. So I
was like, hey man, why do you have all these holes on your arm? Yeah, and he was like I
give blood a lot. Yeah, and that really stuck with me. That stuck with me forever. I was
like that is the light that is a very, very skill. He went to he went to the he went to
to like the you know how like in a in a old TV show like their hero, there's the
the villains are the exact mirrors of the heroes and they have their own evil
organization. Yeah, he went to like the evil mirror dare and he learned like
twenty things to say when people ask you about the track.
Well, I guess he wants to say yes to
heroin. My there's a mosquito problem in my bedroom. That's a tattoo. That's a
failed tattoo. They went really slow. The machine got all broken. Just a bunch of
holes in my arm. I fell yeah
on a bunch of needles and I remember that I think they I was like sixteen, but I
was definitely a dork. I was wearing like yeah flannel and like like blue jeans.
You know like those those deep blue jeans that have like the yellow stitching like
that kind of like Levi's jeans. That was what I wore every day and I
they yeah they were like smoking a joint and they were like I didn't even ask
about that when they just told me it was a cigarette. I was like I know a weed is
man. Yeah, and now you don't know track. I feel like it's a fair. Yeah, I guess if I
don't know, yeah, assumption. I just didn't I didn't hang out with that many heroin addicts
up to that point. Yeah, you know, at least not doing it into their veins. Yeah, but they
were good people. They loved me and they I had a video. It's so crazy. I do. I just think
about this. What was your first time doing stand up? I was fourteen. That is so young.
Yeah, man. Yeah. I mean, that's what I can't do. They let you on. I exactly. Well, yeah,
me and my friend, we had to like find there were maybe like one or two open
mics in Boston that would even let a 14 year old in because they're all bars.
Yeah, of course. So yeah, they're not going to let you like we got turned
away from you could have done. Yeah, yeah, I don't think Muya was around.
Probably not. Yeah, in fact, it definitely wasn't, but it was at it was
at a Cheers. Really? Yeah, they had an open mic there and she had an old open
mic. Yeah, and that's what I think about. It's crazy, dude. I was yeah, I was 14
fifteen years old, I was doing literally the worst jokes of all time. Yeah, so
horrible, like like every joke was like the one I can remember is like this is
probably one of the first ones ever I did on stage, which is like oh like I
love skydiving, but everyone always freaks out when I do it in business
class,
like something like that, you know, like it's like completely nothing and yeah
just all only that that exact set up and punch line. Yeah, I in different
situations of like here's something you're not supposed to do in this
situation. I remember that yeah there are people walking around. You saw me do
stand up when I was fourteen and they were like that was a and they're ever
seen yeah, because I remember all the worst things, the worst stand up sets
I've ever seen yeah. Of course, and these these people definitely yeah yeah
so they were like yeah, yeah you of course you remember a fucking fourteen
year old kid doing yeah. The thing is you have your kid. These are people who
are who are probably I'll run into again in my life
and I almost already accessible. If they were at the cheers open, Mike yeah,
well, I know of a few of them that was Sam Jay there yeah
yeah. I talk to same day like multiple times. So she's very nice. Yeah, she's
very funny yeah, but again yeah, I was fourteen years. That is so fucking
awesome man. That is so awesome yeah. All of my I did that joke and then I did
a bunch of jokes about like that were just made up stories, but not made up in
like, "Oh, these are crazy, obviously made up stories." They were just like lying
stories that could be true.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know? And it was all...
You don't go far enough.
Yeah. But I think if you're a kid, this is a recommendation to all the kids, all the
kids who are not civilians, the non-civilian kids who want to start doing stand-up comedy.
Kids who are in the trenches.
Yeah, the kids who have been enlisted by God in this holy army.
The divine mandate that's been handed down.
If you're a child and you do stand-up comedy, you have to do it about how weird it is that
that you're a kid yeah, you have to do about Pokemon. You have to do it about
like you have to do it about fucking about fucking about sex. That would see
that was you see you were fourteen. You could have done that at sixteen yeah,
you know I'm halfway a man dude that you just like I just got a like I was
eating pussy. The other flashbulb memory okay,
there was this guy there was like he was like a
like a resource teacher type guy
that it was like at my school very briefly and I liked I would talk to him
and we talked about like how I wanted to do stand up and he was like he said
that he was a stand up comedian and then we were like just talking about it and
then he told me one of his jokes and it was something about it was literally so
it was literally about something about his wife's like pubes like it was like
it's like some really graphic, like not like not really a joke, just something
about and it was like it was about his wife like like and he and then I
remember really vividly at the end of it. He was like now don't steal my job
dude. I'm like you should have done it man. What are you talking about eating
my wife? You the other day
I'm in high school. Yeah, I have a wife and my joke. See that would be funny,
though it would be funny. That would actually be really funny. If that is I
mean that's what you have to do. If like a thirteen year old went up and was
doing like Rodney, that's so funny, but it wouldn't because no thirteen year
could ever do Rodney without seeming like their parent was forced. Exactly. That's
the other thing is what if you watch like if you ever seen an orphan, you ever
seen those old clips of Amanda Bynes doing stand up and she's like twelve
years old. No, she's like pretty funny, but it is clear that her parents were
way way way too involved. Yeah, because no kid is going to do this. Yeah, of
course, kids want to play. Kids love playing. Kids don't want to hang out in
smoky, dirty nightclothes. It's the worst experience of all time. Yeah, it's
awful. I used to get really bad stage fright too. Yeah me too man. Yeah when I
was like I used to like be completely shaking on stage. I was like freaking the
fuck out. I remember the second open mic I ever did was like the next week and I
remember being I did I had like I did the math and I was like okay if I do an
open mic every week yeah until I turn 18 I'll have done stand-up like over like a
like a hundred and fifty times by then yeah and I I was like and then I'll be
really good yeah, and I think I did stand up like four times in North Carolina
when I was a kid, because by the fourth time I was like okay, this is this is
this is another cheat code for every for every kid who wants to level up and
become a comedian. Start doing stand up as young as possible, do it ten to twelve
times and then don't do it for eight to ten years and then say and then when you
get back into it, you say yeah, I've been doing it since I was yeah. I started it
about eight years ago. I love saying that yeah, I did it when I was fourteen and
then I only did it for a year and then I stopped and I haven't done it since
that's what that's what I say is I say I say yeah, you know I started stand
about ten years ago. Yeah, it's so fun. It's very especially because like even
yeah, it doesn't even cat is nothing yeah my my second time doing stand up.
It was that it was a
an open mic at this comedy club and it was above a restaurant and there was
kind of like wedding party or bachelorette party or something that was at the restaurant
downstairs and they heard there was a free comedy show upstairs. So right before the
open mic starts, it's like, you know, 30 comics or whatever. That's the only people in the
audience. But right before the open mic starts, like 150 people walk up, just like drunk old
people and everybody else is like so excited. But I was terrified. And the guy who was hosting,
I like met him and talked to him and we like got along and he had these like this was 2000
and 2013 maybe 2012 and he was wearing you know people usually wear like red skinny jeans.
Yeah I can picture that. So he had like red skinny jeans on and when I went up I was like
and me and this guy really got along and I went up I shook his hand and was like thank
thank you guys give it up for yourselves and give it up for your host pants. You
guys
death just pure death and I looked at him and he looked so fucked up. He looks so
fucking sad, didn't talk to me afterwards and then I was what give it
up for spider man, give it up for spider man from the ways down y'all for half
spider half spider man bottom bottom part spider man, give it up for mix and
match spider man spider spider man at the beginning of the movie before he
that's a really good costume y'all. You look like Spider Man at the big
winning wait, wait, wait, this is too much. You look like Spider Man when he's
getting ready at the beginning of the movie
dressed in dressed in the Spider Man costume, like like literally movie
accurates pre yeah pre cost with the part of guys thing and then going up be
like guys. I look like Spider Man at the beginning of the way, so fucked up. I
just real. Oh yeah, someone just told me before I come on stage. I look like
Spider Man when he does the cage match, you all Spider Man before he gets a
cool cost before he learns how to so does he so that himself yeah. I think
he's he so's all of it him. So he even so's the cool one. I'm just can't be
right man. He's literally the most powerful man of all time. He so's
himself suits. He's a genius in every way. He's a scientific genius. Yeah,
he's buff and strong. He can so suits any and a million girls like him.
why just a couple girls, because he's a nerd yeah girls like nerds. Now that was
kind of the he's flipped the switch for us. He did flip flip it over, so I get on
stage. I say congratulations to his pants or whatever. I tell my lies. I do
my anteater joke and I it was a lottery open mic, so I ended up going way later
in the night and I told and my I had a curfew. I was barring my mom's car. My
mom was like be home at eleven yeah, and so I go on stage at like eleven fifteen
and so I'm on stage and my phone starts ringing with the ringer in my pocket,
and it's just like ringing so loudly, buzzing so loudly, everybody can hear it,
but I'm too nervous to touch it. So my phone just rang for like two minutes of
my set, completely dying, and then a lady in the front was like so honestly,
was like, "Hey, honey, are you okay?"
And I was like, "What?" She's like, "Are you okay?" I was like, "Shut up,
bitch. I think I just went like yeah, I'm fine yeah, I'm fine. Look at this
bitch of the front row.
Are you okay,
and then I yeah, then I just ran off stage pretty much God that is and what's
worse than you bomb as a kid bombing is already so do that yeah so many and
then you go and then you go home and you get grounded once or twice. I also
completely forgot everything because I was so I was oh yeah, I had lights. I
I said to to Joe and then we got on a after twenty seconds, your kid you'd be
well. I forgot yeah and everyone's to everyone's too nice. Yeah kid. Oh,
I but you know that you're an adult at heart yeah. I did so. I did the first
one to mature to be comforted. I did the first one and then at the second time I
told everybody that I was in college right and they were like Oh, what
college you go to and there's only one college in my town. So I was like I go
to you and CW and they're like Oh, we go to you and CW. What year are you and I
he's like I get of three yeah. I skipped a couple of grades. Actually, I'm really
smart yeah. I do I'm mostly in the lab yeah run into me probably never seen me.
I'm in the I'm a do experiments. My major is experimental ism yeah. I'm in
the lab pretty much all day and night. You wouldn't even recognize me because
the goggles I have to wear for the safety, because I'm dealing with so many
full hazmat suit yeah, so I'm the guy who walks around as a hazmat man yeah.
I'm a professor
Yeah, and then I remember when I got to college, I was like, "Oh, maybe I'll do
like... Maybe I'll start doing stand up here." They had an open mic there. Yeah.
And I didn't want to 'cause I went to one one time. It was... Nobody was doing
comedy, it was all music.
It was like, "I don't wanna be the one guy who's doing..." And it was in the
dining hall. Hey. Yeah, yeah. Hey. You guys like music? Well, you're gonna love
comedy then.
but I went to a they had an in you know, I just had an idea, sorry, but comedy that
you can dance to
comedy with a beat comedy with a beat and you can dance to it the whole time
you can do the piano accompaniment. Yeah, Rory Scoville did that. Okay, that's
cool. Yeah, but I'm thinking we should get a piano accompaniment for the show.
Yeah, that's a good idea. That's a great idea. That's a really good idea.
Pianos can't be that expensive.
Buddy or heavy.
It's like you don't know the first thing about these. Sorry. I'm a little
confused. He weighs about a pound yeah, fifty two pounds for a piano. I went to a
I didn't want to do stand up, but I was like maybe I'll do improv. So I went to
like this improv like not improv club. I got a jam and it was just it turned me
off of comedy for probably three years. Yeah, I was like this. These are really
these are sick people. Yeah, it's these are sick fucking people. It's it's pretty
pretty tough. Yeah, one of the kids was, I think I've talked about this before, but
one of the kids was like, I met him there and then I ended up having a class with him.
And the first day of class when we did like the icebreakers, they were like, "Say your
name and a fun fact about yourself." And he was like, "Well, my name's Samuel and
I can actually do an amazing Jim Carrey impression." And then he stood up and went, "All righty
and just sat back down and we're like oh wow that's good man and this kid did
improv at my my college. I'm so glad that I will never again in my life have
to say a fun fact about myself. I feel like I had something recently where I
had to on like I think I was it was like shooting something and somebody and we
did icebreakers and I was like I don't need to know these people's names. Yeah
Yeah, get me in get me out yeah, I'm the talent. I'm Tom Cruise. Yeah, what I
don't need to know any of these fucking people's names and by the way, if I'm
ever a movie star, I will not be walking around shaking hands being like oh man,
it's I I'm so glad you're on this one because I saw you on the last one. I'm
going to say, would you mind hey there that tape is peeling up yeah. Can you
re tape that and then they go? Oh yeah right away, and I said I wasn't talking
to you. I was talking to a bug on the ground. Yeah, I was talking. I honestly
can't tell you people apart because you all I would talk to you. I would look at
a fly and I would say, can you tell that PA over there to get me a copy? Sorry,
I just assumed that was your boss,
because he's bigger than you or at least he acts bigger. Yeah,
man, I would be such a good movie star. I would make them build me a house on
set instead of a trailer.
I've been getting these videos on my shorter video feeds
that are is this woman who does intimacy coordination. That's your phone. She
does intimacy coordination. Is there anything on it? No, there's a photo of a
woman as the background. It's a painting. Okay, well
we to make fun of me for being disabled and not being able to tell the
difference between a painting and a photo. Okay, it's a new disability that
they're going to name after, but you can't solve a capture. I saw a cap. I'll
do it right now. You can give me four letters. Okay,
that's
only humans can figure that out. That's really tough. Actually, that's
actually really funny. No, I actually know the real way to do an audio capture.
Okay, it's
you say, okay, tell me what what these four letters are.
That was that would have been hard if you didn't say a b c d. Yeah, if you did
it, but I'm just doing an example. Yeah, it's hard to think of four letters.
It's really tough and not in sequence of the alphabet. No, yeah, that is really
fucking let me try again. Okay,
that was better yeah yeah, it's just scary that you couldn't spell something
by accident yeah. Don't people find captures all the time that say like
you're fat and stuff
you would think that they would have some kind of software technology. I
I used to look at you remember how like fail blog you seven or at least like
there used to be a million sites that were all like fail blog, but they're
like hyper specific. Well, that's why here's why fail blog a really
I hope fail blog never gets Saturday night live never gets cast on Saturday
and alive because they did that one website English remember that I do
remember that yeah, where it was just people from other countries who couldn't
spell yeah, they just had a million of those different and one of them was for
I don't remember what it was called, but it was all captures that spelled things
and they would do a little like rage comics and it would be like I would
have a capture that spell. It said something crazy as part of it. I
remember that no those were sick yeah yeah, we need to be your fat
captures of completely. They suck so bad now click the bike, click the bike
until you can't click the bike anymore. I fail that no capture should ever have
a prompt where it says until you can't anymore. It's like I'll be here all day.
Yeah. Is that a challenge? I'll click fucking everything. Yeah, but I hate when
it says like click that when it's the traffic light one and I'm like well do I
click the parts with the box or do I click the parts that just have the lights
in it? Do I click the if there's like three pixels into the corner of this?
Yeah, do I still click that? Do I click this one? How much does the computer
know is a traffic light? Yeah, well I think captchas are also a complete scam
because I have a VPN and if I have my VPN on, it auto fails my captchas every
time even if I do it right. Really? Or at least sometimes it will be like, well first
of all it will give me a capture every time I google anything if I have a VPN on no matter
where it's set to. What? I've never heard of this. And maybe I'm just in trouble. Maybe
you are in trouble. Maybe they have something on me. You're getting throttled. I told you
they looked at my bag at the airport. So who knows. Have you ever been pulled aside? I
have been. And they wipe your butt? They wipe my electronics. They took all my electronics
leaks out of my bag and I to like turn them all on use them and turn them on
really yeah. This was the for an international flight yeah. That makes
some sense. I guess yeah it was ran, but who's going to fucking who's who's
coming from America, a bomb in a kindle yeah and he's coming from America to
kill Scott. I was yeah. I was when I was flying to fringe. I thought I was going
to destroy the friends. They could tell us a comedy terrorist yeah. They could
they did you know little did they know that you were just going to you know I
because I did I terrorized it man. I laughed in people's faces. Yeah, I
walked around. I said you're you're shite. Yeah, which is the ultimate quite
you are quite shite. Yeah, yeah, you are lower than you need to quite comedy
shite head. You need to shite you your pants shite your trousers right now.
Well, I guess try it would go in your pants before your I don't like that
other word that they call pants. I'm never going to say that word now. Well,
you know if you go if you so here's a fun. Yeah, the pants is what they call
underwear. So when you go to the UK and you say this sentence, tell me I'm
going to go outside wearing only my pants
with nothing over them, they'd look at you like you're psycho or here. That
would be normal unless it was really snowy outside and they would assume you
wanted snow pants over. They say what you're not going to wear snow pants over
your pants, but you don't wear anything over your pants. You could also say I
I have my fanny hanging out of my pants yeah and they would go. You have your
vagina hanging out of your underwear and say no you fool. My ass cheeks are
hanging out. Okay, you want to be on jackass? Yeah, exactly. They'd say you
want to be on ridiculousness and I go yeah, thank you.
Yeah, or here's one. These chips are made out of potatoes.
That one works yeah, but not if you're holding up a tortilla chip. Oh my God,
that would break their mind. Make sense in
either either country, would it to hold up a to teach
tips? Yeah, I guess you're right. That's kind of a nonsense. We're just saying
this is a chip. If you held up a to change, they would go. What the hell
are you on about? Are you daft
cultural differences man? I hate that. Here's another cultural difference over
there. Every instead of saying for rent, every apartment has a sign that says to
let so it looks like every apartment is a sign that says toilet and then a phone
number every single one yeah. Why do they call it letting some people call it that
here, though? Why see it's it's renting here, but then it's sub letting why not
sub renting yeah. I think let is probably a type of form of the verb lease and you
let them use this yeah. You at least you use this, but it's not at least though
unless you are very Missy.
I will Lee. I will lead you use my
apartment. I will well gamers do that's true yeah. They don't have leet speak in
the UK either. No, no, that's just how no it wouldn't work. No, it wouldn't work
at all, because a new is something else over there. A new is probably say that
over there. Yeah, you say it's a grass part of the body. That is my big fear
about going to other countries. Besides there being cartels yeah in every every
country has a cartel except America. I want to get involved with the cartel man.
You want to get involved with them? Oh, yeah, I want to you. We just talked
about this last night, but yeah, you should you should know because I don't
think I don't think you'll hear it from him. Jubio was was I think cartel
scammed. I think he was attacked by a cartel member. Really dirty police
officer pulled him over. Oh, one of the I've that was one of the things I read
about before I go to Mexico is that you shouldn't drive alone at night because
the police will pull you over and shake you down. He got pulled over. The cop said the
tickets $300 and you have to pay it in cash right now. And he said, I do not have any
cash on me. And he said, okay, well, there's an ATM at the gas station down the street.
And if you go over there, then it's only $30. And he was like, and I think Jubio just said,
I don't have $30. And he said, okay, then it's $10. And so he just gave him 10 bucks.
That's what I read about. That's what they do to you.
Why do we not have, why does every cop in America act like they are like, like a wage,
they're like crusaders. They're like, yeah, waging some whole, like it, it means more
than just get your money. Yeah, just get your money, knock people out. Why are you wasting
all your fucking time doing what we need to do? We need to have a system like Mexico where
the normal cops, and you know, now that I'm thinking about it, we kind of maybe already
do, but we need to make we need to model it more like this. The normal cops.
These are the guys they're going to pull you over. They're going to shake you
down. If you're walking from a home and you're holding a beer, they put you in
jail. Yep, and you have to pay ten million dollars to get out and you see
one of these normal cops and you're afraid, but they have the federales.
And these guys, these are the good guys. It's the opposite. Here. The hometown
the beat cops. These are good people. They're just walking around. They just
needed a donut. They needed some money. Cops don't get paid that much, but they
needed a little bit of money. I like the color of the outfit. Can't wear that
color. It's blue, man. I do think that if cops wore red outfits, you'd see a
lot more people signing up. It's just cooler. It's a little bit Nazi-ish, I
I guess. Yeah, well, they didn't wear red. They just had red on their arm. Yeah, but
if they today, well, I'm thinking of Red Skull. Yeah. Well, that was mostly his
face. You're so right more than his clothes. So fucking right. Yeah, but I
guess typically a red guy does wear evil. How do I around is what from what
I said? Could we people ask you and me all the time? Yeah. How do you fix the
police? Uh huh. How do we do it, man? Tears. I mean, just look at it's all.
it's all just different levels. You let you you have one
strata of cops that this is reserved. These are corrupt cops. We need to stay
where a special badge. Listen, you guys can walk around. You can be cops because
if we try to take you off the force, you're probably going to kill the
chief's family or something. You guys can't it's listen. It's it's giving the
it's given the little brother that disconnected Xbox controller. It is
giving that as fuck. Yeah, a five pointed sheriff star. That's what they get to
somewhere yeah and they walk around fuck it a one hundred pointed star,
because you guys are the most special and important police of all and maybe we
split their tongues
and they walk
yeah and cloaks, I said in a registration yeah, because then the game
is here. It's not don't break the law. Yeah, you see one of these cops. You
get the fuck away immediately. That's right. See that's the thing that's so
tough about police officer about fixing the police. You either need to make them
some on just like Singapore, like you do anything and you instantly get your
head blown off yeah or they need to be basically just doing nothing. Here's
another here in America they're in the middle man. It doesn't work yeah.
Here's another solution don't change anything about the cops, but make prison
really easy to escape from,
and then the cops will be there will be more criminals around the cops won't
the time to harass people who are what singing too loudly. I do think getting
me in trouble for singing at 4 a.m. on Sunday night. Yeah, well, the fuck you
I'm listening and it helps me sleep. Yeah, fall asleep. While I sing, I'm
doing rent in my kitchen. Sue me. I live in New York City. Okay. I thought this
is supposed to be the most amazing place on earth. I think I nowadays. I think it
is my oh yeah, because you walk around Manhattan. I got New York a fud. You did
Francis Ha. I just honestly I made a lot of it did make I was like, oh, this is
actually sucks because because it's the NYU kids all just moved in.
These NYU kids, pretty tough nerds. They're really it really is like another.
I mean, you know the type of like the like, oh, I look at that. Look at you
guys. When you see the new college kids walking around, they're wearing their
student IDs on a lanyard around their neck and they're walking around and
they're looking at everything. Yeah. You know that like you see, I was seeing
I was in Boston be like oh you guys yeah. Oh look at you best you oh you don't
know how bad it's going to be. You don't know what it's like. I don't know.
Title nine title, nine title, nine title, nine title, nine
transfer, transfer, transfer,
drop out, drop out, no financial aid, no financial aid, food pantry. You look
like food pantry. Yep Yep Yep alcoholic hit by a car
first one to die. Definitely the first one to die. Look at this fucking kid.
Yeah, you don't get that here because these kids are millionaires. No, these
kids are crazy man. They're really it really completely transforms the
experience of seeing an eighteen year old walking around and you see them
when you can you can fully they're doing the they're doing a movie walk.
Yeah, they're fully there. They're all completely invested in not looking like
that kid, but they're still wearing the fucking lanyard. Yeah, but they're doing
the they're doing a they're doing a swag walk. Yeah, that's when you got to look
at them and you can look at the clothes they're wearing and the way that their
face looks and you say yeah, that's that you're a no bomb back kid. Yeah, you
came to New York because you watched lost in translation. Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know why I didn't go to try to go to a college in New York. I didn't
even try yeah. I probably tried. I didn't I got wait listed really yeah. I
probably I think it I think I thought New York was a wack AF. It's I mean I
think it's kind of when I was a college in New York. Yeah, I think I agree yeah
Yeah, I think it's a I think it's too. I think it's too much. I think I don't
think that you can treat a big real city as a college playground. I think it will
warp your life when I was like when I moved to Boston. Boston was like the it
felt like the biggest city ever to me. It's goaded dude. Yeah, it's very small
though. It's tiny. That's what's so great. I was like scared of it. I was like
this is too big. I need to live on a farm. Yeah, I mean that's what that that
that is you have you that's what I mean. You can't go to the biggest city in the
country for calling nowhere to go, you know where to go, but but down yeah,
which in terms of size
yeah, you could go to Hong Kong. You go to Mexico City. That's true. You got
there's a lot of places in the world to go. I guess technically yeah, but I
don't think Mexico City has that that kind of New York swag. No, there's too
much swag here for a child to exactly. Yeah, that's why I also see that the
kids running around here. Uh-huh. The kids in New York are crazy. It's I think it's I
think I will definitely not have a kid in New York. No, I can't even imagine. There's
kids. There's a kid right now who is going into my wife's work over and over and over
again. He's like 16 years old and the owner was there one day and he was on his laptop
and this kid asked to use the laptop and he was like, no, I'm doing work. You can't use
my laptop. He's like, okay, I'm going to come back and I'm going to kill you. And so now
keeps coming in and being like where's the owner I'm going to kill him and
they're like he's not here. You got to go and he's like okay, I'll be back
tomorrow dude. I can't imagine he's like sixteen years old yeah. I know it's I
can't imagine raising a small child in New York. Everybody lets their their
their eight year old kid walk home from school yeah and it's like you yeah. You
would kids they call them yeah, but I bet the mom and dad are both home
and I bet that I bet they don't have a job at all and they're on there. They're
getting money from the government, probably to live here, probably
specifically to live here. Yeah, no, but I mean like you yeah, you would try it.
You would be trying to raise your kid right and you be trying to to be like
okay. This is the way I'm going to raise my kid or whatever, and then you they'd
be walking home from school and they'd come home and they they'd just know
about Rick and Morty. They'd have gone into a store on the way home and the guy
behind the counter taught them about Rick and Morty on their way home. Do you
never see like like large like especially in this in this neighborhood. There's
like large immigrant families that you're like why in God's fucking name
did you move to New York City? Yeah, why would you move to the most expensive
city in the country move to fucking move to Kansas? Yeah, if I was coming from
another country, there's no way I would move to New York. No, pay $2000 for rent
and have to like fucking it's not right to have a family here. No, it's wrong.
It's morally wrong, completely wrong. You have to you have to be yeah. It's
children should not have to have keys. Children should have their own country.
Do you agree kids should not have to have keys? Yeah, if you are under the
age of fifteen, you should not have to have a key to your house. It should be
it should be so it should be like a
driver's license moment when you get your key. Yeah, you should be like I
remember the first time I got my key to and I put my little thing on it and I
went. I got a key. Mine was a Red Sox key. Holy because that was I didn't even like
my Red Sox. That was the only option they had at the like Home Depot. That's
awesome. It was like yeah, you can have this. It was like it was literally you
can either have the Red Sox key or you can have this like pink fuzzy key. You
should have done the pink. Yeah, but I remember so I was like I got my key for
the front door. I got my key for the back door, which I would never ever use. Of
course, it goes through the basement. There's no reason to ever have it, and
and then I got like a third key for like it was literally like I wanted the key.
I was like I think the third key was literally like a closet or something
something that was never locked and I would never, but I was like I need
three keys on my key ring. You have to you just got to have a man because I
got a jingle yeah check it out yeah. I was wearing a key ring me to my keys
are getting my keys are blowing up. Yeah me too. I have way this this this
office was is a huge because there's two locks man or multiple locks. There's
too much. Yeah, look at all my keys man. Here's one that my mom here's a not a
key that my mom got me. That is a fake key. This is Caleb. That's not I have a
fake key on my key ring too. Oh, you do. Well, yours is a little cooler. Do you
know what this is from? What
my mom got me this for Christmas and it said I threw away the other part, but it
said it was key that said Caleb and then it was a little like piece of metal that
also was on a key ring that said the writer. Whoa, the writer. My mom got it
for me when I went to college. This is a promotional key, a plastic promotional
key for Disney's The Nutcracker and the Four Realms. That's beast man. I don't
even know what that is. Probably a musical, if I had to guess. Yeah, I think
it's a movie.
I think it's a fantasy movie, in fact. Do you want to go see a... Dude, this is
day two of my wife being out of town. Yeah. I realize in the last two years, I
don't think she has been out of town when I haven't also been out of town,
whether it was like just at the same time or we go somewhere together.
How I get one of those every once in a while, it's what do you do man literally
instant complete neat mode, just it like me too. It's the second she's gone only
just just the worst food I get take out. I'd make mac and cheese yesterday. I
ten hours of video games all day video games and movies. Yeah, I do I that's
what I'm doing. It's two to two to three days into her being gone. Text the group
chat. Does anyone want to do anything?
I want to go out tonight. Dude, how did these how did these
I can't? How do these lonely men in America deal with not having your love
around? It's insane. These guys are I mean how this is a worthless life to live
no I like with no love is shit a puppy dog. Yeah, I feel like why I have to take
takes care of a puppy. I feel like I feel like a dog who takes care. I feel
like some kind of mother dog. I really don't like it man. I literally instantly
within thirty six hours, every time I open my door, every time I open my door,
my entire house smells like farts yeah because I've just been farting in there
and there's nobody there to light a candle. The other thing I
I'm not I don't even try to do it, but within two hours the entire apartment is
trashed me to garbage. I don't even know what I do. There's areas that are
trash that I don't even remember touching yeah, and then I literally the
either the depending on what time she comes back the night before or the day
of I do it all. I clean everything. So this is probably every weekend when my
wife works like goes to work early in the morning and I don't have anything to
do and I have one day a week basically where I live like I'm living right now.
Yeah, the house is a fucking disaster in eight hours. It's crazy and then I
clean it. I put aside one hour before she gets home to stop watching movies and
playing video games on Sunday. This is clean the house. My this is my three
days in the middle of the week or like that.
What if she works from home Monday and Friday, so then Tuesday, Wednesday,
Thursday, I at least like I have a dog that goes crazy and he'll knock stuff
over, but I just won't touch it. What are you doing? How are you making the
house messy? I like it. I literally have no idea. Yeah, I think I just don't. I
just pick stuff up and then put it down in a weird place. There's socks in my
living room. I put socks everywhere in my house. I don't know where the fuck
these I don't remember that all the time. I think the dog might be taking my yeah,
maybe your dog is making Phil goes into the bedroom and takes when he wants
attention because he's not allowed in there. He'll take dirty clothes out of
the hamper yeah and he'll bring them into the living room. It'll just chew on
them till you notice yeah. I live. I have the most beautiful
my wife is at work neat life, because I have a I have a guy in my life that I
pay his. I pay his bills so that he can three days a week play eight hours.
And I don't get bored the day
yeah, I literally every day she's at work. I text him at eleven AM. I say
what a play I text him. I say day of play
and then we play for five hours. It's funny that you may have the same exact
relationship with you, but I don't like that he started splitting time with you,
because I had him first. Well, I hit it first. No, no, I hit it. He's with the
real man now. No, yeah, nope. He likes he actually likes that. I make him play
games that he doesn't even like at all.
That's actually what he likes. Now he likes someone who listens to his
problems and feelings and cares about him. I'm a good friend. I was worse
problems
because I'm a real man. Yeah, you're toxic. I'm not you're talking. You only
you're black and brown. I have more colors on today. I'm wearing my shirt.
You guys made fun of me for wearing that one time. Yeah, yeah, but she's with a
real man. Now a man who wears pink, so just black, brown and white, full pink
outfit on
doing that, but yeah, but only talk about the yeah, many words, pink and red
driving a Mary Kay escalade.
Yeah, she's a with a real man. Now a guy who cooks all his meals with an easy
bake of it. I was talking to people about it. He's a real Fisher price man. Did
have an easy bake oven growing up. No, I had a bug zapper. It made it had metal a
metal mould tray that made silicone bugs. Oh, I remember this and they were gummy.
No, you didn't eat them. I mean they were gummy in texture. I think there was
one that made gummies that you could eat to have around. They were like fishing
bait. They were silicone bugs. I mean,
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I had an Easy-Bake oven and I begged for it when I was a kid
and then my dad finally gave in and it came and it was,
they only made it a giant pink oven with flowers on it.
And yeah, my dad--
- Did you not have an oven in your house?
- No, we had a normal oven, but I wanted the Easy-Bake.
- What's the difference?
- Easy-Bake is like a, it's just a,
basically a really low powered air fryer.
- Okay.
- And it comes with like premade,
like mixes for like making brownies and stuff.
and my dad actually the like week after Christmas put me in football.
I like got the easy bake oven. I was making brownies. I was drawing hearts on
them with frosting and he was like, okay, well, you're going to be a football
player now. Yeah, I was fucking terrified of the oven and stove as a kid. I would
not touch it.
Why? Because it had fire and got hot. It does get a gas stove, but did you and it
scared me so bad. Just the just the I mean, truly if the click is scary, yeah,
the click of the I was going to say if it didn't have the click, I feel like I
would have had a comp I would have been have felt completely. I wasn't that
scared of the oven. I was scared of the stove. The stove is a little bit scary.
Yeah, you know what I always I hated those. I burned myself so many times
because my grandma had one of those stove tops, the glass ones that get
really hot.
I don't know can convection. Yeah, I think I know you're talking about yeah,
they're like black glass that turns into a big red ring yeah and every once in a
while she would cook something and then I'd walk in the kitchen. I'd be like
well, Nana, I'm really excited for this meal lean on it on it.
Just burn the shit out of myself. Yeah, my dad would also always tell me the
story that when he was a kid, his mom was like cooking something in a pot and he
was like, ooh smells good and he took the lid off the pot and leaned in to
smell it and all the steam went into his face and burned his entire face. So I
I think that also is like a pressure cooker. Yeah,
that's cool yeah. So I think that also scared me pretty bad yeah. I'm gonna have
to do cooking and stuff. I mean I already that's a thing. Oh, I do all the
girl. Yeah, you're the you're the girl of the house. I clean and I cook, but I
only cook, but I only do it when because she's right yeah, there's no exact yeah.
I mean
even if I was the guy, even if I was cooking at all the meals, I wouldn't be
doing that for myself. I feel like I would still be eating. Well, I'm not
gonna make like a chicken and rice and broccoli for myself. I'm gonna last night
chicken tenders. Yeah, that's when I had four beers. That's what it should be.
Yeah, wow beer and I was up till two thirty in the morning damn and I knew I
had to come in and record early. That's the worst going to bed figuring out
when to go to bed. Yeah, because I don't know. I don't have a bedtime anymore
because she has a bedtime. So I have a bedtime. Yeah, but if she's not here,
what the fuck am I doing going to sleep so early man? I have YouTube videos to
you watch making you sad, sad, thinking about being lonely.
You're not even alone. I know I'm thinking about times I've been lonely in
my life for
three days on it. I will say last night I was I was sitting on my computer yeah
and the clock struck midnight and my first thought was like I'm fifteen years
old. Oh yeah, because I was when I was fifteen years old. I'd sit there. I
played tribes ascend and I'd listen to
YouTube videos. I when I was sixteen, I would stay up till six AM. Yeah, I
didn't go to school about anything.
Just who cares I do. I was lying in. I was I was awake lying in bed on
Wikipedia on my phone nerd. Yeah, nerd man. Yeah, not even up playing video
games or doing it. I would just be
yeah, yeah, doing nothing. If I could do it all over again,
military, I've started going to bed much earlier than I used to like and in the
past
In the past two years, my bedtime is shifted by, I would say, about
four hours earlier. Backward, yeah, yeah. There was a while I was going to bed
at 9 30 and it was amazing. I was like this is amazing. I woke up at 6 30
every day. I went to the gym and then I went out of town one time and I
haven't done it since. When I lived in Boston, my bedtime was 2 AM every
night. I would stay up till 2 AM. That's a really funny bedtime. Yeah,
well, that was the time, yeah, that was the time when I was like, I was like,
okay. If the clock says 2 a.m. I need to get it as I would just and again I'll be
doing nothing. I'd be up watching TV. I tried taking a melatonin the other day,
which I don't take very often because you're bad for you. I stopped taking it.
They're really bad for you, but I took one the other day because I just
couldn't sleep at all and it completely ruined my next day. Yeah, that's I
cannot believe I used to take it all the time. I feel terrible, but I felt like I
felt I wish it would have been better for me to just stay up dude. The crazy
thing about melatonin is that the like maximum dose that you're supposed to
take is ten milligrams. Yeah, and they sell like fifteen. Yeah, that's what I
mean. They sell it in like twenty. Yeah, I take three milligrams. I take like I
take well, I don't take it anymore, but when I was taking it a bunch, I would
take well yeah, I mean I would take like twenty every night for a long time
because I didn't know. Yeah, well yeah, they just don't give a fuck about you.
No yeah, they will let you die. Well yeah, because it's like it's not it's
actually already in your body, so it's okay. I think cancer is already in your
my body. Yeah, I think everybody has cancer cells. Yeah, so it's poop. Yeah
shits in my body. I got piss. I have orange jizz sitting swirling around in
my body, but then yeah, I started cutting the pills in half. That's fun to have a
little routine to be like well, got to cut some more pills. I have my pills and
I only have one more half lip got to cut a bunch in half pill math man. I miss
that shit. Oh man yeah, but melatonin it ruins you yeah. It makes your testicles
not work to do yeah. I don't care so much about that.
I just don't like being tired yeah yeah yeah yeah all right, I'm going to go
take a shit yeah. Sounds good bye friends bye. We'll be back with the
we'll be back to normal soon. TV superstar sorry for everything yeah, but
scheduling crap and I'm sorry that I'm so lonely and if anybody
knows any people in New York yeah, I know a few. I think who like watching
TV who aren't Cameron because he's going out of town also. Yeah, I'm also leaving
oh my god. I'm gonna be fully alone. I'm gonna be fully alone for about three
hours. Fuck okay, before Patrick gets back to that. I'm so fucking alone man.
(laughs)