I
Get a clap this Patrick isn't here
Your fail blog moment was caught in 4k my friend was not even caught on camera
It was a bit caught you slipped and you fell I tripped I tripped over a cord because there's the cable management here
It leaves much to be desired
That is actually true as fuck.
Guys, we've solved the sinking issue.
We had it solved when you were gone.
We had the exact same solution.
And it was fine. We just rolled along.
We paid Jubio to play video games for an hour.
He needs to get a pay cut in his paycheck.
I agree.
I think we are going to, I think, maybe shave off
Just get rid of him.
shave off 33% of his income.
income. I asked him the other day, I was like, what are you going to do one day when you're
not the editor of our podcast or our medium sized podcast? And he said, I'm just going
to not think about that. I was like, that's probably a really good way to abuse your brain
and think about your life. Guys, it's our 200th. It's our 200th premium. But more than
that, I'm in the best mood of my life. I'm glad that we kind of set up. We had a little
arc setting up to the 200th premium where we're all different combinations of each other. And
We're all separate and lonely and now that we're all back together it kind of feels triumphant
and brand new.
It feels good.
We haven't been all three of us together in so fucking long, man.
It's been a minute.
Feels so good to be with you guys.
Especially because I just did a sold out show in Mansfield, Pennsylvania.
Oh yeah.
At Commonwealth University of Mansfield.
Guys, this was one of the best.
If you were thinking of doing stand up comedy, I recommend a great place to get started is
is the hut at the Commonwealth University at Mansfield. This is one of the greatest venues
I've ever been to in my life. Yeah, this was an amazing show and I remember I texted you
guys. I said there's only four people here. There's four people for freshman people just
came in because it's the first week of class and they don't know what to do with their
time. I thought it was a class, but then the classes must have got out or something because
here came on one more person who ran it, and so there was five people. It was five freshmen
and I was we were doing comedy for five people in a giant room. Yeah, and I was realizing
like oh, I remember stuff like this the my first week of college that I just will remember
forever. So these five kids basically high schoolers the rest of their lives. I'll be
like yeah with my first week of college. I saw a show. I was the only person in the audience
at a stand-up show that ball guy kept trying to do crowd work with me for 30 minutes straight.
Yeah, what if you do crap? Well, they're younger than me. So I asked him if they liked fortnight
and they clapped. I asked them if they like germ and one of them was like one
of them was like, Oh, yeah, the streamer
and I was like, yeah, yeah, the streamer guys.
Oh, no, it was really awesome and then so we thought what we thought that it
was five people who came by their own on their own volition and then afterwards
one of the guys was like, Hey, can I take a photo of you guys for the school
paper and we were like wait, did you just come because you got a school paper
assignment? He said yeah,
yeah, I really didn't want to come
Was he a fan, though? Did you make a fan out of him?
I think I made a fan out of all five of these people.
That's great.
I think this was --
Maybe they're listening right now.
Maybe they found you. They found the Patreon. They went up.
Immediately subscribed.
Immediately subscribed. I need to see more of this guy.
I mean, they loved me.
I've consumed all 300 episodes of the free stuff in this past week.
Yeah.
I need in. Let me in.
Neil did say something crazy after the show.
Yeah.
He said to me, he said, "You had a really good set."
that.
What are you talking about, man? Yeah, there was it was just me. It was a
dinner party. Yeah. Did you guys have dinner together? We tried to. We tried to
go to Lambs Creek, the
restaurant across from the hotel. Where I've never- I wish Julio was here just
to show us what- It's near Scranton. You don't know Lambs Creek? Okay. Lambs
Creek is a restaurant across from the Quentin Inn in Mansfield, Pennsylvania,
And we got a reverse recommendation because the guy said that Hannibal Buress went there
and he really didn't like the chicken wings. And apparently he did some whole rant about
the chicken wings.
Oh, it's famous.
Lamb's Creek, some famous rant.
They have a printout of the standup shot on the wall.
Yes, yeah. Right there at Lamb's Creek. And so we went over to Lamb's Creek and we were
like, well, let's have a delicious meal at Lamb's Creek and maybe some funny chicken
wings. Guys, Lamb's Creek closes at 8 p.m.
Jesus. Yep. Lamb this whole city shuts down. We ended up going to a sheets.
Jesus Christ. And apparently in Pennsylvania, they have a problem with
drinking in Pennsylvania. So you can only buy one. You know, only by one six
pack of beer at a time. But me and Neil wanted two different kinds of beers. So
I bought one and the guy said, these got to be in separate transactions. And I
was like, what? Okay, so I just walked back in with the I left one six pack
there and walked back in line with the other six pack. And I get the friends
he's like, "Listen, you have to take the beer out of the store. It's not my rule.
It's some fucking gay law." I was like, "What?" He's like, "Yeah, it's just gay
ass law they passed."
I'm like, "Pennsylvania's awesome, man." Yeah, dude. I was in Pittsburgh, and
there was... Pittsburgh is sick. I love Pittsburgh. We stopped in, I think it
was on the way there, we stopped and I think it was called Hamburger. It was
either Hamburger or Harrisburg. There was a burg in it. There's a Harrisburg,
for that. It was not Harrisburg. He knew it wasn't hamburger. No, no, no, no,
making this up. It was not
let me guess. It was next to hot dog. It was not. It was not Harrisburg.
Harrisburg is close in a bun to I was in bun
Philadelphia. I was in lettuce, PA doing a show. I'm pretty sure it was
Hamburg. So you stopped in there. There's a gas station, their gas station,
some of them, this gas station, full slot machines in the back. Yeah, every
developed state has slot machines and gas stations, except for this fucking, these bumfuck northern
states. These bumfuck northern states don't have gas stations. Like New York City doesn't
have any gas stations. I've never seen a gas station in New York City. I've never seen
one. Guys, we have in the south, everybody has their favorite gas station. For me, it's
kangaroo now called that's an animal.
Nope.
No, no, no.
It's called kangaroo.
It's a gas station.
I also like love love gas station just because that's an
amazing name.
Sheets is way up there.
Sheets is good.
Sheets is just wah-wah, but it doesn't have the reverse
feng shui that Cameron doesn't like about wah-wah.
Well, it's well, you know, there's a novelty to being able
to go into a place that with a name that everyone talks about
but yeah, you don't want to be stressed while you do it.
and it's called Wawa. Talking about Wawa? Yeah. Yeah, Wawa does have something
really, really wrong with it. And it's called Wawa. Yeah, I think my favorite
gas station is probably Shell.
Shell is good.
Shell has... There's not much food in there. The thing that I do... No, that's
why I like it. The thing that sucks... I like the gas. The hungry type.
The gas is maybe a better price. Yeah. The thing that sucks about living in
New York City is we don't get those combination... Like gas station...
combination the gas stations aren't restaurants here like they are down
south. We have more restaurants yeah, but I would trade. I would trade any
fuck
anyone, but okay, fucking bodega, the New York boat is the gas stations are
going to get in the south.
Yeah, the gas station for a human because you need food fooled yeah, but
you don't they don't have the soda machines in the bodega. They don't have
like the frost because they have them on tap yeah, man. I want soda on tap
and every bodega
I want the big gulp machines. Every single 7-Eleven in New York is in
like Manhattan or something. Actually there's one a little bit down the road.
I should start going there more. I was in Boston and I went to Salisbury Beach
and a man died. Wait what? You didn't tell us about this. This is like him
getting hit by a car and he didn't tell me. Who died? Some man. I wasn't hit by a
car. I was hit by an Uber Eats driver. So we're pulling up to the beach and
and it's pretty it's a hot day Labor Day weekend. You know, it's where like oh, it's going to
be packed. Yeah, we're pulling up. There's no traffic pulling into the beach, but going
out its bumper to bumper for like a mile and we're going what the heck do they close the
beach we get there the beach isn't closed. We go in and we're about to swim in the water
and the lifeguard comes over and blows her whistle at us. You can't go in the water.
Yes, the waves are too big. The waves are pretty big. He died from a wave. So we go
back up to the beach. We're sitting around for a while. Then this other lifeguard, you
you know, they drive their cars across the beach. Sometimes, yes, the prime
lifeguards, they're so smug bosses. They go across the beach in the car. He pulls
over in the car.
My mom goes over to talk to him. We'll be like, what's going on? And she's
talking to him. She's like, why aren't you letting people in the water? And
he's like, yeah, we had a pretty serious incident actually just very recently. A
man went into the water and he went under a wave and his heart stopped. Oh,
don't blame the man and then he said, and then he went like this. Oh, I
shouldn't have told you that. Whoa. And you got told this by an elite lifeguard?
Yeah, one of the car lifeguards. One of the elites. You know, he was feeling
left out that he couldn't blow the whistle like everyone else was. He probably
feels bad that it was his fault. He didn't get to blow the whistle, so he's
just going around just for the attention. Yeah, they didn't save the guy.
For the attention. He was just going up to people like, "Yeah, no, apparently
one of these waves killed this..." Yeah. Oh, no. Apparently some vaccinated man
went into the ocean and immediately had a heart attack and died. Yeah, it's
it's funny to be driving up to a beach and see a big crowd of people be like,
oh man, they must have closed in front of everybody in that line. So somebody
die
yeah, you guys ever seen somebody die right in front of you, watch the life,
leave their face. No, I thought I did a couple of times, but I think they were
alive. I mean, I thought I thought I did a homeless guy sleep dead. Yeah, I've
seen so I've seen some guys around New York who are asleep with their head on
a rock as a pillow. Yeah, and I think that guy has to be dead, but I come back
thing he's gone. He's just a got cleaned up or he
talked to got clean. He's a sin. I was New York is full of these cynics
walking around cynics. I don't care. I would say they're imagineers. They're
kind of one of the Disney type, but they're having a big imagine. They're
imagining pillows that they're like. Oh, let me let me roll over in my big
puffy bed. There is a guy bed. The four posters of my bed are these four
skyscrapers. Have you seen the four billboards of times square? The biggest
bed in the world. Have you seen my room is the world? Have you seen the guy
who's the old guy who sometimes he's out here in a hospital gown? Yes, and he
just babbles to himself all day. Yes, he just goes like he I saw him getting an
arm hangs out around my house, the air the other day over there in Ridgewood.
He was going to air of Ridgewood, the air is the air in Ridgewood. You should be
careful. It's very rude
and he speaks simlish is his first language and he's like screaming and
doing karate at the air and stuff, and I walk by these people and I say I like
living here. Yeah, this is a good thing to have. It gives me a sense of
perspective on
on my magic in the world. Yeah, well, this guy's right. There's so much magic
in the world, and some people have
have had a curse befall upon them. Yeah, some people have been bewitched. This
guy was actually bewitched. This guy is bewitched. His tongue. I think he was a
doctor. You think he was a doctor because he wears scrubs sometimes?
I think he gets taken to the hospital and then leaves. When I first saw him, I thought,
"Oh, he's pretending to be a doctor." I thought he was walking around the neighborhood
pretending to be a doctor. Buddy, you are as sharp as any tool in the shed. When I see
people in scrubs and they're on the train going to or from work, I'm like, "Get a fucking
hold of yourself and change when you get to work and change before you leave work." I
I don't give a fuck, man.
Oh, you want me to put, what am I supposed to put a blue, a purple heart on your lapel?
You mop up brain juice from the ground?
The people who wear the scrubs.
You wouldn't be wearing scrubs if you were a doctor.
If you wear the scrubs on the train,
if you wear scrubs on the train, guess what?
I'm going to scrub you.
Yeah, they're going to have to scrub me off of you.
I'm going to be on you like germs.
They're going to have to scrub my brains off of you,
because I'm going to blow my head off in your direction and ruin your day.
the reason they call them scrubs. Yeah, because scrubs wear them that oh that's
right. Yeah, they call them grunts yeah, and that's why they call them lab goats
yeah, because only the goats wear them. So yeah, two or three scrubs. I mean
there's J D and Turk. I think they're heard to me that's turd and turd and D
D D do
and smelly it
and a janitor yeah and and
fartla. My doctor did another bad thing. Your doctor did another doctor did
another bad thing. I need to know tell me about this bad. I got an email that
says you you have an appointment for a new test.
I didn't make this appointment. God yeah, I never was told about I don't
even know what it's for. It was a it's a heart test. I don't need a heart test.
I'm tickers fine. I'm seventeen years old. Yeah, I have a I have a healthy
heart rate and low blood pressure. Yep, very low blood pressure and a very low
heart rate. I don't need a stress test. I get this email that says you've been
struggling stress, scheduled for a stress test. I messaged my doctor on my
chart. I say what the hell is this? Well, I don't what the hell is this all,
but said what I was pretty rude. I was like excuse me. I did not make this
appointment. I was never told about it. Please explain what this is and why I
need it, and she said there's a stress test and it's scheduled for this day and
this time. You know you don't have to go. I know I cancelled it, but I just it
pissed me off man. You don't have to charge me a bunch of money for not
showing up to yeah. It's so fucked yeah. Why would you schedule me and then
don't even explain what it is yeah. I got a message from my dentist that said
the headline was use it or lose it. You got a newspaper from your headline. It
was our subject. I mean and the headline the headline of the thing they're
interchangeable. It doesn't make any difference. Use it or lose it.
And then it said that I had a coupon from them. And then I realized,
like, "Oh, yeah, that's why they wanted to put a fucking crown and do a
root canal so quick."
These doctors, they're thinking about money every second of their life.
Dentists actually do. Dentists and doctors. Well, doctors too.
Someone will tell you, someone who's in your life who lives with you will
tell you something. When you're complaining about your doctor giving you
test for no reason. Some random person who lives with you, who you spend your
life with, will tell you things like, "The doctor doesn't think about money. It's
not their responsibility. You have to ask them about the money." This is what?
No, the doctor's trying to drain my wallet. The doctor literally only cares
about the money. My weird insurance is listed in the doctor's system as no
insurance, and the insurance pays for it, most of it. I still have to pay a lot
of money when I do this stuff, but I know the doctor's going into my file and
pulling up and see, "Oh, here's someone with no insurance. Let me schedule them
a test on a day that they can't do, well, that they could do, but they are saying
that they can't do to suspect the doctor. I need you to be listen.
You're popping off on doctors. I need you to turn it up to eleven. These
doctors, these doctors are not getting it hard enough for me and my friend
stand it man. I really you could treat this. You could treat this episode and
every other episode. I've talked about my doctor as evidence in court yeah in
the future, and you know what they would probably that's a hard. I'm going to go
there. I'm going to use it as evidence because you're going to kill you. I've
been thinking about this shit with your and I've been I've been listen. I've
I'm fighting back against my doctor in the only ways I know how which are
skewering, cancelling appointments, skewering on my podcast,
being slightly rude in the exam room, yeah,
not giving her my vaccine records for months and months, no and saying I have
them somewhere. I have to find them and she says okay, you need to bring those
and I say okay, I'll bring them next time, not and then I don't even look for
no no who cares where these are. No, these doctors need to be in prison, but
yes, here's how sneaky these doctors are. They know legal loopholes, because what
do doctors, what are all of if you if there's a group of people and half of
them are doctors, what are the other half patients very close crap pieces
very well, yes, receptionist, lawyers, oh shit guys, there is nobody worse than
lawyers, lawyers and blondes are at the very, very bottom of my pyramid. Yep,
he's not really blonde, he's got like a dirty blonde. I'm not blonde at all.
he's got you guys only think I'm blonde because I was M and M in my life when
you
yeah, you're not blind even a little bit. I'm not even close to
hair. You guys always
I think of you as a beautiful blonde. I think of beautiful blonde with my
eyebrow was turning blonde. Yeah, that you should go to the doctor. I got it
late in life. All right, here's here's my problem with lawyers. Okay, what
I go man. Oh, you might actually have been I might actually have late in
life. What happens late in life, end of life, you might have your adult onset.
I googled blondness and eyebrow and there's no results. I'm telling you
ocean. Yeah, I'm not going to get a blonde splotches on my skin. I don't
want to be blonde skinned. Yeah, you have blonde. Vito Lago would not show
up on your body. Not yours. You have whiteness. No, no, you I don't think
you have to let go at all. Now that I'm thinking about it, the thing with
lawyers. Okay, is that they have invented... Have you been dealing with
one lately? What's going on? No, no, maybe I should. I thought you were
going to. Yeah, I know. For our war. For our trash war. Oh, right, yeah.
Guys, if you know of a lawyer who works completely free... Trash law. To
help in trash law,
let me know.
Because we have a trash lawsuit on our hands. We have a huge trash law
problem. It's gonna be... It's gonna go to the Supreme Court. Have they been
calling you? No, they said they were gonna talk to me and they never called
me. There's so much that has happened in the past couple of weeks that we
have not been together to talk about. I know it's very upsetting. It is very crazy. But
here's a lobster roll. And it was expensive I bet, market price. Yeah, I bet it was close
to $24. My mom's treat. Whoa! Apparently. Mother's treat. Mother's treat. Mother's treat-treat-sa.
Wow! Oh my God. Lobster roll, mother's treat. Mother-treat-sa. Okay. Mother treats. Mother
treats. Mother is treats ya. Mother treats ya. Poorly. Mother treats ya. That was easy.
treats a kid poorly does not buy him any. Is it true that Mother Teresa is very
swordly? Is it true that Mother Teresa took all the blood out of people? Yes.
And made them eat their own shit? She would make people see she thought she
was a scientist towards the ends of her life. Is it true that she did
experiments on twins? Yes. She would pray experiments? The experiments would be
though she would pray for one of the kids. Did you guys have a lot of...
Here's a question I have. Do you guys, this is something I was talking about
about with my family while I was home. Did you guys have a bunch of twins in
your school? Yeah. How many? I had like... Probably around five.
Two pairs. Yeah, 'cause I feel like we had an abnormally high... Is that
normal to have five pairs of twins? We had triplets and twins. That's hella...
How many? Triplets? There were one group of triplets and then probably...
And then I think four to five to six groups of twins. Yeah, there was...
And by groups, I mean pairs. Yeah, that's around the same
as my school, so maybe... I don't know, yeah, but...
(burp)
Excuse me?
So I'm just curious of everyone how many twins they knew growing up.
Put a twins counter in the comments.
I knew one pair, Heather and Hunter.
And they were two blonde bombshells who loved surfing.
I wish I could tell you about the funny ass twins that went to my school without...
Completely doxing them?
Yeah, because the funny thing about them is their first and last names.
They were called...
Thing 1 and Thing 2, guys.
I swear to God.
Wow, well, the why would you name your first name, but different last names
that is really fucking scary. I told you guys about it. There's two two separate
students in my high school who were both named Seamus Rio. Whoa, really and in the
in the year book, they had to Rio Rio Rio, and they had to differentiate them by
their middle. They were French and Irish, Irish from and they weren't related at
No, not even people would ask them.
But did they look like twins?
No, they didn't look alike at all. One of them was like really small.
That size has no impact on look.
And then in the facial area they were completely different.
But why would they be twins if they had the same first name?
Wasn't that show that was about little people called My Little Life or whatever?
Little People Big World.
Wasn't there a set of twins where one of them was a giant football player and one of them was a small one?
yes, that twins can be anything different. They don't even have to be
related. It's called fraternal. Yeah, there can be even be for parents if
they're close.
If you're close enough friends and you have a half brother,
there's a kid that I just convinced myself was my cousin that I was good
friends with and I because he said that he had an aunt in Florida and I said,
"I have an aunt in Florida," and we decided it was the same aunt.
I never believed when kids at school said that they were cousins. Yeah.
My cousin... I was like, "You guys are fucking lying. You just have the
same last name. I grew up next to both of my cousins and my cousin was like, my cousin
who is now a police officer was a star football player and then my other cousin, my cousin
Rob was, my cousin Robby is 6 foot 5, my cousin Tim is 6 foot 8 and no one believed that we
were related at all. I bet the police cousin has a problem with this guy, his name is Rob.
actually fucked up. Yeah, one guy named cop and one named Rob way. Yeah, two guys
said they were cousins and then someone's like, you know, they're not
actually cousins. I think people would say that
people would be like, I don't believe that gossip about people would gossip
about the same last name, though. These two guys, we did last night. We didn't
have the same. Are these guys handsome to who? My cousin? Yeah, I mean, they're
my cousins. I'm not going to talk bad about them. So they're ugly. So they're
They're not heads, they're weird.
They're fucking ugly.
I can't believe you opened with I'm not going to talk bad about them.
You just said they're tall.
You said they're ugly tall guys.
You said their names.
He called them troll ogre cyclopses.
They're hulking over me and it scares me.
The Hulk is not known for his good looks.
One for me is a nerd and one for me is a giant monster.
He's the wrong color.
Why am I talking shit about my cousin's looks?
I don't know.
I thought that would be funny and it wasn't.
But yeah, I've never seen these guys. I never will.
I think you have.
I'm going to see them.
I've never seen these fools.
I'm seeing them this weekend.
You've never met them. You could meet them. I don't think I've met you.
I'm working on meeting them.
Guys, I learned... Okay. So back to law. I learned about something called a plea deal.
Do you know about plea deals?
Yes.
It's what we're asked to be free.
How is this a part of our legal system? A plea deal?
Wait, what is it?
A plea deal is...
Explain it.
Watching the Tory Lanez case, is that what this is?
I just saw a news story about that. Yeah. And I was like, "Wait, this plea deal shit
it makes no sense. Say you murder somebody and they're like can I go?
Well, it's literally you're like you're like yeah, I murder or they're like you
murdered this person and you say no and they say okay life in prison, but if you
murder them and they say you murder this person, you go yep. I murdered him. They
go fifteen years, fifteen years, and then you can say please can I have
you're being honest actually, please yeah. Why is honesty? Why is the best
policy half of a
I already answered right there. Honesty is the best policy and our
country's policies are all the best.
I don't understand why this makes any sense at all.
I think we kind of need to tear down the whole legal system and
rebuild it from the ground up.
Or at least get rid of this plea deal shit, man.
Yeah, maybe we just get rid of that actually.
And there's no way you're saving so much money on like the court
case or whatever that it's like somehow squaring out.
I mean, I think we can cut the jury. Twelve people.
one guy. One guy. Yeah, because if you think about how many people are
getting jury duty, they're getting live, their lives ruined. They have to
take time off work, which they like doing. They can't go to see this
stand up show, which is probably why your show was so poorly attended.
Those kids probably all... Everyone turned 18 and had to go to jury duty.
I got a jury duty notice when I turned 18, basically, right after.
Did you go? No, I completely ignored it. I didn't even go. And I went
in there, it was
a case about a child being molested.
So how did you get out of it? They didn't let me.
just one look at you. They let me you
you
said, sorry, wait, no, I was waiting there all day. They come out. They say
Cameron Fetter go home. You walked in and they were the
start for two weeks.
No, they just had I said
you were the
listen. I'll tell you and I listen. Maybe this is related. Maybe I'm going
to be completely honest with you right now. I was sitting there six hours
waiting all day for them to see me like a so I could plead my case or plead my
case to be that on the jury. You wanted to be on the door to put this piece of
shit away. It sounds like you got quitted for child molestation. The way
you're telling this, I got acquitted. I wouldn't be dancing around it. I'd be
proud. You'd be very proud.
That's a good point sitting there all day and that court courthouse and I was
sticking it to them. Yeah, you know how oh yeah, I was head. I had open. I got
my phone out. I got his phone out and he he you know I have my ear buds in it was
like I beer, but it was
the camera has called
ear buds in and he comes out of it.
From the
comes out
chopo trap house wow. So they said we ordered episode. Oh, they said this
left the weight out of here. I was probably the episode in advance. That's
smart listen to it all at the
courthouse. I was going to say
you downloaded that episode on
the Wi-Fi and immediately they
were like, okay, we've said
we've detected a download.
That's what I'm saying. They
were looking over my shoulder.
They said this guy knows all
the tricks. This guy thinks
he's going to run circles
around. This is he's he's too
big of a genius to be in this
jury. He's going to outsmart
everybody. The whole case.
This guy's so genius he thinks
the CIA is bad. No, I really I
did get to jury duty and I was
so like, okay, this could be
inter, like, you know, it's not
like I'm doing anything with my
time right now. It'll be fun to be on a case and see how this works and
whatever, and I get into you know like oh yeah, it's a part of the jury. Wow
I'm a child, I'm barely an adult.
It's a brave new world and I get in there and it's a guy sitting there and
they're like so this case is this guy had molested a child. It's like oh yeah,
I want to go home yeah. I don't really want to be here anymore. Yeah, you
just started crying. You dress you dress. I just remember just being
completely like wow, this is crazy. I'm really here. This is so weird. Oh,
it's actually crime is actually
does not pay. I'm completely racist. Excuse me from I think that then I
think that actually works. I think yeah, we'll do that all the time. I was
gonna do that. I was gonna do the thing because I at that point I didn't. I was
gonna say like yeah, he's I can't abide a child molester and he's completely
guilty in my eyes, even without the fact yeah, have you? I feel I would not
listen to any single. What I would say I would say yeah, honestly, I already made
my mind up if you yeah. If you want to get out of jury duty, there's a million
ways you can do that. It's everyone always has with racist, but what if you
go the opposite way? How do you get? How do you? I can't wait to learn the fact
maybe dress up like Sherlock Holmes. Yeah, you're like yeah, you say I know
the whole point is you're not supposed to even be able to think about if you
could be guilty or innocent before the trial begins. So you don't want to be
Sherlock Holmes because they'll be like this guy already knows, but if you're
finding clues, well, that's you're not supposed to get out of it. They don't
want you to find clues. Why they don't want to see my literally why they want
you to be a blob who looks at who follows along with the lawyer and thinks,
oh, I like this lawyer. I like this lawyer, yeah, so it's a way that our
system works is it's literally the olympics. It is the olympics for lawyers
and was to hold on. Yes or no on your little card. Yes, he molested the kid.
No, the kid's lying. No, this four year old's lying. Yeah, yeah, four year old
he's learned about lying in Bible school. He said I'm going to do that to a very
I'm going to mail man. He said I want to sin yeah yeah this is I'm going to sin
against this weird looking strange fifty year old man with long limbs next to me
yep. I'm going to I remember exactly how this guy looked yeah. I mean you don't
forget a face like no, I don't I never forget a child.
Just in case, well, except for this, did you see this guy? No yeah, I remember
his face. I remember exactly what he looks like. He looked like this like
he was kind of like this. Oh, he was kind of an ass. He was ry. He had a ry smile,
yeah he was he was also laughing, but not
that's the worst yeah, but everyone always goes in to try and get out of jury
duty to be they're like oh, I should I should be racist. I should you know that
I think that'll get me out immediately, buddy, you got to try the exact opposite.
You got to say I love every single race and every single person unequivocally,
and I would not be able to find any single person guilty because I don't
think
I think we're just all one consciousness. Yeah. Do you think you could get out of
jury duty, but you know how they do like have you ever seen this person before?
Do you know this person? Can you be like, oh, this is crazy, but I actually
dreamed about this guy last night. Oh, that's Chris for my dream. Oh my God,
I dreamed about this guy in my dream. He killed me and his name was Chris.
I guess he can. His name is Brian. That's what you just say that you just say
yeah, that's that guy molested me. Yeah, yeah, and then you're there like,
well, that's but then that's the problem, because you know you see what
if it's not in real life and it's a case. Oh yeah, that fucking
well, that sets up a whole not trial speeding to molest me.
He was really late to the point. You have to be careful as you say,
you say molested you, they're going to start a whole nother court case that
you're going to have to be there the whole time, whether you're on the jury
or not. So what you have to say is actually I do know this guy. He
molested me and I don't want to press charges. He molested me and I didn't
care. Yeah, it didn't bother me. I didn't care. It changed my taste in
music. That's basically the only thing that it affected me. I like certain
type of movies now and I was weird characters. Also, I was eighteen yep,
so fully eighteen. It wasn't crazy enough to change my whole psyche and it
was really just we actually know I am crazy because of it. I'm crazy, sir.
I'm crazy. I'm sorry I can't do the job. I'm completely crazy. Oh yeah, I
guess that's what I do. Are you fit any reason you're not
fit to serve on the jury be like jury. This is McDonald's
McDonald's right now. Or they say, "Are you fit to serve on the jury?" You say, "Yeah,
circles a shape." And they say, "What?" And you say, "You said fit." "Yeah, I'm in shape.
Circles a shape." And then maybe they'd go... And I run marathons on Netflix. Do you want
to do warm-up for the jury? You go, "Yeah." And then you have a great job. Oh, yeah. You
just do a warm-up comic. You go out, you do warm-up, you're throwing out gift bags and
the jury. They call you so there's the bailiff and then there's also the
goody bag man. Yeah, that's
those are the two people in
first jury. Is this people go? Yeah,
oh my God. All right, so this man is a complete
bad person. Yeah,
I'm just kidding. I'm not allowed to say that shit. I can't say that you
doesn't have to be your chair. It's handcuffs. Yeah, you get to arrest him
yourself. You get to arrest. I don't want to be a police officer, but I would love
to arrest somebody. I'm going to be honest. Yeah, you can citizens arrest,
but I don't think that works. No, you can just walk away from a citizen's arrest.
Yeah, just say, well, that's why you get down on them.
Go down, get down on them. Just get a boogie down on these four.
Yeah, I'm not boogie and down.
There is no crime on earth that is heinous enough to warrant me boogieing down.
No, no, no.
Nobody wants to see my cracker ass dance.
Oh yeah, I'm doing the two step.
Maybe they'll use your dancing in Guantanamo Bay.
Yeah, I would get a kill for that.
They would show all these terrorist guys your dancing and they would confess to not living
in shit.
recently learned about this Abu Grabe situation. Guys, this was some bad news, guys.
Why?
They basically did unconsensual jackass to 50 guys who were just driver taxis.
They dressed guys up as scary things.
Yeah, they said, "Let's do a haunted house and let's scare ourselves."
So they made everybody dress up like a scarecrow.
are so crazy. Those photos of that woman who's got her thumb up next to a guy and he's got
jumper cables on his nutsack or something.
It honestly just makes you think if that's how a woman is reacting to that stuff, how
are the men?
Because men keep their emotions in.
Yeah, or even they like stuff like that more than women.
Oh yeah, true.
So they probably are smiling even more.
Yeah, you wouldn't even be able to fit the smiles in a photo.
The Smilers of Abu Ghraib. Yeah, it's actually really scary. It's the lady who
did the thumbs up. She there was like a letter that she sent her friend where
she was like, I basically don't even know why I'm doing all this crap. It's
actually really disgusting having to electric shock people's poop and then
she just kept doing it. Apparently, she didn't even know where she was and she
thought she was watching TV. Yeah, that's what I heard. Oh, that's actually a
pretty good excuse when you're on some kind of high, high trial. Listen,
they've tried all the defense they did were just following orders. It didn't
work. You still get in trouble. So you were say you thought you were watching
tv. We were making tv. We are making a pilot for mtv speaking of a true bass. I
thought we were doing a jury duty kind of thing and we these guys they didn't
know but they were about to become famous. Every single person in this room
has been is a trained actor except for the victims and james marzian comes
through and starts putting clamps on people's balls.
He's killing them.
And they're like, they don't even know who this guy is, they're from a different country,
they never saw Enchanted.
Well, they maybe have seen Sonic.
Maybe they saw Sonic.
I think good chance they've seen Sonic.
It's possible they saw Sonic with a watermark.
I wish that they took firing squads and they kept them and they kept that as the main way
of killing people in America, but they automated it.
And there was robots that did it.
Speaking of automated...
A wall of pure bullet.
I'm thinking of like the robots from Robocop
that aren't Robocop.
Like those things come out.
Speaking of automated, I learned this recently.
All the news channels,
all the news stations,
automated TV cameras.
You already told me this.
Why didn't you tell him? I'm telling him.
He listens to every episode.
I didn't listen to it, but I don't want to hear about the news from you.
Ok, then do you want to hear...
you want to okay. Did you I was in the newspaper as a kid, anyway, when for
what two days before I went on the news? No, you that's good. You weren't in the
newspaper.
That is not fucking. I said kid gets the most delicious cake ever on his. That
was the headline. That's pretty cool. July 4th, 19, September 11, 2001
kid gets most amazing birthday cake
for having
make a story. Wait, a little boy just had the most amazing birthday party and the cake had
three layers. Spider-Man showed up and they drew his photo on the cake. There was a man
who got his face painted as a tiger. This is a developing story coming in right now.
The cake from Cameron's 11th birthday party turns out to be an ice cream cake. That's
right. Wow. Fudgy the Whale made an appearance. I never had a Fudgy the Whale until recently.
we didn't have carvel down in North Carolina. We didn't have cold stone
creamery. We also had a very clean and these cold stone cakes, guys. I don't
give a fuck about that cake. I like those little cones with the chocolate
that are on top of the cake. That's the and the icing. Did you hear
mix ins? Did you hear dairy queen has completely? I like the mix ins do.
That's the only thing. Queen has completely
by the mix and very clean, remove the ice cream
cherry dip cone. Well, honestly, if they did do that recently, it didn't hurt them
at all because I saw a line around the block for a DQ when I was in really
really. Yeah, I thought I was a very Queen grill and chill so much. There's
DQs north. I wasn't in Boston. I thought Boston was a was or
Massachusetts. I know it's Baskin Robbins. No, that was really yeah. Baskin
Robbins was fairly recent. That was but I remember because growing up, it was
I remember when all the Dunkin Donuts turned into a combination of Baskin Robbins.
They have DQ and Stoneham and Amesbury and Haverhill.
Hudson, New Hampshire, Dairy Queen, Grill & Chill.
They made some really good chicken tenders with the white gravy and the toast on the
side.
The Grill & Chill is underrated.
I guess I just never went to an ice cream chain as a kid.
I just went to all the local stores.
I didn't go to DQ as a kid.
They didn't have a DQ near me. They were all more far away.
Did you ever go to Moo's in Derry, New Hampshire?
No.
Oh, that was a huge...
Did you ever go to Lizzie's in Harvard Square?
Yes, I did.
Did you guys ever go to Coles Custard in Wilmington, North Carolina?
No.
Where a man found a finger in his ice cream?
No, I didn't go there.
Found a finger?
We grew up near each other, though, so these actually make sense.
Mine made sense.
They found a finger in a man's armpit at the arcade and he was being tickled.
during laser tag during laser tag. You remember we went to jungle rapids. We
played laser tag. Yeah, I was just talking about that the to someone the
other day. I don't remember who, but that was you know. I think that's the
second time I've ever played laser tag in my life. Really was just the three of
us and we are what I was trying to remember is that we had was it just the
three of us. It was pierced there. It was just us three of us and it was we
each got code names and it was like the destroyer, the demolisher and then like
was the princess or some yeah. I was like or like the I think I got the
weakest one yeah. You did get a weak. I'm pretty sure it was the wizard or
something later versus the with yeah. I clapped you all up man. You did I
clapped you, but I was I knew the map completely was cheating. He was spawn
camping. I had mass knowledge. He spawned camp. I'm not going to run
around. I'm going to follow you until the the cool off. It was that makes it
we wasted money. It wasn't not wasted. Our money had way less fun. We
went in there twice. There was fog. Yeah, but when you're getting
followed by your friend to home base, it was like buddy, ask any woman
that lives in a major city. It's no fun to be followed. Yep, and if
you think differently, if you think differently, the feminists would
like to have a word with you. Well, I wouldn't like to have a
word with the feminist. I'll tell you that much. I'll have a word
with them. Shut up.
(laughter)
That's good.
S-A-D-D-A-P.
Shut up.
That's, to all the feminazis out there, shut up.
To all the feminazis, I've got a Billy Madison impression I want to do for you.
(laughter)
I want to go, "Shut up!"
Yep, so bad.
I have a couple of Cartman words that I could say to you.
Respect my authority.
I'm going to do that to you.
I'm going to do respect my authority.
Check this one out.
What?
You are the weakest link.
(laughter)
That would work really well against a feminist.
that would be really funny, maybe some Monty Python stuff. It's not really
applicable, but
it's a silly ideology. We won't believe it. So they start saying just a
flesh wound. They start saying something to you. And now for something completely
different. I was just going to say they're trying to tell you something
about the patriarchal, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah. That's why they don't shave
their freaking armpits and shave their hair blue. Yeah, they shave their hair
and it turns blue. They use blue shavers. I've seen this. They use blue shavers,
and then you look at them. You look towards the camera that you've invented
in your head and you say and now for something completely different.
And feminists, they chew too much gum.
They chew a lot of tobacco.
And they blow in bubbles with their gum.
Stop, man.
I'm sick of going to these parties where a feminist is there and I go to pick up
my drink and I take one sip, dip spit in it immediately.
Oh, my God.
It's so disgusting.
These feminists need to stop chewing Cope snuff.
They always want to go to the mall.
They're always wearing these 12 inch pumps, walking around with a little handbag
and a tiny purple dress.
shut the hell up. You're being annoying and you're chewing tobacco. Yeah, leave
your car at home. You don't need to drive everywhere. Yeah, these gas goes
your guzzling. I'm sick of them guzzling up all this fucking gas with their
diesel powered cars, Subaru's that they're driving around. These fucking
fema Nazis are driving around. They're rolling coal. They're chewing tobacco
and catalytic converters there for a reason. And how come they always live
either on the east coast or the west coast or in the middle of the country
or another country or the Midwest. Yeah, the middle of the country. Yeah, that's
completely and the Midwest and then the southeast Mexico. I was getting so mad
earlier driving back from Pennsylvania. Five hour drive. I did today because we
hit traffic and I was just looking around feminist, feminist, feminist,
these giant semi trucks, there was completely destroying the environment.
Hey, feminists enough with the freon in your trucks. Drop them. I don't care
that you need to keep the produce cold and get that freon at the fucking truck.
We don't need the crystal meth. Keep it cold with ice. You don't have to stay up so that you can read Gloria Steinem.
And the hypocrisy of these feminazis where they go to these lots and they look for their little lizards.
Yeah. Yeah. Just get a normal pet. Get a dog. Why are you so obsessed with those lizards?
Why are you so obsessed with these lizards? It doesn't make any sense. It makes no goddamn sense.
When I was in Boston, we went to... Have you been on the USS Constitution? That old ship?
Oh, yeah. The like Navy Yard? Yeah, yeah. I just shipped my pants.
No, you didn't. Target. No. Target ad that I watched eight years ago. Oh, okay. And we
were in this guy who's giving us a tour and he's like a Navy guy in the uniform. And it's
like a, he was, he was not a Navy SEAL. I'm blue, dab it, come on. Yeah, so it's all like
a, it's an old ship, an old frigate, and there's also a battleship there. And it's an operating
Navy yard, so it's all people and you have to go through security. It's all operated
by like the navy. There's a people in military pretty good deal. It's pretty
cool. It's fun. If you're going to join the navy, you want to be stationed at a
museum, so we go. This guy is giving the tour of the of the ship and he takes us
below decks, and this is the I just imagining this. I mean this is so he was
he was giving the ship the tour of the ship and he was just getting like way
way too into it. Yeah, it's like and then the the British were like Huzzah
she has iron sides and he was like yelling and doing voices and stuff and
I was like, Oh, my God, you imagine awesome you go join the military and
this is and you're a reactor. Yeah, yeah, you're a yeah, you're they station
you here to and he's for he was from he had a Boston accent. He's like I'm
from Southie, so it's actually a huge honor
to be stationed here and be given the toys sick. That's amazing. I mean dude
he's getting health care to play games all day. It's great. It was dude. He
yelled so loud. It was like startled me like he was like he was like the guns,
the guns
like baby.
He that you know a real war was breaking out yeah. Have you guys seen those ads
that you get sometimes on like if you watch like a video game video on
YouTube or like a twitch stream where it's like the US Army? They're like we
need gamers now. Oh yeah, I love I used to love the
is that where they're putting force aim high as I always would think it says I
am high. That was speaking of some funny, funny shit. I didn't tell him.
I think that
yeah, I just didn't tell you guys completely about it. I told him in the
car the other night.
You guys were taking car rides. We were taking a car ride somewhere. I was
riding my bike home. We were test driving a new fucking C class, okay. It
was, yeah, we were getting a G wagon for the business. Yeah.
That'd be awesome. Why do we need a G wagon? We're getting a PPP loan.
Actually, it doesn't know cars. We're getting a PPP loan so that we can get
a bright blue G wagon that has an airbrushed... Why do we need a PPP loan?
This guy can't even spell things.
Jesus Christ.
They're called initials Cameron F.
Cameron F?
You're a fool.
Yeah, that's what the F stands for, is fool.
Foolish bastard.
Idiot.
I don't have to take this.
You do have to take it.
We were driving, I think we were at
Neil's show.
We were at Neil's show on Saturday.
We were in the car and I casually
something that I thought I had told you guys immediately, but apparently didn't.
I was hit by a joyriding Uber Eats driver who had just bought an e-bike.
This is like the craziest story ever and you didn't tell me this.
You just mentioned this earlier and I just assumed that it was something that happened years ago.
No, no, no.
It happened weeks ago.
No, this happened...
He got hit by somebody on an e-bike and then tell the crazy part of it.
Oh, he was watching YouTube on his phone.
That's not the crazy deal.
Didn't you hear the end of the story?
The end, oh the end, okay, so he was pretending to be paralyzed in the middle of the street,
found out that I had no insurance, then stepped out of the ambulance, shook my hand and said,
"It's okay, bro. This has happened to me five times this year."
That's fucking, this guy tried to do insurance fraud to Patrick and he did, so it wasn't
just he got hit by an e-bike.
He got hit by me because I was making a left turn and I didn't know that he was like speeding,
I was on Broadway, so I didn't know he was speeding behind me.
He was also on a bike?
He was on an e-bike, yeah.
He was on a normal bike.
I don't think he was an Uber Eats driver.
And you hit him with enough force to send him sprawling.
But he was on an Eats bike.
To potentially paralyze him.
To paralyze him.
And then your handshake cured him.
Well, no.
He got out of the ambulance and then went out.
So once he found out that nothing was wrong with his bike and I didn't have an insurance.
So he called 911?
Yeah.
No, no, no, no.
They were waiting.
It was all a whole scam.
Somebody...
Oh my God, the ambulance was in on it.
Well, okay, now that I'm thinking about it, there was an undercover who was directly behind
us.
An undercover who was directly behind us and he was directing traffic.
An undercover what?
I saw him do this with his jacket and I saw the badge and I went like, "Oh, thank God
you're a police officer." And he went, "No, I'm a cop, but I just got off of work. I don't
want to be dealing with this right now." And then I had to move the other guy's bike and
then he said, I found out he had YouTube on his phone because I was on the --
It's pretty rare.
He was on YouTube.
Don't assume me, man. Look, we both have YouTube on our phone.
We both have similar interests. We both like videos.
like videos. He had YouTube open, so he's like laying on the ground and he says,
"You need to get my phone and you need to call my wife. You need to say
FaceTime Precious." And so
his wife's name was Precious. Her name and his phone. Yeah. And
I pick up his phone and, dude, it's like he's watching like Vsauce or something,
and I was like, "Were you-" Claims another life. "Were you watching, were
you watching, like, YouTube?" And he went,
YouTube music. Listening to Vsauce. Yeah, because there's no way that that was an ad
playing. An ad for Vsauce? No, I don't think so. It's a bald man with a beard talking.
I didn't see Skip Ad anywhere on the screen. See, you should have just turned heel and
ran for the hills because you're dealing with a genius. This guy's watching Veritasium and
Vsauce. He's watching Vsauce, how to do insurance fraud. My bike is fine, which is good. The
the only thing true secret behind and my bike is fine. His bike is fine.
Nothing really happened. We don't kind of paralyzed. He was pretending to be
paralyzed. I tried to pick up. How did the ambulance get there? The ambulance
got there because a woman who was on the side of the street called
and fuck also the cop called and then
yeah, then the ambulance, they got there pretty quick, which is making me think
maybe I was maybe the city hates bikers so much. And let me ask you a question.
trap me. Did I hear you say pray tell a little earlier that the exact words left
your lips. Thank God you're a police officer
in today's society. You said that. Well, I said that because then I wouldn't have
to call 911 and which you were going to do, planning to call 911.
The I don't wanna ever call 911. I had to call 911. We don't call the cops
around here. If I get hit by a car, I fucking die and kill. Leave me in this
We don't call the fucking cops around here, boy.
But I was I thought that I texted it to you guys and then you started reading
through.
Oh, yeah, we me and Pat read through our text for about an hour.
Yeah.
I mean, it's all it's all stuff that I, you know, it's all kind of shit.
He texts us, which I think we should get into.
I think we should get into these questions.
It's the 200th episode.
I think that you're reading.
OK, I read.
I think I forgot to read any of your questions.
You're let me I will say you got to you.
but you usually have some good ones. The ones you asked me to read the other day
were bad. What are you talking about? Read these ones. What are you talking
about? I like your questions and I and it's okay because I have such discerning
taste that I can tell you that I thought those ones were bad. Would you rather
would you rather meet Mugatu from Zoolander or have an OnlyFans that makes
$1000 a month? And you said I said Mugatu and then I said because I because I was
I don't really want to ask the follow up. What time was that at?
That was at 1.31pm.
Okay, I was probably eating lunch.
You were busy.
Yeah.
But I didn't want to ask the follow up because I was going to, I mean it hinges on do I have
to be nude for the OnlyFans?
Yeah.
I was like I guess if I even have one that it's going to be a perception that maybe I'm
nude.
It's also going to be a job. You're basically asking do you want a job.
Well, I'll just have one.
But a job where you're hard working.
Do you want the hardest job in the world?
Or just to meet Mugatu for five seconds?
A thousand dollars a month is not worth having an OnlyFans.
Definitely not.
Well, would you rather make a video with iDubbbz or have the most popular OnlyFans in the account?
And you said?
He said iFubx.
iFubX.
And I want to make clear that this was at 6.50am.
And when did I reply?
8.40am.
So that's probably the first thing I did when I woke up.
Most likely the first thing I did.
And then I asked some more questions immediately after.
These are the ones that I ignore.
So these ones are bad, you're saying?
if I remember it, let me see here. If you were running for press, I think I
would you rather have to be honest as you're running mate
Brendan Schaub or Ethan Klein,
you gotta say Brendan Schaub. Well, let's let's hear what Cameron says. I
completely was asleep for that. I said, I said, I'll ask Caleb. Oh yeah,
because this was these are questions. Oh no, you were telling me to ask these
to Caleb. Yes, for the because I was gone for the episode. Here's the kind
he texted me, "Imagine getting sloppy steaks with the driving crooner in a Dan Flashes
shirt." That's what he said.
And playing the long -- he knows eventually all these texts are going to get read out.
Yeah. And then before that, he said, "Does I look like the driving crooner?" And sent
a picture of him in a hat.
I was at a party where they had hats, and I thought I looked like the driving crooner.
Would you rather be forced to be the driving crooner for the rest of your life or go to
to prison for sexual assault.
And I said driving.
I asked him some questions on the question. He wouldn't even
answer. What was it? What question?
I answer every single hypothetical. We send to each
other. You did not you did not answer. What was this one?
Dark humor or absurdist humor? I said it's absurdism for me.
Can you say wait? No fuck. Don't do this to me, bro. Can you
say that? What is that?
you didn't answer. Can you send me a video of you saying Livvy rizzed up
baby gronk in Trump voice?
Big Chungus says trans rights.
Timmy Turner, dad and Dinka Berg was on site.
Timmy Turner, dad and Dinka Berg was on... Is Mrs. Puff doable?
He sent me, "When I'm in a meme war and my opponent is a Death Grips fan
and a gift of Kevin McAllister and then two days ago or three days ago. He sent
me this question is mumble rap ghetto
blue face and Creshan were toxic as F for each other.
He asked me this one to who has better style, Alex or Joe, that's a real
question. Is it should be answered? Is it still ghetto to sag your pants? If
they're skinny jeans
is random dancing cringe. Most of the...
You sent me fingering or normal penetration with penis.
(Laughter)
Shit, I start a street wear brand called
Hummingbird Fresh. And I said, kind of ripping
off H3H3. He said, how? I said, animal plus
fresh. He said, Teddy is not an animal. I
said, it's a bear. And he said, nah, it's not a bear.
It's a type of stuffed animal. It's not a real
animal. But if I did start a streetwear brand called Hummingbird Fresh, would you guys be
in the lookbook?
Can I get notes on something? I said, yeah. He sent me a self-made stand-up shot that
says, "The pandemic taught us that Joe Exotic don't give a fuck." And I said, "Do flying
fuck." And he edited it to say, "The pandemic taught us that Joe Exotic don't give a flying
fuck."
On Friday, August 11th at 4.27 p.m., he texted me, "Yankee with no brim."
he sent me a picture of Ian finance and said the goat. He is the goat.
He sent me on August ninth. He sent me all in a row here. Our scooters cringe
is peppermint cringe is rabbit movers. Cranes is the mark range is the bus
driver cringe is peppermint ice cream cringe and then he sent me a picture of
a bus and said should I cringe at this? I said yes, no, I don't know what that
is. You don't know yes, yes, yes, okay, well this one was really important.
this is the one that I was going to ask when I was gone. Okay. This is a
hypothetical scenario that I wanted you guys is opinion on is SpongeBob based or
cringe. That isn't the one that is the fact that Barbie and Oppenheimer
releasing at the same time did not result in a Barbie versus Oppenheimer and
instead produced a Barbie and Oppenheimer tells me that something is
healed in the world. I D. K. That was a tweet. I
just said
This is what it is. He sent me a picture of me and Pierce wearing the same outfit and said
twins boobs vibes. It was probably vibes. Wait, hold on. Can I let me, let me just ask this
question. This one I think is really important. Okay. Okay. Would you rather have to eat every
sandwich ingredient by ingredient every time you wanted a sandwich for a year? So if you
wanted a BLT, you would have to eat the bread, then the mayo, then the lettuce, then the
tomato, then the bacon, then the last slice of bread or live in poop city for
six months with two roommates who are pieces of poop.
Poop city, probably the sandwich thing. Yeah, I want to see poop city once in my
life. If it is it free, a Grand Canyon thing, it's not free. Oh, you have to pay
for the sandwich, but you have to live with them for six months, but they smell
like fucking poop. I'm not going to I can't and it's in poop city. I don't eat
that many sandwiches, so it's not that my when I do eat a sandwich as one
ingredient. What compels you? Is this just like in the morning you take your
Adderall and then you go? I don't take my Adderall, but I want, I have a lot
of questions in the world, in the life. Well, I'm glad that it, I like the
questions 'cause it's fun to respond, it's fun to have to respond to them
'cause what I'm used to is the 2 or 3 AM ones that are just a picture,
a blurry picture. Yeah. Of what? Those of whatever you're looking at in that
moment. Yeah, you say, "Look at this." You say, "OMG." "OMG, I saw this." And
it's a picture of the ground and you say wow. What do you mean
let's see you sent him a dot. I've we have some good conversations yeah. Yeah,
when I said when we can and I have discussions when I asked him okay, so
we're asking are we going to Philippe and Ian's birthday? He said he said I
said yeah, then he said, which is
which is best Matt Rice, dark humor, Matt Rife's crowd work or Matt Rife,
sexual humor, and I said his sexual lips and then he said, What time you're
going? I said, I'm leaving right now.
What's better chips or salsa?
Chips or salsa? Chips. Yeah. Salsa with the chip underneath, to which I said
Fred or Smosh,
and then
I said, he said, new idea, salsa that goes on the bottom of the chip. That's
good. And then I I think I just didn't get the text good idea. So I asked
Fred or Smosh, Fred versus Smosh. So I think it's Fred or Smosh. Yeah. Like
what do you prefer? But Fred versus Smosh, Smosh. Yeah. Two guys. To which I
replied fingering or normal penetration with the penis. And I also sent the
thinking emoji.
And he said both at the same time using both hands, which to which I said,
damn you a freaky motherfucker. I'm glad to call you my friend, though. Salute
emoji.
So this is the kind of good conversation goes out. This is how we decide if we're
gonna go to a party. This is, yeah. Oh yeah, I forgot that that was the whole
beginning of the conversation. This is, this is telling me that I need to start
maybe responding to these texts more, 'cause I've never responded to one
except. Well, this is just all the lyrics to Lucid Dreams by Juice WRLD. We send
each other, all types of thoughts and ideas and pictures that we have
between yeah like
on Thursday, August, seventeenth at four or five PM.
Okay, just wrap it. We'll read this like a yeah, okay, Zaza versus perks,
Zaza, Zaza versus lean, Zaza, Zaza versus Siroc, Siroc, Siroc versus
champagne, champagne, champagne versus Zaza, champagne, whoa, not my fancy as
having that opinion, cocktail party versus wine, tasting cocktail party,
being zesty versus being straight straightness one hundred
umami flavors versus savory flavors to which Cameron replied.
What is this? Well, I got to turn off the time limit
with a video.
It's not playing.
It's not
doing
so you're not you're not answering these. You're missing out. I could have
he's sending some amazing gifts of people. There's a bunch of gifts, a lot
of gifts. I could I'm missing out on like I feel like a dimension to our
friendly. You and Cameron are closer than you and me because I don't respond
these. Like maybe we could dig in. Yeah. You know, I think maybe we could start
sending the questions and and here you know what now that I think about it,
now that we're airing out text, I actually have something to say. What's
that?
Yesterday, 9 10 p.m. This is a text from me for you go any further. I did send I
let Cameron know that corn and Adidas are releasing a collaboration in October.
Really big news for him. Yeah, I had already seen it, but I played along and
I was kind. Oh, that's sweet. Yeah. 9, 10 p.m. In the group chat, text from me. Do you guys
want to have a day of fun?
Well, I think...
I was ignored.
I was busy.
You were not busy because you sent multiple texts after that on a different topic.
I didn't even notice that text.
And I'm not going to be kind and not read what you said.
I'm not fucking kidding. I did not even notice that.
And that's the problem, isn't it?
I didn't notice. I'm sorry.
Can I...
Patrick doesn't even notice it. Now I'm not noticing it now. I'm not noticing it
now because I said you spec of dust. I sent you an amazing character idea for
world's biggest army, which was walk med the bread dollar sign bag terrorist
walk like W. Walk med walk med the bread terrorist. Oh, so it's Ahmed the dead
terrorist, but he sips lean and makes money walk med the bread terrorist. He's
a terrorist of money. And you ignored this. So this is I mean a day of fun. I
don't even know. Yeah, you ignored that to say I think there might also be one
of those square road labs in the office. You know why I texted you that?
Because you called me asking about about microphones and I talked to you
and I helped you out and then I sent you a text to help you guys as much fun as
this is. My wife just texted me that she crashed a car, so I have to call and
find out if she crashed the car. No, not my car. Her bosses. She put it into a
fire hydrant.
Oh Jesus Christ. Yeah, but I'll figure this out and I'll send her. Wait, what
should I send her? Which text should I send her? Oh, you should send her
Walk vs Aza. Walk? Okay, I'll send her right now. Oh, Dew vs Claws.
Walk vs... Here's a question you could actually send her. What?
What if you saw a gangsta with some dew hanging out of his sagging pants?
What if you saw a gangsta with some dew?
He has like a, in the way that I'm imagining it is.
She sent me this photo.
Oh, that's nothing.
That's nothing, right?
Yeah.
So I'll say, what if you saw a gangsta with some dew?
I mean, all she has to do is paint over it.
It looks like it's gonna start raining outside.
She probably has some car paint.
I wanna go home.
All right, I'll call my wife.
All right, I am opening for Girl God
in Chicago in November.
Okay.
up. All right. Bye. Bye.
World of Warcraft dream. Whoa. From GXViper98. This means sound crazy, but hear me out. I
was playing this game World of Warcraft when I decided to join a group for a raid on a
dungeon. The leader was JK Simmons. Wow. Yes, the JK Simmons. People were telling me about
his very strict rules about his raids where people were actually dying in real life. I
I remember his game name was Dr. Rain.
Think of his character in the movie Whiplash,
but a hundred times more insane.
Anyway, we start the raid
and everything goes off without a hitch.
I mean, we were tearing through this place at record speed.
We reach one of the bosses that was known to be pretty tough.
The Doc, that's what he calls him, the Doc,
made sure if anyone screw up,
they would pay the consequences.
We start the battle and it was going well.
Then one of our key players starts to lag behind.
He was given a warning, but it continues.
So Doc banishes him from the game, never to play again.
I don't remember much after that.
What could this mean?
- And this is I, I think they fell asleep
while they were writing that.
- What the fuck could this mean?
- Well, okay, the first part about this,
we already said, I mean, we already touched upon that
with the Chris Griffin dream.
- Oh, he sees JK Simmons as an idol.
- Yeah, sees JK Simmons as an idol,
or GX Viper is really, really like,
like upset or concerned with celebrity culture and like there maybe GX Viper
is a secret celebrity that we don't know what could GX be? This could be this could be
G first initial first name that's coming to my head George Lopez this could be
GGL because he replaced Latinx. GX Latinx George Lopez Viper 98 born in 98 or
or he's 98 years old.
Or yeah.
One of the two.
Could be 98, he could be born on double day.
He could be born on double day.
There's leap day and there's double day.
Scary.
High school, a femboy, and nonstop cumming.
*roars*