(music)
everybody kind of messed up in a little way, except for me. Now you messed up,
you messed up, you left your water bottle. You got to put my water bottle
in front of my chair. That's messing up. Yes. Well, you put your water bottle on
a table that was covered in trash. No, I cleaned all the trash off the table.
Not true, because that's why that's no camera and got his water. No, I got it.
That was not on the table. I threw away all the cans from the table. I
purposely did that, and I remember thinking, did you hear that I'm taking
all the trash off the table so that nobody will throw in my water bottle?
so you always will be. I was trying to any time that you are so close to
getting caught doing something wrong or making a mistake. You always remember
thinking something what wrong
you are so good. I made you tell me one wrong memory. You're so good at
remembering what you thought it's almost too convenient. Okay, well, you always
remember no, no, no, no, let's hear the mistake. Let's hear the wrong thing I
did today besides arguing so strongly. The right remembering everything like a
protective you like Sherlock Holmes, the wrong thing you did was waking up
excuse me that's that's way too rude. That's that should be more than a
warning. Yeah, that should be to you. Also, I was choosing sides. I was
choosing the side that I thought was you drink out of a plastic water bottle
yeah, which is you're getting a micro plastic in your blood yeah. Okay, so I
do you think I should be having babies every day of the week. I try to
sterilize myself at least just get remember thinking drinking from that
water bottle. This is the reason I'm drinking from a plastic water bottle
right now. He always remembers. He said it again. He remembers every thought
this guy ever had. He has a walking around like this. I don't remember what
I'm thinking today. I don't remember what I'm saying. I remember exactly what
I'm thinking. I can't remember. I can't even remember a thought from yesterday,
because I'm not a thinker Cameron. I'm a doer and I remember what I did. I
threw your fucking water bottle in the trash with no remorse and I told you to
it out of the trash and drink from it. I'd do it again. Because it wasn't even in the
trash, it wasn't touching the trash bag, it was in a box. That trash bag is filled with
flies. You're acting like Monk. Just wash it off. You're being, you're kind of being
Shaloubian. Just wash off the fucking water bottle. You are being Shaloubian right now.
You're being Monk. I'm not even the one who brought up the water bottle on the show. I
got myself a perfectly good plastic. I don't care, so you're deflecting, I'm saying you're
being Monk. I don't know what that means. He never watches being Monk. You're being a
perfect. You have to describe that to me. You're being a hyper intelligent rememberer. I know
know who plays monk, but I never watched the show or know anything.
You're being a hyper intelligent rememberer who's afraid of germs.
This is what you are looking like. You spelled it wrong.
You spelled monk wrong, but... You wrote monk with a U,
Juvia. Yeah, he's with an O. So it's spelled... It's not how it's spelled.
You're thinking of chip monk. Yeah, this is monk. We're talking about...
I don't know what kind of monk this is. I've never watched monk,
but I'm pretty sure this isn't monk. You spit all over my hand. I
Oh my God, I'm glittering. It's actually beautiful. Hold on.
That's strawberry watermelon on your hand. There he is.
Yeah, you're being like, actually, this is me, man. And not the bald stuff, but just the perfect Zen serenity.
That's me. The bald stuff is the only thing that's you.
And then this is Cameron. Go to the other one.
This one? No, the monk.
No, not this one.
Likeably unlikely.
No, the Tony Shalhoub, the only one that isn't real.
There we go.
You see the pencils are all in order.
He holds a pen.
Oh, actually, you're kind of looking...
Whoa.
Wait, go back up.
Go back to Monk, Shalhoub Monk.
Caleb, you're being kind of Monk-y right now.
No, I don't.
I put my pencil diagonal because I don't give a fuck about that kind of thing.
You were doing this.
But he has pencils in front of him, too.
Yeah, you have a pencil in front of you.
You have one in front of you.
Now I'm being Monk.
I'm being monk. It's not I don't like order. I like chaotic messes. So you
doing? Oh, he was he was testing the point of his pencil. But anyway, I'll
apologize to everybody. I'm sorry for not drinking my water out of the trash.
Thank you. I'm really sorry for remembering what I did thirty seconds
ago. Thank you. I'm sorry. I really appreciate that. Yeah. And now we can
move forward to talking about Patrick being late one minute late. Okay, so now
the next sin, the next deadly sin.
that was one late. Well, well, well, well, looks like the tables have turned
away. Usually, usually all of us are 15 minutes late, but today Patrick was
one minute late. I'm usually the one who's here. No, no, no, Caleb is usually
50 minutes late. Yeah, you're usually late. I'm usually one or two minutes
late. I'm always the one who opens it up. Yeah. So why? I'm here on my
computer. So that's, I think it's an expectation thing is why we're mad at
you today. Yeah. You were expecting me to be early. I was expecting you to
I had the thought I did have the thought this like this morning.
See I just don't you're doing you're doing that monk shit man. You're
remembering having a thought I did that I had the thought this morning. You're
not supposed to remember your thoughts. Oh, Mr. Mr. I was like, Oh, it doesn't
bring your thought it doesn't matter. I'm usually there first. I think I can
be late today. The one day that Juvia said we need to start at a specific
well. He has a history of being asleep when we try to start well, but he was I
know why I'm being dragged into this. Yeah, why is this not my fight?
Completely unrelated. Well, I'm just saying it's the only reason that it
matters for being one minute late. Some of us have had stuff to do and somebody
has been asleep, so I don't think that the order or the...
Why are we having a struggle session right now? What are we doing? We gotta
go into it. Yeah, we should just lay it all out.
Patrick, I hate your shirt. You hate my shirt? I don't like that kind
of camouflage on a shirt. You are wearing a French pervert shirt. I look like a mime.
Yes. No, you don't look like a mime. You look like a doer of crime. You look like a doer
of French style crime. It's actually a Russian army shirt. Oh, nice. I actually got it at
an army surplus store in Chicago, Illinois. Woke-ism. It wasn't woke of me to do that.
Yeah, it was. You got a Russian army shirt. How's that woke? Give him a warning. That's
It's an anti-woke one.
Give them a warning.
Warning!
Don't warn me.
You have no woke warning.
You're not allowed to say don't warn me.
You have a woke warning.
Russia hates wokeness.
Now they do, but back when they had an army.
Back when they had an army?
Yeah.
You're talking about the Cold War?
Yep.
Alright.
Yeah, that's fair.
They probably loved wokeness back then.
That's what the Cold War was about.
It was about wokeness versus Americanism.
I got, I watched a video of the Cold War.
I watched the video.
I got I watched a video the other day that was a bunch of it was like every
time that I think it was a very testy and videos like every time that the like a
nuclear bomb got lost or like almost exploded and I thought I thought it was
gonna be like three times no it happened like 75 times gonna end yeah one of
these times it's gonna be really bad news it's going it only gets worse one of
one of them was they were they were flying
a nuclear warhead around like just around the Soviet Union for like no
reason yeah and then it dropped and just fell in the ocean. Yeah, they do that
all the time. Oh my it just dropped in a plane yeah broken arrow. That's what
they call. There's one should not be touching them. There's one that's in
North Carolina that there I knew that there was one that was lost there, but I
thought they found it, but there was two one of them they found and took away the
other one they found it and then before they could pick it up, there was a flash
flood that covered it in like a hundred feet of of earth and so and
it's it is primed and ready to go, but there's a switch on it that needs to be
turned on. So they put instead of going and trying to find it, they just put a
giant slab of concrete over the place where the bomb is.
There should not be.
And they just hope there's never an earthquake.
In, since I've seen Oppenheimer, there should not be a nuclear bomb anywhere.
There should not be, I don't know why the hell we even have those.
Well they're cool, they're the coolest bombs on earth.
They're the coolest, I don't, you know what, I'm going to say it, I don't fuck with them.
Nah, me neither.
I don't fuck with a nuclear bomb.
You guys want disarmament?
You're one of these hippie, hippie, uh, yuppies.
Absolutely.
That's right.
Who like lattes and nuclear disarmament.
I am one of these.
I love trail mix.
Okay, Mr. Russian.
Yeah.
I'm a Russian.
Mr. Russian Socialist.
I'm a Russian Socialist and I want to destroy the world with thousands of nuclear bombs
if somebody tries to make a white Spider-Man movie again.
If they make a white Spider-Man, I will destroy the world with nuclear bombs.
There will be.
Because of my woke social agenda.
There will be the complete and total destruction of Earth.
If they make a Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles with a green turtle.
A green girl turtle.
They just made one of those.
Without not the girl part.
I hear that this Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles movie is actually quite interesting.
I heard that it's...
It's pretty good if you're 7 years old I think.
I hang out with 7 year olds.
I went to see it with Alex.
You're doing one of those French crimes aren't you?
No.
No,
you're sneaking into the movie theater like
now I don't eleven year old boy bag to put down to the front row, putting a bag
over a kid. Wow yeah, hey screw me for being in the big brother program.
That's what you think the bigger and the big uncle program.
The big uncle program, this is the uniform, the
bopper program. If you keep talking because I will kill you, you mean we're
going to be famous musicians. No, I will be throwing you famous musicians playing
directly into the ground. We're going to have that stupid fucking song where we
talk into a telephone. I never learned a single big bopper song. I just think is
a stupid name and I'm at a really big mouth sucks.
Why do you buddy Holly sucks? Why are you talking so high sucks all these
fifties song? Are you sounding like more like crap?
They all suck like crap.
Jay Leno?
Why did you go so high when you just, you're like, yeah, those guys suck.
Those guys suck!
Those guys suck like crap!
Those guys really suck like crap!
Weird.
I hate 50s crap so much.
I think it's so gay.
I think when they have like a 50s themed diner, it's like, shut the fuck up.
What's wrong with the, you don't like Johnny Rockets?
No, fuck that.
I thought you were talking about music, or you just don't like the 50s?
I don't like any of this 50s crap.
Unless it's a car.
A 50s car is cool.
What about cool stuff from the 50s?
Like what?
There's nothing.
Like the fridges?
The fridges are cool.
And the princesses are cool.
You don't like those fridges?
I think they did it better in the 60s and 70s.
What about the family unit?
Family unit, buddy?
I'm one of these...
What about a sexual family unit?
You don't fuck with that?
I do not fuck with that.
So you gay?
I do not fuck with the nuclear family and I do not fuck with nuclear bombs.
What about Walt Disney World?
Fuck that gay bullshit.
the shit
man calling everything fucking gay, you're warning homophobia morning.
I'm becoming you think that you think that the I'm becoming family unit is
gay. I think that when a man and a woman have a son, okay, what about daughter?
What about a dog in a yard? I think that that's all gay, and I think that if you
you have a little thirteen inch TV in your living room that you can watch how
to duty on that's even gayer. So you think TV's gay. I think that way as
bullshit. You just said you think TV television yeah, we're talking about the
same TV. If it's black and white, if it's a black and white show from the
fifties, that's some gay bullshit, but if it's a color show called solar
I'm talking about TV. If it's a colored show called
black and white is gay bullshit, but don't show in white stuff. How do you
say a colored show? Jeez, what do you mean God? There's black and white and
colors. There's black TV and there's white TV. No, there's color programs and
there's
what do you get it? What are you saying? What are you saying that I'm sounding so
racist and I'm sounding and where is this or opposite how Justin Roiland fit
into this, which that's all that's all colored. That's all colored in
okay colored in I'm starting to understand. What do you mean? What was I
saying? That's wrong. We thought you were saying something completely different.
What
basically we thought that you were saying that you were you were thinking
hold on. I just thought I said that I thought that the fifties is gay bull
crap and you thought that I was calling something colored. You know what they
said back in the 50s? They said there was difference between coloreds and whites.
That is gay bullshit.
Yeah, different water fountains, that is gay. Segregation is gay bullshit. Wow.
We should send you back then, 'cause actually that would actually work really
down like white guys in the 50s. Yeah. Like stop all this different bathroom
shit. This is gay. This is fucking gay bullshit. What is this red lining?
What is it? You want this red line to go in your ass? Are you gay?
Yeah. And they would have been like, "Oh, well, I'm not." Yeah. Herbert Hoover
would have taken off his lady clothes. Yeah.
Was it? No, J Edgar Hoover. J Herbert Hoover was the inventor of vacuum.
Invented a vacuum. Yeah.
But he probably wore lady clothes too. I think they all did. I think all
all of those like big as over 50s men, all those named Hoover 50s fops all
dressing like I'm tired of these 50 fops. They're not gay. They're
can't call them gay. I can't call it gay bullshit because that'd be mean. Do you
guys? Did you that'd be a that'd be a hateful crime?
A fop you think call to call a fop gay? Why the pejorative would be a hateful
crime? Why is your voice sound like that? I don't know.
I think I got choked up thinking about, I think I was about to cry thinking about hateful
crime.
How bad you might hurt a fop's feelings.
Yeah.
We need more fops in this world.
News flash, fops don't have feelings.
Fops don't care about your feelings.
A fop is like a guy with long hair.
He's a dandy.
A fop is a dandy or a Nancy.
Moe, okay.
A dandy or a Nancy.
But what do those mean?
What a dandy and Nancy?
The fraternal order of police.
Hey.
he looks he looks really scary.
This is not what I think of when I think like disgusting, fobbish
gentlemen, yeah, search fobbish
fobbish dandy.
Fobbish dandy.
This is a fob. Who's this bloke? These blokes are fobbish dandies.
These you've never heard of these fellas. I mean I've heard it, but I
guess I didn't know that it was I thought it was more of an insult. I
I am sick of seeing, by the way,
I don't know if it's like a Dungeons and Dragons class you could be.
I'm, I'm, I don't, I keep getting political on here.
I keep calling stuff gay bullshit.
I'm tired of seeing motherfuckers in Bushwick walking around like this.
True.
These Bushwick ass motherfuckers walking around
in these clothes.
It's really just one element away from being dressed up like a geisha.
Yeah.
Maybe the hair would just be a little different.
Bro, you, you see, you walk into a coffee shop
walk into a coffee shop in freaking Bushwick,
and you see a guy behind the counter dressed like this.
- Alabaster white faces with rosy pink cheeks.
Get away from me, bro.
- But you know they make some crazy ass coffee.
- Yep, and you know that they have.
- You know they make the best coffee.
- Some of the best taste in music you've ever fucking heard.
- Is this Bell and Sebastian you're playing?
No, is this Mozart's "The Great Bard?"
Damn, is this a new harpsichord track you're playing?
(laughing)
I wonder what these guys are doing, these three.
I think that they are at a basketball game.
Yeah, they're next to them as a normal guy.
Next to them, it looks like a Emile Hirsch.
Don't even get me started on that.
Look at that fucker.
He's good friends with Sean Penn.
One of them's wearing some kind of Fitbit or smart watch.
No, it's one of those...
That is a fighting bracelet.
No, it's one of those anti-sea sick bracelets.
Are they on a boat, maybe?
Yeah, maybe they're on a boat.
coffee shop. Look, there's a coffee cup next to them. They are and I told you
these are these are baristas. Yeah, three pop is dandy to attend the Chicago
Bulls, New York Knicks game on
I never knew that. I thought that they just dress like this guys. We just ate
the onion.
God damn it. Fuck fucked up. That screws my life up in a major way. On Halloween
night, you think I'm going to dress up as a real actual lifestyle of a person.
yeah, I'm going to make someone's culture my costume. That's like me.
That's like me dressing up like like my word
Evans
I'm going to start. I gotta start saying my word again. Yeah, I think that I
need to start Scott. I say I say my word sometimes. I think he gads he gads is
not as good as my words. Zoons? You mean zooks? No, you're thinking of gadzooks. I'm saying
zoons. That's Shakespearean. Zoons? Z-O-U-N-D-S. Zoons. I was like zounds and then zoons would
be tunes to sounds. Zoons is short for God's wounds. That'd be like me dressing up like
an emo. You took that long to think of that? It didn't feel, it wasn't that long. It was
pretty long and that'd be like
me dressing up like an emo or a cinephile.
You dress like a cinephile right now, a child's in a file.
Okay, just seen the new Winnie the Pooh.
I've just seen
rocking up
standing up at the end of cars for Bravo.
There's a report that the car, the cars for premier got a ten minute standing
ovation from one guy, one guy like it's a
fucking con premier.
It's just in the middle of nowhere. Yeah, it's like a movie theater and
fucking the first showing in Illinois got a forty five minutes standing
motivation. Get the guy out of the from a man named Bruce Mies
local film critic
for Highlights Magazine, Bruce Mies, we're literally describing
M. E. C. Yeah, I guess that is him. Oh my God, but he's a but he's an adult
now. Yeah, that's what I mean. My buddy still goes. He still does little kid.
Oh, he doesn't loves kids. Move he has a new where my buddy released his top
I don't know. You guys probably missed this. He releases top 50 SpongeBob
episodes. Yeah. Oh, God. That's not even I did miss that. I would have been all
over that. I sent it to you guys. Oh, I need it. It's a nice girl.
I stopped cooking links a while ago. I think I sent it as a picture. Oh, so if
it was a link, I think I would have not. I don't look at photos because I don't
like. I mean, I don't I'm just saying I always get worried that when with photos
there, maybe one of those ones where you blur your eyes and it looks pornographic.
So I just don't look at them.
If you don't look at them, you're more likely to blur your vision.
If I even see a square, any squares I don't look at.
Because I think that's cheating.
My buddy was telling me though that he works somewhere in LA and Lights Camera Jackson
is in there all the time.
He works at some PR thing or something.
something, but he was telling me that like he has like multiple times
interacted with lights, camera Jackson.
And I was so, I don't think I've ever been more jealous of somebody in my life
to not even like Bill Gates, billionaire guy.
Like, no, I would not want to be Bill Gates.
How ironic is it guys that Bill Gates is a bill you in there.
They named the money after him.
This is the height of ironic of irony.
Wait Gates windows.
A window is a type of gate and you know, and I just downloaded a picture of a
door and you know his house has gates on it. Wait, build door. Wait, he built his
house. Wait, he played builders game on a windows PC. I'm playing it on a windows
PC. He built when he player character. Wait, can you look up bill gates middle
name right now, please? This is very important. It's danger.
William Henry Henry. He gets hen when he's hangry when he's hungry.
Snickers. You should have a Snickers bill. You're not acting like yourself.
You're not making any money today. Yeah, wait three. Wait, Bill Bill Bill Gates
the three. That's actually that's actually scary and your character's name
could be Henry
and his wife's middle name is French. That's her way. Her Melinda French Gates
Wait, building a French gate to keep this guy out. No, that's not his French
style. Crime Marie. No, crime Marie is a good. We should call this office the
crime. Marie crime Marie. Melinda me, Linda, Linda. Hey, she made her. She's
a caveman or a cave woman. I'm so sorry. Melinda French Gates. Whoa. And that
second picture right there is Bill Gates and Baldur's Gate three. Yeah, that's
That's what he looks like. Do you guys think that he's spreading microchipped
mosquitoes around this universe? I saw him dumping them out of his helicopter
over my house. I saw that too. They destroyed my road last night. My mom
texted me two weeks ago and said be careful of the mosquitoes. They are
Bill Gates mosquitoes and I was like, okay, welcome to the barbecue
motherfucker. Mom, you are concerned about these Bill Gates mosquitoes. You
have five Amazon Alexas in your house.
She...
Mm-hmm.
What the fuck?
What the fuck is that?
You're roasting your own mom right now.
You're concerned about the Bill Gates mosquitoes?
Buddy...
Bill!
You got a Bezos phone in your house.
He's not really roasting.
This is kind of just good.
I mean, just be like, "Bill Gates, you need to lose..."
Or, "My mom..."
Bill Gates mosquitoes, how about you...
You need to lose weight, stop eating taquito.
Keto. Mama, you stupid fat. That's you when you sit on the couch. That's yeah,
when you lay on your bed, your springs break out of the couch. The springs
breaking on the couch in the motherfucking mattress, Mom. See,
that's how I would roast a mom. Or maybe I'd be like, "Hey, Mom, guess
what? Your cooking isn't all that good anymore." She's not the one that cooks
in the house. "It used to be better. Your dad cooks." She's not the one
that cooks. You did an invalid roast. Well, but it's an invalid roast.
I didn't your mom was not an invalid. She you know what happened in the last
couple of weeks going on. Why am I getting warning? Can't say the word
in the wood? You can't say he said that first. No, I thought it was clear.
Don't start an argument.
You are the closest thing to God. Yeah,
Jesus, it's making me really scared of his position. So he has all of the power.
This is an unfair. I
I could give you guys a little like maybe there's an app on the phone where you
guys can trigger some of the sounds yourself. Yeah, something I wish we could
all have the that would be such a bad. I do think it would be bad, but I do wish
that because one day we could just do an episode. It's just the day is the
battle. Yeah, yeah, or maybe we could rotate it. Yeah, because the most of the
levels just stay the same. Yeah, it's pretty. It's really just the sound and
the Julio levels that need to change. Yeah,
ever. Yeah, I mean morning.
Oh, my
God!
See?
Why did that scare me so badly?
I actually just got humanly terrified.
Yeah.
Well.
Welt.
Wait.
Oh.
I forgot.
How did we not talk about this already?
What?
These aliens.
Oh, the Mexico were released on the same day that we were released.
The same day that we were released.
But we didn't even get to talk about them, man.
Yeah.
Those little fucking dusty ass white pieces of shit aliens going down to the beautiful
Mexico City and gentrifying it. Did we talk about this? These little white bastards?
You think these are universal digital nomads?
These are Gringalians. And they are coming in to beautiful Mexico.
They're going to Tijuana. They're fucking prostitutes.
They're asking, they're saying, "Can I get a taco? Can I get a nacho?"
Wait, taco is exactly how Jubio says taco.
No way.
He says "deco".
Really?
Say it right now.
Deco.
That's literally what he said.
I was saying it with a British inflection though.
I was saying "taco".
Taco.
Can I get a taco?
Can I get a taco and some nachos?
Tesco.
And a gordita crunch wrap.
Rip.
Yeah, I hate how people want foreigners to go to Mexico and the way they pronounce gordita
crunch wrap when ordering at street food.
Me too.
Yeah.
Well that gordita is a real thing.
Can I get a cheesy potato burrito?
A gordita is real.
Can I have a grilled cheese taco?
Can I get a supreme crunchwrap please?
Excuse me.
And cinnabon twists please.
Pronounce it right.
My abuela's cinnamon twists.
Oh my god.
You guys should try my abuela's
Baja Blast. It is fucking
insanely good.
My abuela makes the most amazing
You are not, you know what, I'm not going to listen. If you are not from Jalisco, I do not
want to hear your opinion on Baja Blast. You guys don't really have an abuela, right? Yeah,
you do have an abuela. I forgot about that. Who? My abuela. Who is that? My abuela. Birria
is from Jalisco. You have a Spanish grandmother? Mexican. Can you confirm? What? Yes. Yes?
I was right about that? Look at me, my little foodie ass.
You little fruity ass.
What the hell?
What were you guys even talking about just now?
We were talking about, I was talking about the origin of birria.
And you were talking about your abuela, which actually...
Yeah, you were bragging that you had it.
Can you tell me about your abuela's birria?
I just think it's funny. I never thought it was funny until I grew up and found out it's funny to have an abuela.
Does your abuela make birria or maybe some kind of other food that we can transition
this into your abuela stuff?
What?
What are you saying?
I spaced out for the first half of that.
What kind of food does your abuela make?
I don't know.
She doesn't live here.
She doesn't live in Mexico?
No, she used to live in New Mexico, but now she lives in Baltimore.
Oh, shit.
- Ooh, okay, so she's making birria crab.
(laughing)
- That is so repulsive.
- Birria softshell crab.
- Oh my God, pulling apart, ugh.
- I don't know, I think that that could maybe,
if you put Old Bay in the birria,
it's not true birria, but it could work.
- It takes so much to make fucking crab
and lobster and shit taste good.
It takes so much butter.
- No, all it takes is a little bit of butter.
it takes a ton of butter. It takes an entire childhood to make lobster and
crab taste good. That's true. I didn't eat it. I mean, I would catch crabs. Is
that what you took from from what I just said? You think you have to make it for
the span of a childhood? No, it takes a whole childhood to make. Is that no? No,
I think you're saying it takes a whole childhood for you to think it tastes
good. Yeah, it does, though. What do you mean if you don't grow up with it? You
won't like it? Oh yeah, all right. I get that I caught crabs, but I didn't eat
them because they were weird to me and I was vegetarian, but we'd catch them with
their t shirts, but they were like nasty crabs. I think yeah you have
show them their t shirt that says come here
I'm with crab
free money for
wait.
I just thought it was crazy that they boil a boil and alive. How cruel is
yeah
practice something that stuck in my mind forever from how horrific it is. Is my
mom who's so nice and kind and would never hurt any living creature brought
home a live lobster and put it on the ground for our dog to play with. I was
scolding her for it when I visited home this pet because we were eating
lobster. I was thinking about again. That is the most evil thing I've ever
seen someone. Did she when she when she was like so horrible, did she cut
through the head or just throw it in? She's done both because when I learned
that the that it's not them screaming, when I learned that it's the pressure
like boiling their the meat in their shell. Yeah, that fucked me up. Yeah,
it's fucked up. It's better. Wait, it's better to kill them first. It's better
to know through the head, but you're saying it cut it open. So it has up
learning that it wasn't screaming. Yeah, you were like, well, that sound is
probably just screaming, so it's probably okay. Wait, it's
releasing from a shell. Yeah, wait, I don't understand either.
That fucked me up because it's imagine having that done to you. I guess you
Imagine screaming and pain because you're being boiled alive.
Yeah, that's easier to imagine than having a shell.
And like, oh, my air.
Wow.
I wish I actually made me feel really normal.
It actually made me feel good about killing all of them.
OK, you kill all of them.
Yeah, I do.
They endangered. No, they're not endangered.
Yeah, I mean, we definitely mean main lobsters are not endangered, but they
Main lobsters, they have a lot of rules. You have to like, if you catch one.
I watch the videos too. Of the guy who says, "Guys, this is a breeder. I'll clip her. I'll
give her a snack and I'll throw her back in."
Well, he doesn't call them breeders. He calls them, he calls them eggers.
You guys are so good at videos. I've never seen any of these videos you guys make.
Buddy, you need to start watching Dr. Insanity on YouTube.
Dr. Insanity?
He has been making a lot of videos about the crips and the bloods.
When the cop realizes that he's arresting his own son, stuff like that.
Last night, you know when you realize like you don't have the whole thing where people
talking about their like fucking, is this Dr. Insanity?
No, it's not him.
It's like somebody was talking about videos they've seen and just like asking.
Rowe was like, "Have you seen the video of those three Chinese midgets singing on that
mountainside?"
I haven't seen that one.
He asked that and somebody was like, "What kind of fucking videos are you being shown?"
I was like, "Wait, you guys haven't seen that?"
I was like, "What the fuck?
No one here has seen these?"
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't get videos like that. Yeah, I guess you have to like mostly videos
about cute monkeys playing with cute dogs. That's what they were saying.
They saw the diseases that claim to them. There's two types of people in
the world. Now there's two. There's the people who see cute animal videos and
then there's people who see very interesting types of stuff going on in
China. I see some of the China videos too, but not that many. I kind of my I
had I had an old Instagram account and that one got completely taken over by
deformed babies and animals. I kind of made a pretty conscious effort. That's
crazy. But that means there is a kind of many of that content is a content tag on
Instagram. That is so nuts. You know what? The craziest thing is you can tell
that the algorithm lumps like you'll watch one of the you know, the dog that
has like no neck and he has like big shoulders. Yes, you watch one of those
videos like, oh, that's a funny looking dog. That's cute. And then you can tell
that Instagram thinks because you watch that you want to see like a baby with a
cleft palate, like struggling to breathe. You know what? I saw the same thing in
in the robot brain is like, oh, a deformed dog and a deformed baby. This
person must like deformities. I think that I'm in the direct middle ground
'cause you've probably sent me a few of those, and I saw this amazing video,
this dude in Brazil who has
his fingers are fused together into one big...
His fingers and toes are really long. Oh, that's cool. Really long,
like crab claw kind of things. Yeah. And he also had... His feet are
like that too, but he's an amazing skateboarder.
Wow.
And I saw a video of him putting on, like you see his feet doing that, puts on a pair of
Crocs does a fucking sick ass back crook in his backyard.
Wow.
I was like damn, even if you got a crab claw, you can still, you can still, the human, the
human spirit is so indomitable.
Even if you're a Zoidberg.
Well, I would say he has more of a crab spirit than a human spirit.
He's like, interior is the crab.
I don't think he has a crab spirit.
I think he has a crab exterior.
The hands are important to the human soul.
He's like a crab in the sky. But it's the feet too. Crabs don't have claws for feet.
Do you guys want to start wearing those natural shoes or whatever they're called?
Toe shoes? Make our feet spread out? The ones that have barely their sole?
No, no, no. I'm talking about the ones that are like, because all of our toes are so squished in.
buddy. I'm not like something with a really wide like end, then your feet
end up being like giant triangles. I'm not wearing something like that. The
five toes and he runs like thirty miles in the woods every day. Buddy, you know
what I'm wearing? Cactus Jack, Captain Jack Flea Market, Captain Jack Flea
Market, Flea Market, Jordan Lowe's, Jordan Lowe's. I'm wearing the red
mischief boots. I'm wearing the mischief Crocs. Those things are so stupid. I'm
wearing all of the mischief shoes. I'm wearing the Shrek. What does Shrek have
on Shrek Crocs? Did you see these? These are a big viral. These are a viral shoe
that everyone is going crazy for. Is this what these have been viral? This is
ten years old. Viral shoe that have just gone viral. These are completely viral
right now. I'd wear those. Yeah, you would. Yeah, I would wear them if it
didn't have the Shrek logo on it so I could pretend they were for something
else.
Oh, I didn't even realize these were Shrek's. Oh, yeah, actually you're right.
I guess it does kind of look like Shrek. That's funny. Yeah. Wow. Weird.
Have you seen, okay, have you seen the JJJ jowned Crocs? What the hell are
these? Look these up. Look these up.
Imagine, okay, look these up.
Do they, okay. Imagine how much these are, like, show the price now. They're
probably expensive because they have that little piece of gold.
Yeah, actually, that's probably because you said imagine the price. Yeah, that
too, but I want to see the actually the actual price. $75.00. Isn't that crazy?
$75.00 for Crocs. That's pretty, but for like fancy looking Crocs, they're not
fancy looking. They have a little goal and they have a different. I mean,
they're like special Crocs. Those they are not even that special. They're like
a collab. Crocs are $50. Wait, are you serious? Yeah. What?
I said that they were like 30. I guess I've only bought the knockoff Crocs that are $5.
I have mine are second hand. I have the real Crocs, guys. I got mine from a 99 cent store.
My mom bought them for me, y'all. I have. Actually, I'm wrong. I ordered those myself
because I really wanted. And they're the only, one of the only two pairs of shoes I wear.
I wear my Crocs every day. They're really good for wearing outside briefly. Yeah. They're
like perfect. They're so much better than putting on. Now that the fall's coming up
and guys, it got a little cold, you're going to see my Crocs a lot more often. I might even
buy a second pair. I might buy a fashion pair.
Wouldn't you rather wear them when it's warm?
You should get those JJJound ones.
My move is, I might get them. My move is I wear big, big socks, big thick socks and my
Crocs and that's my fall shoes, y'all.
My Crocs are like three sizes too small for my feet.
Unless I'm doing something active AF.
Mine hurt my feet when I wear them, so I can only wear them for a short burst.
I love them and they have comfort. I wear them to get my mail. My dad wears them in his house.
This JJJ jownd I learned about a couple years ago and then I was like really astounded.
It's $25 on the shirt for a gold thing.
The other stuff that they have is pretty expensive. It's just like a plain shirt.
That's still too much for a croc to be though.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean it's definitely a more expensive croc but it's not. When you said it was, guess
how much this is? I thought it was going to be $300.
You know who's their biggest hater is our buddy Eric.
Really? Yeah. Eric Howington, who lives at... You don't even know his address. I don't know his
address, yeah. Yeah, I do kind of... He is their like number one biggest hater. It is so funny.
For a long time... He's the only guy I can talk to about this. I mean, because it's probably the
most boring conversation you could possibly have. I hate the people who overcharge for
white t-shirts. This is like... I know. You're just doing what people said about APC like 10
ten years ago.
Yeah, you know what, you're right. I think that I've seen the errors of my ways just now.
Thank you.
And I think that...
Every conversation about fashion is just, "This shirt's cool. This pants is too expensive."
Yeah.
That's kind of the...
That's always it is.
Every conversation about mostly anything...
Anything that you can buy.
...is either like, "This is good. This is bad. This is overpriced. This is cheap."
There's no middle ground on clothes. It's not, "Oh, that's okay."
Explain what you mean.
Oh.
It's always, "This sucks."
I was about to say, there's nothing between shirts and pants.
There's nothing between shirts and pants.
Yeah, I was like, "Buddy, there's a belt and a cummerbund."
There's a lot between my shirts and my pants.
A sash. A girdle.
A girdle.
My...
What's that other one called? My corset?
A middler.
My cummerbund.
I already said cummerbund.
I have another segment of my body like a centipede.
I'm an insect, so I have two torsos,
so I can wear two shirts and one pants.
You need a middler.
I wish I had two stomachs.
Why?
One for sweets, one for healthies.
Everyone has that.
We've talked about the dessert stomach so many times.
We've talked about it?
I would say we are some of the foremost researchers on the dessert stomach.
How you can eat...
Can we do like a...
I could go to Olive Garden, I could have 40 bowls of fucking brajul.
Rice.
And more 40 bowls of rice.
He's trying to show off his Italian heritage.
I'm brajul.
I could have 40 bowls of soup.
I could have 40 bowls of fagiola.
Fagiola.
I could have 40 bowls of Alfredo spaghetti. I didn't do that at all. And then I go and
I'm going to say bread steaks. I didn't say this. Okay. You guys are doing some Italian
Elon Musk stuff. Okay. Very, very funny. I get to have 40 and days meant I could have
I love those.
Those taste like toothpaste, but I love them so much.
I could be so full to my brim.
The soup could be gurgling up my throat.
We've got to go to Olive Garden.
If they say, "Would you like some fried ice cream?"
I'd go, "Yes!"
One second, let me turn this crank on my chest
and switch which direction my esophagus is.
Like an iPhone game.
Exactly.
I think that we should go to Olive Garden.
I would love to.
We should go company lunch. I'm trying to think where the closest one is. There is one. No, wrong.
There is one only 20 minutes away up north in Woodside. I'm down. I love Olive Garden. One of my favorite locations.
We can go and get the endless breadsticks. I only went that one time.
He only went that one time and he got yelled at because they thought he brought methadone in. Oh, yeah.
yeah, well we'll see
they gave him a sample lemonade.
There's a funniest thing ever. They gave him a sample pink lemonade at like at
the entrance and then we sat down and we're sitting there and he's got this
little cup with a pink liquid in it and the waitress comes up and she's like
hey everybody you, but you can't not bring that shit in here
and to her credit. I was you know long haired, not shave probably beard down my
neck, probably had a limit, a green military jacket, hadn't slept in day
yeah
frayed clothing yeah and also probably world weary stare
fiat
I know you work for I know you serve this country, but you cannot do that. It
was literally the most insane. She changed her accent. She changed
every way she got so and then I was like no. This is a sample you give it to
through the door and she's like oh, I'm so sorry. They just bring that stuff in
here all the time. She just yeah. It was next to a methadone clean it cleanly
the little neck. I don't think it was I must have been it was no. Is that like
the mall and like like south of in that like big shopping center with the movie
theater? So I where is that? I don't remember south of Boston, the downtown
somewhere in my brain. I think that like they'd somehow would remember me at a
different location. I'm like this is my free pass to bring in methadone in with
methadone they like you can't bring that here like no. I remember last time it's
pink lemonade. It is lemonade. Remember like last time. I don't even, I don't
even know methadone was pink. I don't think it, I have no idea what methadone
looks like. I couldn't tell you what it looks like. But I guess this is a
fucking lady knew. Yeah, I guess it's pink lemonade. Yeah. I mean. Speaking of,
have you had this new, Kim Kardashian has partnered with Aluhia Energy or
whatever the fuck it's called. She has the Kim Aid and it is the, I had it last
night I drank like 400 milligrams of caffeine before I went. I did that show
last night and I don't know why I was just really tired. Yeah, I didn't sleep
good and I that's the guy the craziest I've ever felt in my entire life. It was
on I was up on stage and I was just like doing donuts with my feet on stage just
walking around. So I was doing donuts dude. You had a you had a full panic
attack at the stand. I did. I did. I really did. It was crazy drink caffeine.
No, no, no, no. And I had three beers to try and cancel it out, but it did not
work.
Yeah. You think beer is an anti caffeine, but it actually will charge you. It's
a make you like doodle. It just makes you go like Chris Farley doodle kind of
thing instead of like what is hold on what
no one knows doodle God. Yeah, doodle God. You know, play doodle God. It's a
game where you combine things. You mean it's not that much doodling, though.
Well, no, the doodling is this that it's a it's a game that's in two
dimensions. Yeah, you played doodle. No, I haven't played doodle. God, you
wrote you up on the computer. You never played doodle. Basically, you can
get it. It's the best shit ever. You can combine game of all time. Wait,
didn't we play this on your we put this on your TV? It's with your brother.
Yeah, okay. Yeah, we played it. We played it on my mom's fucking TV. Now I
remember it. Yeah, shit's fun as fuck. It's great. Yeah, we were coming up with
what's wind mixed with rocks? Yeah. Oh, sand. Holy shit, that's amazing. Yeah.
Turn it off. Wait, he just... Shut it off, 'cause I'm gonna sit there. Turn it
off. You can't show us that you're playing it. Put it on a different monitor
if you're gonna do that. Just play it on your phone. Yeah. It's okay, we don't
mind.
We should... Yeah, you can't combine beer and caffeine. It does make you go
crazy. That's why they outlawed Four Locos. Yeah. 'Cause it was turning... You
That shit was turning Orange County into the Wild Wild West.
It already was.
With the Four Locos.
Orange County is like Huntington Beach and stuff, right?
Yeah.
Four Loco is turning that shit into...
I don't think it was Four Loco.
I think it was maybe the high skinhead population.
No, no, no.
People were doing Wild West duels with...
That's actually the scariest thought in the world is a bunch of Huntington Beach skinheads
jacked up on Four Locos.
Did you guys see that picture that somebody posted of like a guy with
really shitty line tattoos, like clearly a gay guy with like bad line work
tattoos? The doodles, the paper clip. And they were like,
"Okay, so this guy's a Nazi," and like 'cause he has like something that looks
like a black sun, but it's clearly, it's clear that he just is like
just a guy who saw like four tattoos on Instagram and thought they were cool,
and just put a bunch of lines all over his body. But they are pretty
very fortunate because one of them does look kind of like two S's. Oh,
but they're just like bad. Like that is it. Oh, wait, wait, wait, girl tattoo.
Yeah, yeah, the guy, the guy who has like they called them, they're like,
how are you going to be a Nazi and a pansexual? Yeah, yeah, it's like so I
mean, I don't know if that person like because they had, they had a thing
about they had a room on their chest. What it was, what it was. No, the
thing about the thing about Nordic ruins and the thing about SS bolts and the
thing about the black sun and the swastika is that if you are just
drawing lines, you're going to make one by accident. Yeah, and I remember like a
couple of years ago when you're just kind of
a man whose brain is cloistered from the world and you're drawing straight lines
on your body, you will eventually end up definitely, and I think a lot of I
think a lot of people who like try to find these these people from like
January six or whatever and be like, Oh, my God, they had a Nazi tattoo. They
don't realize that 90% of people get tattoos because they think they look
school and that is the end of their thought process.
Yeah. I would say that that is 95% of people.
There's no... If you research your tattoos before you get them...
All of them have some bad thing that is why they started that way.
Exactly.
They've all been used in some crazy way.
Right.
And that was so funny when people would find people and be like, "Oh, this firefighter
has a Nazi crop or whatever."
I mean, it's happened to me.
every yeah yeah exactly yeah yeah spider web, but it's so fucking funny, but that
was just that one was making me laugh that he just got like tattoos that like
aunts get. I love seeing the I look at the
tattoo removal tips sub reddit. It's so funny to see the stuff that people want
to get covered up or people yeah people accidentally get like dicks and and
accidentally yeah they'll like get a design that they don't like either. They
they don't realize they ask for design and then they don't realize it or the
artist would just be really bad and they'll like somehow make it look like a
penis and yeah, it happens so much on the it's so fine. I seen this thing with
like swat like also another really good. Another really good resource for that is
the the people who get blood born tattoos, the game. Oh yeah, they get they
always get the gayest fucking tattoos where they just get like symbol like
video game tattoos already suck, but the blood born one suck because there did
people get them giant on their form, a huge like logo of the game, but they'll
also get people I've seen it like three or four times people will get like
there's like runes in the game to give you powers and one of the runes is
literally like a swastika, but with curves instead of corners. Oh, like it's
just people like three or four people. They're like no. I just got all the
runes from the games and they just have like a bunch of runes and like two of
them are just swastikas with curvy lines and all the comments are like
arguing over be some people being like no it's different. No one would make
mistake that for a swastika. It's curvy and everyone's like come on right.
I've seen the funniest cover up.
I think John posted it somewhere.
It was like a right here.
Memoriam for mom.
Covered up all Pokemon.
All the ghost Pokemon.
Could you clearly see it through?
It's like, it's like, it's like
Phantump and like
Capagrigis.
Have I ever told you about?
The original tattoo was like, like
"Rest in peace, Mom." And then it just--
Wait, he covered up his mom with Pokemon.
And it was Ghost Likes.
That is crazy.
Did I ever tell you guys about my friend's mom? I won't say who it is,
but you guys know his mom has a tattoo to honor her husband.
I don't think I've said it on the podcast, but she has a tattoo to honor her husband,
husband and it says his name rain over me and it's a bunch of rain drops all
over before and it looks like it's just come on or
like black and gray, just like come drops all over. Oh my God, I can't wait
to have a tattoo that I that I have to get covered up for some reason yeah
before because like not one that I'm like oh this looks lame. I don't like
this. I want to I want I want to eventually have something happen where
It's one of the tattoos I already have. I need to get it covered up and it
results in the worst looking thing of all time. I hope they never make tribal
some kind of hate symbol. Yeah. 'Cause I need more tribal tats, man. They're
just... You wanna get more tribal tats? I literally wanna be fully covered in
tribal tats. It's not a hate symbol, but there is the people who say you can't
get tribal tattoos 'cause you're not a part of that tribe. Tell me what tribe
about that. That was that's the slip. Not
right.
Yeah, that does look like the slip. Not
yeah, come on. Just realizing that now
that's actually so sick. Yeah, that is
so sick.
I want to get I want to get old English
words. Tom and Jerry on my stat. I
still think you should do that. I just
I think I think one of us has to get a
fucking tummy rocker. So I do. I will
I'm think I will next year. Probably
Tom and Jerry tell me rockers
like
cartoon
Friday
teaching
I've been thinking yeah. I
terrible tell me rock. Yeah, I want I want to stomach to do so. I would
honestly get swag yeah. I was wagging. I thought about all these man. I really I
really need one or just like a name of like somebody I don't know. It's like
George Bush Nathan across my belly.
Yeah,
wait getting ticklish done like a do not resuscitate
ticklish
man to be
you should get I'm allergic to carrots rock. Yeah, that's right on here as a
medical tattoo or maybe yeah, like I get the word carrots tattooed across my
belly so that people know. Oh yeah, allergic to cringe, allergic to cringe,
allergic to cringe. My girlfriend just got a Tom and Jerry tattoo. I just
remember. I'm getting a Tom and Jerry tattoo at the end of the month. Yeah,
you're copying my girlfriend. No, he's copying my girl. I think you're both
copying your girl, your girlfriend. You're both copying
Anna Barbera. Oh, yeah. Oh, I'm not copying. I'm paying homage.
Well, pay him some money. I didn't copy. I didn't copy my girlfriend. Buddy
homage. Don't pay the rent. Homage. Don't keep the lights on brother. They
just had a barbarous struggling movie. They don't they're fine. I don't think
that movie did very well. The movie was one of the most incredibly high
grossing movies of 2020. That's true. Well, no movies came out in 2020. Well,
buddy, the adventures of Tom and Jerry. I would love to introduce you to a
little movie called The Lovebirds. What was it? It's not. The Lovebirds. Shang
Chi. Shang Chi. Shang Chi. Godzilla vs Kong.
Zack Snyder's Justice League.
Every movie came out in 2020, oh yeah. And we gonna go back to the movies.
We're sitting in the theater and eating the popcorn and then I'm gonna go get
more or oh and then I put them in my shit and then I go take a shit and look at
tits on my phone in the bathroom looking at porn on reddit and then I'm gonna
make fucking jazz in the sink I'm gonna eat my own crap no at the movie I'm
gonna eat my own crap at that I got a robotic now that you're getting a war
that is actually I'm stealing the flow from the song Zelda are by Devon the
dude. Zelda. Zelda R. It's a song about Devon the dude meeting an alien and
smoking the weed with him. Would you guys smoking the weed? Would y'all go that hard for
that bitch Zelda? No. Link is doing so much shit. You better stop and listen.
You better stop and listen. I can't believe that she gets the legend. And she dresses up like a ho.
She gets the legend because Link is actually destined to do that. But I don't
I'd be like, "Fuck you, fate."
Yeah, I'm gonna watch some TV.
Fuck you, fat Zelda. Lose some weight.
Yeah. Well, Sheik is actually...
Sheik is a boy.
She got no tits, no ass.
We need to get Zelda.
We need to feed her some
fucking goblin meat. We gotta get Zelda
a BBL. I'd be down.
She's like 13. A big legend.
Zelda is not, no, Link is 13. Zelda is
a full grown woman. Is like 100,000
years old or some shit. I think they both are.
Are they both 13?
37.
Zero years old.
Wait.
Wait, what the hell?
Six years old.
I thought that they were both.
Oh, no, that's the age of the Legend of Zelda.
How does the character Zelda go down?
They they are.
Well, OK, there's child.
Well, you know, there's child Zelda and then there's adult Zelda.
Exactly right.
And adult Zelda is 16 years old.
Wait, no.
Wait, this is why she look like that.
Well, we didn't know that.
I didn't play the games, dude. I don't know what I'm talking.
Those games are trash and they're the worst games ever developed.
You think the new Zelda games are trash?
Yep. They're actually fun as fuck. You're crazy.
No, I thought the new one was bad. I thought it was mid.
I thought it was mid. That's right. It's mid.
The first one was fire.
The first one was mid too.
You're stupid.
The first one was fun, but yet mid.
I like Majora's Mask.
I never played any other ones. I'm going to get a Majora's Mask tattoo.
Don't do that, man.
No, please don't get a video game tattoo.
Please, for the love of God, bro.
the majority mask your drop. I'm going to get the bio shock logo on my chest.
That would be sick. That's a
daddy like to get one of those tattoos where it's like he's ripping out
that'd be so
video game tattoos or they really truly are the most corny thing. I'm going to
get it just a giant. I need to get a giant Mario on my base. I need to get
every getting a tattoo of Mario. I actually like that photo realistic new
Super Mario Bros. Mar yeah, I kind of like
I kind of like a like a two two and a half D like like Mario portrait or
something on your leg bit Mario. That'd be so funny. That was going to get a
screenshot from a video game. Yeah,
yeah,
exact
right here. Yeah, just like a person. We're like, why do you have Mario over
your heart?
I don't know, man. Why do you have elephant Mario in your heart? I can't
believe they made this Mario. They didn't make him yet. He's not out yet.
The whole... What are you talking about? His game hasn't come out yet. What
game is this? The whole belly. There's a new one that is coming out. It's coming
out for Nintendo Switch. Getting the whole belly, the Majora's Mask.
Yeah. Yeah, the entire... The whole entire belly. You should get a
Crang tattoo like cranks and you're crying from ten year teenage mutant ninja
turtle crying crying.
Refrain crane.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
I got bored.
You got bored of me telling you that you should get bored of him talking to you
bored.
Shut up.
Okay.
Well, what do you want to don't put your that's tired.
That's not bored.
It's not the same thing.
Why are you holding that like that?
I don't know, but I'm trying to sleep.
Am I being a copycat or am I being a copycat?
You are being a copycat.
Wait, you two just copied each other.
Wait, hold on.
Wait, what's the whole...
Warning, you will be derezzed.
Yeah, what does derezzed mean?
Derezzed...
resolution or something?
Oh, ok. Derezzed means
dead. Yeah, it means dead for
a computer. Derezzed is the
Daft Punk song. Yeah.
That one go hard as fuck on that
soundtrack. I think Daft Punk is made as well. Whoa, that's actually crazy.
That's actually crazy of you. I don't give a fuck about dancing. I don't care
about dancing. I love dancing. I love dancing. I like that was always the
thing where my friend, some of my friends were into it in school and I was
in like middle school. I was like, I didn't know anyone that was into it, but
I assumed I just thought of it as like music from commercials and stuff.
Discovery is yeah. I didn't get into them till like two years ago. I mean, I
All their albums are sick.
That song Superheroes, where it's just the Barry Manilow sample, that one is fire.
The one with Get Lucky is sick too.
Get Lucky, that's actually a good album.
Yeah, I know.
That was the only one I listened to.
That one's good.
That one came out when we were in high school.
When I was in high school, when that came out, we went to this party and it was a high
school party.
Fuck!
With girls?
It was my friend Tyler's going away party.
Where was he going?
Military school?
We got smoked weed and got in trouble?
Yeah, probably.
Oh, shit!
But, oh yeah.
Instrument.
Wait, he's making a Daft Punk song?
We like went to this party, somebody had, you remember they had Xbox music or Zune music
on the Xbox?
Yeah.
This, no, he didn't tell us his, like, he went upstairs and then like everyone was downstairs.
The Xbox is on, he didn't log in, so somebody just put music on, but then it was like, they
They played "Get Lucky" but then it was like a 30 second free sample snippet.
But it looped for like 5 minutes.
I was fucked up and I was like, "Can somebody shut the fucking song off?"
I asked them to shut it off because it was...
Can you imagine you're in a high school party basement?
Oh yeah!
as a
hold on. Imagine you're at a party, though, but they keep playing. It's this
it fades out and then it goes back in. So it's like
they're up
dude. Do you have any more smear enough? Isis bro? That song is already really
annoying. Yeah, so they hear just the one part right there. I understand what
happened. I don't I don't think anybody's confused. Yeah, we should beer bong
something you guys my hold on let's Bob for apples bro. Wait, I don't have any
dude. Let's do a cake walk.
High school's amazing bro. You got you open the door to someone's better and
someone sitting there like blowing the party blowers.
Wait, let's get under that big, multi colored tarp
bro
there. He just he just brought a skip it there.
Derek's going to college bro. We're thinking about doing a gymnastics part
the foam pit son. Wait, I'm bringing grips. We're about to bounce that shit
off of a shit into each other's mouths dude.
My girlfriend got iced the other day at work. I did not think that that still happened.
What other day when?
Iced? When you get Smirnoff iced?
Oh, the thing where they hide the Smirnoff.
Yeah, some old person told me about this recently.
Yeah, that was a thing that my cousin was doing.
They used to do that back in the 40s I think.
Yeah.
I never heard of that.
Yeah, they never did that.
Yeah, it was like in the 20s, 30s, and 40s.
It was back in the Roaring 20s.
Apparently people used to get Smirnoff iced, which means you hide a Smirnoff ice somewhere
somewhere and whoever finds it has to drink it.
Which these days, I would do this with probably water.
Nowadays, they do it.
Or an app.
You have to hide an app and you have to die.
You have to open it.
Huh?
They would do it nowadays with Prime.
KSI and Logan Paul probably would.
You would get Primed.
But why don't we do that more?
Because that kind of thing is funny.
Yeah.
Hiding things and finding them.
But I do not like smearing off ices.
We should start icing each other.
No.
I don't wish to do that.
We're going to start icing each other.
I don't like smearing off ices though.
You guys, be prepared to get icing.
We should Colt 45 each other. A 40 ounce of malt liquor.
We haven't done an Edward 40 hands episode.
Because he wouldn't be able to use the soundboard.
Well, we could have...
He had 40s on his hands?
He could have both.
Also, I would not survive that.
Edward, that's not that great.
I wouldn't survive it.
I would take his hand, right?
One 40 right here.
Okay.
One right here.
Well, that's Edward 40 arm.
Edward 40 arm.
That's Edward 80 arm.
Edward 80 arms. The last time I drank more than one beer I was hungover for the whole
day the next day. You have a hummingbird's liver. I just don't drink and I'm proud of
it. It makes me better. It makes you worse at drinking. But you know what? There goes
his beer we just bought. Oh yeah. Well I don't really need to go through Caleb for it because
Julio like I said he begs me to come on almost every week. I'm like dude that's your thing
I don't really want to be. I don't want to like a coach on that. He doesn't beg you on
to pick him on. The first few weeks he was obsessed with me coming on. He wouldn't stop
asking me. He's obsessed with you. Well, but I still don't want to go on. I don't want
to go on Monster Crazy. Oh, you don't have much time left and it's impossible for you
to do so. Yeah, well, I don't want to go on. In fact, it's impossible for you to do so.
It's impossible for you to go on Beers We Drink, even though I know tons. It would be.
The problem is that it is possible, but I'm just saying no. No, it's really not possible.
It is my new as the my new solo podcast. I mean the one at that time when you
were gone, who we wanted me to know so bad. No, he didn't. Yeah, he did. He
told me he was planning a prank on you. No, no, and he was gonna get he was
gonna get you that he was playing a prank on you. So you don't even care.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
have you call in and then he was just not going to not answer or maybe get all of
your ex-girlfriends on the zoom call and they were all going to laugh at your
body. Yeah. Well, the funny thing is I said no, so I wouldn't even have fallen
for the prank, but which it wasn't. So Julio just had to have sex with all the
ex-girlfriends instead. Okay. He had cyber sex. All of them. Every last one.
Every last one. All right. Well, no one gives a shit about my new solo podcast
that I started writing. It's a narrative story podcast called Patrick and the Jitterbugs
and it's about me and my world famous band and how we toured the world and then there
was some infighting in the band and it's basically a docuseries about how me and the other jitterbugs
don't talk but we're going to reunite for one final show.
Didn't Blowback already do that?
No.
I'm pretty sure that was their last season.
That was like the last season of Blowback.
Blowback did not cover Patrick and the Jitterbugs.
Yeah it was.
They literally did.
Patrick and the Jitterbugs. There's like giant explosion sound radio sound.
You guys remember the Jitterbugs, right? Yeah. Well, so do we.
Blowback season five. Season five, Patrick and the Jitterbugs.
All right. All right. Oh, that's time. Let's plug our brand new upcoming show, guys.
October 20th at Little Field in Brooklyn, 635 Sackett Street. We are
doing another World's Biggest Army. A new sketch show. A whole new sketch
show that we have writing. Underworld's Biggest Mummy, Port of Skull,
Halloween City. It's a parody of the first show's name. But the sketches
won't be parodies of the first show's sketches. There'll be funny sketches
on there that will stand on their own whether or not you went to the other
one exactly probably will do probably one thing to parody is a parody of the
last show for us. Not every sketch has to be for you. In fact, most of them are
for us. Most of them are. I mean, really, really, really. And of them only
make you're just you go to this show to give us a com slash shows and we don't
care if you laugh or not. Go to this website right now and you can care about
is the money by a ticket. Wow, there it is. Uh huh. Oh, and then I am opening
for
But I will be doing a funny new character.
Holy shit.
Alright.
I'm bringing character stuff back.
Bye bye my friends.
Bye.
[BLANK_AUDIO]