(music)
Big clap.
You do sound like Bruno Mars with all the high voice.
(music)
Whoa.
Is that Bruno Mars that sings that?
They might say hey, they might say hi.
But they might wonder who might be died. Who might gonna die? They got
nothing. They might say hey, they might say hi. I'm getting it. You might say
hey, and I might say hi, but we never were, or not. You might say hi, and I
might say hey, but we never worry about what they say.
Yeah.
Because they got nothing on you, nothing on you, babe.
Nothing on you.
That's Bruno Mars featuring Travi McCoy.
I remember the nothing on you part of that song.
I remember hearing that.
I never paid attention enough to it to realize I was talking about saying hey and hi.
Is it Travi McCoy or is it Bob?
Oh, I think it's Bob.
I think that one is Bob, actually.
Yeah.
That's so funny to make that song.
Pretty much all of Bob's career is just like magic by Bruno Mars, that song, like the most
poppy bullshit and then he's like Bruno Mars or magic by by B. O. B. with
rivers Cuomo and then he's immediately like the earth is flat. Everything has a
global conspiracy. Hidden Valley. It wasn't it took him a while to get the
hidden Valley. The hidden Valley is actually in Africa. This is a theory
that me and Patrick have been working on guys. They're trying to hide it from
you. They're saying white people and they're saying white people invented
ranch. No, it's not white. No, no, no, no. Hidden Valley has is a valley. I mean
it's hidden because it uses Wakanda technology to have a hidden completely
screen around guys. Open your fucking eyes. Ranch dressing was invented in
Africa. Yeah.
Ranch dressing. Think about it. Ranch. That's the stupidest thing we've ever
said.
Ranch.
It's the stupidest fucking thing we've ever said. Dressing. Black guys are good
invented dressing better than white guys. You think a white guy invented
dressing you are actually stupid,
just my theory yeah, but that's just a theory, a theory theory. Do you remember
that when
when when B. O. B. Went flat earth crazy whenever that was I remember it like
the day my
being like okay. So B O B is literally a Nazi yeah
really. What is this? They're like well, don't you realize that a lot of
flat earth theorem theorists are actually originally Nazis yeah. I mean
that is
a Nazi, not flat earth actually now that I'm thinking about it, they like, but
that was that was what hollow earth. Oh, that's what people are all earth.
I just made up a big. There was a theory that young thug had a new earth that
the earth is tall. He had he he said you've never seen the video where he
says they discovered a new earth. It's exactly the same as this earth. It's
twice the
everyone
is two times this and I'm from there way. That means that you've never seen
it. No, I've never seen that means he's a little as you are yeah. That means
all tall earth is a theory. I just came up with where the earth is a cylinder
planet man. Yeah, he's from new earth
Whoa. And it's in French?
It's the same as this Earth.
It's Earth though. It looks identical.
Everything is the same.
You ain't heard of that yet?
It's ten times bigger than Earth.
It's another Earth they just found.
It looks just like Earth though.
So they call it Earth. I'm probably from there.
I don't think I'm from here.
This.
That's so sick, man.
Ten times bigger.
ten times. He's definitely not from a place ten times bigger. I don't think
he's a big guy. No, no, no remember that article that came out a couple not a
couple, maybe ten years ago, this point where it was like some reporter follows
him around and he doesn't eat yeah. That was like
he's like he gets eat only eats out of vending machines and I was two cheetos
and be like oh, I'm full and then well that was that also the same article
where they're like they when they followed him around. They were like when
he goes into the recording booth. He doesn't write any of his lyrics down. He
draws pictures yeah,
years, like he would look at this picture of white Goku that Patrick made and he
might say something about some fruit.
White Goku.
No, I'm guessing the picture.
I feel like white Goku.
Because how do you draw?
I'm in your city, call it Roku.
Oh shit, wait, that was actually nice.
Roku city when the Goku hit me.
Godzilla.
Watching ThrillerCon.
He wouldn't say that.
Watching Thriller on YouTube.
You know I'm in a bad mood.
He has to be mad disrespectful.
Why do you think you can come in here in the middle of the episode and defend a
rapper? When you normally won't even answer a question.
Right. Well, because we asked him questions and then you don't say anything.
We pissed him the fuck off by saying something rude. That's disrespectful.
See, he's got to defend his man. Wait, are you YSL? He is. Yeah. Oh my God.
So are you in trouble right now? Yeah. Shouldn't you be in some kind of...
Yeah, 100%. Yeah. Oh shit. I guess that makes some sense. Yeah, I would love to
be eclectic, but I just don't have it in me. No, you mean eccentric. Yeah, yeah, I
would love to be eccentric, but I just don't have it. I mean, maybe that's kind
of one of my only time you're dressed eclectically right now. Some people,
some people would think that I mean, if you're trying to be eccentric, right? If
I don't think eccentric people know they're eccentric, do I look like I sell
most eccentric people really know they're eccentric and really are kind of
of milking it. Yeah, I do. We're their cat. I glasses, dude. These people who
do these house tours, yeah, where they're walking around their houses,
forty five different fucking colors and they have like you'll see animals
everywhere. Shut up. You'll be walking around, especially in New York. You'll
be like walking around. You'll see some guy. It's like, okay, buddy, I get it.
You got you got the long beard. You got the ragged clothes. You're walking
around like, yes, dude. Oh, I'm tired of these eccentrics. These eccentric
hipsters in Brooklyn. I hate these eccentric hipsters. They walk around
instead of a shirt, they're wearing a big drum instead of shoes, they're
wearing two pedals instead of lipstick, they have a harmonica and then instead
of just normal gloves, they have two trombones. Some of them are golden men.
I'm tired. What is? Yeah, exactly. The hipsters who walk around as gold. Oh,
wait, I'm gold. Yeah, wait. Oh, look at me. I made a silver and I don't
move at all. Yeah. What the fuck are you doing? I just sit here and
then somebody tries to touch me and I stand up. That's when I stand up.
Oh, I think moving and being a normal color is mainstream, so I will do this
because I'll be completely silver. I will be a silver unmoving hipster and
then when they do move it's like hey, what are you moving at twelve frames
for twelve frames per second?
What do you even do you're doing? You know what other you know what other
eccentric hipsters I hate what like like oh look at me. I'm wearing a polo
shirt with a with a golden M on and I stand behind this counter. Oh, don't
even get me back here. I'm on the other side of this counter from you. Yeah,
I come over this everybody who's main stream sits on that side, but I sit on
the behind side of the food rest.
I'm so
a hipster. I sit behind the cash register and set up in front of it and
I get to press the button and I don't even love pressing the but I don't even
order the food. I don't even food is to mainstream. You order the food. I'm too
cool to order food. I stand there and listen to you with no expression while
the order yours and then I'll say, okay, okay, yeah, sure, that'll be right out.
Yeah, sure, I'll get that for you. What kind of soda?
That is so fucking hipster. They say, "And what kind of soda?" They're so obsessed
with fucking being taste makers and trendsetters that they're literally always
asking people, "What kind of soda do you want? What food are you gonna eat?"
It's like, "Chill out. Just think about yourself. It doesn't matter what I
like or I'm gonna get." 'Cause you know what they're gonna say? Do you wanna
make that a large for an extra 60 cents? What does that mean,
you freaking hipster? You know what they're gonna say if you say, "I like
They're gonna go like, "Well, Coke's okay, but I just don't like the fan base of Coke."
Exactly.
"I just don't like the fan base of Sprite."
Let's not get ahead of ourselves here.
Let's not get into that.
Let's not get into sodas.
What?
Let's not talk about sodas.
I'm tired of talking about it.
Why?
What?
I'm tired of it all week.
Everyone's like, "You have to promote sodas.
Oh, you played Faygo."
I'm done.
In the E1 original production?
They keep Charles.
Charles is a fucking monster. He keeps berating me.
He's berating me.
He kind of just steamrolled our whole hipster thing.
We had a really, that was probably the best thing we've had.
We were like right on the precipice.
We were not on the precipice.
That's true. We were on a breakneck downhill sleigh ride. It was incredible.
It was North Pole, Grinch, Hart Grove.
I'm sorry. I'm going through a lot this week.
We were on our way to a finale.
I am going through a fucking lot this week.
We were on our way to a jet plane pentagon finale on our Grinch sleigh.
but this was about to be like the thing that popped for us. We were popping. We
were popping and we were hitting top forty and you just fucking say you don't
talk about sodas because I did a podcast this week. I got to
I had to use my stress toy. This is your stress toy. I dismembered a dismembered
arm.
I want to dismember your member. I don't want to dismember this at all. No, no,
no, no, no, I don't want to remember. This is something I never need to member
again. Speaking of man, these member berries are funny as fuck. I've been getting back
into the member berries. These member berries are amazing. I love them. I wish they kept
going with the member berries. Where did they go? They just did them for like two seasons.
But guys, bring these member berries back and they can go. Member. So if they're off
the show, if they're off of South Park, can we have them here? What? So they're off of
South Park now. Oh, in fact, they're walking in right now. Yeah. Can you, Jubio, just get
like a PNG of the member berries and just put it right here. Could you just edit
away the background of like 50 member berries real quick? Yeah, and just put
all the member berries right in front of the table. Scatter them all around the
entire screen. Make them animated. If you can animate them, and preferably in
three dimensions. Yeah. Here we go. Okay, we got a PNG of the member berries.
Okay. Yeah, so the member berries, they're in studio. Yeah. They're about
to be here very, very soon. Don't save it as an HTML. He's just trying his
artist. It's a way. I don't know if that'll if that'll work. Let's see if we
can get a different file here. Yeah, let's get a new type of fun. Maybe you
got to get like a P and JPEG is not going to be good. JPEG is not a loss.
It's okay. It doesn't need to be lost. It needs to be transparent, though.
Fine with loss. You're fine with loss. I deal with loss. It's a part of human
life and when listen, when you when you lose loss, you become something like a
necromancer. I hate loss. I agree, man. That's honestly that leads you down a
path not that far away from being hit. Fuck loss and fuck grief. If you're
grieving right now, if you're grieving, fuck you. Alright, Charlie, Chuckie,
Chuckie Brown. He says good grief. He likes grief. He thinks it's good. He
doesn't like... He says good grief sarcastically. Yeah, 'cause he... I mean,
I will admit that he wallows. He said... Yeah. He goes, "Oh, good grief." I
I thought he likes it.
No, he doesn't like grief, you fucking asshole.
He's grieving.
He's grieving when he says it.
No, he's wallowing in misery.
Yeah.
He likes it.
He's calling it good.
Which sin would he be?
Did you see this video?
It's not a sin.
This video of these two Filipino guys with a podcast, and they're sitting there, and
he's like, "Did you know that all of the holidays equal every single one of the seven deadly
deadly sins.
What was their argument for that? Their argument was Valentine's Day is lust.
Christmas is greed. Thanksgiving is gluttony. St. Patrick's Day is
sloth.
You got wrath left. You got envy and you got pride. Wrath is angry day. Pride is
fourth of July July
envy envy is also valentine's day
also. No, it would be Christmas. I don't even know that was really, but it can be
both yeah yeah. Well, then why can't valentine's day? Two things can be true
at the same time. My friend, I honestly think there's space for every sin on
every holiday. Yeah, well, you know what about you know what? Let's make some
more since wait. I mean yeah. Well, the argument is how we seven deadly ones
right seven deadly sins
Buddy, let's add seven more.
Okay, where would you start with that?
Okay, so the seven more deadly sins.
Deadlier?
Deadlier sins.
Which would be?
For the modern era.
Okay.
Being...
Being?
Being a hipster.
Being a hipster? Okay.
Go back to the center.
We're already way past that.
You're the one who Matrix yanked us out of that.
Matrix yanking?
number two. No, that's a sin. I was the matrix Yankee. I was falling asleep the
other night falling asleep. Wait, actually, I was doing that as well. Twin
my twin, that's me and my twin in him. I was falling asleep the other night and I
was thinking about how good it probably feels to be in some kind of alien goo
farm. Yeah, be like sliding down a very long tube forever. I was like I think
that I would actually really enjoy you. You're thinking of gun. If I was
abducted and want to be gunged well, but I want to be controlled by a higher
being in the gun. You want to get an avi positive or egg in you yeah, so if I
was like if I said you woke up and I was being abducted and I was sliding
through a tube into a UFO. I really think I would enjoy that feeling. I
feel like it would be very comforting. Did you guys like to see that movie
fire in the sky? No, that was you should watch them. That's a good movie with
the it has the it's the alien abduction scene where they're like doing they put
milk in the guy's mouth. They put milk in it. Dude, I would just drink it.
How are you talking about bro? It's something like that's similar to that,
but it's good. So this is a movie you made up. Yeah, it's really it's a
nasty alien. I just think that you should you'd like that scene. Can you
roll that clip? No, we don't need to see this clip. I don't see it, but he
didn't watch the clip on your own time. But anyway, yeah, I just think that
that a lot everyone says that's the most horrifically horrible abduction scene,
I think it could feel pretty good to have a little fire all over your face.
Basically, nobody. Yeah, empty movie with no one.
That is a good idea. Actually, it's a pretty boring movie, except for the one
part where they're in an alien spaceship and there's no gravity. So they're like
jumping around and flying around and they get getting surgeried. I just
realized how to end this whole actors writers strike guys. Yeah, movie with
nobody in it. And completely empty movie with nobody in it and just keeps
changing scenes. Just different pictures. That's called a documentary.
No, no, no. It would be like pictures of... So you can't have actors, so it would be pictures
of like animals walking around.
Right, a document.
But isn't it...
Close-ups about them like mating and stuff, and it would be like a movie with nobody in
it.
Is it the producer strike or the people are striking against producers because then that's
a movie that would be made by producers?
That's what I mean is they can just keep making movies.
Right, no, I don't think the producers are on strike right now.
Wait, why...
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
How come these animals aren't going on strike? That's actually a really good point. And these
nature doc... Because they can... Everybody likes nature documentaries. They do very well.
They could do a March of the Penguins right now.
Also, why aren't the directors on strike?
They have a whole group.
Isn't every guild on strike right now?
Isn't everybody that has music videos to make?
What?
Isn't every guild on strike?
I think it's just the actors and the writers.
I think the directors get to do whatever they want.
You know what guild I think should go on strike?
The Thieves Guild.
Yeah.
Stop pig-pocketing me just because I'm walking through the village, man.
You're stealing out of my barrel.
You've got to get that Italian lady to follow you around.
You're stealing out of my fucking barrel.
Leave my barrel alone.
You seen this lady?
coins on top of that. Who? Attencion pickpocket. No. Have you seen her? No. This little Italian
lady runs around Italy and just like. How little? Screams. She's like. Stop. She's that
small? That small. How many feet is that? She runs up to people and just screams. Attencion
pickpocket. She runs up to people. She runs up to active pickpockets. Oh. And she stops
them and films them with her phone. I think that I would be a pretty decent pickpocket.
Yeah? Well, I can feel you in my pocket right now. That actually sounded so fucking sexual.
I can feel you in my pocket right now. What are you doing? Leave me alone. He just touched
my dick. I didn't touch his dick. He literally just reached down and reached in between my
legs. Stop! Okay, I can't even attempt to pickpocket? Do you guys feel like we are penis
penis friends penis for like well. You guys have seen my penis.
Okay, I know what I mean. I know what you mean like I went to the I went to I
know exactly no. I do know I went to the bathhouse last night. I think we're
really where I think we honestly have been for years and years been completely
teetering on the precipice. Well, I broke the seal. I broke the seal on the show.
Yeah, that was three years in. You showed us. You don't even remember this.
You don't remember. I showed you the photo picture of his penis in his hand.
so that was like not really. It wasn't what are you talking about? There's also
a picture that was all of my penis.
What do you mean that was that was my whole thing like nothing there, you
know yeah, it's just kind of boring, but I went I went to the bath house with
somebody last night, a friend of mine and I got it was Brian. I got change in
the locker room because I was like we're penis friends. I can look at my penis on
a he's not going to look, but he can be around my yeah, he's not going to yeah.
he can smell it. Of course, it's a locker room. Everybody's penis friends in a
locker room. He can feel the aura. Yeah. But then... Yeah, that's penis partners.
That's like penis business partners. It's not even friends. Yeah, that's like...
That's... If you're in a locker room... A fellow commuter. That's like you're
riding... That's the guy you ride the train next to every day. Yeah, exactly.
You can show him your penis on the train. I have seen...
I have seen some really, really big ones recently at movie theater urinals and
also at locker rooms. Oh, yeah, movie theaters. Movie theater urinals? There's
the movie theater downtown where the urinals are really, really close to each
other. I went in there and saw bottoms. They're really, really close to each
other. No, buddy, you saw fronts. And there's a
I saw many fronts, and I was sandwiched between, and there's no way you always
have to look at the guy's penis, because you're right, it's way too close, and
there's no divider. You can look forward. But my peripheral vision is picking up
information. Yeah. Right. I'm not, I do not have a cone. You need blinkers like
a horse. I need a dog cone, blinders. Yeah. Blinders. Blinkers.
they make
you should have done what me and Caleb did and had two different coffees and
energy drinks, but I was sitting there next to so little coffee this morning,
because I didn't feel like making it. I was saying
opened up next door. I was sandwiched between the biggest penis I've ever seen,
the smallest penis I've ever seen at that. I'm between the biggest and
smallest, and I was like this is nice, because this is me. I'm that means that
I'm medium, but I got my got my penis sandwiched between the biggest ball ever
seen the smallest ball I ever seen.
damn
one big one, one small one and they're sandwiched right now. My balls have
stopped growing. Yeah, finally mine stopped growing. I was like I think mine
got smaller. I think mine. I've also gotten smaller recently. Yeah, I think
it's maybe it's the weather. It's all them drinks. You guys are drinking right
now. Yeah, it's I put once I get when I get my first kidney stone strength, your
balls. Yeah, my first kidney stone is going to be like so horrifying,
especially you know that it'll be the first of many. Yeah.
Oh, you probably have one. You've probably had one for a long time.
You probably have a fully calcified kidney. I think I've passed a kidney
stone before. No, you know, no, no. You don't do that and not know.
There is a time... It hurts badly. There was a time where I went pee and
it hurt after. My cousin did that and it changed. It probably doesn't hurt
after. It hurt during. I feel like it probably hurts during and then you see
a stone. During and after. I didn't see a stone. Yeah. It probably hurts so
maybe the stone went back in have a lot of trouble. Yeah, my penis has been
hurting at random intervals. Recently, I've had pain in different parts of my
penis before. Yeah, yeah, due to different. I think it's somewhat normal.
Yeah, I think it's normal to have basically any type of stabbing pain
anywhere in your body for two to three weeks. Yeah, yeah, any longer than that
and you should probably see a telehealth professional. Yeah, you might want to go
to an urgent care where they don't take your insurance and then go home. Yeah,
and you walk in, you say, I don't have any insurance, but I need you to look at my
penis right now. You go in screaming, you throw you what you do is you throw your
ID in a plate like in a in a lock box that you have with you, throw the ID in
the lock box outside of it so that no one can get in, no one can break into it
and then you walk in and you say you just start screaming. So they have to
take you in as a John Doe. Oh, I see. Oh, why not just leave your ID at home? Why
do you have to put in a lock box and throw it out? Do you think they might
I notice you're throwing a lock box outside. No, no, no, no, they would not
investigate this. You go and pick up the lock box and take it. Why not just
leave? Well, if they pick up the lock box and take it, there's also an air
tag in it,
so you can go to their house. Get it. You know what you know what you can find
even easier than an air tag your house. I think that's all up for debate. Your
address. I think it's all up for debate, dude.
I'm going to air tag at my house. Do you think they would take me at the er if I
walked in and told and just said I'm going to just hold my breath. If you
don't take me
My little brother used to do that. Yeah, I wouldn't get its way. It's a kid. That
I mean,
that's what I'll do. I'll say I have a scab and I'm going to hold my breath
until you cover it with something
and they're going to go really funny, very funny. Okay, stop holding your
breath. Okay, stop holding your breath.
Admit this man right now. Yeah, I think that's how it would go. What you have
to do is you have a if you have a minor injury that you don't think they're
going to
push you up to the front of the line at the ER for you just have to break your
arm or your neck or something also.
You should just you got a sore throat, you want to get seen immediately, you
just kind of, oh, you won't take me? Yeah, exactly. How about now? I'll kill
myself. How about now? I'll fucking kill myself if you don't take me. You got to
walk in with, you got to slit your whole chest open. You know what you got to do.
Your heart's beating out and you walk in and you say, I need to be seen right
now, I have a sore throat. It's so annoying. And also, please can you close
shut us up. The health care industry in this country is so annoying because the
only way to get into these fucking ERs and these urgent cares, you gotta pull up
with a squad of, like, fine ass women and you gotta,
you gotta pull up in your best, you gotta be wearing, you gotta be wearing
Amiri jeans and, like, a Gucci shirt and you gotta be-,
you're standing in line, like, they're not gonna, they're not gonna pull you in-,
they ain't even gonna look at you if you walk in. They're not gonna pull you in
is your 10 deep with a squad of finance Instagram feed. If you pull up in the
faded glory, they're going to turn you around the door. They are not putting
you. You got no boundaries on bro. You got no boundaries on diamond supply.
Co. You got my diamond supply. Go. They will bring you in bro. Diamond supply.
Co. You think they will? I forgot about diamonds. I was singing the other day.
I saw a kid wearing that the other day. I was like, holy shit. Me and Neil
really wanted to buy like full diamond supply. Co. Young and reckless fits for
are that college show we did. That would have been so sick, dude. You're wearing like the
diamond supply coatees, the ones that had like the little tag right there. I looked on
eBay and I searched young and reckless shirts and it was a bunch of things that were like
$75 vintage 2015 young and reckless t-shirts. Dude, it's so funny. So awesome. Like the
reseller market is so stupid right now. It's going to like, once this recession fully hits,
it's going to be so funny. I don't think it's going to hit, man. You think it's just going
of bubbles going to keep growing and growing. I don't believe in bubbles. I'm not a child.
I think we're entering a golden age of prosperity. Interesting. Why does everything have to be
a bubble, man? Everyone's prospering and buying. When I close my eyes at night to go to sleep,
my soul flies high above my body and I can see this country and the world as if I'm playing
civilization. And it's all going all right. And I'm moving everything around for everybody.
Everything's all night long. Full green bars all around. The economy will be saved from
from putting it. I'm the economy will be saved from putting the word vintage
zoomies shirt,
VTG zoomies, two thousand and seventeen golf Wang. Yes, yeah, oh damn, I should
sell my vintage golf Wang shirts. Yeah, should do you have any? I think I don't
know if I had one yeah. I don't know what happened to it. I definitely don't
have the ones from twenty twelve actually would. So those would do pretty
well. I should check. Maybe it's at my dad's. I my girlfriend had one that had
My girlfriend has the, uh, the fucking from the, the shoes, like the golf
left floors that she never, she wore like one time.
Those would sell pretty well.
And then she also has like the corniest, like, it's like the golf
wing, like Trump Hitler shirt.
You guys think I could make you guys think I can make any money selling
my, uh, my five finger death punch shirt.
Yeah, actually, definitely.
You actually, dude, I don't know if I have that one either.
Yeah.
These kids, these kids nowadays, it's so fun. You see like kids wearing Jenko's and stuff
and like they're all wearing like the vintage Y2K shit. You can sell like a Slipknot shirt
for like probably like seven, depending on when it was from, you could probably sell
for like 75. Yeah. And all the, I'd see everyone always selling and buying all the Deftones
stuff too. Yeah. The Deftones shit is insane. Basically styling. I want to live in a world
where the most coolest and most expensive shirt is a white t-shirt. It is actually.
It still is. It can't beat a classic. It's called an APC, man. I want to be buying vintage white t-shirts.
I think that basically style and clothing is almost cyclical in nature.
Yeah, they almost have a relationship between each other where it's like this, like interlocking fingers.
Yeah, where I feel like stuff that used to be cool and then wasn't, it almost
comes back and it's cool again. Yeah, retro. Yeah. So like completely vintage. It's like
video games. It's like how Pac-Man came back into Smash Brothers. Pac-Man was my nephew's
favorite video game character for like too long. And then the Mario movie came out and
he moved on to that. But he was telling me stuff about Pac-Man I think I've never heard
in my life. There's a Pac-Man enemy. In five years, everybody's going to be rocking full
asbestos suits just covered in asbestos, breathing the shit out of it.
And asbestos in the middle of the summer.
We're not going retro.
BPA is coming back, guys. Get yourself a hot-ass plastic water bottle.
Leave your water bottle in the car, drink the plastic that comes, that melts out.
When are we going to be opening Depop and starting to see the listings pop up?
Vintage breastplate, vintage queer ass, vintage claditorial helmet.
Vintage queer ass?
They already got that on e-pop, man.
They got that in spades.
Vintage chain mail.
When are we going? When is the retro?
You can buy chain mail in there.
I've actually seen some people wearing chain mail.
I've definitely also seen people wearing chain mail.
Okay, then what about samurai outfits?
You know what else I saw? I saw people wearing chain mail.
I also saw people riding horses.
Yeah, what if someone pulls up...
Dude, what if in ten years somebody pulls up on you,
right, and they say, "What's up, what's up? Check it out.
I got the wheel on me."
a wheel one big wheel and yeah, big made of rock wheel and they're going to
our side. Check this shit out. Check this new wave. I'm on and they make a
fire right in front of you. If he was still alive right now, still love.
What if somebody pulls up with the aqueduct?
Oh my God, you got the aqueduct.
He got the
he got the wood and he pulled up with a whole last aqua duck. He got the
sundial on his wrist. Damn son damn you nice for that gag from Amish paradise
when he got the sundial on the wrist. Well, that's why Amish people are this.
Oh my God, they don't go far back enough, though, but I'm just people are
pulling up. They're saying check out the the four sided barn. We just raised.
he goes, damn checkers, new carriage, it's got two horse power. Oh, my God, he got
the two horse power buggy dude, God damn dude, you see, you see the Amish dudes
right, you you're like scoping out a like group of Amish people right, imagine
this, you're looking like you know how you see him at the bus. Sometimes you
see like the big Amish families, you'd be better not to be getting on that bus
boy. I know, I know you're not allowed, but you see like a group of Amish people
right? You're like like like six of them lined up, six of them lined up, one of
them, one of them is just wearing that rogue status to rob dear deck all over
gun print shirt. That'd be so sick. It's just like well, I've actually held to
get
spreading hype beastism in the Amish community like smallpox. Yeah,
giving them
do Amish people
Do Amish people have to be always 200 years behind or are they going to stay there forever?
I think they stay there forever.
I think they stay there.
So in 200 years they won't be watching Spongebob season one?
Maybe, maybe they just jump ahead.
They'll probably still be reading books about Spongebob like they do now.
Reading the novelizations of episodes.
Yeah that is sad as fuck.
They'll read the screenplays.
They have to read Fall of Reach instead of play Halo.
Yeah.
That's actually sad.
I've seen an Amish dude, he had to draw a succession. He had to draw Kendall Roy.
Really?
Yeah, with like a piece of burnt thistle or something.
With the thistle?
With the burnt thistle, he had to draw it. Because he doesn't have a pencil.
They don't even have a pen with an ink reservoir?
No, no, no.
They have a quill.
I want to use one of these pens.
They don't even have a quill.
They have quills, man.
No.
What kind of quill do you want to use?
One of the big dippers.
I had one of those.
Was it amazing?
fire. Oh yeah. I feel like Slytherin. I felt so cool with the nib. Yeah. I did my
art teacher in high school. She let me use those because she said my pen and ink
drawings were good. That was one of the goaded things to be autistic about.
Dude, learning the crosshatch. Learning the pen and ink drawing with a nib. Oh yeah.
Wow. You're learning the different pressures you got to put on it to draw
certain lines. Oh my god. Oh I missed that. I need to get, we need to get that.
should get some some I would love to get that big calligraphy writing set pill
shaped pens nib to me is a some kind of bite size pretzel buddy buddy but that's
just my that's just my American way you're thinking of a nibble that's just
my fucking American way nib is a type of pen tip. I think I might be willing to
get into art recently. I started playing a Japanese video game and I think I'm
becoming obsessed with Japan. That's one of the number one games to make you
you're obsessed with Japan. Yes, I
walked in. You can literally like I feel like that is the that's the like kind of
like
you know, like in a video game where they have the level save code and you like
the old video games, you enter the password and it like puts you right in
that save state. That's like playing that game is like that's your brain code
where you can like kind of like retroactively create a high school era of
weebism just by playing Persona. It's kind of what's happening to me. I wanted
to, I walked in here thinking that I was going to start, like I want to start
talking like the text from those kind of games, not like not in Japanese, just
like hello travelers. I'm here with Patrick Patrick and Cameron Cameron, and
here we are we're doing our our work for the day. It just is so awesome man. It's
such a fun game, and I just it's making me want to move to some very small
make you want to hang out station schoolers badly.
This is so bad. What are these games about persona? You're in high school,
and you're a got into so far. I just walk around. They're all different.
They're none of them are connected. They're all just the same story and
see places. It's all about your you're a Japanese high schooler and you find
some kind of supernatural serial killer thing going. I had the same. I had the
same feeling that you guys are talking about when I played Simpsons hit and run
on the Bart mission.
He said, take me to spring. I was like man. I want to be. I want to be a
Springfield child, so that a weeb for Springfield
I'm walking around. I'm like to Springfield so bad. I wish that this
was real. My friend
start showing up in just the like the plain shirts and pants.
I've got my hair spiked and it's died blonde. I'm just sitting just walking
around
trying to order a duff at every single bar you go to. Do you have to do you
have a duff acting like it's got a pretty? I'm getting a little hungry.
Do you have a tomato?
They have this incredible store in Springfield. It's called quickie mart
going into going into a seven eleven and forcing the guy behind the counter to
call it a squishy for you lying on your bed with your feet kicked up in the air
and spending all day on tick tock swiping through people doing like this
is my trip to quickie mart. When I buy
this is what quickie mark is quickie mart is like in spring
you're watching tic tocs that
barton
made
this is what food is like wait eat at quickie mart for an entire day. Okay,
here's how many here's everything I ate doing one meal a day at most tavern
Dude, I want to be there so badly, man. Yeah, here's my day. Okay, it actually
just my heart just broke because can you imagine if Springfield was a real place?
Can you imagine how ruined it would be by the Simpsons TV show? You imagine the
tourists and people would flood the most tavern to they would stand on on Homer
and Marge's on all day and look try to look in the windows. It would be
completely destroyed. You know, you know what you don't even have to this. This
a real thing bro. Universal Studios Orlando. Yeah. Oh true. Wait that's where you have
to go. I've been there a lot. A lot? Ok Richie. I've been there more than you know. My ex's
dad he was obsessed with Halloween Horror Nights and he would fly us down. Wait so you
saw the scary side of Springfield? Oh I saw spooky Springfield. You saw a tree house of
horror type. I would go there. My ex's dad would take us probably every single year.
That would also be a YouTube short that you'd watch that would be like "Everybody likes
like Springfield right. It's a happy normal town, but things get a little
different around
have you heard of tree house of order.
They didn't do enough tree house of horror stuff, though I will say that I
will say a universal studios step your fucking game up on. We should we need to
do a tree house of horror. I want to go back to horror night so bad. That was
the coolest thing that somebody has ever done for me is maybe bring me down
there.
No, well, no, but like the and I change all the names yeah, so it'd be like
Caleb Spitz, Caleb Pits of Hell, Patrick Do-ran, he ran away from home.
Patrick or Treat.
What?
Patrick or Treat Doran.
Or Patrick.
I thought you said Patrick the Treat.
No, no, no.
What does that mean?
Patrick the Treat.
That's here, we're having some hearing problems.
I thought that earlier you said my Gatorade thing is here.
Yeah, I still don't know how you could have gotten Gatorade out of what?
You said my Larry Wig.
Cameron Fester.
Oh.
I want to make sure I'm not saying the wrong name.
I'm not saying the wrong name.
Fester. Oh, Cameron Fester. I want to be Uncle Fester. That's good. And then we could call
the show like Frog Ash Abound. Like cast a spell, like a witch. Oh, wrong cast about
spells. Spell cast about tricks. Spell cast about tricks. Yeah, see, this is like our
treehouse of horror thing. Yeah, lips. Spell cast about lips. Yeah, well, that would be
I guess next month we have to do every single episode has to be a treehouse of horror type
thing.
Pod kiss about lips would be our valentines day version of treehouse of horror.
Pod kiss about lips?
That's our valentines day thing.
Did you say treehouse of horror?
Valentines day version of treehouse of horror.
What is going on with my hearing today?
I think you got too much variety coffee.
I think I did have too much coffee.
I had a prime and then a coffee.
and I I'm all for I'm all for I'm all for chains of coffee shops and cafes, but
I'd rather have a variety of different local stores than a variety
coffee.
Yeah, and
Starbucks, I get that you're hiring these stars, but I ain't giving you a
buck for that trash ass coffee. That's right, yeah, and
Pete, why don't you your business should Peter out? Yeah,
and Jimmy John's. How about you Jimmy your way over? It's not a coffee shop.
Okay.
Yeah, I'll touch your Jimmy into the John.
They sell coffee there. Hey, Tim Horton's. It's about...
Hey, Tim Horton's. You pay me.
Yeah, I guess if they pay you.
Hey, I'll touch your Jimmy in the John if you pay me. You pay me enough.
No. I'll do more than Jimmy it.
Can we go back to coffee? Be like a gymnast. Hey, Tim Horton's. I think
think it's about Tim pointing at my wrist. Yeah, it's about ten that you
whores sell a ton of
lemonade.
Tim Horton's this this Horton Horton tastes a poo instead of Horton. Here's
a yes. Oh yeah, that's good. That would be that would be clear to and Hey
Duncan Donuts, don't even get me started.
How about you dunk yourself
into the into a don't go on his canal, Duncan Donuts, your restaurants,
don't on it. Hey, Duncan Donuts, your restaurants great for breakfast, but
here's something I'd rather have lunch than donuts.
Yeah,
like you guys just do breakfast, call it lunch and restaurant. They actually
have lunch. Why is it so funny to me to call it to call Duncan Donuts a
restaurant? I don't know. It is technically a restaurant, I guess, but
does it be like yeah, these other these other coffee shops names,
because it's all basically there's port city java in Wilmington. There's also
Aroma Joe's. Hey, Aroma Joe's in New Hampshire. Why is it called that? That
makes me think that you're a fart store. That makes me think that you're that
makes me think that you're a fart store or a candle store, maybe or maybe a
candle store. We should name a coffee shop bean center. Oh, hey, the bean, the
The Bean! Is that one? That's one and it's owned by the Jollibee Corporation. Is that
true? I looked it up because I went there one time with Xavier. I don't like that all
of the coffee shops... The Bean, how about you be in Dahl and get the hell out of here?
Why is every coffee shop nowadays just one word called like magnet? And how come every
coffee shop just serves breakfast and maybe lunch? Just give me some spaghetti. See, The
The bean doesn't have a pretentious staff or annoying coffee names or boring elevator music.
Good, because I'm basically done with the pretentious staffs at these coffee shops.
This lady at the coffee shop at Variety, very nice, but I said, "Can I get that carrot cake
muffin?"
She said, "Oh yeah, well it's not carrot cake, it's a morning glory."
Right, and it's not a muffin, it's actually a scoon.
And I said, "Oh, okay."
Shoved the muffin in her mouth, made it break away all the edges and stuff.
You didn't do that.
You actually had a good time there.
I didn't have a good. I wasn't yet a great time there. I have a good time at
the new
coffee shop. You had a good time. There's a fun over there. You had fun. We had
enough fun. I said, Hey, we got an officer here and then I said I'll be
seeing a lot of you and she said that yeah, she said, okay,
and then because I'm trying to go on a date, we're trying to we're trying to
develop a community. I don't want to put them out of business. You want to
start? We said that we talked about that. We talked about putting a free
a sign on our office door or a sign that says variety coffee, extra seating,
a bunch of chairs.
I have no coffee at all. Just make people come in here and just guys try
to work on their laptop. And we're sitting here just screaming. Yeah,
we're making it
funny to put audience seats in here. It says hey.
I do want to do- Need somewhere to drink your coffee? Come watch us record
the podcast. I want to do like a Good Burger or like Barbershop style war with
business across the street. And we need to like, we have to turn into a coffee shop.
We just need to like ruin their business.
You know what would be so funny is if they were trying to buy this office space for their
coffee shop.
It's just too small.
Yeah, actually there's not two exits. Well, there is two exits, but you know, it's not.
This isn't zoned for that.
Yeah, this is definitely not zoned for that.
Maybe for my eventual kombucha bar, but not for coffee.
What's your kombucha company's name?
Turd Shine.
Turd Shine?
Like June Shine?
No man.
I don't know. I haven't come up with a name yet.
Poon Shine?
It would probably be called like
Particulate.
That's not a good name.
What are you talking about?
Particulate?
Particulate is not a good name for kombucha.
a particular there's a there's a problem all that's come hard particular there's
a really uh... uh... big problem a small batch kombucha is where they have little
worms in them here's all of it you know she
because the scobey i was trying to tell you and i think we're going to be a
particular
i find it hard to get a fine if i was making a worm booted karma form organism
my friend of verma form
was that
verma form
warm shape verma form warm shape
Vermiform means worms. Vermiform, worm, shipe. You called it a particulate. Well,
you said vermiform, so you also, you went too far. You also went, I know I'm
trying to get his attention. You did get my attention. You can just snap him out
of it. You can just tap his stuff. I don't want to touch him. You don't want
to touch him. So genuine. I don't want to touch him. I've definitely had too
much coffee. I honestly want to keep my arms crossed all day today. Yeah, that's
is what we call bad news.
Is you get across my arms all day today? I don't have a neutral express. I had a
waiter the other day and I was crossing my arms way too much and I got in my
head about it and was like, this guy thinks I'm such an asshole, because he's
crossing your arm. He's bringing me food and shit and I'm just sitting there with
my arms crossed like a dickhead, but he doesn't realise that my hands get cold.
Yeah, yeah, you're sitting there. The worst types of arm crossing in public.
Yeah, I look so bitchy. Speaking of you remember weird types of arm crossing.
never seen another human being ever do.
Show me.
You've seen me do it.
I mean, yes, I have.
This?
I do this.
That is pitiful.
Yeah, I do this a lot.
Well, that's thinkerly.
That one's more normal, but it's still bad to do.
You should only do that at the library.
This one is the terrible one that I just realized I'm doing.
This is purely pitiful concert goers.
It's insane.
I do it when I'm talking to people.
That's like the...
To people I don't know.
That fucking photo of Jake in the hard times.
Remember that one?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
out that was him. That was awesome. I need to be in another Onion article. Yeah. Oh yeah
because you're, it's just a family photo. They used a photo from my mom's Facebook.
You don't think that's unlike, you've never checked the Wayback Machine? You don't remember
the name of the article? It was called Gay Guy Spotted in Family Photo. Gay Family Spotted
looking like shit. No, no, no, that's not true, man. No, it really isn't true. It
was investigative journalism from the Onion. It was it was called like
amazing. These two orphans finally got adopted and then killed their parents or
something. It was something with a dark twist. Yeah, and it was like the first
couple of weeks that the that the click hole was open. I think it was click.
Oh, it wasn't. Yeah, it was click. Oh, yeah, dude, you never thought to look on.
you never thought to look on the way back machine for that? No. They definitely
have. They probably have it saved from day one. My mom emailed them and asked
them to replace the photo. Well, how'd she find out about it? Fucking do look
for it. My brother sent it in our family group chat and was like, look how funny
this shit is. They used a picture of you guys on the thing. And we were like, oh
yeah, that's awesome. And then my mom was like, just sent an email. This is
unacceptable. They took this from my Facebook page. And we were like, fuck you
bitch. This was awesome for like two seconds. It made us so mad. Why were they on our Facebook?
I'm going to look for it. Probably thought she was hot, dude. Yeah. Oh, it's a fucking
smoke show. The click hole editors. Click on her hole. What are you talking about your mom like
that? I forgot I was talking about my mom for a second. You said your mom is a smoke show and
they're going to click on her hole. Kind of blacked out for a second. I'm sorry. I don't have a sister,
but somebody hot in my family, imagine it was about that instead.
Warning!
What kind of warning? What kind of bullshit warning is this?
No!
Okay, Mr. Chicago.
Just a little defensive kind of voice that I did.
A defensive Chicago voice?
No, no, no.
Was that defensive Miller? Is that what that was?
It was a little defensive Miller, I'm sorry.
What kind of bullshit warning is that?
Yeah, I don't want that warning.
You got the warning. Buddy, that warning is the warning they could have used when Napoleon Bonaparte
was getting fucked by the other army. I don't know too much about history. I can't really do Dennis Miller stuff.
I love all those videos. He always has some very weird reference that he does to prove that he's a smart guy.
And I hate those episodes where he has Norm on and everything that Norm says, he just goes like,
"Norm, buddy, you're a riot."
He just says that like 40 times.
And Norm's just like talking about the lunch that he ate.
And he's like, "Oh, what?"
"You had a turkey sandwich?"
"I had a sandwich, you know, I had, you know, like, cut in half."
"Let me guess, Norm, it was a club sandwich?"
"Yeah, yeah."
"Oh, Norm!"
"Hey, you know, I don't even know what kind of club it is."
"Normie, you kill me."
"I don't even know what club this sandwich is from."
Oh, Norm, you're just too good.
It's one of the worst things ever.
That's every Dennis Miller interview.
And he went on probably 4,000 times.
Yeah, he was good friends with Dennis Miller.
Yeah.
Dennis Miller, you are a conservative asswipe.
I hate conservative asswipes.
You are a fucking conservative asswipe.
You know, I had a nightmare the other day.
About what?
I had a daughter and...
Hey, there's the nightmare.
No, it's not really a nightmare.
That's the nightmare.
It gets worse.
Okay.
Uh-huh. She walks in, bringing her boyfriend, first time meeting him over for dinner.
Dennis Miller? Not Dennis Miller. That would have been acceptable. My 16-year-old daughter
is on a date with Dennis. My 24-year-old daughter brought home a white boyfriend.
That was your nightmare? Insane nightmare. Yeah. I'm a liberal democrat. I'm not going to have this
in my fucking house. You don't want your daughter dating a little... Bringing home a white boy. Oh
- Oh, fuck no.
- Little five foot two Filipino guy who's good at pool.
- Yes, that's what I want.
- I know that's exactly what you want.
- I don't want a whitey coming into my house.
They smell weird.
- Yeah, they smell like butterscotch.
- They smell like PB&J.
- Walking in smelling like an old book at the library.
You better not put that.
- Every single white boyfriend of your daughter
smells like a copy of Moby Dick that has mold on it.
- Buddy, if you're--
- From being in the library too long.
whatever you do to my daughter, you better do to me. I'm going to do it to
you. I'm not that scared of you. You do to my daughter. I'm going to do to my
wife.
We're kind of old and we don't know how new people do it. We need to learn
here buddy. Whatever you do to my daughter, I'm going to do to my left
hand. Okay, so watch yourself because that's the hand I don't normally use
yeah. Watch your so honestly, honestly, buddy go nuts.
please just do something. You know, let's do
that already. Go ahead, do it right now,
holding up
do it come on come on okay here. I'll start
okay. Whatever I do to my hand, let's reverse it to whatever I do to my hand.
You do to my daughter.
Come on. What are you doing?
immediately moaning.
He's just immediately come on get in there. What are you fucking doing? You
see in his hand, it's covered in spit. It's come on. It's covered in spit and I
just ate a lot of I just ate a lot of honey mustard pretzel pieces. My hand
smells like shit right now. Oh my God, you better make my daughter smell like
honey mustard pretzel pieces. I'm going to do so much after my hand that I'm
going to want to throw it away. Another hand. Oh,
wait, wait, honey, go get your sister. Oh wait, wait, my hands. Whoa, what are
you two doing? Oh my God, you're
just shoving your hands together, whatever my two daughters do and then I
run in guys stop,
what
cool, you're going to boarding school. Okay, here go my hand. You already
built a two little different boarding schools, having your hands walk around
first day of class, a bunch of other hands, they're both meeting at boarding
school who they miss met two beautiful feet
you're doing like a whole puppet show or like you've now you've painted your
entire body to be like the ground and you're using your feet and hands to walk
around and yeah and here are my two beautiful you rip off your button up
shirt and your slacks yeah and you've got a whole you've got the whole city of
London because you sent them to boarding school.
Oh, my hands are coming back with British accents.
My oldest daughter is at Big Ben, but my youngest is at Parliament.
Why would your chest be Big Ben and your dick should be Big Ben?
I don't know, I didn't think it through.
Yeah, why is the penis Parliament?
This father is weird.
Little Ben.
Yeah.
Nah.
Do they have a Little Ben in London?
Yeah, they have Little, Medium, Big, and Extra Large.
the bins are what you call the trash there. Oh, if you throw up like a potato
on the ground, let's talk about the differences between the you, the EU and
the US. It does piss me off that they name clocks over there. Yeah. What kind
of backwards bullshit is we don't even have the name of a clock at least I
would name a clock. Oh, that's big Ben. Well, what the fuck is this then? Huh?
Yeah, what's this? That's one of the one. What's this little Caleb? Hello,
little kid. I guess it is kind of little Caleb. I want to see you grow
what's this and watchy
and
that's big bed. So what is this fucking watchy? Hey, I want a hello watchy
I never noticed you before watchy.
That's interesting.
watch. He wants to go to bed, watch he's tired. Why is it so funny to imagine
being alone traveling in traveling to London and doing that on like a tour?
Yeah, it's like a twenty tours and you and you're a big man at the yes,
right at the front yeah. Oh that's big Ben, so that's big Ben. What's this
watch? He just doing that
yeah
hi
this door's boring. The tour is continue.
Wachi that is that is you're so rude. Watchy I want to tell you a secret. I
say it how it is just having a clearly like a
watch you that you're like you clearly on the plane. We're like okay, and when
I see big Ben, I'm going to writing it, writing it on a notebook, just like no,
that doesn't make any standing. I would watch you say that guys watch you want
to be signing on a grass, put a name tag on them and you have a mini name.
Hello, my name is watching
I
was this
girl. Oh, who's that? Is that Mickey Mouse on your watch? Sorry, lady looks
like our watches are in love. Guess I'm gonna have to go home with you. I didn't
book a hotel.
It's almost like we're like in laws now, because our watches fell in love.
Yours is kind of more the strong silent type. Yeah, I can't get watch you to
shut the hell up.
Yeah, I said, well, yeah, maybe, maybe watching and you're watching, you know, hang out, maybe
we'll learn something from them.
We'll see what happens.
See where the night takes them.
Somebody's talking to you.
They're, they're asking you at one of the restaurants, what would you like to eat?
And then watch he starts ordering and you have to cover him up real quick.
He did not say the A5 Wagyu.
Watch he does.
Yeah.
Watch he does market price.
What are you doing?
Come on.
live a little
okay. We are not getting a serpent. What you get the turf? I'll eat the
watchy
like what are you doing? You're like oh it's watchy like if that's big Ben,
then what's this watchy
pointing out that we're nowhere near big Ben. You're not in London. Yeah,
like at that point on a Europe vacation, that's big Ben, then this has got to
watch or some shit. Yeah, I came up with in the watching you came in. It was
crazy. I know I'm in Italy, but if we could see Big Ben, this would make a lot
of sense. If you know a Big Ben, he's like basically watchy on steroids, but he
doesn't talk that much, but Jackie Chan did a fight on him and I'm hoping to get
Jackie Chan involved. Yeah, we want a little Jackie Chan on watchy.
It's just a good idea, man. I think that I think that we could even make a some
kind of electronic watch that maybe it says as eyes. Well, maybe like a GPS
man, yeah,
you know how GPS is say like it really get an apple watch setting for one.
There's an app you can get for apple watch that makes watchy called make me
watchy make me watchy. I become watch dot IO.
Yeah, you have to homebrew it. You have to like like jailbreak your wife and
then it's just a little face. Why aren't talk? Why aren't apps told not to learn
apps titled in the first person. They used to be yeah. Jinx I beer I beer yeah,
I watch, but I am like when I early up
what's the car? I Carly, I Carly, I know I Carly the name of the show. We need to
be called I I Carly. Well, the app that I Carly was named after an app. Yeah, it
was no better and there was all and all the phones were pairs. It's bullshit
apples. It was in some sort of weird parallel universe. It was an attempt to
court the child demographic, but unfortunately one of the producers
tried to court the child demographic in a different way. I'm trying to go to
court. Yeah, he went to court graphically demoing children. Yeah, he made up to
children. He said we're entering courtship. I'm courting you. I would like
to woo your affections young lady. He made those children put ketchup on their
feet.
Yeah, that's a video. That's a video of Victoria Justice or Ariana Grande and
he's like, what are you buddy a cannibal? What do you want to eat their toes?
are you a cannibal only it's hey hey buddy buddy watch a shut up with the
enough with the jokes watchy watchy. These jokes don't make very much sense.
What are you a cannibal that only eat feet when the kids are alive and only
got kids feed and
watching this is not watching watching you sound insane.
You said hello. Who's that? Oh yeah, I can put you on the watch. He
watch. He gets a call SNL audition. Oh my God, you're standing there studio
whatever holding your foot, holding your off stage, holding your hand on stage.
He's doing different impressions and you feel you feel you know that's big Ben.
What am I watching? Yeah, so we love you feeling we love watching, but I don't
know yeah, we're thinking I don't know. Maybe somebody else's wrist, maybe John
legends wrist. Yeah, maybe we could put watch on John legend. I mean, love it so
it's love. It's good come back. We could have love. It's come back. That's a good
idea. Watchy and why is John love? It's a little bit yeah.
Oh my God,
Watchy and Lovitz on the radio.
- On the radio?
- No, you gotta see Watchy has a face for TV, man.
Come on.
- I say I literally have a face.
- What do I got a face?
- Dude, and then wait.
- I literally got a face!
- And then guys.
- I literally have a face.
- Yeah, and I got two hands too.
- What about this, man?
You see a paparazzi photo of Paris Hilton
getting out of a limo, right?
- Oh shit.
- And she has no panties on,
and just kind of hanging below her skirt,
you see just this.
(laughter)
I was thinking a different thing where it's like
Wachi is uh
like leaving a car, right?
And you just see
that. You see a walking
Wachi's gaping hole. Oh no
that's not his hole
I'm saying what if Paris Hilton shoved
him up her fucking pussy. Then where is Wachi's genitals?
Inside of his body.
His whole body is a genital.
His entire body is a genital. That's what I'm saying.
Interesting. He could please women by
being shot up inside of him.
Okay, so this is his face and then the back is his body.
He doesn't need, he's a watch. He doesn't have a body.
He has a bracelet and a face.
Man, is he shit and piss.
He doesn't shit and piss, he's a fucking watch.
He does not even real.
What?
If that's Big Ben, this is watchy.
That was the original thing.
But he's become his own thing now.
Well, it's not a real, this isn't true, Patrick.
We're making all this shit up and we were saying that.
Do you know what he's talking about?
Maybe we can find a middle ground. Maybe Wachi will be like, "I'll be right back. This guy has to go piss and shit."
And then he can still take bathroom breaks.
He shits and pisses for the guy. Wachi shits and pisses.
No, no, no. Wachi doesn't do anything.
Dude, how are you not understanding this?
Wachi's hands move around.
Wachi is just the guy making a voice.
That was the whole thing. And he's schizophrenic.
And he's pretending that...
If this is Big Ben, that's Wachi.
Or if that's Big Ben.
that's big Ben. This is big Ben, then what's that
way? Look up this was big Ben look up really slowly. This is a watch and who
wait
take that off real quick. Why do you keep one my watchy and by the way it's a
watchy now
holy shit is that a tree house of horror vibes is that is this what my arm would
look like if I was dead, putting watching on a severed arm. That's actually scary
fuck. He couldn't figure out how to do that. That's how Wachy can live on his own. Just
put him on an arm. It's just like that Tales from the Crypt episode with the dummy. I didn't
see that one. With Don Rickles? I've seen maybe two or three episodes of Tales from
the Crypt. These days it would be Tales with the Crypts and Bloods and the fucking... Well
there's blood in the Crypt. Blood in the Crypts. Blood on my Crypt. They have to have done
Tales from the Crypt episode about the Bloods and the Crypts. What's scarier than this?
yeah
walking around what is way and I'm getting beat up by a bunch of gangs,
because I'm wearing all fucking pink in the middle of honestly. Now that I
think about it, if every if horror movie directors, they're trying to make
movies that are scary right. So every time that a horror movie director is
making a movie and it's about and it's about a werewolf or a vampire or a
ghost, they're basically literally saying. I think that ghosts are scarier
than the bloods in the cribs. It's like the bloods of the if you're trying to
scare people with your movie. Well, you're not putting the bloods and the
crypts in the movie. You are saying no, I think it's exactly. I think that a
ghost or a vampire is scarier than violence on the street. It's exactly like
Freddy Krueger, though, where you make the they're only scary and they only
have power. If you give them power, they have plenty of power. Well, we used to
have vampires. Now there's so much fanfare about Justin Bieber, Taylor
Swift and Olivia Rodrigo, Justin Bay Bay Bay Bay Bay. You used to have
vampires. Now there's fan fire about just a
and a bear
and watching the bear, the buyer on hello on how you like hello. Hello,
hello,
why do you keep saying hello?
Can't really do it with hulu.
Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, I'm watching
you're watching who is a TV name watch because you watch. Oh my God,
watch it's like Garfield tale of two kitties where there's watch and there's
watch yeah is that way
places is and then he tries to put the TV around his wrist. That's such a
watch and then the watch is on the wall
right. They switch place. They switch places and no one can tell Friday watch
Wednesday watch you watch a Wednesday, Wednesday,
that would be okay. If you in in first real, though, if you did
I'm trying so hard to think of another stream service, but I'm so to be
to be or not to be
let's take it to the Max.
this
man. What an episode this was not to be to flex or not to flex net net to
flex net to flex net to flex. Well, what's another one? I mean, you know
prime
for
this is
All right. Is that time? Is that what it is? Time? Yeah, we do have
okay. Come to if you're in New York City or if you're a freak and you
wanna travel, travel on October 20th. October 20th at Littlefield, we have
a show called World's Biggest... Underworld's Biggest Mummy, and it is
a tree house of horrification of our sketch group World's Biggest Army.
World's Biggest Army. So it's almost as if you...
it's a parody. Yeah. So the funny already starts at the beginning. Yeah,
the funny starts in the name. The funny starts immediately. So if you like
shit like that and if you like stuff like Hulu... And Watchee. Hulu. If you
like stuff like Hulu and Watchee, do not come to the show because it will
be a completely different type of scary humor. I think I might be writing
a Watchee sketch. I hate to say it. We will be putting a Watchee Easter
egg in the show. Watchee could actually be great. We should just do
Watchee. We'll do Watchee. Yeah.
Alright. Didn't we do that last time we had a sketch that was a
a direct rip of something from the show. What did we do? Watchy? I don't
remember, but also I will be opening for Girl God on November 5th in 2023.
Shareholder. And there's a shareholders meeting on
the 28th. 28th. 28th. Come through. Just get your ass in the call and come
through. And come through. Bring a good cue for us to A. Yeah, we will answer.
So, basically, what the shareholders is, is we do a little
fart like that. We do a thing and then I mean if you're already paying for this,
you probably know what it is. We and then we do a Q and A thing at the end.
Okay. Do we have anything else to plug?
Jubio Timber.
Jubio Timber is still going. It is over. It's over. It's not over. It's almost
over. I really don't want you guys to have your reaction to this fart be
recorded forever. No, we're waiting. We're waiting until
I
I really enjoyed reading about all your adventures on the blog. It's super hot.
The fact that you escort me and that I have the opportunity to be with you makes it even hotter.
I just like the whole experience in general.
In fact, I get most of my clients either via this blog or via my profile on our escort website.
Kevin booked me for an hour. He actually considers himself a groupie. I like that.
So here's a photo of him and- of her and Kevin.
*laughter*
I have censored it.
This is an example of a standard sex job.
This is, I'm guessing, as fat as you could possibly make your character in Second Life.
Walking around, I'm not seeing anybody have this kind of body.
but the uncensored photo he has a he has a bright pink little tiny cock and she is
and there's a lot more photos from this from this engagement and I would really
like really quickly like to say so her services cost a thousand Linden an hour
okay how much is so I looked it up a thousand Linden is three dollars
For $3 an hour she has sex with guys that don't look exactly like George Clooney.
Here's another one.
One of my regular clients is very imaginative and a bit of a pervert.
Every time he hires me...
Maybe it's Cameron's rival here.
You think this is Cameron?
Oh it could be pervert one.
Every time he hires me he comes up with another kinky thing to do.
For some of his dirty fantasies it would be rather difficult to find a non-professional
partner.
That's a job for a professional sex worker.
The last time I met him, he made me kneel in a dirty stall of a pig's die.
I sat right between a couple of pigs to serve him as a dirty sex toy.
I had a long shower after that one.
And let's look at a photo from this experience.
Sex in a pig's die.
Fucked in a pig's die.
But the pigs are there!
(upbeat music)