(upbeat music)
- Is that a glass of whiskey you got there, Caleb?
- Where we started?
A glass of, which one?
You think this is whiskey?
- I thought it was.
Maybe it's just the color of the glass.
- 'Cause I have a beautiful cup that my wife buys
that doesn't hold any amount of liquid.
This is our larger cup, guys.
- This glass has a belly on it.
- That looks like it gives you,
it looks like one of those things
that later she's gonna throw out
because she saw that there's a lead poisoning recall
on that specific cup.
- It looks like this happened with me
and my girlfriend multiple times.
She buys some shit and then is like,
"Oh yeah, it has lead in this."
- Dude, look, I have a couple of cups here on my desk.
Look at the coffee cups that I have in my house.
- Yeah.
Oh, no way that doesn't have lead paint in it, dude.
No fucking shot that that doesn't have lead paint.
- What is this, bro?
feel like some kind of emperor drinking out of this cup.
Oh yeah, this cup gets skinny at the bottom.
You look...
Well, except for this one, buddy, this is my cup that I brought from home.
Check this out. This is the one I'm drinking in right now.
Porsche.
Dang.
That one also is skinny at the bottom.
Porsche cup.
Damn.
Well, it goes fat and then it gets skinny.
Yeah, but it's...
This is a mug. This is a cup that... a travel mug that my grandpa...
Looks like a mug.
My grandpa walked in, didn't buy a Porsche, and got a mug.
That's cool. That's a cool thing to do.
Yeah.
That's cooler than getting the Porsche, I think.
I think way cooler, dude. Yeah. He's like a social engineer.
Did I ever tell you about the time he went into a like an electronic store
on Christmas Eve and they were having like a Christmas Eve party
and he was trying to buy a radio for his car and they were having like
like an employee's only Christmas Eve party.
They had like a full food spread in like the office.
And he was he just walked in and started eating like all of the food in this
at this office party.
And then the guy was like, hey, can I help you?
And he was like, yeah, I was looking for a radio,
but I don't think I want to buy one here.
And they just left.
He didn't even buy anything.
He just stole their food.
Well, that's beast.
He is a beast.
Guys, as you can tell, we're not on the set today.
We are in a biblical situation.
We're in a biblical in two ways.
We've been sinned against by Pierce Campion for stealing our cameras.
And then also every single one.
And then God tried to smite him with a flash flood
and ended up doing collateral damage to the rest of New York City.
See, I'm here in our you can see our beautiful, beautiful studio
here in Ridgewood, Queens.
I have a I have a little coffee story I'd like to like to tell you guys.
I've never wanted to hear something more.
Yeah. Are you excited for my new?
I'm really sorry.
Yeah, it's going for Patrick.
It's about coffee.
Oh, my God.
Wait, let me cut you guys.
I'm kind of cozy.
Oh, can I get a blanket? Yeah.
With this rainy ass day?
You see me with my new little coffee?
Yep. I see you.
OK. Doesn't look so new.
It looks like you've been drinking it for a
minute.
I had to get a new one at the store
because I we were texting each
other about not having the cameras
still.
And when I was going
to put the lid on,
I think there was a little bit of pent
up rage in me.
I squeezed the cup so hard
that the side of the thing cracked and it squirted all over the coffee store.
And I had to get, the guy gave me a new coffee.
Thankfully.
That's not right.
He shouldn't be giving you, that's your fault.
That was my fault.
That was not a brand new coffee shop.
How do you squeeze a coffee enough that it breaks?
I was, I was, I was furious.
I was furious with impotent rage.
Once you start hitting the chocolate.
Yeah.
Impotent rage for sure.
Plus I have been getting it.
You'll feel that.
Kind of pent up.
That'll do it to you.
Bro, I have it.
That'll do it to you, bro.
I haven't been getting it at home.
The wife is not even giving up
the thang, the stang.
If I don't get it twice a day, I grab a
beer can and I put like five holes
in it for every finger.
Pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop.
You got the sharp fingers going on?
- How do you put the holes in it?
- Let's talk about our sex lives this episode.
- Well you don't, doesn't squish the can
and just puts holes in?
- No, because that's how fast it's going.
- Is it a--
- It's like a--
- It's puncturing them instantly
and then I can play it like a, like a, some kind of flute.
- We're gonna get down and dirty with it this episode.
We're getting, now we're gonna talk completely about,
in graphic detail about our sex lives.
- You guys wanna hear a funny story
that I don't think I ever told before that,
about, that's actually, I was thinking about this morning
since we said we were gonna do a remote,
I was thinking about how we used to do remote all the time.
I was thinking about how we used to do remote all the time back during COVID.
And I remembered, that was so back then, that was when I was living with my mom and I was living in my mom's basement and basically an actual dungeon.
And there's no insulation at all whatsoever between it was literally like I looked up
and I saw the floorboards.
I remember that place.
So everybody could hear everything everywhere.
And I remember we were and my mom's a teacher for those people who don't know.
And this is during COVID.
So she's doing she's a fifth grade teacher and she does doing remote teaching over zoom.
I remember really vividly that the reason I started having to go sit in her car to record
some of the episodes.
I forgot about that.
I saw that too because she came up to me one night after we recorded and I remember it
was the episode where Caleb told the story, maybe it was the second time he told the story,
but the story about how his like family friend or something was a little kid and they came
home and the kid had his arm up the dog's ass up to the elbow.
Oh yeah, the great name.
my mom after King Lobster's, I'm obviously
you can't record in here anymore if you're going to be yelling about kids,
or some dogs.
Because my fifth graders can hear you.
That was such a funny fucking time of our, that was so crazy.
COVID was crazy.
I was just reminiscing about that this morning when I was thinking, wow, back to,
back to Roma.
Now my girlfriend's in the other room, I can, yeah, I can yell about this stuff.
she'll hear her boss. She likes it. Yeah. I had similar because I like went through that
breakup then I had to move back in. I had to move in with my sister and her ex one day,
I think we were recording late at night one time and he had to work like five in the morning,
something like that. And he woke up to me doing Gilbert Gottfried voice and was so mad he wanted
to kick me out of there.
- Yeah, he wanted to get you out of there.
- That's a pretty bad one to wake up to.
- You're hearing, like the other room,
you're hearing like, "Sucking and fucking
"and eating poop and."
- Yeah, that would drive me crazy, I think.
But do you think it'd be worse
if it was actually Gilbert Gottfried?
If he was like your Craigslist roommate?
- Are you kidding me?
- That would be--
- He's your Craigslist roommate 'cause he's frugal.
And he's doing voiceover for the new Affleck show.
- Have you ever met somebody from,
like that you've never met before,
maybe somebody from online or somebody,
and then you meet them
and they do have an insanely grating voice.
- Yeah.
- Everybody online has a grating voice.
That's the reason they go online.
- Listen to me, listen to how I talk.
- That's how you, that's the reason you type
instead of talk to the people around you.
- Fishing for compliments much?
Look at him.
Yeah, your mustache looks good too.
I wanna have fucking sex with you today.
I am feeling very, very cozy.
- Me too.
I just wanna sit around and I wanna watch a bigger guy,
a guy who's four inches taller than me
play LA Noire for a couple hours.
That's what I wanna do.
- I definitely have, after this,
I'm gonna get in the blanket.
- Yeah, I texted Caleb and said the same.
I said, "This weather make me wanna eat some good soup
"and watch a spoopy movie."
- And then I said, 'cause you text me something like this
pretty much every day, and I responded, 'cause I--
- Can you read the text I sent you before that?
Yeah, hold on.
But I responded and I said, "/SRS?"
And I was SRS.
But why didn't you tell me that?
'Cause I wanted to have a conversation about
what soup we would eat.
I was trying to set up back here
so that it wouldn't be on my computer all episode.
Too busy to send one text?
It was really hectic over here.
Okay, so here's what he said before,
"This weather literally makes me want to eat good soup
and watch a scary movie popcorn emoji."
Before this, he said, "Bruh, what did I eat last night?
My diarara smells so bad, skull laughing,
crying laughing emoji.
- Diarara.
And then before that, I said, "Bubes or badonkadonks?"
And he said, "Bro her hair."
(laughing)
- That's the best one.
- Bro her hair.
- That's the best one I've ever picked up.
- Easily.
(laughing)
- Bro I don't think about boobs or butts, dude.
I think about a woman's hair.
Oh my God, her makeup is so amazing right now.
And then before that...
You know why I text you guys that stuff?
Because we are co-workers.
Spoopy season is a month away.
I hate you.
We, OK, so the funniest thing about
that, my mindset when I text
this stuff is that we are co-workers.
And imagine getting like, imagine you work at a restaurant, right?
And you're like, you give...
We basically work at a restaurant.
Yeah, pretty much. This is a restaurant that I hear...
Sorry, here's another one.
The Room is like the best worst movie of all time.
So we're co-workers and imagine you're at a restaurant and you give your co-worker like
your phone number because you like hung it, you smoked in his car or something.
Yeah.
And then he just texts you this shit.
Text me the room is good.
Trying to become better friends with you.
Yeah, the talking period.
The talking period with your coworker.
The talking period of coworker friendship.
I have been in a talking phase with every manager I've ever had.
Never gone past that.
But they are brutal.
Yeah.
They are brutal.
Hey!
Did you ever get a nickname from your manager?
Well, they're doing the talking phase and they're like,
"Hey, Kathleen called out sick. I need you to come at 8am to cover her shift."
It's like...
Yeah.
Leave me alone, bro.
Back off. We're not in that phase yet.
I'm not I don't want to be you're just a situation ship for me.
Yeah, for me, honestly, like you're my work.
I mean, just to go like personal for a minute for me.
The talking phase is like 10 seconds long and then you go to the
well, and then I go into it.
I knew we were going to get wet and wild on this episode.
I knew you were going to talk about our amazing sex lives.
Do you think our unbeatable sex life?
Fucking amazing right now.
Oh my God.
I literally am shaking thinking about it.
moment of time for men who talk about that kind of stuff.
But imagine if one day we made the turn.
Would you say that you kill pussy?
Would you say that you blow out people?
I'm the murderer.
You're the murderer.
Do you do you blow out backs, Cameron?
I never understood what that means.
Maybe because I've never done it.
Yeah, I snap spines.
Getting in there, snapping necks, breaking fucking breaking toes.
Oh, they call me sub zero.
I'm in there pulling her whole spine.
...dugesting Mortal Kombat fatality stuff
to my wife, my one and only, destroying her.
[LAUGHTER]
And then I say, "Finisher!"
And then I go, [IMITATING GUNFIRE]
She turns around and is like, "Huh?"
What?
Did you say "Finisher?"
No, I didn't say that.
That was the announcer.
[LAUGHTER]
(laughing)
Man, that is the type of guy though,
that is like guys who are--
Who talks about sex?
There's like podcasts where it's like men
like talking about their sexual escapades.
Do you ever, you ever have--
I think that's what gets views on YouTube shorts and reels.
So I think if we wanna step our game up.
All right, here's what, here it is.
Have you guys ever been having sex
and you realize that you're gonna jizz too fast
And so you start thinking about trash.
Big bags of trash with green stick lines going off it.
It works really well, because trash is not sexy.
No.
I thought of the Vietnam War.
That's the first thing that pops up.
Like explosions, battlefield, bad company, too.
That shit's basically--
--cool, man.
Yeah.
I just have like a--
That shit's going to harden me up.
Yeah.
You think that's going to brick you up, bro?
Yeah, for real.
Thinking about R.A. the Rugged Man.
It's literally so masculine.
Yeah.
Imagining me in the war.
Well, you have to imagine.
So you're nutting too quick because you're thinking about how
masculine it would be to imagine how masculine I would be in the war.
Yeah.
I'm imagining myself in the Vietnam War, like running into the foxholes
with a machine gun and just like, you know, perforating every single
Viet Cong, pow, pow, pow, pow, pow, pow, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Throwing grenades into just ant hills.
Just blowing up everything.
Basically, I'm doing the thing that they do where they pour liquid metal into an anthill.
Yeah.
I'm pulling it out with a crane.
Just a bunch of Viet Cong kind of stuck like this, frozen, carbonite style.
A bunch of Vietnamese villagers who I guess live underground.
And you catch that one dude in the hostel who was jacking off.
Oh my God.
No, I'm finishing him.
Completely encased in metal.
No, I'm finishing it for him.
Isn't there a guy in Pompeii who was jacking his penis off and he got frozen at the time?
Yeah, don't even don't knock that till you try it.
But thank God they invented nuclear bomb.
I think as you just get destroyed.
Well, you get on the wall man.
Oh, that's why I will never if I'm ever jacking off in a nuclear explosion happens.
I'm going to face towards it while I'm jacking off.
So I don't get stuck in that side profile.
Everybody can see how small my penis was smart.
Yeah, you got to have you got it.
That's why I've stolen so many tactical plans from the government to figure out where the spots the danger spots are for nuclear explosions.
- That's so hard. - Yeah, you're trying
to find your-- - Always face towards them.
- Trying to find your J-O zones
in case of a nuclear explosion.
- Yeah, 'cause when-- - Yeah, imagine if you,
imagine if you, so you got,
your silhouette got painted on the wall
by a nuclear bomb and you just happened
at that time to be fat.
- Yeah. - Yeah, you're fat.
They're like, what is he doing with,
oh, is he eating a piece of sushi?
You're jacking off with chopsticks
'cause your penis is so small.
That'd be like, that is--
- My penis is a roll. - There's not even
any number-- - My penis is a roll
like a piece of sushi.
- Yeah, exactly, my penis has that kind of thing
where it's like there's a base like onigiri.
- Mine's still got the skin on it.
- And then there's something on top.
Yours does still have the skin, like a rotisserie chicken.
- Mine got the skin on it.
- Yeah, that's the best part.
- See, I'm trying to get, I'm trying to get,
I'm trying to have like real fodder, you know?
I'm trying to have like shorts fodder.
'Cause that's what we have been missing,
is reels, TikToks, and shorts.
We gotta start getting sexual as hell.
- Why do you want it to be so sex?
- You've been, yeah, you kind of are really going in.
- I'm going in on this. - I mean, there's stuff
that gets clicks, you guys.
I was watching the YouTube reels earlier,
and it's podcast guys, and they just say like,
"Yo, like, have you ever been smashing with a girl,
"and like, she got a little turd hanging out of her butt?"
- That people aren't saying that.
- This is what you watch on YouTube?
- People are talking about dingleberry sex.
- I watch this on YouTube shorts.
- In the fucking, on YouTube shorts,
they're talking about dingleberries
popping out of a woman's ass
while you're having sex with her?
Have you ever been smashing with your situation ship
and she got a little bit of turd poking out
of both her butt and her mouth?
Name, what podcast is doing this?
- What podcast are you listening to?
- The Sexual Boys.
- This is not, is that a barstool?
What is this?
- It's a Nelk Boys spin-off.
- Oh, I actually fuck with the Nelk Boys heavy.
- Yeah, you like Happy Dad Seltzer?
- I love Happy, I wanna get a Happy Dad wrapped.
- Smart car?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
Happy Dad's Seltzer wrapped smart car.
What the hell? My watch going off and I can't find it.
Oh my, it's not even 101.
Your watch is fast.
My watch is fast. It's always two minutes fast.
I have to subtract two minutes.
It's three minutes fast today.
That's crazy.
Well, it's two and a half minutes fast, basically.
All right.
So 101 has never been 101?
It's never been 101.
But maybe it's a common thing to say, but every time I see a smart car driving on the road, I do have such a vivid imagination of me just running into the street and pushing it over.
because two hands under the side and just
foom, just flipping it.
They get destroyed whenever there's like a protest.
They get destroyed whenever I throw bombs and rocks at them.
Also, whenever I let my acid tongue let loose on these owners,
they get fucking destroyed. I'll tell you what.
I say nice car for an aunt.
If it breaks down, you can just kind of carry it behind you like a rickshaw.
Yeah, that's true.
Anyway, or just put it on your head like a guy
holding a big pot in a different country and just move that thing home.
What is their addiction to that in other countries?
Get that off your head!
You know what their addiction is?
Hold that thing in your hands!
What?
You...
God gave you hands for a reason.
Your head is not a hand.
You're not one big hand in your head's hand.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Which by the way, it'd be weird to carry around stuff on your thumb too.
You're acting like a clown.
Exactly.
All those videos...
Yeah, literally acting like a clown.
It's cocoonery!
Where somebody's walking around, they have a TV or a refrigerator on their head, they're
riding a bicycle.
Oh, yeah, I know that guy. I know that guy's
Guys, there's a bunch. There's one guy. There's one guy in New York that does that
No, I'm talking about videos in other countries where somebody is trying to move
It's a task rabbit type job where you move a TV from one place to the other and they're like a profile on him on
Jankum, I don't need a car. I think I need a head. I'll put this on my head
He rides a bike and he put a fridge on his head. Why are you so we all know this guy?
We don't care about this guy.
- You're talking about one or two of the opposite guy.
- You're viral videoifying our conversation.
You're taking us into meme territory.
- You're trying to put us in a reel.
Have you seen this guy who drives around?
- Have you seen this guy?
- No.
- Well meanwhile, me and Caleb are trying to figure out
what the hell is going on in other countries
that makes them act different from us.
- It has to be some,
because they don't have fluoridated water.
So they are actually acting in the way
that you're supposed to.
You're supposed to use your head like a Christmas tree
and put a star on top of it.
- Did you say fluoridate, like Florida water?
- No, like fluoride.
- Oh, well if they, I mean, to us,
what they do is some Florida man type behavior.
And we have fluoridated water.
- You're saying that people in other countries
are Florida men. - If they had a Florida,
if they had a Florida, they would know
that all that stuff is bullshit.
- That's gotta be one of the most viciously racist things
I've ever heard in my entire life.
- What?
in other countries are Florida men. That's what you said. Florida men, which is almost
always used as a derogatory term for a crazy person on drugs. What are Florida men known for? Drugs,
domestic abuse, crashing their car, stealing. What countries are we talking about?
What countries do they carry things on their head? You said every country.
Every single country doesn't have their own Florida though, unless they do.
- You think that there's like a Florida type of thing for--
- I don't think there's a Florida anywhere
except for the United States.
- That's interesting.
You don't think there's like Canada's Florida or like UK's?
- No, I think there's one Florida.
- The world-- - There's two Georges.
- There is two Georges.
- Oh, okay, that pokes a hole in your fucking logic.
There could be two Floridas now.
- Okay, let's go look at the map then.
- Okay, let's consult it.
(laughing)
- It pokes a hole in the logic.
- Is there an Atlanta in the other Georgia too?
Yeah, it's exactly the same.
It's literally like...
Yeah, they have all the same people in places.
Do they have Magic City at Georgia?
The Balkan Georgia?
Yeah.
I would love to go to Balkan Magic City.
I bet the chicken wings are even better.
Well, there's a Florida, Massachusetts.
Yeah, that's true.
I've been there.
That place is fire.
There's an abandoned motel there.
I don't think two places should be able to have the same name, personally.
No, it's a non.
There's a Boston, New York.
Lebanon, New Hampshire?
Yeah.
Come on now.
Wait, Lebanon, New Hampshire?
That's real?
Lebanon, New Hampshire, they pronounce it different.
It's like Berlin.
Yeah, but...
It's different.
It's Liebannin.
No, they don't.
You're lying to my...
As a native New Hampshireite, it's pronounced Liebannin.
Is it New Hampshireite?
Yeah.
Oh, it's not like Hampshireian?
No, no, no.
It's New Hampshireite.
Well, that'd be cooler.
You have to admit this on recording.
You know, I just now for the first time ever realized New Hampshire completely won.
I've never once heard of original Hampshire.
Yeah, true.
Hampton, I have no clue where it could even be.
I would assume probably in the UK, but I don't care, but yeah, I've never heard once of it.
No, it must be not that cool.
New London.
That's a place that lost.
They lost.
Yeah.
Hard.
New York.
So hard.
New York though.
New York kind of bodied it.
Yeah.
York kind of completely.
But they went from losers to winners.
It used to be New Amsterdam.
They would have lost that one.
♪ It's a New Amsterdam ♪
Wait, but they would have won New Amsterdam too.
Maybe. New Amsterdam is now--
New York City's way bigger.
What?
New Amsterdam is now for complete Alkies.
What are you talking about?
New Amsterdam vodka, New Amsterdam gin.
Oh, you're so right.
This is for the, oh, speaking of,
Days like this, right?
Six months ago, seven months ago,
what would I be doing on a day like this?
I don't know. Sitting back,
rolling a fat joint, taking two puffs,
losing my mind, going crazy,
trying to find stuff under my couch pillows.
But I can't do that anymore, 'til I can't smoke weed.
So today I have, so far, it's one o'clock,
I have been getting high on food.
I've been eating so much food.
I am on food in a major way.
Days like this, stuck in my house,
I'm eating tortillas, just plain tortillas,
putting them on the stovetop,
making them hot and eating them.
Isn't that crazy?
- Dude, the corn tortillas on the burner?
- Yeah, what am I doing though?
- Make a little tortilla sandwich?
- I'm just eating, yeah.
- It's a snack, man.
- But why am I snacking?
I should be eating probably bison meat and creatine.
- You know what it is.
- I'm not the kind of person who eats tortillas like this.
- You said that you used to be, on a day like this,
you used to be smoking weed.
So right now you have kind of like phantom munchies
or whatever, or what's the word?
- I never got munchies.
Whenever I smoked weed, I hated food.
- That's crazy.
- Isn't that weird?
- You loved food.
- No, I never was somebody who liked eating
when I smoked weed.
- Yeah, you were.
- I literally was not.
- That's strange behavior and weirdness to boot.
- No wonder your therapist said it's making you psychotic.
- It's so psycho that I would not eat food.
- Yes.
- I would sit there and somebody would be like,
"Dude," you know, the people I hang out with,
they'd be like, "Dude, let's order chips."
- "Let's get chips."
- I'd say, "I fucking hate chips, man.
Get that chip shit out of my face.
I don't want chips.
I want water.
I want electrolytes."
- I did like to drink so much water when I was high.
Back when I smoked weed, I drank so much water,
I would throw up.
- When I-- - What?
- You can get water poisoning. - That's weirder
than not wanting food.
- No, no, no, it's called water poisoning.
- Drinking so much water that you--
- You can get water poisoning.
It's a real thing.
- Yeah, but I wasn't getting water poisoning.
I was just drinking too much water.
Drinking too much and it would kind of back up into his throat.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Speaking of water poisoning, this water is poisoning the damn city right now with all this rain.
That is true as fuck, man.
Thank you for saying that shit.
It's being, our streets are flooded and our subways are decimated.
Do you think that they're going, that it will destroy the Statue of Liberty?
Yes.
That's fucking sad.
That's a piece of copper that they put in the middle of the city.
The Statue of Liberty.
Did you know that it was originally
that thing?
If lightning struck it?
It was originally bronze or copper.
It was originally bronze in color, and now it's completely green due to rain and erosion.
It's actually due to the air.
It's oxidation, man.
Yeah, it's called verdigris.
Nice try.
It has nothing to do with.
It's called rain or erosion.
Well, why doesn't somebody get some salt and vinegar and scrub down the whole statue?
That's a good point. Why don't they buff all that green shit off it?
I want to see the beautiful, the beautiful bronze...
She probably was just... She was probably a dime piece before all this green shit stuff.
She must have been fine as fuck, man.
She was probably the most beautiful woman in the world, then she turned fucking green.
Oh, bronze-skinned lady sitting right there in the Hudson Bay.
One day it's going to rain salt and vinegar and she will be...
Acid rain.
She will become so, so, so beautiful again.
With her giant big ass boobs and her hair.
She has a scrub.
They scrub away all the green shit off of her and she's a completely different shape.
She has a complete hourglass figure.
There's just so much built up.
Oh my god.
She looked like she got a BBL but it's natural.
They scrub the green shit off and it just takes all the clothes off.
(laughing)
- It was French, originally she was definitely nude.
- It turns out she was never holding a book at all,
this was just a big lump on that forefinger.
- I don't wanna know what the torch was y'all!
Nah, I'm not gonna go there.
- Y'all, it was a third boob.
- That's what's wrong with today's society,
no countries are giving each other statues anymore.
Listen, we're all tearing these statues down.
- I thought, didn't they erect like a statue of a fuckin'
They put a statue of some celebrity in one of these Balkan countries.
No, okay, let me rephrase. No countries are giving us
statues anymore. Okay. Yeah. We're giving out statues left and
right. Willy nilly. What about that statue with the, that's in somewhere in New
York now with like the girl with no legs and she's got crazy Medusa hair.
Did a country give us that? That is the Statue of Liberty.
No, that's not it. You're thinking of that. No, it's the
- Is there a Liberty Spice? - Yeah, like a monocloss?
- Spiky thing around her head? - Yeah.
- No, she's got a bunch of tentacles - Is it Liberty Spice?
- and just green? - that are basically
like an early sign of the apocalypse,
kind of Mark of the Beast type shit.
But I think another country gave us that,
and if I had to guess, it would probably be Germany.
- Yeah.
Who gave us the Wall Street Bowl?
Was that Spain?
- I think actually just a guy did that.
- Oh, what was his name, Michael Spain?
Michael, no, I don't think it was Michael Spinn
or Michael Pena.
I think that it was probably just some rich guy
who was really good at making balls.
And I think he started with the balls
and tried to put them in Wall Street.
- Worked his way back. - They were like,
"You're gonna have to put something around these balls."
(laughing)
I was like, "Okay, fuck, a bull, I don't know."
- All right, all right, all right.
- Whatever.
- Oh, you know what would be a good prank I just thought?
To take that new girl sculpture.
I don't know if that's still there.
- Wait, let me guess.
Shaving cream on the hand
And you tickle somebody's face while they're asleep.
Is that it?
That would actually be a really good prank to do on a statue
because their little hand would hurt really bad.
Exactly.
And they'd slap their own face.
That would hurt way worse than a human hand.
Okay, what's the idea?
You just put the girl at the back so she's looking at the balls.
She's doing this.
She's doing the...
Yeah, she's doing her fearless pose.
Top story tonight, somebody has moved the brave little girl to the back of the bull and now
she is staring at the bull's balls.
Looking pretty upset.
Looking pretty upset at the bull's balls.
New Yorker, we go to the street to talk to New Yorkers about it.
Oh, what the fuck?
That little bitch looking at those balls.
Who the fuck did this?
What the hell?
What was that character you just tagged in?
You thought your character is we go to New Yorkers in the street to talk about this?
What the fuck?
That's a classic New Yorker.
What was that?
That's Mr. New York himself.
It almost didn't need the second part of the guy.
Yeah, it did not need it.
You already did the news announcement thing.
What the fuck?
Our second story tonight,
a man swore on TV
and we couldn't believe it out
because it was lied.
We go back to the same guy.
Well they wouldn't want to cover that on the there's a lot of holes in this kind of story is a lot of holes in this story I'm sorry that I even brought up going to the streets of New York this is why you're not gonna get on the office reboot man.
Damn I can't wait really bummed that I was like bald on Pam I was black bald completely and diet or no not Diane Phyllis.
Diane of the reboot Phyllis maker boobs what about a new to be hired a woman a
new woman on the office reboot named Diane who has humongous she is humongous
is huge users huge ease
ok see that's what I'm saying her name is Diane Hughes and she earns the
nickname
huge huge ease oh shit okay huge so they're doing is a little bit big what's
up huge hey huge and then it tackles sexism in the workplace it actually all
works out perfect from the reverse angle where they're like the guys calling them
huge or cool that's the moral this is the yeah yeah it's the the the poptimism
that Michael Schur loves. Do you think, guys, what kind of stories will they tackle
with this office reboot? What are they gonna do? Work from home.
Work from home. Run out of paper. Work from home. Oh shit, COVID-19 shuts down the office. Yeah, we have run out of
complete paper. Paper is getting replaced by iPads. Encroaching influence of China on the
business sphere. China, they got to make the papers have some kind of, it's a
different dimension now. It's red paper, it's communism paper. They
They accidentally have a four-hole punched paper.
Maybe Stanley has an OnlyFans?
Wow.
Look at my butt.
Yep, and it's all just the same photo of him basically doing the same pose as the Wall
Street girl, but it's from the back, we see his ass crack.
It's from the front and from the back, and it's the same photo every day.
It's a photo of him leaning over on his bathroom sink.
I subscribe to Stanley's Only Fans and he did the same photo every day.
Bro, let me guess.
Kevin is going to start doing Binging with Babish videos, Toby is going to start streaming
with Kai Sinat, what else is going to happen?
I almost feel that with the next up-reboot of The Office, which will most likely be woke,
I almost feel as if they're likely to change the name of the original Office to The Offense.
That's an actually amazing point!
God damn. They probably will do that. I feel it's likely. God damn Cameron. Exactly. And
they'll probably change parks and recreation to parts of violations. Yes. Where they are
gonna violate, because they're violating some kind of work office relationship policies.
Or parts of race. Because actually at the end of the show it was a pretty big melting pot
of different cultures. But the first two seasons. That's a good point. But the first two seasons
though. And community, they're probably going to reboot that and change it to
"white community." "Canceled community." "A community of canceled people."
"People." "Come." We're going to change it to "white community is bad."
Probably do it to "con." Or maybe they'll just say,
"Continuity." "Constituency." "We found it." Yeah.
And it'll probably end up being some kind of political thing about AOC.
Yeah, probably be political in some way.
It'll probably be AOC instead of Jeff Winger showing up
to the first day of bartending school.
And she has all these different groups of people
that she's having to represent.
She gets elected to school government, but she's also in the bikini
wet t-shirt concert.
Concert.
The wet t-shirt concert at the end of the show.
Very, very funny.
That happens at the end of every episode.
which is including all female pop stars. Yes, do a leap. Oh, we'll be making a
girl's
the
how's the
Judy Garland
Judy Garland is passed away. Man. She's dead. Speaking of a I will change that
though. Sentence sent it her Diane Feinstein has officially passed away
after this world and she's on to greener pastures. Y'all
don't hit the sound. What was that?
- That wasn't right. - Come on, bro.
- Nobody did a-- - She's moldering in a hole.
- Don't you-- - Who did that soundboard?
- Jupio did, man, he's got the soundboard all cued up.
That's fucked up, man.
Nobody home run baseball bat Super Mario Baseball.
- How would you feel if your great-great-grandma
was being eaten by mildew and someone played that sound
right in your face?
(laughing)
- Yeah, if your great-great-grandma turned to bug stuff.
- Nobody would like that.
- This lady who bravely survived since the 1800s
and you're making light of her being thrown into a box
over here on a lace flower.
- Yeah, just because she was born the same year,
or she got elected to Congress the same year
that baseball was invented,
you thought that it was appropriate
to play this fucking baseball sound, man?
She's a dead woman.
- Nah, but if I get invited to the funeral,
I'm sneaking a peek.
- You gotta sneak a peek.
Getting under there.
- Did you play that sound because she used to have a,
was in a situation ship with Abner Doubleday,
inventor of baseball.
(laughing)
I honestly feel so invigorated just imagining
her being in college and experimenting as a lesbian.
I feel like she definitely was doing some of that shit
back in the day and it makes me so happy.
Bro, when she flew that confederate flag
on the, in San Francisco.
- In the Civil War.
Which is why she flew it in the 60s or whatever.
I learned about that this morning,
didn't know she did that.
- Who gives a fuck, dude?
That was 100 years ago.
- I don't know a single thing about her.
- Yeah, that's true.
- All I know is the videos where she doesn't know
what she's doing.
- Yeah, where her brain is completely milk.
- How are we getting so many people in Congress
and Senators who are like,
we have like three now that just can't even talk.
- It's because Congress is the opposite of progress.
Oh, shit.
Oh, damn.
If you look at that, it had words involved in the name of Congress.
Well, it's almost pretty close, yeah.
Congress.
Hello?
I'm having a gress time.
God damn it.
Which is a combination of great and best.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, so I guess that does make some...
Con, pro, con.
Do I refresh?
Oh, Puppy's audio has all disappeared.
And he's completely disappeared.
Patrick's name is Puppy, by the way.
Hello.
I didn't realize nobody could see that.
Yeah, you're completely back. Good job.
Oh my god, dude.
Did the flood destroy?
The rain is affecting.
Okay, here's my question for you guys.
If the rain continues at this pace, there's no doubt
that this entire globe will be flooded with water.
Right?
You and us, me and you,
need to build an ark, and we need to
pair off into twos, and I call Patrick.
Alright, that's fine.
Okay, then I call Cameron.
I know y'all's babies are gonna be
to be weird AF. No they won't. Yep. How would our babies be weird? They're going to be born
with externalized internalities. I mean our babies are going to be born bald, I can tell
you that. And they're going to stay bald. Most babies are born bald, man. They're going
to be born bald and stay bald. My baby's going to have hair all over his body. You're going
to have a monkey baby. I'm going to have a werewolf baby. I'm going to have an all hair
- No, you don't want that. - My baby covered in hair.
- I actually would love if my baby was covered in white hair,
like a dog.
- That would be cool, 'cause, well,
white hair. - Like those videos,
you want your baby to come out,
and it looks like those videos of the--
- I want my baby to look like a spirit animal
from Chinese mythology.
- Have like bright pink skin,
flowing white hair, really long white hair.
- Translucent, translucent white hair,
and very pink skin. - Hair designed by God
to be viewed by moonlight.
That's gotta be the most beautiful poem you've said.
I know, what that is amazing.
Can you imagine antlers?
Oh, antlers.
You want your baby to look like, if you're a parent--
Drifting in the wind.
You want your baby to look like one of those
homeless guys that gets a haircut?
No, I want my baby to look like a mystical dragon.
You want it to have scales and also white hair
and also antlers.
Yeah, and it flies around. Antlers.
- And we don't-- - I don't think you even want a ba--
I think you don't want a baby.
- You're right, I want a pet. - I think I want a spirit guardian.
- You want a-- - This has always been my thing.
I've always been talking about this.
You have.
With my relationship counselor.
You want some kind of crazy Sun Wukong god
that follows you around and sits in line for you
when you don't want to.
- That's-- - Yeah.
If I had a spirit animal like that,
that's pretty much what I would make it do.
- I'd make it do chores. - I'm gonna--
I'm not battling many people.
- I'm gonna train my baby to sit on my shoulder.
(laughing)
- He's at graduation, you're just like,
"All right, one last time."
And you're just like a photo of him,
just completely, like perfectly perched.
- That's right.
- I've been playing these Persona games
and I feel like mine would pretty much
just do the dishes for me.
I'm not running around hunting bad guys much.
I'll just need him to--
- Oh, your Persona, I see.
- Maybe have him sit on my--
I'm sick on my--
- Thought you were still talking about your baby.
- No, well, my baby would also do the dishes,
no doubt, when he turns five.
But I would also, oh, a baby would be good for this too.
You wake up and you know that you got a football game
to watch at 1 p.m., but god damn if that couch isn't cold
by the time you sit down at 1 p.m.,
and I'm trying to sit in my office chair
and play video games for a couple hours.
Put your baby on it, heat it up.
- I'm thinking now about--
- That's basically what most kids do for their dads.
- Heat up chairs with their ass.
- Yeah. - Personas right now.
And can you imagine a situation where your soul is on fire
or whatever and you're letting loose
and your persona's about to manifest
and you're like, "Ah!"
And your spirit guardian appears
and it's completely, you can tell
that the character designer,
that it's completely pink and frilly
and it's wearing a dress and it's really cool.
It's flowers all over it and it's like,
abilities like pink's-- - I'd be fine with that.
- But what if-- - Pink aroma.
- What if you do that whole,
you go through all the animations
and then just like a single fly comes out
of your ass crack.
(laughing)
Lots of fuck your head.
- Or just like a little fucked up,
like a human head with just legs.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- It's like, ah!
It's like screaming in pain.
- His strength is biting. - It was so badly.
- This is a reflection of my most deepest being.
- This is who I really am. - This is who I am.
- This is my shadow.
- All he can do is bite.
- Just some guy whose head is duct taped to his feet
and his ass is completely like fully dilated,
goatsy, walking around.
- Yeah, what if you get one of the ones
from the Persona games where it's just a demon
with a gigantic cock that he's just stroking?
You know those lurks? - Or he has two skills.
He has biting and he can play the harmonica
with his foot to his mouth.
(laughing)
- It's so sick how many different Persona monsters
there are that are different variations
of guys sitting on the toilet with a big dick.
- Yeah, it's pretty awesome.
It's pretty awesome. - I gotta try those games out.
I need to try everything Japanese at this point, guys.
I'm gonna go, you guys will,
I'm gonna do some fucking, whoa!
(laughing)
What the hell are you doing, man?
Something happened, oh my God.
PT Productions.
Don't worry about it.
Okay.
Just keep talking.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Would you guys think I was wack if I dressed up
as something from Persona for Halloween?
You want to be a Persona character for Halloween?
Yeah, dude, I'll spend like $500 on a full cosplay outfit.
You are probably the most anime-looking person in America.
That would be pretty funny.
I think if you were like Sora from Kingdom Hearts or something.
I don't know about any of that shit.
Just put on that orange wig, you look completely Final Fantasy vibe.
No, I'm going to be the main character from Persona 4,
and I'm gonna get a completely white wig
and a whole schoolboy outfit. - You should be
a clown strife.
- I didn't play Final,
I have no interest in Final Fantasy,
I don't know why. - Final Fantasy is--
- You're crazy for that. - Blame, blame.
- Final Fantasy is basically honky version
of an actual Japanese video game.
- Yeah, well that's-- - Yeah, it's for honkies.
- I mean, yeah, they made it for,
that's why the name's in English.
- Yeah, exactly. - Yeah.
I haven't played any of these like personas or anything.
I've played Final Fantasy and Kingdom Hearts
all the way or yeah played all of the Kingdom Hearts games.
I want to get into something really fucked up.
I want to get into like Dragon Quest or some shit like that.
Yeah, Dragon Quest is cool.
Something insane with a thousand games.
It's the same art director from Chrono Trigger, right?
Yeah.
Dragon Ball.
Did he also do Chrono Trigger?
I don't know.
I don't go in for all that type of crap.
I tried to play Final Fantasy 1 when I was in middle school
and I was like, fuck this shit, man.
Yeah, it's an NES game, right?
I don't I liked it, but that's the thing I liked any I liked any stuff.
But I liked it.
Yeah, it's retro, man.
I realized like it's as far
that shit had like I tried to get into it when I was like 13,
something like that.
I tried to get into like retro gaming and I was just like, this is
I'd rather play games that look like this T-Rex on Cameron's screen right now.
Oh, my goodness.
I'm into retro games, but really retro games.
Yeah, like Pong.
I'm talking, no, even more retro.
Atari 2600.
I'm talking about, you know, hunting down.
Hunting.
That was the original game. Big game hunting.
Yeah, that was the original game.
Hunting down people.
Yeah, that's what they had before retro 8-bit games.
Fighting people, moving a rock around, kicking rocks.
That's an old game. Before 8-bit gaming.
How old is 8-bit gaming? That's all they had.
Wouldn't it be awesome if rock, paper, scissors was the oldest game in human history?
I think it is.
I think somebody would have to believe that it is.
And scissors.
Scissors more than paper.
Is it the oldest game or is that lacrosse?
Lacrosse ain't that old, dawg.
I thought lacrosse was the oldest game.
No, it's paintball.
Is lacrosse a Native American game?
Yeah.
It's an ancient Native American game.
I thought it actually was.
It's what all the kids who played lacrosse in my high school said.
I think it is a Native American game.
That is worse than the Trail of Tears,
what we've done to that fucking game.
That's crazy that that used to be Native American
and now it's like the most annoying white race sport.
Maybe I'm off here.
I hope I'm not.
Yeah, it's so insane that they probably played that
for hundreds of years
and then all these fucking honkeys came in and did that.
Lacrosse is credited to Native Americans.
Yeah.
That's a big credit.
Huge crowd. The name derives from the French word for the stick.
Why is there boy lacrosse and girl lacrosse in there?
It's like two different sports.
Isn't that every sport though?
Yeah. Not really.
WNBA is different, right?
The difference is...
Don't they have the...
Do they have a four point shot in the WNBA?
I heard they have a 100 point shot.
They don't have a four point shot in the WNBA?
I do think that dunking should be a golden snitch
in the WNBA where if somebody dunks,
it should end the game, you win instantly.
Yeah.
In lacrosse, women's lacrosse, they don't have like a,
you can't, it's not contact, and you can't,
like the fucking holder, whatever that shit's called,
the lacrosse stick doesn't have like a pocket in it.
It's just like a flat piece of like very tightly.
- Do they have ringless football?
- I genuinely got the WNBA and the Globetrotters mixed up.
- Yeah, I would say that those are the two most
different things in the world if you've watched.
I went and saw the Globetrotters when I was a kid.
Yeah.
They played some sorry team, the Washington something.
And let me tell you what, man.
These commanders are a bunch of fucking jabronis.
They weren't commanders, they were generals.
Generals.
Oh, the commanders is the football team.
Yeah, commanders are a real team.
But yeah, dude, these generals.
Listen, if the Globetrotters ever come to your town,
definitely go see 'em.
If the generals ever come to your town,
don't go see these guys, they're bums.
And they cheat, too, they're dirty.
We live close to their stadium.
I mean, not close, but you know,
where it's a train ride, a couple trains away.
We could go there.
To the Harlem Globetrotters?
Yeah.
Where do they stay?
I thought they go all around the world
based on their name.
Yeah, they globetrot.
They're from Harlem, but they trot.
When's the next game in Harlem?
The home game?
Yeah, when's the next home game?
I don't wanna see,
they already have such an advantage on the road.
I would hate to see a hometown advantage, home stadium.
they would be destroying whoever they're--
- It would be so funny to be like a fuckin'
sports ball kinda guy about the Globetrotters,
like going there and just being like.
(laughing)
Go team!
- Oh yeah, it's so cool when you balance
the balls on your head.
Yeah, that's seriously gonna get you a job after this.
Oh, oh, did he get a field goal?
Did he get a four point field goal from half court?
Is that type of guy still running around?
No, I think that's been...
We squashed him out, we exterminated him.
Did we get him?
I feel like everybody who used to be like that is so, so into basketball now.
Yeah.
I feel like every one of that type of guy completely got absorbed into basketball and
they go crazy for it.
You're pointing at me?
Yep.
I was never a sports ball guy, man,
'cause I always liked bad sports.
I always, like I liked paintball and shit,
and I liked football when I was a kid.
I liked baseball when I was a kid,
and then I tried to be a sports ball guy
and my heart wasn't in it.
Yeah.
You can't look like you and not like sports a little bit.
No, I gotta like something.
Yeah, and also you wear so much sports,
like vintage sports hats.
Oh, yeah.
is awesome, by the way, but you wear so many of them that it would be embarrassing.
Why'd you say which is awesome, by the way?
I was just saying it's awesome to wear hats from different teams that you've never seen.
Teams, yeah, and not show allegiance to any one of them.
You don't care about at all.
That's cool.
I'm putting on for different cities.
I would literally never in a million years wear a piece of merchandise for a sports team
that I didn't like or support or know about.
I would rather kill myself as a matter of honor.
But it's cool for Patrick to have just absolutely zero courage or backbone where he's just flipped
courage depending on what what oh what a little too much courage a little misplaced.
I like me.
Have you ever seen me wear a Yankees hat I would never touch a Yankees hat.
Here's my senior.
I support every other support.
I support every team but the Yankees.
You like any team that covers your bald spot man.
You don't care about these teams at all.
I would never wear a Yankees hat bro.
You would.
Uh uh.
No I wouldn't.
had if it was old enough. No. That's just because you were born in the wrong place. You were
born in a bad place. I was not born in a bad place. Yeah you were. That's actually, that's
allegiance, that's courage, that's having a backbone. And you're saying, oh well. You
know what team, I hate this other team so much because they hate the team from the state
next door. How embarrassing is that dude? That's not embarrassing at all. That's embarrassing.
At least move to the fucking states. You are a Toronto Raptors fan. That's because they
They were the coolest one when I you are a Toronto Raptors fan.
Yeah, you are you she wrote you are exactly like Drake.
I'm not in a good way.
Thank you in the corny way.
Thank you so much like Drake in the corny way.
Drake is actually growing everywhere.
I think he broke think he from the six.
I'm not from the six.
I don't want to even go to Toronto.
I liked Kyle Lowry because he was you had a similar build.
Oh, so bad.
I'm scared of it.
Right now.
Caleb is he's close.
he's closing every time he closes his eyes he imagines a new type of poutine.
That actually sounds pretty good.
Y'all having a Reddit off?
Do you guys?
Damn, that's actually savage as fuck.
You are the weakest link.
Yeah, you are the weakest link in terms of Reddit.
In Reddit.
You're like Godzilla.
You're being Reddit right now with your damn MCU overlay.
What you talking about?
Speaking of Toronto, okay, wait.
You're supposed to put your face in that.
Your suit looks amazing, actually, now that I'm looking at this.
It doesn't really fit you, though, I'm going to be honest.
Speaking of the Raptors, buddy, I'm tired of you talking about the Raptors.
Speaking of Toronto...
You're sitting there in your Raptors flat bill.
No, I don't.
This is a...
I don't have a...
I wish I did.
Would you get one?
I have a 2019 championship t-shirt.
It was $40, man.
Listen, I have...
That's vintage.
I have started listening...
2019 championship, that's vintage.
I'm hearing this kind of music, speaking of Toronto, because there's a lot of like
patois speakers there. What is this type of music that I've been hearing every single
time I walk down the street where it's a Jamaican guy and he's always saying something like,
"Your pussy so, I need your pussy, it smells, your pussy is so smellily stinkily, pussy,
pussy, pussy." What is this pussy music? Is this reggaeton?
I like, you know, I do like, have you, you hear this like the, like you're in Bushwick or
whatever you hear it, dude, like going down the...
It might be grunge based on the...
What, why is it so, they say pussy, they're throwing pussy here and there, I smell their
pussy, I put, I lick her pussy...
Here and there?
Here and everywhere, here, there, everywhere I'm hearing pussy, pussy, pussy, I'm trying
to walk...
Here, there, and everywhere, that's the Beatles.
I'm trying to walk down the street with my children and I'm hearing pussy, pussy, pussy,
pussy, pussy...
I think it's based on the details you just given, I do think it is the Beatles you're
hearing.
not have Jamaican accents and you're thinking of...
No, you're thinking of... You have been hearing
"Pussy, Pussy, Pussy
Marijuana" by Andy Milonakis.
Could have been that. That's what you've been hearing.
But have you been hearing these
like... When I lived in Bushwick
I would hear this every
like day because somebody
would drive down the street. These like
reggaeton songs that sound like they're being
sung by a little alien.
Can you sing one? You know these ones?
They're like...
♪ Da da da da da da da da ♪
- Yes, yeah.
Well, there's that one that's like,
♪ D-S-O, digga digga dig ♪
♪ D-S-O ♪
I hear that one so much.
- No, that is so crazy.
- It's really good. - That is the craziest kind of,
it's so sick.
- It's for dancing. - To just play that.
Yeah, I guess that makes sense.
- I love all that stuff.
- Listening to that in the car is crazy though.
You can't be dancing in the damn car.
You can't be dancing behind the wheel.
- Oh, has someone ever danced in the car before?
I've done carpool karaoke.
You have not done carpool karaoke.
No, you haven't, man.
Not officially.
Not officially on the show.
Not sanctioned carpool karaoke.
No, no, no, not with JC.
Amateur carpool karaoke.
But I've done it very amateurly.
I've done it, I almost did it in an Uber one time.
You almost did it in an Uber?
It was, I was coming back from some shoot
we were doing at Emerson,
and the Uber driver turned on all these lights
and was telling me about how he used to be Peter Dinklage's neighbor.
And he was supposed to be like a he was like, yeah, I was in this movie
called Smithereens.
I played a young boy and I was going to be a famous guy.
But now I do carpool karaoke sometimes.
Check this out.
Turn off the fucking flashing lights on.
But he didn't let you sing a song.
I told him that I didn't want to sing because I had to poop and pee so bad.
Oh my God, I would have done Ring Me The Life.
He stopped at a Dunkin' Donuts for me,
and he was actually a five-star driver.
If I did something like that...
He stopped at a Dunkin' Donuts for you?
Yes.
For you to walk in or at a drive-thru?
To walk in and piss and shit.
Whoa.
You shit? He let you shit?
Yeah.
What the fuck?
That was five-star, five-star, 30% tip.
That's six-star.
That's insane. He let you take a shit while he's on the clock?
Yeah, well, he was like, "I'm hungry anyway.
I'm gonna go to the Dunkin' Donuts."
beautiful would it be? This is when I lived on the Revere Mulden line. If you get into
that Uber and you pick a song that has like a very famous duet or something and you're
like I really want to sing this song. I got you babe. Yeah. You know what? Buddy punch
out. I'm going to tip you $100. You come, you sit in my fucking apartment with me. We're
going to do karaoke on my TV. Yeah, I don't like, I love. I have a karaoke machine in
my house. A karaoke machine is just a computer, man, and a TV.
You too, it's a Roku. You just need a fucking
microphone that's got a lot of reverb. That's all you need.
You can just sing. That's what makes a good karaoke.
Yeah, you don't even need a mic. You don't need a microphone in your house.
No, you need that microphone with the reverb, dude.
You just gotta yell.
Just yell loud enough and have a high ceiling.
Yeah, I guess that works too.
But I like the digital reverb.
What's up with you and reverb today?
I'm thinking about it.
Why?
Why do they put movies in reverb?
They should.
They should get an option.
They do that.
What movies in fucking... I want to watch movies in reverb.
The new... I heard the Barbie movie they released it in reverb.
That should be an option when you go...
When you go into the movie theaters, there should be two theaters like they have for captions.
You should be able to go see one with maximum reverb, everything echoing.
And also there should be bats in the movie theater when that happens.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
So you feel like you're in a cave and little water droplet sounds.
OK, they should do a movie theater like they do with those
where you can go into the the like.
What's it called?
It's like not really a sauna, but it's like a storm simulator, like a pool.
And there's lightning flashes and thunder sounds and rain coming from the ceiling.
Do you know what I'm talking about? Have you seen those?
That should be a movie theater.
Rainforest Cafe style movie theater.
I went to the Alamo Draft House
and I was walking in there saying
"Oh, which side am I going to pick? Cowboys or Indians?"
They don't have anything like this at the Alamo
Draft House, dude. It's literally just...
Especially at Alamo Draft House
they would not say "Indians" when referring
to the natives.
Make it themed a little bit.
Does that have to do with Native Americans?
Make it themed. That's what I'm saying.
understanding my point at all. I'm not understanding your point at all. Make it themed.
Yeah, make it themed like the Alamo. Yeah. Probably was back in the day, but then all the hipsters came in.
It's more, it seemed a little bit more like the Draft House. I agree. It's honestly themed like a movie
theater, you guys. Yeah. This is barely themed like anything. Put a couple, let me, give me a
sheriff star when I walk in. Make me feel like it's the old west or something. They should have each
screen in a movie theater. Each theater in there should have a different theme, and you pick,
they rotate the movies through them throughout the week.
So you pick what theme you want to see the movie in. I agree.
I should be able to go watch hereditary in like a race car bed.
Yeah. Oh dude. Imagine.
Oh, 80% of the way to race car beds.
You put your head outside the window on the race car bed, right?
And the fucking chair, the car reverberates.
Oh, that'd be cool.
The head stacks on the tree.
But you make a very good point, Cameron, which is we are having comfortflation
at every single movie theater in America.
Every movie theater seat goes all the way
to a straight line backwards.
And I, there's a direct correlation
between how much, how comfortable these seats have gotten
and how many times a year I'm falling asleep
in a movie that I paid for.
Yeah. Yep.
I'm not even getting the movie that I paid for.
When I was at a,
I can't even remember what movie I was seeing.
Oh, it might've been the,
no, it was fucking the Meg 2.
I went to see the Meg 2.
Well, first of all, like six people walked out in the first hour.
Awesome.
But one guy who didn't walk out was reclined his seat all the way.
He was sitting in front of me and then he rolled over onto his side.
It's like, you know, you lie in bed on your side,
like on his hands, and then he took out his phone and was just scrolling.
Well, he just goes to sleep.
That's awesome.
Bringing a white noise machine into the theater.
Just doing the pose of like having your knees bent and your legs.
That's so funny.
Looking up at the person next to you to.
And he was with someone.
He was like he was clearly like he's somebody wanted to see the movie
and he was like, OK, I'll go with you.
And then the part where there's like, fuck it, I'm going to pretend I'm going to sleep.
That is so fucking awesome.
I'm going to do my bedtime routine real quick
so I can muster up the tiredness to fall asleep during this movie.
He was winding down, dude.
Yeah. Getting up and going to get some warm milk from the from the lobby.
Drinking, drinking, rubbing your eyes.
- Do you guys have any warm--
- God, this movie is so fucking boring,
but I need to read for 30 minutes with my nightlight
before I'll be able to fall asleep.
- I have to read a bunch of Wikipedia pages
for other movies that I know about.
- Guys, I can't sleep.
Can I come stay with you behind the concession stand?
(laughing)
- I flew up in a Fido.
- I think that's a good idea, man.
More people should be at least trying to fall asleep
in a movie theater.
I fell asleep.
I went to I saw scanners
at like a like a midnight
thirty five millimeter print thing
at the corner.
That's that's a boring movie.
Well, yeah, dude, I want to see
part in it.
Yeah, I feel like maybe
that's a cool music.
I think I was up for twenty four
hours and I just fell asleep there
and the tickets were like twelve
bucks. And I was like, yeah, I
guess it's worth it.
When you me and Joe
and Alex went to see the
birds at the film forum and you fell asleep during it and you started snoring really loud.
Oh did I?
Everyone was quiet and you just started going *snoring*.
I forgot I did that.
I was shaking you.
That's so, oh my god. That, okay, that movie is a fucking, it's pretty fucking boring.
Yeah, it was just so funny. We were all laughing so hard.
Perfect storm for me to fall asleep
Please full actually. Oh, yeah. Yeah
Snores my snores are fucking crazy. I mean you guys both know
You literally need to get a CPAP machine or else you will die before you turn 30
I'm gonna die from something else before I turn 30, but why not leave?
my coke
my coca-cola not
I said fentanyl in my coke and then did actually mean Coca-Cola like I was trying to joke.
Dude, you're a drug addict.
You're making this public now that you're addicted to cocaine, you do it every single second of every day.
It's not, I'm not addicted to cocaine.
Fully addicted, completely habitual, can't even breathe.
I don't do that every single morning.
You can't wake up without it.
And then drink a coffee and then drink a bang energy and then drink a...
- When you say, "Oh, it's just a key bump,"
little do you know, it's one of these giant keys
that goes into a dungeon door.
He's doing a humongous pile.
- The key to the city?
- A key bump with, yeah, the key to the city?
I was just gonna say that.
(laughing)
- A giant-ass key.
- I'm just gonna do a quick key bump.
- There's a key bump.
- The Dungeon Tailor's key ring of like,
- The bag is the same size.
The bag is the same size as the key to the city, too,
so you have to hold it with your whole arm.
You're pouring it on like you're making bread at Panera,
like laid in a giant bag of flour directly onto a huge key.
Yeah.
Oh, I found that I went through my Shazams while we were talking
about the...
What kind of weird behavior is that?
I went through my Shazams because...
You shouldn't have Shazams.
You're trying to remember songs that you couldn't remember?
I was telling you about the time that the reggaeton was playing
from some guy's car so loud that I heard it so clear in my apartment that I was able to
shazam it and figure out what the song was.
Wow.
And it's called Manhattan Pa El Bronx by El Cherry Scum and Do Bwa Mantana.
That sounds pretty good.
It sounds like this.
It seems pretty normal.
This just sounds like a normal.
Yeah, that was normal.
What the hell?
*Music*
That guy sounds cool.
He does sound cool.
Yeah I don't think he's... Stop.
Stop flashbanging us.
We have to end the episode because they're finding
toys on the other side of my screen guys.
I found this.
Who played Bang?
Office Space Vibes with this one.
That is Office Space Vibes.
take that shit, dog.
Yo, stapler.
Guys, go check out the world's--
Underworld's biggest mummy.
We've never remembered the name one time.
Well, it's just--
It's maybe confusing.
Underworld's biggest mummy at swagpoop.com/shows.
It's a sketch show in Brooklyn on October 20
at Littlefield with us, Piers Campion, and Home Planet.
And we were coming up with some funny ass ideas
that will be quite hilariously to see
performed live in front of you on stage
alongside videos and screenings.
- If you liked our idea of the new office,
wait until you see the four or five sketches
we're gonna be doing about it at this fucking show, dude.
And if you thought that Dianne Feinstein dying was funny,
we will have some very timely sketches coming out
in October about this. - About baseball.
- About baseball. - And to clarify here,
the show is called World's Biggest Army Presents
underworld's biggest mummy,
Port of Skull, Halloween City.
Yeah, that is a lot.
If you can remember all of that,
you can remember to buy tickets at
swagpoop.com/shows.
All you got to remember is,
think about this. Start, you think, I
got to remember something.
Oh, I have to remember something
about poop. Now, what's poop?
Poop is kind of swag.
OK, so swagpoop.com.
And then you can think, what do I do
after I poop? Shower.
show is shower showers showers shows swag poop dot com slash shows.
And then click on the link to event bright dot com.
And then you're thinking, huh, what does an event make me feel inside scared?
So, Oh, Halloween city, bright rhymes with fright.
Oh, right.
Is the name of an emotion, an emotion and the emotion of your
Your mouse should be over the buy tickets button.
Oh my god.
Well you guys figured that out.
So we're gonna go.
Alright.
Woah!
I'm gonna stay completely neutral on the two.
I'm gonna say my first memory with, I think the first memory I remember is the shadow
of a hot dog poking out in my bedroom when I was a kid.
I saw the shadow of a hot dog on the wall.
And it was kind of like a come to G like a Batman type moment.
Come moment. Nope.
Come to Jesus shadow.
I got molested. I'm saying I saw the shadow of a hot dog.
Are you trying to say seeing a shadow of a bat?
Are you saying shadow?
Oh, did he see the full bet?
I don't know. I thought he saw the shadow of the moon.
My bad. So you got attacked by a hot dog.
No, I was attacked by burgers,
but I saw the shadow of a hot dog that saved me.
And there's nothing about molestation in this.
Why are you bringing up molesting on the high hamburger versus hot dog debate?
Well, you brought up the shadow of a hot dog on your bedroom wall.
Which kind of makes it, it feels like that's what you're getting at.
It feels like you were trying the way you were kind of laughing when you were saying it.
I was imagining a hot dog style Batman.
But what is the shadow?
Why would you be a shadow?
Is because Batman is of the night hero.
That's a shadow.
Is Batman of the night?
What are you saying? Like you bats are a bat man, like a shadow of the night.
Is that what you just said? Just move on.
We're not even going to get anywhere.
This actually makes the most sense to me is what I was trying to say.
What makes the most sense to you?
This is what you're trying to say. Is that a hot, a hot dog as Batman on a plate?
You're making no sense.
You're something is wrong. I feel like I just went crazy trying to puzzle out.
Can you answer, did you actually say a hot dog is, or a shadow is the Batman of the night?
Or did I?
Was I like falling asleep?
I heard that too.
[MUSIC PLAYING]