I
as a bad clap. There it is. Oh, my God, starting off the episode with a burp.
Are you kidding me? Guests have been getting a little too comfortable,
lately they have all every single guest has been way too comfortable with
belches. Have we started yet? Yeah, we're started. You know how they always
I guess that when people go oh yeah, like Maren yeah yeah, yeah, because I have
something to say that I don't want on the record yeah. Oh yeah, what do you
want to say? Well, that's what you would say. Oh yeah. I mean I was kind of
going off before, but yeah, we're going off. What were you saying?
One million like that, okay, that's what you don't want anyone to hear.
Well, everyone just heard that's that's what you don't want anyone to ever it
out. If we need to yeah, there's no post work that goes into this. There really
is not it's just a thing where it's not it's not quite the perfect. I know you're
I know you're looking around you, you're you're looking out the door right now,
you're laser focusing on people to say things about, but we're not cutting
anything out. This is crazy wait. Can you get to this camera?
You got to the Joe
this is the best.
This is the best idea we've ever had this camera right here. The joke, can't
Oh my God, stop drinking too much,
stop drinking too much Joe. You have a drinking problem. You have a drinking
problem that's yeah, seltzer, tell my grocery bill that
well you're going to drink all of them. You're going to drink the rest of this
box of white claws right now. It's like when it's like when a parent catches you
smoking a cigarette, makes you smoke the entire carton. You can't make it too
much seltzer. You make me drink a bunch of you've been playing too many video
games. I'm going to make you play all the games in the Assassin's Creed series
and we'll see how you like
little do parents know you're going to sit your ass down. You're going to play
a game on every console. Let's see if you start. You're still having fun.
Yeah, you like that you like that Atari twenty six hundred game. Yeah, I like
that you fucking moron. You fucking idiot, you fucking little weird fucking
ugly kid grub, you grub of shit, you grub hub, you grub of shit, you grab.
I would call my kid. I'm going to eat you. I'd call my kid a grub of shit.
Oh, you like that cigarette. Let's see how you like it. When I eat your whole
body.
You want to smoke that cigarette? Let's see how you handle a punch.
That's the
pure discipline. Let's see how you handle a
let's see how you handle a knuckle sandwich. The nerd dad who's eating is
let's say I handle a knuckle sandwich kid yeah he played. He like lost a level
on his. Let's see how you like a swirly. There was there's a story from like a
long time ago where oh you're you think you can smoke my cigarettes. We'll see
how you handle a purple nerple giving your kid a swirl.
There's a story from like two thousand and six or something where
a combat veteran
beat the shit out of his girlfriend's kid within an inch of its life, because
the kid deleted his Vice City save.
Wow and I don't know if that's an urban legend actually now that I'm thinking
about it, but
that's kind of the opposite of the nerd dad. I was thinking you were going to
say TSD yeah, we're going freak mode. I was I was thinking you were going to
say like the
something funny. He I thought he was
the most depressing. I thought you were going to say that the military dad like
used to like craft my God or something on well, yeah, you just training yeah
you just training was like like spinning around and let's
oh the TV's not. I was about to say Julio. Can you look up? Why isn't that
on? I'll turn that on right now. You introduce our did somebody my cousin
that reminds me of my cousin. Your cousin did that to his nephew or no, no,
I have a big family and my cousin, he's like a computer-y kid and he has a
Minecraft world that he spends like, you know, hundreds of hours building and
everything. And then another cousin, different parents, deleted his entire
Minecraft world. I think you told us about this. And then he started crying.
He got in trouble because he was crying. That's so crazy. It's something that he's like
I've worked hard on like yeah for months and then his mom is just like a
computer game. You are you're yeah shut up. Don't be gay. Just shut the hell up
it's messed yeah yeah. Minecraft is probably I would beat the crap out of
my kid. If he played Minecraft, I think it's changed the I think it's probably
changed the way that kids interact with their parents for yeah, because they
think that they could just parent relations, I never mom until she
becomes a diamond. Yeah, if you keep going deeper into your mom,
when it comes a diamond. I never like my what I mean either. I did not fuck. It
was like there. I was obsessed with Minecraft for a little while, but I
don't I really think it was play Minecraft. No, I think it was. I think
it was like encouraged. I feel like it was like a mass psychosis thing where I
was like so obsessed with Minecraft in like middle school, like me and all my
friends played Minecraft like every day. Did you have like a zombie shirt with
the no? I was I was a cool type of guy who was making machines
very making circuits, circuitry and LCD screens in Minecraft. But then I feel
like I went, I tried to go back to it a few years ago and it's like the worst
game. I couldn't even play dog five minutes of I wanted to dog kill myself.
I like that. I don't understand how you can like something that much and not
even have a nostalgia factor. Like I don't understand how I could have liked
it so much and then now I can't even like think about it. We have a server
for up. We have an official that Ralph runs.
Why do we have that? I hate that game. Do people use that you know? I don't know
if you play in our Minecraft server. If you play in the the podcast about this
Minecraft server, guess what you're getting you're you're going to be
shipped off to a
facility and we're going to run experiments and tests on you. You're
going to get it's the flayed yeah. If you're bad, it's going to happen to you.
If you play that damn thing, make a comment in the video. If you play in the
forever and we're going to nothing's nothing's going to happen now.
Nothing, nothing actually I'm kidding yeah, we're lately. I'm actually
completely kidding isn't it fun that everybody on these premium patron
episodes, everybody who comments we have full access to their address payment
information, full name yeah and email address. That's right. You better you
better stop talking shit about my life. Isn't it interesting to anybody who
comments below this? It's you think you're leaving a youtube comment, but
that you're really leaving. I have your actual fingerprint with every piece of
information
your entire life, a trail of bread crumb isn't it crazy? Okay, we can click. We
can click one button and download an excel spreadsheet of thousands of
people.
Yeah, we are going to be sending some powder in the mail to a lot of people.
Joe, what are you sipping on today? Today we've got a little spin drift
mojito, a spender, oh my God, should do drink of leaves yeah. It's pretty good.
I was I was I like you lime. Is this is this okay? I said you should do reviews
and for example of Rios, it's pretty good. I like the line it's lime and
mint. Do you is this one of the so is this a new because what you do and I
think that it's not crazy to do this
Joe will like a drink so much that he buys pallets of it pallets is a pallet or
you buy a couple boxes like you buy every two weeks. I get two boxes of liquid
death, Arnold Palmer, yes, that comes to my house before I've done coconut water.
Yeah, you when we live together, you would get like boxes of coconut water and
that what's that tea called
the green tea that comes in Ocha yeah fuck yeah. I get that like in you get so
so many boxes of that that the fridge, I mean that fridge was empty a lot of the
time. Yeah, there was not a lot of contribution. There was like like it was
like it would be like Neil's yogurt and then a bunch of my beers and then like
twenty four green teas. I mean, I think in an ideal world, did you ever see Mr
shy city? No, oh my God, Julio, can you pull up Mr. Shy city? Well, stock. I feel
like I know we're not going to we're not doing video. We have to know we got to
watch it. No, we're not watching a youtube video just because you like
the youtube. I think I think it's a perfect video. I feel like I have a
similar drink situation to you, where I really like water and I have a whole
infrastructure built in my house to just for water all the time. I have my
multiple rooms like you have like Brita filters.
I have like it's basically it looks like a metal tube and it's got two knobs, so
you can either get one cold type of water or a hot, which you're not supposed
I drink, but I do drink it in multiple rooms. Yeah, two rooms. Well, you have a
really really water in your house. Literally it's like if I want to drink
water when I'm cooking my meal yeah. I can do that if I want to drink water
when I'm shitting. I do that too. I have to yeah. There's actually two. I have
two vessels in one room of that where I can drink about and I guess if I'm
thinking about the bathroom, I guess I really can drink water out of three
places in the bathroom. Yeah, or if you have a shower shower, shower, shower,
tub. Memo is the third one. I was thinking toilet. You have two toilets
toilet since in the bathroom. I have three toilet sink shower tub. Remember
when you're saying a separate bath challenge yeah. He did the ice bucket
challenge with toilet water to raise awareness for no clean water in other
countries. Who did he was Matt Damon and he was like
I know this is an ALS ice bucket challenge, but I'm going to do
something a little different. I'm going to use water from my toilet and I'm going to
dunk it on my head. And he did that. He dunked toilet water all over himself just so he could
raise awareness for that. Buddy, there is already awareness being raised for that challenge.
You're going too hard. These people with ALS, Lou Gehrig's disease, you're trying to make
it Matt Damon's challenge.
I waited so long to get challenged for the ice bucket. I had an ice bucket
challenge filmed by
and I was just waiting for you. You filled it you're like. Thank you.
I will nominate me for the I just went no intro to it. Oh my God, but I had it
and I know you went crazy on it to big bucket. Lots of ice. No, I did mean
naked in my tub with just an ice tray because I was a funny one that it was
funny, but my friend got challenged. I was like dude, I'll film yours. I think
challenge. I think I did cup funny, funny little cup type of joke. My this is
probably pretty formative experience for all of us and in making yeah making
video. I didn't make one. I didn't make an ice bucket challenge bro. My you
know, people die from the ice bucket disease. My forty year old neighbor knew
me as the video kid and came over to my house and said hey, you like do video
stuff right. Can you help me do something really quick and he asked me to film his
ice bucket challenge and I told him no. I wasn't going to do that because I was
busy. I told him I was ending another video
and then I think my my older brother might have filmed it or maybe talk to him
about filming it. It's a pretty easy job yeah to film a nice, but I'm just
filming your forty year old something. No, you didn't. He said he wasn't going
chaos or anything you just said I need somebody to hold the camera for me. You
know back in the days, they would be like in the fifties. It would be if you
filmed your neighbor doing an ice bucket challenge, they'd bake you a pie or
something yeah. Nowadays, these adults have no respect to kids time. Now they
do not have respect. I say mo my they say can you mow my lawn? Okay, you're
done mom on now. Can you mow my lawn in the metaverse? Yeah, it's just chivalry
back then yeah, but that back in the like
you would think like oh yeah, like if I want to raise money, I'm just going to go
like like shovel old people's driveways right. These old people were giving you
like five dollars yeah. That's a back that was one billion dollars yeah back
then, but like that the old people, but they didn't change their amount. Oh
people did not they're like old people are like Costco hot dogs. They did not
just for inflation, like here's a nickel go buy a new xbox exactly yeah. It's the
same thing with the two bitch to fucking old you crap to going in your house to
get the shit out of you bitch you're I'm out here with a shovel and you have old
brittle bones and I could slam you. I have a weapon
telling an old person immediately like when they're by the way after you show
by the way, if it's lower than twenty yeah, you're going to get this show in
your fucking finish. I finished mowing the lawn with their big gas mower and
the their doorbell rings and they come to the door like what is it and they
open the door and I'm standing there with the mower like red like right in
front of the door. How much you going to pay me? How much enough I start mowing
all their carpets, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, ruining their on all their floors and
for
going in scraping up the hardwood with a fucking with a push mower from like
eighteen hundreds that they have you ever use a push mower. No, it sucks. I
know you have sucks man. Yeah, I don't know that I've ever mind a lawn. Yeah,
actually, I want to use a I want to use a push mower again in my life. I also
didn't have never mode. No, I did mow a lawn. I used to I lived with my sister
and she lived on this kind of like this house with a barn,
and they had a ride on mower,
and I would just drink. - Oh wow.
- It was like peak COVID, so I had nothing to do,
but drink and do the podcast,
and I would sit on the ride on mower,
and just had two white claws on it,
and I would just drunk drive the lawn mower around.
- Did he do a good job with the mower?
- No, no, no, no. - You fucked it up.
- You would look, and it would just be clear
that I was doing donuts for a couple minutes. It's just like a big chunk of
grass that's just like over mowed. Yeah, a ride on mower seems fun. Dude, it's so
awesome. A push mower is kind of fun in a, in like a Tinker Toys, Rube Goldberg
kind of way. Yeah. Where it's like, oh, it's
I like the idea of pulling a thing that makes a thing work. That's the opposite
of a push mower. You ever seen a push mower? You know what a push mower is?
It's the, it's like the toy that a kid has where it pops when they push it.
it's just it looks like a dolly like it's just a little way and a handle and the
wheel spin the blade. It's that circular blade thing right yeah, yeah and the
the fuck at least the one I had yeah that one the the the the on the top row
yeah yeah, yeah, well, he doesn't know electricity. Okay, old as fuck, but a
push mower is also one with a motor on it. Did you I guess I never know where I
mean I'm not to I'll be honest with you guys. I'm not too well versed in the
landscaping world. So I have no idea. I don't know what this thing was called.
I'm not well versed in the the landscaping world either, but there was
a thing. I think we can safely say none of us are well versed in the
landscape. Well, I did I worked for a landscaping company for one day when I
was fifteen. So you got some or fourteen rather. I
shoveled driveways for old people. We went out and we would shovel. I made
sixty bucks shoveling driveways
and
where it's like, oh, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, I remembered what I was originally gonna ask.
Have you ever, like, do you ever have like a friend
growing up that had like some old piece
of like landscaping equipment on their front lawn
as like decoration?
- No.
- Like one of these, I don't know if it was a ground,
if it was an excavator or something, like an old, like,
but this kid had like an antique, like,
it had like giant teeth in the front.
and if you like pulled some lever or something, it would have dug into the
ground and like lifted up earth or something. And I almost used it and it
was this kid that I'd only hung out with one time. I think I got a sugar rush and
tried to use it in his front lawn and his dad came out and just started freaking
the fuck out at me like, "No, no, no, no, no, no, don't touch it!" That makes
sense. Sugar rush. What were you eating?
Candy and sweets and soda. Yeah.
I'm sitting inside this kid's house and drinking a bunch of soda and then you're
like
I need a machine. I need a machine. I was a
available to you just be ocarina of time. So you're running out of we were
let's go running out of the house like a bird's eye view. You can see the
dotted line of your path and you're running out of the house. It's going to
like cross the street into a junkyard and yeah pulling a lever on a giant like
car crush
making cubes, making cubes out of cars, carrying them back to his house and
just throwing it through his windows. I really only was allowed after that. I
wasn't allowed to hang out at that kid's house. Damn you are you probably was
that your own arm off. I didn't rip my own arm off. I almost destroyed their
front lawn, but there was a there. They had a talk with that kid and we're like
you can't. This kid is not allowed. Yeah, it's a misbehavior. I oh yeah, I know I
know that other parents hated you. No, not as much I other other parents.
Usually I was like I know that when you were around they were like oh hey, they
were nice to see you and as soon as you left they were like oh my God, that kid
no
but yeah, I did
I did talk a lot. I did try to
because I used to watch like I love the s and stuff, so I tried to like talk to
parents about old movies, yeah, an old TV, old movies that you saw a two minute
waterbun yeah the a and Michael Ian Black being like that movie was gay.
Do you like the movie? Do you like the movie short circuits
with fish o stevens? He plays an Indian guy. Do you like that? It was so crazy
of them to make that decision in the s yeah nowadays that would not fly. I
feel like you were probably a kid who was you were probably very polite to
parents yeah. I was put I was a like kid in general yeah. I was scared of parents,
but then when the parents were gone, I'd be running around their day. Oh, I know,
oh yeah, yeah,
I was my friend real castels. I was he was like really bad at school and I was
okay at school and his mom used to talk to me like
like. Can you like get him like to do his school? Like can you get him to be
good at school and I was like I don't know where you got the memo that I'm
like a great student. That's probably you glasses. I had glasses. Yeah, that's
like yeah, you want to kind of the bad kid starts hanging out with the kid with
glasses. It's like the mom is like all right, you're a great influence. That's
kind of movie vibes. That's kind of like the mom being like please yeah. You have
to help am I supposed to do? I don't know what my husband just left. I hang
out with your son because he has unlimited soda
unlimited soda and pizza whenever I come over yeah. I'm not here to do
homework. The pizza kid, the pizza kid at school, dude, a pizza kid. Oh my God,
every kid who would have Papa Gino's at every birthday, a fucking pizza kid.
Dude, pizza kid, kid who brought in cupcakes on his birthday. Good kid,
kid who there's also the rice cake kid. Who the fuck is that? The kid who was
allergic to stuff and they forgot their lunch snack. Okay, there's a kid.
There was one kid in my school
and every whenever someone brought in cupcakes, he had like a stash of rice
rice cakes that he could eat. So he felt like he was also yeah. Okay, you go to
the nurse's office. If you forgot your lunch and they could get or your snack or
something and they give you like a crackers or rice cakes or something. I
would now I would actually eat a rice cake over. I put all the peanut allergy
kids at one table yeah, because they could all have different types of
allergies. Yeah, but just like being like you guys have to sit at this table and
it's the table where we taped a bunch of paper that has pictures of pictures.
no be yeah tormenting the fucking kid. You guys both have that you didn't want
that at your school. You probably I guess you went to some progressive woke
school where everybody had peanut allergies. We weren't allowed to bring
peanuts to school. Yeah, you weren't allowed to bring to school at all. Well,
no, you could have like a peanut butter and jelly sandwich, but you couldn't
you have to eat or there's something there's some like tree.
Yeah, the bathroom away from the special table where you have to sit. If
you had a peanut allergy, I used to sit there. I said there was a while kids,
barely any kids with the peanut allergies. So yeah, it's literally that's
what I mean it would be like yeah. Two kids max yeah, I'd be like forced to sit
at a table alone. Couldn't you just kind of go against the grain and not do it? I
mean, I guess it depends on if you want to die to either of your allergies,
you're allergic to like carrots and yeah,
but I I'm not allergic to any food. I'm actually I'm allergic to some medicines
penicillin yeah me too. I'm allergic to penicillin, moccasin,
I was like OTC raw cherries, raw carrots, raw apples, raw
you are so first hazelnuts. It does feel like it's a kind of thing that you just
didn't like them when you were a kid and now I loved fruits and stuff. When I
found out that I found out that I couldn't eat peaches, was like I ate a
peach and then my lip started to swell up and I got so mad because I love
peaches. You went insane on the lawn after that dude. You got a serious hole
excavate some fucking kids house. That is kind of I mean I've seen you eat guacamole
and it was a troublesome situation. Yeah, it was. Yeah, I'm allergic to. Then I got
the rest of the tacos. To pain killers. I can't take like Tylenol or Ibuprofen or anything
like that. You must be enduring everything. I endure everything every day. Oh my God.
To hold that on your shoulders. Yeah, pretty tough. Holy crap. It's actually completely
pretty fun. I think that people are babies if they have to take a
painkiller for a headache. Yeah, I just like it. I actually like the pain. I
know I just like taking pills. Yeah, no, I could that's what I mean. Like I
can't imagine it's so weird to me to be able to take a pill to have like when
you have a headache or something. I just don't understand. I think it's cool to
take a pill. I don't know. Maybe I love taking pills for everything else in my
head. It's like so scientific in my head. It's like like, oh, I'm feeling this so I
can take this. I can take this to make it go away. Yeah, I do think if I if I do
like an allergy to it because it's been a long time since I've had like it was
when I was a kid that I found I was allergic to it, so it could have gone
away by now, possibly, but I haven't like tested. I feel like if I test and it has
gone away, I think my entire life is going to completely change. Yeah, you're
going to just start come up. You did the allergy thing with like the big well, no,
So for that, I took it and I started to not be able to breathe.
Ah, bummer.
Anaphylaxis.
Planetary anaphylaxis.
Anaphylaxis right in the pterodactyl.
Oh my God, save this for the next five fingers, dude.
That would be insane if we did a rap about allergies.
Anaphylaxis.
There's a rap about allergies I'll show you guys after.
Oh yeah?
Yeah, but I can't.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
but I can't wait. I remember that. I remember the talk about it. We'll put a
we'll put a we will remember this. I can't say anything about it right now.
I should do that. I should do a cover of that rap. I think it's been taken off
the internet. What like what's that song that fucking Johnny Cash song the I've
been everywhere just doing that, but just listing every single allergy that
you
man is still in my to sillin
man. I fucking hate allergies, though yeah it is the most hate my allergy.
This past allergy season was so bad. The pollen season, yeah, the worst ever of
my entire life. I really hated myself. I feel like in general the weather's kind
of been yeah. I feel like something's been happening with the weather lately,
but I can't think of what feels fucking a pocket. Here's a this is an actual hot
hot button. The flood stuff that's been happening recently yeah. Is that really
global warming? Yeah yeah, no way feels like it's not it rain happens all the
time yeah, but if dude bed, start reading like that is crazy. I think it's
like it. I mean I agree that I don't this is not to say that global. I think
the reason that it rains more is because there's more heat and so it's fucking
with the wind and the rain patterns. I think is a weather. The weather is
weather is actually about a system of hot and cold. Yeah, it just feels like
attacks bro. You just blew my fucking mind. Oh my God, but yeah, I think so. I
think that that make I mean it is it is the past few years have been not to get
to
to get real as fuck, but the past years have been very real crazy because I do it
is like I feel like I'm living in a different world than I was when I was a
kid. It genuinely feels completely different. Yeah, definitely summer does
not feel good anymore. The summer was pretty is different, too. I like this
new winter, though I like and maybe it's also because I moved to New York from
New England that the winter feels different yeah, but we've had we had
snow all the time. I feel like there's not going to be snow this year, but it's
still always a little colder. It's feeling like it's going to be a great
Christmas. The first year that we lived here to get the last time it snowed
two thousand and five. I was going out the super storm. Yeah, I was going out
in. I was like going out and skating in a T shirt and jeans in December. Yeah,
that's crazy man. Two years ago, three years ago, when I moved here, you know
what else is crazy that I was thinking about the other night when I was getting
ready to go to bed. So which is when I have most of my thoughts
about this kind of thing. Isn't it crazy that there's one continent that's all
completely, it's only ice, there's it's nothing but there's no land, there's no
trees, there's no- That's not a continent. I guess it is. It is a
continent. No, but you gotta have like a McDonald's or a Subarro or something.
dude it's a it's only ice there's it's there's not even any dirt. It's just
ice. It's only ice in the water and like a bunch of fucking animals all live.
I is just
it's pretty tough that they got like full continent. You know pass yeah that
crazy that I don't know you got to have at least you got it's cool. It's cool to
have what they got mountains. They got a will you pull up the have you heard of
ice mountain? No, it says all the different flags that own Antarctica. Oh
so yeah, it's also it's cool to have a continent that they were there like
okay guys. We can finally can at least agree that this is one continent that
will belong to nobody because nobody wants to
don't go here. Guys, how many flags are on there is that is am I oh wait that
little weird thing with the flags on it. Oh, that works, okay, is this even a
real thing like nobody?
Why the fuck does Argentina got it because they're mad close? Oh, they're
right now. Yeah, they're that I don't even think of Argentina is like cold and
I see at the bottom. I didn't even fucking think about the world is so
insane. Why would you need to think about it? I don't I don't know. I just
don't think about the planet at all. I think about I think about the United
States and Africa and Europe. Geography is probably the Africa to like Africa's
and Australia, Africa, okay, I guess I think about everything, but south of the
hemisphere south of the border. No, every once in a while I think about I
think about the different place in the world for a while. Yeah, I would say
you're watching this video of this couple who went to Chongqing in China
and it's they're like it's like a tick tock, like like travel video and
they're like guys. This is the most incredible city ever. There's so much to
do and it was like a fifteen minute video and all they do the entire time is
look at building. It's all like just like like cyberpunk twenty seventy seven
like sky, like skyscrapers with neon light and they just like they just look
at everything go and this is what we did next. We went and looked at this
building and it was incredible. It's like the blade runner like type city. I
don't know. Do you know the one I'm talking about? It looks like blade
runner. Yeah, the one in... I don't know which one you're talking about, but... I
think we're talking about the same one, but yeah, there was like a whole... Oh,
it takes one day to get there. That sucks. It takes one day to get there?
Yeah, it would take one day to get there from here. But can you... Isn't it
crazy that you could go to China, the most wonderful country on earth, and all
you do is look at buildings? Yeah, they didn't even take in the local cuisine.
no, though there was five straight minutes of the of the they also yeah. The
first half of the video is just them in their hotel being showing the different
windows.
Oh my God, I look at the
reasonable yeah, but you're going you're traveling to China to look at buildings.
Yeah, I think there's also probably a factor of like being a vlogger. You need
to like do some shit yeah. If you're like one of these, but that's what I'm
saying. They didn't do anything. It looks at building of doing things. What is
buildings. Maybe they're like an architecture blog. It was it could be
they weren't they were just they were just they're just on vacation. Yeah, I
guess if you have if you're that that is I always have I always have one one day
of a of a vacation that's like that like yeah, let's just go look at buildings.
I don't want to do it sometimes vacation. I don't like like I don't like a hard
schedule. Yeah, no yeah, of course, I want a very I just want to of course not
dude. I don't want to I literally I if I go to like a city or something, I do
I'm just saying I'm on an NPC walk cycle. I'm going to the same thing.
There's I look up on the map. I immediately look up Walgreens near me or
like severe like department store or whatever yeah. If I'm going to do
pharmacy, I immediately I try to embed in the local country. I know I know I'm
going to work.
I know
I'm getting up. I'm getting it with five AM and I'm walking with with a bunch of
other salary men. Yeah, just getting an elevator and pressing the top floor.
rough day yesterday opening a street food. I'm opening my own street food
stall. I'm in a suit street food. Yeah, I'm still in a suit yeah. I'm like
yeah.
I wish I could do that. I like to if I'm in a different place. I like like even
Canada. You just get the different candy and soda that they have. Oh yeah, yeah,
so you got to look at everything. I love the different type of chips. They got
the different Doritos in Mexico. Yes, I had some of those in Mexico. The coolest
The thing that they do on their bags is they have a big warning label.
Sodeo Excessivo.
What's the word for sugar? Azucar?
Azucar.
Azucar Excessivo.
I feel like I've been transported to Esplanade.
And they have giant, they put giant stickers on all the food that say that. It's so awesome.
It looks like the food you're eating...
Both of your guys' pronunciation is so amazing.
It looks like the food you're eating has been banned and it looks like you're in a Fahrenheit 451 universe for cookies.
that's yeah and you're fighting against the government. You have a secret stash
of Doritos. You see those big warning labels and then you realize like oh
yeah, we're just eating that shit all the time dude. It's like how to think
about the cigarette warning labels go so fucking hard yeah like we're going to
put that on every piece of food. We're going to put that on to read yeah
picture, but just a
fat guy. He's crying.
That would work. I get a mirror just like
this is how we how we're going to come back. Obesity is just putting a picture
of a big guy and it's like well, it's just rude. Can you imagine like how
fucking hard it would go if they had like on every chips of hoy they put like
a picture of like a guy like cover in a morgue, like with his feet sticking out
with a big by a seat, a big blanket with a giant like a rump on it. Yeah yeah,
just like an appendicitis scar yeah, just because no wait the panker like a
pancreas surgery scar yeah on his controls. The what I the thing that
would deter me the most is like a really puffy big fat hand with cheese dust on
it, like the like the Prince Andrew finger thing. They remember that she's
got a looned up like sausages. I do remember it's just a thing of imagine
that those with fucking
spicy sweet chili Dorito yeah, they should or that just on the outside of
the bag. Yes, so that when you pick it up at the store, you know the texture
that you're yeah, they use that hand trying to go into a pringles can and not
and it can't fit. Yes, and then and then I get Pringle and then you flip it over
and then they're crying because they can and it's they do like a tag on the
side of it. It comes on a string that you can flip over and see they do it.
They do like a like a to like a comic where it's like multiple panels of
different pictures and the first one is a is a fat guy and he's waking up and
he's eating Doritos and the second one is he's going outside and it's snowing.
The third one is he's going out and he's walking across a frozen pond and the
fourth wise hand is
and said this can this can happen to you. If you too many to read, it's like in
the Harry Potter world, it's like a little animated video that that's what
I have in the future yet
yeah, does it's not even related to like being overweight. It's just like a fat
guy falling into a man hole
with the Harry Potter. I just said that you can't like you, you know you watch
that and you're like oh in the future, we're going to have like moving
pictures, movies on foods, but now it's just like I don't want it, but they're
you're going to have it. It's screens instead of like magic actually doing it
honestly screens are magic yeah, but it's I just see that you know. I see
through the magic. I know it's just lights, but that's the thing about those
like labels like the excesses of if they were to do the cigarette type things,
the only warning that they could give on like Doritos and stuff is like you will
become fat yeah. There's no like no, no everyone would be so mad at no. You
know what they do is they just have to show a guy who's going like oh yeah,
so you will have a stomach
stomach
on a chocolate bar.
You eat excessive amounts of this. You will get a tummy ache.
There is no way in hell that that will not happen. Just pictures are like
babies throwing up because they ate too many like Doritos yeah that really
that's the only thing you could do that wouldn't piss everybody. Yeah, that
wouldn't be like a wrong thing to do. It would also need to be controlled. You
you need to have like an FDA guy who just eats Doritos and it's like
how many duries
picture put it on the bag. Then there's one guy picture. Yeah, one guy's just
got like Joey. He's like the Joey chestnut of Doritos and he doesn't even
know it yet. This one he's at the CDC or whatever the FDA and he's like like oh
my God, you guys
stymied a Dorito machine. Yeah, I guess I'm Doritos. You can also do
I guess the other so it's either it's either stomach a guy, yeah picture on
label or you could have guy who it's too spicy. He's crying is he's tearing
at his nose, dripping these labels would look amazing or or little piece of
little stuck piece of Dorito stuck on the roof of your mouth. Yeah, stuck in
the tooth, shard, shard, I guess yeah. I guess the only two warnings you can
have the only two or three is like that and then like dental warning yeah, I'm
like a bag of smart food yeah
to make sure we'll get stuck. It'll get stuck in your tooth and it'll be
you put that on lettuce to yeah, you got to put that on lettuce and kale and all
that you put warnings of everything that can happen with need on every they
need war. They should every food they should print it on each individual leaf
of lettuce. There should be a warning ink picture on popsicles that say once
you're done with this brain freeze, but once you're done with this buddy, you
going to laugh yeah laughing. You got a laugh
pointing at
his head, holding his head and his leg yeah, yeah, it's got having a heart
attack. We can't tell, but then at the bottom it says you're going to get a
brain freeze and you're going to laugh. It needs to cover every possible side
effect yeah brain freeze, maybe melt out stained hand stain, good sticky hand,
stained hand, laughing at the thing brain freeze and then also you bit into
it. So your teeth are called splinters splinter from the mistake
man go. You know,
we're actually returning to be a google right now wound man. We just reinvented
the wound. What is wound man? The wound man is a medieval art motif yeah. This
is what we've just created, but for food I just realized
can you expand one of these pictures, please one of the what was what was
wound man supposed to this is just shows all the different ones you can get. Oh
my God, this was a warning against like swords. Basically, in I don't remember
seems like the only this is a this is a dope as it's hard. It's very cool. I
sure there's a million dark souls fans out there who have this tattoo. It's
like the only wounds you can get or just something stabbing you yeah right.
It's
I think I might be on a stick of medical
do we need to create the modern wound man. We just did we did, but he's the
food man, but we need to create a modern wound man,
a food man, but then like you know, like things that could happen to you like I
guess a bullet tired, tired, yeah, bullet tire. You can eat this possible. It is
the most prominent man is just getting shot at different parts of his body.
Yeah, different guns. It's just a big cheese screen. It's a surgical diagram.
Oh okay, so it's like
a doctor. It's like how to operate on the different like injuries that you
what's happening to this guy? It's just a doctor's seeing that's be like Jesus
going to pro cam. See it's like a very hard. What did you do? What just
happened? You killed it now, okay, that's fixed. There we go.
What we were showing was too gruesome. Yeah, I guess it was. It's a surgical
diagram, I guess, so we literally did create the food man is completely, but
see if I'm in surgery and I see this. I don't think it's going to help me. I
he's going to show you're not looking. No, no, no, the surgeon is looking at
manual on the other surgeon is going to do to you. What do I do my I'm in
search? They're about to take up my appendix. I'm like buddy. The incision
is supposed to be vertical yeah. Hey,
I'm looking at the. Are you sure you're doing this right doing your own surgery?
Pretty pretty cool. My uncle was he's like an air force medic and I think he
was like study. He was like living at my house at the time before he like
joined the Air Force and he was like studying up on all that stuff and he had
just had like all these medical like journals and shit and one day I was
like I think it was like at after breakfast. I just saw him reading and he
went. I was like what is that? What's that book and he just turned the book to
me and it just showed me it was just a woman with a fork in her throat, like
stuck right there. He was like check that out and I was like
I think about that image all the time to this to this day. I think that's one of
the scariest and most traumatic things I ever saw as a child was a woman with a
like a trachea trachea to be yeah real life squidward yeah yeah. He was
showing me real life squidward
female squidward in squidward squidward squidwardina
so they ever give squidward a girlfriend in the show. No, he can
not only gay, he's canonically gay.
that's why my cousins weren't allowed. I thought one Bob was a gay. No, is all
the others, canonically a sexual Sponge Bob is gay. He's a sexual. I think
that's what he was in like the Nickelodeon pride. No sponge, but post
a squid Villa, whoa, I would use a crush on her. Wait a minute. Does squidward
first, but he has a can you imagine writing an article about whether or not
squidward has a wife that looks exactly like my girlfriend? You guys
I'm getting rock hard right now, imagining me as squidward and my
girlfriend is squidville. It's kind of fucked up how similar he looks to her
yeah. I mean it's just as well. It's because all squidwards look the same
whoa
by an episode is made evident that every single squidward looks alike.
That's when sponge Bob got too real for yeah, so yeah, I've got fucking racist
to see that's when I stopped my kids from watching sponge Bob. My dad didn't
let me watch sponge bob. My mom did he was it was it because he thought it was
they were gay. No, it's because when he was in the other room, he didn't want it.
He thought it was like an annoying sound. Oh yeah, that's why my friend wasn't
allowed to watch Sweet Life of Zack and Cody. I wish I didn't watch any like
Disney. I didn't I didn't in a bid. I have a hard time relating to a lot of
people my age. Yeah, I don't go like what's fun at what me. I didn't want to
have the
what that's what Raven used to say. Oh snap, I never watched raven. My dad also
said we couldn't say snap because it just meant that we were saying oh shit yeah
that's smart. It's custom or dead. I mean we had watch it like here and then, but
like
I got I found out about adult swim too young and once you like see like an
adult cartoon like that, it changes like it's like well that one looks funnier
for me. I didn't really watch many of those those shows when I was growing up.
I was more of a computer kid than a TV kid, but then my younger sibling was a TV
kid. So I feel like I saw all the like Disney shows that are like five years
younger than us. Yeah, I feel like I know a bunch of the ones that are like
people younger than us would know that no, you have a chance guy. They don't
watch that one, but I'm trying to think of an example of one and you guys ever
watch Ant Farm. No, the girl that was this girl from my high school dated one
of the guys on that show and that's that huge news in town. That's one of the
show like I feel like that shows that are that are younger than us that I feel
like I saw so much more of those than anything from our age short. That was
his name Jake short yeah. She dated Jake short and everyone was like. Did you
hear wait Jake? Jake short is completely the opposite of Jake long short,
who's Jake long the American dragon yeah. I remember that there's a kid.
We used to call Jake long on the bus current interesting. We like he was he
was not Asian American, but maybe he called him Jake like it is. No, you
called him this kid, Dan Seminek said that he looked like they would that was
his last name and he said he would call a kid S E M A N E K damn and he did an
amazing to
and he would call this kid American Dragon, and I think he might have been
he might have been like Native American or something or I don't know why he
would call that boy American Dragon yeah and it was a racial. That's a cool
nickname to have
well, maybe if you're American Dragon, if you're an adult out of the context of if
it's specifically in reference, call you get on the bus and everyone's like
what's up dragon that's beast that's so sick. It's really depends on the kind
like if it's not if it's not earned for doing like cool fire breathing stuff
yeah. No, that's a good point also yeah. I think it depends on who who of the
kid, the kid kid liked it okay. I can he laughed at it, but I don't know if he
liked it. There's a kid in my school who kept calling me uncle Joe yeah. This van
is trying to smash through our door. Oh my God, it's Amazon Amazon Prime just
the rave up on to us. Guess what basos these new trucks are kind of get us kind
of scary man as space ag yeah, yo yo
where you guys are all derailed there. What were you guys like bullied at all?
I was bullied heavily from the ages of one to five yeah, yeah, that's crazy. I
think I was
definitely was when I was in like first and second grade. I was a pretty
annoying kid yeah, well, you know, because yeah, they had to have a how to
they pulled aside because like these kids that were like friends with me
decided to like bully me sounds like they weren't and I didn't even know I
was getting bullied.
Sounds like they weren't friends yeah. They were not. What are they doing? I
don't know they would just like fuck with me a lot and then the teacher had
to pull them aside. This kid, Chris, Laskawa,
call him out yeah. Fuck you, that's right.
We became friends again after that, but yeah
that I think I was more of a me. Not really yeah. I think I was. I think I
was a door for a while, but I was I was. I think I was the archetypical
mean nerd mean nerd yeah, but getting and giving and receiving you what
Liz Lemon Liz Lemon. I was a Liz Lemon yeah pretty much. I think I think we
all were Liz Lemons. Huh we've all kind of been Liz Lemons and at some point
in our life, it's honestly one of the most resonating TV characters of all
time and we're all just looking for our Jack
have you guys ever had a mentor? Yeah, yeah, I have one of millions of mentors
in my life. Damn it, I had a I'd be a perfect mentor your school, like you
look at them as like you are my men. Oh, no, we just played. We played we played
hearthstone together
at school, made made me have a mentor because I was doing so badly and missing
everything yeah and then he was just very cool. We just talked about over
watching hearthstone every yeah, but you got your homework done with him. No, we
had to do. He didn't do shit some mentor. We had some fire like that, too, but it
was mostly me hanging out in the after school. I would have to stay after
school to do my homework, so I had something called like the periods went
from a through H. It was called I period and I had to me and like five other kids
had to stay after for I period. It was like two hours. It was also because my
my mom and dad like worked a bunch. It was like they didn't know what to do
with me after school, and I would have to go to an after school program just
to do my homework, and I hung out with this old man named Mr. Mac, who loved
the Beatles, and he had his assistant was named Mr. Colachi, and Mr. Colachi
knew what Team Fortress two was. Yes, so that was my homie. I was talking to
him about yes, yes, yes, I was showing him Gmod videos. This is an experience
that so many kids with ADHD have, finding the one, the one slightly younger
adult who knows the one thing that you also know, and he was telling me how
good he is at Huntsman Sniper, and I was like yeah, I mostly play as demo man
right now, but I've been switching over to pyro.
It was like the like the only time I've ever felt like a connection to an adult
and an adult teacher, your language, yeah, the only time I've ever been like
this teacher somebody like that in my life again, somebody who's who's like
well, that's the thing we're like years older than me. We are not the Padawan
anymore. No, no, it's time to go find some kids man
pass it on on the way up here. There was a fire drill. It was like hard to walk
up here. There's like from a school yeah. There's no idea what you're saying
like two hundred. What do you mean you're in a school and there's a like
where were you that there's a but I understand now that's one yeah, so you
went and hung out with all the kids and you're trying to mentor them. Is that
where you're telling I was just shaking going up to the kids and be like
making all the kids. Don't be afraid guys. A fire drill doesn't mean there's a
fire. It's usually a test, but it's going to be also don't now don't start
don't start running around yeah, because you don't want to stay in line
stay in line. You don't want the muscle memory of fooling around during a fire
drill. You don't want to disrespect your teacher. You never want to
you wouldn't want to disrespect your teacher and run around. Would you the
teacher like catches you
hey
you run
you
the kid goes over the teachers like like Miss. There's like scary guy like
points at you and you're like I don't know what you're talking about. I'm
simply in your average adult. I'm one of the students of the
astute. I am the student and
you get to go stall trying to be
making it way worse, making it way, but all yourself, the student inspector,
like just got to you just behind bars like a fucking thought that one would
work. I am the student inspector and I take a close look at the student body
to make sure nothing is abnormal or out of line hanging out outside the school
in case of a fire drill like twenty four seven yeah.
I'm here to be we are old studio back inside our old studio was right next to
a in elementary school. It's impossible to do anything here. That's not right
next to an elementary school. Yeah, there are a lot of fucking suck for
pedophiles to live in this area of New York, because there's a school every two
blocks. Yeah, I guess all the pedophiles have to live in like go on us next to
all the I feel like they are shipping kids in from Connecticut to go to school.
You're like charged up about it. I it's crazy. I don't know I just there just so
many schools. Yeah, one I've always lived next to a school. So it's a very it's a
very dense densely populated. Yeah, we live right our first apartment at twenty
two star. We lived right across the street from a school, across the street
from a school old office right next to a school. I live next to a school right
now. Yeah, I live a block away from a school. Yeah, I live a block away from a
school and then about like maybe four blocks from another school. You know
what I made it out of a school. I live two blocks away. I actually I'm thinking
right now and I there are three schools within four blocks of me. Yeah, you live
by hell of schools. Yeah, that's what I'm saying. It's so many you live by like a
school on every block. How do you how do they need that many so many people?
There's too many people. It's a very easy. Some schools have better education
than others. Yeah, I mean there's also a thing of like, but that even with how
many people you don't need them that close to each other. You do know you
don't rivalry. Start a rivalry is bad. Rivalry is good. According to the my you
know what rival, you know what rivalry has created what and honestly this might
it too far to say I'm going to say it anyway.
Rivalry caused the Holocaust.
What was the rivalry, the rivalry, which were the teams and the Jews one on he
was jealous of what they could achieve. He can he's he's the only Jewish one
here. He can talk about it right. You're Jewish me yeah. I thought you were
Jewish. I'm a quarter Jewish, he's a quarter, but I don't count. I'm not
allowed to be was that not the mom side, but think about that when you're talking
we're putting schools a block away from each other. Well, think about what you
might about how, but but also rivalry created you know Microsoft and it
created apple. Two of the most evil fucking companies of all time, Bill
Gay, first of all, Bill Gates, who is
it created he's an evil wizard, who's dropping mosquitoes all across the city
to suck blood out of people on leave them to be as dry as potato chips and
Steve Mosquito Jobs is straight up a mother fucking zombie. He dead. He
drink the juice till he died. He he drank juice when he had cancer because he
wanted to get to hell faster to reform it
and rule over it. He wanted to streamline hell. He wanted to put kiosks
all over hell. Yeah, he wanted to put a genius bar down there so that he could
he could make the the deviling experience a lot more streamlined and when
he did you know what hell right now, completely white, completely white,
looks like an apple store. There's tables everywhere and guess what they
all wear shirts all where wait. Why do I feel like? Why do I feel like hell would
be completely but not white and banal and heaven would be like tie dye with
fires going on and like hell a partying and smoke going up in the heaven
probably looks like fucking burning man. I mean that that's the original
rivalry right heaven versus hell yeah
speaking of rivalries, I've spoken upon this a million times, but there was a
my high school very small compared to our rival high school, which had four
other cities that would they would bus kids into,
so it was like a student body of like probably like twenty thousand versus
like I think ten thousand or some shit. I don't know the numbers, but every
year there's a student body of twenty thousand kids, something like that
there's a
I think I'm exaggerating the numbers here. I'm exaggerating the numbers of
your school had ten thousand and there had twenty
if you tip the scales correctly, we went to a really small school, really small
school. No, I'm in the district, the district. I mean it's craziest building
ever yeah. It was huge no because that school Pinkerton Academy looked like a
fucking. It looked like a fucking college campus. That's the name of a
school in a book that Tim Burton adapt yeah and like twenty nine and that was
the right. That was my rival high school was called Pinkerton Academy. Will you
look up jacket academy. It was huge. It was it was like it had different. I just
build down my high school and rebuilt it into a gigantically large building.
Yeah, Pinkerton Academy, it'll say how oh wait yeah, just set it right there
number of students three thousand yeah, that's big. That is pretty big
twenty thousand. Well, then look up legendary. I see a picture of pink
legendary. I probably was Pinkerton good at sports. Now I'm thinking about it's
probably the same yeah. That's what that high school looked like versus my
fucking shitty. I
go there. So
you guys wanted to go to Pinkerton Academy. So bad, dude, I want my dad to
move in my home town is crazy. I wanted to move literally three blocks, three
city blocks away. Was it a boarding school? No, damn that's fucking. It was
just the it was just the high school for the town and I wanted to go there
because they had a better video and TV program than our school and but you
just got like districted into the other yeah yeah, just I mean I probably could
have gone there yeah, but I had to go to fucking London, very high, where all the
teachers hated my guts and they blocked me on Twitter. What is London? There's
no building that they built for my high school. It's gigantic. This is not even
the full thing. This is like half of it. I can see it in
in real life. Look, they had a sugar house. What's a sugar? I don't know if
they had a fucking sugar house. Look at that. I would guess that someone look at
name. Look at this fucking shit. Wow, it's like a museum dude. Everything got
better when we left it.
Isn't that fucked up the city? If we move out of New York, they're probably
going to make it. They're going to go down. They're going to make it bigger.
How would I add a new borough? If we leave, they add a new borough called
okay, wait, fuckers, native New Yorker, lifelong. If they added a new borough,
what's your dream borough? What would the name be for the sixth one? Probably
Motown. Okay, I would say they probably have like delis and maybe like like oh
like a Japanese grocery store. There's a dog park. That's actually nice.
How big is it? It's really, really big, but all fenced in know the the burrow
of the burrow. It's like a city block,
so it's like the whole and where would you put it?
I would put it like right around my where I currently live right now, yeah,
which is
it's I'm not going to I'm not going to say that no, no, don't say it. Don't say
your address, although you can probably find me. Do you look hard enough? I'm
not hard to find you're a tall person yeah and I do not go very many places.
Yeah, you go to like that makes it harder to find you. You were an insane
creature of habit.
Why you like I mean you buy the same drink in twenty four packs. I live with
you. I know I know that you do the same shit every day. Yeah, sometimes you're
supposed to do yeah. I mean sometimes it's well you're you're you're like
Amelia Bedelia. You are you are very
ever really thought about that yeah. We do kind of live exact opposite. Yeah,
that's why we were such good roommates brain styles. Yeah, there should be a
to you do a lot of you guys yeah, yeah, just living in different like like not
hanging out sometimes
hey what's up man? I'm going out tonight. Oh we're running into a street. Oh
hey man, I got oh yeah, I gotta go to the store. I'm gonna play fall guys.
Yeah,
the TV show yeah, it just keeps cutting a joke.
Patrick going all over the city doing like crazy stuff, meeting new people
going to do like new stores and stuff and I play fall guys. I put the
controller down. I take the dog out. I go back and play more fog. Yeah,
everyone, you take out your phone and you go to the living room to watch a
movie new skin on fall guys.
There did well. I thought you guys would like it. They put in like Godzilla
stuff yeah. You had already told me about that before, though, so it's kind
of old news. I didn't see the one of the three headed dragon one, Gidora,
what was a king in the living room?
What you put like he Joe put like a hall of fame in the living room. Oh yeah
yeah actor or person hall of fame pictures of actors that Joe like
well
when it's treated with like the, you know, reverence, the reverence of the
hall of fame,
the guys right, it's more than the guy's name from blue collar, yeah, fat,
putting the fat coto and like putting the names of Rosa Parra, Rosa Park,
Elaine May, Tom Green, Tom Green, Tom Green Coolidge, Tom Green, Jennifer
Coolidge. We were kind of like looking to fill out the roster a little bit. I
like Jennifer Coolidge, Tom Green. I think with Tom Green was a patch right
that like jennifer coolidge, why even say that what you just said, what I'm
just saying like there was kind of fucked up. If she hears that she's not
going to be having, I'm just saying we had a oh no, she deserved it. She was
hey, she was still in the hall of fame. I wasn't
I
fucking pissed off kicking like I wasn't nominated. I wasn't elected getting
every time you see your hall of fame. You set up getting so pissed off that
you're not on it. I was pretty pissed off. I just didn't like that house. I
I just remember here like you had the hall of fame up there and I just
remember like our other the Alex and Neil like having girls over and just
immediately having to be like oh yeah. Our roommate Joe did that still the
funniest things when Alex brought oh my God, we had like the prop gun that we
use for the gun that you've seen us pull out a million times and it looks real
very
realistic. This is on like a first date and he came back to that apartment and
there's just a really real
on the
on the like coffee table and then she like they like hung out for a little bit
and she's like it was like going well before that she's like I'm going to go
yeah and then he was like oh fuck
a gun. It's not real look, look putting it on your head, putting in your head
at this point. Look, it's not real. It's fake. It's a fake. I the thing I
remember hearing about from that apartment that always made me laugh as a
and this is a funny Joe thing is
you're on trial, buddy. Yeah, the trial of Joe Gleason is movie points. Oh my
fucking God. Well, it never works. My fucking God, I forgot about movie
points. It never works.
Movie points was a was a it was pitched. It never really it never happened, but
it was a system where we each gained. I've never let me say also be points
for never. I've never ever heard how it's work, how it actually worked. I've
never heard Joe talk about it ever. I only heard it about from the heard about
from the three other members of the apartment separately being like others
movie points.
Well, what we wanted what we were trying to do we were I was trying to build like
household camaraderie and like have a fun thing. No, you know you were treating
the house like it was summer camp, which was honestly it was really, really nice.
It made I really loved it a lot. It also meant I don't like, but I mean a
bunch of shit like points that well movie points. It was where every Friday. I
think we're supposed to watch a movie all together. That was the idea that and
you got to choose the movie based off of you, the accumulation of movie points,
but that was terrible in that house because it was then a competition. Well,
I don't know. I don't really understand how you got movie points in my mind. It
was you got movie points at the beginning of the month. You what you
don't understand how it works. He did not understand.
It was still in like the conceptualization phase. Okay, it never
it was really flew. It never took off and I think there's another problem with
that house was that people didn't do
people didn't do chores or like shit. You know, Patrick was big into cooking
something and then leaving it on the stove and then I would do it the next
day. Yeah, which is tough, but that's right gross. I know that's real was Neil
was now you know Neil, which honestly with a woman, honestly, what kind of was
worse was that Neil wasn't we had a dishwasher, but Neil was insistent on he
would is not going to take part in the dishwasher. He's going to hand wash his
own dishes, so then that also meant that sometimes they're just either dishes
there in the sink that he didn't wash yet or they would just be like poorly
washed dishes put away yeah and then Alex is just like you know you can't get him
to do a single tour. Well, he'll do a chore, but you have to kind of be like
hey man. Can you do that chore? Yeah, yeah, I guess no, you can actually get
him to do a chore. If you say, can you do this for me, but
but
but Alex definitely didn't, but he doesn't like Alex doesn't want to do the
yeah around the house. Who wants to do chores around the house? No, no, no, of
course, no, I would I want when we all in order to moved in and we were like
it's just going to be bro down time all the time and Joe came in and was the
only one who had a level head about it and was like okay, someone has to do
these dishes. Well, I've been the I've been the bad roommate before yeah and I
I wanted to be the room. It was that I was the yeah. You have to be the bad
roommate to become a good roommate yeah. When I
Joe well for for me and Joe,
but like when Joe moved out and then it was just me, Alex and Neil, what a
fucking house that was yeah. I was the I was the worst roommate in the world
that just I think that that was just the worst apartment. Yeah space. Oh yeah,
my land, my our old landlord Rupert, who is number 20 on the landlord watch list.
Do not rent from list. Shout out Rupert. Shout out Rupert. I thought you're going
to play a sound effect. I was thinking about it. I didn't want to because then
I have to upload a whole separate file for the soundtrack and for one sound
right at the end. Who cares man? Yeah, but yeah, that we had black mold and a
hole in the ceiling. And if you left your dishes in the sink, the mice would
come out. I'm trying to what's like it was also just the like space yeah that
place sucked yeah. It was seven Stanhope Street apartment three are do not to buy
that place. Do not rent it. We did a bunch of videos there, but it was always
like it always felt crazy crazy. There was a hole in the in the ceiling for a
year. You can't make it look like a place that's like a nor it can't stand it for
like a normal apartment. No, no, no, I feel like if you pour that's a place
sure if you poured an an insane amount of money into it, you could get like a
movie style apartment. You could get it on a part a new york apartment. You would
see in a movie. It's like you'd have sod is falling apart. The stairs up or like
yeah, freaky and wow yeah, but yeah, that's only the actual into those
stairs were horrible. That whole building was horrible. That whole
building should be condemned yeah, unless there's people still living in
it. That door to is crazy. I think there should be condemned and the people
should be locked inside. Oh my God yeah, there was no door knob on the door yeah
There was no doorknob on it to get in. You had to go like, like you had to
jiggle twice up. Here's how you break in there. Okay, so you get the key to
the... Actually, I still have the keys. If you want the keys to that building.
I've never had a really bad apartment. I feel like the one I had in Boston
was like, it was pretty good. The only problem with it was that there was
a guy who would always come on... We had like... He would always come on
it was me. It was me. The guy's always coming in loud. There was a window out into the alley
that was right behind our apartment. We were on the first floor and there was a guy who
would always, yeah, right by the Com Ave. Let's say all of our old addresses. Green
Line. I'm trying to remember the address, man. I can say my old address right now. Right
in front of the Green Line. 211 Harvard Ave, Apartment B. Harvard Ave stop, I think. I
honestly can't remember this place's address. I'm trying right now so hard. I know it was
on come have kind of nice yeah. It was a it was fine. I mean, but there there was
this guy who would come on his lunch break every single day
and just smoke a bong outside of right outside of our window and he and one
time
girlfriend was doing like like an exercise video and he was standing out
there and he started like mimet like doing the things he was doing. That's
the time he was there when I was pointing at him out the window and going
like this
at him and going like and then he never came back.
Boston's ridiculous. That's how I handled yeah. He fucking got that guy
out of there. You don't know the address. I'm
blanking on it. I don't know thirty five. I can't remember it. Thirty five. I
feel like it started. What was your what was your what was your what was your
old two eleven Harvard have apartment be God right across the street from be
fresh. I feel like it might have been a thousand. Oh, you know what I found out
we've talked about it on the show. I'll look up what's right. I know where it
is on the map. We talked about it on the show before, but I used to be on. So it's my old
apartment was right across the street from Great Scott in Boston, and I used to be on
the Apple map Street View. I looked like you would look up like 200-206 Harvard Ave and
you would just see me and I posed exactly like Bigfoot, like walking back to my like
it was like a basement apartment. You remember that you ever go to that place or I was Cameron
did. You know how they had that like that little stairwell and like all the
homeless guys would like pee in it because it looked exactly like a
bathroom. And yeah, there's like a photo of me with my head out the like
basement door like this. And then a photo of me in front of this dentist's
office that was right next door to it. And I'm like posed exactly like Bigfoot.
I looked it up the other day because Great Scott is now becoming a Taco Bell
Cantina. Yeah, which is so funny. I wanted to see it. I was like, oh, I
I wonder if I'm still on the street view you guys I'm completely gone. Well,
you can go crazy. You can go back on Google Street. I there was thirteen
hundred something. I don't know why I can't remember. I can't go back on on
Apple Street View, bro damn uh-huh. I love going back on. I have the
screenshot still. I can post it now. That's all that I don't care about
leaking my old addresses, unless there's text things that could get me fucked up.
You're probably fine. No one's going to get you in trouble from your patron.
yeah podcasting thirty five brookline street. Where else did I live me what
thirty was it thirty five brookline av av cambridge massachusetts yeah, I was
a little there. I live there, I live there with me spot yeah. This whole
podcast at the end now has just been us reminiscing about different streets,
which is a problem that I have. It is fun. I mean that's that's all you that's
all you got is the memories now
that we lost at the end of I was in a class called listening to music with
that lady, Frederica King yeah, one of the best racers I've ever had it. So it
was the most ricos class ever, but at the very end it was all about classical
music and like recognising different periods and stuff and at the end she
played see when you get there by coolio, which starts off with pocket bells
cannon. You know it's like plays classical music and then there's a
record scratch and a beat drops in and there was supposed to be like a look
like all this classical music is still like inspiring music today, yeah and
ever it was a thing of the music scratch and everyone was sitting in silence and
when in the beat dropped, I was like
and I was looking around here. The only one and nobody can no one else cared
about it. I was like that's such a fun way to end the class man. That was the
best class I ever took. I love when teachers get I love when things get
sent to me. I took like I took like four different class. The reason I dropped
out because I didn't realize that I was stuck at Emerson taking Gen Eds and I
took like three different like listening to music, like all these music classes.
I have a jazz yeah yeah, I did I did no no no I wasn't in history of jazz. I
was in history of American pop and then history of American music and
you did not go to school for music at all. No, but I think halfway through I
was like to three different maybe I'll be a music writer. Those are like the
those are history classes yeah yeah. So I was taking them for history classes,
but they also filled elective credits that I needed to get yeah. I remember I
was you just reminded what I think in my senior year I took a I took a had to
take an econ class yeah and I was trying to remember the exact context of like
and this is this is Emerson, where it's a bit of a woke school, but I remember
the the econ professor was
I don't remember the exact quote. I really wish I'd written this down
somewhere, but he was like to we were like he was going over stuff before a
test or something and he was like so doing so like something about supply,
like some like econ thing and he's like and if you don't understand this,
you're a retard.
Everybody in the class like looked at each other,
I just remembered that, like the other day. I can't believe it is so fun, so
literally no reason, like no reason to say it doesn't make any sense. It's
about something just like it. Yeah, nobody's on it. Nobody just kept going
yeah everybody's going to oh yeah. I had we had a moment like that in my
history of American pop class, but it's because she was showing that footage of
Russell Brand at the VMAs in two thousand and eight and she was like like
talking about it was a whole section on like protests at award shows yeah and
she was talking about Russell Brand
and there's a speech. It's pretty like crazy. He just goes off and is like
George Bush. George W Bush is a retard. Do not vote for him and every single
person in that class went. Yeah,
it is crazy crazy teachers at that school professors loved to say the N
word in a quote and then send an email the next day. I'm so sorry, I'm so
sorry, yeah, I did and you know they do that every single semester. I think
this is the semester where I can get away with saying a hard R N word,
because I'm quoting somebody and
all the tenured professors are just pushing the envelope at this point,
where it's just every single one of them is just like all right.
What can I get a one with this year? They're going up every single tenured
professor at that school is going up and just like like trying to have their
fucking like Joe Rogan like moment where they're like or their Louie moment,
where they're like I said it and I got away with it like that, like the way
that like the most annoying comedians in the world act. It's also the funniest
school to do that at because it's a school full of people who are actually
not listening to anything. I know
people who are there because I didn't get into NYU for film yeah
ears perking up when they
right
drafting an email to hit send on it and then immediately not remembering that
it like happened yeah, I'll just on college was crazy. You got to love
college man. I hate college, but love all the part. I love women. How long
we've been going? It's been an hour ten. How
why did we bring you on today? What did we bring you on today to promote pray
tell so on you can add me on PlayStation Network
my it's all guys easy to remember because my PSN is home underscore
underscore planet. Your PSN is home. Oh my God,
it's I don't know why it's be funny. If you're playing fall guys and like do
they have voiced voice chat on there, you can voice. I was like yo yo is that
to play? I think maybe I think I may be doing it. So someone eventually is like
that to have yeah, I'm not actually because I love my God. I love your
racist guy eating soup. I only have two friends of who on fall guys on my
epitome. You came on here to promote so just I would just say if anyone, if
so anyone still plays fall guys, add me on fall guys, and you can also add
distinct Finch
five seven three. I think five six three. Maybe
I just I just would like I would love to have a full squad to run with
to
bench. Well, they may automatically automatically give you what are we
doing? We brought you on here to promote under world's biggest mummy port of
skull Halloween city. We're doing another show at little field. There will be
home planet videos. There'll be videos, they'll be our sketch,
gripes, war, largest army or should I say undead sketch on
dead sketches, our sketch group, world's biggest army, the
combination, the combination of us podcast about list home planet
and pierce campion october twentieth october twentieth at
little field in brooklyn. Happy birthday to pierce's grandma.
Look, we talked too much about our past, our past lives on this
show today. Okay, we just it was basically about the future. It was a
hangout episode. Okay, we didn't think of any. We thought of the food man was
good right
cutting between Joe and then completely neutral expression to his
so the food man was good. Did you like the food man come to the whole episode
and come to the come to the show? We can you can ask us details about our
personal lives that we talked about today on this episode about our
apartment at twenty two stars, twenty two star street apartment to that's
where the show will be and you can know it'll be at six thirty five sacket
street, a little field in little field in go on and you can get tickets at
swag poop dot com slash shows the event bright link for tickets. You better go
on by head. I'm taking the twentieth of October. If you get them day of you get
a day of its five dollars, one of October
it should be fun. It's got to be it will be really. I think you just had a
mistake where you said I think I said should by accident. It shall be so yeah,
both of you guys, the whole episode
we cut to go pro
also
on November fifth, I'm going to be opening for girl god in Chicago. Shout
out grace and April. Yes,
oh wait, also look also go to go to home planet on twitter and youtube and
Instagram and watch some funny ass videos to get to get laughs in and
apparently Joe has to show us something. Joe's finding something on his phone to
show. Oh my God. Joe is announcing the short that we made over the summer. We
made a bigger movie. We made a short film and it might be at World's Biggest
Army. Maybe we'll see if we have enough. Yeah, but don't say that because that's
not a that's don't yeah, it won't be. It won't be most likely won't be. It
definitely won't be. We'll play the trailer. No, we won't.
But yeah, look at our fun little have a fucking trailer for that. Look at our
fun little poster. Yeah, revealing the poster revealing to you guys.
Somebody at this table has a gigantic role in this movie.
It's me. It's actually was supposed to.
Oh yeah, but then it didn't make any sense. See Patrick door and Caleb pits
And Anthony DiGiorgio. Anthony Giordano. Giordano. The old man. Happy Saturday. Halloween.
What a day. Oh yeah, waiting. The brain. The brain. The owner of Mint Mobile. Uh huh. Star of waiting.
And the owner. This fucking guy. Aviation Jin. Aviation Jin. I want to see him like personally
cancelled people's accounts.
You know, I don't fucking care.
You better pay me.
You should have paid.
And then he looks into the camera.
He looks into the camera.
He says like, um...
This is what happens when you don't pay.
I want to hang out with him so bad.
I get so fucked up on Aviation Jim.
Make Mint Mobile prank calls to people.
Oh yeah.
Yes, the binder with all the phone numbers.
A binder.
Oh, a binder. Yeah. You send out the alerts to every single person's account.
It says your phone will self disrupt in five minutes and then
we have this is a Hawaii alert that said that there was a nuclear bomb
dropping. Only the mobile people got that. Oh my God. He could do some epic
pranks with mobile and he's just wasting it. If you have this phone,
everyone's gay. Damn. Alert. That's not a good selling tactic. Amber alert.
There is a guy holding this phone.
What are your thoughts on X?
I'm all in on X. I've bought a bunch of stock.
I've been X-ing all day.
I just constantly X-ing.
I X like it's 2009.
Like, "Got a sandwich today!"
Like, "You might do a pedophile joke."
Like, X, you know, 2009 pedophile jokes.
Just trying to be epic on the computer, nonstop.
What would give me an example of a 2009 pedophile joke you're doing?
It's like, "I'm a pedophile."
"I'm a pedophile," said no one ever.
that actually can you and then you reply to it and say, except for pedophiles,
except for pedophiles, and then ten years later, you have to make some post
under that one. I don't understand what this means. I did not mean I don't even
remember posting this at the time. I think I got hacked. I think I was
honestly, I was probably off that scissor. Yeah, yeah,
all those posts of like comedians from two thousand and eight where they're
being racist and they just respond like the opioid epidemic has affected us all.
[MUSIC PLAYING]