I
hold on now cup chin cup.
You look like a pharaoh. I know man wait get us a go pro
chin cup
and cup cup chin cup chin. This is a new style that I've been working on for a
use as a what is affect your voice so much because it's on his bottom. I
knew my lot on lit. He can't new a lot of his lot and I cannot new new the
new. I can't do my thought and I dot on lit.
It actually is starting to really hurt me. I want to try to take I take the cut
off my chin, take the cut off your chin. If it will be
a lead the room, a lead circle, it will depressurize the room because all the
the stink fumes that are collecting under
from his breath, take it off man. I'm coming to the episode with to get a
shit and new techniques and you guys are nothing new.
Okay, come get your redness. Whoa, whoa, new angle film two thousand and one a
space odyssey. No, they film that shit in space dog. Yeah, that's a good point.
Actually, Cameron, he did get you there. No, it's false. Do you guys think that
he faked the moon? Do you think he faked the moon landing? Who failed? I think
certainly is someone else. I honestly think they went to the moon. I don't
know why you would fake that. They went to the moon, but not that day, not on
this, not in the hell. Are you talking about man? I don't think they went to
the moon in the six. Why would they not in the fifties? Yeah, I think they went
way before that. I think they went to the thirties yeah way before silent
movie era. I saw somebody went to the I saw somebody go to the moon and put a
they landed their rocket right in the moon. I saw somebody on the moon in
1732. I bet somebody went to the moon, but they weren't these show off tell it
all the world needs is we got to put this on one of these modest countries.
Yeah, like
probably ancient the Ming Dynasty. Probably they went to the moon. Yeah,
there's a lot of research that you can look up and you can see that the Ming
Dynasty went to the moon. So well, it was truly the Sumerians within their
sham ships sham that true sham google sham google sham what the hell shim
shamsham was an old spaceship back okay. So that's no a son sham
shampoo. Shampoo funny moments sham. Where would you ship with him from
spaceship
stooges you don't know shampoo. Shampoo. Yeah, what am I thinking funny funny
moments now go to images. This is a sham here in the first picture. Maybe
oh that looks that looks like a minecraft house.
That looks good guys. This actually looks like a big cookie and I want to
eat it guys. I big news. Yeah, the war is over. Oh yes, yes, we have not won
the war by losing it. Yeah, not the one you're thinking of the war. Well, the
war you're thinking of is still raging. Yeah, but we lost a battle, but the war
that we are in our war is over. You know why man,
because okay, here's what happened during for those who did not listen to war
diary number one. We go listen to that. That's important diary number two. We
are in a bloody endless war in the middle of in the middle queens,
and it is us versus garbage people, and you might be thinking that these are
people made of garbage, yes, and you'd be close. They're people who pick up
garbage for a living and not even and I God bless these good garbage men and
women who pick up this nasty, disgusting, these shits that and
the toilet wiping that I put in the trash bags. It's the bosses. It's the
PMC class of the garbage world. Yeah, though, honestly, I fall on the side. I
kind of don't like the blue collar picker uppers. I mean, I don't love them
either. They smell bad, but the people who are actually sending their capos are
where I have actually the blue. The blue in their collar is from all the
blueberry juice coming out of our trash. Cameron drinks a lot of V8 blueberry
juice. Did they make blueberry juice? V8 blueberry pomegranate.
Drinking what? Pome wonderful. Pome wonderful. I don't know what that is.
What are you guys remembering? What are you texting right now? I'm just
relaxed. People thought that that was a... It's important. People thought
Pome wonderful was healthy, but that's basically like a soda. Yeah, it's just
sugar. Yeah, it's a fruit cocktail. Yeah. It tastes good as fuck, though. It
because sorry to interrupt about juice. So the war is now over and I'll tell
you exactly what happened guys.
We had a
I mean we were building a dossier on this on this trash company security footage,
security footage, security. We were gonna give them a trouble stories told by
us about what happened. Security's fraud. Maybe they were engaging in. We really
don't know. They were. They allegedly alleged by allegedly they were engaging
security fraud. Yeah, because guys, we were, they attempted to sue us. We got a
letter from them that says that in seven days they're going to start suing us if
we don't pay them $800. And we got it, the letter was sent on the sixth from a
lawyer and we got it on the sixth day. We got it on the 11th. Yep. And so I had to
scramble. Those sneaky, sneaky, sneaky. And at first, at first I got the letter and I
said, you know what man, let's take this shit all the way to the Supreme Court
because there's no fucking way shot man that I will give these fucking pieces of
shit and let me dime. Let me let's back up and explain this a little bit here.
The intent to sue is because we they so here's what happened. We hired this
trash company to come and pick up the trash from our office. They come
reasonable request, by the way, which we're paying them to do yeah. They
come. They don't pick up the trash. They come again. They don't pick up the
trash. Hey man, can you pick up the trash? Yeah, we're going to pick up the
trash. They come again. They don't pick up the trash. This happens and happens
that happens. So eventually we say okay, we're going to get a different company
who we're in love with and we love and we like them and they always become our
friend. What's his name? Thank you, Mr T. Mr T. Mr T, we love you and then we
say so we're not going to pay you guys this some four hundred dollars that
you're some forty four some four hundred dollars that you're you're asking for
because you didn't do the job. You never did it once. They did not once pick up
the trash. So why should we single you're breaking your contract? How we
signed a contract with you and you are breaching it and what do they do? They
get a lawyer to send a letter to us that says excuse me, you have breached the
contract by not paying, and now you have to pay twice as much money. That's
bullshit. Guess what, motherfucker? It's not even a breach of contract. Guess
what? We got scared and we paid the bill. That's right. 'Cause we got really
scared. 'Cause you, even though you, you motherfuckers at whatever your trash
company, I don't even care enough to remember the name of your company, you
guys know, you're trying to scare us 'cause you, that's why you had the extra
because you know the second we step foot in court, three guys representing
themselves, a triple lawyer situation. We represent each other for your fucking
lawyer, man. We would represent one another. He can't debate us. But you guys?
He can't debate us. You guys? Here's what I would say. We have the security
footage. We can talk fast. Here's what I would do. I can talk over two friends.
We can talk over each other. Imagine what I can do to a lawyer.
We can talk over each other completely. We talk over each other all the
time. Here's what I would do if we got into court with them. Here's
what I would... Here's how I would prove our case, okay? I would say,
your honor, I'd like to call to the stand the Mr waste connections and then you
okay and this fucking big fat idiot would bumble up and how you doing coughing
and burping. He's got he's got boils and pimples. He looks like the onion from
veggie tails and here's what I would do. Okay, he'd be sitting on the stand and
I would say
pick that up and if he says no and he there's no way that he would do it, you
know what and I would know he wouldn't do it. You know why he doesn't know how
because he doesn't know how to pick the trash. Oh no, I would drop my soda on
the ground. I'd say pick that fuck, pick that up. If you're such a trash, if
you're such a trash man, pick that I can tell you what I would say if I was on.
If I was I was representing myself here in this case, I would you know how I
seal the deal. I say I would say I would say well, I do the kiss at the end.
Okay, this is how I would start. I guess the judge would start sealing the deal,
but I would finish sealing the deal with a kiss. I would say could I please have
everybody direct their attention to exhibit a and then I would have all an
exhibit with all the evidence that proves. Oh right, but you guys, I have to
say one thing,
this, these, this court fantasy is very,
I'm loving this a lot, but you guys, we did get the last laugh.
We did get the last laugh. We got the last laugh. And this is what I was,
this is what Patrick was asking me when I was texting, I was sending this over.
Okay, thank God. This is a strike that we made in the war. Listen, you guys may
won the war by making us pay money, but we got soldiers of fortune. We have
mercenaries working for us. This is like the guys in Japan that didn't know that
World War II was over. Oh yeah. Wait, this is the call?
Okay. This is a... A soldier in the field. We got shooters.
Yeah.
Turn that up.
It's up as it will go.
Okay. I just had some questions for you, if that's all right.
Um, do you guys pick up feces?
Yeah.
No, do you pick up human feces?
Okay, what if I hide it in a bag? Like, will you check?
They'll check that for human feces.
How do you guys check that?
The driver will check that.
He opens up the bag and he checks for that?
Yep.
Cool.
Seems strange.
I think that's the end of the call.
Yeah.
And if you thought, if you think...
The driver will open the bag and check.
And check for human feces.
that's what that's apparently what waste connections is going to do. I don't know
if we should be saying their name because we just admitted that we could get
prank calling. We could get pierce in a lot of legal trouble. I don't think you
can go to jail for break, and I think that we said the name of the thing, and I
think that these little rabid soldiers. Well, there's a bunch of different things
called that name, but the point is this man, if you think that's if you think
that is the end of the prank calls that we're about to unleash on your small
company,
you are sorely mistake. You really may have ended, but the other war has just
started. Well,
end of World War One everybody. Oh, we're going to go kiss in the middle of
Times Square. Oh yeah, let's go. Let's just let's disarm Germany. Yeah, yeah,
that'll really work and then Germany comes the fuck back. We are Germany,
that's right,
versus you. Oh, we're going to take away all Germany's armies and weapons. Yeah,
great idea. Wait for us, yeah, you fucking idiots. Do you know what you've
Everyone at the bus stop in front of this building just heard us say that.
The other shoe is about to drop.
Uh-huh.
And it's a 400-pound shoe and it's dropping directly--
A 400-megaton shoe.
And it's dropping on your ass.
And you are about to take yourself out to the trash can and put yourself into a compact cube.
You're going to end up in a bag that you work in.
The morgue is going to have to check your body bag for human feces, buddy.
Yep.
We're shitting on you.
Yep, because we're shitting on you.
This is what we need.
What are you going to do?
We need another legal battle right now.
send us another letter with intent to sue for defamation. Oh wait, I
think I forgot. You know what I'm doing? We're saying allegedly the
whole time, so you can't sue us for shit. Yeah, we're saying allegedly.
It's not a slander or a libel because we're just making it up. And also,
we're playing characters right now. And my name is... I'm Mr. Fruit. Hey,
guess what? If you do send us a letter with intent to sue over defamation
for saying we're gonna nuke you with a shoe and poop on your body at
the morgue, that means you had to pay $5 to hear this shit. Yeah. And
We are making back our money one month at a time, buddy.
Uh-huh.
Because you're going to forget to cancel that.
You're going to forget like a lot of people did.
Over months and months and months.
All it's going to take is 1,600 months, buddy, and we're going to pay back our legal fees.
And guess what?
I'm at home right now.
I'm doing Mark Wahlberg and fear type shit.
I'm punching myself in the chest.
I'm punching myself in the...
You know what I'm doing?
I'm bringing my trash from home here, and I'm throwing it out because I think that that
that affects you somehow. Yeah, I think in my twisted brain, I think that that
affects you. And let me tell you something else, waste connections. If
anything,
anything happens to your business, to your personal apartment, to anybody in
your life, if any, they get injured in any way that seems accidental, if they
contract any disease, if anyone dies or is hurt or feel sad in a day, yeah, we
claim responsibility for that shit. We did it. We're planning to do it. And
Another thing, we're not so smart, so we're gonna start eating our trash because we think
it makes you mad.
We're very, very stupid about this whole thing.
We thought that you could just stop paying a guy who has a contract, okay?
Imagine the type of stuff that we do at home that's just when people aren't looking.
I'm so stupid that the guy said, "You signed a contract."
And I said, "No, I didn't."
And then he sent me a photo of it with my signature.
This is how...
You don't want to fuck with somebody who's this dumb, man.
well, we'll go all the way up and down every which way we're going to go at you
like wonk is elevator. Okay, we're going all the way and you buddy, you're
going to need a gob stopper because I'm going to be gobbling up all this damn
trash.
Every piece of trash because we know that you like that shit stop our gob and
guess what? We're going to get
everyone in the city to start recycling and composting
apartments, their own backyards, and then there's going to be no
trash. You should pick up your own. You could pick up your own stuff. Pick up
your own body and also by the way, and I don't even like saying this kind of
thing, but you will soon be replaced by AI, aka Wally. And when Wally starts
pulling up, I'm gonna pet him. Uh-huh. And there's gonna be a Wally listening
to Wally. Wally listening to Wally. Listening to All Day. Listening to All
all day by Chitty Bang all day all night by chance, the rapper yeah he's gonna
while I while he gonna pick up a wrapper and and but for real, I do have a map of
all your stops on where you pick up trash and I'm going to be hiding feces
and we're going to pick up the trash before you get to it. Yeah, we're
starting it to the next house down. Oh, that's what we're going to do. We're
going to take every piece of trash from every house on your on your route, move
it to the very last house. You go, oh, what a quiet night. Nobody's throwing
taking away tonight, get to the last house, you're not going to be able to
pick it up. It's going to be too much for your little muscles. There's too
much trash. You know what we're going to do? We're going to take the trash
from one side of the street, the even numbers, we're going to put it all
over on the odds, and we're going to take the odd number streets, put it on
the even side. You're going to have even and odd trash mixed up. That's how
we get back at them. We start our own trash company. Yeah, we're turning this
whole building into a trash thing. All the people who live upstairs and stuff,
they're going to smell it all the time. They're going to love it. I can't tell
you how badly I want to go to court with these motherfuckers, man. We want it.
we thought maybe I want to be I
funny we're talking about I'm seeing a about like a
situation of us three because they're still the company they're still in all
of us. We three we get we step into court with this guy, this lawyer that
he's probably a good lawyer of the this trash company. I heard some trash lawyer.
Yeah, send a letter with his name on the top of you guys. I think maybe we step
into that courtroom, three of us representing ourselves. Yeah, we got
little we got little levelier Mike packs on we go. We got Pearson, Jubio
sitting in the in the pews, the church pews of the house with cameras. We turn
that shit into content. We make the absolute funniest best episode of a
podcast that's ever been made, and then we each owe fifty thousand dollars to
the government for perjury and go to jail for execution, tax a ten years
stuff like that yeah. I don't give a fuck. Can you imagine how they would
fucking mythologize us if we went to jail? If we defeated I mean the trash
people who pick up trash have been a scourge on this city for God knows how
long since the since forever. Okay, because it used to be right in this
world. You used to shit out of your window, used to shit in a bucket and
throw it out the window. And there's a little
you to be able to litter. Well, someone just walked by wearing a David S
Pumpkins costume. No way. I really hope. Not a big deal. But bring them back
here. That kind of stuff doesn't scare me anymore. It doesn't bother me either.
I actually want them to come back in here and we can interview them. Weird
shit like that doesn't bother me this time of year. Exactly. You just got to
get used to it. I saw a lady dressed up as a clown the other day. We should
interview David S. Pumpkins on the show. He's a really hard guest to get. Okay.
He doesn't do much public appearances unless it's on Saturday Night Live and
he plays himself. Alright, alright, alright. I just had that amazing thought.
Yeah. That soothed me so much. Your bloodlines over. Waste connections,
allegedly. You're done for. You're done for. The only connections to waste is
the connection of your veins to your heart. Wow, your blood is a waste.
Your blood is waste. I wouldn't even let your heart is a trash. We don't
believe in violence, but that's not gonna stop us from killing you,
from killing you with our gun and our hands. Yeah, just our hands. We don't
have to. No, I don't have any guns.
I have a gun, but it's for me, it's for me, it's more about falling in
love with every single one of your family members and getting them to move
a different city far away from you. Oh, that's smart. And we're going to rising
them all one by one and I'm going to break up with my girlfriend, getting
them to move, get this, getting them to move out further onto the coast. Maybe
we take them to Cape Cod or something and they're all there in 50 years.
That's going to be underwater. You are taking your whole family on a all
expenses paid trip to Provincetown. We're going to take you,
family. We're taking them all the province. That's right. We're going to
we're going to take your we're going to take your eighty five year old mother.
We're going to take her to Provincetown. We're going to introduce her to her to
where
she's going to be hard. We're going to introduce her to some really kind, nice
bears that are going to completely change her perception about the entire
homosexual community and she is going to start supporting gayness and bringing it
into your home. A man, and these guys, these trash guys are really homophobic.
Of course they are. We take your grandmother right, then we take a plane
private jet out of out of Provincetown. We give them pills so they don't freak
out on the plane. Then we go to and this is going to be whenever the Folsom
Street Fair is we're flying direct flight Provincetown straight to Folsom
Street Fair where they are going to be in
the Folsom Street Fair. Everybody's going to think it's just part of a
normal thing that gay people do in Provincetown one where they take
no, it's P town. I love this time of year in P town. I do want to go to the
Folsom Street Fair, man, but yeah, it's farting and having sex with each other.
It sounds amazing. There's that
photo of that dude getting fisted in the middle of the street. It was crazy.
That's what I mean. Why do people complain about that shit? Yeah, it's fine.
Seems so funny. Who cares? Well, the thing, the reason that people complain
about it is they think that it's not like the street isn't blocked off. They
have like- The guy who, the guy, the like sixty five year old straight guy
who's lived in who lives in like on the on an apartment on the top floor and
Folsom Street is looking at us and windows like
province. I'm like fuck shit. That's not it's in San Francisco. Okay, yeah,
the Folsom Street fair.
That's why we're taking the private. Yeah, there I was making kind of a whole
gay city where no, no, no, no, no province town is where the gays who
don't go to Folsom Street fair. I was probably seventy five percent girls from
my high school. I love Provincetown, man. You see a bunch of couples that look like
twin brothers. I liked it when I was a kid because they have a bunch of stores
with puzzles and games. There was a lot of puzzles. What's that? That Navy store,
dude? Yes. Oh, my God. That place was so sick. Old Navy. Old Navy. I bought a
military helmet similar to that one there as a kid, and it was like a really
heavy one. Yeah, it made it. They have it to block all the stonk. But Waste
Connections, I'm gonna pay so much money. I'm gonna get your mom and your dad. I'm
gonna take him in a limousine every day to Peter Luger.
Your mom, you'd man me a grease-fied--
I'm gonna lose thousands of dollars doing this.
You think, "Oh, that's so nice to do."
You think it's nice to do, okay, until the day that I stop.
They've adapted.
Yeah.
They want a limo every day.
They want the steak every day.
Can you give that to them?
I don't think so.
No, man, you got $800 in your pocket.
Now, Gels, I know nobody else is paying for your stupid company shit.
I don't want to eat chuck roast.
I want to eat for a minion. They're going to be saying that to you. There's a
gross and you want you want to take your I'm going to take your old ass mom to
Sephora and I'm going to make her a I'm going to dress your mom up, but I
want to be a jeans. I want to be a slut. Now I want to be a slut. You can't be a
slut, Grand Mama. We got to pick the trash up. I want to be a slut and I
want I don't want to I'm going to exert an influence over her life that changes
I don't want to eat pork chops. I want to eat steaks. I'm going to start hurting
myself and it'll be your fault.
Straight up. That's what we've already been doing. That's what I said. I was
doing doing fear, Mark Wahlberg type shit. I'm punching myself in the chest
and head. I'm doing everything from every movie where I'm doing. I'm doing
that. I'm doing taxi driver holding the hand over the fire. I'm doing where
maybe Forrest Gump runs too far and he hurts his legs. And I did. I did an
impression of your grandma and it was scathing. Does Forrest Gump sleep? No,
I've never seen that for us, except for one minute of it. I in that movie. I
think he doesn't sleep. I think he runs all the way across. Nobody does sleep
most movies, though. No, he does not sleep well. I guess he sleep. He sleep
runs. They wake up usually yeah, yeah, a lot of is a bad movie, but it
grows. I think they should go back to having every single movie start with
the main character waking up and with them going to bed early in the morning,
because how else am I going to relate to this guy? Me that I tell you there
There's this one time I went to a Bubba Gump because I won a gift card at Universal Studios
for doing a survey about a show.
You went to Hubby's Bump.
I went to Hubby's Bump and I had to do a focus group and then I got, I think it was like
fifty bucks to any restaurant on the city walk.
Went to Bubba Gump.
My ex-girlfriend, never seen Forrest Gump, because they do trivia there.
Ex-girlfriend, never seen Forrest Gump.
Australian family, sitting at the table next to us, never seen Forrest Gump.
they put you in pods and then in the middle of the dinner, the way to
comes over like little like the bugs, eat the shrimps, eat the eat the
shrimp, shrimp or bugs true. They put you like into groups in the restaurant,
then a waiter comes over and is like all right, so now we're going to do
some forest gump trivia and I had to do I had to answer every single question,
because I was the only person who'd seen the movie. So is the movie I
haven't seen the movie for us gump is it about for his gump eats shrimps as
bugs. He doesn't know any better. He owns a shrimp restaurant called Bubba Gump.
It's a
restaurant in that movie. He owns a restaurant and doesn't know he owns it.
He doesn't pretty much. Okay, it's a movie about- He doesn't know shit. He
doesn't know much. It's a movie about if
he's a doofus.
He's a doofus and he's- everyone around him is a douche bag. You know, that guy,
I always thought Forrest Gump kind of looks like David S. Pumpkins. A little
I feel like they should play brothers and stop getting me. I keep thinking that
because he said somebody walked by earlier. I keep thinking that he's going
to walk in and it's going to be like us like doors locked. It's like a David
s. Pumpkin David. I'm going to tell a nightmare that somebody tried to break
in here. Yeah, and I would let them. Are you kidding me? What are they going to
take our people are going to kill me man. People break in all the time, man.
People walk in and they say, I'm sorry. What is this a store? You say dude, I'm
in there. Somebody right now. Everybody walks in here goes literally exactly
like this dude. What is this? Yeah, we said I don't want to fucking know man.
It's just our room. I don't want to know what do you wait? I'm trying to
trying to
we don't want people. You will cry. If those people come in, you actually will
get so I would not you will have to deal with it. Well, we would do it by
saying hey, we can finally okay. Sorry, my friend here actually is some
difficulties and inefficiencies. People people come by all the time and open the
door and say what is this? We say it's a podcast studio. We finally have the
we can actually show them us in action. This is like you know when you go to
like the the factory and you see where the sausage is made and I never go to
the factory. You see where the sausage is made and two guys are competently
excitedly making sausage and one guys like this.
I can't make the sausage when people are watching.
This is how the sausage which should we start doing podcast tours for fans. I
I was thinking of renting out the studio to anyone who wants to start their own
podcast and then I sit right there and I operate the switchboard for them.
Remember a lady wanted to...
Yeah, she wanted to do an America First podcast.
No, the other lady who wanted to rent the space.
Oh, I forgot about that.
She scared you.
Me or him?
Me or Caleb.
Oh, yes.
Oh, well, she thought that she could... She thought this was an apartment for
rent.
Yeah.
No, we actually have a lease here, lady.
And then we went on a date, romantic.
And I give her a flower.
You didn't go on a date with her.
I'm making shit up, man.
You did not go on a date with her.
Did you guys know that they're doing a Bachelor show?
With olds. With olds?
Yeah. That's disgusting.
I kinda wanna watch it,
but I don't know where to watch it.
I was told that it's the saddest thing ever
because it's like, the Bachelor is kinda funny
because he's like telling these money-grubbing whores
to get the hell off the island.
Now these are money-grubbing olds.
These are beautiful old women to be honest. The love part of the bachelor
is by far the worst part. It should they should get rid of the bachelor and they
should just put all the crazy women on the love part is fake and they should
just well it's real. They get married, but then they always come out as gay
after yeah or is it with each other? No, I mean both.
Did you guys ever watch much of the bachelor? I've never watched a fair
amount of you watch the reality show ever watched his Jersey Shore. I like
watching reality TV. I would I probably wouldn't turn it on when I was on my own,
but I when it enters into my life, I enjoy it. I was housewives. The house
wives are fire doomsday preppers. I watched that's a and then I've seen
clips barely even counts yeah. I've seen clips of like dance moms and like
Vander pumps and stuff dance moms is crazy. The Abby Lee Miller was that
her name. She's the one in the wheelchair shows I've ever seen in my
life. She's just yelling always wasn't always in a in which it's literally
all too much candy and put herself in a wheelchair right. I don't know.
cow member honey boo boo. Yes, the dance, the dancing, the dance mom show is like
completely so horrible and it makes you want to kill myself. You like you ever
watch the dancing bear. We talked about this. We've talked about the dancing
bear, the reality show. No, yeah, what he was that we talked about it already.
We've talked about we talked about the dancing bear with react. Wait, that's
real yeah. That stuff is actually happening. Reality show.
they go to real women's bachelor parties and make the way it's sad. They go to
the reality. What I want to see is the other. I want to see the man watching.
I heard there was one that got banned where they went to a funeral and they
made all the women start doing it anyway.
Dancing bear showing up to a yeah. I heard that they didn't have a place to
film that day, so they just kind of mixed in. They kind of like there was a
funeral going on.
There's a mix up on the
widow with a veil over
the fate yeah.
Yeah
no, but for real that's not
that would be tragic death. Honestly, I want that at my funeral. Yeah, the
dancing bear to show up, not telling anybody, sort of putting plans into
motion for when I die. If I will, it's a you can't tell anybody this yeah,
dearly beloved
way. The best part of the dancing bear videos is is when they're just dancing
the guy's penis. I like the guy dancing before that when they don't do any sex
or anything, I just like this. I like the naked guys in it is my favorite part
probably that I like when I have clothes on, but they're still hot. I like just
their bodies. I like when he's in the bear costume because I think that these
women are being getting attacked by a bear. You know it would be my version
that I like that if I was a girl because I would not would be my CTE. I wouldn't
be like a slutty girl, so I would my version of the dancing bear that would
really good is that he comes out and instead of taking off his clothes, he
takes the head off the bear and he shows his face. Patrick said he has CTE and it
makes him like when women are attacked sexually by a bear.
What? And we're letting this fly by? I didn't even hear that. Yeah, we're letting
you, we're letting you skate, letting Pat skate by on this one. He's making shit up
right now, Caleb. He sounds insane, doesn't he? Are you, I mean he does, but
if he's saying something you said, then you sound insane. That's a weird thing to
I'm watching women get attacked by a bear. You are making things up and then you
added because of I have CTE. You're acting crazy man. You're acting insane
Cameron. I'm not acting insane. You're acting completely crazy.
He's, look at him. He's off his rocker. He's off his rocker.
Stop, whatever man. See he's making no sense. This is probably what people
want instead of me talking. Nobody wants that. No, people, people like how it
works. You can't press it. It's not like an MPC. Sorry? MPC. MP3? It is an
You see? Hello, traveler.
Like a...
Yeah, you can't make beats out of those.
Well, I could set a drum.
Or you could set it that way.
Yeah? Whoa.
Wait, you've learned so much new technology recently.
I know.
It's easy, man.
Wait, can you...
(beatboxing)
(laughter)
There we go.
It's not that funny.
It's really not that funny.
What are you talking about? That's awesome.
(beatboxing)
Wait, that's actually fucking cool.
You can't even do it, man.
(beatboxing)
Just press it.
Why are you doing a weird finger trick?
Doing drums.
That's not how you play drums. You play drums like this.
You use a stick.
That's a sharpie. That didn't even work, man.
This is not working at all.
This is nothing at all.
Alright, yeah, you're done.
Alright, alright.
We cut your ass off.
Alright, alright, alright.
Even though I started it, it's Patrick's fault.
I agree. I agree. He took it too far, man. He took it to another level.
Once again, I don't know. I don't have good instincts and I ruin everything completely.
Pretty much.
Let's list things that you didn't ruin to make you feel better.
You didn't ruin the trash.
Let me think.
My dinner last night.
I ruined the trash.
Oh no.
What?
He's not talking about his dinner.
You just muted the mic that isn't plugged in.
There we go.
You're getting a little too comfortable here.
Yeah.
Bitch don't get too comfortable in the future.
Oh you know what I learned?
Wait, start talking about your dinner.
My dinner was so amazing white boy.
That doesn't do anything.
that doesn't do anything. No, you just do what do you mean? Do you want that? I
learned that this is like a fader.
I'm about to fade you, you don't catch this. I had my fade
the people who listen probably think I'm beating you up. Yeah,
stop, stop beating me.
Can you say hi? Yeah, anymore? Is that no? So I've definitely said hi. Yeah, a
bunch of times and every time had somebody recoil a little bit for hi. Yeah,
that's because they think you're about to attack. I definitely felt a kind of cringe from Hayao,
which surprised me because I never thought of it, but I guess it is kind of maybe racist.
I thought it was a word that meant I'm hitting you. Yeah, I thought you just say it, but
I guess it's maybe an approximation of the Japanese language. They are recoiling because
you're going, "Whoa!" True, it might be. Yeah, anytime you say Hayao, people block
it. Yeah, they're instinctively blocking. Racist cringe. Guys, I look nice. I don't
look like the kind of person who would say, "Hey, I need somebody." You look like a sensei.
Yeah. Exactly. You do look like you've done some time in a dojo. I did not do a tenny
time in a dojo. I thought you were a tenny time? A tenny time, yeah. I did some time in the dojo.
I told you guys, I did taekwondo and I was the best at push-ups. Yeah. I was one most obedient
multiple years. I had two. Yeah, I had two awards for most obedient years in
a row. They finally invented an award below most improved. Yeah, they finally
like this. The poor most improved. He's feeling so bad, but he did. We're
trying to be nice. Okay, we have to make something up. That's even worse.
So obedient because I never got in trouble. One time, imagine imagine.
Yeah, you got most obedient and most improved the same year.
you are the slave of the I was I would get all the pads and put them out and
they only I only really trained with kids who are younger than me because I
was so bad. Oh my God, but it wasn't. I remember any of the moves now. I think
maybe I did do some karate as a kid. I'm trying to remember. I remember of it,
but I think I had I think I had a what's the first is the first belt, a white
belt. Yeah, I think I had that do I remember any moves on me.
I don't think
you jumped him. He jumped. He said, Hi, he said, Hi, it's okay to say, Hi, I
was a I was a I think it's probably a tone of what I think you know what? Oh,
you know what? You probably
you probably can't say any, but you probably can't have trouble getting away
with going like, oh, and a high pitched for type of
oh, like a kind of yeah, but one yeah, that that's probably the one that will
really probably that's probably worse. That's that's why you can say in a
minute. You can be like, Hi, yeah, and you can also go. That's even a little
like that's still maybe, but for me, like maybe it's just because I'm so
Japanese. If you just don't change your voice, if you just go like this,
like
yeah,
yeah, strike, strike, oh strike, yeah, people say. Yeah, maybe you gotta start
saying it, maybe you just gotta start saying, calling your moves up, calling
your shots. You know, if no other culture is gonna step up and invent a
thing to say when you hold your arms in the air and your leg in the
air, we're gonna use the Japanese one. And it's also not wrong,
like no yeah, there's not an alternative. Give me one alternative. What does Gael
say in Street Fighter? Gael. Does he just say Gael? He doesn't have the how do
ken? No, he doesn't. He shoots a sonic blast. That's Ryu. Oh, does he say
sonic blast? Well, I think that's what his move is called maybe, but I could
be an inventing, sonic blast. Camilla Caballo from motherfucking Street Fighter.
She was fine.
I keep adding fine characters to Street Fighter.
That bear.
Why can you not make a game called Street Lover?
Yeah, Street Lover.
Street Lover.
Wait.
What's up?
Why can you not make a game called...
How come there isn't a game that is a fully simulated sex?
There is.
There surely is.
And I can guarantee that Chun-Li is a character in it as well.
Chum-Li?
Chum-Li.
From Pawn Stars?
Oh my God, the Pawn Stars game where you are a seller.
- They put Chumlee in the Chumlee outfit.
- You are the seller to the Pawn Stars, right?
And it's like one of those, it's like a text-based DS game
that has a bunch of mini games.
But-- - Oh, that's a text-based DS game?
- Or, you know, like it's mostly like text at the bottom
and you're like clicking different dialogue boxes
at the bottom.
And there is a heart, there's a heart and then a hand.
On the left side is heart, hand is the right side.
- Love or hit. - Love or hit.
And you can talk to Chumlee--
which I'm really men. Love it. I'm Lee love her or hit her. This is in this is
a
your DS. This is Nintendo love her hit her. No, no, no, no.
It's like mother three. They didn't release in the U. S. The exact same
cover art. Look up the
guitar jam. DSK search. D. S. Guitar here on tour. No guitar search jam guitar
jam. Nintendo DS. I would eat guitar jam. Yeah, sounds good. It's the
this is the exact cover of love her or hit her.
You play as that guy and you decide to love or hit yeah and you're you're
talking to chumly or whatever at the the what's it called the gold rush pawn shop
and there's a pond, gold and silver pond and then there's the romance button or
the
I would romance an old guy who died. He seemed so cool, which one the old one
who passed which is new all cramps, all old gramps, yeah, it didn't make sense
until he got older, but he was always old gramps. Maybe I'll name my kid,
never grandpa grandpa's a good name for you never watch ponsters. Did you watch
storage?
Road show that storage war stories, wars, road shows, the like yeah, so
George was at the guy that went yeah, yeah, Darrell or Dale or one would say
up and add the couple who guys love is not real. They broke up
every couple on TV ends up breaking up except for us. Yeah, it's okay. Pat
they're going to probably get back together later in life after they'll be
in heaven together. Lesbian is at least they're going to experience lesbianism.
You know, no, actually they will stay straight forever.
Okay, it's going to be okay. All right, they're not going to experience
I don't like having sex with girls normal.
I feel like lesbianism is the best way to do it.
Imagine the sisterhood you would feel with all your other lesbians at the bar.
If we three were women, would we be chilling at the bar and trying to pick up one guy to share between us?
I think we would be lesbos.
No, we would be lesbos.
You think that's not lesbos?
Three of us fucking one guy, that's not lesbo?
He would be funny shirt, funny t-shirt lesbian and he would say, "Damn, it feels good to be a lesbo."
With the two shockers, with two shockers on.
You'd be one of those fake lesbians where they...
Where I only do it when the camera's on?
Yeah.
Damn.
Being a lesbian is going to be so awesome.
And got the camera on me.
Dude, okay, here's why being a lesbian is awesome.
I love doing that.
Oh yeah.
yeah, when you're a guy, here's what sex is. Oh, I'm lifting you up, I'm
throwing you and I'm jumping around and oh look at me. Oh, I'm bouncing around,
I'm having to pretend I'm King Kong in your ability doing hula hoops. Oh crap,
but here's your sex. When you're a lesbian, you guys just sit there, you
talk, you talk, that's sex to sex for lesbians is sitting and watching TV. You
watch like a period piece and you think about the boobs in a corset. That sounds
awesome. I guess so much better than I have a lesbian sex all the time. When I
go home. This is basically this is basically
when you put it like that eat dinner.
What is lesbian? What the fuck do they do man? I really never learned. I was
completely
I would have to imagine that has to do with the living room. You're sitting in
the living room with your mom and dad, Downton Abbey's on, you just go whoa,
that was crazy.
please fuck on down Nabi and no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
I'm saying that that's that's lesbian sex is watching. I'm asking a separate
question. I've never seen down. Have you all seen blue is the warmest color? No,
what's that? It's basically a movie about lesbian. So they like they pick up food
together and they walk around. They look at trees at the same. Why is every
romance movie about walking around and looking at trees? Why does every give me
one? Then listen, give me a romance movie that starts at the end of dinner and
ends when you go to sleep. Yes,
yeah,
where are these in one location or on a to maybe to maybe to one position,
maybe for two minutes, a two minute long movie in one location, one position
that's now here's a sex move. Let me put you on what's you say hey girl flip
over no all the way over back to where we started.
What do you call that
The waffle. The pancake. The hotel waffle maker. Flip that thing all the way over.
Do you remember that E-Fucked video? I remember every single one, just name it.
That one where it's like the... Except for the really sad ones.
Well, this is the saddest one. I skipped all those.
The E-Fucked was so awful because half the time it would be somebody farting
and half the time it would be people having sex and then the guy would be like
"Argh!" and like punch the girl's arm or something.
oh, this one isn't funny. Who's watching this shit? No, the saddest one was the
one where it's like the guy.
It's like, I just like this is the virgin who won the contest and he nutted
immediately. That's not sad. That's a that's a giant victory. That's a victory.
That's a victory for him and the girl. Yeah, I guess you think that when
someone nuts too fast, it's a tragedy. Well, he's embarrassed in the but when
they not too long, it's a comedy. They not too long and
not too long plus time beforehand equals comedy equals comedy, nothing plus
equals sex, nothing plus mouth equals funny, nothing plus poop equals funny
for some. Would you guys sexual for you guys were a girl? Would you eat nut? I
would I would try both ways. I would have two boyfriends, one boyfriend. I
would always swallow the other. I would always spit one boyfriend, vegetarian
and I would switch it up on him after a while. So you think it sure to make
sure it's not just about which guys not see. I knew I knew that if Cameron was a
girl, he'd be a complete. Do you think you think nut is more? You think that
having two boyfriends makes you a slut? You have not seen anything of the modern
world. Yeah, yeah, basically women these days will have forty to fifty
boyfriends. If you're in New York,
they got fifty boyfriends. Sorry, thirty to fifty, thirty to fifty,
boyfriends,
thirty to fifty, feral boy. Can we bring that shit back man? Bro, I want to
transport to do
calling your penis a hog. You too, man. That's what I have you ever seen the
video where Joe Rogan's at the gym locker room and he has his first of all,
I don't know why saying my thing a hog gave me a like a heart,
phantom pain. You have one. Oh shit, I cut my thing off. Listen,
Joe Rogan in like 2008, he hired Brian Redband to walk around with him and film him all the
time.
Is that different from Brian Regan?
Yes.
It's different.
Brian Regan is a guy.
Clean comic.
Brian Redband is another guy.
Is Brian Regan a clean comic?
Yes.
Yeah.
And he's also one of the funniest comedians that has ever lived.
He says moosen.
He says, "Damn, these bananas are good."
It's funny.
Remember that joke?
Remember the...
I only know the one about the moosen.
He has that joke where he says he wrote on the Planet of the Apes movie and he's like,
Yeah, it's when the ape general is coming out and he's like walking, he's bringing all the
prisoners into the prison and I wrote this line where he says, "Man, these bananas are
good." Great joke.
Joe, what's the, I think the one before that though is like where they put in the title
at the top, they always put the title at the top of the book that you're reading on the
pages.
Oh yeah.
They always have the title at the top.
And he does the act out.
He does the famous gif.
That shit is funny.
God damn, that special was amazing.
I'm going to go home today and I'm going to watch Brian Rees.
I'm going to go over to that
funny anyway. Brian Redman was his cameraman and there was this guy who
went to his gym, who went to Joe Rogan's gym that Joe Rogan was like you're gay
and you always look at my penis in the locker room. They film the the
consultation yeah, so they fit they bring a camera into the men's locker
room and film him being like
man you've been looking at my penis. You're looking at my dick the whole time
and the guy clearly is like mentally disabled yeah and it's just like looking
down at the ground all the time and Joe Rogan decided to bring in a camera to
the
men's locker room.
That's a no no to bring a camera into a locker room. It's not supposed to happen.
Except for a Dancing Bear reverse video. They don't do those in locker rooms.
Flip side of that coin,
he also brought his camera to the comedy store and there was just a time where
he was just confronting motherfuckers. He brought his camera to the, his flip
video
It's a little loud.
Scrams.
I guess I could turn it down.
You're addicted to scrams.
If somebody plays scrams, I scram.
I'm getting the fuck out of there.
I'm getting ice cream.
I'm sitting down watching the rest of the show at the ice cream parlor.
Everyone keeps making fun of our genre.
It's called Screamo.
We gotta think of a cooler name.
Scrams.
We gotta think of something no one will make fun of anymore.
What about Scrams?
What about like the name of like an alien that you didn't know the name of from Star
Wars?
What about a weird snack from the 90s and the Middle East?
No.
Scrams.
we have to call it something different. We have to call it midwestern
emo.
That's not emo. Emo is already such a bad name. Yeah, emotional, hardcore.
Yeah, that's fucking way and it started with dag nasty in the eighties and and
I ended with fucking black parade bro. Yeah, that murdered it. Yeah, when I
was fucking hate what these scene kids did to emo because I'm sitting over
here. I'm trying to listen to stuff like cool bands like cap and jazz. Yeah,
And I'm trying to listen to them do a cover of "Take On Me" where they can't
sing any note that's above a B or below a C. I hate these scene kids wearing
skinny jeans. It used to be you pull up to the Hardcore Show and the 55 white
guys wearing propeller hats. That's what we need to bring back. Exactly. Oh my
God. Now that now... Propeller hats, bro, you got me thinking of death grips.
Yep. I have a death grip on my propeller hat, so nobody takes it.
When you're in a meme battle and you...
I need to me battle your opponent's a death grips fan.
Damn that would be a fucking annoying. I would kill myself if I was in death
grips. I would feel so horrible. I that guy has a big cock, big white car.
Yeah, yeah, I got that. I have that on on vinyl, and you lick that. I like it.
You put using it. You use it like a look at this. You thought it was a
place mat yeah, yeah, I should make a place matter that that'd be funny. It's
a funny album cover. It's a very good thing to make and when you first hit
they just they don't deserve what no, no, no, that really should not have
happened. It could not have happened to people who I feel like would take it
harder. They seem like very like esoteric, kind of like serious people
like they have that video. The interview with M.C. Rodney's like I'm
not interested in surface reality. That's like yeah and you're like okay
man, you probably want to die so bad right. You know what you brought in
all these fucking annoying as teenagers,
all these like demons names tattooed all over you and like yeah spiders and
stuff. Yeah, yeah, man, sometimes the most cringe people make the most based music
bro. Yeah, but I honestly can't imagine how death grips feels. I don't have any
experience that's like that at all, where I do anything and the people who like it
are annoying or strange. The people who like this show are good working class,
good blue collar folk, working class sixteen year olds, yeah, with
boogers, they always got boogers in their nose, like that little kid in Wind
Waker running around with a big snot bubble. Oh yeah, why do they do that in
Is that a common problem in Japan that somebody will have a giant bubble of
snot because they fell asleep? So disgusting I had to that was that you
did not have a giant snot bubble. It have a big snot rocket. I was walking
home from school. I had a
I shot it out my nose and it I'd let it hang for a second. I took a photo one
time the entire inside of my mouth turned into snot dude. I'm really feeling
like not and it came out when I was a kid. So it's let me see on let me bust
I just try it man. You don't want to see my mouth. I'm really feeling recently
like not. I don't want to
man leave my mouth leave his shit on stop trying to bust in. Jeez dude, I'm
really insecure about the inside of my mouth. Don't put your penis in his mouth
and jack. I'm going to buy that's not what busing means for me. I work hard to
keep a biome that is acceptable. My cousin's got a mouth. How come people
didn't have to brush their teeth until we invented toothbrushes? They think
they died at fifty years old. Yeah, they lost all their teeth at twenty five.
Yeah, I'm going to lose my teeth soon. I'm losing a lot of mine. I think mine
are I think mine are all going to go at the same time. This out. I think my
entire front top row of teeth is going to all fall out in the next two or three.
You see that right there in the next two or three dreams. I didn't have enough
money to get a crown and then I had a temporary filling and then the temporary
filling fell out. So now I just got a cracked tooth again. I haven't had a
tooth dream in a minute. Remember I had that crack tooth for like a year. Yeah,
That was evil. Yeah. I've been feeling recently not like I want to go to Tokyo.
I've been feeling like I want to go high up on a mountain somewhere in Japan and
become maybe a fisher. Yeah. Yeah. For me, it's China. I just don't. I think
Japan clears China all day. All day. I'm going to stay where I want to go, which
is South Korea. It's kind of so five years ago for you to say that. I just
please don't I don't know it's a little cringe to be honest. Well, then I
actually like it's a little normy. I want to go to the north, the Santa Claus
North Pole.
Okay, that's honestly even more cringe. Is that why because that is for kids?
They don't take adults there. I want to go to toy land.
Why do I do a podcast with these freaks? I want to go there and I think that I
could, but I keep watching these videos. Have you seen this guy? I don't remember
his name, but he's this guy who like interviews people in Japan. No, you
haven't seen this dude. He walks around and he asks people like, "What do you
think of foreigners in Japan?" And they're all like, "I think they smell bad."
So a lot of them like them, though. There's a big... That's why... That's what
every... It really breaks my heart. Every real life jumped out of the TV screen
comic book guy, they wanna go to Japan because they read that in Japan, when
people... When Japanese people see a person with white skin, the women will
basically jump all over them like the which is not credibles. The video is
sticky ball scene. I've been you get you go to Japan, you get covered in black
sticky balls. Well, the black sticky balls in this case are a metaphor for
Japanese women. Oh, okay, you've been on a crazy tip lately, but
yeah, straight up, you've been saying some weird shit, but it turns out, but it
turns out that as much as Japanese women like white conversations have got me
don't so much like fat and stinky guys. Oh yeah, which is oh maybe maybe that it
maybe it's a selection bias where the the kind of people who moved to Japan
from America just smell kind of bad yeah yeah,
but no, I think we definitely talked about this before, so we don't have to,
but I feel like I want to live in rural China, but I don't want to be the white
guy who moved to rural China, so I'd like to just steal the life of a Chinese
guy and take away. Yeah, we talked about this two weeks ago yeah, and then he
said he wants to move to Japan and become a high schooler and then I
change my answer. I want to live on the island of misfit toys or I guess I
could be a werewolf. You're only one to live on the island misfit toys,
'cause they got a dentist there.
Maybe that elf, maybe it would be why did he get free dentistry? I don't
think it's free. He only did dentistry on the king. Dentists are the biggest
scammer. Crazy shit to come up with an elf dentist. They must have been
smoking a toy. Stick to the normal Christmas shit. They must have been on
nitrous. They must have been on crazy toys.
But think about it. That's the most evil elf of all time because he wants to say
like, "Oh, well, I can't take that tooth out because you don't have enough.
You don't have insurance." No, he wants to take the teeth out.
There's no insurance. Why is he Jay Leno?
Yeah, well, you look at this, you got a little piece of shit in your mouth.
Oh, dude, that would break my heart if you went to the dentist and said,
"I don't, I listen, I hate saying this. I really do." You need a brush better, man.
You literally have a piece of shit in your mouth.
listen, listen, and your dentists, Jay Leno in this in their hard turd, your
teeth in general, they're very clean, pretty you're taking yeah, you're taking
good care of them, you're on the right, you're clearly flossing, you're clearly
brushing too, but please get a love of God, just at least brush one time before
you come here, because there you left shit. There's actually you must I can
tell you a shit before you can maybe you didn't even eat it, but you did put it
in your mouth. It was in your mouth. If you're going to put shit in your mouth
and again, your teeth are clean, they're fine. Besides the shit, you teach that
we have the worst prank on a dentist is walking, walking in and you have a
horse poop in your tooth
and it's just the dentist is picking around with that little stick.
What do you think's the most embarrassing thing? You know all those
stories of like, oh, this guy had a toy shoved up his ass, there's an x-ray.
What's the most embarrassing thing to find on that x-ray if you go to the
doctor? The doctor or the dentist? Specifically, are we still on dentist?
The doctor. I feel like there's almost nothing more embarrassing than just a
big turd in your body. No, that's what's him yeah. Well, no, because you're not
going to go to the you're not going to like go to the super market, get
embarrassed of the food in there is
what go to the super market. Yeah, well anyway, based on what Patrick said was
maybe extrapolate think what he was trying to say is that the poop isn't
really your fault. So yeah, so maybe it was a poop that they could clearly tell
did not belong to you, but maybe be really embarrassed, but it's like a big
poop. It's like okay, you're something your body did clearly. You didn't a dog
it's a with a name tag on it. We're going to we got the poop out. We're
going to have to run
it's a is actually we can tell if this poop came from a girl in the in the in
the in the x ray. You can see the poop is wearing a name tag that says Brian
yeah and it's like dude. You got Brian's poop in you. This is actually made.
This is now we've ran. We had to run a bunch of tests and it was kind of
confounding the lab guy a little bit. He this is he said it was the strangest
case he's ever seen. This is actually a hundred different people's poop. It's
would mix together. We're able to tell it was mixed together with a spoon in a
bowl. I think we're going to have to bring in Doctor House on this one. Yeah,
well, the thing I think the most embarrassing thing that could happen is
you go into the MRI machine and you got a fully metallic, but plug in you forgot
to take it out from the shoes around shoots right through you like a bullet.
You'd probably like it, though that should be a mortal combat fatality.
should put a doctor in the
M. R. I.
They should put a nurse in mortal combat that can't fight back
why
is killer.
They're adding all types of characters. These days, superheroes to mortal
combat. They put Jason and Michael Myers in it. I was
a
so did you guys hear this Jason Mamou? Apparently he was drunk and he said
that Amber Heard was going to die. He dressed he dressed up as Johnny Depp and
was all drunk and came to the set and demanded that she be fired. Oh my God,
the new Aquaman trailer. I've seen it a couple times in theaters before movies.
It makes me laugh every time for the two things in it make me laugh or one
when black man it's like a normal trailer and then it just cuts to black
man and he says I'm going to kill Aquaman, destroy his family and also
always try the world and maybe on every and then there's a and then there's
also at the end of the trailer, the amber heard is back in the movie, I
guess, but they only show reveal her literally for point two seconds. I do
like a shorter than any cut has ever been in a movie. They just show her
for a like clearly just be like okay contractually. We have to show that
she's in the movie, but we need it if we do it fast enough. Maybe nobody will
notice and get
that's so for that. I thought you were saying we're not taking side of this. I
you're saying like like you know in like they reveal that like Spider Man is
going to be in the MCU. Oh yeah, I do it like
clearly trying to black is so hard. It's like it's crazy. What does she even do
so she she moved in a bed and she I guess was also what's wrong with that
the rude to him over him biting her finger. Oh, she was rude to him. She this
guy bet bit her fingers off and then she said ow did somebody's finger get bitten
enough. I don't know in this case. There was a photo of Johnny Depp asleep next
to a bed. Somebody's finger got bitten off in this. I'm like eighty
two percent. Do you think that us three any one of us could put together a
pretty good kind of like case it like a against Johnny,
we should do a mock trial.
It probably will be
probably will be a trial. You said I said mock trial. You left you said yeah,
when you press the button for ketchup. Yes,
why
okay, imagine that us doing the mock trial right, okay, you guys order in the
court. This is
what does that have to do with anything? I don't know that's a flop. That's a
certified
flop.
We recorded two episodes back to back. Explain yourself though. Crazy as hell
or so you're thinking I'm gonna we're on another level. We're on we should
record two episodes every time and throw away the first hour. I kind of agree.
feels so good. Yeah, I feel energized beginning of the first episode. We
recorded that will come out next week, so I guess we could hint about stuff in
it and do I was tired. I was sinking into the ground. I was getting dragged
into underground heaven and now I'm being affected. I am wide eyed,
bushy tailed and I'm ready to fuck. There were certain factors to the old
program that we did before we shifted into this video where we would sit there
for I think thirty minutes and just sit at the microphones and not hit record.
when we would do it. When did we ever do that? We would do that all the time.
We'd sit in front of that. We would sit there and then I remember doing like
six hour stints. Every single time Caleb would go, "Okay, wait, press record
right now," and then that's how we would start everything.
I'm not sure I remember that. I think I remember Caleb saying, "Press record
right now," when someone sang a funny song or had a weird butt. We would
basically just sit. Yeah. We used to sit there until we had a song. We would sit
there until we had a song. We need to sit there. I'm on cloud nine. Yeah. I
think I was cleansed. How can we bring you back to earth? Yeah, let's get you
back to maybe you could get that what I'm in like you're addicted to drugs,
man. I'm not into drugs. White cocks. I'm on is the cold, brisk air of the
autumn season. What is this? Five o'clock right now, right? It's four
forty
o'clock. I'll chug one right now. Grab to do
what man? There's two. I'm not an able. I can't chug one right now. I gotta go
to the dog park. This is bullshit. I'll fall asleep if I drinking it. This is
bullshit. I'm flipping out now. I'm having a meltdown. I'm freaking out.
You're keeping me from the thing I love.
I'm not keeping you from anything. You're keeping yourself from crawling
under the table. You're afraid there's a monster down there or something.
Look at me. There's no bugs on the floor. Look at me in my eye. Pat,
can you check under my chair for a bed bug?
Here, I'll check.
why are you making the dick sucking noise? I never done that before
yeah yeah, hey check this out guys.
You just think that's what you're supposed to do. Are you okay?
I'm
supposed to do. I ever saw a video of two guys, sixty nine each other. I saw
that video. The was I saw the video video, the dinosaur never seen a video
two guys sixty nine. How did guys sixty nine the balls are around? I think they
like the balls. I think most guys who well fuck they like wearing the balls as
sunglasses
really sunglasses type. I think I'm gay yeah. That's just funny. Have you ever
had balls on your eyeballs? No, but one time all my cousins took turns farting
in my face while I was asleep
and then I woke up and I hit and then my the last one to do it was my brother and
I woke up and I thought just he did it and I beat him up yeah and then it
turns out just walk around. All my cousins ran a fart train on my mouth.
There was this there is. I think I told you guys about this, but there is this
we were all like is me my cousins and then like our friends from school. My
my cousins live down the street. We're having a sleepover and
this one kid was like I have to go to bed early. I have a wreck basketball
game in the at seven in the morning and I'm not going to miss it and it's like
zero. Why did you even sleep over? You were the first one to fall asleep.
There's there you are in for a night of pranking and we put I think it was like
his legs, icy hot on him or something. We might have like done like a icy hot
slap to the face or something or some crazy thing we did with icy hot and then
he ran out and attacked our one friend who did nothing. Yeah, that's how it is.
It's always if you wake up from a if it's like a bunch of people, you find the
one guy who's just like that's because he's the we know no defense. Yeah,
because of course the the weakest guy is not going to do the prank. He said he
screamed, fuck you, cocksucker, and then wasn't on the ground, kicking up and
said, only pussies kick, but he was kicking while he was doing the the while
he's doing that phrase. Okay, call it, tell that to Bruce Lee. Yeah, only
pussies dead. Yeah, tell that to his son. Then one of the funniest movie, one of
the funniest you know after when Bruce Lee got popular, they
they tried to make a bunch of like they tried to capitalize on it. So they got
a bunch of other guys who are not Bruce Lee, but we're just also Asian and they
named them like they gave them stage names like Bruce Lee, L, I and like all
a bunch of guys and like that that was like a big. It was it was like like a
bunch of copycats, obviously movies and then when Bruce Lee died, there's
something that came out. It was with I think it was with Bruce Lee, L, I may
very different bruce lee an imitator type guy, but it was it was called exit the
dragon enter the tiger.
Oh my God, okay,
exit the dragon, exit the drag, enter the
so funny
that's insane. Imagine if there was like
like just they were doing that for like Daniel Tosh or something Daniel Dosh
we're putting in your thoughts. I guess is exactly what happened with Rob dear.
That's ridiculous, and he's Daniel Dosh Daniel Dosh. You know you,
hello, it's me, Daniel Dosh, Daniel Dosh. Hey, imagine if there was like a
sketch show at little field on October twentieth that that happened yesterday
and no, no, okay, wait tomorrow. Oh my God, this happened back. Well,
right, this we backlogged yesterday's or Wednesday. This is exit the dragon
enter the tiger. Now it can be told see Bruce Lee choose his successor and then
because Bruce Lee his death avenged by Bruce Lee, I the new martial arts master
was that's sick. That's actually fucking disrespectful. That is so
disrespectful to do that. I feel like this guy actually chose his successor.
It's the guy who we gave a name. That's the
exit and Caleb. What were you saying
you need to exit the dragon and enter the sketch show at Littlefield on
October 20th. Guys, it's us, it's Podcasts About List as well, and it's also Pierce Campion
and Alex Forrest and Joe Gleason.
Why'd you say Podcasts About List as well?
Because those are our altered egos.
Those are our stage names.
And then also, you, it's, also.
It's tickets at swaggroup.com/joe.
You gotta buy a ticket, man. It's gonna be fun and it's completely different from the
last time.
We've grown all completely. Look at the new sketches over there.
Okay, now be a nerd.
Oh, you look weird, man.
Now be a nerd.
Okay, yeah, well, I think we have to end now because now we're just playing with a GoPro.
But, come on out, guys.
Time to eat.
Ketchup.
K-K-K-K-K-Ketchup.
Bye!
K-K-K-K-Ketchup.
Is it unattractive to women when you throw your back out?
Yes.
Really?
Man, if you hurt yourself.
That sucks.
If you ever stub your toe, this is what you should do. You say, "I didn't stub my toe."
"I didn't stub my toe."
Number two.
Wait, can I just ask your fans real quick?
Lady fans, what is more attractive?
When a man peels off his shirt like this and then kind of drops it?
Well, you just did that gaily.
Right.
Okay, well, if he did that straightly.
If someone did that straightly.
If he's peeling off his shirt.
When he peels off his shirt?
or if you just pop out of it. If you pop out of it. If you pop out of it.
Do you mean rip out of it or you mean pop out of it as a different thing?
Like if you kind of flex. Like you go like this, you go like this and then
you're next to all your clothes falling in a pile next to you. You get raptured
out of your clothes. You get a nice crawler bamf out of your clothes.
Like you have clothes that are on you with suction cups. No, like there's a
tear on your, you flex your bicep and then your bicep pops out of that. I
I don't think a single person has ever done that.
That necessitates having a very tiny shirt on for anybody.
Right, well that's what I mean.
Is it more sexy when you peel off a tiny shirt?
If you're a woman, leave a comment down below, address it to Pierce, say "Dear Pierce."
Write what you think is sexy about a boy taking off his shirt or whatever, however way.
Is it sexy? Because I think it's sexy when a boy pops out.
The question is, so your question is, women, do you think it's sexier when a man takes off his shirt or explodes his clothes?
Do you think it's sexier if a man explodes his clothes or takes his shirt off?
Women, do you like it when a man pops out?
Pops out or takes his clothes out?
Slides.
Slides or pops?
Do you like it when a man slides on you?
Sliding or popping?
Dear Pierce, I like sliding. Dear Pierce, I like popping.
This is a new column. This is a new column for the show.
Amanda.
Dear Pierce.
'Cause all men have this relationship.
My boyfriend has been taking his shirt off.
He's been sliding.
He would pop. I wish he would pop.
How do I get him to pop?
All men have this sliding and popping dynamic that they do in their daily lives, right?
[outro]