I
there it is yet there it is welcome back to another amazing by the episode of
guys about letter what little recorder in your coffee. What is that it's a
straw man? What way I'm getting shit on and you know what that's a beat straw
episode over episode. Oh yeah, it's got the beach logo with this shit. It does
I have the beats logo. It has a water some kind of hydro drop on a hydro
drop. He does not have a hydro drop. He has the beats by Dre. What is a
hydro drop? Why'd you turn up now? You made my head to find my head
so loud that I can't hear my own thoughts, man. This is this episode is
already falling apart. You have like that you enter. First of all, have the
little this is like the thing that the guy from the Pogues plays when he's
doing his little
who's the Pogues. He's not gonna know the Pogues. He's not gonna know the
Pogues. No, you should have known he wasn't. Yeah, what I know the Pogues.
you don't know the I know the pose man. Yes, okay, I like all four of them
that buddy. There's way more of them. There's probably like twelve people in
that band. Yeah, and I knew it was a band, but there's four main members.
Now there's one main member. Yeah, well, there's one. There's one main member
and then three secondary. There's one main matter would always tell me about
meeting him. Shane, me and your dad met Shane McGowan. I'm a drink. Oh, I bet
he remembers that
probably probably it's probably a really special moment.
Definitely Shane McGowan, that guy in Boston, Bob, me a drink
yeah, that's exactly my dad bottom a drink and then he immediately just like
on that's literally exactly my dad.
I think he's filled shane's drink or something and he was like
a
is
You would like this guy. You would like looking at this guy. Oh, the TV's off.
Julio can't even pull up pictures of him. Oh, hey, Senor. Shane McGowan is he's
the he's he's got like the worst teeth in the world. Yeah, I know, dude. It's
like what do you would you eat a
rock?
Who did you turn down? The one that's not plugged? Oh, okay. Sorry. Our fourth
ghost member. Yeah, I was going to I was going to turn his down. I don't know
why, why, because we're talking about yeah, this is her talking me and
Cameron. This is a this is this is Irish chat. Do you guys want to hear
another funny Ireland experience that I remembered last night that I completely
forgotten about that happened when we were in Ireland? I we went to this like
you know we went to like a colonial village type thing like like a
you know, like
yeah like a yeah, yeah, we went to one in Ireland and they had like a bunch of
animals like it was kind of like a not really a petting zoo, but they said
animals like they have there. We were just walking around looking all the
animals and we turned the corner and there was like a pasture and we looked
and there was a tiny
pony like a Shetland style pony. Yeah, that was just standing completely
rigidly still as if it was a statue and just like against the fence, like
putting its head through the fence and just standing there completely still,
just staring straight ahead and we like walked up to him. We're like hey and it
did not move just breathe and look. It was completely the most miserable
animal I've ever seen in my that's an early reincarnation. Yeah, this is a guy
who used to be like a CPA or something and this is day two of being a pony.
It's like that was the most I've ever seen an animal want to die yeah. I mean
I think that a lot of animals like a lot of dogs try to kill themselves. I don't
think that any all the dogs know that cars will kill them. This was this is
though this is the most like human representation. This is like when you
see when you're like oh the the cat knows how to turn on the TV, like oh, I
can see that my behavior in this cat. This is like this. We saw the this is
like pure, the most of your horse and desire to be annihilated yeah, just
when you said like colonial head between bars and just looking straight
dead and not reacting when to walk up to you just God. I mean you said colonial
village in Ireland. I was just imagining like as like a a tourist trap or kind of
like like you know how they have like the Japanese like rock abilities and
stuff yeah, just imagining like the Irish doing like a colonial Williamsburg.
Yeah, well, that's what it was. I mean, I guess it's not colonial. I guess,
yeah, just all yeah, but that's just what the type of reference point, but
yeah, I mean that's what it was. They had a little they had the little stores that
you go into they had the they had the classic school house. You go into the
school house. Can we this is where they learn? Okay, oh my goodness, they had to
sit in front of a chalkboard. That is so boring that fucking stir bridge village
trip. You probably had to do yeah. We did Plymouth plant. Yeah, Plymouth
plantation, then what do you have like did you go to colonial will? I've been
there probably four times yeah it do that shit so no. I think it's cool. I
it's so fried. I think it is cool. Don't say it is right. Well, because there's no
ledges and all those all those people that are there are toy as fuck. That's
lies. It's fried. That's lies. Do there's a number getting up? There's a
there all the way. There's a sword maker there. There's a usually a blacksmith
and this time it was better because all the people it's easier to imagine these
people as coming from the fourteen hundreds because they all have Irish
accents. True. A lot of the people who work at Williamsburg are like guys used
be drug addicts in Philly. Yeah, now they're there. They're hiding a tattoo
yeah in the summer. They have to wear a war like a wool shirt. Yeah, I know that
you are the number one Roku fan in the world.
You can't hide that from me. I can see it in your eyes. Yeah, do that's the
worst. You go, you go to the colonial things, a colonial thing. You go to the
colonial things. Sorry,
now me
Roku fan and you were like yes,
yeah, I am a big road
called out. There's got to be a bigger Roku fan than you. You don't even have a
Roku.
I just remember you have a fire stick.
was the worst day ever. My straw socks and I don't have a Roku
Roku is fired. Yeah, there's got to be you're saying Roku clears Amazon fire
stick all day easily puts it in there. Have you ever heard of someone talking
about Amazon fire city? No, they don't even have a city. No, have it. There is
no city for Amazon fire city is just a picture of some like a movie that they
put at the top. We don't even get or you know Amazon fire city is instead of the
the Roku City us Amazon people who are logged into our mother in laws Amazon
account get to see pictures of every person from my mother in laws church all
the time on my TV. Oh yeah, that's nice. They got that photos, it's just a
photo, photo, and I am so terrified that it's going to be like one day, like
weight loss before and after photos or something popping up. There's always a
danger yeah, because I don't think she knows that her all of her photos are
tried to my who would just show up in my letter
you like the photos. Some of them, some of the guys, there's a photos of me and
and my my in laws that are they're nice photos. Yeah, you know I've hair in the
photos, by the way, grow my hair out like yeah, you're going to grow it out.
I'm going to grow it out. All I can go bald now
dude no because then that will trap me in whatever you just up hair style. This
you guys can both be bald. That's what I say no yeah. I mean you basically
you are bald. You basically I'm not bald. I just like you can't go the extra
that you are. You look too similar to Caleb. Is that the no? I just that
people will mix you two up. I don't think that we can't both be. We can't
both be bald because one
the there's two. Let's strap in here. We got one reason coming up, so that means
there's going to be more.
No, because this is my, I have a joke about this.
He's sliding into a stand up, man.
He's sliding into a stand up.
You know, you guys set me up to be like Jay Leno on Letterman.
Here's what I got going on.
Oh my God.
Just go, just shave that shit off, man.
Yeah, I might.
I've done it before.
You have the mustache and the earring are enough to make you look.
Yeah, but then I just look like a gay guy in the 70s.
What's wrong with that?
Yeah, that's not my vibe.
That's not your vibe.
not your that's the thing. There's no chance that's your vibe. You don't like
to think that I was trying to say that the thing that I was trying to say
about the
like the colonial Williamsburg people and like myself, like there there's like
specific faces now that I feel like it's probably because of the blue light from
screens, but there is some kind of thing that makes people like the you know what
I mean though, like it's the right. Yeah, the blue light people like an iPhone
faces. Yeah, blue light from an iPhone must be morphing our facial structure or
something, or giving us, like, some kind of skin thing that is, like, okay, this
is a face that could only exist in, like, 2023. Like, this is a person born in
'98. But you don't have one of these. I think you have an olden face. You think I
have an old one? You got an old face, man. I do. You have an old face, olden
face that I think you'd counteract with new clothes. Yes. Okay. I think that you
you have a perfect you have a perfect sailor face. Huh, you belong on a ship
and you need to die and the boy like I sit like in a bad is mad about the
strong. No, I'm not mad. So mad about that. About the straw thing. The straw
doesn't matter anymore. I even think this straw is cringe personally. Yeah,
why do you say one of your wife's purchases? Is the straw with you? Okay,
guys, you brought the straw to the store.
don't bother giving me a story. I brought my own story time guys story time bundle
up because this is about to be an amazing story. I went to I went to Duncan. I got
a free cold brew because I had 700 points. Okay. I didn't do that at Dunkin
Donuts. Those are very nice people. They get yelled at enough. I went to the one
on Fresh Pond. Nope. It's the one on Myrtle. I went to Duncan. Hold up. Hold
up. Hold up.
Run that shit back. It was the one on Myrtle.
Caleb Pitt storytelling.
Okay, I'm doing the one finger of stories. Okay, give me a beat the one
finger of stories. Here it is.
Okay, that's mean. That's kind of a mean finger. There we go. I went to
Duncan, I grabbed this on the shelf, I forgot to get a straw, I got home,
I said, "Oh, do I have any straws in my house?" No straws, except for this
little doodad, which I've never... That is a doohickey. This is a doodad.
It's not a straw. It's a wide straw. It looks like I'm nursing. You know what? I think that
I'm actually now that I've seen you sip from it, not jealous of it. Why? I think I was
making fun of it because I was like, "No, they don't make straws that wide." Okay, I
actually quite like it. He likes it. The straw? I think that my... It's mixing mixed up between
the straw, the coffee. It makes the drink stay cold because it's metal all the
way. It makes the drink stay cold, the metal goes going all the way, and then
the width of the straw, you're getting a lot of liquid. You put a lot of liquid
on the end of my straw. I did not put a lot of liquid on the end of the
straw. You did, did you? You had full lips all the way. I do have a
spit problem. What's this problem you have? Too much? It's probably something...
Yeah, I think I have too much spit.
Overactive gland?
Yeah. I think there's a... maybe I got a mouth stone from all the energy drinks over the years.
Could be that. Oh, I want to see you pop one of those so bad.
That'd be cool.
Did you guys ever watch video of popping disgusting stuff out of their bodies?
Yes.
Oh, I love that shit.
Dr. Pimple Popper.
But also this... when people get the salivary stone...
Those are gross. I don't like those.
They're awesome. I love them. I want them to shoot out.
you know what I went to the one time I went to the urgent care in Boston and
they were playing a video. They were playing some TV show that was like Dr.
Pimple Popper on the TV for the waiting room. Everyone was there because they
were sick or miserable, but it was Dr. Pimple Popper, but it was for pets. I
don't want that. I was bought that dude. Have you ever seen the video?
Animal surgery, but if you ever seen the videos where the where the dogs are
like walking around the street and then they are like, oh, look at this dog.
I get closer and the dog has a million worms. Yeah, it is body. I've seen
those. Oh man, you know what I saw the other day? Oh my God, yeah, you say
yours
you know those like in the in the caliber of like pimple popping and like
like the oddly satisfying human disgust or yeah body horror stuff. The disgust
or the
the oddly satisfying disgust or crew have now started to do ingrown toenail
pair, which I saw a video of somebody getting like an ingrown.
I've seen that one.
They peel the thing away and then you just see the pus shoot out and it's like a whack-a-mole
for the poppers.
I had one really, really bad when I was a kid and they had to put a needle, they had to
numb my foot.
I had the same shit with my thumb.
I was like...
My toenails are always ingrown constantly.
I had a big ingrown thing right there on this thumb and I had to go to the hospital because
there was a red. Oh my God, you got the end of the the classic infection, the
classic Nazgul infection. Yeah, you had a red line. I had a red line. That's one
of my fears. I never heard of that. That's what they say. They say if your
cut is infected, if it's like if it has like pus and if you see a red line, you
need to go to the hospital like immediately because it's like your blood
infection or whatever. Whoa, and you live to your heart. I guess I had that.
It's like a my dad said, yeah, how far up did it get dude? How close are you?
that's right next to your heart dog. It was pretty close, but I was just like I
went in and they just like, they just like, I'm sorry, that's I am viewing you
completely different. You had a near death experience. Barely. It was just
like, no, don't downplay this shit, man. The heart, the line was close to your
heart. The coolest thing though was when I was in, I was taking my, oh, the
coolest thing was the line. Let's be real. Yeah. But the coolest thing was
when I was taking my art final in, it was my senior year of high school and
that's when I noticed the infection and I took just like a like it was like I
think it was like the nib for like the ink pen that I was using and I just
fucking and like
push down on it so hard that like it shot so much puss out that it went up.
It was like a squirter.
That's the coolest part. Dude that's, yeah the pittin'.
Oh the line was cool man, just leave it at the line.
Did you use it in your art, the puss? Yeah. No, 'cause I had already turned in,
I had already turned in my final and I was waiting for the. So you had some extra
time to. Yeah. Mutilate your body. Oh okay. Well I didn't, I wanted to just
draw with the ink pen. I thought that I the thing I saw yesterday was old was
the most disgust or thing I have ever seen in my life. What was it? I am a
face
and a mirror,
your face in a mirror. Why'd you say that come on? Sorry, I said it to myself
actually.
I thought I was still
that's my bad. I thought I was completely talking. I was walking home.
I saw this homeless guy sleeping on somebody's friend. Oh yeah,
it. Oh
it's just so insane. Yeah, he was sleeping on someone's front steps and
then the person came home and was walking by him and like kind of like
skirted by him, like didn't really say anything just like to go unlock the
front door and when he when the person step by him, he like sat up and started
to like gather a shit. He had like like a blanket and like he set up to start
gathering his stuff up and move and when he lifted his head, I saw what he was
like lying his head on on the stairs was like a wet, dirty stuffed animal monkey
and then on top of it like that it was directly touching his head was a giant
wet dead rat
and that was he was using that as a pillow and he just sat and the person
going into their house just like looked at it and then just like one inside. Do
you think that was like oh my just so insane? So the craziest thing I've ever
to you. Do you think he was like like he had to pick up the dead rat and be like
this is what I I'm sorry. The combination of these two things will
make my head comfortable. Which one should I put on top? Which one should I
directly lay my head on? Should I lay it on? I bet that kind of feels like
depending on how fat the rat is. There's a big fucking rat yeah. It was huge. I
bet that kind of feels good. I wouldn't I don't think so. No, you know you like
you you're you lay your head on like your girlfriend,
you know,
hairy leg. Yeah, here in the back of her hairy leg cold.
You know what I'm talking about? You follow you follow you're watching TV.
You fall asleep with your head on your girlfriend's hair. That means you if
you're falling asleep on your girlfriend's body, you're the girlfriend
man
straight up facts sleep on her cab dude. I feel like I'm well. I don't want to
make the world is getting grosser. I don't want to make this about me, but
The woman who used to, who was a homeless lady still is, and she tried, when she could walk,
she would like hunt down Phil and try to kick him all the time. I ever tell you about her?
No, you never did.
I told him, yeah, I told him. There was this lady who would just like, every single time
we'd be down the street, she would beeline to Phil and like wind up a big kick and then
miss.
Oh my God.
The first time I was like, what the fuck is wrong with you, you fucking crazy bitch? And
then by the third time I was like, nice try, man.
Yeah.
Missed.
She would just like get mad that she missed the kick and keep walking.
Anyway, now she can't walk. I think she lost one of her feet or something.
Diabetes or did you think she kicked up?
Diabetes, yeah. This homeless lady is eating so much candy that she got diabetes.
She's living such a lavish life.
Well, yeah, what's the cheapest thing at McDonald's? The ice cream cone.
Oh, that's actually a very fair point. Anyway, she started, she is now, she's resorted to,
for the last couple of months, the bench in front of my apartment, using it like
a toilet and shitting through the slats of the bench every single morning.
That's sad. No, it gets worse. And when that didn't work, now...
It didn't work? What do you mean it didn't work? Well, it didn't make me
mad enough, I guess. It wasn't enough for her? Yeah, 'cause I guess she's
trying to ruin my life. Why didn't you have a
nemesis? She's not my nemesis. Maybe I'm her nemesis, but I barely think about
her. Wow, that's cold. That's cold as fuck. But now she's pulling out the
The ultimate move to ruin my mornings, which is that she is
every single morning laying down on that bench and crying very loudly.
And it is really harsh in my vibe, man. Yeah, I can imagine. I think I'm
gonna walk up to her and be like, "Here's 100..." Fuck, no. "Here's 100
Mr. Beastballs." She tried to kick my dog. I'm gonna say... Mr. Beastballs?
Yeah, it's a thing I made up. It's an NFT that you can sell.
I should give her an NFT. You're giving her a poor tape.
That's a good idea. Well, honestly, as somebody who owns an NFT, I can tell you it doesn't
make you happy. That's true. Yeah, he owns a shard. I have. It's actually it's it's a
fragment fragment of a shard. But now I have now I have no choice of the moon, but to save
her life. Yeah, because even though I don't want to, because she tried to she tried to
kick my dog. Now I have to save her life and fall in love with her. Yeah. So I'm in a really
bad spot this week. I know. I mean, I can't imagine that your wife wants. She's not happy
about that, but I mean I brought her inside. I'm gonna have to like clean her
up and make her a hot meal and have her make her and then make her a hot meal.
Oh, I'm gonna eat her. Yeah. Oh no, no, I thought you meant what do you mean that
he's gonna eat her or do you mean yeah what are you saying like making her like
a snack make like make her a hot meal yeah what is that I'm not sure how that's
that's changing like make her like her emphasis on yeah her. I know she's the
one that's going to make her a hot meal and make her a hot meal hot meal. Oh
okay.
Yeah, so hot meal
anyway meals, I mean that eat that a hot meal. I've given her food. Why we we
could have been wacky packages writers. That's the thing dude. I
I tried to I tried to squash it. Yeah, I've given her I even when she was
kicking Phil every once in a while. I if I because there's a pizza place right
yeah. If I got a slice of pizza, I'd grab an extra one and give it to her,
but she still came after Phil with these feet. Yeah, and then God, you can
know you're trying to bribe her. Yeah, I kind of was I was more it's probably
the the homeless person in the history of my life that I've given the most
stuff to
purely to stop her from trying to hit my dog.
I mean homeless people, I guess, could learn a lesson from that. If you want a
from money from Caleb just try to kill his dog. Yeah, dude. It's really I mean
we live in a backwards world. Did she so
did I mean I know Phil personally I know him. Yeah, that's my dog. We're pretty
good. We're pretty good friends. He hates you. He doesn't hate me. He despises you.
What are you talking about? He hates me. Every time he sees me, he runs over to
me. To try to bite you. No, 'cause he thinks that I'm a fellow dog. That might
be true actually. He thinks that I'm... You probably smell like a dog. He thinks
that I'm a dog and he comes over to me. I mean you see you, you can vouch for me on
this. Phil runs up to me every single time he sees me. That's because you go
very excited. Yeah, but he likes that. No, he doesn't. Phil runs to you. I don't
like it. It doesn't matter what the dog likes. Yeah, that's why you, you're saying
that he hates me because you don't fuck with that. But I know that he, well, he
does run towards me. Maybe he thought this woman was me. She does look a lot
like you. He could have been running, he could have been running towards her. I've been having
an incident, a thing recently, I'm wearing a collared button down shirt if you can't notice
that. You pulled up in the most Tony Soprano ass shirt the other day but then you, we were
doing that episode with freestyling. So I had to cover it up. You covered it up but that,
it looked cool. Whoa, the truth comes out. Listen. I've never, I have never ever once,
what's the word I'm looking for here? Disrespected me. Not disrespected or
respected. I've never once,
somewhere in the middle,
never once not admitted when a shirt looked
swag. Ever not once admitted when a shirt looked swag. Okay. Yeah, no,
that's good. You're saying you say when you see a shirt you like, you say it.
It doesn't matter who's wearing it. It doesn't matter. It's so hard to get
your point across. Yeah, it's difficult these days. That is true. What was I just
saying? Things have changed. Because of long COVID. You don't have long COVID. Do you
actually believe you have long COVID? And chronic Lyme. No, you know that I don't even believe that
exists. I didn't know that. I think it exists. All right. I think that it kills millions,
probably. Millions a day. Every single day, millions die. You're talking about your shirts.
Oh, yeah. So I've been having a thing recently where I'll be walking the dog
and I'll see a very ratty, tattered clothes, staggered kind of person,
coming, yeah, I mean, dressed like a zombie, walking towards me on the street, and I'll
kind of bring the dog a little closer because, again, I'm like, "This guy is a homeless guy.
He's going to kick my dog." And then I get next to them, and basically, I realize they're dressed
exactly like me. They're wearing a ratty hoodie that they probably overpaid for,
and just like old jeans.
Yeah.
And then I'm like, I wonder how many people a day think that I'm homeless walking down the street.
I mean, you're like doing like the
like the Shia LaBeouf thing where you wear all the ratty ass clothes.
To say that people don't notice who you are.
Oh, that is what I'm doing, dude. I'm trying to be incognito in plain sight.
Be like, that's a celeb.
Yeah, I don't want people to say,
"Dude, parking ticket."
Me, personally?
Oh my god, that's Trixie Mattel.
Yeah.
Yeah, no, that's...
Wait, no, that's not my name.
Wait, that's who's that? Oh, you're saying the owner of the Mattel fortune.
No, no, no, no.
So, they're saying, because obviously they're thinking I'm a rich guy.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God. Can I have your autograph?
Who do you, what? Okay, so obviously I'd be Jason Statham.
I mean, it would be hard to tell, it would be hard to tell if he was
Trixie Mattel because like there's...
They would go up to him and they'd be like, "Oh, my God. I love your
performances." He's like, "Thank you."
Oh, thank you.
Oh, well thank you. Upcoming short film.
Appreciate you.
Your associate. Coming out soon.
Upcoming short film. Thank you so much.
Who, what celebrities do you guys think
that you would be mistaken for the most?
David Krumholz. Ninja.
Ninja. He does a big ninja. Definitely ninja.
Definitely ninja. We got it. Dude,
you have to be ninja for Halloween.
Wait, who's David Krumholz?
Yeah, I don't know who that is.
He's the fat guy in Oppenheimer.
Which what?
Benheimer's best friend. Oh, I know who you're talking about. I look exactly like
him. You don't look like him. I look a lot like him. What are you talking about?
Yeah, there's one photo of him that
I look... He has a girl's name in that movie. Pretty much exactly. His
character's name sounds like a girl's name. What's his name again? I don't
know. I'm trying to remember. All I remember is that it's a girlly name.
Albert Einstein, man. Yeah, his name is Alberta Einstein. God, why can't I
remember it? I saw that movie seven times.
No, you lie. I didn't see it. I saw it two times. I didn't see it even once,
two times. It's good coming to digital soon. Well, I'm like digital. Don't you
think there's a little far in the future for a movie like that? Damn
that's yeah,
that shit should be coming to analog man, which I'm not sure. I mean, I guess
just a reel of film, maybe this is who you think you look like. This is who I
have been told by multiple like show the show the GoPro.
I'm not.
Um, honestly, yeah, I'm not going to lie to you that he looks he's he's tubby, but he
looks, he looks similar mustache, similar eyes and stuff.
Yeah, he was on that show numbers.
If you remember that.
No, I never seen that movie.
They would let us watch that in my math class in high school.
That's cool to teach us about math.
And there's so many times in like my, my school experience where we would be watching something
It's like we're watching a movie in a class where we're not supposed to be
usually watching non educational movies. And I came to that. I was like I had the
realization like, oh, I'm in like the second lowest of this version. I took an
economics class and we watched that movie in time with you. I was like, I was
like, Yeah, I'm glad I'm not doing work, but I'm going to get quizzed on this.
I'm getting quiz on for economics. Yeah, we used to watch teacher was this guy.
his name was Mr. Roop and Mr. Roop was like a,
he was like a musician on the week. He's basically the first experience I had
with Sean Stevens. What kind of cool nicknames did you have for Mr. Roop?
We never called him Mr. Boop because he let us watch in time. So we were like,
okay, he's actually... He's swag. Yeah. Mr. Boop. What the hell was that?
What the fuck? Mr. Boop. Mr. Boop. That sounded crazy. I think he had a tattoo of a clock on
his forearm too. That's badass. Do you guys remember my old roommate who had a full...
Maybe you guys never even met him. No. My first roommate in Boston, it was me, Neil,
this guy Dante, and this guy Stan. And Stan got a tattoo. Oh no, because Stan had moved
out at that point. Stan got a tattoo all the way up his arm that was a clock with that was
every, it was like however many stages, faces of the moon, all with the clock as the moon
going all the way up his arm. And so the top of his arm dude, fully black circle. Tell
me that's not the most badass shit you've ever seen in your life. And I said what the
hell is that about? That is a metalcore ass tattoo. I said what is that? And he said it's
is about time. People who are into stuff like that love to get Roman numerals. I
think he actually had another. I think
well, you can't read normal numbers. Yeah, the hell's wrong with you. You
think you're so cool. I can read Roman numerals. I think Roman numerals are so
whack. There's a reason we got rid of them. Imagine how much cooler the
Coliseum would look if instead of Roman numerals all around it, it would like
engravings and that kind of stuff. It was just numbers. That'd be way more chill.
Yeah, if I like the look of numbers, numbers are fire. Arabic numbers. I you
know, I can't really do I can't really add and subtract them or multiply them
that well. Yeah, you don't know a lot about these. I don't know a lot about
them, but aesthetically I do like them. Do you have any? I think that the three
three is the three is a went off with three. I'm my favorite seven. Seven
looks good. Seven seven is well done across the seven eight. I do that two
73s and this I do the slash through the zero to that is that was fire man slash
through the zero.
That's a really good through the seven really good looking number. I'm getting
excited to write some numbers when I go home really good looking number 72 72 is
pretty cool. That's true. It looks like a seven and upside down seven Carlton
Fisk Carlton Fisk or with it as a triangle.
Ooh, I don't do that shit. That's kind of there's so many ways to do that, but I
don't do it so much anymore, but it just is fascinating how many different ways
So many different ways you can do a four with the loop. You all do to with the
loop. That's the a two two with the loop. Oh yeah, I actually do a two with the
loop. Yeah, I do think about all the different types of numbers there are in
the world. Do you guys do eight as two circles or do you do it as one line? I
do it as one line, but I do I do like to imagine it as two threes kissing.
Whoa, two threes. I'd like this front. It would be better if they had the
staggered ends. So it was like they're going into each other. That'd be more
hot. God damn it for three. It's not for me. I just want to download just like a
bunch of fonts. I just want to download a bunch of numbers. Just fucking look at
a bunch of numbers and download a bunch of fonts and type in all the numbers.
You know what I do not fuck with? What? Oh wait, this is a great math problem. A lot
of beautiful numbers here. Huh? What's this letter doing here? Yeah, wait. Is
that a fucking X or a Y? Is that supposed to be an X or a time sign? Yeah, get
that shit out of my numbers, man. X literally took multiplication sign
multiplications like you have to now you have to be an asterisk. Yeah, that
literally I'm turning you into a butthole, but yeah, dude, a bunch of a
star, yeah, bro, but whole bro, it does a jacked its whole flow. Yeah, he stole it.
He stole his shit in a major way. I mean, well, I don't know who stole it
first. Actually, did X come for X probably came first. I think the X came
first before the using that for a multiple. I think that X has been around
since the beginning of time, but I think that well yeah, the beginning of time,
the beginning of time started with X right. That's why we call multiplication
times tables right time x wow here's here's what that's why that's why
disrespecting it making it a butthole is fucked up. Algebra was invented by
by algebra, but the times thing is in the Bible go forth and multiply yes and
math was invented by Charles Mathis
Mr. Ath. No, it is a math. And food was invented by food.
Foodle-doodle. And this is basically how history has been forever.
The old Roman emperor, Foodle-doodle. No.
No. It is funny that, you know, do you know
where the word cynic comes from? No. Where? Does it come from the word dog?
It comes from basically a guy whose name was was cynic or sineos or whatever, and
he was just a crazy homeless guy. Yeah, and he had a bunch of gang of a bunch of
different homeless guys who would walk around Greece like it was San Francisco
and just fall over and people would be like, oh, these guys are cynics. Yeah, so
we have fun. I mean, it's funny. That's what most I feel like that's a lot of
words are like that where it's just a guy's name. Yeah, or a group of people.
I hope that one day there is a so he was like the Caleb ism yeah. He's like the
Roy Monson. I don't know what it is. What is it, then you don't want to know
what I do want. I've obviously already coined the term, but not about what's
not about you, but okay, good. It's
it's about it means when you're a bald guy who's a perv yeah, and it was about
a different guy. It's not about you, but it's just unfortunate that it happened.
It's about Caleb. I'm bald. Why the perv Caleb? That's not about you. It's
by a different yeah that guy Caleb Knits and I TTS was his last name and it just
I mean it sucks that you're bald. It does kind of feels like a kind of a confirms
so that the idea of
must be the same. Oh, and his name's Caleb. Oh, my God, it's kind of like
unfortunate, but yeah, it's not really your fault. Don't worry about it. So
you're growing, you're growing that out. Yeah, dude, I'm thinking I could do. I'm
going to grow it out and try to have a normal haircut. Yeah, I'm going to try to
do just a normal. I'm not going to do just do this one say put the.
Yeah, you
I'm bald. You got to get rid of this guy right here. I like that guy.
All right, you guys cool. Yeah,
I said you look like you look like the grandpa from house. You'll look like
the grandpa from House of a Thousand Corps and that's what I want to look
like as a grandpa. Yeah, I'm kind of going for a grandpa kind of look.
Yeah, you got tired of the completely bald shit. It's just a it's a hassle
man. Yeah, it's a hassle and the expectations of everybody around you.
Yeah. You know, they're like, Oh, let me touch your head.
Baldness is powerful. Oh my God, it's so smooth.
Yeah. And everybody always says,
dude, I actually like it better when you're bald.
Yeah. Dude, shut up. No, you don't.
People say that? People say that all the time.
You like it better?
Oh, you actually have a good head for being bald.
Oh. Shut up, man.
Let me just, let me wallow.
That's what I've been saying. I've always said it.
If you are going bald, just don't get on finasteride.
Don't get on minoxidil. Just let that shit turn into the horseshoe.
And just don't pretend that it's cool. Just admit that you're suffering.
Don't be like, "Oh, it's actually empowering to shave my head."
No, it's not, dude.
No, it's not empowering to shave your head.
It's a chore.
I thought you were saying, like, "Oh, don't act like you're suffering for the growing of the thing."
That's why I don't brush my teeth, man, because I gotta pick one.
I'm not gonna be in the bathroom for ten minutes every morning.
Oh, speaking of teeth, that temporary filling that I had completely fell out,
and I didn't realize how big it was, and now there's a giant hole in my mouth.
Just eat it.
I did.
Really?
eating a no. How many times have you eaten your teeth at this point? It's the same tooth
that remember I you just keep eating the same tooth. No, it's the same tooth that I cracked
like two years ago when we were. Were we doing the no I wasn't on the pod at that point. But
do you guys remember we were all hanging out at City Place and I cracked my I think you
were there. I cracked my tooth eating a gummy worm or something. Yeah. I think I was eating
a
yeah, I
that's a
you can't blame the gummy worm. No, no, no, it's my fault. I
that's what I was thinking. Yeah, I don't remember that. No, who was with me?
Then I might have been with you. I just don't remember. It just didn't make an
impact on me. We were
you didn't like the first couple of times. We were like every time Patrick
is like dude remember like that. I don't remember anything. I especially don't
I don't remember any time that I met you before. I remember maybe three or four
things from the last fifteen years of my life. All right, what do you got?
Well, yesterday,
yesterday, I remember kind of, oh, I had pizza yesterday. Oh, yeah, pizza for
lunch. Remember that?
Oh, did I tell you guys I forgot how to tie my shoe? Yeah, yeah, you never knew.
You forget how to tie your shoe. Yeah. No, like I. You got him do that for you.
no, no, no, I like sat at the town. I tried to show you to tie your shoe a
bunch of times before I learned how to do it. I remember yeah, okay, so I
learned how to do it and I've been doing it for one number. Thanksgiving last
year, yeah, I learned how to time. I this was crazy. I learned how to tie my
shoe and this is about a year ago. I learned how to do the adult way, not the
bunny ears. I learned how to time my shoe the fast way and the other day I
was getting right. I was going to the gym, but on my my converse tied my left
one perfectly fine, did the same thing on the right, but it just didn't work and I
was like, what? And then I sat there for four minutes trying to do the same thing
over and over again and just failing and it didn't work at all and then
eventually it worked, but I think I had like a stroke. Yeah, I had four minutes
where I just sat there trying to loop one lace around the other and nothing
happened and I was like, am I crazy? Did they change this? The world has been
being updated lately. Yeah, something something taking away days. This was a
glitch in the matrix. Some might say some people on websites last night.
That's another glitch and we worked hard putting that trash out there.
I don't really think that that's a glitch. That's a glitch. That's more of
an oversight. Yeah, it's a glitch because the trash is supposed to disappear
overnight. I don't think no, it's guys. It's a job because we put it out too
like after they already came. We did the infinite probably which
infinite trash, which well what are you? They picked it up and it stayed here.
Now that will be a glitch. That would be crazy to sell it. If trash was worth
anything, if it wasn't, it's worth something to someone. One man's trash is
another man's treasure. My friend, something they wouldn't they wouldn't
make it a saying. If it wasn't true, some I guess that's a literal sense,
something in that trash was worth a lot to pierce last night. Somebody threw out
his Oreos. He I talked him through it and he threw them out. Wow, you convinced
him. Well, he was he kept out. He was complaining that I throw his Oreos and I
was like I did not throw your Oreos. I threw away a bunch of cans unless your
Oreos were in a can or in an empty bag of chips. I did not throw them away and
then he would kept being like no you did and then I was like I just literally
didn't. He said well, they were in a black plastic bag. I was like well, I
didn't throw that away and he was like oh wait. I did
you had a girlfriend argument with him. It wasn't really an argument. I was more
I would say it was more of a therapy moment.
Yeah.
It wasn't heated. It was more of a, I was kind of guiding him towards the light.
And was he grateful for you once he realized that you showed him?
Yeah, he basically said I was the best guy ever.
Really?
No.
Oh, shit. Well, never mind.
But I didn't throw that shit away, man. I wouldn't throw away Oreos.
No, no, no, no, no.
I can smell that shit. I'm like a...
Why would I throw that away?
You see the blue Oreo thing, you're going to check immediately.
Is there an Oreo in there?
There's an Oreo in there.
time my cousin had a sleeve of chips of hoi cookies that he left outside
overnight, and we woke up and we walked past, he put them on a bush, and we
woke up, we walked past and there was a snail, like sliding around on the
cookies, and he just took the snail off and ate all of them.
Oh. Isn't that disgusting?
I think about that all the time. Can a snail carry disease? A snail can carry
goo. It actually does carry goo and it drops it off as it goes. Yeah, it's
is mucus. Is it gooey though? Is it mucus? Yeah, I mean, some guys not
your mucus is the word for goo. Oh,
but it really disgusted me and it really stuck with me man. Yeah, mucus is
just what scientists learn. They can say instead of goo or slime, scientists
and doctors. That's kind of a bummer. Yeah, what is that? They don't say
slime, your slime membrane. Yeah, I wish it was called that. Oh, you've got
a lot of, you've got a lot of slime in your sinuses. You've got a lot
goo in your sinus. That's what I was wondering about all that pimple popper, all that fucking
stupid bullshit. What happened to just picking your boogers, man? It's allowed. I'm keeping
it alive and well, buddy. Where is the videos of a guy picking a booger and saying, "Check
how big this booger is." It's not as good though. They should make a Pluto TV channel
that's a split screen and half of it is for girls and it's pimple popper and the other
other half is for boys and it's a guy a fat guy picking his not
yes
and eating it. You oh dude,
that looked like a chunky way that was big and you set up a blanket for it
like a blanket curtain, a divider yeah like no screen sheet yeah yeah yeah
you can't screen cheat and look over at me watching a fat guy. He's a like
you're playing halo, he's eating boogers and he's drinking a beer and
then everyone so every like four scenes. There's one scene of a guy writing
the Cotty yeah, just like they did make that, though it was on crash box, but
you have to learn words from it. It was the
revolting slob. I saw the funniest final Jeopardy yeah. What do you say
thing about Pluto TV was it boogers? It was it was you know, so you know how
they like announce the category and then you you wager whatever you work. So
like you wager based on the category and they're like it was like a really
heated game. Everyone was like really close at the end, like final jeopardy
was really going to matter and then Alex Rebecca's like and for our fight, our
final jeopardy category is get your wages ready. It will be today geogra
flea.
Well,
you could see everyone is going like what
what was the my God, it was like it was like what deposed person like fled this
country like it was like oh okay, but L E yeah that was F L E, which made
geographically like bugs from different. Today's you it was it was much funnier
just with Alex Trebek's voice, say
geographically. Have you seen that about that and we'll be right back?
Have you
just a complete not who made do me
blue? The seeing everybody with
food
Have you seen that clip of Alex Trebek's, like it's the Alex Trebek bloopers,
where he's just going... Saying like, "Fucking God damn, fuck this shit." Yeah,
yeah. He's just being like, so like, you know, how he was, just like complete,
like, just like, "Oh my God, this guy's in complete... I can look at him,
I can just tell this guy's in complete control all the time." Yeah. And just
seeing him just go like, "Well, fuck." He says, "Fuck." The clip that I saw,
it's like he's about to say, like he's doing some TV promo and just goes like,
and we'll be the fuck
way. He says it. It's so
was so dude. He was the man. One of the greatest
regrets of my life is that I wasn't him really good at Jeopardy in time to be on
the episode of Jeopardy with Ken, when Ken Jennings was the host and that for
Final Jeopardy, I could write in I'm going to kill you Ken Jennings. That
would have been really what is I'm going to kill
- That would have been so sick. - Just drooling over the scratch marks.
- He's not on it anymore? - No, it's someone else now.
- Still Mayim Balik? - Yeah, I think so.
I don't watch the current episode, so I don't know.
- I think it should be my ass, dude. - Yeah, I think so too.
- I'd be on there. - They should make a show called
- Chill Jeopardy. - Yes.
I have been watching so much Jeopardy. I'm existing in a crazy psychic dimension
where I'm every-- we're working on this sketch show that has passed by the time
- this episode has come out. - It actually was so fire.
left all day thinking about the sketch show. Then I go home and
immediately fall asleep watching Jeopardy. I think it's cooking my
brain. Yeah, but it's probably making you smarter. You would think so, but
instead it's making me have strange dreams. Okay, what is a what is
okay? Wait, what is exactly this
this
chocolate
what is guy? Whoa, chocolate guy was the mascot for what deodorant brand
in 2006. What is that? Wait, there's two guys. He won, but you said, but yeah,
no, it's not what it would be. Chocolate guy. So it's really two questions. You
had it. You made two chocolate guy was the mascot for this deodorant company.
This child, you need a photo to say this chocolate guy. Well, I'm not the expert
even then you're like him. It would be this this deodorant brand used a
chocolate guy in an ad campaign. Okay, all right, is that what is axe? Okay,
which is which is what I would say. If somebody said what is axe, I would say
this today's final jeopardy category will be chocolate guys in deodorant
commercials. Yeah, exactly.
Chocolate guys through history
will be yellow sponges that live in bikini bottom. Chocolate guys through
history.
(Laughter)
Well, let's say, okay, okay, wait, wait, wait. Let's reverse, we're going to reverse engineer a Jeopardy category right now.
We're just engineering.
100 for 100. I mean, obviously, it's going to be Gloppy. That's the easiest one.
Who's Gloppy?
Candyland.
Oh, okay.
This chocolate guy lives in his own swamp.
I think it starts at 200.
Okay.
Well, this is low stakes Jeopardy.
Yeah. Okay, then 200 would be Gloppy immediately.
yeah okay, and then the question would be this is who this is who is that this
guy
what
and he lives in a chocolate swamp okay four hundred
axe guy okay, six hundred
what's another chocolate guy. So this is so
jeopardy not so easy to make
right, you're saying, oh, I can do jeopardy, then you can't did chocolate
you can't you pick too insane of a category. I'm going to be honest with
you. No, I think that there's another there's more chocolate.
Jeopardy thing that I was thinking about that is how like can you imagine
watching Jeopardy your whole life sitting at home on the couch and like
you know, yell is you say the answers out loud. Yeah, your girlfriend doesn't
care every time that they ask a question and you do that every single
night for years and years years and for your birthday. You finally she gets
your ticket to go be in the studio audience for jeopardy and you go to
that you go there and you have to sit there and every single question they
ask you have to be completely silent. Yeah, I would get kicked out in five
minutes. I would I would not be able to. I would literally a completely
involuntarily just be like Oh, what is ax
yeah? They would ruin the entire episode and they'd kick me. They have a quiet
room for jeopardy like church yeah.
it's a room full of guys, it's a room full of dudes and there's just like a
sheet of glass and it's just guys sitting there just going like
I literally I would do that. So I single time I go
oh, even if I didn't say the answer every time I go, oh yeah, that would
actually be this is another amazing jeopardy idea. So first of all, this
episode would have chocolate guys through history, but then it's there's a
little glass little like club room. You pay an extra two hundred, I guess they
have to put you in there, but in that room is a bar and you can watch
Jeopardy! live like it's the
executive booth at the football game. I'm sure that you can probably already
get a drink at the Jeopardy! No, no, no, no, no, no, no. This is a
room, this is a room, this is a room where you can stand with
six other guys that look exactly like you. Banging bullet proof glass.
Banging bullet proof glass going, "Let me out, let me out, I know the
answer. Well, no you're in there watching putting a hundred dollars like
the scene and scream is that scream to or scream three where they're in the
like the
fucking soundproof room and everything getting killed. If you have negative
money on jeopardy, you owe them my you owe them money. That's the worst part
about it. I think you I would never think it depends on the on the like
because I think sometimes I think you still want money if you're negative,
but I think it really depends on I think they pay you for your your well. I was
watching episode the other day where someone ended with negative money and
they said you go home with a thousand dollars, but I don't know if that's if
it was like a special. We need to I think that game shows are far behind the
inflation rate and we need to every game show should be for a million bucks. I
think it's not I'm not playing giant fucking putt putt if it's not for a
million dollars. Well, you if you you're not you don't really win jeopardy
unless you win you with fifty days in a row and win three million dollars. Yeah,
nobody cares if you won one episode. Well, I would care well, it doesn't matter.
I'm saying I'm saying that's the that's the inflation valve there. What's that?
The people who win they're winning seven? How do you even study for jeopardy? You
just have to be an annoying person. Yeah, very annoying person. Think about every
single jeopardy, all the Arthur to Ken Jennings,
may embolic
the I've got celebrity jeopardy. There's a got one guy who's a bartender who's the
first one Watson knowing no no Watson is another annoying guy. The IBM, the IBM
computer computer that thing is fucking annoying. It's annoying really a
bartender, though no, but I know this in the future yeah could be probably yeah
yeah. The bartender guy is really annoying. He's just like he's like
I'm a bar and he shakes his buzzer. The sports betting guy, you know that guy,
the guy who has the record. He smiles like this
you
God and he makes jokes all the time. What kind of fit would you get off of the
jeopardy shit? Oh man shirt mesh mesh shirt, swim trunks,
bottom print sponge Bob Matt painting print yeah, swim trunks with the
flippers to him. Yeah, get the flip group, goggles, a floaty, a floaty and
you got to be ready and yeah we're going to be and then we're going to be
having the Tom and Jerry hobo style top hat with the tin can opening. Yes,
yes,
and then fingerless gloves with study, a Ocarson style, yeah, yep, and then
fingerless gloves with an embroidered that says
on the back, he showed up like a home, and I'll be wearing pit vipers,
sunglasses on the back of my head and standing backwards the whole time.
what would you put your name down as Fudd?
I would put my name down as Ken Jennings, Junior
Frank is s
reverse Jennings
so
and a returning to
reverse Jennings.
What isn't
that's not the rules reverse yeah
Oh, man,
that's so funny. Doing the backwards man on Jeopardy would be pretty awesome.
I need to be on Jeopardy. I was laughing. I think you could get on there.
I was imagining just like... I don't think I could win, though. I wish that
your reality TV show thing worked out, man. Me too. I'll make it onto reality
TV. I'm probably gonna marry one of the girls from Vanderpump Rules or something.
Whoa. One of the pumps? I guess. Is that their name? Vanderpump? Yeah,
Lisa Vanderpump. Oh, God, is she beautiful? Yes. Holy shit. Is she the
Is she the one who's on Real Housewives?
I think so.
Is she British?
No.
No?
Who's the British Lisa?
Is Lisa Vanderpump British?
I really don't know.
I thought that she was...
You know what?
I wish we had the TV so we could look at a picture of Lisa.
I get Vanderpump mixed up with Big Ange.
I don't know who that is.
Big Suze from Peep Show?
No, no, no, no.
Big Ange?
Big Ange was this...
Oh, she was on Real Housewives, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
She was like the Italian one?
Which housewife?
She was like a Long Island...
you look like a surfboard. She's the British real housewife. Okay. This is
Lisa Vanderpump. Hello, Lisa. Hello, Lisa. Hello. Hello, Lisa.
Oh, and her husband, this is her husband. Her husband is cool. I forget
his name,
but he looks like this. Oh, my God.
He looks great. Is that Rod Stewart? What the hell? He looks amazing. He
looks like a honey bun, dude. His skin is exactly the same shading. That's
the... It doesn't suck that when you're that guy's age, that's pretty much the
the best you can hope for yeah. He has a pretty good life yeah. He's I mean in
terms of those surgeries to make himself look like that yeah yeah that's like
about it. That's about as good as a sixty five year old guy looks yeah yeah
you either you either have to end up. I feel like your your your options are you
either go down the like
glasses on a on a string, yeah, Albert Einstein kind of path or you can go down
the kind of Robert Pollard guided by voices path where you're the cool old
guy and you're kind of fat, but you wear a T shirt and that's kind of cool.
Or the only way you can break out of that, I feel like, is if you take
steroids. Is that is the Robert Robert Kennedy? Is that the same type? Yeah,
that's the that's the last three. There's two branching paths that go
left and right and then the Kennedy path goes up. Yeah, it's a up to heaven.
That's the scale and then there's the Z axis.
That's what I'm going to be. I'm going to be like one of those old guys who's like 4% body fat,
but still doesn't have abs and instead just has like two humps on the front of their body.
I want that shit.
I'm going straight for the Gillesse's string. I'm going straight for Benjamin Franklin.
I just can't imagine that there will ever be a day where you're like,
"All right, time to put the dime sweatshirt down and pick up the polo."
Yeah, you're on the Jerry Seinfeld path.
I was going to say it would be so funny to show up to Jeopardy wearing the exact outfit
that Jerry Seinfeld wore in that Kith ad.
And to an extent where it's like, everyone is looking at you and they're like, "Oh my
God."
That clip of Jared Leto, have you seen this one where it's like Jared Leto is sitting
at a runway, see somebody wearing this green fucking guest like suit and then
he shows up to the Suicide Squad premiere in that. That's bad. It's so clear
that I like saw Jerry Seinfeld in that Kith outfit and then I bought the exact
every single thing that he wore in that. That'd be sick man. I think copying, if
you're gonna copy, you got to go all out. Yeah. And there's a lot, I have respect
somebody's fully copying and not being like, oh I'm dressing up like this guy.
Just completely 100% stealing their outfit.
Every single, to the socks.
Maybe I'll steal your outfit.
You know whose jacket this might be?
This might be Connor's old jacket.
He saw me wearing this and was like,
"Did you buy that at like a thrift store in Manhattan?"
And I think he sold this to like a Buffalo Exchange or something.
And then you got it?
And then I bought it.
Holy crap.
It's insane.
I don't believe it though.
He was like, "Is that a Big Mac jacket?"
and I was like, "Yes, it is."
- Oh my God. - You only made one of it?
- They only made one of this jacket.
He made me take it off so that he could try it on
and see if it fit him the same way.
- That's one of the most interesting things I've ever heard.
- It's not that interesting.
- No, it is a little bit interesting.
- It is a little bit interesting,
but it's not the same thing that you were saying.
- Yeah, I was saying you need to copy somebody completely.
- 'Cause I didn't know Connor even owned this jacket.
I was saying maybe I would take your entire outfit, including the head. I mean, I already
have the headphones, but maybe I'd take the hat.
Here's what I would do if I was on Jeopardy. You know how after the first commercial break
they come over and they ask you...
You kind of look fly, right?
Yeah, you do look a little fly. You look more than a little fly, I'll be honest.
Thank you, bro.
You look very, very fly. And you know how they ask the leading questions to make you
tell some fun fact about you? They're like, "So you met your wife in an interesting way."
Yeah.
And I'd be like, "What? What do you mean?"
What? I met her at school.
No, I didn't.
What do you mean? What the fuck?
So this says here you're a big fan of the beach. I'm not. No. I like the
mountains. Who told you that?
How did you get this information? Are you the feds?
Bro, keep it under wraps, dog. Don't tell it. I told you not to. I told you
to keep that in confidence. Okay, so I basically signed a fucking form. I
think the funniest thing to me you can do on any TV show is someone asks you
a question and you say, "What?" I think the funniest thing you can do is they
I ask you, you blow up. You explode. You explode at them, get really mad. Your meat flies all
over Alex Trebek's body the second he says anything to you because you're so nervous.
Did you know in the early 80s, when Jeopardy! first started, he was getting invited to BET
awards, not the BET awards, or no, the NAACP was trying to give him an award because they
thought he was a black guy. If you hold in a fart your entire life, will you explode?
You're trying to divert the...
No, sorry.
I was just doing something separate.
Well, you won't poop then.
Yeah.
Well, no.
Well, yeah.
Okay, you don't poop and you don't fart.
Will you explode?
There is a mancer.
Your digestive system...
That's what I'm asking you.
You have a lot of impacted poop.
Yeah.
So, I don't know.
Yeah, maybe you're...
I guess you're...
Probably your intestine might burst.
Have you seen the videos where they drain the cow of the air?
Yes.
We talked about this.
The excess methane.
I learned about this from you because you showed me the video of the...
make the fire. Yeah, the methane thing. No, no, you know what it was? The porthole on the
cow. Oh yeah, that's different. I almost cried thinking about that happening to me. But sometimes
they stab a hole in the cow and they let out all the air, or the methane. And it looks
like it would feel maybe good to put your face in front of it. No, because that would
be like putting your, that would be like holding down a lighter and just doing that. No, not
not the fire. You would not like yeah,
well, no, because it would be at really fast velocity. It would feel like
getting a blow out. No, I don't think you know what getting a blow out feels
like. I probably you will soon. You think I'm going to grow my hair, go get
a blow out,
look like Travis Drit. You got
I think it'd be bad. Grow your hair out
least. All right, looking like Travis Tritt. You grow a little goatee. Oh wait, I
got to pull up. You got to see what he looks like. What's he from? He's from
country music. Oh, I thought he, who's the guy from that other thing? The flock of
seagulls. Oh my god, yes, I want to look like that. Put it to the GoPro. Scott
Stapp, you're thinking. There's a really, really, just show the camera. He looks
beautifully. Here it is. He looks good. Caleb looking like this. Show it without the hat though, because you were showing pictures of his hair.
hair. I think that'd be bad ass dude. Yeah. See that's the kind of hair I'm going to.
I want to go for giant like a gemstone dude. Giant fucking forehead. Some kind of a affliction
t shirt and some long balding hair. I think this would be a really good look for me. I
think my haircut will look like that soon. This is what Caleb could look like in a year.
I think that I will. We gotta fly you to Turkey. I will look like that in a year. You can't
grow that shit out. We got to fly you to Turkey.
I'll grow it. If I was focused, I could.
Yeah. All right. Let's see it.
I'll goatee.
I'll grow it out right now.
Let's see. Let's see you get a goatee.
I'm trying to grow it.
You need to look like this, dude.
You're right. I have no other option in my life than to go down this path now.
He looks good, man.
You would look good with flip flops.
No, I'm just a bit. You would look, you would go crazy with this, dude.
Go crazy on the...
You look like the button down the affliction button down with that too.
Oh my God.
I love this new.
Pinstripe everything.
I love this new leaf we're turning.
Some of these jeans with the pinstripes on the back.
You're going to get.
Pinstripe cross on the front of my jeans.
Noah's going to take you to the truey store.
I need that shit.
Oh my God.
And I'm not going to sag it dude.
That's disrespectful.
How come different brands of clothing get their own store?
For marketing purposes.
That's a very good point.
It's just not.
There's a lot of type of stores.
We need to open the Potabat List Outlet Mall.
Yes, oh my God, I've been thinking about this for I want to I want to own a
zoomies yeah zoomies. We could have a puma outlet. Yes,
Adidas,
we put them right across from each other right because the history, yes, they
have and we would also our Adidas would say all dre, all dre, I dream,
all day I dream about sex, all day, all dre, I dream and then inside one of
the stores there will be an auntie and and then inside the auntie ends, there
would be a cold stone creamery. Yeah wow and also we would do an on the ends
mixture, cold stone creamery and auntie ends where they chop up a pretzel and
mix it with a bunch of cheese
and I was thinking okay. I actually got hot dogs on pretzels yeah that sounded
so good to me. They chop it into a disgusting goo and they put it in a cup.
I was and I say I gotta have it. They sell that I was thinking that auntie
ends
like the pretzel cut up and then put into like a
like a caramel ice cream.
- Oh, that sounds good as fuck, actually.
- A pretzel on ice cream is--
- Salted caramel ice cream with pretzels.
- All right, well, we know that you're gonna become a chef.
- All right, well, so to end this episode,
we have an exciting bonus feature,
that an outtake from the last regular episode.
So today we did the six fingers of music on YouTube.
Today we're gonna do the seventh finger,
the forbidden seventh finger,
and Caleb is about to rap over the seventh finger of music.
- I'm gonna rap, oh shit.
- So are you ready, Caleb?
Here's the 7th finger.
And I have a show to announce.
Yeah, oh man, back in the fuckin', back in the studio, over the finger.
I'm a fuckin' rapper, not a singer.
Chillin' with my homies, watchin' T-
Watchin' T- sorry, I'm tryin' to catch the beat.
I'm back in the studio, back with the finger.
Yeah, I fuckin' rap, but I'm not a fuckin' singer.
Patrick and Cam, I'm back with the mans.
We back with the hands, throw hands, throw bands.
Throw my man, throw my...
Pop my gun, AK-47 for fun.
AR-15 with the silencer on it.
Got a bunch of motherfucking rhymes that are on it.
And this, man, this finger...
- Let the beat breathe, man.
- This finger is fucking hard, dude.
- They're gonna do this one on Swayze.
- This is a really hard finger.
Alright, I give up on this finger.
I give up on this finger.
I can't do this finger, man.
I do have a show to promote.
Next month, November 17th, me and my buddy Gus Viveiros, guys, we are doing
two half hours, that makes one hour, of comedy, stand-up style at the Yard
Theater. I don't have a link for the tickets. In Los Angeles. But I will soon.
In sunny Los Angeles. Oh, and also I'm still opening for Girl God in Chicago,
and then I got a bunch of shows in New York, too. No, you don't. All right. Bye,
Bye friends. Bye. And I'm going to show Cameron my wiener.
At the library. Okay, your turn. I'm at the library.
I've taken out six books at a time. I'm at the library.
I'm doing more of a hook at this time. I think I did more. You were,
I was saying doing more of the hooks at this time.
But this might help.
Reading is not a crime.
I do it all the time.
Whoa.
I'm reading books about limes.
Damn.
Lime scooter.
Hit her in the cooter.
Hit her?
Wait, drop a gunshot.
Hit her in her cooter.
With a lime scooter?
With a lime scooter.
Lime scooter directly to the cooter.
Doing some evil kenevil shit into a woman's thing.
I'm evil.
This is a good way to learn about your instincts.
My instincts.
Store hurting women's vaginas.
Hurting women's vaginas with cutting edge application based technology.
Using an application vehicle to hurt a woman or thing.
I went in a self-driving car.
Really?
Tell us about it.
I was in...
Oh yo.
I don't...
Well, I was in Phoenix basically and...
A rap is about it.
Yeah, you have to rap about it.
Yo, imagine a whir-
Well, actually turn this beat-
Uh, keep it the same actually.
I was in a car that had nobody driving in it.
I felt like a creamed spinach.
I had- I literally got exploded on with the whole vehicle exploded.
It was crazy. Phoenix fell into the earth.
And then I- and then I blow up all crazy.
I have no- I have no idea what's happening to me.
I got a lobster hot pocket.
Oh.
I met two hot two two girls with two lobster hot pockets.
That's again, the self-driving vehicle.
You got to go down and I could show you what it's like when I'm laughing at Jason.
See you.
Vehicle to see a goal is insanely good, man.
That's the type of shit that I'm expressing myself about for a second.
All right, Cameron.
Okay.
Well,
Well, I'm sitting here and I can't...
Oh, it ended.
[outro]
(Boo!)