I'm so excited to be here with my two little sugar bears. Yeah, honestly, can I
tell you something? I thought we were gonna record it too. Yeah, when I found
out we're recording at noon instead, I was like, yes, really? I get to be here
earlier. That's why I wasn't gonna die. I was honestly gonna sit on my couch for
two hours. I was maybe gonna go to the grocery store, but I wasn't gonna go to
grocery store.
No, no.
That's too much.
That's too much, man.
Going to the grocery store.
Speaking of the grocery store, I have a story to tell about, yes, two days ago I was trying
to go to the grocery store.
Hold on, Sugar Bear, you have an eyelash.
Beautiful.
I was going to the grocery store and you know that there's that tall guy on my block.
No, I don't know.
Okay, well there's this guy on my block.
He walks up and down.
I think his mom follows him.
I'm pretty sure he's got schizophrenia,
'cause a lot of the time he's walking around
and just making like guttural sounds,
and then his mom is just like making sure
that he's not like doing anything like crazy.
- Okay.
- Not crazy, but like--
- He chills with his mom though.
- He's chilling with his mom.
- There's nothing schizophrenic about chilling with mom.
- Well, no, he's just walking up and down the street
going, "Gah, gah," like that.
- Like a bug ass on his throat, yeah.
- I've never heard him speak a word of,
like I've never heard him speak a word, right?
Okay, I've only ever seen him walking up and down the street going and then his
mom and toe behind. He's that guy from that Kendrick Lamar song. He is. He's
got got got got
until two days ago I was walking to the grocery store and it seemed like he was
in a very bad mood because he's making a lot of sounds and I passed by him on the
street. I passed by him
and then over my headphones, I hear he does like a boy. If you don't and goes,
you smell like shit at me,
I've never heard. Was his mom like, Oh my God, his first one. I don't know if
it was like, I've never heard him speak a word of English and he went, you
smell like shit and then just kept walking. My God. And I was like, Oh, no
wonder you bought new jeans. Yeah. Oh, you want me to bring up the jeans now?
He's trying so bad to get to the jeans.
But he did like a like, "You smell like shit," and then kept walking as if
nothing, he just did nothing, and I was like, "You guys should have... Yesterday,
you guys should have, like, smelled me."
Did you smell bad? No, no. I was... I went out of my way to make sure I
smelled good. Oh, because you were self conscious about what he said. I became
so self conscious.
think about it. I've never heard you speak a word. You've given this man the
power of speech. You've bestowed conscious human consciousness upon a
green line. I went into his brain, a sims thing. I went up above his head.
Tell me that I smell like you, shit like shit. He was that was a burning bush.
I was like oh my God yeah, no, I put on like I put on like after shave. I put
on like do you wear cologne? I do now. I had it. I didn't wear it as much,
but now I'm like I did like Jeremy fragrance, like full, like
spraying the shit out of myself. The only cologne that I wear is every once
in a while, I'll wear this cologne that Noah got me that's called Barack Obama,
and it's like a laser blue and it smells terrible, but I'll put it on sometimes
'cause it smells like cologne, you know?
And everything-- - Oh, it's a cologne.
- It gives me like a migraine
every time I put it on. - Yeah, I know,
I know the kind of smell you're talking about.
It's like-- - I don't fuck with cologne.
- It's the smell, you know the smell that I'm talking about?
- I don't even like underwear.
- I don't, you didn't say anything.
Like the first spray is so pungent,
but then it doesn't smell like anything.
- Yes, yeah. - And then it's just like
this lingering scent that's like on like your clothes
or whatever and you're like-- - Smells like you ate
something. - Yeah.
It smells like you ate perfume.
- It smells like you cooked something,
that's what it smells like. It smells like you made your own tea at home. It does not
smell very good. No, it smells like herbs and spices. You shouldn't be having that stuff
on your skin maybe. That's what I think. It's just a natural. Well, it has to stay there
on you. I bet you braid your armpit hair. Oh, I wish. That'd be cool. That'd be so funny
if you came in one day with a single dread. You need to become a hippie. I basically have
dreadlocks. You don't have dreadlocks. Nowhere close to dreadlocks. I might as well. Then
you will just do it. Then, if you might as well, just do it. I'm letting them go.
Yeah, I'm seeing people. People still get mad about that. Yeah, about I feel
like the window is closing on white guys with dreads. Yeah, I think I will as in
terms of them getting in trouble. Yeah, I think it kind of doesn't matter again.
I think I think I'm sure people would be. I'm sure that you would run into people
who would be like, hmm, oh, but probably in the same way where if you like, you
know, you're you're twenty and you wear bell bottom jeans or something. Yeah, so
like yeah, it's like just goofy. I want it to live in the Bahamas and have dreadlocks
so bad. I want to dreadlocks too because of corn. Should I get dreadlocks with my current
hair? Yeah, yeah, which I'm growing out by the way. You should grow out your hair and
get dreadlocks. I'm gonna get my hair cut soon. There was this kid that I knew he would
like ride BMX bikes. He was in one of my math classes, so he obviously very not a very smart
boy and I saw he like showed up on like the suggested files on Instagram and I
was like I wonder what he's up to full drug rug white kid with dreadlocks. We need more of that.
I honestly he like is dressing like a type of guy he's like fully Roz Trent and
it's like I have not seen that type of guy in years and it made me so happy to
know that he's still out there putting on for white dudes.
I saw a white guy with dreadlocks on TV that was very funny that me and me and on Pluto.
So I discovered this yesterday.
Me and Leo are watching Pluto TV and I have a Pluto TV channel that is a lot.
It's live bullfighting live broadcasted and I thought it was the same thing with Pluto
where they someday it's not always why it's just all the recycled stuff.
But they like the announcer was like you are what like you're watching the what this whatever
for both fighting turn in for the people at home watching on Pluto TV, like
stick around like it was like fully live and there was one camera operator who
was really bad like it would be like the camera like you know how the bull runs
out and the guy is like on it, you know, and it goes very fast yeah and it
starts at the gate and it runs out in the middle and the camera was just like
sitting at the pointing at the gate and the bull just immediately runs out with
the guy and it just runs out of frame and the camera just sits there on the
gate and then you can see that the camera got picked up and turned really
past, like someone with Julio, like someone was like like someone's like oh
fuck and like quickly turned it to follow her like who's that camera operator and
then from another angle we looked to see like who's filming from that area. It
was a really old white guy with
with white dress. Was this bull fighting? Was this bull fighting taking place in
America? Was this an American both? Oh really yeah, it was well. They had one
that was fighting or riding. There was both okay, oh they and they also had
barrel racing, which we did not. Also, one of the announcers was a
rodeo clown type guy who was just there's also nobody in the audience.
Yeah, so sparse. Nobody cares about this event. I would be there. I know
I think it was a kind of York, but no one no one no one cared about it.
The announcer is this rodeo clown guy who's got the clown makeup on, but
he's not dressed like a clown. Other than that, he just has clown makeup.
Yeah, and he's what he has just like a like a Bluetooth headset type mic and
he's the announcer. So he's just walking around and trying to kill time where
like get wrangling the bowls and he just being like everybody clap along to the
song and you can just like see him. He's walking around and then, when the
bowl comes out, he climbs into a barrel and he's walking around like a Mario
enemy or his head is poking out of the top of the barrel and his feet are out
of the bottom, and if the bowl comes near him, he goes inside the barrel like
a turtle. Whoa, it's
barrel barrel beats bull like rock, paper, scissors, apparently yeah, he
seemed completely fine. Oh my God, just walking around in the bear. It's so
really funny, though, because you see him just talking and be like, well, the
next person we have going up and he's like just walking, waddling a barrel.
We should do an episode in a bullpen, yeah, where we are trying to avoid
getting to be it. I also look thought that I could by looking at at least the
bull fighting. I could do that. Yeah, I mean, I don't think I mean, you always
think all you do is well, it's just a man. It's like a thing that all men
think that they can do all men. All men can do watch this, because what they do
is they just stand there and they go like this is the bull. They wave their
arms and then the ball runs at them and then they step to the side and the ball
runs by yeah. Bulls can only run straight yeah. I've learned this from
that's all it is. They jump out of the way and then it's always like they get
they have like a time limit. They have to do it for and it's like half they're
doing like all these like dodges or whatever and then the other half that
is go stand on the other side and the bull doesn't run at them or anything.
Yeah, the bull is not that interested in fighting because they scored on points.
So it's all just about like if you want to get style, you just have to do cool
stuff. I did like a jumped and did a flip over a bowl and stuff. Oh, you and
definitely get him. Yeah, I would not you get him. I'd be a great clown. You
will be a good clown. I'd be good at the barrel. I'd be good at the barrel.
You could be the barrel guy. You should all be the barrel guys. Three barrel
guys. We walk out. Oh, you know what we do? One barrel comes out. Patrick's
head pops out. Oh, there's the guy in the barrel. Wait, there's another head.
Wait, there's a third head. Three guys in one barrel. We're in like a whiskey
cask. Not even that big of a barrel. We're really stuck. Yeah, they're gonna
have to dismantle the barrel to get us out. Yeah. Was there like, is it like
pro wrestling where people have different kind of different attributes. So the the
bull fighting, it was like yeah. They all had like themed outfits kind of
they were all dressed in these crazy outfits that were like partly cowboy,
like with the cowboy hat and the fringe, but then also looked a little bit like a
NASCAR outfit where they had like the branding and the monster energy and the
Arctic Fox and whatever, but then also they had clown elements as well. I was
going to say they were wearing like truly insane outfits that I've never
seen and they all yeah. One of them was named. Oh fuck. What was his name
Sasquatch there's a guy named Sasquatch. Is there any of them that actually try
to hurt the bull?
Not that I well, it's a disqualification. Why though that's
it's not animal. It's human cruelty creatures. The bull is trying to kill
the guy. Yeah, you can fight back. Look, why he could not be in the I have no
I'd have no
sympathy for the bowl. The bowl is charging straight ahead at a clown. It
is so funny to me. We're talking about this to her watching it that they they
engineer these animals lives where these the bulls are living such an evil,
terrible, horrific, miserable life here, how that that they've engineered it so
that when a bull, the bull is standing in a like a metal gated room and they
open the gate instantly. The thing that the bowl instantly knows it needs to do
is it needs to run out in a straight line and kill the first
because they don't like do anything like it's just in there. They open the door
and it runs out and tries to kill. I had an amazing like thirteen year old
fought the other day where I was thinking I was like and I
this really I blew my own mind and I was like you know what dude as you as the
quality of life for humans in the world has gone way up. The quality of life for
animals has plummeted. Yeah, that is so there's more so fighting animals used to
walk around and just chill. I think my my thirteen year old thought that I think
literally probably four times a week and I blow my mind with it every single time
is that, can you believe that humans are animals and they built cities and cities are like
big ant hills.
Wow.
You look at your phone and it's just like I shouldn't have that.
Yeah.
This shouldn't exist.
It's just crazy to me that we, that we're animals that did all this crap.
And I'm looking on my phone and I'm looking up how did this phone get made.
Uh huh.
And I'm like who the fuck, like a hundred years ago, you know, not to get all, most
of the 13 year old thought in my brain is like oh my god you show like a person from the
in the 1800s, one picture on an iPhone, they're going to fucking kill themselves.
I want to live in Mesopotamia. Yeah, so bad. Me too. I want ancient technology.
I don't like this new technology. You want like Dunmer? I want a piece of rock
with blue lines that move through it. Yeah. Blue glow lines. Legend of Zelda,
the Breath of the Wild. I want that kind of thing. I want the Dwemer stuff. I
want like the stuff from Skyrim that like you go in the caves and then it's
all like this gold plated like guys on the little ball. I want no technology
at all. I would like to live in the world of weathering heights. My wife made fun
of me because she said if you could go back in time and to any time what and
see like anything in the past, what would you say? She said dinosaurs. I said I
went to see the the hanging gardens of Babylon.
Yeah, she's funny for that. She said I was gay.
My own wife said I was
I wanted to see the hanging gardens of
they're stupid man. They're bad ass gardens. It's probably hang or wonders
than yeah. I did, but you don't know because you've never seen it man. I
would want to see Colossus. You would feel so disappointed you would get
there and you'll be like that's a fucking tree. Wow wow and then your
your way to get back after seeing a million
yeah
not
bone might as well be an alien like the most she's got like new cavemen friends,
they had different flowers that we've never had. They had even more
different flowers back in dinosaur times, bro. I don't want to go to
dinosaur time. I don't want to be mosquitoes. What if you go to the
hanging gardens or whatever and they got different flowers back then and you
have the like worst allergic reaction to the you also you would you would not
know you would not be looking at these flowers and be you would you would look
at a flower and you'd be like oh my God, this is an ancient flower. They don't
have any more and they'll be like yeah, that's called a tulip. Yeah, no, you
I know flowers, you know, I used to be a gardener shut up. You were not a car.
I was I had a container garden on my dad's back deck. Oh my God, you guys are
so fucking stupid. I had a container garden with over thirty different
flowers on my dad's back deck and me. Oh my God, name all the flowers name all
of them names thirty flowers right now. I want to hear you name thirty flowers
a rose
keep going a tulip. Okay,
that was you can't tell a naming of our said it. I just said Lily
a these are all women's. These are the flowers you had a dumb dumb. That's a
yeah. Okay, that's a pop a
what sucker, but the sucker yeah, no it's not a pop. That's a sucker man.
The say what are they called? It's a sucker. What are those perennials that
are always that you can get an eal perennial is a not a kind of flower.
it's not a kind of flower. It's a name. What are they called? They're the ones
that you can plant anywhere and they live forever. Fern no, not a fern ferns,
not a flower for here's one. Here's one. I'll blow your fucking mind
chrysanthemum hydrangea chrysanthemum. Okay, hydrangea hibiscus.
These are the kinds of flowers. I was rocking with. You had all these flowers
in a container. A container garden means that you have pots instead of instead of
row. You had all these yeah, you had roses. I had roses. I had two rose
rosemary and they would hurt me rosemary, not a flower. That's an herb.
We had no food, no herb, anything bad idea, putting just flowers out there.
You should always just put herbs out. Oh, this guy hates beauty. No, I like
food crocus. I like crocus. Those are good flowers. I never seen a crocus.
You've never seen a crocus. You've seen a crocus. I've never seen one. You've
seen it. You have definitely seen a crocus. Azaleas are good too. We had
azaleas. Well, azaleas are actually bad because they only bloom for two weeks
out of the year. Well, they're good. And then it's like the ugliest fucking
thing ever. We had hydrangeas and crocus. Well, crocuses, you don't really grow.
they just they pop up. I think my mom would have that's a we just on the
porch. Yeah, those are the ones that come up during spring. They're a little
tiny purple. It was one flower that irises irises. I used to propagate man.
Yeah, that's how hard that's how heavy into this shit. I was. I used to
propagate things when I was like you're not really helping your case really of
being lame or gay or anything like that. I think he proved that he knows bad
ass, man. Flowers? That shit is badass to own flowers and cultivate them.
When I was like six years old, I didn't, I mean, I still to this day couldn't point out
the different types of poisonous plants.
Me neither. I don't understand.
I tried to make homemade camouflage as you do as a child.
Ghillie.
I tried to make a ghillie suit. I tried to make a ghillie suit by stuffing plants and
stuff into my shirt.
Inside your shirt?
I was doing this, I was like putting like, like, like plants in my pants and then my
shirt so it would stick out because I thought that it would hide me.
So I was putting like plants up my back and stuff and it turns out like half of them were
poison ivy and for...
You made a poison, you made some, you made a...
A poison ivy...
A green maiden.
Yeah, I don't know what that is but...
Like an iron maiden?
Oh, but with, okay, yeah, then I did that.
I did that and I got to stay home from school for two days, but it was the
itchiest two days of my life.
I was covered in fucking...
We had like this expired calamine lotion.
It was just like this pink fucking goop that I was pouring all over my body.
I was more pink than anything.
Pink slime, man.
I was a pink...
I looked like Mr. Bubble.
You looked like Patrick Star probably.
Bubble gum, man.
I don't think I ever got poison ivied.
I got poison ivied a couple times.
Are you one of those guys that aren't allergic to it?
Maybe.
I probably have gotten it and not realized.
I don't know.
I realized me. Yeah,
well, I don't know. I don't think I've ever gotten it, but it seems I mean
it's not like I'm going to you've gotten it. It was so bad that you deleted
the memory from your head. It was so painful. That's not true. It's
completely true. It's what I would know if I gotten it. I wouldn't be able
to. I wouldn't it's not conceivable that maybe I got a rash or something
and thought it was a random rash. Yeah,
that's a good point. I think you would know it's
raises up on your white body and it hurts so bad.
Yeah, you get little pustules.
I thought it was just itches.
You get little pustules that you can pop.
Yeah, it gets disgusting.
My mom told me that if you pop them, then that can spread and just make the itch worse.
Yeah, I always heard the story of my great whatever, you know, someone you hear, always
hear the story someone burns it to get rid of it and this oil and the smoke goes under
their lungs.
Yeah.
You probably heard that story.
No, what happens?
Well, I don't know if it's true or not.
I feel like maybe it's one of those things.
It's a wives tale.
Yeah, but like you, the story of, I was always told that someone in my family, some great
grandma or aunt or something, burned a bunch of poison ivy on her property to get rid of
it and the smoke, the oils on it, the irritating oils go into the smoke and you breathe it
in and you get it inside your body.
Yeah, that shit's the worst.
But I don't know if that's true or not.
Do you guys have skunks in the northeast?
Yeah, my uncle got sprayed by, he had this Australian shepherd that like tried to bite
a skunk and it sprayed him immediately.
They're so stupid.
is the worst smell because I can smell it in my house.
That's scary week. Nope. One time ago. I haven't seen a skunk in a long time.
I've skunk walked right in front of them though. If they didn't spray their
stink everywhere, I think they would be amazing pets. I like their coloration.
Yeah, yeah. The stripe, the stripe is cool. The stripe is cool. I do love
the skunk. It is a good is God's perfect. Have anyone domesticated?
Yeah, I've seen
It's it's illegal to take their gland out. Yeah, because you they need that.
It's like that to to make it's like a cat like it's very immoral, but in the
UK, I think you can look at these animals land to them. I mean, dude, you
can do whatever the hell you're a cuter one in Russia. This picture looks
fucked up, man. I mean, we've talked about it every which way, but you know
you can just own a caracal cat in Russia. Oh, look at the one with the
the bow. Click that one. Click the one with the bow on it. I always love when
they put a bow on a female skunk. Wow! You always love when they put a bow on
a female skunk. It's the stinkiest creature in the world, and then they've
made it look cute. This is a free Twitter profile picture to somebody who's
really annoying. To some very annoying woman. That's a freebie for you. Why has
it got to be an... Also, how do you know that's a female? What, because they
wear... You're wearing female jeans today. Well, it could be a bow tie.
but that could be a bow tie and the sky doesn't know where to wear it.
Show the jeans. Show the jeans. Show them.
Okay, now stand up on the chair. Okay.
They're just a little bit thin, like skinnier than the jeans I normally wear.
They're really blue, man. Yeah.
What's wrong with where I was? I was saying, as I look into these and I'm
start to get like nitrogen narcosis, I feel like I'm getting raptured of the
deep. I'm getting drawn down into the depths of the ocean.
It's just my scuba tank has run out of oxygen.
I'm looking taper a little bit.
I'm looking down.
The only thing that's wrong with I'm looking down at the sea floor.
I think I'm looking up at the at the surface and I'm swimming down down.
I'm seeing a ring of glowing lights.
They stretch, too.
I bet there's a colony of of James Cameron aliens living inside those pants.
Went all the way up his pants, pinching and I felt nothing.
I just got to say that.
I just feel like I have to say that I felt absolutely nothing in his nose.
These are pants that a human sized doll would wear. I'm looking at these are
these are doll panties. That's what's disturbing about it. There's so
it's this seam right here. Yeah, this is the doll seam. It's the Carhartt
whips. WIPs. Oh, they're Carhartt. Oh, I take every then they're actually
badass. I do. I do like them. They're just so they I've never seen that much
today. Shade of blue on you before. Yeah, you guys are just you guys are just
it's like when a father shaves his beard. Yeah, you know, I'm not wearing some
like I'm not wearing some ratty old jeans. I bought new jeans and you guys
are freaking
I don't know why we're yeah, they're pretty normal. Oh my God, they are
really causing reaction. Okay, hold your arms up over your head. Look at this.
He's got the ocean down here, then he's got the forest up here and there's the
beautiful white clouds. Oh my God, and the orange sun. Yeah, wait, you're
dress like the earth. You are dressed like my shoes and my shoes are great.
My shoes are gray like rock station really bedrock that total. Those are
my craft bedrock shoes under the ocean. Wait, they actually look exactly like
bedrock. Yeah, I like your earth fit man.
I am in the world. You should fit. I like your earth fit. You should dress up
like more planets. Speaking of the I'll do that. Maybe all of next week
months of I want to see Jupiter. How many episodes wait? How many episodes do
we have?
How do I how do we there's there's many episodes of yeah? How many episodes do
we have in a month? Typically is what I mean well, eight or eight in a month
years, nine planets yeah well, unless you don't count Pluto. If you don't
count Pluto, there's eight eight. We could definitely I think also well,
also you could do planets. You knocked earth out already, so you can do the
mouth of planets yeah. They can do this without earth the month of, but I want
see the sun to I'm not going to yeah. I would like to also see the sun and the
moon. I would really get a bonus, a bonus. You know, like those people,
those people that do like is like outfits inspired by
character. Next month, can we do the month of planets where each of us we're
all doing it and dresses Patrick? We all come in
that's not we all have to be like every week we come as the same plan. Yeah,
we can do that. We could do that yeah. I think that right now this is kind of
perfect earth outfit yeah
for I guess I have earth colors. I've got green and blue and I've got green
and blue on my shoes too. I could do really blue that's more green and you
are green. Mars might be too easy, but we got to do them all. Mars is easy.
What what planets are there? Mars and Neptune? These are these are easy.
These are these are my very eager Mars, Mercury, Venus, Earth,
butters Mars, Martyrs Jupiter, Saturn, Neptune, Pluto Neptune, Uranus Uranus
Uranus, Uranus, Pluto Neptune, Uranus before Neptune, then Pluto, us nine
yeah
okay, we can do that and then the sun as a bonus week and Mercury,
okay, Mercury, I will be the regular good about Mercury and then the moon
will be the bonus episode for that. We yeah, so we'll do five weeks of planets
of planets. Okay, Mercury, the five weeks, let's say what we know about
planets. The five weeks of November is five weeks of planets. Well, we can
start planning our so Merk, we'll start with Mercury. We can plan it. We can
plan it. We can plan the month. Yeah, this is such a good idea. The
ideas for episodes of what to do for the episodes. They could be different that
we could just do a whole every episode is about the planets that we're dressed
up as yeah and we talk as the pie. We say I have a toxic atmosphere. I can I
would pull up my third grade. I did a project on Mercury. That's huge. What
did you spit about Mercury? What do you know? What do you use the rotation
around the sun one year in Mercury, the revolution, the one one year for
Mercury, eighty eight days really yeah. Well, so how old was you be on Mercury
to the sun closest one of the sun? I don't know how old I would be on
Mercury. It's hot as fuck. I can't do the math. I'm not going to lie. Basically,
scientists call Mercury the sun's moon.
No, they don't. That's not true.
Why would a scientist say something so stupid? Scientists have been calling
Mercury, like, the sun's moon. Is that what you... What was your go to science
fair project when you were a kid? I didn't have the science fair. Yeah, I
don't think I had a science fair either. Or like, you had to make a diorama or
Oh, we I'm going to die around about walruses, the diorama that we had to
beavers to why are you being so different? Yes, that's what I'm asking.
Yes, that's what I want. I want to know what walruses and beavers, whatever.
Okay, it's you don't have to be so mean about it. We did a we did a thing
called
we did a thing called bottle guys,
which if you remember bottle guys, you remember bottle guy dot com. I remember
well, bodily you took a
You took a two liter bottle and then a little like styrofoam ball or whatever and then you'd
have to do like a history project on them.
They would put them out in the hallway.
And I did mine on Lou Gehrig.
Oh, very cool.
Did you guys follow the I did a rod?
Yes.
My guy did not win.
What the hell that is?
Mine neither.
The sled race, the dog sled race.
It's what the movie Snow Dogs is about.
Africa. Yeah, my something's wrong with me. Snowy Africa, snowy Africa. There's
some parts of Africa that are snowy where the middle of the mountains.
Yeah, probably the south part. Did you guys do an egg drop challenge? No, I
drop an egg into the pan and fry it every morning. Not a challenge. It was a
challenge for me. I wasn't very good at it in third grade. I did the sun drop
challenge. Mm-Hmm. Where drink two bottles of sun drop to two bottles of
sun drop. You gets real sick. Yeah, it wasn't really nobody ever won that
Where is, have you seen Sundrop Re, is that a discontinued?
I don't know what that is.
You posted something last night.
Oh yeah.
I've not stopped thinking about which is.
The cacti hard seltzer.
What happened to the cacti hard seltzer?
That got discontinued after Astroworld.
Oh really?
Yeah, but that was a good.
They thought it was the alcohol?
That was a good hard seltzer.
It was really good.
It was really, really good.
It was seven, they, it's like the bodega
next to my apartment pulled it out
from the damn archives or something.
It was sitting in the.
A vintage.
It was a vintage. Yeah. Here we have a cacti. They didn't even know what they were sitting
on. I kind of wanted to go like ask them. Did you buy it? Yeah, of course I did. Did
you sip it? I had to clean it first. I had to clean that bottle. And then you drank it?
There was some mold on it, but I scrubbed it all off. Did it hit? Dude, it hit just
as good. I remember that summer in 2021 where I was just like, you know, drinking every
single like partying. Cacti time. I was partying all the time. You were on cacti time. I was
on cat time bro. You remember that? It was like, oh, like I had like a college hibernation
and I was like 23 years old partying like it was college all the time.
Well you get, if you were sober for a little bit.
That's true.
And then when you're not sober after that.
I was sober for six months.
And then you're like, I gotta make up for lost time.
Yeah. I was so boring when I was sober too. It was so fucking crazy.
Yeah, I hate to say it man.
Yeah.
Yeah, you were boring.
You weren't around. You were still in Boston.
I didn't like it. Your head was two sizes smaller than it is right now. Yeah,
I was sober too and I was longer than him. You were sober for longer, but you
getting, you getting sober is kind of just like, oh, it's longer though. So
no, like you getting sober, kind of like what is longer? So I don't know why
we're not talking about me. We can talk about you. Yeah, we can talk about you,
I guess. What do you want to say? What do you want to say? Well, we'll say
anything you want about. Okay, well, let's start talking. When you were
sober, I played a lot of fortnight. You played a lot of fortnight. How do you
pretty much. How could you possibly play fortnight not on drugs or alcohol?
I'd managed that's impressive. I don't know when you were sober. It was like
everyone kind of respected it. When I was sober, it was kind of like everyone was
waiting to like had another beer. Yeah, it felt like the doomsday clock was at
like it was almost like midnight. Like it was almost like we would go out and I
would like we would go to that bar and I would get like a fucking orange soda or
something and then
would like almost buy me a beer every time. It's funny when people are
straight edge or they used to be alcoholics or something. It's so funny
to buy them a beer and be like, Oh, you don't want it. All right, it is mine. I
think I did that. Yeah, I did that to brace after you got to do it every time.
Do you have to shot? You got to at least you have to test their you have to test
their gang right? It's willpower. Yeah, if you're really good about it for six
months, it doesn't mean you will if you don't have the willpower to stay
a straight edge in the face of a friend exactly offering you alcohol, then you
don't deserve to wear the badge. I honor that is straight edge. I one hundred
percent agree. You should be every single person in your life is like an A
or whatever you should be like asking for their chip should be tricking them.
You should literally be trying to trick them water. Yeah, I know it's a normal
seltzer and then if you can't if you can't smell it before you take a sip,
you should be yeah exactly. If you don't have the diligence to check for the
poison that is ruining your life and every single your touch, your touch
should remove alcohol from liquids. You should be making a cup, a liquid in the
cup disappear. It's it's it becomes yeah yeah, and if they don't break on the
seltzer trick, you should be inviting them over and making alcoholic beef stew
and trying to
bring it in a hard
I'm saying and they're two by ten. It's delicious. I'm like
fifteen percent
so you like it. I fucking knew it yeah. They're like alcohol poisoning. Yeah,
fuck up is so funny. God damn they don't make edibles for beer. It was
sitting with your your homies and watching watching a sports game,
evaluating beef. Still yeah, so
spilling it everywhere, causing with those shallow bowls, six bowls of
stewage
dying to getting up to go to the kitchen, like a way to
you are in the kitchen just looks like so a diary
you're trying to fucking pick up the ladle and like get it into your the
ladle gets dropped into the still. All the potatoes have this like weird like
foam over the imagine how amazing
hitting the beef bong. Oh my God, how amazing is that? That would be the
greatest Super Bowl party of all time.
Alcoholic beef stew.
Oh, where's the beer?
No, the best would be chili.
No beer, but you gotta try this.
We don't need beer today.
We don't need beer, man.
We invented a beef stew with alcohol in it.
Get some crackers, dude.
Get some crackers, dive right in.
Oh, that's so good.
You made it out of crackers.
I wanna do...
You put any little oyster crackers in it.
I wanna do a new...
I wanna do a new bachelor party.
I wanna redo a bachelor party
party where there's no drinking alcohol and only edible alcohol, only
alcoholic beef stew, only jello shots. Yes, I will pull up with a crock pot
full of alcoholic beef stew. You know, I will know you know, you're clear
green alcohol and it will get you so I'm not going to do any math about it
now, like coming to work and you're like you're wearing the sunglasses.
You're clearly so hung over and they're like oh you go to the bar last night.
You're like no, no,
I went to the crazy, the craziest out of my life. It's a bunch of alcoholic
beefs. Oh, there's something so funny about getting getting the drunkest
you've ever been in your life and having to apologize and explain to people that
yeah, so it was I
texted you last night. Yeah, I was off the alcoholic. Yeah, Oh, what's the
crock pot? Is that a new bar
the four AM text for you, WID
eight hours later. Sorry, bro. I had alcoholic
this the most insane excuse. Yeah, you're making it up. You're panicking.
Yeah, it's like when you try to yeah, you lie to your boss to tell them
you're sick to get a day off and you make up too many details. Yeah, yeah,
my friend invented alcoholic be stew and I had a bunch of me and tell anyone
that it was spiked.
He spiked the piece.
I would eat that man. I was really getting excited. You were saying
There's no alcoholic edibles.
That's what jello shots are.
Well, yeah, but, well, okay.
So the, so the way, what I'm thinking is how you could make this alcoholic beef
stew is that it's not like, so like, you know, when they have like the,
the stock gelatin, you know?
Yeah.
So what you would do, right.
Is you like, I dunno, I guess like reduce, uh, some kind of like beef bone or like
beef broth or whatever with maybe ever clear, or I was thinking Guinness just so
would have that creaminess to it.
- Well, but then that's not gonna be high enough ABV.
- No, exactly.
So it's gotta be like something that's a very, very high ABV.
Maybe like a grainy or nephew.
- You just gotta season it enough that you can't taste it.
- Oh, mellow corn would work.
- Mellow corn would work really well.
Some kind of clear whiskey.
- Marinate the beef and yeah, and some.
- The marinade would work okay.
'Cause people marinate stuff in beer all the time.
But the thing is you would have to,
it would be really, it kind of sucks,
but you would have to make the beef stew and then in the last ten minutes you
have to pour a gallon of alcohol. Alcohol cooks off so easily yeah, so it would
yes, it have to be it would just have to be as just you have to taste like
you have to put yeah yeah, I mean very bad yeah, which is fine. You're not
you're yeah. You like the taste of alcohol eating for effect. Exactly
right in to get I'm eating to get drunk man. I'm not eating. I'm not getting
someone some fruity flavored
beef to to get fucked up eating like a bowl. You're sitting at home with a
bowl of beef stew and then dropping a shot of whiskey in it like it's a
boiler maker. Yeah,
I think this is a good idea. This is a really good idea. I think yet again is
an incredible another amazing. I was so many good food ideas on this podcast
that it's a shame that Babish does not listen. I think that we I actually think
but now I'm thinking that we should fully make this alcohol. We should make
alcoholic beef stew next month for a Thanksgiving episode. Yes, I'm so
fucking
I'm so fucking
we got to consult the we can just pour alcohol into the beach. I don't know. I
wonder if we consult the chef. We want to see what you want to come up. We need
a chef to come on the show. This is going to happen. This is coming. I made
I
that's actually a good idea. That is not a bad idea, but I need to get I need to
there. I fucked up off some beef stew. Yeah, fucked off beef. I'm going to get
fucked off some beef stew, man. Okay, wait. So let's think about all the
recipes we've created over the years, right? So we have now alcoholic beef stew
is the number one, the hot, the hot burger, right? The hot burger, Chinese
style euro.
I do remember that. I don't know. That was the you weren't on that episode.
That was on the moneymaker symposium. It's a, you know, like a Szechuan euro,
but what is what's the bread? What's the meat? I'm not gonna okay. The bread is a
scallion pancake and then oh my God, it's amazing. It's a really, really good.
Great idea and it's like char siu pork. Oh, what's any sauce? No, I think I don't
know, but which is you'd have to make like a Chinese style. Siddiqui. You know
what I like? Yum yum sauce. I love you. Could be a sauce. They don't have it at
my grocery store. Maybe they sell it at the grocery store. Yeah, I mean, you can
just may I make it, but I thought that was only a restaurant sauce. No, you
can buy it. You can buy it at some place. Yum yum sauce. Yeah. Holy. How
do you think the restaurants get it? Man? Isn't just man? Why are you
counting? I'm trying to remember other recipes. He's counting the three.
These are the top three right now. So it's the alcoholic beef stew. Yeah.
Hot burger.
Chinese style euro. I don't think we create that many recipes to be
honest. We create a good amount. Maybe you do. Yeah. I think my first ever
was yeah, I don't have ever thought of an idea for a recipe. You've thought of
recipes on here. Like what? Name one. I'm trying to remember. I think, I think,
with the exception of alcoholic beef stew, I think I'm the only chef on the
show. You know what I always thought would be a good idea?
'Cause people always like to eat either a pancake or a waffle. A poffle. How
about a pancake and then a waffle and then a pancake on top? Pan- waffle
sandwich with pancake bread. Yes. That's a pretty decent idea. That's not so
bad an idea, but I was missing some French toast and a French toast. I meant
you have to say and a French toast spread. If you are one of these guys that
makes spreadsheets about the types of hats that we wear and the types of
drinks that we have, if you can scrub through every single episode and find
the recipe, find all of our recipes together, a cookbook. Oh my God, book is
not a bad idea. I think we actually had an idea for a cookbook a long time ago,
but I don't remember what it was. I do remember. I remember just that that being
green idea, but I think we've got very far a lot of cocktails to which is you
know that's a good book and thing like the end of the book is all cocktails
because we have had patries delight.
I'll call beef stew is probably the best transition. That is the one yeah it's
between a cocktail and a food. So that's the one that comes before the
whole new genre of type of thing called a food tale. We can put no or cock. Oh
yeah, no is cock food, cock food,
cock food, yeah, maybe we could put in a poop drink. We could put in a recipe for
the week at plate to the week. Yeah, yeah, what one half serving of turkey one half
serving with one roll with a bite out of it, yeah and and
set up the plate and then eat strudel for four hours. Wait to set him up for
another pick. I've been thinking about it. I'm such a I'm so not going to frame
him. I can't make Thanksgiving this year. I've been thinking why not it's my
nephew's birthday. So I actually I haven't seen my brother's birthday. I
I haven't seen my family in like five months. Probably I have I got to go home
for one of the holidays. Who cares about your family, man? Yeah, it's a good
point. They're going to go home for Christmas anyway. Yeah, Thanksgiving is
about friends. Thanksgiving is about the people. That's true. Thanksgiving
Thanksgiving is about the Native Americans becoming very good friends with
the pilgrims. I used to hate Thanksgiving when I lived at home and
then I moved to Boston, started doing it at my house and I was like, it's magic.
this is the best felt completely magical last year. I get to I want to tell you
guys something right now. I'm on a ham break because I'm so excited to have
some ham with everybody. I've been taking a ham break for a few weeks now.
Wow, you usually eat a lot of ham, not a lot, but I do I do eat it. I mean I
have it in sandwiches. Yeah, I really only eat it at Thanksgiving. Yeah, I'm
not eating like you know a glazed. I would like to eat a glazed ham, but it's
coming. It's coming. That's what I can't. I've been literally I'm not even
kidding and Julio can attest to this, because I think I've probably talked to
him about this a lot, but I've been thinking about ham since last
Thanksgiving. I want to know I need I need that ham ham on the on the Hawaiian
roll.
My God, I'm so jealous of you guys right now. I'm so bummed. I can't Jack was
showing me pictures of his Thanksgiving last night. Yeah, and he has the most
fucked up Thanksgiving food at his family's house. It's like yeah, they'll
of mac and cheese and he showed me that he showed me that he's the only person
who eats a single bite of it. They just make it every year and like box stuffing
and like a turkey with no nothing on it. They just put the turkey in the oven
just let it just cook for 10 hours. They're not even putting butter under the skin? You
gotta put the butter under the skin. You gotta put the butter under the skin. I'm buying...
I'm finally gonna make a turkey this year too. You're gonna miss on my first turkey.
- Oh!
- And I have a sage butter that I'm gonna be
- Fuck my life, dude. - Involving into it.
- Fuck my fucking life.
I'm missing Friendsgiving.
- And Noah might be making some cocktails,
some batch cocktails.
- I literally, I was so excited to make
like the Brussels sprouts again.
- Those are good, man.
- I know.
- You need to triple the recipe though.
- Yeah.
- We're gonna have a big Thanksgiving this year.
- I showed up with a little bit too little food.
- Yeah, you showed up with the weakest,
the weakest Friendsgiving pan.
- But the little that was there was very well cooked.
- It was very good.
And my girlfriend made those sage butter biscuits.
- Those were good as well.
- Those were so, she's fuckin', she's cracked at baking stuff.
- You got it like that.
- She do got it like that.
- I'm really--
- Do you remember, did you have those,
what was that shit she made?
Oh, I don't know if you had it,
but she made these white miso cookies
that were kinda like gingerbread cookies,
but not gingerbread cookies.
- That's a little too weird for me.
- But you think it's a little too weird,
then you take your first bite out of it,
and you're like, holy shit.
I don't even, isn't miso like a soybean, fermented soybean or something?
She fully did, she fully went off with it.
Popped.
Uh huh.
She popped the fuck off.
And we're all, and even if I do come to Friendsgiving, we're all going to miss out because she's
going home.
She's going up to, she's going upstate.
Maybe I'll have Noah make the, maybe I'll have Noah make the poop drink.
The poop drink.
Last Thanksgiving.
If I miss out on the fucking poop drink, I will kill myself.
You know what you're going to miss out on?
I will fucking kill myself.
What?
last year for Thanksgiving, I have you guys remember I made some mashed
potatoes that weren't necessary and nobody ate a single bite of something.
I might do that again. Yeah, no, I come up with mash. Did I pull up with
mashed potatoes? You come up with that? No, did I pull up with mashed potato?
What did I? I had the roasted veggies. I brought the mashed potatoes and they
were unnecessary. Then my girlfriend brought those those sage butter biscuits
and then some other things, some other pastry.
I'm on ham duty, chipotle mac and cheese, and green beans.
Mm-hmm.
That's what I make.
Maybe I'll get a pie or something.
And this year, man, I'm making a turkey.
I just told Patrick.
Can I bring something?
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Leo's going to be there.
Gordita.
Yeah, please bring some traditional--
last year, not to Thanksgiving, but last year you came
and visited and you brought--
Oh, my god.
--a bunch of Mexican candy.
Those little--
That was--
--the Nutcrunchers.
And it was so disgusting, man.
No, half of it was good.
Half of it was good, because it was caramel.
and then the rest of it was so just unruly.
Those... I'm gonna bring empanadas. Okay. I'll eat empanadas.
I'll eat some empanadas. Like a dessert. Yeah, like a...
Caramel apple kinda thing? That would be good.
You'll see. Okay. I wish I was seeing this.
Why are you not... Oh, 'cause you're gonna be in... I'm probably gonna be
in New Hampshire, yeah. But if I'm not, just say you're sick,
man. I could fake COVID. Just fake COVID. Sorry mom. Although I think that excuse is kind
of running dry. That excuse is running dry. You can kind of just, especially in my family.
Last year when I was pulling up for Christmas, or no this was two years ago, so it was when
it was very bad. My family jumped the, that excuse became very dry. Yeah, very quick.
two years ago, my dad was picking me up.
Or no, my dad was here on business and then was like,
"Oh yeah, you guys are gonna drive home for Christmas or whatever.
Yeah, I'm just worried about your younger brother's COVID."
And I was like, "What?"
She was like, "Oh yeah, your younger brother had COVID."
I was like, "Did you see him like recently?"
They were like, "Yeah, we saw him last week."
We were just around him.
I was like, "Oh, Jesus Christ."
Well this was like two years ago when it mattered.
This is like, they were telling me, they were telling me, they were telling me like you
know how freaked out I was about it for like a year?
And they were telling me that like at the tail end of me like really being scared of
it.
And I was like oh my god is he, I don't think he's vaccinated.
I thought he was going to die.
I don't know why I brought this up.
No, no it's good.
Okay the poop drink is.
It's not good.
let's talk about the food. The poop drink is as far if I remember it's basically a
Sazerac with Sherry Sherry wine, a brown wine and some kind of syrup, but it's
like a foam right well and then at the top, so it's a completely brown drink and
then at the top it's served in a like a gimlet glass toilet it's served oh yeah
it's supposed to be served in a toilet yeah it's served in a some kind of
toilet glass yeah a prank glass like a parrot drink yeah yeah and then at the
top it's a pistachio foam yeah. So it's green, so it's green at the green poop
on yeah,
I thought it was like
well, you know, like gold flake on it.
That would be a good idea. Why not just put some corn kernels? Yeah, you can
just put corn on it like a sweet corn and one of those really a couple of
really dark and hell throw some poop in there to put a couple of turds in it
throw some poop up. Who gives a fuck? It's already called a poop drink is
it in a fucking toilet. Just make it taste like shit. We talked about poop at the eating poop
at the bar for an hour the other night. It was me, Leo, Corey, and then Shreider and like a bunch of
other people. And then I got a text from Corey. You were like, are you guys still there? Yeah.
And he was like, yeah, we're all here and we're talking. We've been talking about eating poop
for one hour. I was like, okay. And then I got stuck in the conversation. I kept trying to get
get out of the conversation to when you got there, we were fully out of the
conversation and then you know I had to bring it back. It fully looped back. You
know I had to bring it back eating poop last night. I told her I just remember
this the like a month ago, Pierce made a bunch of girls leave a bar because he
was talking about a penis being mutilated. Oh really, I was talking about
it really loudly. I forgot what he was even to he's saying something about
something going up as the urethra and a bunch of girls in the outside bar area
and they all stood up and left. I think about that sometimes if you put
something too big. He was talking about something specific. I can't remember
what it was, but it was so funny. He was and you can imagine him talking about it
really loudly and it was just yeah and it was and then a bunch of people left.
Oh my God, I did it. Were you trying to get seats? No, no, these poor people just
didn't want to hear. I mean there was yeah hearing peers say about this cock
yeah in your cock banana peeled back and it looks like it looks like an elite
my mouth from a low
manner puss
manner
you remember nanner puss. No, you don't remember nanner puss. What is that
now?
Name for Denny's, I think so yeah, one of those types of nanner puss was one of
the biggest Super Bowl commercials.
Oh my God,
yeah, that's what you want to do to the meme that never was. What do they mean by
that it was a meme man. Everyone's but they're saying they're saying it's the
meme that never was and this is what I mean and it was apparently a cursed
commercial. According to the cursed commercials wiki, a little bit of a
biased source. Well, anyway, but yeah, that's a penis. Good. That could happen
to one of those. What are you guys going to go as for Halloween? I could have so
many decisions. My girlfriend was going to be Lila and I was going to be Fry.
Yeah, I was my girlfriend being Billy from Saw the Puppet. So I think maybe I
might kind of phone it in and be to the guy and saw us to cut his leg off and
just wear a shirt with blood on it and can't have a saw. But I don't yeah
because there's no other there's no identifiable characters in the soft
franchise except for the puppet. That's really it. I think this is the year
that I go all in
and I finally become a bumblebee. I was thinking of being a mouse, but I was
already a cat before you already were a cat and I was a beer last year. So this
year, this is the first year in a while. I haven't had a I haven't had an idea
about it locked in costume idea. Yeah, I could still be fry. I have the
really don't look anything like figure, but I put that I put that orange wig on
over there and I
take my money. I could put makeup over it. Make up over your mustache. It would
look so disgusting.
Like Henry Cavill, Cesar Romero and the Joker. No, I don't think that's going to
work man. You could be he had a flat mustache. Yeah, mine is pretty bushy.
Yeah, it's not going to work for you. Yeah. Maybe I will be a maybe I just go
as Dracula today. A really pretty girl. Yeah, either would be a mouse or a bug
likely. I thought you were going to be you were going to be a character from
persona.
Oh yeah, it's going to be you
me. No, his name's you. Why you me? Me? Nara Kamei from his name's camera. What
are you calling me? You know, recalling from from persona four and I found a
costume for it, but it's three hundred dollars. Oh, it's probably not going to
do that. If we wear it on the episode, we can put on the company card. I don't
think you would be that happy about subsidizing my Halloween costume. If you,
if I could see you dress like this,
does it be pretty nice to see you dressed? I think that I would, I think I
would body this outfit. You're, you're, you're, I think you can just go buy a
granny wig and then I don't think that this cost you got to, you got to, you
got to slim your legs down a little bit for this one, though. I don't think that
this costume is that hard to make it all you from persona for what are you
calling me not? No, I'm not. This is he said fat you implying you're not fat.
I would be fat you right yeah, okay, you should be fat bastard from Austin
powers, not so fat. You should be you should be actually should be teddy from
persona. Now that's an expensive ass costume. Go look that look that up show
Patrick teddy from persona and then this tell me that tell me this would not be
one was beautiful and I don't care perfect costume for Caleb.
Well, it's actually T D D. I
the human form go search human at human. No, no, no, this is already. This is a
really good one. You am you am the look of the first one. Oh my God, I would I
could do that actually. Yeah,
yeah,
all right, all right, I'm gonna do this. I'm gonna be a little boy with shocking
blue eyes and a blouse and a rose and a blonde hair. I think that actually now
I'm thinking about costume stuff, I think that one of us should be Bad Luck Brian.
It's going to be you.
Bad Luck Brian?
That would be dope.
My favorite meme, man.
Bad Luck Brian or Dramatic Chipmunk or maybe Numa Numa Guy.
That's a good idea.
I told…
Do you see, three months ago, Numa Numa 2023 dropped.
Really?
Yeah.
I haven't even heard about it.
New Numa 2?
Not even New Numa 2.
New Numa, Numa, Numa 2023 Remaster.
He just redid the original?
Just filmed himself in his original bedroom.
Gary Brausman?
Gary Brausman is doing Numa Numa 2023.
He refilmed it?
He refilmed it.
And he called it a remaster?
I think he re-recorded the song.
He re-recorded the song.
You know what I think the plan was there is that he recorded the song, his vocals, made
the video again because the original one Dragosta Dente, already a song, so he did a cover so
that he could mint it at his NFT or something.
- You can either-- - Okay.
- That's my theory. - If you are going to do
a video like that, you can either be Numa guy
or you can be Star Wars kid.
- Yeah. - Those are the two options.
You can either hate, you can run away from it
like Star Wars kid has.
Star Wars kid-- - Create a law.
- Star Wars kid, we need you back, man.
- He has a crazy real name.
- Star Wars.
Star Wars kid. - Luke Skywalker.
his name is like I think he was like a Finnish child or something. I thought he was American.
Well I think he has a crazy name for an American then. I just don't remember his name. Can
you look this up Julio? Star Wars Kid real name? Because it is honestly it sounds like
a Star Wars name. I think you should name your child Anakin. Whoa! Yeah. Whoa. Ghislaine
Raza. This is he has a Star Wars name. Oh my God and now he's doing a he see he's breaking
breaking his silence. If you make an amazing YouTube video and then twenty
years later, you have to break your silence about it and he looks like that.
Come on, man.
Come on, man. You're making a documentary about how I think I just found my
Halloween
that would actually you would you would buy that
the Star Wars kid, but I'm the Star Wars kid now. Yeah, it's Star Wars kid
alternate star. What I
mean,
I look like a face up of me.
Yeah, it really does. That
looks like when I'm doing the
face at whoa fire in the
neighborhood. No, probably
not. His his fucking glasses
look like the belt on a
cartoon character works at
the circus. This is what
look at that. This is what
really made a lawsuit
against. He made a lawsuit
against bullying him online.
Yeah, yeah, and how is it?
No, dude, it's not bullying.
I'm not saying on fact the
original. Okay, I should be
bullied now when the video came out, nobody was no and then that video was
fucking cool. It was bad ass. Yeah, that's what I'm saying. He looked dope.
It's smart of him to when he has such a
big circular head. It's actually very clever to have a small circle of facial
hair going on. That's not him.
That's not him. Wait, unrecognizable. It says unrecognizable. Is that
is this a different guy? Star Wars kid, the rise of the digital shadow.
What the fuck is this?
It's a documentary about him, man.
See, look, everyone made him look dope. They gave him real lightsabers.
I just don't understand
why this was ever a problem.
Yeah.
He was so fucking cool that people couldn't
They couldn't fathom it.
They couldn't fathom it. No.
And now he's a humongously giant guy.
Al's toy barn and shit.
He does look just like that guy.
He lived long enough to see himself become a villain.
He used to be cool, but when he complained about all that stuff, it turned him into a
male Karen.
I agree, man.
And this is what a male Karen usually looks like.
This is a male Karen physiognomy.
What you're supposed to do with bullying is you're supposed to say...
I know you are, but what am I?
Just a hard rubber in your heel.
Slap him.
Exactly, bro.
And I'm not fucking with nobody who can swing a lightsaber like that.
Straight up.
No, no.
That's proof it wasn't bullying.
Would you bully a guy with a lightsaber?
No.
Hell no.
No, you'd bully the guy like, you know...
He'll chop your legs off.
You bully a guy that is no threat to you.
Yeah. And that's a bad way to go, lightsaber.
You get chopped in half, you stay alive.
If I was, I'd be like, "Oh, what a nice necklace, Hasan Piker."
Like, I'd say stuff like that.
And that's calling me cool because he's so cool.
Yeah, that's a compliment, actually.
Yeah.
By the way, that's a little bit of a glass house calling me Hasan Piker.
Why'd you put this pearl necklace on?
Because it was sitting on the table, so I put on a pearl necklace
and you're just now noticing it looks so at home on my on my I saw it's a
whole time. I didn't even think about it in the in the monitor here. It looks
like you're wearing a necklace of bones. That's what I was hoping for. It looks
like all the knuckles of every enemy that I've ever killed. If you were doing
that, I think also I think making a necklace of knuckles is that's a little
bit that's a little not fair because you know you make a necklace of of ears or
whatever it's okay. That's only two years per person you kill you make a
a necklace and knuckles, you get like fucking 20 knuckles on every person.
Right? You can't even tell.
Unless you get all their middle fingers.
Unless you get a full necklace. Yeah, it's got to be...
It's got to be one finger.
People have too many knuckles.
Yeah. Ears make sense.
Ears is good.
Uh-huh.
Do you think if us three...
Noses.
Noses is scary.
Well, you've got one nose.
Yeah.
Do you think if us three discovered a dead body, it would change us as a trio?
No.
I think that it would change me. I'm very susceptible to...
If I saw a dead body, I'd probably walk by and pretend I didn't see it.
I think I would too.
I would see it and I would make too big of a deal about it.
You'd be like, "Oh, I saw a dead guy."
I would say maybe months later, "And you know, when I saw that dead body..."
And it would...
I mean, what would you do?
I would just talk about it all the time.
You know what I mean?
I'd say something and then be like, "Yeah, it's like that time that I saw the dead body."
You would use it as an excuse.
Yeah?
Yeah, you would use it as an excuse.
How?
You would do something, you would like go up at an open mic and just tank and then be like
yeah.
I saw a dead body earlier.
Well, I hope you guys know I saw a dead body four months ago.
I've been stressed about this.
That's really all I can think about.
Every time I look out I imagine all of you is this guy's a dead body.
Speaking of bombing, Alex made me feel really bad.
Oh, that's good.
He bombed in his friendship with you?
No, no, no, no. He told me he was fucking with me, but last night I couldn't make a show that
we were supposed to both be on, so I sent him there with Little Patrick.
The blow-up doll.
The blow-up doll. I put a shirt on him that said my name and some pants.
And did the pants say your name?
No.
That's a classic Patrick outfit, is walking around with a t-shirt that says your name
on it.
It says Patrick Doren on it.
Just so that I put it on so the crowd would know it was me.
Right.
You know, I mean there's probably some people there that have never seen what I look like.
And I sent him there and I sent him like 15 different audio files of reactions that I
could have.
You know, just like saying stuff like, "Oh, I would have noped the fuck out of there!"
Like stuff like that.
Because what was the show?
It was the Troll 2 Riff Show that Alex asked me to do and then I said, "I can't make it."
And you definitely couldn't make it.
Because I thought we were doing the shareholders.
And so you had a lot of stuff going on, couldn't make it, really wanted to go to the show.
I got that.
I got that letter from the IRS and I had the panic attacks.
I had to stay home.
You got a letter from the IRS?
Yeah, I'm not going to talk about that.
But he called me instantly because I'm his tax guy.
You are my tax guy.
Yes.
I'm really just like you're in case of emergency.
Anytime.
I've never gotten a phone call from you and you were just like, what's up, man?
it's always like can you bring me to the hospital? I'm having something really
bad. You have a car yeah. It's never you never call me just to catch up. What's
that about? I see you every day, but still man call you for that. I can, but
why not just why not just call me one time so that I'm not terrified to answer
the phone every single time you call me literally yesterday. Every time you call
me yesterday, I realize this you call me and I go
and then I answer the phone. I have to do it in your voice. I have to do this. I
you go what's up yeah and I always am dead serious what's up man yeah what is
it what do you need well maybe one day you're gonna get a call and it's gonna
be a prank call for me that I forgot to do star six seven but I sent Alex to the
show with little Patrick and then he sent me a text that said that bombs so
fucking hard and I guess it was it didn't bomb but it it would have done
better if the audio, like if you pick up the mic, could pick up the phone better.
They did it right out of the phone. That was the problem. Should have set up a full sound
board for something like that.
Yeah, exactly.
Or you could have just showed up.
I could have just showed up.
Yeah, yeah, because again, the thing you were going to do got cancelled, so you probably
could have just gone.
Yeah, but I think that that bit is funnier.
Than being there.
Yes.
Okay.
I think sending a blow up doll in your place that has 15 pre-recorded things that are like...
you had done MF doom
impersonator. I
want to do that one time. I want there, but it shouldn't be you. It should be a
guy dressed up like MF doom. Yeah,
but guy white guy in an MF doom. Yeah, yeah, I mean if I do any shows on
Halloween,
that's what he sound like to me because he's because he's buried underground.
Yeah,
they buried him. He's dead now. They burned him. Yeah, I was thinking they
burned him. They burned him alive. Jedi think they could well.
They burned him alive and they spread his ashes in a candy store. Yeah, they
buried him with over all the buried him. They filled his coffin with mac and
cheese. Can they if you want to do something disgusting with your remains?
I know I'm not trying to make light of it, but I heard that they
they laid him on down on a bed of mac and cheese. Really, I swear to God,
but they crisp the top. I heard that I heard also when they when they they
lowered his coffin into the ground and they were shoveling dirt on it was
Oreo crumbs
here. There was a real comes in gummy worms
shoveled down on to really yeah, he's not trying to make like I heard any
gravestone. He's a Graham
and it's very I mean the saddest part is that the I mean all it was really
eaten. Yeah,
big fan. Yeah, and they put him in a beef jerky. That's reminding me.
That's reminding me that I when Leo was here, I immediately showed him cooking
with Jack just to, you know, I wanted to show him a true American. Yeah. And he
liked it. He what he had his mind blown. Yeah, I showed him you show somebody
aunt Myrna's party cheese salad for the first time.
fucking mind boggling. Yeah. The part where he's like about to eat it and he
go or he eats, he takes his first bite and he goes, it's so it's kind of got
like a pudding effect. He lost his goddamn mind putting effect, putting
effect, which also my girlfriend met him and I think that she's never met a
British person in her life. Well, why would you? She was asking him questions
like, so do you have health care? That's what I do like that. Yeah, you got to
you ask about Burton? Is this just an American thing? I've known him for so long.
Every time I see him, I still ask him all the questions about all types of
different... You wouldn't do that to like a... I think that that's like... I
would do it to anybody from any different country, but I guess I'm fascinated
by the world. Yeah. Well, it's just like the funny... Meeting a white person
from an English speaking country is kinda like when you meet your mom's
friend
from work, and you're just asking them just like... What is it like?
Is my mom weird at work?
Or does she behave?
Does my mom wear bikinis at work?
Does my mom ever talk about me?
Do you have this at work?
Do you guys have staplers at work?
I guess it is kind of like asking what is different about a different place.
It is like that.
Oh, now I see the connection.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I've always...
Julio, in Mexico, do you guys have any animals?
It's just a very weirdly American thing, I think.
There's no animals in Mexico.
it's a very weird American thing that we all do, because we just can't fathom at
all that other places are normal. I don't like when people say that shit
about me. I can fathom anything. I'm easily a fathomer yeah. I just I can't.
I honestly I would I would I would ask those questions about when I find when I
need somebody else who grew who grew up also in Massachusetts, but like one town
over I would ask them about it. Yeah, do you have Cumberland Farms? I'm so
interesting ashby by did you guys know that that I just found this out that
Wegmans is a New England thing yeah. I never even saw or heard of a way to
all because I was the mula's market basket had the fucking market cornered
yeah. I've literally never. I thought Wegmans was a was some from somewhere
else. I just found out that it's from here. It's really sad that grocery
stores are regional yeah. It's crazy. They should be going. You know the said
the one thing that made me sad is that it's a it was a a grocery store that was
regional to me and I didn't even know it. Yeah, that'll kill you because the
the family I've never been inside one before my entire life. If you want
there's one in Dumbo. I know I walked by one in
they open a new one in Manhattan. That one in Dumbo is like
it's like a like a warehouse.
They have so much crap in there. I love the great. Their hot bar is amazing.
We honestly we should make a pilgrimage. Let's go right now. Do I make I would
to go. I would really love to go. Is Publix rotisserie chicken fire more than other places?
It's up there. It's up there. I would say Costco is amazing purely because of the price
and how big them chickens are. It's not even a chicken anymore. But Publix got the Pub
Sub. Publix has the Pub Sub. Harris Teeter has an amazing Sub sandwich. We do it differently
down south at the grocery stores. Market Basket, they got Subs there. I do have to admit that
you guys do it a little differently. Market Basket's taking something from the Southern
playbook. Market Basket is cool. The Market Kitchen. Market Basket is not for me man.
You haven't been to a good one. It used to be cooler. You haven't been to a good one.
You gotta go to one. It's too full man. You gotta go to a Market Basket. They go fucking
nuts for Market Basket. It is crazy. It is insane. It is an ant farm in there. It is
the rudest experiences you will ever have in your life is at a Market Basket. The best
part is it's an anti-Trader Joe's. It's the anti-Trader Joe's. Yeah, well fuck Trader
Joe's. Trader Joe's amazing. I like in Market Basket how they make everyone wear the name
name tags that say how long they've worked there. So you'll see somebody
who's you see a high schooler and it says one year and you're like, Oh,
that's nice. And then you see they're working alongside a woman who's 80
years old and it says 50 years. Yeah, I don't like that. They do it as a
fingernail tally marks on the thing. Yeah, that's a bad idea. But those
jackets that they wear, it's cool. Man, those jackets like those jackets are
you should have you should be forced to work a job as a high schooler where you
have to wear a jacket. That jacket, I think it's where you have to dress as a
hop. Yeah, the jackets that they wear there I think are just Dickies Eisenhower
jackets which is why I own so many. Because you want to work. The
Market Basket blue jacket is one of the best looking jackets in the world.
But you went to the one in Somerville or Cambridge or whatever you
got to go to one that's like got its own dedicated parking lot. Yeah. Like one that
has like. Dedicated to you. Yeah, dedicated to some kid that died in town.
to go to one in like the one in like Plastow or something like the fucking or just like
the one in like like Salem or you're not gonna miss me. It's better. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, sir. There is a very good market basket in town and what grocery store do they
have in Los Angeles? Ralph's Ralph's Ralph's and Vons. I'm going to be at Ralph's and Vons
buying groceries because I'm going to be in Los Angeles doing 30 minutes of stand up comedy
with my friend Gus Viveiros at The Yard on November 17th. Guys, go get tickets over there
at the website that we'll put in the description of the episode.
Gus Viveiros, somebody that shopped at Market Basket a lot.
He's from Boston.
Yeah.
And I'll see you there.
Oh, and also...
Yeah, you go first.
No, you go first.
Okay. Well, I will be shopping at Jewel Osco on November 5th.
The hell's Jewel Osco?
It's a Chicago-based...
Oh, I see.
hello. I see grocery store and I will be there opening for girl God and tune in
on Wednesday for Mars, the beginning of ours, the beginning of the planet month
in one week. Five do we start from five weeks of planning mercury? Yeah, I meant
mercury. I was going to be a good one. Every episode is going to be named after
the planet. It's going to be very simple to follow along. This is a new series.
we're starting five very excited. Five weeks of planets, five weeks of plan.
It'll be like planet earth, but it'll be us giving our skewed take on the plan.
We're gonna be, we're gonna be gonna be science based. Ow, my back, I broke it.
All right, you're right.
Bye.
At the library. Okay, your turn.
I'm at the library. I've taken out six books at a time. I'm at the library.
I'm doing more of a hook at this time.
I think I did more.
I was singing.
I'm doing more of the hooks at this time.
Wait, this might help.
Reading is not a crime.
I do it all the time.
Whoa.
I'm reading books about limes.
Damn.
Lime scooter.
Hit her in the cooter.
Hit her? Wait.
Drop a gunshot.
Hit her in her cooter.
With a lime scooter?
With a lime scooter.
Lime scooter directly to the cooter.
Doing some evil,
Knievel shit into a woman's evil.
This is a good way to learn about your instincts.
My instincts store hurting women's vagina
but with a cutting edge application based technology,
using application vehicle to hurt a woman or thing.
I went in a self driving car.
Really?
Yeah.
I was in, uh, yo, I don't, well, I was in Phoenix basically and, um.
A rap is about it.
Yeah, you have to rap about it.
Yo, imagine a work, well, actually turn this beat, uh, keep it the same actually.
I was in a car that had nobody driving in it.
I felt like a creamed spinach.
I had, I literally got exploded on with the whole vehicle exploded.
It was crazy.
Phoenix fell into the earth.
What?
And then I, and then I blow up all crazy.
I have no, I have no idea what's happening to me.
I got a lobster hot pocket.
Oh,
I met two hot, two, two girls with two lobster hot pockets.
I said, getting the self-driving vehicle.
You got to go down and knock it.
Show you what, what it's like when I'm laughing at Jason.
See you.
The goal
vehicle to see your goal is insanely good, man.
That's the type of shit that I'm expressing myself about for a second.
Alright, Cameron.
Okay.
Well...
Well, I'm sitting here and I can't...
Oh, it ended.
[Bowser's theme]