*outro music*
(thunder)
- Dead in the middle of little skibbity skibby
did we know that we skibbity
- Skibby did we know we riddled some camera men
who didn't do skibbity.
- Who didn't do skibbity.
- It'll be a cold day in toilet the way I,
the day I take in a loilet.
- Take a loilet.
- Skibbity skibbity skibbity.
- Make no mistake for.
- Boil it.
- For boil it I won't, I wouldn't hesitate to toilet.
- Just an idea.
- That's a good, that's a good idea.
Can someone one of you three explain to me or you to not this guy, somebody
explain to me why I ate chicken Marsala for breakfast at nine thirty in the
morning. I asked I did the same thing. No fucking way. Fuck yeah. I did the same
when we recorded the first day of planets. Maybe this is maybe this is a
plus a planetary sign, but I the stars are left over. I had the stars are
literally aligning for the five weeks of planets. I'm not even kidding. I have a
story to tell today. My God, shit is shit is getting fucking weird out there. I'm
not kidding for breakfast for breakfast on the first day of planets. Mine's
worse. I had leftover marsala and garlic bread. Mine's so much worse man. Well,
it was at eleven ish around nine thirty and I didn't have leftovers man. I woke
up and I made chicken marsala at nine thirty in the morning. Damn. That was
just what was in my fridge. I was like, oh, I have all the ingredients for
chicken Marsala and I ate it and I immediately fell asleep.
Do I cut up the chicken? Yeah. And it's cubes. It was like...
You wanna hear something fucked up? Yes, I do. Okay, so this is
my dad's... My dad cuts it up into cubes, right? And you know how you're
supposed to get a little bit of prosciutto or pancetta, put it in the
pan. Yeah. My dad, when we were growing up,
I think it was just a broke boy thing, my father put cubes of
regular ass ham in the masala. He did that so, he didn't even put parsley in it or I don't
remember if he did or not.
I mean I wasn't doing all that much crazy shit anyway.
Replacing the prosciutto with ham was so insane.
Yeah, that's like cubed ham.
Cubed turkey or like Oscar Mayer ham.
Yeah, pretty fucked up. Pretty fucked up for you to do, dad.
Yeah, that definitely put him out of it.
Now when I make it, I always use pancetta.
Do you think you've been affected by nitrites because you had so many growing up?
I've been affected by nitrites as well.
I think that every single one of us has.
I'm starting to think that the reason I have diarrhea right now is because of the tap water
in my house.
Maybe.
I think I might have evil tap water because I drink it all day.
I think it's because I drink only out of plastic and eat out of plastic only.
And you reuse Gatorade.
I eat plastic on everything.
And you read plastic books too.
Yeah, the Kindle, man, that shit's made of plastic too.
I basically touch as much and eat as much and smell as much plastic as I can on a daily
basis.
You can't avoid it. You can't avoid literally the only way. I'm sorry to
jump into this too early. Maybe the only way is literally to leave planet
Earth. Yeah. Holy shit, guys. Welcome to Venus. This is the second and third.
Well, technically, the third episode. Welcome to week one of the five weeks of
planets week one day to week one day to one out of five two day week today. I
mean, what were you saying? You were saying something about the stars aligning.
I need to hear what I'll get to. I'll get to it. I'm sorry if you five weeks
I talk about really been well. No, I want it after we do do all of our Venus
intro stuff. I'll tell this if you couldn't tell we're dressed up like
Venus today, although we had some some amount of disagreement, I guess over
what color Venus is. That's okay. I got both going on. You do have both, but
what's the black about? Well, we'll go down. You want me to start with my with
my costume? Yeah, I'm just up as a line. No,
I'm just up as be any if I walked out on the street right now, any person who
was literally who attended at first grade would know I'm dressed as it would be
some people
Coraline. No first grader would look at me and say that's Venus. No, they would
a child who was into science and into movies who would have seen movies. Why
did you say movies and of course they'd say Coraline man? Well,
if it was movies around Halloween time, if they saw me in a costume like this,
they would say Venus. They would say that's Coraline. She's very pretty today.
No, they wouldn't say that they would say I like Coraline's mustache jumping
off of pretty here. Venus is actually the name of the God is Venus is named after
the goddess of beauty and of love. So I elected to put on a beautiful wig today
and a
my beautiful hair camera. Now you're asking about the yellow raincoat. So let
me explain this to you. Venus, the color can be some people say it's yellow. Some
people say yellowish white. Some people say beige. This raincoat is yellow,
definitely too yellow for Venus. Some people at this table would say beige. I
I think two people would do, but say beige Venus has it's surrounded by
sulfuric clouds. It has a sulfurous atmosphere, which is why it's that
color and in the upper atmosphere constantly acid rain.
Wow, wait, so I'm dressed up like coral layers of rain, so that's the
yellow. It's the yellow acid rain and then I have a yellowish white shirt
here
to this is kind of closer to the color. I feel a little bit like coral
lame and then dude chill. I'm just as Venus. I don't know why you guys are
stuck on this. I don't look anything like Coraline. You pull up. I said
Coraline. It's going to look completely different from what I'm wearing right
now or a lame, though. Yeah, he said that's not then that you said nonsense
word and you're proud of that. You're proud of making up a word.
That's you man. That's I don't know what you're talking about. I didn't try to
dress up like this. No, wait, no, she has blue hair. I literally did not
think about this in advance and try to dress up like this, guys.
It looks exactly-- you do the Coraline cover.
Anyway, I'm wearing-- I got beige pants on, too, to cover the beige.
You have striped leggings. I can see them from here.
Uh-huh. I'm completely beige right now.
You're completely beige. Yeah.
So you went for basically only color and didn't really think about the science?
I'm wearing a pair of pants. No, I did not think about the science.
It's just a difference of like--
It's a difference of style and how people do costumes.
You may be the most scientifically accurate dude, but honestly bro, you look like a herb.
I don't.
You look like a herb.
Guys, guys, uh uh.
You know what it is?
You're getting...
Why are you roasting me so hard like the hot atmosphere on Venus?
You're roasting him because you guys, he's dressed up too much like Venus and you're
in your head, you're thinking of Venus, right?
Yeah.
And you're thinking about the OJ the Alien song Venusian Destroyer.
What's Venusian Destroyer?
I haven't heard that.
Julio?
crack drop that shit right now that shit right ass now oh my god pull it up on
screen to Julio if you if you aren't already oh shut it off he's got to put
it on the right browser and that was a little bit of a give us a bomb drop oh
sorry run that shit back
Well, well, well, Venus. It looks like we meet again.
Don't think that I forgot about you, 'cause you're about to enter a galaxy of pain.
Fat Venus, Fat Venus, Fat Venus, we hate that shit.
Venus, weakest planet out of all nine. Think of you and hate just run down my spine.
*music*
Oh my god
Odd Future style
This is a diss-diss-style?
It's an Odd Future diss track, yeah
*outro*
My name is OJ the alien
You know me, I'm from planet Glarion
I got scaly skin like Amartalian
I'm Marginocephalian
And I only eat citrus
Venus, that's a planet that's shitless
Venus, you've been on my shit list
And I'm addicted to citrus
Fuck Venus
Fuck Venus, we play dog shit
♪ Fuck Venus, Fuck Venus, Fuck Venus, We hate that shit ♪
You shouldn't have tried that shit with me.
Didn't you know I'm a fucking crazy motherfucking psycho alien?
And guess what?
I'm about to blow up your whole shit.
Whoa, dude.
In part two.
What?
Let me continue.
That's right.
Part two.
Oh my God. Okay, wait. So now this is bringing the lore to a place where I
can understand it. His name is OJ and he only eats citrus. He's from planet
glarion. He's from planet glarion. He only eats citrus. What is a marcino
cephalian? Marcino, what is it? Margino cephalian means it's kind of like a
dinosaur that's got like,
like three, like a triceratops, you know? It's got like a... He's a dinosaur now?
he's got like a dinosaur like face because he's got skin like he's a
reptilian. Oh,
it's a reptile alien. Well,
cephalos head right, so yeah, Margino is that small? I think it's small head. I
don't know. Marjoram, I butter head, butter head,
maybe he's a butter head on his, it's like a Amish slur. Yeah,
maybe on
She's a butter head, which is like, it's like, yeah, you know, oh man, OJ the alien
looks so good, butter head.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, shit.
Butter head, the head that he gives is bad.
I do it gives a bad head.
I did explain butter face to my 25 year old wife the other day.
She did, she didn't, she had heard it and thought that it meant that somebody had a
face that looked like melted butter.
That's reasonable to think.
But I, I explained it's way meaner than that.
It is.
It's way meaner.
here. Yeah, well yeah, I guess yeah, but still it's a it's a backhanded
compliment. It is definitely a compliment. I agree more of a comment
than your face looks like melted butter. Yeah, that's what I try to explain to
her. She's a
your body looks like shit.
That's a butter face could mean yeah. All right, I have a new so every every
week every day of the week. We're going to get a new every day of the week.
no, it's a two day week, a planetary week. We're doing five two day weeks.
Thank you for saying that, man. A lot of people don't realize that people need
to learn about the planetary weeks that are going on. Learn today, man. We're
gonna get a new OJ the alien drop and I've also decided that I'm gonna start
doing, 'cause I realize last time when we did Mercury, which tune in if you
haven't heard the Mercury episode, tap the fuck in. What the fuck you even doing
here? Turn this shit off. Go back to Mercury and come back here, bitch. I
felt, I tried to read some Mercury facts and I felt like I was a little
disorganized and the facts weren't so interesting. So I decided to do some
research and I'm well, no I'm doing every planet from now on I'm going to do
write a planet report. Wow, I'm going to research it and write a report with the
most important. Do you have a theme song? I actually do have some music to play
while I'm on my bed, so well, it's not a thing you can still do a theme. So
mine is just kind of background music
I'll add a theme song. That's a really good idea. Yeah, I'll do that next next
time. Okay, this one is a planet report. This one is called with Coraline
guys. I'm not Coraline. Sorry, I didn't mean to say it. So I'm going to take my
costume off. If you keep talking about it, don't take it off, dude, Coraline is
too young to strip naked. Yeah,
don't do that.
Okay, I'm going to start my report now.
Visions of Venus, a planet report by Cameron Fetter,
of all the planets I've done research on so far, Venus is the one I've done the
research on. In the process of writing this report I've honestly started to feel
very loving and possessive toward Venus. I feel like this wonderful planet belongs
to me. I've started calling it my planet. Just one of the many magical feelings I
felt during the five weeks of planets. Now, on to the facts. If you've been out
and about at night you've probably seen my Venus before. My Venus is very easy to
to spot with the naked eye. Just look in the sky for something yellowish white. Yes, my
Venus is yellowish white in color. My Venus is named after the Roman goddess of beauty
and sex. My Venus is sometimes also known as the morning star or Lucifer, which are
both names for the devil. My Venus was the first planet to ever be discovered. My Venus
is the second brightest object in the night sky besides the moon. The reason for this
is the clouds of sulfuric acid that surround my Venus. A day is longer than a year on my
Venus. My Venus is very hot. The hottest one. My Venus is even hotter than Mercury, even
though my Venus is further from the sun. My Venus is around the same size as Earth, which
leads it to sometimes be called Earth's twin. But it's rather small compared to some of
the other planets of our solar system.
you should say my son as well. Yeah, my son, yeah, it's further away from my
Venus.
Yeah,
for example, you could fit about four of my Venus's into Uranus and still have
some room left over
the four of my Venus's and Uranus would be rotating clockwise because my Venus
rotates clockwise.
That's my report on Venus.
That was an amazing report.
It rotates clockwise.
I'm really impressed by your planetary knowledge.
Thank you.
I did a lot of research for that one.
I'm glad that you are bringing knowledge and facts to the planetary report.
I'm glad that I can bring music and Caleb, I want to know what you're bringing.
Yeah, what are you bringing?
Because me and Cameron have stuff.
Well guys, as we said yesterday when we were eating Mexican food, I felt left out because
because you were making amazing rap and Cameron was basically being
scholastically studious and I realized that I had nothing
until
a spark of inspiration hit me and I realized that I'm an amazing artist and
here is my rendition of the planet Venus, guys. Wow. Oh my God. Can you zoom
in on this, Julio? This is incredible. Wow, I'm seeing a yellowish... Can you
describe this yeah blurry yellowish planet, a yellow, a bit blurry planet
and I put the space is like kind of behind its stars, dotting the entire
galaxy. I really am happy with how this turned out. I think it's pretty good.
Who is this? Who is this? I'm seeing a woman kneeling yeah up. Oh that's yeah
that's Amanda.
Okay, who's that? She's just like on there. She looks good. I guess yeah.
that is I mean speaking of butterfaces wait, that's wrong with their face.
That's the only part I painted.
That's the only part you painted.
Because I use a what do you mean by that? I use it.
They're not what I traced over on my app on wait. Let me see what the app is
called. Hold on. I got a painting app. I think I'm getting really into painting
recently. Yeah, I wish you had the go-pro.
It's really good. The painting is called Ibis paint X.
I've been saying that app is called Ibis paint X and it has different girls that
you can trace. Oh, and so I traced this girl, but she basically had an egg head.
So I added lips and a nose and some eyes and some hair. Yeah, I can see the hair,
but that's a man.
Two big strands of hair in the front of
on Wikipedia or something. It said that there was an,
an Amanda on. Okay. So I just basically,
can I see the reference photo that you used for this? Yeah, I can show you.
Hold on. I just want to see. I got to make a new on Ibis paint. Hold on. I got to make
a new photo guys. Okay. Hold on. And now I got see you go over here and then you go like
wait, where did I more of the this is less about V. Yes, you can do. Okay. Tracing sketches
apps and I try to get one with a lot more feet in it, but they didn't have any. You
can do different like I could have done this one. Oh, you just try it. So it's a trace.
Maybe I'll do this one next time. That one's not so bad. It's like two guys sitting on
on each other's butts. Yeah, it's pretty impressive. Well, I really like your
do you have a title for your Venus painting Venus or no sorry Amanda.
Okay, yeah,
but I'm pretty. I never thought I'd see Amanda sitting on my Venus. Yeah, and so
this is basically I'm going to be doing a painting of every single one and then I
think maybe and now I might even go back and do Mercury. Oh, that's a good idea.
That's not a bad at maybe then I was thinking maybe we could do like a like a
book a book like with the report and like a table, but a coffee table book.
Okay, here it's a coffee table book. It's got the paintings, it's got the
reports and then you know, like a birthday card that when you open it, it
plays music wow between every few pages. It's got a different song.
We'll find we can find out a way to do that. That's actually that was an
amazing, amazing idea because it could have on the left side. It would have
the report yeah on the right side. We'd have the pain and then it would play
you're hearing it all and it's ten pages.
well ten, it's twenty twenty pages of really thick, but you know what it
could be a birthday card thing yeah. You know what it could be is one of those
old
those books that have like the buttons on the side. Oh yeah, I used to have
there's ten, but that's also sway ten buttons there. So there goes
mercury yeah like that kind of thing yeah yeah wow that's an amazing idea or
it could be you open up on one of the pages. It has grooves like a record and
can put the boy to a table. Yes, it's like a man. Oh my God. I remember books
like that. Yeah, we all had books like that growing up. So record book. I
want a record book in a raffle as a kid.
What really? Yeah, it's a real thing. I was making a joke. I know that's a
real thing. What can't be true? Look it up, look it up, look up, use the
pages of a book as a fucking record. Now, the cover is like vinyl and then
search a vinyl book record book is just gonna be a record. Yeah, it's gonna
be
vinyl record book.
Vinyl record book?
This can't be real, man.
And it's like it would...
I remember books that you could take in the bath.
It was like a...
Okay, you're not getting anywhere with this search.
Yeah, you're a bad Googler, man.
Yeah.
Okay, there we go.
I still think it doesn't exist, man.
No, it exists.
I believe you.
I'm willing to just believe you here because I don't think we're going to find a good picture
of one.
Okay, that's fine.
That's fine.
Yeah, I think that some kind of...
I don't know.
I think that some kind of...
I think we're going to find a good picture of one. Okay, that's fine.
That's fine. Yeah, I think that some kind of or a calendar we could do a
calendar at nine
a ten month calendar. We can add two more. We can we can for it's exclusive
for just the calendar. That's actually a genius idea earth and the rings of
Saturn. Yeah, the asteroid belt, maybe earth could be Christmas.
I actually just remember another Venus fact that I didn't put in my report.
This is another Venus fact. Venus is the only planet that we've discovered so
far with a fly trap.
True could be more out there, but that's the only one we know of right now said
that man Venus fly trap is from my hometown. Yeah, I have I have I've roots
in Venus literally literally roots literally the roots of a Venus fly trap
while from one week to Venus flies. That's where that's where it's like from
completely. It's yeah, it's only there like a fifty mile radius that this is
that that plant is in yeah, wow naturally they say yeah, which there's
nothing natural by outer space. Well, that's actually it's that why it's
called a Venus fly trap, because I think that it came from a different planet.
Yeah, I think so. Well, that's what happens in a little shop of horrors. I
couldn't find the real shit I was talking about. All I could find was the
simply read album, so I think that this is an un Google thing, but it's that
a for the vinyl record. It's very bad SEO, but my first grade teacher, Mrs
Iosu, I got a book from her that she said I don't have a record player
anymore, but I'll just read the book to you guys. Why the hell didn't he just
fucking kill a bunch of dogs and feed it to the plant in that movie? That's not a
bad point. I think I wanted humans, but it doesn't know that I think it likes
you. It does. It did. He didn't give him any. No, no, he fed. It's a big point of
the yeah, yeah, yeah, he feeds on. It gets a taste for human blood, so just
that's why like dogs. Oh yeah, he could have said that it was a dog. He could
have said I'm a dog. I'm a dog. I need your human blood. He could have been
like
the original one. Now the it's it's not so good, but it's the one really funny
part is
the one before the Rick Moranis one. Yeah,
yeah, Jack Nicholson is in it. The old Roger Corwin from the sixties is it a
singular a singular a musical? No, it's supposed to be funny, but it's not very
funny, but one very funny part is there's a character who Dick Miller plays
a character who just is always in the flower shop and his thing is just he
just likes to eat flowers. That's funny. It's so funny. He just comes in and he's
like I'll get like a dozen roses and they're like and they're like oh it's
for your wife. Maybe he starts eating them and it doesn't a bunch of times
dick. Miller sounds like a frat house prank yeah.
It really does that you would pull on somebody now yeah in the old dick
Miller yeah or Miller Dick, the five weeks of planets is taking over the
world. Yeah, people have been talking about it. This is a crazy. Can I tell
you something I this morning when I got my haircut? Oh yeah, wait, not this
haircut, but the one on the city,
the barber he was talking to me the entire time and I didn't bring this up.
He was the one who introduced this topic. You can be kidding. We were
talking the entire time about the annihilation of planet Earth. Oh, by
what all types of factors from outer space, Jesus from outer space, not
where you get your right solar flares the same place that Joe went. Is it in
Bushwick? No, it's right on it's right on myrtle species, but yeah, I didn't
bring it up. He just started talking about it and we were I was having a
ball talking to him about
the
barbers, and it was there was a guy getting his hair cut next to me, who
was like he was like a
sanitation worker guy, kind of a gruff sanitation worker guy, and
Barbara was talking about
about how the Earth's magnetic field switch. He also was talking about global
warming is fake, but he was talking about how Earth's magnetic field is it
switches every hundred thousand years. It switches poles that's true and he was
like yeah and who knows how it could affect any it is true, but he's like who
knows how could it could affect stuff like it's going to mess with our
electronics and this and the guy sitting next to was like yeah and it could move
everything and then the guy said it will move every
and they both just agreed with each other that it's going to move. I'm going
to move every day. Yeah, it will move everything, for example, fishes,
fishes will move. Do they have a date for the polar shift? I think it's
happening right now. Well, that's what he said. He said we're going through it
right. Oh my God, I've been feeling like something has been shifting. He also
said that Russia is trying to figure out how to make a yellowstone erupt to
destroy the United States. I could that destroy like good chunks of the earth
like a whole planet. I think half of America, yeah, have a mirror, but also
it might even crawl up to that old, but it's I mean the real problem is
volcanic ash that blocks the sun. That's the trouble. I mean the whole I would
I think that's one of the troubles.
The other trouble is the...
Well, that's the trouble for the planet.
Oh, yeah.
Well, but also, they don't get...
I mean, Hollywood gets destroyed, so good luck getting your movies.
We truly...
I think I was talking about this last night.
We truly have the whole market cornered on movies.
It's not a very insightful thing to say.
Earth does?
No.
That's true.
America, USA.
Well, no, they make movies into every country, bro.
Yeah, but have you ever seen a movie from...
RRR dude. RRR was amazing. Every Japanese movie is all incredible. Every Japanese movie bro.
Types of deep intellectual words. I think I was talking to Alex. This guy doesn't like
stalker. No, you know what I think I was talking about? I was talking to Alex last night. Pusher
1, Pusher 2, Pusher 3. I was talking to Alex last night about that fucking. Looper. Looper,
jumper. That Israeli SNL show. Frogger. Oh the Israeli SNL show. Yeah, I was just saying
that they are so bad at comedy in Israel.
Hmm.
I don't know if I'd go that far.
I actually think some of it's funny, man.
I said I was...
A lot of my friends are actually on that show now.
Okay, you know what?
I'll...
I said it already, but I'll admit it.
I was pretty drunk and I said...
I think I said that, "Don't come for my Jews, but these Israelis are not funny."
Damn.
You said, "Don't come for my Jews."
I said I fuck with my Jews heavy.
I said I fuck with my Jews heavy, but these Israelis are not good at comedy.
You said I'm starting my Israeli boycott tomorrow, guys.
That's right. No more weather for me. That's what you said.
I didn't say that, but you did.
That's right. I'm done with the weather.
I'm not enjoying any kinds of weather anymore.
Due to my Israel boycott.
That's part of BDS.
Yeah, and I said, "Dude, you can't say that shit, man."
I don't know why you even brought that up.
shut up. I think that it's the hangover speaking,
speaking of hangovers, back to the movies, back to the movies. We should
make barbership. That was a that's oh yeah, that is a good idea. So
barbershop, barbershop, exploitation, but it's alien. So plane on soul ship,
soul ship, holy shit,
how's it all playing on a space station in that is incredible barbership
barbership
that would be such a good movie
bro. That would be such a this is less about the movie and more about just a
spaceship. That is a barber shop, okay, you can imagine their tractor beam when
they're beaming stuff up. It would look like the barber pole. It would yeah
so many amazing ideas. The alien comes up and he has like kind of twill, like
kind of head and they and the guy like
that's not my hair yeah or they cut it and he's bleeding everywhere dies and
sprays blood and the bloods green and the guys like an ice cubes like bro. What
the hell was I supposed to cut plasma cube? That wasn't your hair man and this
could be a space station next to Venus.
I mean I yeah it could be anything.
I'm just trying to keep it on theme with the jumps around most likely yeah,
we'll get back to Venus. We'll get we'll get back. We'll get back to me. Don't
for now. We're on the barbership. I wish I wish man and then you got a white
alien walks in and a records.
Oh yeah,
what's up man?
Yeah, I'd like to get a just a little bit off the sides and the top leave the
top pretty long. Okay,
they give him the craziest haircut of all time and he becomes cool and afro
yeah. They give him an alien. So this
going around it or burning is afro. Yeah, he swagger's. Yeah, it could be a
teaching moment, though it could be he walks in wearing a shirt that says back
the blue gags, a shirt, a shirt that says that's a blue backs, a shirt, a shirt,
back the blue gags, which a blue gags is a space police or something, and then
they have a police, and then they have a con conversation about this, and then a
sit down, they have a sit down, and then this is like a teaching moment in the
movie, and it's actually the script is actually so beautiful, and then we win an
Oscar for it, because we basically turn barbership into crash. Okay, and then we
would get and then we would get maybe someone I can imagine someone writer of
you that would be like this. It would be like
barbership makes you laugh and has thrills aplenty, but I'm left wondering
would racism still exists exist in space and then it would they would kind of go
off on that. They can also do be about how there is aliens around
the human race with probably another another review for that might be like
barbership is officially the most racist movie
three white made by two white guys in a core line.
This is got to be one of the worst. This is the worst most racist. It's five
hours long and I was long because it starts with two hours of prologue.
That's about the earth being destroyed like
civilized three at the premier. We're all dressed in all white suits.
Nobody's taking photos, just tomatoes getting thrown.
What what happened? What the fuck? Why is everyone mad? Why are you mad about
barbership man? We tried to bring the every world together. We realize that
this shit transcends race is actually it's about species yeah.
There's not you know it should be the and then I mean after the after the
press response to barbership. I think that we know that barbership too is
going to be starring Mel Gibson and Kevin Sorbo only people who sign on
and it's an action
barbership
to destroy
nothing to do with the original cast.
The ads Mel Gibson and Kevin Sorber like
them trying to kill the original
characters.
So we're getting readings of a barbership
Armageddon,
just building a giant laser beam to destroy the barbership, barbary,
barbary, they I'm just saying man. They should have done more barber movies.
Yeah, they made barbershop three. They should be doing every shop. I mean they
should be doing every single movie in space. Also, that should be a given
the s one that should be just a third one should be in space. Always the second
one should always be in Asia summer. Oh yeah, and the third one should always be
in space. Second one should always be in take place during the summer, summer
vacation vacation. Now the first one summer vacation of any movie, the second
one, they should be abroad yeah, and then the third one, they should be up
the third one. There should be a rival and one should always be old west yeah
the third one. The third one deals with a rival thing that arrival like family or
something that in the end you realize that they are basically parallels and they are
not that much different from each other. Like what movie does that? Like Cheaper by the
Dozen 2. Do they have a rival Dozen? It's two Dozens right? It's two Dozens. It's Eugene
Levy vs Steve Martin. In what? A kid off? What the hell? They have a kid off. It's like
Alien vs Predator. Yeah. I've never seen the third one. Well it's the second one. Oh I've
seen the second one. I don't remember that. The second one is Eugene Levy and Steve Martin
than having a child. I thought it was pretty much the same movie, but they got
a bigger house. No, no, no, no, you're thinking of yours, mine and ours.
There's a lot of now. I'm imagining having too many kids that came out. I
imagine imagining now they make a they make a barbership prequel and it's just
on earth and it's still it's barbership three origins. It's just barbershop is
barbershop exactly and then and then they go back for and then they have one
where it's barbership. I think I actually developed it on a boat. Yeah,
master and commander style. Yeah, exactly. It's part of the sea, master and
commander, yeah. Oh, yeah, yes, it's like a pirate ship. Yeah, yeah, that's a
good idea. It's just a sail and navy vessel, not a pirate. No piracy involved.
Well, I think pirates are cool, so whatever. Well, there could be a pirate
ship that boards the vessel. They fight and attacks, and that's Mel Gibson and
Kevin Sorbo. That's how they stand. It's their ancestors, and it's why they
became so evil. Yes. Pirate, their ancestors, they had pirate blood. Do you
guys think that I have pirate blood? No. No, not even like the guy who's like
the not even like first main. You maybe have me boy. You have that's what I was
saying. Yes,
you could be people talk shit on me. My great great great great grandfather was
me my
doing your
I found out that I'm really
me bro. That's not so bad man. I close I'd rather be smith and one of the guys
gets beat up by a kid. Yeah, me gets beat up by a kid hard. No me just chills. No
me does not show me. He's not just chill. Me is honestly a representation of the
banality of evil. Wow, holy fuck. Evil doesn't always look like a captain hook.
Sometimes it looks like a me. Yeah, speaking of me,
me, me hungry, me hungry, me want food, me very hungry for that's what Venus
fly trap. You're not no, you don't eat a Venus fly trap. I don't know fly. Yeah,
we've been, we've been slowly drifting out of Venus's orbit. Okay, let's, let's
go back, let's bring us back. What do you have to say? I liked barbership.
Barbership was good. Barbership is really good, but then we started talking
about pirates. Okay, let's talk about this, guys. How would you, so Venus is
basically one of the most hostile environments to life as we know it in
the solar system. As we know it. It is hundreds and hundreds of degrees
Fahrenheit there. The atmosphere is so dense that it would crush you from the
force of the of the pressure crush some and on me. It would also it also is
poisonous atmosphere. It's sulfur, so you would die from breathing it in.
There's lightning storms, high winds that blow rocks around the planet. It is
pretty pretty much impossible to build a house there. Yeah, but how would you
guys go about it? How would you colonize Venus? How would you get past all these
obstacles and build a city there? I wouldn't want to pal city for some
reason. I feel like Venus is the worst planet
really well we could tell by the way that you distant and somebody's a dish I just
saw Amanda she's so fucking beautiful sorry
for some reason I completely believe that Venus is trash I think compared to
every other planet is the worst one you would not want to build a colony on I
would not want to build a colony why not bro I could maybe see us building a
colony on Jupiter
or we're not even there we're not even talking about see you said let's bring
coming back to Venus and I say I like Jupiter more. So, so far if we're
going, I don't actually know. I feel like maybe it doesn't. We maybe should have
done a little bit more research. Well, I did a bunch of research. He's the
research man. That's true. I'm the artist and you're the rapper. Yeah.
Does Venus have a moon? Does Venus have a moon? What would it look like? Neither
Mercury nor Venus have any moons at all. Oh, because they're too close to the sun.
Yeah, it would get sucked up by the sun probably. So, here's my question and
Maybe there's a video of this, but what would it look like if Venus fell out of
orbit and crashed into the Earth?
It'd probably explode.
Is there a simulation of what that would look like?
It'd probably look like two planets hitting together.
That's what I like.
Yeah, but isn't Venus just like a ball of gas?
No, it's not a gas giant.
It's a rocky planet.
Even a gas giant has stuff on it.
Really?
Yeah.
Huh.
There's stuff in there.
A little bit.
A little bit of stuff.
want it crashing into your shit. Yeah, straight up. But Venus is not a
gaseous planet though. Oh, I thought it was. It has a gaseous atmosphere. Yes,
yes, that's what it is. A very dense atmosphere, but very dense clouds,
cloud cover. Cloud city. But it would probably... I bet you could look up a
video of Earth crashing into the moon and then mentally paint it a little
yellow and then you probably would get the same idea. Is it only the size of
the moon? No, it's the size of the Earth. Well, I would wanna see... I'm
just saying it's two planets crashing together. I would wanna see, 'cause
it's earth's twin. I would like to see what it would look like if the the I've
seen I just had a good idea guys. What
they are going and this is an idea of something that's going to happen that I
just remembered is happening. They are releasing next week a mortal combat
expansion pack where all of the characters are planets and you fight
against you fight against each other as planets and they do fatality. That's
true. Is that real? Yeah, I just came up with that and it's true. Oh my God. So
what kind of fatalities would Venus do? Venus crashes into earth and explodes.
that's okay. What does it do that to every planet? Yeah, I guess right now we
have every other planet in his Mercury and yeah, Pluto does that to shut up
don't talk about a different planet. Shut the fuck you asked if every planet
does it you're
and I answered you said shut the fuck. It was a trick question. It's not a
trick question. It was a you people. I could tell by your eyes. You were
genuine be more vague. You saw my genuine eyes,
so my genuine smile.
I'm not answering any more questions from either of you guys ever again. Okay,
answer my question. If you're not Coraline man straight up, what question
just answer it bro?
Shut up and answer it. You're such a bitch about it.
Let's see what I was thinking. We can maybe brainstorm some fatalities for
planets. Yeah, but we can only talk about Mercury and Earth and Venus right
now. Okay, so we haven't unlocked. I guess we're not allowed to bring it up.
I mean you can say them in comparative, you know, like a parent in comparative
ways, like you can say like, oh, you could fit, you know, you were saying you
could fit four of your Venus. Have you guys ever seen a
a set of twins speaking of Venus being Earth's twin where you're like, oh,
that's Earth and that's Venus. Yes, absolutely. Isn't it interesting they
call Venus Earth's twin when I feel like Mars should be its twin. I think Mars is
a little bit bigger than Earth, right? Well, twin, but just just their vibe, the
five. Venus is so I don't think Earth is Earth is not doing tick tocks with
Venus and me and my that's my twin in him. No
Venus and Earth are kind of like the twins where it's the two twins who have
rain ones rainbow one the goth yeah exactly yeah speaking of twins Venus and
Serena Serena is definitely the Earth. Why didn't they name her Earth? That's
I've been asking that Venus and Earth Earth Williams.
they name for earth. They are the right there. Serena's she is the earth. I bet
that's her middle name. She's by far the better twin. Is she really yeah dude and
she has a earth style. She looks like earth. She plays a game that's for the
style and her play around earth game. Can you pull that up her, but a giant
round, but you pull up a picture of a giant round, but the tennis ball is kind
of like earth. If it had no ocean, that's and had a wax, a white Grand Canyon wall
old China combo that went all the way around in an interesting pattern. A
tennis ball could be a tiny planet and we don't even know. I think about this,
we're kind of, all of our atoms are like planets as well. Yeah, that's true. Do
you guys think that if you zoomed out far enough, we are basically, basically
the planet?
We're toenails on Earth's floor. Yeah, I mean, I guess we could be toenails.
That's incredible. Like stinky atoms on a disgusting nail. Stinky atoms is a
good, is a good atoms family cousin. Wouldn't that suck if we found out that
We are the toenail of a guy named Dave. I do think about that pretty often. We zoom out really far and we're part of something's body.
Yeah. We're germs. I think we definitely are germs.
It is making me think a lot about... Germs.
Germs or no, it's making me think that like
there's no guys on Venus at all.
There's no... That we...
It's true that we know of. It's been making me really scared at night ever since we started the 5 Weeks of Planet.
Ever since we started this I have just been thinking like... It's been making me feel so small.
like oh my god the universe is so big we're nothing man we're complete and
we're not and we're only talking about the Milky Way we're going past the man
literally doesn't matter what you do here man. No, nothing matters at all.
Venus is in the Milky Way. That's disgusting. Oh, you said Venus, sir. My
Venus. Yeah, he said Venus, bro. My bad, my bad. I'm so glad God put my Venus in
the Milky Way. It sounds like vagina penis. Yeah. What about a planet called
the vagina. I was worried. I'm glad that it that's the real twin of Venus,
vagina, Venus and Pagina
damn when I pulled out my Pagina. That's what it would be called. That's what
they would call the Venus's moon is vagina vagina. Did you guys say vagina
when you were a kid? Yes, how much people always say that how often you
say in vagina as a child a lot because you tell your friends. I heard there's
something called a vagina. Yeah, I would say it a lot. I never said vagina. Yeah,
I said it still don't say every single day. I said it every single day guys
really guys really made out like bandits in the name. Why do I feel like that's
a word trump would say but he would say folks they're touching my vagina.
That's like my little brother, so they're pulling they're pulling my pants
down and touching my vagina. That's nasty wait who's doing that's not right.
That's not right. Stay that's the D. They should be doing that to try it
doesn't matter who it is. It is pulling down my
touching my vagina. They're touching it. Does he? He doesn't sound too happy
about it. He's getting assaulted by the deep state, man. Yeah, that's what he
says all the time. He says he's getting assaulted by the deep state. Fucking
finger him. They're trying to finger my vagina. No, that's nasty. They're saying
I smell, they're saying my vagina smells like skate. Why the hell would they
skate the fish? They're naming a specific fish.
naming a specific fish that my vagina smells like. Why the hell would they
finger it if they thought it smelled like a sting? What the hell are you doing with my pants down
touching my vagina? I don't like this man. You don't like this? It's really nasty. How is this
nasty? It's fucking Trump getting sexually... Trump has a vagina. We don't do this kind of
podcast man. We don't. We're a science podcast. What if Trump was getting sexually assaulted in
his vagina by the deep state? We say stuff like... Well what if he said I like it. That makes it
reason. No listen and on this part now that we love it, we're not going to do
to we're not going to trump impressions like that. We're going to do stuff like
for example trump. I don't maybe I love it. I'm on Venus and I'm appreciating
the scientific marvels of this planet. Yes, that's a good trumpet. Okay, now do
that okay. We're traveling through the solar system and learning as we go
yeah
learning amazing things
learning, completely amazing thing is educational comedy mother to make a life
after the entire
stop it.
I watched him on a spaceship and he's going to every planet. He's getting
off and he's I had a guide a great trip to Mercury today. It was very cold
Mercury worst planet I've ever seen in the sun came up and it got very, very
hot, completely, completely, must be the hottest planet ever besides Venus.
This is a walk. There's nothing but gray wait. How is is Mars hotter? Sorry,
never mind. Never mind. I haven't unlocked it yet. I'll save it. Mars is
the hottest planet in the solar system. But why isn't Earth mega hot as well?
Well, it will be soon. 'Cause we have more zone. Yeah. It's the zone. We got
more zone on us. Well, what I learned from my barber today is global warming,
it's not real. The Earth just goes through periods. That's what my father
said. That's what my parents said growing up, too. Yeah. And he said that's...
That's the most common belief about global warming, I think. It's very... At
least until recently. I think recently people started believing. I believe that
man bear pig caused it.
Okay, but you know who's making it worse?
Turd sandwich
slash douche
making it worse man.
Oh election day is very soon. It's election day. I don't even think I'm
registered. Is that next year? No, there's a there's a there's a local
the election day. I was running
they're running. I don't know guys. I think I might out of those two options. I
honestly feel like I might vote for Pedro. That's a good idea. That's a good
member Pedro
member Pedro.
Yeah, I think that turd sandwich. I think Pedro has integrity straight up
through no fucking doubt.
Yep, God, I need to watch that show again. Seventeen thousand dollars a
member Pedro Pedro has Tegrity I'm voting for Pedro instead of a douche
entered.
We make seventeen thousand dollars a month, so we can do stuff like that.
Yeah, that's true. You know what we did spend some money on? Oh yeah. Big mouth
billy bass right there up on the wall, man. Yep. That's an amazing. That's a
type of animal that could live on Venus, a fish. Yeah. Because they're oceans? No.
I just want to say this before. I was thinking of a flying fish that could swim
through gas. Oh, that can talk? I thought, yeah. Because this one's up on, this
one's up flying. I guess that's true. Before, before we move on from South Park
completely. Yeah. I just want to say that me and my friend Rupert kept sending
Dumois blind items that were like this dime square scene stir killed and made
a killed and made a boy eat his parents at a chili cook. I wish to remain
anonymous. What the hell is Dumois? You don't know. Dumois is like the
celebrity like gossip thing or it's like like things will show up on their
Dumois is like you don't know the celebrity gossip. Maybe I would do a
Professor gossip. Yeah, right. My professor. Yeah, that's my version. I
don't know who there's like some shit that Dumois put out that everyone was
like this is like so amazing blah blah blah and it's just like so like it's
just stupid catty celebrity gossip and yeah, we're just sending them a bunch of
shit saying like Cartman just Cartman stories.
This
This celebrity pretended to be Osimo at a music video.
(laughter)
We were probably doing that for like an hour.
That is funny actually.
That is actually awesome.
I really think that that would be
maybe the logical conclusion to our careers
is that we get hired to be
On Dumois?
On TMZ type?
No, on South Park.
We would be so good at TMZ.
Matt and Trey, you think we'd be good at TMZ?
I would be really, really good. You would be bad at teams because you get shy
about talking to the celebrity. I would I'd would be so fucking good and TMZ. I
love talking shit so much. Oh, my God, and I could wear all sorts of disguises.
I'd be good. I would literally be I would literally be interviewing. I'd be on
the street as a proper at sea talking to the celebrities, interviewing them,
saying like, Oh, my God, I love your dress. Who did your hair and then they'd
leave? I go, What a fucking bitch Jesus Christ. I would be breaking news. I
breaking news. I need is a bit that conversation sucked. He's not a good
conversation.
One of the biggest celebrities in the world and just turning what a fucking
fucking fucking surprise so mean. Probably she seemed like she wanted to
fuck me too,
but I was not into she's honestly fucking ugly to me. I think I'd be good
to be a good Harvey Levin type. I'd be good at having a 32 no the 32 ounce mug.
you know I'm sipping my that's on the t and I just go. What do we got and I
that is really you would be really go like I got something for you, Bella
hadid's a bitch and she dressed ugly on our date and then I would say
I went on a date with this girl Angelina Jolie, which is me outside
taking photos of her feet. I went on a date with Angelina Jolie and she and
then you a cup of coffee. I'd be raising my hand really politely and then you
call me and I'll be like
Helena Gomez showed cleavage on instagram. What that crap she's a slut
for that I would just say all the celebrities who showed cleavage on
instagram and I'd just be like slut alert
and then sit from my big my big thing and just you know somebody at the slut
button yeah it'd be you know it'd be in there. Lawrence wore shorts in a movie.
Oh
whore tastic that this bitch is a slut
and it's a big thing. It's like a pre made old fashion in there. No, you
look like you have like a one of those big water bottles, like a hamster water
bottle. You're trying to suck a smoothie that has too much banana in it. It's
ten minutes to get up. It's not getting through the straw. The straw is small.
The straw is very small. You look like a warhead. Yeah. The straw is trying so
hard, taking deep breaths. No, these are my cheekbones.
Yeah, I got my buccal fat removed. What's the deal with buccal fat, man? I
know but some of these celebrities have been getting their buccal fats out and I
don't know if I I thought that was a but a name for a butt yeah I guess buccal I
realized it's like mouth it means mouth like like bouche like French bouche
speaking of great do I look great like this Patrick look Patrick looks best I
think Patrick looks bad because some I didn't notice that he only has like a
a quarter size cheek. His cheek is lower than you think.
I didn't know that.
What about me?
You look cute. You actually look cute. You look like you're just
sucking on a warhead. You look like,
what's that skinny girl's name? Bella Hadid. No, the actress from Ant.
Ant. Anya Taylor-Joy. Ant from Opie and Anthony. Yeah, Anya Taylor-Joy.
Did you guys ever see that movie, The Menu? No. That was the worst.
That was the worst movie I've ever seen in my life. I thought you were going to say The Minion, too.
Yeah, I did not want to. I saw the trailers for that movie so many times. I thought it
looked so stupid. I could not believe that people wanted to see that movie from the trailer.
I thought that looked annoying, but you know what I did watch was all of the Babish videos
about it. I saw that. I saw that. Andrew Ray. I heard that it ends with a cheeseburger.
Respect to Babish. Babish, if you are hearing this, we need you to come next month for Christmas.
We need you to come here and make us a Christmas dinner.
No, not a Christmas dinner.
We need to make the four course meal of all of the recipes we created.
I'm still on this.
You think Babish needs to do a P.O.W.L. episode?
I think Babish needs to do a Podcast About List episode with us.
How come he's never done any shit like that?
You can do Venture Bros, but you can't do P.O.W.L. man.
What has more cultural cachet?
He did Venture Bros?
Yeah.
He also has a--
He made the food from Venture Bros.
What food is from Venture Bros?
Spaghetti and meatballs.
Or maybe he didn't do that.
Maybe somebody else did.
Is there spaghetti and meatballs?
There's a bunch of food on there.
I don't remember there being food in that show at all.
There's food.
I'm sure people eat food, but I'm not imagining--
Never mind.
A different guy did the drinks from Venture Bros.
Oh, I remember the wrong--
Oh.
There's tons of drinks in that, apparently.
Did he do Fortnite?
Fortnite chug juice.
Yeah, he's made his chug juice before.
Noah tried to make me a chug juice.
I want the sheal mushroom, man.
It's that guy, How to Drink.
You ever see him?
you know, I might have he's like just a big but kind of looks. I just watch I
just watched Korean videos with Julio called giant shrimp mistaken as lobster.
Oh, yeah, the only time I watch a five hour video basically every other day
called the downfall of SpongeBob when I was living. I just watch I watch. Yeah,
I watch either. I watch either most incredible shining sparkly pork meat ever
sold on street. Yeah. And then I watch the history of every tool ever made by
the human race.
That sounds fun.
My YouTube channel is connected to the TV and my old roommate Neil would make fun of me
all the time.
He's not that old.
Well, he's not my old roommate.
He doesn't live with me anymore.
He would bring this up all the time to every single person that knows who I am.
He opened up the YouTube one day and there was a video that was pretty much almost all
all the way watched about the downfall of White Castle and he told every single
person that I know that I watched a fucking two hour. It's fine. It is such a
life saver to me that my girlfriend's YouTube is logged into the TV, so it's
all vlogs when I turn it on and it's I don't have to be assaulted with the
horrible things. I'm mine is mine. Any time my wife turns on the TV to watch a
video of a lady walking through a house, she always has to scroll by like ten
videos of guys playing blackjack. Yeah, and I yeah, sorry, fuck you. Yeah, it's all
the trying to try videos. Yeah, too lazy to try Kevin Hart wore a dress and he's
in the Illuminati. Yeah, and I'm going, oh, I don't know. I watch too many. I
watch too many Elden Ring PVP clips and now my entire recommend front page on
YouTube is just all videos of guys with beards and it's like Elden Ring run, but
is epic. I'll do a mean character. Damn mine will be some of the smartest thing
you've things you've ever seen in your entire life, like something about kind
of Kierkegaard or Camus that type of thing very kind of cool videos that are
eleven minutes long and then a four hour video about Rocco's modern life. Yeah,
and these are kind of staggered because you have to listen. You can have candy,
but you got to eat your best. Yeah, that's true. That my vegetables is
Theanderthal videos. My, I guess... There are vegetable videos. Am I just only eating
candy? And you like, every once in a while, you crave the vegetable videos. I think I'm
only, yeah, I guess my vegetable... You're a full candy video? I watch a vegetable video
every once in a while. My vegetable videos are... I only watch vegetable videos right
now, I think. Yeah, you're only watching like... I go in phases where I'll go full veggie.
I used, I think I, I think I basically, I was over-served in candy in my, my young adult
life and I can't, I can't do it anymore. Can't no more candy for you. No, yeah. What was
used to fall asleep to eating can. I'm about half it. I'm about half and half.
I try to fall asleep to the best. I used to I used to every night fall asleep to
eating five hours
yeah. It's not good for you make you a bad. So now I just try to if I have some
down time, I'll eat some vegetables between three and four last night and I
better dreams. If I if the last video I watch is a vegetable versus a candy last
night, I watch a candy video before I went to bed and I had a dream that I was
trapped in a million stack of pancakes. Whoa today this morning I was woken up
because my girlfriend was in bed next to me and she sneezed and it it startled me
really bad when I woke up like I went and then I looked over at her and I don't
remember this because I still mostly sleep, but I looked at her like this.
I was really, really mad. I woke up twice last night. One was from the pancake
thing, but the first time I woke up was I woke up. I was having a dream where I
was fight. I was doing like Kung Fu or something and a woman in a red gi was
coming at me and I woke up doing it. I literally jumped out of bed doing this
and then I just and then I just had to and I before I even process what I'd
done. I was going to the bathroom to piss, but I ran up with my hands cocked
lethal weapons ready to kill him. I woke up like five times last night because
the tickets for the new Godzilla movie went on sale during last night, but they
went on there. There was no time time what they were going on sales. I thought
they're going to be at midnight and then they didn't my body. I was like I'm
I was going to set an alarm for like six AM and wake up and try to get them, but
my body woke me up like every hour to check naturally. I had a natural clock
for my body wanting to Christmas, Christmas, but yeah, and then Pierce
got them for me. I still get Christmas sleep on Christmas and I don't even get
anything for yeah. I get Christmas sleep before if I have anything to do the next
day.
I have to go to the grocery store. The next day I have Christmas. Christmas
sleep is one of the worst sleeps you'll ever have. You know, absolutely I
- I, during Christmas, I wake up and I,
or I'll wake up 40 times on Christmas Eve night,
and then I wake up and I get nothing.
- There's nothing to have.
- But I just like the spirit of it so much
that I love spirit.
- You know what I got for Christmas?
- Spirit Christmas would be a good store.
- For Christmas two years ago,
my aunt buys like all this shit.
- Your aunt's buy.
- My aunt buys all this shit in advance.
So she doesn't really like vet anything.
She doesn't ask my mom, like,
"Oh, would so-and-so wear this?"
And two years ago, she got me this True Religion V-neck.
That's beast, dude.
Did I? I think I gave that to you.
No.
All right. It was in the costume closet for sure.
It might have been destroyed in the flood.
No.
But it was like metallic,
overprint True Religion V-neck.
That is so sick.
And it was like two sizes too small.
It's like something that like the guys who wear,
who like give ethical loan samples at the mall would wear.
You should wear a dress like that.
Dude, I should, maybe I should get those biker jeans.
My aunt Phyllis was giving away until the last couple of years.
She was giving away just,
she bought a bunch of gift cards a long time ago and then would just give them
away. Cause they lasted like three years or whatever.
And one time I did get an expired Blockbuster gift card for Christmas after
Blockbuster had, it was like the year that it just didn't exist anymore.
and she just nobody told her. She was really upset when I was like...
My aunt got me the Game of Thrones trivia game.
You got me something that doesn't exist?
Literally doesn't exist. This money is just gone.
This is nothing?
There is nothing.
It's just a piece of plastic.
You have no recourse.
Yeah.
My aunt got me the game of... the same aunt got me the Game of Thrones trivia cards, like
Game of Thrones trivia game.
Why are we not playing that?
I've never watched it in my life.
I watched the first season.
I watched three seasons.
I watched I think one season. I read a bunch of them. I read like two and a half of the
books and then I read the, well watched the first season. So I could probably be okay
at it. You'd be better at that game than me. I know some of the characters names. Daenerys
Targaryen y'all. What is that? She's the queen. She's basically the dragon queen. Okay. She
gets, I know what's his name? Aquaman fucks her. Thule. Fucked. Who's Thule? I just made
him up. Oh, there's a guy with no penis. There's a guy named Theon. He has no balls I guess.
Theon. Oh yeah, I remember that guy. What was that called? A eunuch. There's a eunuch in
it. Did they cut your balls and your dick off? I don't know. I think just your balls
maybe. What's Dinka's name in the show? Dinka's name is Dinka. No, Dinka. Lil' Dinka. Who's
Dinka? Peter Dinka. Oh, Peter Dinklage? Peter Dinka? Tyrion. Tyrion. Tyrion Lannister. Oh,
The Lannisters and they're fucking each other man.
The Lannisters, the Targaryens, the Starks, the Monsters.
That's all I know.
The Dragons.
Leo was telling me this story, I forget who it was but he was saying that like.
I know who's story it was.
Whose was it?
Jeremy Lovix.
Oh okay.
And you're stealing it bro.
No I'm, yeah I guess I'm stealing it but it still makes me laugh so hard.
He was doing some like improv show or something before a jazz band and then the jazz band like
no one liked the improv show and then the jazz band went up and was like, "Get a load of
those guys." And then the crowd was like, "Yeah, ha ha ha," was on his side and he said, "Alright,
I guess I should tell a joke now. Peter Dinka is the most famous midget of all time." That
was the whole joke.
Yeah. Yeah, I mean I'd be laughing if Jeremy told me that maybe because that was his story.
Yeah, Jeremy, that's your story.
You gotta apologize right now.
I gotta apologize.
Can you punch in on me?
Jeremy, it's your friend Patrick.
I told a third hand story of yours.
Do you have like a sad song you can play?
I'm trying to figure it out.
Wait, I got a sad song.
Alright, just start talking and I'll fade in the sad song.
Hey Jeremy, it's your friend Patrick.
I am a little bit under the weather.
There's a lot going on in my life right now that's making me a little bit fucked up.
And I told the third-hand story of yours and I told it wrong.
I apologize.
What are you doing?
Is this not genuine?
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Can you start it over?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey Jeremy, Levick from the Jeremy and Rajat video series. It's your friend Patrick Dorn
from Podcast About List. I told a third hand story that our friend Leo, Darth Erogenous
on Twitter told me, and it wasn't my story.
(laughing)
- Wait, that was actually fire.
It can't be that, you know.
- Yep.
- All right, Venus.
- You ghosted.
We never talk about you again, man.
- We didn't even want to talk about you on this show.
And you know what?
There's gonna be a Hit 'Em Up style track releasing soon.
- With all three of us.
all three of us rapping about how fucking bunk you are. What do we have
dropping next on the next week of planets?
We got a painting, Mercury, Venus, a new painting from, from,
what's my painting name? DJ Alamos
about Mars, about Mars. We will have a Mars planet report as well. And what
will we have also? We are gonna have a collab of the century.
Maybe an old friend might stop by. Maybe an old musical friend of ours. And you might
know who it is. And our new musical friend. Our new musical friend will be collaborating
with our old musical friend from our American Idol episode. So be on the lookout for that.
And be on the lookout for me in Chicago tomorrow. And guys, November 17th, the biggest show ever
for
not a bad idea. I got bad news. What's that? What's the bad news? We have a
mid-earth threshold. Oh my gosh. Wait, okay, we have a change.org petition. I
didn't even realize we did this. I forgot that we did this. I forgot about this
too. 21 signatures, we need four more signatures for guys to leave the galaxy.
Basically, we're trying to make it known that we don't want to leave the galaxy,
With space travel advancing at a rapid rate, it seems as though civilian space travel to
outer space is a thing of the past and will soon be in the age of outer galaxy travels.
With some of our brightest minds, Elon Musk's Dave Chappelle and Mark Zuckerberg might think
This is a good idea.
Visual storytellers, EA, Ubisoft, Nintendo,
have already been warning us for decades
that this might be a really bad idea.
That's why we as Podcast About List invite you all,
want to invite you all, the world,
to let our global representatives know
that we feel like we shouldn't leave our galaxy
for the sake of not signaling our position
and invite cosmic horrors and space bandits into our home.
Please guys, let's not leave the galaxy.
And then this is a Mass Effect 2.
- Your contact lenses just arrived.
1-800-CONTACTS. They can't have my brand. I have special eyes.
Sleep with your special eyes.
My brand!
Wow. A Source Filmmaker video.
And Abraham Stewart says it's too scary.
Steven Washington, I like this galaxy. It's fine. Why do we need another galaxy?
He said, "What owe we Neif another one for anyway?"
Exactly. That's what I've been saying.
We don't want oafs and doofuses signing our thing. It dilutes our point.
you all reasons. How many supporters do we have right now? Twenty one twenty one
supporters, so one one. Can you do something for me? Not can you send this
petition to four friends? Can you do this? Everybody text this petition to
everybody in your contact or you'll be
send out a blast unless you want to get dead spaced man, I don't know blast or
something and tell them to check out the five weeks of planets. Ask people if
they know about the five. Here's a script you can use for telling people the
five weeks of plans that I've already been using with some of my friends.
Hello? You say, "Hey, have you heard about the five weeks of planets?"
They say, if they say no, you know what you say? You will soon.
Oh, and if they say yes? That's it.
Oh, that's it. Okay. If they say yes. If they say yes, say cool.
Cool, me too. I've heard of that.
Yeah, I also know about it.
All right, boy. I'll see you later.
And you guys, I need to debut my new single.
Okay, I want to hear it.
My new single under my new space rapping name
OJ the alien. All right. I want to hear this shit. Okay. Are you guys are you all seeing this? I'm listening to your stream mate
Mercury, I'm gonna fly to you Mercury, I'm at your knee and you
*music*
See I'm doing an alien voice. I hear that.
Mercury, I'm gonna fly to you. Mercury, imagine me and you. Mercury, I'm gonna fly to you. Mercury, imagine me and you.
Mercury, let me fuck on you one time
Hope I make you wet with my dope rhyme
On this planet you age like a fine wine
So around you look like a fine time
Put my nut in you like a Clark car
I put my butt on you but I won't fart
Pull my spaceship here like a pair of hearts
Got my clothes and shoes they from Primark
Mercury, let me fuck on you one time
Hope I make you wet with my dope rhyme
Like a fine line?
I'd let the Adobe Premiere do the transcription.
I think that was a... I should've double-checked that.
Mercury, imagine me and you, Mercury.
*Growl*