(upbeat music)
- Good, hearty clap.
- Uh-huh.
- Hearty, beautiful clap.
- You guys, I got a couple of recipes
for alcoholic beef stew.
I got a few people, I put out the bat signal,
the stew signal, I put it out.
I got a couple things, somebody told me
to put powdered alcohol in it, and I got too scared.
but you didn't you got to scared you didn't do it. Well, no, I read you about
it. I read things about people getting sent to the hospital for consuming
powdered alcohol. Well, they probably weren't consuming it cut with beef. Did
we already talk about we're going to we're going to booth the beef stew? We're
going to say that yeah, because then it yeah, yeah, it'll be stronger. You get
more of the beef flavor. He's the
no, but I got a we all wear gym short. We
and then a good idea and then we get in a jumping competition with yeah. That's
a good idea. I'm actually in a mattress. Oh my God, a big funnel, a big funnel of
our but we should go to a mattress to go to a mattresses and more or whatever we
believe is for move the beef stew and then we have a jumping competition on a
bed and see who leaks more beef yeah wow.
I was told to just put Guinness in at the end of the beef in the bow. That's
we're not alcoholic enough. Yeah, that's very low. I can't even think about we
are doing all right. Let's not I can't even think about this because yeah,
we're not what we're going to be talking about. You started Jupiter. It's
Jupiter today and you started with beef.
I got beef y'all boofed beef. First thing you know, as beef man, this is
actually hurting me so badly. What's beef guys? I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
It's just that fucking Ethan and Hassan are fucking fighting. Oh, bro. They're
writing man. It's over political differences. I heard that I heard
sleep. I mean I heard that Hassan was begging Ethan to go back on what he
said. Really? And I heard that Ethan said that I'm gonna say what I said.
Yeah, I said what I said. I meant what I meant. An elephant's word is
100%. That's what he said. That's what he said. Straight the fuck up.
He said that shit. He should have said a teddy's word. He stood on
business. He should have said a teddy's word is 100% because of his
that is an intrusive thought I had. I was trying to fall asleep and I thought
probably a thousand times in a row, just he's standing on business over and over
for no reason. Guys, this is my new favorite thing to say. Y'all standing on
me. I'm literally looking at guys who are at sitting at bus stops, looking at
them and thinking brainily. He's standing on standing up and I swear to God I was
trying to fall asleep and that was keeping me awake. What genius came up
with stood on where it is who said that recently the best shit I ever heard man.
I just heard Noah say at one time Noah is the filter of which I get like all like
teenage lingo from. And Noah said, he said something about, did he stand on bidness,
talking about our friend Chad, like making mac and cheese or something. He was like,
he stood on bidness when he made that mac and cheese. And I was like, I don't know what
you said, man, but I'm going to say that every day for the rest of my life.
Yeah. I can hear Noah in his room sometimes just watching. It's just like I can hear a
million tic talks per minute, just like yeah, like I can hear the scroll like
the
it doesn't go. That's how fast he's watching him three times. He's pumping.
That's how
it's like. It's like sending the mail tube. Yeah, he's got a vacuum tube with
different phones that go into his room. I need to be shrunk down and sent in. Oh
my God, I want to be putting a pressurized to see the you know, you
know where else you would die if you were to succumb to the pressure.
Jupiter, yes Jupiter, y'all we made it it's day
five right for for next saturn is five mercury venus mars. Oh my God, Jupiter
for well. So if you really want to get into it, it's week to day to week to
episode to a so to the five weeks of planets part for guys. This is about to
blow your mind man. We're talking about Jupiter today. We're fine. We're out of
the fucking terrestrial planets. We're done. God rocky pieces of shit. Yeah, I
it's on to the gas giants and this that's what this is for gas man. There
is just got it more gas, nothing but get all gas, no rocks. I just got it. We
should have him on the show through space
all
to
doing
landing on Neptune.
He's interviewing an alien, but then he's interviewing the aliens on the
other side of the planets that they have beef with to show that basically
we're all the same alien. He's interviewing the alien Neptune. The
and he's like
anti backs and he's like whoa man, whoa, you don't believe in the vaccine, huh?
Autism
huh,
wow, cool, five hundred million dollars
direct deposit into his bank account. He got mad at me one time because he
thought I was trying to have sex with his mom. True story,
true, true story. I stood on business. I stood on business. I'll say it dude.
Now that he's now that he's persona non grata. I can say this story guys. One
time I was at a bar, my friend Xavier walks in says there's a milf at this
bar. I want to have sex with a milf. I go dude. I fucking love milfs. Let me
see the milf. We walk outside. He points at a woman says there's the milf and
brace belt and says what are you guys doing? I said we're looking for a milf
and Andrew Callahan sitting right next to him and he says
and then Xavier says man that with the milf is Andrew Callahan's
and then I guess he told people that he wanted to fight me later. Yep
Oh, that feels good to get off my chest.
Yeah, that was two years ago.
That was two years ago.
Is that the first time we've ever done?
That was the day we got back from North Carolina.
That was the first, that was literally like after we got off the plane,
after we recorded with Uncle Matt for the first time.
And he's a big guy, dude.
He would beat the shit out of me.
Who, Uncle Matt?
Andrew Callen.
Oh, he's not that big.
Uncle Matt, we put Andrew and Uncle Matt in a ring together.
Look at Uncle Matt, just hear him.
He might be little and a little scrawny and maybe a little pudgy too somehow,
both at the same time.
me know him, but you get you get in the ring with him. He's going to start using
some type of
I wasn't
and you think sure I'm going to be able to fucking one punch to the face. This
guy's flying through the wall, but no, then he pulls out the anime hair powers.
His hair is going to be entangling or he's staring you or he says, bro. I'm so
drunk. Get the fuck over here. I go. I can't help myself. Dude, you're so hot.
I got or you get in the ring with him. You're about to throw a punch. He
straight up pulls out the mic and makes you reveal a secret about yes, yes,
twist it on you. Yeah, you seem like the bad guy now. Exactly did I'm now I'm
sitting in the he's going to put a mic and say so. Do you like do you like
Mills or do you hate Mills? I'll be like dude Mills are fucking epic to the
maximum man and I like to wave my own farts in front of my face. Oh, why'd I
say that? Oh my God, my life's ruined. You're the part guy who just have a
power to call me a Mac
and I'm for Mac. I'm on no jumper. You're a
bees with absent words
and that's on far.
I did that on far. I stood on fart when I did that
fart Mac gas giant. There we go. All gas in face.
You're walking around with the suit in the Mike and you're just saying can I
for in your face
fart on you. Yeah. Straight up. We should just start doing that show man. Yeah. All gas, no
farts. Yeah. I mean, that's anytime somebody gets canceled, you should literally, you should
just like if they have a show on HBO, you should just show up to HBO and be like straight
up. I'll just keep doing it bro. I directed Chinatown. I'll do it. Yeah. I'll do Chinatown
too. I directed Chinatown. I directed Rosemary's Baby. Ro-Mary. Ro-Mary Baby. Yeah. Which is
a good idea row Mary by you
Omer baby down at the I roll I do retty Romano. I had to roll the canoe and by
you row Mary baby Mary. I had to marry a baby down at the by
down there on the road. I knew Roge, oh fuck was it was a devil down. There was
a devil. It was a
devil down that baby of baby was the devil.
That's the first thing that I see you meet a Cajun guy in the bar. The first
he says to you is that baby was a devil.
Well, that's what they should do. I was married, baby, you know those old
videos, Roman Popeye ski, you know those video,
you know those videos where it's like old
people walking out of like jaws or something or star wars theater. They
should do that in Louisiana and see it so yeah, they are
everybody
baby, the devil when it's somebody walking out of like they'll be walking
like revenge of the Sith and they'll they'll get the Mike and the reason
like say that was like the greatest movie. I ever saw
they're talking
now see dog. Vadas has taken a new turn yeah. This is what you never anybody
talking. It's from like two thousand yeah. It's from twenty years ago and
they're like now God and state is one of the best movies. I've ever seen
that breath has done it again yeah. It's a screening of
the Harry Potter seven in l a and someone's like I say
the
fire now. Now listen Hagrid is back
Hagrid was
who stood who stood on business the most in the Harry Potter movie.
Ron Weasley, Ron or Dudley feel like it's got to be snake Dudley was
talking was Dudley was a bitch bro. Dudley became a hero at the end. He
became no, he did not, but okay, not a great in a story. He was did not become
a hero at the end and also he did not stand on business. The most he did not
sit on business. He maybe did one or two times near the end. He made a fucking
squealing pig. Maybe at the end he maybe became certified. He became certified
for sure certified definitely became certified. Stay, but stood on this more
than anybody in every single Harry Potter. Move actually right. It was
fucking snape snape sure he's on business like no other man. So he
popped in Voldemort. He popped his O. G. He's
he stood on business because he got broken by Harry Potter's mom. He was so
in love with her. He wanted to know he's heartbroken, you know, heartbroken,
that he stood on some within he came back and you're so bad. I've become Mr.
Potter. I've become Sigma.
I've become sick, but can you imagine those snape completely trying to hit on
if you're a girl and Snape is coming up to you and he's like, "Oh, you should come over.
We'll watch Netflix tonight." "Show me your butt." "We can watch Harry Potter." "We can
Netflix and chill if you know what I mean." "Show me your butthole." No, you don't say
that again. "Show me your butt." He wouldn't say, "Show me your butt." "Butt-over, cadaver."
He's texting her and he's texting her a picture of two little baby pandas or something and
he's like, "This is us. This is so us." "That is you and me." "This is completely us." It's
forgive for the penguin with its yeah
that is he made to any man who tries to talk to you prove it.
I'm glad he died. Personally, yeah, he was kind of a creep. I hear yeah. Well,
he literally made evil potions, but yeah, that was his job at. It's not much
of an excuse to be into the dark arts to do it to defend one child. The dark
arts is the teacher that they rotated out every year because of yes things
happening. Yes, kind of a stupid that writing kind of stupid writing. Why?
Because it's gay and that's on BD. Not on BD is not the same as business man. You
can't say BD dude. Harry Potter is gay and that's on business. There we go, that's
better. Yeah, there we go. You can say that. Yeah. BD I think is a gang related
thing. Oh heavens. Yeah, you don't want any. Oh me? I don't want to say that. I
I want to say on BD then unless BD is a bull Durham,
my favorite movie.
What the fuck is a bull Durham? It's a movie about baseball.
Okay, not my favorite movie. I'm more of an angel than an outfield kind of guy.
I was trying to be the most honky I could be. All right, y'all, Jupiter.
Jupiter, man. We have been distracted. You know what? Let's start with the
outfits. Let's start with the outfits. Okay. So me, I got the Jupiter
coloration. I know it's a little more saturated than Jupiter actually is, but
some of the pictures you'll see it's got this kind of deep orangish color with
the lighter stuff interspersed and it's got the important part about Jupiter,
it's got clouds and stuff, so I feel like I got the clouds going on. Yeah,
you got red. And then up here, I got the great red spot, which we'll learn
about, I'm sure. Oh, yeah, I'm looking forward to that. But I got the red
spot up on top of the hat. And your bike's a red spot as well. That's two,
I got two red spots on them. You probably didn't even need the hat. Double
Jupiter, Jupiter. Yeah, Double Jupiter, that's a good... Jupiter, Jupiter. That'd
be a cool name for something. Then I have this Jupiter kind of style shirt.
If this was all blended together... This is a good Jupiter shirt. This is a
This is all blended together.
Jupiter, I mean, it does.
That's the pattern.
And then this is supposed to be the dot.
I thought that the dot was more orange, but then I got beige pants on and then.
Blue shoes on blue shoes on man.
You are.
Let me let you just you gave him the Sharon Stone, man.
It's crazy.
Holy Sharon Stone.
That was a new type of Sharon Stone.
That was like doing that in the movie.
but she like she's on one of these chairs in her butt. Keep what I saw was like if
Sharon Stone was hatching out of an egg in that movie,
like she was like pressing against the membrane. Nobody does nobody's rock.
Nobody fucks with how come the camel toe gets so much so much beloving love, but
nobody loves moose knuckle no more. Who is who's rocking with camel toe? I love
fucking camels. I'll do girl. Every guy's love camel toes. I don't know any
guy that's like I'm and you're hanging with the wrong crowd. If you're if your
circle is not
moose knuckle knuckle but but toe but toe but toe but toe sea urchin. We call
that
the but the butthole camel toe is the sea urchin sea urchin is crazy. Wow but
the whole sea urchin is crazy. It is. That's crazy. That's so gross. Shut up
bitch. That is so because it's a hairy spiky object is that it's got a
seeing that on a but I seen him. You see no sea urchin. I seen him all
way around.
Let me walk you through my outfit. Okay, okay,
brown hat.
What's that?
For some of the brown, it's on the
cream. Perfect. I would say perfect to Jupiter colored hoodie, right? Yeah, I
got some green same green pants. There's a little bit of green in the Jupiter
thing. In the photo I saw, the photo I used as a reference for my painting,
which we'll get to later, and brown shoes. And guys, there's another layer
to this. Well, there's two layers. Is it the round spot of your head? No.
Your red head? No, no, no, there's actually many layers. I don't have a
red head. I'm pink, if anything. If any colour, I'm pink. I have a round,
bald head, which reminds you of a planet, especially because of its size.
but then also I take this off. Oh my God, I would eat high die. But wait guys,
guess what I made in this shirt the other day. Let me get spaghetti sauce
and guess what it gave me a red spot. A red spot. A red spot. Wow. Got the
red dot, make your head high. Holy shit. I feel like we killed it. I feel
like you guys killed it a little more than me. I feel like we all killed
it a little. I think you have been on some shit lately.
you've been on one you've been crushing it. So we have a kind of representing
different aspects of the of different colors. You can see if you search images
of Jupiter. Yeah, if you look up Jupiter color palette like I did, if you're
seeing one that's about that's teaching kids about planets, you're gonna see
something that looks more like me, orange and red. Yeah, but for the real adult
scientists who don't need bright colors to care about the planet, it's the
pastel. Who is the most looking like Jupiter? Subscribe in the comments down
below, subscribe below, subscribe below and let us know. I'm loving our energy
We are on one. Yeah, we are on one. I have this kind of, I got, I went today to Middle Village
Bagels. Oh, that's nice. And I got an egg bagel, which is, I found out when I, I got a bacon,
egg and cheese, and cream cheese on an egg bagel. I found out an egg bagel is more of
a dessert style bagel that tastes like a donut. Not a bad move though. It was good, but it
was a bit of a slap in the face. Yeah. And I got some Italian wedding soup, guys. And
I was eating the Italian wedding soup with the tiny little meatballs. And I was thinking,
Dude, these meatballs might as well be planets.
- They look like Jupiter.
- And these tiny pieces of couscous.
- Planets have been everywhere lately.
- These might as well be fucking stars.
And the vegetables could be a vegetable that's flying around.
- A space vegetable, space veggie.
- 'Cause we don't know.
There's so many mysteries in the cosmos.
- Imagine the type of vegetable that would grow on Jupiter.
- Should I go ahead and do the Jupiter planet report?
Are we ready?
- Yeah, I'm ready.
- All right, I need to see this.
I need to hear this.
Join us once again on a five week galactic journey through our solar
system.
Be prepared to learn and to laugh a little too.
And now the Planet Report with Cameron Fetter.
So I changed the background music this time 'cause somebody in the comments
last time said that it made them, always made them think the episode was over
because it is the outro music, which I guess makes a lot of sense when I
think about it. I can make you a new song. Well, I made one for myself.
I think the episode is only people, but I think the episodes fifteen minutes. I
made a new planet song for you and this one's on the last time I did poetry.
This one is more a little more comedic, so if you could imagine I mean, if maybe
if we had the resources I could be standing, you can imagine me standing up
with a red curtain and a microphone. We can hold a pause right now. Let me get
you a mic to hold. I can just stand up and hold this one. I guess it's the
camera that's the problem. All right, we can yeah, I'll change the camera and
and yeah and then I'll get the red curtain from over there. You keep talking okay.
Well
okay, here I'll just say something funny that I thought of yesterday. Well, this
all happens. I was having Sam. We're talking about something yesterday. I
thought it'd be really funny. If you lived in like a
to just a normal two bedroom apartment like in in Brooklyn, but you had a
butler and the but let's you in one bedroom and the butler lives in the
another bedroom
like he might as well just be your roommate.
Okay, are you guys ready?
Okay, hold on. Let me play this new music
and this is kind of sci-fi type music.
Okay.
All right, I'm going to go.
All right,
the joy of Jupiter a planet report.
Jupiter is by far the largest planet in our solar system.
That is if you don't count planet Lizzo
(laughing)
- Okay.
- One year on Jupiter is the equivalent
of almost 12 years on Earth,
or roughly the time it takes my girlfriend
to get ready to go out.
Jupiter is composed almost entirely of gas,
much like the day after I get Taco Bell.
Its core could be either liquid or solid,
much like my shit the day after I get Taco Bell.
(laughing)
- Oh damn.
Holy shit.
- Jupiter's surface is made up of many cloud systems
and vapors. And for all you stoners out there who just perked up, these gases would be toxic
for humans. Although I guess that's never stopped a druggie from chasing a high. So let
me just make it extra clear for all you degenerate dopers out there. There are no Doritos on
Jupiter. Thank you. Thank you. One of the most interesting features of Jupiter is its
red spot. Sounds like somebody needs a tampon. The red spot is actually a raging storm that's
gone and been going on for hundreds of years. Reminds me of the weather when I want to go
outside and play. Jupiter has a very cold exterior, but it gets warmer the deeper you go, like
a butthole. Jupiter is named after the Roman king of the gods because yeah, somehow gods
weren't powerful enough. We need a God that's also a king.
Yeah, I was waiting for the clap. It's the end of the paragraph.
Yeah, there are 95 confirmed moons orbiting Jupiter. Don't
let Buzz Aldrin find that out or he'll kill himself.
Let's talk about EO Europa, Ganymede and Callisto. And no,
Those aren't the names of Angelina Jolie's children.
Those are the four Galilean moons of Jupiter, more massive than the others.
They were discovered in 1610 by Galileo Galilei,
who takes his name from the famous dinner gibberish scene from Billy Madison.
Europa, the Galilean moon, second closest to Jupiter,
may have a water ocean underneath its surface,
which means it could conceivably be home to extraterrestrial life.
Wow, how exciting said nobody ever.
It's often been said, and this is the conclusion.
This is where I get kind of real.
OK.
It's often been said that girls go to college
to get more knowledge and boys go to Jupiter to get more stupider.
But with modern science, we know the truth.
It's actually girls that go to Jupiter to get more stupider
and boys go to the planet report to get more handsome and smart.
Cameron Fetter, everybody. That's today's Planet Report. That was amazing.
Yeah, I'll put the camera back. I feel like you,
I feel I feel like you really figured out a lane for yourself.
Yeah, I think that we should just have you do different kind of reports
every episode. I'm really liking writing the reports and thinking of my ideas
for the reports. Yeah, I think y'all ain't ready for Saturn either.
Oh, my God. I'm excited for Saturn.
I'll say that much. I'm so excited for Saturn.
It's just incredible to me to be able to make people laugh while also teaching
giving them a factor to about the great spheres and that's the best part about
this. I could see you taking a kind of role as a bill nye style science
educator or beekman kind of vsauce veritasium
fuck bro beekman is my I don't know. Beekman is that a bird and beekman is
not a bird. We've told you we've schooled you on beekman before school.
We schooled you on young boy. We
Beakman hundred percent stood up. Who the hell is Beakman Beakman stood on
business Beakman man Beakman from Beakman's world is he he has so he has
his own world. He was a scientist scientist don't have their own world. He
had a world where he taught people educational things and he had a big
haircut
Beakman big haircut. He had a big haircut. Yeah,
that sounded like a piece of cardboard falling over. Oh God,
(laughter)
Why did I do that?
Oh God, it smells so bad.
I need to hail all of it before you smell it.
(sniffing)
- That really was a crazy sounding fart.
- Well it hit the metal chair.
- I know.
- That was a school fart.
- Yeah, that was, Jesus Christ.
- Yeah.
- Oh my God.
I'm starting to smell it.
- Yeah, it's not good.
- I'm gonna work on not smelling it.
- Yeah, you should work on that.
- I'm gonna do my best to not smell it.
- But I think that you should have your own show
where you tell people because that was really well done. Thank you. You like
the jokes. I feel like adding humour to it almost made it funny. Yeah, yeah, it
makes and the thing is it gets people's attention. It disarms people because
right, you think you start telling talking people about science. I
experience this a lot. I started talking to people. Get away from me. You're
like, oh, I don't know. Oh, you think you're better than me? You're going to
talk to me about science and mathematics. You're a scientist. Fuck you. And then
I do, but I say, you know, I'm talking about math and I say, yeah, why six
afraid of seven. Why? Because seven, eight, nine. It's true. Seven, eight, nine. It's true.
And then they're learning the numbers and they're laughing. Yeah. Yeah, they're learning
about the sequential order of the numbers. Yeah. But you brought up a good point, which
is that girls go to Jupiter to get more stupid or boys go to college. You know what I thought
you were going to say? Nowadays, girls go to OnlyFans to get more money bands. And guys
Boys go to Andrew Tate to learn about what's right.
Scams we hate.
Yes.
Yeah.
To learn about scams we hate.
Uh huh.
Is that what he does?
He talks about scams he doesn't like.
He debunks scams.
Boys go to Baldur's Gate.
Yeah.
To get more bald and straight.
Bald and straight.
Yeah.
That works.
That makes sense.
Yeah.
It's simple as, man.
It is simple as.
It's simple as man. It is simple as that is. What do you guys think about living
with a one roommate who's a butler?
I could see that.
And you get home and you're like, there's like, there's dust all, he
hasn't been dusting with his feather duster and you can hear him in his room
and he's playing Overwatch. I mean, I live with my wife. You guys live with
your girlfriends, we already live this reality. Yeah, living with a butler. I
already live with a fucking butler. Yeah. Actually, my wife lives with a butler.
I'm the butler in my house, unfortunately.
I hate to say it, I'm the butler.
- I do know that about you.
- I'm a complete butler.
I have a checklist every day. - Your wife has a real job.
- I have to vacuum the carpets,
because to get all the dog hair off,
I have to pretend that the dog was never on the couch.
I have to do all sorts of crazy covering up
to make sure that she doesn't,
I have to get rid of every stain
from when he chewed a bone on the couch.
And I have to do the dishes every day before she gets home,
or else she gets home and she--
- Hits you?
- Well, no, she just kinda-- - She won't pay you?
so he starts crocheting and kind of a weird mean way. You have kind of like an
Andy Cap and his wife kind of relationship where she's always chasing you around
with a rolling pin. Andy Cap is a chip, bro. Andy Cap was a cartoon before it
was a chip. You just blew my fucking noodle.
He thinks that were my noodle is in orbit. Your noodle is going around Jupiter.
My noodle is- Is that what a chiptune is? Whoa. Holy shit. A cartoon that became
a chip. He's the original chiptune. Or, well, but also, in another way,
he was a chip. What was Pringle?
What was you never like this? You never ever watch Pringle is a show on it was
on ABC family, but it was only runs. I actually remember that and it's a who
can do it. Pringle can yeah, I remember that shit yeah. That was the theme song
there was okay. There was speaking of actual potato cartoon.
There was a Mr. Potato Head show in the nineties that I used to watch and I
It feels like a dream.
Like that and then like we've
Oh and Timmy the Tooth.
Do you ever watch Timmy the Tooth?
You'd be pulling out these
TV shows never heard of.
I was so obsessed with
puppetry as a kid. I was so obsessed with puppets
that if anything had a puppet in it
I would watch it. So what you liked
these politicians?
God damn.
We're on fire today.
What the fuck is up with me today? We are going nuts.
guts. Holy oh my God, you know this is dude. It's the it's the it was the
Andrew Callahan story. It put me it put me completely on fire did it gives you a
special boost to say something you shouldn't say a gossip, say something
that yeah being to be I would say over we one percent gossip about just a
pretty standard misunderstanding. Yeah, standard, miss already walking it back.
So
yeah, no, he's actually a good
standard misunderstanding. Well, speaking of stories
today,
there's a new Jupiter based track
by OJ the alien.
Who's OJ the alien?
We mean Dr. Dazzle? Oh, he was that guy on that Dr. Dazzle track last week.
Oh, I remember him. Yeah, he's yeah. Yes, I was bodied on my own. He was
bodied on his own track. He got renegade. It's not me. It's not me. I feel I feel
bad about that, but I heard Dr. Dazzle does not care. I remember that. He does
like the hook or something on that Dr. Dazzle song. I feel bad for OJ the Alien
because I mostly and then he made two other Dr. Dazzle songs that didn't have
Dr. Dazzle on. Well, there's one there's one OJ the Alien song today that is
actually a harrowing tale and I think that we need to listen to it. I'm sorry
to bring the mood down, but there is a very harrowing. All right, let's hear it
from tail. You can check all these songs out on the lyrics master on. Yeah, go on
YouTube and just search the way this one's unlisted. Well, they'll they'll
become listed. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I'm trying to remember what this
is a cover rip. What is this of again? You'll see. Oh, this is okay. I remember
now. Actually, I completely let's listen. Let's listen.
This is Dance with the Grouperter.
Oh my God.
I once knew this boy and his name was Grouperter
His main concern was getting real stupider His mom raised him on the streets of Jupiter
He hated his moms, he would always go poop on her
He never ate limes, lemons, or clementines All he did was jack up all the time
Addicted to jacking and he never ate limes By the way, he did lots of crimes
One of them was his hatred for limes He hated all fruit, especially clementines
He hated rap too, he hated my dope rhymes
Hated dope shit like fruit and Adventure Time
He just jacked off, he was addicted to gooning
Jacked so much that his dick was ballooning
He'd sit in his room, holler and hooting
And then one day, he did a homeschool shooting
Shot up his house with a gun called a Baus
Alien gun, if bullets are a mouse
But anyway, back to the story
He didn't eat fruit, so he got the scurvy
That's when his life got all topsy turvy
It made him insane, all up in his brain
Also Jupiter has helium rain
Oops my bad, got distracted again
He shot up his house and the new Aubon pain
Was a massacre, employees were slain
He shot a guy in his left gastric vein
Then robbed his dead body, he took his gold chain
Made his escape on a passenger train
Then he hid in a new Aubon pain
A different one from the one with the shooting
And when he got there, he started gooning
The cop shot him.
I can still hear him mooing.
When he died, he started mooing.
It fucks me up.
Why'd he start mooing?
This is all true.
I'm not just poo pooing.
This happened to a guy I knew when I was schooling.
Eat your fruit.
Eat your fruit, y'all.
It's OJ the alien.
Signing off.
Peace.
Wow.
Oh my God.
It's a cautionary tale about fruit.
But also it does feel like Dr. Dazzle somehow...
I think Dr. Dazzle is more of a pop artist.
Dr. Dazzle like changed...
He like... OJ had to switch it up after the Dr. Dazzle thing.
Like OJ made him reconsider his entire life.
I think he became more conscious.
And he's still doing the thing where he makes up a word to rhyme and then explains what that word is.
it's an alien. It's different kind of things. Explain the culture. Yeah,
you have to explain it's called bullets are a mouth as bullets about shoots
mouses, mice, mice, mice, a bow. So it's bullets are a mouse. It's a mouse
that you put in and then it deteriorates the mouse and turns into bullets.
When it comes out, it's actually very scary technology that doesn't make any
sense. You just shoot a mice. Why shoot a mouse? A mouse? Why does it? Why
does it have to turn it? Are a mouse? The bullet, the clip is a mouse. Oh,
the clip at the mag is it just didn't rhyme look. This is you can also this all
stuff you can take up with OJ the alien on maybe his genius video. That's going
to drop soon.
Is he going to do one? Maybe that's a good idea. Maybe there's an OJ the alien
great. I can't wait. I honestly can't wait for when this album drops in the
press cycle. Just when OJ is going on interviews and stuff. When Nardwar yeah,
but did you hear the Fallon performance? Did you hear the twist ending in that
- Not really, man. - He knew him?
- It was his brother.
'Cause he was homeschooled.
- I'll say that a guy I knew when I was schooling.
- Well, you don't necessarily get homeschooled
with your brother.
- It's his twin brother.
- I like the dance with the devil twist a little more,
I'm gonna be honest.
- Yeah, I was expecting something crazy
at the end of that one.
- You should've just made him fuck his mom.
- I did have an audio clip that says,
"And he fucked his mom too."
It was supposed to go at the end, yeah.
- But you did?
- I can always put it in, I mean, I got a day,
I had a day before this comes out.
- True, yeah, you can change that.
- I can change it.
- But that's not the one you wanted me on, bro?
- No.
- Even though you know that I have that kind of ability?
- I made that beat and I was thinking
maybe Caleb should hop on this.
Maybe Caleb should hop on this.
Maybe there's still time for--
- Do we think we're gonna see a return
from Dr. Dazzle at all?
- The people are clamoring.
- Maybe, maybe there's another one.
I think that there's a beat in the future
for Dr. Dazzle that I made that I think I already showed you.
I want a full doctor dazzle rap album. Now, I think that I showed Dr.
Dazzle
every week.
It's fun to wrap it. So I'm having so much fun. This is the most
to do a song like this. Every single song is such a great idea. Every
episode that and then we just use it as the outro music every time. Yeah,
and also listen to it to a well over fifteen times in the middle of the
show. We could do like the like sway. We could be like, hold on, run that
get back and then hit like the explosion. That's like you know if we're doing if
we're doing say we do like for example on our OSHA episode, we could have just
done a bun a song about OSHA yeah. Every topic we have we just do a song about
it. We got to make a full album out every episode yeah. Why not make an
album every episode? That's a good episode listening to what I you know
what I heard recently do what little Wayne when he goes and he does an
album or not an album. He goes into the studio and he records for a night. He
he does like eighty songs every single time. Yeah, I was like I can do one song
a fucking day, yeah, seven songs a week. Funny, I love, I love whenever they do
like
like it's like there's someone's writing an article about a new album that's
coming out and like the it's not even the artist who's saying it, but there's
like apparently like yeah, this person wrote one hundred and twenty songs for
this album and it's funny because you know that those songs are all it's like
there it's like eight second long yeah,
and that's all there is. That counts as writing a song that you cut from the album.
I have a million beats on my computer that I just don't touch. You don't have a
million beats. I got so many in there. You probably have. You have a billion
beats. I would say you have 17 beats. I think it's more like 23. 23 beats.
That's basically a million. 23 things that I started and then maybe finished.
A lot of it is... Wait, that's a great name for the compilation album.
Of the 23 things I started. Whoa. And it's a photo of me like this. Yeah.
J Dilla Donuts cover. Yeah. You laughing into your hand. Yeah. Damn. Wow. It's a
good idea. That is a good idea. I've got a beat for Dr. Dazzo and I've got a
beat, maybe, maybe OJ the Alien is gonna step back and just only do production.
Dude, people need your... Alchemist style. People need your bars, bro. Alchemist
raps. Oh, he does? Yeah, dude. Oh, then maybe he actually has to become more
like the alchemist you. I think that you have historically been the worst
rapper on the show and it's not even close. Like you, you've always been
really, really terrible and I'm still seeing kind of shades of that in the way
that you write these raps, but
the end product so far, everyone has been a banger. It's sublime. You are, you
are, you are levelling up your rapping ability in my way, in a way I never has
better. In a way I never ever thought that was. I thought that you had a brain that was
wired wrong for rap. I thought you had a rock only brain. It is and I'm being trained. Neuroplasticity
man. I'm training myself to become one of the greatest rappers of all time. You really
are dude. If you did this, if you kept this up for like 40,000 years, you'd be really
pretty good. I think once I turn 56 or something, maybe like I could put out a full album. Yeah,
you're already putting out a full rap.
Well, a 56-year-old put out a full rap, like serious rap.
What's going to be the name?
56 years old, already had like a way already forgotten about comedy career and then you
put out a very serious rap album.
Very, very serious, like it's all about stuff that happened to me.
And it's just like Michael Rapaport style.
A Dance with the Devil song about your SNL audition.
That would be so fucking crazy.
when he fell down his shoelaces were tied together. I don't know why
yes. See that wasn't anything. My girlfriend this morning showed me a
tick tock that she saw on her feed. That was a guy performing a live concert,
and he was you could like really only hear the vocals. Mostly, I couldn't tell
what kind of music it was, but he was just going like this, like, pastor,
please, pastor, please, why are you taking off your jeans? Oh, and then all
the comments are like the pain in his voice. Oh, my God, and I think you
to do that yeah pastor, please pastor, please you taking off those he was
doing it partially like he was rapping, but he was also doing kind of like
don't know what
oh
there's trauma inside. You can't go in there. See when you rap about something
you really know, like being molested by clergyman. This is bars man. See I was
going to say pastor, please pass the bees. That doesn't make any sense.
Nothing makes no sense at all. Yo, pastor, please pass the bees. I gotta
ash my tree and then I asked it for free. I do wanna hear it. Yeah, I wanna
hear
this.
Oh my God.
That's almost exactly... What was that, man? That's almost exactly what I
thought it was that was Hamilton crazy yeah that all the comments are like oh
my God, this is the saddest thing I've ever heard in my life. Is it about him?
Please wait
later, where he says like I'm only nine years old and you're fifty two wait
play the whole song. Okay, I gotta hear this whole thing man. Yeah, I was gonna
say I need to stop about is this about him being gay with the pastor, but then
no it's about getting molested yeah, but he doesn't make a song by being gay.
That could be a good balance.
[Music]
what
dude actually wait. I just had a
it's at a concert, we got a concert. Everyone's like
I just had a mental vision of just driving down driving down Malcolm X
Boulevard and an escalate just go at eight miles an hour, blasting that so
loud, blessing that in the drive through and like cook out to please. Why you
take the quarters in the cup holders are shaking
I did right through it cook out and you're I just get
yeah barbecue plate
sorry, hold on, hold on and then it fades out and then it starts playing again.
Hold on. I love this song turn it all the way
hold on. That's the best or pastor. Please, pastor, pastor, please. Why are
you taking off your jeans is the craziest? Why is the pastor wearing
g? I know that's what it's because why is he wearing jeans so funny to me that
he's a he's wearing jeans and Sunday shoes? Yeah, what the fuck is that? Hold
and wait kind of pastor is ways the twist ending to this one, the devil and
the devil and the
the devil or what's that song dance with the dance with the devil, the devil
twist there. The man is the pastor who's singing well. That would be one
saying to himself in the mirror. I did forget I was listening there at the
pool. I also like that he it's a it's a song where he's he's getting molested
yeah and he has to throw in like I thought you said that Christians
gonna be gay? Yeah, no. Why is he throwing that in there? I like the Eminem song about
being molested. Oh, so you're gay, buddy? Oh, you're molesting me. That means you're
gay. You can't be Christian. We're kicking you out of the church, buddy. You're gay.
Caught ya. Got ya. Everett, there's a camera. I'm an undercover nine-year-old. There's a
camera right there. It doesn't really rhyme with the other stuff well either, so you know,
he just like wrote, he was like, oh, this is good. I have to fit this in there. Yeah.
Pastor, pastor, please, why are you taking off your jeans? It's fucking crazy. I mean...
He bodied that. I can't lie. He bodied that shit. That sounds like Hobo Johnson.
Yeah, it does, doesn't it? Maybe it is. Maybe it is. Could be. Is that Hobo
Johnson? That's what he sounds like? Yeah. I wanted to knew it. He doesn't
speak English. My hair is too curly. Can you imagine if the forefathers of rap
came back to life and heard Hobo Johnson and gave him a medal? Bullshit, man.
No, they wouldn't give him a medal. They'd say, "Dude, you have four pillars there, but
you're missing the fifth one."
B-boying.
You're missing knowledge.
You're missing B-boying.
You're not a B-boy, straight up.
No. Show me a headspin right now.
Right now.
Show me a fucking headspin.
What happened? How come B-boying has fallen out of vogue with our popular rappers? Roddy
Rich can't spin on his head.
No.
Can he do this, though?
He could probably do that.
Most people can do that.
Bad B-boy.
Bad Baby can't.
No.
bod baby. I don't know, I don't know baby Daniel Burgoli,
but
but baby,
I want to perform with but baby
bring me bad baby. That would be so sick man. I've request about the baby
rolling out wrapped in Dracula's castle. You walk in a Dracula's castle. You
the can you're like the door slam behind you like you turn around you're
trying to get out and it comes in. Don't kill me, bring me bad baby,
bad baby, like your for the music. You don't want me to bring the woman,
play this. Oh, I want the woman. I want to take it to rolling loud. Oh
my God, imagine a Dracula at rolling right loud and he's doing like a like
red carpet interview. I want to go to governor's ball. It's a contract.
and Drew yeah
I like to be
he's like yes. I like blood
all right.
Oh my God, Dracula and funny Marco talking that be so sick. I want to be
front row for ski mask. The slump God
reap xxx.
I'm going to fucking kill playboy card. I had to say it. Well, I have to say it
imagine imagine how amazing the Dracula X Bobby Althoff interview would be that
be so amazing. I don't know. It is amazing Dracula, so the amazing can't see
him because you know he's being filmed and then you would set it up as a
mirror. Yeah, so there's mirrors in your you can't see you can't Dracula can't
see himself in the mirror. Yeah, well he can't see himself. He loses it. He like
forty five minutes and he's he's fed up. You're such a fucking bitch. You are
such a vied to be. Do you not know who I am? How do you not know who I am? Where
Oh, he gave up. Wait, he gotta go get Bobby.
Somebody's here?
Who the hell's at the door? Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
It's mail again, dude.
Wait, maybe it's the gift card from Verizon.
Maybe finally.
Maybe finally they sent it.
Because we were late on two payments, and I think that maybe that's why they didn't send us the $300 signing bonus.
They were holding out?
They were. They said that in July, and then they said, "Oh, yeah, direct deposit."
Is anything from Verizon?
No, it's for the...
God damn it, man.
I have to call them now. I have to call them and say we never got our signing
bonus for business Fios. I want to show you guys my painting. Bring my mood back
up because I'm thinking about this lost $300 gift card. I'm going to be honest,
last week, dude, I'm going the opposite of Cameron this week. Last week, I went
funny as crap with my paintings, trying to be fun. I mean, look at this. Remember
that I was doing more watercolor paintings in my free time and I think
that I just like painting now. Yes, that's what happened when I think it is
completely... This has been, it's opened up. We found passions. We have, it's the
greatest week. Oh my god! That looks just like that! Look at that paint, look at my
Jupiter painting. What's the black dot? That's the red dot because it's black in
in a photo that it's a very dark red. All right,
yeah, I just had a great time painting this and it had nothing to do with the
fact that it's my wife's birthday and I had twenty minutes to paint.
It was because I got so in love with painting looks great, but I also give
that to her. I'll show right. I think I'm going to paint her something beautiful
tonight. Yeah, it's nice. You're going to paint a picture of Phil.
I was going to paint a picture of you really
for your wife.
I
like George
like a cane in front of a fire place. Yeah, I thought you would love that, but
I also wrote a hike because I'm getting into this to its forty eight by fifty.
It's not it's five by seven by five to big to hang up. Oh, you're talking
about painting. Yeah, a giant painting.
This is my
I
like
tears like a huge burger. I want fries right now.
That's the whole hike.
Don't what kind of dickhead?
I like who is 17 syllables man. Yeah, you should have been counting them out.
Yeah, I want you to count them out. I thought I was like I felt like I was
missing a syllable.
Alright, ready?
Give me the music again real quick.
Missing a syllable.
Flying to Ridgeville.
Alright, watch this.
Woah, that was C, holy shit, he's really learning.
Planet Jupiter.
Layers, like a huge burger.
I want fries, right now.
Wow, that's 575 y'all.
575.
We don't need that for a haiku man, you're getting a long vibe from my camera.
Alright, so we're going to be doing a little bit of a haiku.
I want fries right now.
That's 575 y'all.
575.
We don't need that for a haiku man.
You're getting the wrong vibe for my coup.
How's that?
That's fine.
The clapping.
I don't think you clap at a...
Snap I guess but I don't have a snap.
Dude I went to a bar that had a jazz performance the other night.
Oh yeah?
It was amazing.
But...
They do haikus there?
No but what the hell?
Are you supposed to clap when they finish jazz?
Yeah I don't know.
I don't know.
I don't know you're supposed to go. I was I started clapping, then I felt kind of
rude wasn't nobody else was clapping a couple of people, but I think they were
clapping because I started clapping yeah and then it was every song. As soon as
I finished, they started clapping and then the guy to like justify the collapse
introduced the bassist and the drummer, because it was a guitar player, a
bassist and a drummer, and he introduced them every single time, one of them
every time between songs. He'd be like and on the drums you got Nick. Here's my
question was it was a background situation or there was a like a
concert like it was like was it like people were hanging out and they're
just they were it's like a restaurant and they had yeah it's like a yeah,
I think the vibe there is probably just that in general nobody nobody knows
what to do when a song ends like that. Nobody knows you're supposed to call it
no matter what kind of music it is. Everybody knows that he's trying to
clap. It was not so I think you created you made everyone feel bad that they
hadn't been clapping before probably yeah. Oh fuck you probably made everyone
go. Oh shit, maybe we should be clapping. You made someone think in their head
douche chill. I know exactly what me you remember that from remember that from
arrested development. You think they got a douche chill for me to do is chill the
bias. You and K would say that douche chill. I somebody somebody said douche
chill in their head. No, I think so. No toasty under that an hour of this.
Remember that yeah,
those days from mortal combat. What else do we remember
still? You remember okay, guys, we have to do jupiter. We barely talked about
Jupiter. We barely what time are you put or we're at fifty. We got ten minutes.
Ten minutes. We have
well, this is all the time. We'll do a two hour episodes. We talk about
Jupiter. Yeah, let's just talk about Jupiter. All right. Okay. What is your
experience with Jupiter? Don't know much about it. Big as fuck. It's you. Did
you guys know it's like
really
quite big? It's the biggest planet. It's the biggest planet on the solar system
and it's I think it's bigger than like all the other planets combined or
something like that. Do you feel like
because it's a gas giant, there's a little bit of an issue in terms of size.
Yeah, 'cause it is its atmosphere. Yeah, so it's like who gives a fuck,
really? I think it still is anyway. I think visually, it's the planet I would
like to take a bite out of the most. I think I agree with you there.
Actually, no, I would like to put it in my mouth like a jaw breaker.
I think Neptune looks the... It looks the candiest, but we'll get to Neptune.
Yeah, don't talk about that. If you had to fit any planet in your
asshole. This would be the one to do because it's just air. Yeah, it's true.
Well, that's what I thought I've thought I found interesting when I was doing my
research. They don't they don't know what the core is. They don't know if the
core is all it could have no solid. Well, let's send it be let's send a let's
send someone in there. The first manned mission to do because there's been a
woman to mission every single year to get stupider, but a manned mission yeah
to find out what's in that core. Imagine I just ask the girls
I don't understand. Oh yeah, they're too. I don't know what a or is too dumb to
play it because they went to do they got more stupid. What's the difference?
Yeah. Can you explain? Yeah, sorry, I forgot you got stupider there while I
was in college. They so they learn so much while they're on there, but then I
think the gas itself, I think that's what it's supposed to be saying and that
it's like kind of like how Ring Around the Rosie was about like
whatever. The gas is a neurotoxin. The gas is a neurotoxin. So all these women
go there and they're very, very smart. Then they, you know, hang out. Our
brightest minds. Yeah, well, yeah, how they're gonna get to Jupiter and then
to get to Jupiter and then their brain kind of it's like you know you sit in
like a room full of carbon monoxide for a little bit you're going to feel stupid.
Did you guys also know the same they named Jupiter after the king of the gods
back in Roman times or whatever and they named the they named it that before they
even knew it was the biggest planet. It just happened to be that Jesus Christ
is that incredible discover planets back then they had telescopes man in the
sixteen hundreds even they were looking up rocks. They were just taking pieces of
glass and putting them into different pieces of glass. You just put one piece
of glass here. I saw this crazy telescope in Ireland called the Great Telescope
that was from hella long ago, and it was a big wooden telescope that was huge,
like a NASA telescope, like giant. Really? And they could adjust it, and they
were able to trace the planets and stuff. Did it go like, "Click, click, click,
click, click, click"? I don't know, they didn't move it. Would you, if you got
sent back to a far away time,
What is one thing that you think with the knowledge that you have today, you could
invent there and get credit for?
RCA cables.
I can invent the kickflip.
Kickflip, maybe, but you'd have to invent a skateboard.
Oh, right.
If I went back into the 1970s, I could invent the kickflip.
And also, I don't think they would have cared that much about a kickflip,
honestly.
That would have been magical.
No, they would have cared more about that back then than they do now.
Yeah.
Kickflip?
Kickflip means nothing now.
People were swallowing swords and eating fire.
every single day. Yeah, but a new type of trick completely it would blow their
minds. It's a trick. It'd be a rolling. It'd be like this is a trick flip a
rolling kick flip. So not like
not like a just, you know, stationary, stationary. It's like, Oh, what the hell?
How the hell did you do that? If somebody could, if somebody could magic
back could jump more than one foot in the air in the olden days, they would
call them the human frog. Yeah, it called them leaper. But then they kill
you, man. What? Okay, that what's that? You have to strike a balance. Get last
names like Smith first you're going first you're saying they won't care now
you're saying they'll kill you you think you get him in an RCA cable yeah it's
easy it's just red yellow and white I guess that's true the red goes in the
red yeah why didn't they call it a r y w cable yeah I don't know I think is
great because they were invented by the RCA corporation shut up man mystery of
media arts how long ago would you have to go back okay I'm trying to think of a
really easy. How far in time would you have to go to invent like I mean, I
guess I could go back to really long and invent the wheel. That's a yeah, but
even then man, I don't know how well of a wheel I'd I'd whittle. I would find a
rock
that was kind of like a basically already a wheel and I would you know
smooth. I would rub it on other rocks and smooth it out a little bit, but then
even then, what are you like? What are you? Are you going to use that to move a
piece of meat. I'm just going to show them about it. I'm going back to the
year one and I'm a venting doggy style.
I'll go back.
I think dog that's all that was the first one. Yeah, yeah, no you would need to
invent the Amazon position. Can you imagine that guy, the guy who invented
missionary? Yeah, wow yeah, did John John mission. What is one brown? It was
yeah, it's definitely John Brown. It was John Brown from the evolutionist era. I
guess that for a real answer, I mean you could go back to cave men because they
were using tools, but they none of the tools they had had handles. They were
just taking rocks and you didn't eat it. So I could just I would just do the
classic, you know, medieval tool of just I would just take a stick and I would
tie it with a vine
onto there. I would just take their axe head that they already made. I'd be
like see you'd be doing that you'd be there would be a lot of going. Yeah,
and then honestly to be so honest with you realistically scientifically, they'd
probably start fucking me. I didn't fake breasts
breast implants again. I think going to the and inventing I'd get cantaloupes
and watermelons and cut them in half. So we have different approaches here. I'm
saying we could you could go so far back that you could invent something easy and
it would be incredible and brand new. You're saying if you go recent, you
could you have more tools to invent. That is a good point. That actually you have
outsmarted this question. Yeah, you could because I could go to the if you go
back you could go to nine years, seventy nine hundred and seventy invent like
flat jack or in venture time. I know another I know another good way to cheat
this question. What's that just memorize a mathematical formula? Oh yeah,
but you're walking around theory, but you're walking around Pythagoras, but
then also you have to all those guys had to prove it on a big chalk. The
Pythagorean theorem is easy to prove. You just draw triangles. Well, that's a
good point. I would invent the isosceles triangle. I would go back to like the
when you I would be like pre pre homo sapiens, I'd be showing it to like
australopithecus yeah, just like trying to draw a triangle, the butterfly of the
one of them, grabbing my leg and trying to pull me into the river to drown me
sitting in a car. You go and change that and then some kids in a third grade
class getting taught to. I saw some of these triangles because you could
remember the
yeah. I saw some of the I saw some of these triangles. Yeah, you go back in
time when you teach cavemen about triangles and you go back to the future
and is everything is a triangle. Yeah, yeah, no other shapes in the world.
Yeah, exactly that's that would be my big fear. I triangle heads because I'm
a
like when you mold a baby's because they started like it's just natural
selection of people who had the kind of triangle head. It's been a hundred
thousand years. There's been time yeah of triangle selective breeding yeah
damn that's what they do. I'm too much of a believer in the butterfly effect to
anything with a time machine. Yeah. I wouldn't do it, man. I'm too scared. You can go forward.
I mean, I just don't want to get hurt. I have to worry about the butterfly. Then you'd butter
or butter is amazing.
The forward thing would suck as you go forward in time and you find out that you're going
to fucking die because of stray soccer ball. I'm dead. I'm going to die. What was it? What
was that truck honking sounded like dramatic chip. No, you guys are like
newly adopted dogs. You heard a car before I've heard of a car.
You don't have to worry about going forward, though, because the butterfly
effect would just apply to the people in front of where you go. You do you do
all this butterfly effect stuff like you go back in time, you invent the
isosceles triangle or whatever, and then you come back to the future and
Ashton Kutcher is got a nosebleed. Oh, she's got some new. It's a every worth
it. And every single holocaust, when you come back nosebleed, Ashton Kutcher's
hurt. Actually, I would do it now because he's proven to be a CIA asset.
Was there... Did somebody... Was this in a Freddie Wong podcast or was this a movie where
somebody stops the Holocaust and then comes back to the normal time and stuff is way worse
somehow?
Freddie Wong did that?
Like a guy was like, "Oh man, the Holocaust almost happened. I'm going to do it 50 times
bigger. Yeah. Yeah. No, not for anyone. I feel like somebody talked about that on a Freddie
Wong podcast. Huh? Yeah, but that's a scary thought. Yeah. What if we're in the safest,
most amazing timeline that it could possibly exist? Well, I know I aren't. Well, you are
for sure. I know I am. Cameron is. I mean, because he's going to make a quantum leap
one day. I'm never going to be killed. You don't think so? He's going to be preserved
can imagine as well. I will be in as well. He wants to be preserved in amber
rather not be killed. Would you guys want to get cremated? You want to get put
in the ground, say cream,
would you rather be cremated or cream pod when you die? When I die, I guess
moments after you feel it yeah, you won't you know sometimes they don't
people's body. You know sometimes they donate people's bodies to science. I
want my body to be donated to pleasure. I want to be my body. I want my body
so don't it to the fan. Would you like to see what we're doing with your
grandmother?
My body was donated to the fan bus. I feel like we have baby alien wears it
like a mech suit. I fuck bigger with
I feel like we've taught we probably I feel like we maybe talked about it
before, but yeah you don't your grandmother don't answer body to
science and you come to see what research they're doing and they're using
her to invent a new flesh like
taking molds of her. I'd be sad man be tragic. I would re that make me rethink
my entire throw up yeah straight up. I would honestly be the least of the
reactions. I have I emotionally it would shatter me. I'd bar for a bag. I hope I
get donated to like a sushi bar yeah and they use me to put to do the taxidermy.
You you think you'd be great, no not sushi great not to eat, but use me like
one of the naked things to eat off as a plate. Yeah, I want to be a play. I
think I'd like to be a plate when I pass. I think that's a good idea or maybe I
want them to use my body to make an RC airplane or helicopter. I truly want to
fly. I want to get donated to the science to the haunted house science.
Wasn't there like some story I God I'm
there was some story where they thought like some guy was like, oh, my
grandmother is being donated donated to science and then the army put a bunch of
explosives in her. Yeah, that happens all the time. Oh my God, that's so fucking funny.
I think something like a huge percentage of people whose bodies are donated to science
get donated to like weapons testing. Yeah, they get donated to the army. And they get
stuffed with dynamite and they do MythBusters stuff with everybody's dead creatures. It's
so fucking funny. It's so funny how gross that shit is. That is so awesome. Oh my God.
What a terrible world.
I would want to stop. I would want to be donated to the police or something.
Yeah. I want them to, when I die, I want them to like dissect my brain and study it and
use the information to make a pill that would make people like TV more than normal.
Yeah. I want to be donated to like a college classroom. It's just like a pinata for like
the last day of class.
Pinata is good, yeah.
Last day of class.
Oh, pinata is good. Oh yeah, getting donated.
I'm feeling filled up with Kindles.
Oh, I have a good one.
I'll be fat by then. I'll be fatter.
I'll be fat by then. I want to get donated to a guy who needs somebody to sit in his front seat so he can get in the carpool lane.
That'd be a good one.
I want to be donated to the city so they can stuff me like a bear and then put me into the sewers or any abandoned buildings to scare urban explorers.
So people are like, "Oh, we're going to go exploring."
That's a good idea.
It's you holding a gun.
And a cop outfit.
And a big text bubble made of cardboard that says freeze.
They turn your body into a pyramid head from Silent Hill.
Yeah, they should make me a ghost.
And then they just put you in like abandoned hospitals.
Yeah.
And just have you stand there.
Wow.
That's a good idea.
Just in general to be scolding and scaring people for doing something wrong.
Oh my god, that'd be so...
To have a job in death.
To still have a purpose.
A purpose for your entire legacy.
To have a purpose even when you're gone.
Yeah.
That's how like Einstein must feel.
Wearing a shirt that says one way, pointing.
Yeah.
All signs should be dead people.
Because who's catching
when you walk by one of those billboards
that has a fake person hanging off of it
that catches your eye man.
I've never seen one of those.
These should be outlawed.
Imagine how you would feel when you're walking down the street
you're like, "Oh is this the turn? What street is this?"
You're squinting up at the street sign. It's your friend who killed himself last year.
Exactly. Yeah, giant hole in his head.
in his head. Oh my god, you know what would be perfect is getting turned into a bike.
Like arm like this, holding the wheel and then the feet are also the wheel. Like an
HRT gear thing. Yeah. That's good. I can just like this. Mic stand. You want to be a mic
stand? Yeah, well someone could be. They put the microphone in your mouth when they're
done. That's a good idea. You know what also would be good is if maybe I have the same measurements
as like a celebrity who's about to be in a wax museum, right? So they can just take my
body, right? Put it on chains. I got a movie to show you, man. Put it on chains and then
dunk me up and down into a big thing, a big tub of wax and then mold my face into like
Obama or whatever. I hope you like Paris Hilton, man. That movie's so fucking good, dude. They're
gonna turn me into Paris Hilton? I love that movie. You like the House of Wax remake? It's
It's so good. I've been watching it since I was a kid. I've never seen it. It's really,
really good. I remember it being disgusting. It's so gross. And they spent like fucking
millions of dollars. It's like the, he has a huge budget. Really? They built a town for
it. Whoa. It's so swag, dude. It's awesome. All the marketing for it was like, "Watch
Paris Hilton get killed." Yeah. That's what all the trailers were. And me and all my boys
lined up, dude. Midnight premiere. What a movie. I got that shit on Blu-ray, man. Wow.
I watched it this year. I'm gonna have to watch it rewatch it. I believe I've never seen it.
It's sick dude. You know it's a good movie. The wrong guy. I watched it again on YouTube
for free. What's the wrong guy? Dave Foley. That movie is so funny. Dave Foley, Joe Flatterdy.
Free guy. Jennifer Tilly is in it also. What's it about? It's about a guy who walks in on
his manager dead and then he flees. So it's like it's like the Alfred Hitchcock movie.
It's like the player. I don't know my favorite movie man the player. Julio pull this go on
a YouTube look up the wrong guy 1997. No whole movie on there in HD for free for free free
but with ads probably no. If you have not if you have YouTube premium. Well I do have
YouTube premium or if you know how to download one hour of medieval M&M. Why are you pulling
pulling up this meme shit bro. Yeah, pull up the wrong guy. We don't need to show
anything. We'll have the last hour of the episode and it'll be us watching a show.
We're not actually doing a two hour episode, man. I want to shake you so bad. Don't shake
me. Do you guys want to go to a giant buffet? I want to go to a buffet, so I've been thinking
about it. I want to go to Fogo de Chao. There's a buffet over... I never got to go to Fogo
de Chao. Over a Chinese buffet. Really? Yeah. It doesn't look like it is good. But I kind
I don't want to go to like a big I want to go to like a golden corral. Yeah,
golden corral. Yeah, I miss that fucking seafood buffet man. We gotta get back to
murder, murder beach. We gotta go back to murder. That's just the best idea ever.
We grab legs. Oh my God, it's fish sitting out all day. Yeah. Oh my God, on
a hot sternum. That place, I drove by that place on the way to
on the way to the airport. Calabash. Yeah, the Calabash seafood place and
it's called like Captain something. Yeah, but a guy had a guy had driven off
road into the sign and it was like I passed by right as it happened the like
big brick sign a bunch of cops were there. That's crazy. Pretty badass dude.
Yeah you know what's badass? The wrong guy. Stop talking about the wrong guy. It's a really good movie.
You gotta stop speaking on the wrong guy. Okay you are not standing on business.
I'm not standing on business but what if I change the movie up? Let me stand on
business and promote my show. Oh yeah that's right. Can I promote my show?
Yeah, you can promote it. Guys, there is very few tickets left. How many? Probably, let's
see, it's a 110 cap venue, there's two shows, there's probably only a hundred and
fifty tickets left guys. Wow. Which is almost none and we're one week from
today that I'm recording this is the show. The Yard Theatre, or the two shows,
the Yard Theatre in Los Angeles, me and my friend Gus Fiveros are doing 30
minutes of stand-up comedy. Julio, can you pull up this poster? The poster was made
by Neil Linsky, little known fact. Whoa! And Neil is going to be... I would call it a
known fact, I knew it. We're flying him out to host it and mostly to just hang out with us.
But this is going to be an amazing show guys. Please come out to this. One show at
eight, one show at ten. I wish I could be there. I wish I could go to the show. Maybe I give
you a two-minute video you can play up the top that says hello to everybody. Yeah,
Yeah, probably.
Why do you keep asking people to do that?
You're asking that to Pierce too.
What?
What is this thing with you where you want to film a video for people to play before their shows?
I would love to be a part of the show in some capacity.
You're trying to make it about you, man. It's my show.
I'm not trying to make it about me.
How about you do 30 minutes with some guy?
Maybe I could. I could maybe do that.
Who would you do it with, huh?
Because I already got Gus.
It would be Andy Kaufman.
Andy Kaufman's long dead, man.
Andy Kaufman's long dead. Andy Kaufman? That's what you think. He was faking it the whole
time. Dude, he's dead as a doornand. And then, and then it's my, then I reveal, basically
I'm the one that's revealing it. That you're Andy Kaufman? No, that I know him. You're
so crazy. That I know him. You hate girls so much. I beat up every woman I see. I wrestle
women. I've seen you do that at bars. Wrestle random women. You ever seen Andy Kaufman?
off and yeah and you have to hold me back by my chain. You have to start
bringing me. I have you on a chain right up step right up. Watch the I call him
the
human
the human people. Look at him. He's foaming at the mouth. Please come out to
my show. That'd be really good. Go to Pierce's show. Oh, and Pierce's show is
also that night. So you do have to choose that. We'll just go to the eight
the clock in line and go to the his show at ten o'clock. He put the day on the
same show as you. Yeah, I don't care, bro. Here's this is your burn notice.
I'm standing on business and I know you're gonna stand on everybody. We
didn't talk much about Jupiter today, but you can rest assured that we will
be talking a lot about Saturn on the next episode, which is the next planet
coming up. I wish we had
stay tuned for all types of special surprises for the planets coming
forward. I wish that we had planned this. I wish that we had planned this.
Saturday.
Shareholders meeting is when?
Saturn would be on a Saturday.
21st.
Well, it's okay.
Shareholders meeting is on the 21st.
That's 21st of November, so subscribe to the executive producer tier on Patreon.
And we have something pretty amazing, I think, for the shareholders.
We got to explain what the shareholders is.
Yeah, go ahead.
I'm going to go pee.
We got to explain what that is, because I don't think people understand.
We are doing, we do basically a monthly live show.
Remember during COVID when everybody was doing Zoom stand up? It's basically that.
It's Zoom stand up.
So if you missed that, come on in.
We'll release one on YouTube or something so everyone can see how awesome it is.
Yes. Maybe we're coming up on one year of shareholders.
Is that true?
Yeah, pretty soon.
That's unbelievable.
Yeah, that's true.
All right.
And then Julio has a show coming up.
Yeah.
You want to plug that?
Yeah. I'm coming to New York. I'm going to be doing five minutes during Thanksgiving at
at Kills apartment. We're going to have Julio do his first open mic set at a bar
in Bushwick.
All right, Thanksgiving on Thanksgiving. Happy Jupiter, y'all.
Wait, guys, we should literally become a spa worker so we can see women naked all
the time.
It's a great idea. I'm all these people who are wasting their time jacking off
to porn. Just get a job at a
We have to go on Shark Tank and we have to pitch this to Mark Cuban and Mr. Wonderful.
A spa for women who don't mind being ogled.
Yeah.
A spa where you...
How about this?
A spa where you go for free and you get a bunch of perverts who pay.
Like if a woman wants to go to a spa, you could either...
You could either...
The perverts are paying double what the women would pay.
Yeah, you could either pay...
$1,000.
This is a great idea.
You either pay $50 to go to a normal spa or you pay zero.
Meanwhile, the perverts, Patrick and Cameron, are sitting behind a...
I didn't say that I was going to be there.
Oh wait, here's the thing though.
You could even do tears.
I'm literally the inventor of this company.
I wouldn't be one of the perverts.
You could even do... well, you have to test it out.
You could even do tears of the...
I would honestly be whipping and torturing the perverts.
The pervert tears could be this, dude.
Listen to this.
You could either have...
You could say, "It's a pervert honeypot."
We pitch this business on Shark Tank and then we post that.
We tell them afterwards like we and this the secret don't air this part on your
TV show, but actually we're going to kill all the perfect.
We don't want to kill.
We're going to get that and John and conchig were you guys.
If you OK, you guys are fucking idiots because you're wasting a million dollar
idea. You can even have it.
He wants to go.
You could even have it be tiered where there's windows that you think that
they can be seen through both sides and that tickets 50.
Well, they already have.
But then they shut up.
There's one that is that is a mirror.
What do they call that?
A double sided mirror, one way, one way, two way mirror, a two way mirror.
it really is. And that one is more money so that your identity is hidden.
And then there's one that's even more that is a private cube.
They have this already, the window and everything. It's called a peep show.
But these women are just doing their own thing. They're not like put on a show.
Yeah, but wouldn't you want to pay for women doing the show?
If we're trying to maximize profit, I just thought of an even better idea, Caleb, kind of jumping off your two-way mirror idea.
What if we have it, it's all two-way mirrors, the
perverts pay a hundred dollars to come watch from behind the mirror and the
women also are charged a hundred dollars to use the spot they don't know the
perverts watching
[MUSIC PLAYING]