[Music]
Oh, actually, this would be perfect for...
Okay, here. I'm starting with this.
Okay.
[Music]
Uranus is one of the hottest destinations in the galaxy
for Thanksgiving festivities.
Ever since the blue planet formed 4.5 billion years ago,
space pilgrims from planet Mess have been making pilgrimages there
to soak their maximally absorbent dipe suits.
Uranus's rotational axis being tilted more than 90 degrees
means filling a diaper with piss and shit
much more enjoyable as it causes the mess to flow
in an interesting way.
Uranus is cold and icy, so interplanetary visitors
have always made sure to bring what is now
one of the most common Stinksgiving delegacies,
bobo stew.
A beef stew with high alcohol content,
this food forged strong communities between pilgrims,
filling their stomachs and then filling their diapers afterward.
As the pilgrims became more and more intoxicated from the bobo stew, they found themselves sharing
funny pictures and stories from online communities with each other and laughing their slimy brown
asses off.
This also became an important aspect of Stinksgiving, the part of the feast known as "Diaper Talk".
Messians from the brown and yellow planet of course later learned of the existence of terrestrial
planets beyond Uranus and matched a full-scale secret invasion of Earth's governments and
systems.
hold over human culture is the reason we celebrate Stinksgiving here on earth.
But this is the five weeks of planets, so it's time to leave the earth. Today,
we'll celebrate Stinksgiving more traditionally,
the way pilgrims from planet mass always intended.
Welcome everybody to diaper talk five, Stinksgiving on Uranus.
Wow. Oh my good.
Happy Stinksgiving everybody.
You gotta do one of these. You need to jeer.
gear one time. You deserve that. That's what jeering is? No. Yes. Is that? No. That's
jeering. What is hissing actually? I know, but like do people do that at a stadium? Boo
and hiss in context? Yeah. I think it's just be... It's hiss. No, that's like a... What
is that called? That's the autistic hiss. No, but what is that called? Like a... Sucks
teeth. Sucking your teeth. Sucking your teeth. Teeth suck up. But you do that when something's
cringe. I know you wince a little. It's a little bit of a wince. It's like a cringey
I think it's more of a wince, if anything.
Or a cringe.
A sharp intake of air.
Listen up, man.
I think that we need to eat this bobo stew while it's still hot.
We need to...
Is it even hot?
It's not hot.
It's not going to be hot at all when the...
Suck my dick, man.
I fucking made this all day.
It looks so good.
It tastes like shit.
How do you know it tastes like shit?
I took a bite of the stew's part.
It doesn't taste like shit, but there's no rose in there.
Well, it's going to taste like shit in a second.
second. It's about to be it won't taste like shit. So here's how we're doing
this. We talked about
no. Oh yeah. Try to do a cap full with this dickhead.
Oh
no. Yeah. No, go ahead.
Do a fucking cap full with the core. I didn't know it was a core. Let it soak.
It's not even a real cork, by the way. This is an overproofed alcohol, isn't
it? Yeah, this is. Oh dear. George Dick.
George Dickle White. Corn whiskey, mellow as moonlight. Number one foundation
recipe. I'm so sorry. Pour it. It's 91 proof. Wait, we... Give it... Wait,
no, we need the cups. We need cups. Give me cups. I thought we were
gonna have shot glasses to do it like a boiler maker. But we're still
gonna do cups and we'll cheers. Yeah. I'll pour myself a little something.
Some of that dickle. Some of that white dickle. Pour up that white dickle.
Let's get a stew. Pour up that white dickle. Let's get a stew. Can't go to
ways. Mr. Spiller white nickel all right little bit of white nickel huh not
enough. Oh wait. You're crazy me. Oh my God. This guy was fair more more white
nickel spirit. All right,
so
white
okay, guys wait before we do this. What are you thankful for? Stink full? I'm
thankful. I'm stink full for
everything that has happened this year. Wow, I'm very thankful for the fact that
the five weeks of planets has lined up so beautifully between the stinky planet. I
actually call it. It's actually unbelievable. I think it's the stink
clip. It stinks.
Stig clips is better than stinking. I'm stink. I'm thankful for our friend
Pierce for being here. This is an amazing, amazing. I think you guys so
much and this is my this is my favorite community. I love you guys. Stinky
stinkful happy Stinks giving my favorite online.
It's so much
much
it's gone off. It's so
literally completely inedible now. Okay,
I was like it smells like when you're cooking. I'm sorry. It
smells like when you cook more. Sala Jesus Christ,
Caleb, you went right in.
I'm gonna eat the beef.
It's kinda good, man.
I'm gonna have a bite of beef.
I'm gonna kinda skip the broth, maybe.
You gotta get the broth.
Ugh.
No, it's chewable.
Guys.
Oh, he spit it out.
Oh, but.
Oh, it's not stinkful.
Oh, no, no, no, that tasted exactly like throw up.
That tasted exactly like when I throw up.
You eat beef stew and black caviar?
Oh my god.
I'm gonna eat the beef.
- Oh my God. - You eat beef stew and vodka?
- Well, it doesn't taste good. - No, it doesn't taste fabulous.
- I mean, it tastes exactly like you think it would. - It tastes exactly like...
- I mean, I will say, if this had been a big bowl of beef stew...
- It literally smells like fucking ethanol, dude. - Oh my God.
- If this had been... It's over-brewed whiskey.
If this had been a big bowl of beef stew... Let me get just the broth.
- I'm gonna do some broth here, too. - I can't do it. I can't do it.
I can't believe it. It just tastes like whiskey, like alcohol. It doesn't.
No beef stew in that at all. Okay, somebody told me to do powdered alcohol,
but that has sent too many people to the hospital.
I also brought delicious handmade pierogies. Oh, thank you, Pierce.
The carrot is not so nice. The carrot literally absorbs all the vodka
immediately. That's why you gotta eat it fast before I come back. I'm gonna
need that to cool off. I think that once that's completely cool, okay, drink it.
I'm going to like it. Hold on, hold on. What?
We did the spillers prayer
before this
and you just put your bowl down by your feet.
At least it's something that wouldn't be a nightmare to clean up. You have this
alcoholic beef stew. You got to spill it. It's not really a big deal. You got to
push it a little bit away from your feet. You got to put it like towards the
cameras because that okay, everybody review of beef stew of the alcoholic
beef. I just eat the whole thing. Yeah, I think you put your pierogi in
anything to cut now that I'm past the initial shock. It's just it's just a
shot that you have that you have to take a long time. The longest shot. Yeah,
it's not. This is like a jello shot. Yeah, yeah, I thought that the beef stew
dilute the alcohol, it doesn't at all. No, it sits on top. Yeah. It sits on
top of the fat and everything and then it like... The worst part of it is
the way it looks.
Let me... I'll just come show one of the cameras. Hold on. Spiller time.
Jesus. It keeps getting on my hands. The stew?
I'm glad that we did this with seven minutes in.
Spiller, spiller, spiller. That's dripper, that's dripper vibes. Spilling onto
for the power strip. That's a drip. Yeah, drip on a power strip, bro.
You dripped on the strip. It keeps getting on my hands and like your brain
is supposed to do certain work for you when you smell your hands like, "Oh,
I need to wash these, they smell like shit." Or like, "Oh, I need to water
these, I've been out by the bonfire for too long." These swim now.
You need to water these?
You need to water your hands?
Oh, you get ash on them.
Alright, I'm gonna try a carrot. I do kind of...
The longer you wait for the carrot, the more dangerous it is, I'm gonna say.
it's going to soak something up a little. I well guys, you know what I just want
to point out.
All three, I think
I can't eat the stew because of my own,
because I'm weak, but also I
just want to say thank you. That's a good point. I want to say thank you
you guys for giving me the part of the stew that had no carrots in it.
I did that because I thought that you couldn't eat any carrots. I know,
I can eat cooked carrots. It's a cooked carrot. You're fine.
Cook carrots are like a dirty potato. The alcohol is only on the skin. Maybe
I'll try. It just tastes like I'm eating a potato that tastes normal, except
it's maybe covered in dirt on the outside. Yeah, some kind of pesticide or
soil. Yeah,
guys, I'm gonna be real. This is not my favorite food I've ever had in my
entire life. It's up there. I literally don't, I don't even take shots without
thinking that I'm going to vomit. And so the stew that is, I mean, it was a
lot of alcohols. The Bobo stew. Yeah, the Bobo stew. I don't know how they're
eating this on what plate. Somebody... But it's only... You are only consuming
that much alcohol if you finish the stew. So we're fine. I'm gonna try one
more bite of the meat. I'm gonna keep eating. It's like my brain... I'm
gonna eat until I feel it, man. The meat actually is... Yeah, it's chewable.
Pretty good. It's not bad. But my brain is shouting. My brain is
shouting at me that this is going to kill you. That's a good...
I feel exactly the same. It was just pure
just off enough from alcohol. Your constitution is so amazing. I know you
would be ninety nine HP in any video game. I just I feel like if we're gonna
do a fucking alcoholic beef stew, you gotta eat it. You gotta be we gotta get
fucking plastered off of this stuff. You're a hundred percent. This is not a
day. That's what I'm doing. It's thanksgiving. I'm gonna shoot the broth.
Cheers, my friends.
Oh, no.
We have no one.
Okay.
Before we do any podcast.
it's so fucked up and then we do the worst episode of all.
I was a God, we gotta get these in while we can, because I'm pushing thirty
years old and there's no way I'm going to be thirty years old eating poop
food
a video once a year. Yeah, I can't do that man. You know, it's crazy. It's
like I bet shit is a little bit more toothsome and like I bet you're I bet
smelling it is just a little bit more pleasant. That is such a such a crazy
word to use for
I need nicotine. I'm popping a yeah yeah. You are going. I was like I have to I
can't have normally if I was having a drink. Of course, I'd have nicotine in my
mouth, but I'm not gonna put
and then eat stew. You're gonna eat. You're gonna take a shot of the stew
later or take a bite later in the zen. The residual mint is gonna be still in
your mouth and it's gonna make you vomit. That actually sounds a little
better. Yeah, I feel like you should have spiller completely or you guys are
No, I just dropped one. I just want to say, I mean, no, no disrespect, Caleb.
It was really nice of you to make this, but you watch Ragusea. He always says,
he always says to over season something if it's going to get diluted later.
And you said you put in a little bit of salt.
Wouldn't it be really nice if it was salt?
Like to over season it?
Like herbs and pepper and chilies.
You should have put like Cajun seasoning in it or something.
Yeah, Old Bay, like something that would actually hit the senses.
I didn't want to dilute the, it's not about the stew, man.
man. Okay, I think we had the alcohol. I don't know. We had a little bit of hot
sauce. I think we could stomach all the eating room temperature,
beef,
do it. It's dude for
it's dude for hours man. It's dude for hours, by the way, just going going to
the to the liquor store and they have all they have all the vodka's and I have
like the raspberry and the and the lime and they're all it's all like you can
see they're all pushed back on the shelter. One was coming in and buying
I did you see the one shelf. It's completely full. It's the
full clip of beef, but all the way down. I did think about bringing a couple. I
didn't want to spend too much money on this because
it's of what it is, but I thought about maybe buying a bunch of different kinds
of alcohol so that everybody could choose. Oh my God, that would have been
a good idea. It would have been a good idea. Yeah, look at what it looks like.
You know what you know it would have been good. What oh my God, I mean it
already is good, but it looks like they go by.
It doesn't look human. It looks like a fish shit. Yeah. You know what would have been
actually good is a couple years ago Arby's made a curly fry seasoned vodka or seasoned
fried vodka and I think that that would have been the best, the most viable option here.
I listen, nobody would have liked it if we took a bite of the alcoholic beef stew and
it was good. It's actually pretty good. That's true. But then we would have eaten a lot of
have it and gotten really hammered and all like we're going to be eating it
over the course of the night. You're still going to eat it. Don't worry,
yeah
and over the course of that is
by the way. If you're playing at home, you got to take a bite of beef stew
either a stew. It's a it's not a drinking game. It's a
take it by a spoon full of beef stew. You got to take a full of beef stew
every time that we mention like the and you know guy or the terrifier
eating just being like you want to come out. You want to pre game before we go
to party and play an eating game. Yeah, that's what you guys like jello shots.
I hate that shit. You hate jello shots.
I don't like I don't like jello.
Yeah, like jello fans love
someone takes a jello shot and says, oh, I should buy a six pack of jello
tomorrow. This actually hits. I know one guy who loves jello shots that I
still don't think we can. I don't want to blow a spot up on the show, but
we're talking about him earlier. I think you know what I'm talking about.
Number one,
Jell-O shots, yeah. That's the type of guy who's a Jell-O shot fan, I think.
I mean... Not a Jell-O fan, but a fan of snacks. I have been thinking for a while that they...
I mean, that's what we talked about, actually. That was the origin of beef stew was alcohol
edibles, right? Yeah. Yeah. That's what we were talking about. I think so. And I think
this proves that it's a completely viable business. I mean, I hope to see dispensaries
popping up. They do make... I was looking into it. They do make, like, gummies. Alcohol
like edibles yeah you can like it's champagne and a good bite here so oh my
god pierce you look so scared.
I love you.
You do look fucking you look like a kid about to get a shot.
You don't like this at all that's good.
I truly don't drink hard alcohol.
You've seen my figure.
Yeah.
It's slim.
That's true.
But I got a beer belly.
Because it's only beer.
Yeah.
All right, should we let's dive in dude. Yeah. Wait. Well, what should we do?
Should we dive right in or should yeah, by the way, instead of painting on my art,
my masterpiece was the beef stew. I hope that's pretty clear. I'll be perfectly
honest. It does look like Uranus. Mm hmm. A little bit, but not the planet.
Dude, chill on me. Chill on me, dude. No fucking don't sound effect me, man.
You know, I'm too far to touch that. The fuck? Sorry. Why haven't you said that
every single time he's done it then.
You know I'm too far to touch that.
You always sit on that side of the table, you've always been too far to touch it.
Yeah, but he...
I'm pointing out a logical fallacy in here.
No, it's not a fallacy.
I'm gonna touch you after.
When Patrick gets vodka drunk, he turns into fucking Ben Shapiro.
Actually, you've always had that comeback, but you never used it.
What do you want me to say, man? I just thought of it today.
I thought of it a couple hours ago.
Beef time, y'all.
Yeah, okay, try it. Take a beef. Hit a beef. It really is like eating a bull.
My biggest beef, y'all.
Oh, that's the biggest one.
My biggest beef.
Let's see you take it.
And how's that?
The beef hits. Once you get used to the beef, it's not so hard.
Yeah, beef is fine.
Beef hits.
I've got a letter here.
It doesn't hit anymore.
I've got a letter here from OJ the alien, but I'm going to read it, I guess, after we
play this song.
What kind of fucking, who's delivering these space letters, man?
I just found it on the front steps.
It's kind of scary.
I found it on the front steps earlier.
So Julio, why don't you play this new song?
I believe it's called...
I've been loving these tracks by the way, Patrick.
Oh, thank you, Pierce.
And Dr. Dazzle really shined on the last one.
That was two songs ago.
There was another one.
Dr. Dazzle probably would say thank you if he knew you said that just now.
And OJ would also say thanks.
It was called OJ the Alien Floop on Uranus.
Floop on your Uranus.
Yeah.
shit.
Alien bitch with a hat full of Lincoln logs Mailman open up let me see your stinking balls
Pussy get wet like a tube down Niagara Falls I don't want that I want mailman stinky balls
I just did a drug called "Flute" at my good friend Paul's
Watching new guy, favorite actor, yeah it's DJ Qualls
Paranoia is in, I just inhaled aerosols
I wanna look at my mailman and his big fat stinky balls
I need fluke everyday
I don't poop, I got withdrawals
I'm here mailman
Take out your big fat stinky balls
Freaking the fuck out
What the fuck was that?
I did too much fluke and I'm freaking the fuck out
It's a rap outro, they're dated but they still happen
Here's a joke
Oh it's another song
Yeah you thought bitch
Woah
You're an idiot
*laughter*
Hmm
(upbeat music)
- That was an interesting one.
- It seems like some kind of drug.
- Yeah, I think that's the end.
- It's not the strongest track by a mile.
- No, I think the drug is really affecting
the quality of his music.
- I think that, yeah, I think something's going on with him.
I got this letter too.
- Yeah, read it.
What does it say?
- There's a notice to cease and desist.
What?
This is a letter.
Just read it. Read out what it says.
Notice to cease and desist.
Dear podcast about list.
This is a letter served upon due to the song
Floop on Your Uranus being played on your YouTube channel.
They sent it before we even played it, man.
I think he didn't want to.
Yeah, he's playing 40 chess.
I think he didn't want us to to play and get his signature here.
I drew an alien.
He didn't want us to.
I love that.
I think he didn't want us to play it and look at his
it's notarized because he said
why didn't he want us to play it? I don't know. I guess it just because it
was he was all drugged up. Yeah, I think I think he wants to play
something. Yeah, he's talking about he's he's wants to grab his mailman's ball
sack and stuff and
I don't know. I think he probably wants us to play a song that he's
more proud of
what like
Julio, can you pull this other one up?
- Yeah, two songs? - Let's just play this other...
- Two songs in one day? - Is this one also about uranus?
Um, maybe.
Whoa, was this... did he send this over email?
I think so.
It's Sojay the alien, y'all.
Oh, his voice is back
high again. - Oh, okay, good. - He's off the drugs, I guess.
Or maybe he's on the drugs?
Yeah, maybe. We'll see.
Playing in my bed
I hear the
♪ If the clock can't think of you ♪
- All right, that's enough of that.
- Yeah.
- What the fuck is that?
- What?
- I know, what is, that's four minutes long.
- Is that a cover?
- Can we just scrub through real quick?
- Yeah.
- Can we just, can we scrub through it?
- Yeah, scrub through a little bit.
Maybe turn it up a little louder.
♪ Time after time ♪
♪ If you fall I'll catch you up and you'll be waiting ♪
- Can we just keep scrubbing through,
maybe not linger too long on any?
I think I get it. Yeah, I think I'm time after time. So why would he do time
after time? I think the flu is affecting him because why it makes no sense for
him to send a cease and desist and it makes no sense for him
to start singing when he's a rapper
and he doesn't have a good singing. It appears OJ the alien has lost the plot.
I think that some things are going wrong in OJ the alien's life. It's such a
it really was really P. He was doing hard and so fast and then fell off. This is
like when I really I just started
doing shows in Croatia. Yeah, I kind of am dreading the news. I'm going to wake
up tomorrow and he's been zapped. Yeah, oh my God, self got in with some bad
about crowd and yeah he got zapped in his in his space. Yeah, he died on the
prober like Dallas. He pulled up at a purple light
and they zapped him. Yeah, damn yeah, I just really hope I really hope he can
get his act together. Maybe he needs to go to some intergalactic rehab. This is
his like dark period. I don't wanna see, I don't wanna see the last thing to go
through his head to be his
his green tongue, like
he needs to go to like, he needs to go to
Galactaholic. Nice. Yeah, or Flupus, sorry. Unonymous. Galactaholic's
unknown space, not a galactic ononimus. Why didn't they just call it unknown
amiss?
We are
known
I'd like to remember my
some very fascinating information.
I'd like to voice changer, because I'd like to remain completely unknown to
did you say I'm known in this city? No, no, I said whatever you think it's
supposed to be. I said
unknown and my name is
most
why'd you do
there? We go be like on the phone. I forgot that we have a voice changing to
do guys is beef stews kind of hit me hard. I'm not going to yeah, I'm already
drunk, but I think that to it's I don't think I called. I really don't want to
come back for more. I think we're done for until we can have later until we're
done. I'm definitely done until my next bite, no doubt about it. I think the
table, I think it's time to get going. You all must get going, man. I think it's
time to ride. It's thanksgiving, dude. Guess what we fucking do on thanksgiving.
We talk about people who like to wear baby stuff for all kinds of reasons, not
just because they want to be a baby fetish wise, but because they might want
to be a baby. Some of them want to be a toddler fetish. Yeah, right. But it's not
always a fetish. Some people just leak. Some people have a leaky pipe. Some
people have some guys. I'm proud. I'm very proud to announce that for the what
fourth year running, I have resisted developing this fetish when researching
it. Yep. Every single time I get a little scared that I'm going to be like,
"Wait, I actually like this shit." No, it's always you get scared that you're
gonna understand it too much. And then I never have. I never have. Yeah. It's
like if, like if, if, if like Jane Goodall went to live with chimpanzees
at the time.
Stupid monkeys
coming back and presenting it be like
monkeys eating shit.
They fucking
Jane good on today. We're going to be thrown pooping monkeys.
Why are you getting on a flight to Africa to hang out with the fucking
monkeys again just or I guess it's
they're funny. I don't know yeah. I need I need a hobby. You know who is
cooking? You obviously hate hanging out with those. You obviously hate them. No,
I just feel like I need to get
next time I hang out with the apes. I'm going to make alcoholic stew.
It is basically like
fucked up next
so funny. If I got if I got fucked up in the stew is dribbling down my mouth
when I was hanging out with monkeys. Damn, that'd be sick as sometimes I feel
like the only way I can even stand to be around these chimps is being completely
off my
they don't even speak English. Has she passed away? Yeah, oh God, past
past a monkey, past a monkey. Yeah, well, probably on the street. I will say
every time I read the diaper forum posts, I don't I don't get any closer to the
fetish, but I do think it is so weird that we landed on toilets like as a way
as a way to handle our process. There are a lot of people on the on the forums who
are like this is the future, like people don't understand how amazing it is to be
able to poop and pee wherever I didn't include it, but I saw a guy on because I
did all my stuff is from the ABDL subreddit. Yeah, I'd never looked at that
before and I finally looked at it and I saw a guy who was like, do you I really
I don't want that. I was a guy was like, I really think that if we started a
diaper party in the United States, it would get 10% of the vote.
And everybody was like, I think it'd be more than 10% because it would be...
It would unlock something in people once they knew that it was okay to do. People
think that everybody has this urge to be a baby. They also have so many posts where
they're like, "I was at a concert and I was looking around and my theory is that,
yeah, there were 200 other people there in diapers because I could tell by the way they
were walking." He was just walking up to women with big asses and just like, "No,
no, I'm you got a diaper in there. I'm checking for a diaper. Don't don't no,
no, no walking around Magic City
diaper. These women got diapers on Holy shit,
but yeah, okay, I'll go first. I spoiled what I did. Yeah, but did you? Oh,
yeah,
yeah, I did the ABDL subreddit. Normally, we do the forum, but I had a hard
time searching on the forum and finding out how to search because I'm not very
good at that. The computers kind of stuff, right? That's Cameron's ball game.
Okay, would the ABDL community, we'll go back, would the ABDL community want a
diaper that looks used? Just curious if a diaper that is yellow at the bottom so
it always looks like the baby is in a used diaper would be appealing. Like a
prank gift, like a gag gift? I think it's like a... No, it's like...
You always got it on you. Yeah. Like you never caught lacking. Like you always...
I think it's like, "I always got this thing on me." Always got it on you.
It's so you can't tell. It's like how that... Oh, true. It's like the general
going into war wearing his brown pants.
Yeah.
You know, that's this classic joke.
Is that a classic? I've never heard that. Tell it.
They general goes in, they say, why do you wear a red shirt?
He's like, so if I get shot, my men don't see the gunshot wound
and get demoralized.
I say, oh, then what about the brown pants?
Shit, shit, shit himself.
Yeah.
I heard that's a diaper is always yellow.
No one's going to, everyone, no one will look at the baby and say,
oh, the baby peed himself.
They're going to say, oh, it's a diaper.
It's a diaper that's yellow on the bottom.
It's got yellow on the bottom.
And a pee stain shape.
It's very fashionable.
the real reason is because the blood drips down from his shirt and then
obviously when it oxidizes it turns brown. That's why generals wear brown
pants in the leg right yeah yeah. I heard generals have to pretend they
didn't get fucking shot. Generals have to pretend that they didn't get shot.
Yes, that's hard to do. That's really going to be the hardest job ever,
yeah, especially when it's on a like part of the body that's visible.
Soldiers have to pretend that they did get shot
true yeah
good job. You can go home.
Okay, next slide, please.
This is a comment where it says, How about a brown one as well? The O P says
yeah, maybe LL and then the guy replies again or maybe the front is yellow and
the back of the diapers brown interest. Wow, really good brainstorm designing
some yeah, okay next
a B D L and Christianity. I'd never considered this. I know that very few
people in the a B D L community are a Christian. That's a shame, but I figured
I'd make this known anyways. So I had recently spoken with a friend. He's a
deacon at my local church, and I told him about ABDL, saying how I was confused
on whether or not it violated God's law, and this is what I gathered. ABDL isn't
a God, it doesn't directly include idolatry, adultery, or covetousness. It
doesn't harm your neighbor, aka anyone. For any Christians on this subreddit,
single or in a relationship, keep this in mind when partaking in ABDL. Do not
idolize ABDL. Do not covet others' diapers just because you don't have the
print they have. And most importantly, do not commit adultery with someone else's
baby
or themselves and save those thoughts and actions for your spouse and or future
husband slash wife. Lastly, and this might be unnecessary, but but always
find time to read the Bible and be with God and then find time to be in your
little space undisturbed adultery with a baby. So that's like an action Bronson
line.
What does God think of someone when they're in their little space? Does he
does he hold the same tenderness to that person as he does to real infants? It's
kind of a hack to get into heaven. Yeah, yeah, just when you're when it's time to
die, instead of like thrashing and saying, I don't want to go thrash but go
die, die like a baby, just die. They don't even know. Isn't that the thing
like Mormons, like when they have like the separate kingdoms and like if you
are like before, like if you die before the age of eight, you get to the best
one, you get into the best one. Yeah, maybe that's what maybe some of these
ABDL people are Mormons and they would they know they're going to, they're
ready to die. It seems like Mormonism would be different from I think a B D
would be not allowed in more. A Mormonism has a lot of just
Mormons have special underwear that they wear. Oh yeah, they're wearing.
Yeah, they basically are. Oh my gosh, bullet proof. Wait, what if that's the
reason that they're always wearing the special underwear? They're allowed to be
weird. They're only allowed to be weird. Yeah, they only drink soda. Only in a
specific way. If they break outside of that weirdness and start doing odd
things like drinking coffee than they on things like being gay. Well,
or being of a different race than white to them. That might be a little to me.
Those are the two most normal things ever.
Next slide, please.
You're not alone. Thanks for this post. I definitely do tend to covet other
people's diapers. Sometimes, God, that's wrong. Great. Thank you. Diaper Danny
for admitting diaper. Danny Diaper Danny, you gotta go see the diaper. Deacon
confess to this sin. Okay, next one
which food
makes the biggest poop
burger.
I didn't include any responses because people were saying
cillian husk or something. It is so funny that if you spend time thinking
you're a baby and you then go on a community for people who do that, it is
the closest you get to a community for baby.
Baby's going on
I have a lot of stuff like that makes the biggest food. I know the food and
poop are related.
This next post is would wearing an American flag print diaper be an act of
treason?
Oh shit, we got to look at the forum here. I mean on one hand people wear
American flag shirts all the time and there's nothing wrong with that, but
also like you're peeing on it and stuff. So does that change it? I need to hear
you're like being on it and
what else doesn't want to say doesn't want to say boom. Yeah, they don't say
poop that's or number three all right next.
Oh, I did that one twice. That's awesome next you awesome. Oh, my God, the fiery
pits of hell are no match for this little demon baby. This is just
face up themselves on a bonfire burned alive
there. You're like a weed shirt, an all over weed print shirt and huff weed
socks and they have a little, a little bafflement. That's why they're going to
hell. See, I don't understand the diaper. It's because of the weed. Yeah, I guess
this answers what
we were saying earlier about going to heaven and being like a baby. Yeah, you
just go to hell, but no one fucks
not even the devil.
Well, imagine you
you go to hell, but no one
they don't want to poke you with a pitchfork and the diaper and the
stuff come out yeah and somebody replied to this very kindly and said, even in
hell, your diaper's still soaked. Kind of a come on kind of sounds like a yeah
that sounds like a line from Mad Max Fury Road. Even in hell, your diaper's
I don't get it. Why would I leave? Why would you be brought any relief in hell?
Well,
yeah, you like you want it so so here's what here's what I'm thinking. You like
it soaked, but hell is as hot as an oven, so it would dry it out exactly yeah.
this is this is this is like a saying you're. This is why it's such a great
compliment. There's a the odds be ever in your favor. You did such a powerful
wedding that even the flaming brimstone pits of hell could not dry this out
right. I wish we could say stuff like that more to each other, like to our
closest friends, like hey, your your ass is so loose that not even the biggest
dicked gargoyle in hell could make you feel it.
they'll be kind. We should say yeah, yeah, all right next
tip for making nice explosions. I I've already tried both banana and marshmallow
inside and I had some wonderful explosions. What else can I try inside
and the first do very it's oatmeal isn't it do yes, bro.
Next slide, this guy knows his shit next. I call it the oatmeal trick.
We talked about the
three tricks, the marshmallow trick, the oatmeal trick and the banana trick.
so oatmeal is great. This guy says eaten or inserted. This guy says inserted or
poured into your diaper and then he replies insert it and then double replies
again to the first post as inserted inserted like like you put the oatmeal
on and then you pretend fit and you know you or you you feel you can also just
fill your diaper with. I don't have hours to make poop.
I guess
you have the money to eat to buy and eat so much food that you explode exactly. I
have that kind of money. Just go to Taco Bell or another person and eat as much as you can.
Yeah, I just started a ABDL story YouTube channel and I need more of these. I include you. I
included this video. I included this video. I want to watch this video. This is a story
that they that they this is unbreakable. I fucking got in Henry's journey of Oh, wait,
actually, this isn't the one I wanted. Wait, can you go? Well, this might be good, too.
I haven't heard this one, but let's hear.
Little World Journey.
Unbreakable Bonds, Ben and Henry's journey of love and growth.
Time to take a bite.
Hello. Hello, Ben and Henry Journey.
We have a great time over these past couple of months.
I had to get used to this, but it was smooth.
Henry had no problem with giving up control of his own day to day activities.
Henry it's time for lunch. It's your favorite mac and cheese with chicken nuggets.
I just had to pick him up in his high chair and snapped him in.
How are you doing after your nap baby bunny? I asked.
To make him feel more like a baby I made up a little nickname for him.
He was very happy for that I had a good nickname for him.
As we were getting ready for the first trip, I was thinking about the job was a good thing for me.
Baby Bunny and I had a rocky start, but now I would have changed it for the world.
There will be a full Baby Bunny playlist to put them in order.
oh my God,
I don't think that this will mean anything to you three, but this is
functionally exactly identical to the song Jennifer by pig destroyer. This is
really this
could be on. This could be a bunny. Yeah, it's it's a it's a text to speech, a
text to speech fucked up. It's kind of scary man. Yeah, I'm gonna be real.
It's really scary out there listening. We'll know that song. Yeah, all right,
next line. This is that
Let's see what do I have here? Oh yeah, yeah, I don't need to hear that again
looking for a BDL gamers that play GTA
looking to play GTA with other babies like myself. Let me know if you're
interested. I don't even would you there's no room for baby. It's a
make the role the role playing server. It's just you pushing each other and
you only get to play as a baby for the moment that your characters ragdolling
on
There's not a more adult acting game that exists in the world, I think.
Well, role playing as babies in GTA, you just don't leave the house.
You just all are in different houses and you're not allowed to leave.
Yeah, babies don't do anything.
You know what?
Babies don't drive cars.
No, you can't open up a door.
They ride carriages.
You know what game you should be playing?
What's that?
The first two minutes of Fallout 3.
They would love that shit.
That's all you need.
First two minutes, don't touch the book.
Sitting in the crib, don't do it.
Don't touch the book at all.
Just walk around.
around. Just don't do anything
don't touch the book. Don't make your special go up. He's just playing it for
for twelve hours and
that's my dad trying to play fall out
games. Not fun. You just plays a fucking baby
that you have to touch the book. How the fuck is I supposed to know that
do you think babies used to bark at each other like dogs before we invented
civilization
absolutely probably babies in separate cribs just going and then four minutes
later
that's how they talk man yeah. They talk to each other. They go to be a
bigum yeah. It is funny when a long johnson
cat says that
an adult cat yeah all right. I think I just have a title on here. Daddy is
daddy daddy pissed in my ass. Jaddy deleted
Jaddy
this. I really debated about whether or not including the body of this post and I
decided against it because it was truly one of the most repulsive things I've
ever read. You should have put it in sometimes have to draw the line. Yeah,
it was about a woman who comes home and her her husband, who is her daddy,
takes off her diaper and and pissed it in her. I don't know what to tell you
I'll say, oh dear, better left to the imagine. Yeah, you don't want any
we're thinking about it. I mean like it's hard to it's hard to get a good
stream going when you're hard right. Yeah, it must be difficult to piss in
and actually
she said he had the hardest cock I've ever seen and he pissed in my ass and I
was like I call cat. Yeah, I smell cap right now. I know I know what you got
sure yeah sure yeah yeah daddy pissed at a hard to your yeah. No, I really
believe that no daddy would have had to have a soft a soft cock and he would
have had to spread the anus like a urinal exactly. She leaves the group to
go to the bathroom. I was like she's such a bitch. He's always lying
daddy pissed in her ass. I know her well. A lot of people people decides me
smelled cap everybody on here was saying people
people
smelled cap
forgot about this stew at the beef.
Caleb don't eat it like that.
You're going to get in trouble. I like it
people besides me spelled cap and said take this over to to new news, new
website slash r slash
a b d l stories. Oh, and then I discovered a whole nother world. And I
think I just have one post from this wife treating me like a baby wife
treating me like a child wife treats me like a baby. Hi everyone. So my wife is
super hot and I love her very much. She's middle aged with two Children of
ours. Wow. And there's no other way of saying it, but she treats me like a baby
literally. For example, the other day we were in a friend's gathering, she
randomly comes up to me, or comes up to squeeze her nose, saying, "Do I need
to do a poopy?" At the dinner table, she spat on a tissue and wiped my face
with it. I have to call her "Mummy." She pats my butt in public, uses baby
wipes to wipe my face, calls me a good boy and mommy's boy all the time.
She even threatens to put me in a stroller. Once we were traveling and
there was no space in the car as it was packed with stuff, but the
baby booster car seat was empty. She strapped me in and took the whole ride
there with me in it. Now she asked me randomly. Do I need a change and
checking if I do well? I'm sure your have now figured out what she means by
that and what she has got me wearing. Please help. She even bought me a dummy
pacifier. He gets in the in the car to go on the road trip and she just like
there's just a bunch of like not even like just clean tissues on the on the
passenger seat. She's like oh that looks like there's a mess in here like you
can't sit in the passenger seat. I can't because there's only one spot in the
car. You can sit a piece of tissue paper, just a water bottle as well. Yeah,
I
forgot to screenshot him, but he has two comments in this thread where it's clear
that he is the only person on the ABL stories. He was not telling a story and
he actually wants help and he's saying help help and does can anybody help me
with my situation? He doesn't like this. He doesn't want to be like a baby. No,
they're encouraging it and they're probably like fuck I'm jacking the fuck
off every
posting it in character. No, he's looking at his username kind of kinky
twenty twenty two, but he's only kind of kinky.
He wants to become a baby and sit the back seat born in twenty twenty two. Oh
my God,
I'm like a baby. Wait a second. All babies want to be treated like normal
yeah toddlers. My what you mean your mom buddy right? That's a little confused.
Yeah, children do get confused and try to marry their mother. Yeah, it's when
It's like it's like calling your your teacher mom actually calling your mom,
your wife, right? Do you ever call your teacher mom accidentally yeah? I never
did that. I think I have missus Iosu.
You mix that up with mom.
Okay,
that's cool. All right, so that's all I have all right. Yeah, all right, I'll
slip in here. I want to yeah. I mean look minor. Do you how many do you have
because I have like I want light and anticipation of peers having five
hundred. This is how many I have and they're all extremely long, but I'm not
I'm going to read all of them. I didn't even I didn't even it wasn't even worth
putting these on a slide, but do you guys remember the guy I read last time who
told the story about smooshing with knees while spooning? No, it all blends
I pretty much don't remember the last one because I was so drunk. Yeah, good
that it blacked I blacked out. Well, this is his name is for taped with with
three DS, so I'm just going to read some of these and look I can go and then
someone else can go and then you can even come back to me if you like all
I can remember a few years back I was in Walmart riding one of those disabled carts
I was wearing a disc diaper a mega max and I knew I had to poop real bad
But I just needed a few things and the aisle was full of people shopping stocking shelves
But I only needed one or two things and I was out of there
So I rode right up to the deodorant I needed and I was getting off the cart and I just started to shit my diaper hard
It wasn't like I was trying to but it just exploded out of me made lots of noise snapping poping
snapping and pooping that squelch sound as it met resistance against the seat of
my diaper and it blew out one or both of the leg holes, and I was a stinky mess.
I tried to avoid eye contact with people, but I know they were all docking
docking spelled G O C K
at me. I sat down on the seat of the cart and there was a loud squelch. I
just wish I had never been in there that day. I have had a few bad accidents in
that store, but I rode to the front paid for my two items, then squished towards
the door and my diaper was full and sloppy leaking into my sweat pants. I had
not put my plastic pants on over my diaper that day either. My wife drove me
home with the windows down and she said, believe I had just messed myself like
that in the store. I tried to say it was an accident, but she was just embarrassed.
It happened for me, I guess, but I woke up the next day, so it didn't kill me.
Wow.
Beautiful.
Wait, so he...
This guy's not an adult baby though, right?
No.
This guy's just incontinent.
Here, actually, he has a story about how he became like this.
So he blew out the legs of his cotton shorts in a rascal scooter?
Yes.
Oh my God.
That might, yeah, that might keep me from ever going outside again if I saw that.
He's just in Walmart, you see a guy...
A guy in a disabled scooter just shitting himself.
Like the airbag prank.
like yeah,
it's so loud. It's like a trampoline,
yeah, and it's you would be walking down the aisle behind him and he would stand
up to grab his deal, yeah, and then it's go up and he was in front of you. As
soon as he started, when we were kids, we saw people walking or riding around
in those disabled scooters. We thought that's so unfortunate. I mean, maybe you
feel a little bit of like revulsion like that's so lazy. You should be walking
around, but then you were like no, you know what this is not a disgusting
loony tunes volcano
and squelches out of their jeans to the point that they're like a whole pop. I
should be nice,
not for that,
just the image of like, like a fucking air bag going off under the seat,
snapping
wonder thinking someone sneezed on your arm.
The fuck is this
okay? This is he has many he's told his story many times, but this is here's
one a short a short version of spark notes. I hated it when I first became
incontinent. I true I truly tried to kill myself several times, but for
reasons I can't explain. I just didn't think too deep after that, as I lost
everything that I was as a man everything and I was a hard ass patch
building biker. I said what I wanted, did what I wanted, took no shit out of any
two people at once, and I felt invincible. Then one day, I got hit on
the head on my bike.
74 miles per hour. That all had the bells and whistles as far as HP speed,
never been in an accident like this, so now I got nothing. No bike, I would
never ride again, my job, been a teamster, dock worker, union rep,
everything and now I have to wear a fucking diaper to boot. I had been to
jail, lost very close brothers. I would never see on this earth again. I was a
fucking man, God damn it, and men don't go out like this. I was left only with my
wonderful lot wife and my five kids and what am I going to do? I was in a very
dark depression. I wish I was dead and to top it all off, I had to wear diapers to
Once latter, I was able to get on the toilet by myself.
And as I said, I lost who I was as a man,
and I wasn't ever gonna get that back.
My job, my club, being able to take my wife
on a nice vacation, everything.
Then I had a long couple of really deep talks about God.
I had been a Christian for decades,
but I wasn't walking with his cadence.
My health started to go downhill fast.
Other shit started to happen.
And somewhere in that time,
I found myself having to wear diapers again.
And that went on for months.
I had been to my doctor, and in a month and a half,
I went to see another doctor.
They did tests.
I went to another specialist in another month,
went by and the months went by and I'm still in diapers
as I go to get up to the toilet,
but I'm pissing and shitting my diaper.
And I was working on my attitude and praying a lot
not to get healed.
My left leg was as good as it ever was gonna get,
but I had nerve damage in my back from the wreck.
And that had just exacerbated my back.
Now I got nerve damage.
Long story short, I didn't wanna get the surgery done
as it was my back and the doctors really didn't know shit.
So yeah, I was gonna be stuck with the shit.
Yeah, I was gonna be stuck in diapers
and I couldn't tell myself anymore. So I just slowly accepted the fact and I
became impartial to diapers. Then I grew what felt better until I became one of
them and a D L diaper lover. And now I just love how they feel. This is that
old saying, you can't beat him like it's insane to me. You hear that story and
you think my God, how you could be brought so low, how ignominious of yes,
how horrible yeah, she could just be hit on the head and be dragged into this
world of suffering. How terrible is this and then you realize that this guy is
also spends his day posting five hundred post a day on a forum alongside like
he's just chatting with people named like baby kitten one to
I wish you lovely boy and so
wake up every single day. It's bro yeah. This guy, this guy wakes up every day
and he's like I'm going to go on the diaper lovers form and do a full good
Isabella's voice over yeah
here. I'll just finish this. Well, yeah, I've suffered the most horrible fate.
You could possibly suffer and still be alive time to go chat with my my
friends. Yeah, it's not so be a two thousand
I was maybe one one one.
Have I been going forever? I can I can read maybe a little bit. I got I got I
can cut you up. Okay, I'll just finish this story.
That old saying you can't beat him join him. Well, I join them and every time I
going something the marines, the club, the teamsters, I going hard a hundred
percent. So I went from hating life to embracing it and diapers are something I
just had to accept and find a reason to embrace them. That was a long time ago,
and I am still here and now I sort of look forward to every soaked, messy
diaper as what else am I supposed to do? I am finding ways to have fun with it,
so I don't get into a funk, which just takes me back to square number one good
enough for yeah get into a funk.
Yeah, so I don't get into that. Put me in a fun. Yeah, my life. Yeah, if I
get a scooter, I will say we should definitely go pretty long today,
because I think we have twenty minutes up top of us silently eating stew.
Yeah,
yeah, I wouldn't worry too much.
This isn't my slide show. Mine is
it says Patrick Diaper.
What is Patrick stinks giving gift? That's from last year from last year.
That's last year show.
Okay, so this first one here.
hold on. I get it. Okay. Now I'll be able to read it now.
Wondering which celebrities could be good caregivers and which would be good
babies. I think Anne Hathaway would be a perfect mommy for adults. Babies.
Alexa Bliss would make a perfect adult baby. That's from baby Joe 698. And
then this next one looks so much like a baby. No, he does not look like a
baby. He looks like a kid rock. Right now. I could see Taylor Swift as my
mommy and Selena Gomez as my AB sibling. Of course, it's a weird,
unobtainable dream. Now this guy looks like a fucking baby. Yeah,
this guy looks a lot like a guy has it figured out even as a
mobile. Uh huh.
This next slide. What's that? What's I forget on what's on the
next one. Oh, and the governess
I don't know, but a resident evil character, nappy to truck
driver, padded truck driver said
this next one is the future or of or diapers, which I think was
supposed to be the future of diapers. And this whole thread
was just people explaining just things that they hope for the
future of diapers. The baby link nine said, I'll paraphrase
what is next for diapers. What could diapers add? Is there a
feature that you have always hoped for diapers, but have they
haven't got it yet or something you think that would be fun.
Diapers could always be upgraded in leak guards or absolutely
their absorbency absorbency. Thank you. But what other things
could they possibly need and Marcus P said my idea is to add a pocket of
sorts to the front of the diaper, such that it would allow males to be erect at
night and not leak. I've seen a ton of stuff about people complain that they
can't get hard. Well, no, when they get when they sleep and they get night wood
or morning wood, either their penis is erect up, they tuck it, they tuck it up
in the waistband and they pee all over their belly button. Yeah, they it's
sucked down owner make some P their boner goes well. They're incontinent, so
they P in the bed, but they might get a boner when there's in asleep as well. So
if it's down, they say it hurts too bad. It does and a diaper was not. I don't
think most diapers were built with boners in mind. Yeah, no, at least not
human human boners. Yeah, baby boners. They don't get the or dog bone. They
get boners. I don't get you seem to be the expert on that. I'm a fucking expert
Yeah, next slide. You don't want to talk about that more. My diaper would be that
of the rectangular style diaper with the high capacity of today's diaper. Just
like the first style pamper. I do want to go back to 100 and I do think that
they should make a tiny little pocket. Just a tiny one. That's what Marcus P
said. So you're stealing his show. Yeah, you're stealing his whole flow. Marcus
P. That's who the guy from before the guy in the last slide. Yeah, yeah. But I
think that he was saying that he wanted a pocket for his adult erection. Caleb
Caleb was saying a baby erection.
Caleb was saying baby erection.
Like Tom Brady's kid.
I think that there should be one for a baby erection.
I can't admit that my little brother
when he was a baby used to walk around
You can't admit, hold on, stop.
I don't know what you finished the sentence with.
He used to get a red one.
It's like a dog bone.
Yeah, he used to get a little red one.
And on the cover it should be a little baby boy going like this.
And it should say with pockets.
it's with front pocket with front pockets for a little red, but I don't want to if
I'm a dad, I don't have to talk that shit. I don't want to think about that
talk. My baby's dick into a fucking pocket before he goes to sleep. That's
fucked up, man. You can't explain that to your kid why he's got to put it in
the pocket. Then you got to explain what a is. Yeah, you don't see nothing. He
can't be explained. I know, but you know, by the way, you'd never have to
explain what a boner is. Nobody ever explained to me what a boner was. I'd
I'd like to see a variety of good ones produced in the US. Instead of China, I
like that shit. I like that shit. This next one, this next slide, did the TSA
get better at catching diapers? So I went through really recently with a
diaper and got pulled aside and just patted down. It was extremely
professional. I've always wanted to wear through TSA and it's not bad. I said I
was embarrassed and they said they deal with it all the time. But imagine this
crazy. We we have we overlapped so much really would completely different posts,
but we have so much of the same. I got to
and and new diaper invention. Oh my God, yeah, so holy shit, that's incredible.
We can go deeper into both of those things. I was just imagining like diaper
like I don't know to come and stick a dynamite in the diaper. You're not going
to go past patting you down. Yeah, yeah, I have I mean in my slides. I
discovered the explanation for why this happens, why they get with the diapers.
All right, so what's the next one? I understand that.
Okay, next one. That might be my last slide. Damn.
All right, let me do mine fast and then we sorry I was making a song.
Here's can do as many as okay, great to end it. Okay, does that sound great?
Sure, okay, is a millimeter wave detection, though, that the rest of your
too. Did you didn't even finish yours finished the whole thing? Let me see
sure you want me to show you the inside of my stomach. Show me the bowl. I ate
the bowl to
why do you want some boys to he didn't finish yours. Yeah, I did finish it.
All right,
Caleb,
you're having a tantrum. I'm not you're having a lot. You need your day. You're
having a lie. I like it when you tell the truth better. Okay, I didn't need
and
we can skip these first couple slides. We go up to
skip this first makeshift diaper. Oh, my God, I may use a cut block bag and put
a lot of paper towels above it. This is this is a
last active
is a close up
putting guns and holsters and then just one
so I just mostly put this one in because of the subject line, the title
airport security finally got me. Wow next slide, and this is the reason that
they get people with diapers. I fly all the time and only ever got flagged once
and it was because my diaper was extremely wet as I was running late. It
says they let they stop there. They stopped after they pat me down. Let me
use the room to change as they stepped out wasn't a big deal. The scanner just
picks up on the wetness. Oh my God, that makes they made me take I really ran to
the airport water in Chicago. I ran to the airport in Chicago and then my hat
had a little bit of sweat on it. They made me take my hat off.
Yeah, I always get I always get clothed right here. Yeah, my sweat they get
the they get the fluids they're checking to see if you're gonna blow up. Oh my
God, so that's because diaper wetters they cannot help. You know that a diaper
wearer is wedding in the TSA line, but that is the number one place on the
planet to wet your diaper. They give you that is the one place I would wet my
diaper. Oh yeah, yeah out of fear. Yeah, but do you think do you think that
there's no a B D O terrorists going through TSA because they're so happy
with their diapered life that like like I can't imagine being a diaper guy and
like a mass shooter. What would you crash into to send the perfect message
about diaper percolation
Yale? Yeah, I was opposite thing possible. Yeah, yeah, I went back to
toilet factory is really good. Yeah, I think yeah, they got diapers there to
would bring up a good point, though, which is that there's never been an a B D L
extremist. Well, there was a few like like
die hard communities of which there is no violent crop. Yeah, they should like
themselves on water.
There was that you remember that that woman, I think she was like a NASA
astronaut or something or like there was some thing where it was like a woman
like kidnapped somebody and then drove across the country in the diaper. I'm
misremembering all the details. That's just that's pragmatic. Yeah, if you're
going to drive across the country, there is like some story. I don't it was on
Nancy Grace a bunch. Oh, well, if there's a story, well, if there's a story, then
tell it perfectly with all the details.
So the next one is does wearing diapers regularly alter the mind over time? Yes.
Would you say that wearing diapers becomes addictive, leading to a diaper
dependency over time? I'm specifically aiming this question to those who are not
currently in content, but nevertheless feel or feel a need or even a compulsion
to wear a diaper and Roland double oh seven says the fun part in this
question is that somebody would not notice that thinking is not a linear
path, but thoughts come and go convictions can change memories are made
and lost. The mind changes all the time. These people convictions will never
change. They will always be on the record.
This next thing I'm going to read this next ones. I'm going to read the really
fast. These are really making me laugh. This is a post a topic called new app
Dypestash wow. I saw the post about this on the fucking reddit plain white
diaper post. I'm excited to see Android users now have an application to use
like iPhone users. It's called Dypestash. Has anyone used it yet? What
do you think antenna wearer says or someone says what does it do? I
literally have next to nothing app wise. I hate cell phones. Lol antenna
wearer says you're not the only one but trying to get a phone out of the
hands of the youth is like prizing a ray gun out of the hands quote of an
alien. Oh, yeah, even have a plain white diaper says it keeps track of
my inventory. It's as hard as something that doesn't have
it keeps track of your stash. It also tracks usage and helps remind you of
what you need to order. I also like that you can look through the catalog of
all the different kinds of diapers was the crinkles app and iphone only app
yeah, they talked about porting it to android, but I never heard of that
being completed. Lazy program. I just started using crinkles to track my
stash. It's good. I even set up ios shortcuts to quickly log a change for
my watch. It's pretty basic, but it does the core functions. Well, I haven't
I've seen dike stash, but it's just like this guy is talking about it. This is
like the this is your apple fan boy Fred from friend from high school who has the
full like workflow set up on his apple watch, but he's got linking he's got his
diaper linked to his apple.
They need there needs to be like a like a whoop like slap sleep tracker for
diapers and then notification that just is just okay. Well, this is and then
this is the last thing about this is omg three. One says nice app you mentioned
I'm on iPhone, so using crinkles, which is great, but the
dive stash app looks almost identical. I wonder if it's by
the same person, but under a different name for Android
users. I do recall many people mentioning that at one point
crinkles let you select if your change was wet, messy, etc,
but they no longer seem to do that or let you put in notes
now speaking of crinkles.
That's true.
Crinkle noise.
We got a or Pierce came back with not just the pierogies,
but also a big brown cake.
This is this is brown flavor.
This is not chocolate.
doesn't taste like chocolate at all.
And we don't have other forks.
I've never had a cake that tasted like nothing.
That is just brown.
This is just a brown cake.
It doesn't taste like a single thing.
There's clearly ingredients in this.
No.
Yeah. Look at all the layers of ingredients
right here.
What are you doing?
I'm pulling the top off.
Why are you ruining it? Why are you chopping the top off the
fucking cake, man?
I'm just lifting up the hood.
But there's no cocoa.
There's no cocoa.
It looks like to be covered in it, but I guess that is
flour.
I'm going to have wheat flour.
Here's the here's dipe tank.
This is diaper users pitching their new ideas for diapers. This is so good.
Okay.
What diapers do you fantasize about/wish actually existed? I wish I had diapers
that were covered in fake fur with a tail attached to the back. That's the
first post. And most people on here, 90% of them are... They just... They say,
"I want old diapers back. I want the diapers from the '80s." Diapers used
to be better, they said. They used to be better. They also say,
"I wish that they made baby diapers in adult sizes with the same characters
on." I wonder why they think that diapers used to be better. Everything
everything used to be better. I did used to be better. I wonder I wonder there's
maybe I wonder if there's maybe like a
like a memory that they have as you put in the Tucker's in
maybe one is in so bad, say his name,
but so those are the main things that people say, but some people have a more
interesting ideas that I think we can look into one problem. I was mayhem
whose picture is a guitar yeah that's an eight string guitar. Yeah,
it's stupid. That's an Ibanez says one problem that I find with the printed
slash ABDL diapers these days is that they aren't really crinkly. We want
crinkle. It would be great to sound like a bag full of leaves when I walk
around my house. Yeah, I wouldn't do everybody to catch you hear you from a
mile away. Buridan says no escape diapers. The tapes are adjustable for
five minutes after the diaper is put on, then the adhesive sets the tapes
cannot be undone until moisture reaches the top of the wetness indicator. The
weirdly strong plastic is resistant to household scissors. A saw trap. If you
think it sounds like a saw trap now, just wait for this one day they workshop it
here. I like someone says I like they use the word weirdly to like imagine
explaining that to the engineer that's like building and make it
use a plastic that's weirdly strong. I love the idea of no escape diapers. I
just got a lockable diaper harness, which is close to that right now I'm
locked into it. Of course I can unlock it whenever I need to. Sometimes I
pretend that an imaginary daddy has the key and I'm not allowed to unlock it.
Myself might want to look online for a timer lockable container to lock the key
into what vendor did you get your lockable diaper harness from would be
interesting getting one myself. You could try freezing the key in a block
of ice, no access until the ice melts free timer. That is literally a
satra. Yeah, that's fully frozen. You have to fill your life. You have to P
warm enough you're sitting on the block of ice. You have to P and poop warm
enough that it melts the ice that you can get the key out to unlock. So that's
genius incredible.
Here's someone who wrote a poem about their ideal diaper. Whoa for me, what I
wear in my dream, anything cute will be the theme thick, so I know it's always
there discreet, so that no one will stare wow and then covered says this is
going to sound bizarre, but then I suppose we are all are really one made
from the fake flesh that's
like you're fucking pissing your skin. Yeah, your barbie yeah, you want you
want like just a new but
right
of the cheek. Here's a scientist nasty. I theorized a diaper with a two layer
core.
I don't need to read the
I fear I do have to read the rest of it. So interesting all the with a base
or that's high sap and a lower sap top layer with a border of high sap. Think
of it like an hour glass shaped inflatable raft filled with fluff theory,
high sap barriers start to repel fluid as they're fully hydrated and push the
fluid back in the low sap core to be wicked to other zones of high sap.
What's a p? I don't know
absorbency something maybe yeah so maybe that's that stuff that's in a diaper
solid and
power it shit bits anemone says
I dreamt a couple of nights ago of a new design of pull ups in turn of the
century style featuring many mouse lifting up her long skirt to give an
impressed Mickey a clear view. Also they fit very nicely. I woke up sticky.
I was to say they were pretty good wow and then this is the last idea someone
had or no yeah diaper corsets like this
way and it is a corset with a diaper on the bottom of it. Dude he dropped that
like it was a complete nuke. He didn't even punctuate diaper corsets like this
for a course. It's like this no never been seen before a diaper course like
oh my God
diaper courses like this like this, you know,
just like this, a
picture crazy and this is just I just found them floating in the cliffs of
moher yeah. Why is that the background? Yeah, so odd this looks like a sci fi
fantasy graphic yeah, this just looks like an unlockable in the shadow of
more to her. This is a destiny skin
things he likes doing in pooped diapers as a kid and still like doing as an abdl
as a kid. One of my favorite things to do after filling my diapers was to sit and
slide my butt back and forth on the carpeted living room floor. How do
people remember what they did when they were wearing? He's making it up, he's
lying. Yeah, no, I don't know. I feel like I feel like if you can remember if
you if you became conscious too early in your first memory is you have a baby
doing some with your shit. I think it makes you might make you an a b d l. All
these people probably developed consciousness way too early. Yeah, okay,
skip ahead to the slide that says your name. This is the other thing
it says Julio. It says your name, okay, your name. Why have you chosen the
foreign name? You have forum name you have, so we have two kind of ends of
the spectrum here. This next one here, this is this guy's name is crazy
smoker
and it's a picture of
cigarette. I think it's not a pacify. It's like a cigarette coming out of a
portal. Yeah, it's the ignorance and get knowledge. That's just a signature.
various forms in the church, and this is the other one. I have who's from a
deleted member, so we don't get to see their username, what their username was
originally, but he says that eon in my name is referencing my belief that I'm
my own God and that I co create my reality. The little not only points to
my age play, but also that I'm still young in my spiritual journey, still
learning how to hone my skills when it comes to mastering my power to shape my
mind and reality. Also to add eon is a name that comes from a paraphrase quote
from Heraclitus delivered in a lecture by Terence McKenna, who states the eon
the child at play with colored balls. Imagine believing you are a God, you are
shaping the universe and you make yourself an adult baby diaper lover. This
is the second coming of Christ. What did you look up to? Oh yeah, you looked up
name. I thought you were like just looking up anything. I was I think
you're looking at Terrence McKenna on
I wasn't really excited when
it's the ending of men in black to right where they're in a marble yeah and it's
an alien playing with the marble, yeah, and the alien is kind of child coded
right? Yes, it should just shit its diaper in the last moment to
what do you have for us? Yeah, you have some cake camera. I don't know if you
got to eat any while you were reading a little bit a little taste. It went in
my windpipe. Yeah, it really dry cake. I've never had any cake that just is so
man like any. This is literally the most mid cake. I was like give me a slice
and then I she took it out and I was like that is enough for four guys. Give
me the whole thing. Wow, I don't make this cake. This was eleven dollars. I was
really only going to get a slice to put me over the minimum here. Here's a good
Been there, done that. I have always had a wet spot on the front of my pants.
From the size of a silver dollar to six inches in diameter. And guess what? I couldn't cower to less.
I have been out in public many times in my thick cloth diaper, soaker, and my plastic pants.
And a huge load in my wet diaper, which I couldn't help.
But it came out luckily. I was dressed for the occasion.
But I don't stand there or stay in one place for too long, as I can't smell it for a short time.
And I split outside and look for a place to sit down casually, just to squish it around while it's still warm.
still warm. By the time I get up, my big lump, my big lump has went up my back and
under my balls and I have to wet it real good. And when I can feel the mess up in
the front, I just leave to see if I can poop some more and completely soak the
diaper until it is fully soaked and loaded to my satisfaction. I once get in
my truck, will gulp several 12 ounce bottles, not all at once, but half here,
than just give little pushes until I have one or two little wet farts and then I
push a little amount of wet poop the size of a hot dog into my poopy diaper,
and I will repeat that until there might be four hot dog size poops added to my
mess and my whole diaper is soaked. That's a lot of poop. Yeah, man, and from
my waist long does that all does make me thirsty for hot dog poops for a period
the time that it's okay to have yeah I'm going to hit I'm going to hit the
carrot
and my whole diapers here with the cake spoon squishy and from my waist to my
butt that diaper is maxed out warm squelching. If I'm lucky, it won't leak,
but the belge is huge and I am just starting to get brown crescent marks on
my jeans and the backs of my legs, but now I'm safe at home and I will sit in a
chair on the front porch until it gets sticky and cool, but I might wet again
and warm it up, but the diapers very puffy and I have a little brown puddle of
brown under my body before I wait again.
I have a little brown puddle of brown under my butt and it stinks like ammonia
and old poop and I go to the backyard to wash up and hose my diaper soaker
plastic pants as clean as I can in my butt and diapered area. I'm looking over
the fence at my neighbor doing that
it's been hosed of enough just to wrap a towel around me as all the yucky stuff
gone from my crotch and but then the wet things are picked up and soaked in a
five gal bucket until I get showered up and then during the bucket hose,
then done all the brown water off everything load the washer with soiled
garments and the clean up is all done. Anybody who has a routine, anybody who
doesn't work in a factory who has a routine that involves a five gallon
bucket is a serial killer. Yes, he has a five glam bucket dedicated to shit.
Yeah, the shit that he did on purpose. I just had a great idea when I get home.
my wife's probably going to be asleep. I'm going to get home and I'm going to
walk up and just breathe into her face
guess what the fuck I had for dinner.
I read one more. Maybe I can smell my breath every time I talk. I still I
still maintain. I think the funniest part of alcoholic beef stew is if you
get too fucked up off it and you're really hung over the next day and you
have to explain to someone I'm sorry man, like I feel like shit. I might be
there. Alcoholic beast, I think I will definitely have a already feel hung
over. I know I feel like shit. I'm having a headache, but I never
think about. I think we have to call it. Be still,
a couple more posts. We need a couple more posts. Yeah, these are easy.
My wife knows she helped me when I first had the accident. She helped me by
changing my wet and shitty diapers for a while and she isn't into changing me
anymore, knows that I wear diapers, but not just where I am with it. Like, she came home,
found me wearing a wet, slightly but a little poop diaper under my PJs or shorts, and patted
my butt or rubbed my butt. If it's full, she lets me know it's time to clean up, huh? And
she's caught me in a very loaded, soaked diaper in my room, and she makes a face and closes
the door gently. So yes, she knows, but she doesn't want to get involved, and she still
loves me."
- That's a sweet one.
- It is nice. I'm gonna be honest.
- She said something about your daughter.
it looks like he's going to die right now. I think maybe we should end on such a
pleasant note that you got it. We got to stop it. You look so sick. I really got
to go. You look pale. Yeah, you're normally all of who would have thought
he'd be the first person to tap out from alcoholic beef. The beast to broke him.
The beast is broken. This man, bro, the stew, the stew has claimed its first
victim. Okay, how about this? Oh, no, like beef stew has claimed its first
victim of all time.
Oh no, oh no, here comes seconds, wave,
and this hot shit is just reloading
and overloading my diaper as a large, steady,
thick stream of wet, hot, even stinkier mush
is just pouring out of my butthole,
and that has just made a huge, thick puddle of piss
and slimy shit on the floor, on my legs feet,
and I'm 15 away feet from the bathroom,
or I'm six feet from the porch door
as I walk stiff leg to the door.
The mud slide of my diaper is just hanging on
as I open the door.
The mess is starting to ooze out of my leg holes again.
This is by far the biggest poop I have ever just had.
Just show up in my waiting diaper.
I am lucky as not to drop,
falls out of my diaper and gets in the door jam.
But as I stepped down onto the garage floor,
I can hear it splattering on the concrete floor.
Just imagine that sound.
- Oh, like you're starting to paint the garage.
- Yes, but now just steps away from the backyard
and the hose, finally make it to the hose.
And now as I stripped down,
I can see the mess from the end.
Yes, every square inch is covered in an inch
of now just stinking shit and mixed with piss
as the aroma of an outhouse.
I get the hose going and slowly slide my shorts down
and I can see that shit is caked to the crotch of my shorts
and down both legs.
So much shit.
They are just covered in slimy brown shit,
but I got them off and rinsed all the shit
out of my shorts.
What a mess.
Then I grabbed the lawn chair and go back
where nobody can see me and sit down with a big squelch
and poop comes out over the top of my diaper
and out the leg holes.
Now I can really smell myself, yuck.
but I am very smelly. Now it's a combo of ammonia and very stink has Matt waste
poop and then somehow salvage my plastic pants. I'm half thing. I'm just throwing
him out, but I stick my fingers in the waistband and my whole diapered area is
dark brown slimy mess, but I just don't stop.
I'll stop there, though. Oh my God, you ended you almost ended on such a nice
and then you just read that you really made me feel like I was going to throw
up yeah man.
this is the worst one we've ever done.
I might be also be broken. That was I feel like I feel horrible. I literally
feel so dehydrated. I feel like someone has this is the first time that I felt
like someone has plucked water out of me like an airbender. I think it's a
combination of the salt and I think it might be the beef stew in the out. Yeah,
I think maybe there's a reason you don't make how calling. Oh God, well, we
learn something important this year, because what we are, we are nothing. If
we're not scientists,
experimenters, yeah, American test kitchen, that's this happy Stinks giving
happy Stinks giving everybody we'll see you next year. Five weeks of planets
will resume. Oh, I have a quick planet rhyme,
because I thought maybe I was going to get on the verse, but it's a guy. It's
a guy who doesn't want his cock sucked. He just wants his ass eaten okay, and he
says you're sick of dick. Well, I'm curing this. Don't suck my cock girl.
That's where the urine is.
Yo!
Holy fuck, drop a bomb on that.
Thank you.
Thank you Pierce for being here.
I love you guys.
I love you too.
Thanks for the cake.
Can I have a Zen?
Yeah man.
Alright.
Bye bye.
It's normal for a penis to turn blue.
You guys, enough of this cock talk.
Let's talk planets.
Okay.
Let's talk Saturn.
Let's go through the outfits here.
Let's start with Caleb because you have an interesting outfit on.
Alright, I feel like I'm going to be the first one to go.
I'm going to be the first one to go.
Saturn let's go through the outfits.
Let's start with Caleb
because you have an interesting outfit on.
Alright, I flopped you flopped.
I think I yeah, I think I flopped.
I couldn't think of any things I dressed up
like the ring because there's a ring on
Saturn multiple.
I think we may be all flopped today.
Well, I'm dressed at I think that none of us own
any Saturn clothes.
I'm gathering.
Yeah, I just want to play.
We could dress up like cars.
Oh like a Saturn.
I was maybe gonna, I was gonna,
'cause Saturn is kinda like brownish, beige-ish color,
I feel like, so I was gonna maybe,
I did, if I had a shirt that was that color,
I was gonna wear that and then put like a duct tape ring
around my stomach, but I didn't even have a shirt
that was that color, so I'm just dressed as the rings.
'Cause they're, in one picture I looked,
they were kinda blue and green and stuff.
- I'm kinda dressed like the rings, too.
- Yeah, I think we-- - Show us here at Walkin' Through.
- And you're dressed as the ring, one of the rings.
- And then I went to the barber shop this morning,
and I don't know, I think he got--
I don't know. I think he got...
I think my shit got fucked up.
(laughter)
I don't know.
It looks good. What did you ask him for?
I asked him for the ring of Saturn.
And they did this?
Damn. What is up with our barbers
and being interested in planets this month?
I know. It's really surprising.
These guys are really, really, like, knowledgeable
too. Like, they knew what a ring was.
I mean, look at this.
This shit is too fire.
So for our audio listeners, Patrick has a
completely bald except for a ring of hair
around the top of his head.
And I think that honestly, now that I'm seeing it on camera,
you'd like it.
I think that this is going to catch on as a hairstyle.
It looks really good.
I was so excited because when I walked in
and saw you on the computer, I did see through the back of your hat.
I could see the line.
God damn it.
I should have worn a fitted head set.
Did you see the part where I cut way too close to his skin and he has no hair at all?
Well at first I saw the back of his neck, he has one part that's going to shave it all
off so well and I was like...
(8-bit music)