I don't know.
Ten thousand twenty one thousand
don't touch that man.
I'll get to that shit.
OK, I'll get to that shit.
I just realized don't I don't realize
there's a lot of realize right now on
D realize now do it right now.
Sorry, I ruined our song about our
subscriber count.
Guys, we want to hit ten thousand
subscribers. We are almost very soon.
very soon, very soon like Pluto. Let's get the fuck into this shit man. Let's
get this shit is easy for me these days to do Pluto to talk about Pluto. First
of all, completely deteriorating. Can I ask you that first the sands of time or
taking this hat down the shore? Yeah, it's yeah. Do I have to retire this one
to have to put this one in the hat Hall of Fame? How many hats do you have?
Give me a number right now. Give me between I have no you. I was going to
I ask you to give me a tens number between from thirty to forty, forty,
fifty. There's some that I don't wear. Yeah, you don't need to be wearing a
hat like this if you have forty hats. Yeah, I agree. I like it though,
and I think that I'm gonna do a big sale on my hats. You can wear a hat
like this if you're forty years old, and it's your one hat. I might do hats
for sale. You might sell something. I kinda look like hats for sale.
What's hats for sale? You remember the book? Caps for sale? Caps for sale,
sorry. I could do caps for sale. He's slinging cap. I could be... Yeah,
got caps for sale. Don't even, just chill on me. You're capping on shit all day. Chill
on me today. Black Friday deal 100% off cap, buy one get 1000 free from Patrick. I would
sell a hat to you Cameron if you wanted it. And even that's cap, you have to buy two.
If you wanted a hat I would sell one to you. You're capping right now. I would sell you
a hat. At a discount? Yes. Guys I got super glue on my teeth man. You did. This is feeling
fucking crazy. If you want any of my hats, a specific hat that I've worn on the show
I'm willing to get rid of it, you can DM me about it. I will sell you the hat for $30
each because I wore them and I'll sign them.
You never...
Thank God.
Nobody wants to... That is actually repulsive to me.
It's repulsive?
It's nasty.
Signing hats and selling...
I'm trying to get my money up this year.
$30 for a sweated hat?
Sell two hats for $30 and you're going to sign them for $60?
Depends on the hat too, because some of them are the Ebbets hats that I was either given,
I was given all of them.
You never bought a hat made?
No.
No, they're too expensive.
They're too expensive.
I never bought a hat.
You guys ever do flat bill brim hats from New Era?
I've never worn a flat brim hat in my life.
And you ride on the brim?
Mine said ex-vegan-ex, man.
Oh, you did one of those?
Oh, for real.
Oh my God.
I used to wear it.
This is my daily driver outfit, ready?
I would wear a flat bill hat, new era hat that said X Vegan X on the bottom. What
team was the don't remember couldn't for the life of me remember what team it was
had that it might have been just a blank one. Actually, oh, that's even blamer.
Is that crazy? I think you went to lids. I went to live at the thirty dollars on
the play, but I was like sports or game. Yeah, whatever nothing so that right
Abercrombie sweatpants that had the tattered, the tattered pros down the side of it that
said Abercrombie.
I know the ones you're talking about, the wool ones that are really worn.
They were comfy.
Wasn't that like...
Aero-possil t-shirt.
Aero.
Wasn't that like a thing that dudes in the hardcore scene would do though?
I'm not done, man.
Yeah, dude.
And you need one that you grew up in.
Yeah, and here's what I'd do, bro.
I'd take my sweatpants.
This was the wave in Myrtle Beach, Myrta Beach.
Myrta Beach hardcore.
you would take your waistband on your sweatpants, you'd roll that bitch about
forty times. You roll up your waistband, right? None of this. Who came up with
this shit? Yeah. Who decided that this looked good? This sounds like they
gonna be rude to say, but it sounds like somebody saw a special needs person and
said, I love that guy's swag. I love his swag. We need to, we need to,
and then... We need to do this in the hardcore scene. Dude, and then some...
Yeah, that guy's moshing like crazy. And then either some old schools,
I'd get the old school vans or I'd have some like DC shoes with the laces taken
out. Which DC, like DC court graphics. The one with the big, the heel.
Something big. The DC heel logo. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. There's the court graphics.
Something big, man. With that big tongue. Yeah. Big puffy tongue, man.
I was wearing like, when I was like probably around the same age as you,
I was wearing like three quarter sleeve shirts,
like the fucking those ones. Oh yeah. And then like the,
I was wearing like high water pants, dude. I need to see that. Oh my God.
You could not believe I had like, I would put pomade in my hair and shit.
Dude, I used to put pomade in my hair. Yeah.
I can't, I think that you used to,
when I'm picturing you at the same age, like the same age that we're describing,
what age are we talking about? Like 16, 17, something like that. I was fucking 11.
Oh, you were 11 doing that? Yeah, my brother dressed me up like a doll
Every day, man. He took me to the mall. I used all my Santa gift cards at the mall, and I'd
just dress like him and his friends.
There was a specific type of wave that skaters were on in 2014 where every single one of them
was slicking back their hair, wearing these fucking high water pants. You could see your
socks.
I've had so many insane eras, man. I had a crazy ass Christmas sweater I used to wear
every day when I was 15.
Don't even try to play on me.
I didn't play with that shit man. Don't even try to play. I had three of them. I'd wear
these like. Mine was from Urban Outfitters dude. I've had a lot of eras too. I used to
dress like Mercury and I dressed like Venus for a while. I feel like I had a Mars era
for a minute. What era do you feel like you're in these days? Honestly? Be real with me.
You looking mad Plutonian. Probably Pluto. Pluto I could see that. I'm thinking about
it and I feel like, I'm not sure it's going to stick. Yeah. But I feel like I'm like Pluto
last three days. Did you have any errors like this when you were younger like we're talking
about? Well, I think you can probably guess that I was, you know, new balances. Yep. Cargoes,
cargos or glasses, full pajama pants, glasses, tape in the middle, glasses, pocket protector,
sweater vest. No, I would not wear anything that I the least it just might not as well
I'll not even be clothes. Yeah, okay, could you were full PJ you dress like a
slug? PJ PJ. Oh yeah, you dress like the cookie monster. I bet like I just woke
up
four days. I bet cookie monster sweat pans and he was walking. Imagine walking
behind him in school and seeing that that that that meat that meat way through
those thin ass pants.
Thin as pants of all time. Yeah, I really went to school. My pajamas every
day showed the print. Yeah, you had the print a huge print. Yeah, huge print.
yeah, that middle school print three prong print. What happened to my print?
My print was bigger in middle school than it is now as an adult. Yeah,
what ratio of your legs? I think that
my print got smaller. My print doesn't look small. You're a big pricks or
little
bro. My print, my print, just a dot. You got that dot my print. My print
looks like it's like you get your like wearing a glove, like a knuckle and a
glove. Looks like I brought my own eraser. My print that I'm walking around
both. I got the damn the the freaking Larry David poorly fitting pants. Oh
yeah, I'm talking about that. I know that. Yeah, I got it. Probably got it
right now. Yeah, I had that shit the other day in the airport and I look at
my
I'm seeing your tent bro is
strong.
Oh, my God, get that shit away.
Next thing man, we have to be done with the gray sweatpants challenge in the
print the dick print in the yoga pants and whatever.
What you got to do?
Whatever the fuck.
No, you know what the best is?
It's about the tent nowadays.
The tent, the best thing, the best pants.
The tent pole.
You got to go to the thrift store.
You got to find these like, you got to find some corduroys from like 1990, like a Joseph
A. Bank style corduroys that were meant for a corduroy suit.
Okay.
Those are going to, you're going to get a huge tent from those.
I don't want corduroy.
I want, if I can get a tent.
I can get a tent and literally any pants I wear because of the weird shape of my
body. That's true. It's all happens to me. There's yeah. There's extra room
there. Yeah. I think that the best looking ones for a print would be
something like corduroy, but it goes the other way, because you have that sideways
like a lot of that horizontal. It looks like it's moving back and forth.
Exactly. Horizontal corduroy. You have the
horizontal line man. Yeah, now it'll make that shit look wide. Yeah. See the
long line. I think people think I got that skinny pole. I don't have a skinny pole.
No way. I shit wide and small. It's like a tuna can. Yeah, nice and short. What
you want to yeah, what here's the new here's the new thing is the tent right,
but you're sitting down, you're at dinner, not with your family. Just to
clarify.
I mean, I don't know. Yeah, that's what that's the dinner. The most recent
dinner I had was Thanksgiving. It wasn't with my family, but this isn't at
Thanksgiving. Then it would be a wigwam. This could be a dinner with a bunch of
women you want to fuck or something okay, but I've had those yeah Charlie's
their own dinner. You got to you got your lap. You got two tents dinner,
which are at least the one biggest fuck one medium size in the same and in the
same pants you leave. I'm guessing how the hell you do which one is real and
which one which one and which one is just is just empty space. Yeah, air,
which one the fold of the pan you're going to have sure the run confused is
fuck at this table that bottle in the bag magic trick is going to be doing
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I bitch that's a scary, no nail in that
cup. That's the that's a real life five nights at Freddy's jump scare. Did you
see a tre? You see that David Blaine greatest magician who ever lived hurt
his hand? How he did that? He did the nail in the cup and he did the nail in
the cup trick where you smash the thing with and he guessed wrong and he put his
hand through a nail where his nail through a nail, his hand on through he
oh yeah his hand through the nail. This is really yeah, the or he put his hand
around a nail yeah all the way around all on the sharp part. He put his nail
through his hand. It's not his nail. I mean it may be well. It was made
probably brought it from home, just a like magician,
carpenters.
Guy who's got like a hammer very
that's how you I mean well, that's how you you you be like it's not my nail.
See it's not a pre prepared nail. This carpenter just happened to be working
under the yeah yeah this Richard scary carpenter that's walking around with a
hammer around. Is anyone having his back a box and a saw? Does anyone have a
trick box with strange compartment? I saw a very talented woman. Does anyone
have a deck of cards with they're all the same card all five, except for one
that's marked except for one? Thank you. I
have a marked card for me. I think I David Blaine actually scares me a little bit.
Yeah, a lot of that stuff is scary. How the hell does he roll the pussy posse
with a pussy? Pussy posse was a Leonardo. I didn't know he was in the pussy posse.
It was Leo DiCaprio, Toby Maguire, who named it. That's just two guys. Hardly.
There was other guys, too. David Blaine. And there's more to those. I knew where
the tree you pull up was a posse. Google pussy posse. You look, can you look them
up there? They made some movie that they have tried to scrub from the world
about being a pussy about
be it's a movie where the coolest guys in the club, the guy the ones having the
most fun, but they were also assholes fucking hooligans
way. Oh, Don's Plum is the movie. Kevin Connolly Don's Plum is the movie and it
just makes Leo DiCaprio look like the worst person. Look at that pick, bro.
Yeah, there's blame. They're all coming. That's the pussy posse. The pussy posse.
That's what that's what you look like when you're running around getting in
I know people say it all. Every time the Pussy Posse comes up, somebody says it, but it's
so funny that Tobey Maguire was in the Pussy Posse.
Oh yeah.
Look at him, dude. He was a hot piece of ass.
He was getting it, man.
Bro, he was Spider-Man.
He was Spider-Man. Everybody wants to fuck you if you're Spider-Man.
Yeah.
No doubt, man. I can take it two girls.
Mary Jane and Gwen Stacy.
Gwen Stacy.
Hey, Mrs. Stacy. Tell me how you been.
Wow.
Yeah. My song.
That's a song you wrote about Gwen Stacy. If this shit doesn't taste like Wumpa
fruit, I don't even know what the fuck does. Crash Bandicoot 4. I wish I could
take a sip of that right now bro. I already had, no I'm trying to lower my
caffeine intake. One sip man. You wouldn't say something like that if you
weren't gonna drink it. Yeah. I wish I could have a sip of this right now.
I wish I could have one sip. That was a big sip. I wasn't, at a different date. You were
begging to get peer pressure. Oh that's disgusting. You were asking permission.
you like one per for that is so bad from crash bandicoot for it's about time that
is so disgusting. Why what style of for the one per it doesn't taste like a
mango. It looks like a mango, but it gives you points. Yeah, I don't exchange
them. It tastes exactly. It tastes like they mixed mango and cotton candy.
So you don't touch it. Oh, I don't touch Cameron. I had a new apple.
Recently, I'm going to touch it. Don't touch it. I don't like touching that
type of thing. Don't even take a sip. I don't want it. Had a new apple recently.
You had an apple cosmic crisp you're bragging.
Never ever heard of you know I'm allergic to the what it's a called
something Jen specifically cosmic crisp.
I'm allergic to cosmic crisp bro.
That's it.
Yeah, it's a new breed though.
They drop it.
Yeah, and last couple years.
I've been on the golden delicious back on the golden delicious.
Oh delicious is my favorite Apple.
I know it's old as fuck.
That's I haven't had one in a while, but I back on back on that's like 3G man.
Yeah, I know that's not how could I be back on them?
if they were new. What's that? They're old, man. Oh, Fuji apples are still the goat? Shut
up, man. No, what are you talking about? Those are the crispiest ones. Try Honeycrisp. Honeycrisp
is fire. Wait, wait, wait. Cosmic Crisp now is up there with Honeycrisp. I want to try
Cosmic Crisp. I didn't even know it dropped. Cosmic Crisp, I will say, man, the flavor,
less good than a Honeycrisp, but the crispness of it, out of this world. I usually go to
a Honeycrisp, yo. And because of this whole planet shit that I've been on, this new kind
a wave. I don't know if you guys have been on the show. I'm eating more cosmic
things, cosmic brownies, I'm eating more things from other planets or at least it
seem like they are like, for example, one per fruit, which I don't think crash
bandicoot is on Earth. I don't know the UN would allow space cake space cake
space cake sounds good as fuck to me. I've been eating a lot of we had we had
a galactic ham galactic ham. We did have a galactic ham because it was as big as
a galaxy Mars and cheese. We had Mars and cheese galactic ham green bean
green bean, asteroid, blast roll,
sprouts again, green bean, asteroid, blast,
you know, like an asteroid blast yeah, yeah, no, I got a rocket blast role.
Well, I don't think you need it.
They're worried in it. Green bean, asteroid, rocket, blast, maybe it would
work, maybe like green men, green men, green men, casserole, green men, little
green men, casserole. I'm not eating green man. You already did, bro. You
like that shit yesterday. I guzzled it
pumpkin, guzzled it down bro pie pumpkin space lot. I can pies in the number man
or pumpkin space lot is good, but we didn't have that for thanks. You know we
didn't well. You could have had it in the morning. Well, I didn't though, but
yeah, morning on the way to okay. I said a cup of coffee. Yeah, I coffee I had a
Mars fee. I had a Celsius. That was that already sounds like a planet. Yeah, yeah,
the Celsius. Here's how fucked up this Celsius versus Fahrenheit shit is right
today. It's what thirty some degrees. It's like fifty fifty yeah right. You go
up to Canada. It's seven. What the hell that pisses me off. That's kind of nice.
So cold there. It's so cold so much colder. It's seven there. It's seven
here. It's much cold. No, but if you're from Canada, I picked up my friend from
Canada today. If you're from Canada, you touch down and say, oh, it feels like
seven out here. You shut up this and this is seven touch down man. Have you ever
talked
ever been a conversation? What is going on right now? Touch down all right walk me
through the fit. What do you got? I would just looked at the first picture of
Pluto on Google images and I saw it had elements of white and blue and brown and
this was kind of the closest thing I had to that. It was a reddish brown like a
patina to brown. There was a bunch of different all these planets man. When
you Google them, they have they everyone nobody wants to give it to you straight.
those conflicting answer. They go all the pics are spectrographs and enhanced
color and whatever the fuck it's. I don't want to reach colored, but I will
say always they're like okay. This you look at it's like oh wow, it's bright
purple and it's like actually the colors on this picture represent how gaseous
the atmosphere is. Yeah, that's not what colors I hate that when they colorize an
old photo to yeah. I will say Pluto is the definitely the coolest looking
planet, most interesting looking one. I find that to be Neptune. Personally,
Neptune is just completely blue. That's cool. It has different elements of blue.
Yeah, it does have different shades.
And it's got rings.
Pluto looks like multiple...
A golf ball, bro.
No, no.
It's got like a red corner.
Pluto looks like the Grateful Dead logo.
Pluto looks like a Star Wars video game planet.
Yeah.
It looks cool, man.
That's why it's a beast.
It's got red and blue.
That's why it sucks that they got rid of it as a planet.
What do you have?
What do I got on?
I have on a...
Well, I saw the photo that I saw.
It looked red, white, and blue, so I put on blue mostly because when I was a kid, I was
told that Pluto was blue like Neptune. I thought so too. I thought it was fully blue until this
week. Yep, me too. So I put on, I've got red here. I'll never forget that Thanksgiving
2023, I found out that Pluto was not completely blue. Yeah. Took me most of my life to get
there. Yeah. I hope this is just my life. We all looked at a photo of it and went, oh.
Yeah. And then that was it. Yeah. Even though it looked cooler than I thought. It was the
whole thing. You know, you got blue, a little red on the hat. Me, you know me man. Abstract.
Okay, what do we know about Pluto? I see no keep going man. Well, you small readers
small. Okay, or my smallest shirt. Okay. What does it say on your shirt? So skater
and ice skater. There we go. Wow, another element. I was about to get to that man.
Yeah, I was trying to alley up you man. It was that I see you alley up yourself.
Oh, I got I know you didn't you didn't catch. I didn't catch on. I got to do it
nice on to that is a crazy thick chain. I know for a white guy. What the hell
barbed wire, bro? Yeah, my house. We gave it to me supposed to go thin man.
Yeah, I don't know why that was like a robot's arm. I think it was a beast.
This is a Halloween costume. What the hell? Well, I had to be iced out like
Pluto. He got the Greek. Mm. You're completely Greek. Yeah. So there's a lot
of big changes going on in my life. Now you became Greco came Greco. Holy shit.
Holy shit.
Well, I'm wearing a tiny shirt.
I'm wearing a tiny shirt.
All right, give us a planet report, man.
I need to learn about this fucking planet right now if it's the last thing I do.
Wumpa fruit.
What ever this is.
Travis was again on a five week collapsive journey through our solar system.
What the hell?
Be prepared to learn and to laugh at the truth.
And now the planet report with Cameron Fetter.
I liked it though.
Yeah, I loved it.
I was going to just do the fast part.
Well, just play it twice then.
Travis was again on a five week collapsive journey through our solar system.
Be prepared to learn and to laugh at the truth.
And now the planet report with Cameron Fetter.
You still get all the stuff from it.
Be prepared to learn and to laugh at the truth, and now the planet report with Cameron Fetter.
get all the stuff from yeah, I got a last time. I like the song. You still hear the
song. It's just Michael and I like my core.
So I'm doing a little different today. Okay,
and I know I've been doing these planet reports, but I'm actually doing a
different type of report today. That's still Pluto related. There's better be a
book report. It's not a book report. It is a book report.
There's part of it. That's a book report. Oh shit,
Michael E. Brown, a loser report.
Michael E. Brown is an American astronomer from Huntsville, Alabama.
He is a professor of planetary astronomy at the California Institute of Technology, and
he is the author of the 2010 book, "How I Killed Pluto and Why It Had It Coming."
No, it was a book report.
One of the people responsible for the demotion of Pluto to dwarf planet, but being one of
the people isn't enough for this nerd.
He has to claim all the credit.
So let me share some quotes from reviews of his book on Goodreads.
I actually care less about the topic now that now than I did going in.
Mike Brown is an engaging scientist from Caltech, but this book is incorrectly titled and misleading.
It includes a great deal about his personal life, especially his obsessive interest in
his newborn daughter, Lila, and very little about planetary science and the decision to
the very minor role that Brown played in it.
And here's the last review.
Horrid bad book, boring high hubba bobbin,
hubba, hubba, hubba, hubba, hubba, hubba, hubba, hubba,
Bob bluff, hubba, hubba, hubba, hubba, hubba, hubba, hubba,
bye, hubba, hubba.
Michael E. Brown, you are a clown.
- Wow.
- Your work in the field of astronomy is irrelevant.
Your book is a flop and you were ugly,
not just on the outside, but the inside.
Big whoop, you discovered the dwarf planet Eris.
How about you discover some platform shoes?
You don't need a telescope to find a dwarf.
You just needed a mirror.
I don't know if he's short or not, but he is, man.
I can tell based on his name.
Anybody who needs that middle initial is short.
That's right.
The plutonians are coming for you, Michael.
You picked the wrong galactic army to fuck with.
I hope you like being zapped with electricity because they have electric powers.
Wow.
The plutonians do?
Yeah, their army does.
That's amazing.
Just the army?
Yeah.
watch this report out, I'd actually just like to promote my new book. It's
called How I liquefied Michael E Brown into a boiling slurry of deconstituted
flesh and nerves with a pulse rifle and why his wife married me afterward.
It will be out very, very, very soon, but you're only part of the team that
destroyed. Yeah, I'm a minor and it's mostly about my family.
So he wrote this book about how Pluto was sucked a dick, but he mostly talked
about his daughter. Yeah, is it like oh my god, I guess you haven't read the
it's about I read the like the like blurb for the book is like it's like a
witty account of one scientist and it's that like it's like oh, I was the so the
way that he that they de planetized Pluto is because he and his team
discovered a new planet that was bigger than Pluto, called Eris and they were
like okay. So if there's something bigger than Pluto, Pluto can't be a
planet. Why not just add errors to the mix of there's a whole bunch of there's
a whole bunch of crap, go commercial, taco commercial. Why not both man yeah
yeah, okay, okay, no, they should have, but they didn't and that's why this guy
is a dick head, but I guess, but the book is like and but like even when we
were working hard, like what was more important was like the discovery of
human life and like it just like very like yeah, it found human life on
Pluto. They found human life in his family. Oh, and his wife's stomach.
Whoa yeah, I feel like without that the book is probably that big yeah, that's
literally all the found a bigger one. The reviews that are positive are like
yeah, this book is like more than half about his wife, like how much he loves
his wife. I hate that shit man terrible to any literally. They also said all
the science stuff is just that it's just just hear him writing like we looked at
the data when we didn't see anything. Then we looked and we thought we saw
something and then there wasn't anything and then we kept looking and we didn't
find anything and then we found eris shit pissing me off man terrible bit
like cash in Bill Simmons book, the big book of basketball, barely about
basketball. Mostly is about fucking his oh me and my dad used to go to the
basketball games. Talk about why the ball bounces yeah. Why how does it bounce
what it's got air in it? There's air outside the ball. It's all friction from
the air. There's air. It's probably the same amount. I think it's because the
balls made of rubber. Yeah, but what's it? Why is it got air in it to bounce?
Fill the ball, but just fill it with more rubber. If it's so fucking bouncy.
Oh yeah, but it'll be too bouncy. Yeah, you put air in it so you can control the
bounce. Okay, less bouncy. You guys should have written the book and not
fucking bill simon. We basically I went to the I went to the Celtics games in
the seventies and oh no all the entire book is him going yeah man. We used to
go to the seven in the seventies. We go to the Celtics and no nobody was racist.
He's like oh yeah, everybody says it was racist. No one was racist. Talk about
the ball yeah and the net. Why does it happen? Why did he did about the
orange was pissing me off too because he the even all the reviews are like yeah.
He didn't even do anything. He was like put one member of the team. He writes a
book called How I Killed Pluto. That's like did your parents hate Al Gore when
you were a kid? Yeah. Yours definitely did. Did your parents? I don't think I
remember hearing about Al Gore at all. My parents talked about Al Gore. Why did
their parents talk about Al Gore so much? 'Cause of Inconvenient Truth. Why
the fuck? 'Cause of that, that movie came out and they were like, "Well, now
we gotta, now our cars have to be gay." Yeah, my, my fucking mom was complaining
about Al Gore was the, probably Al Gore's name was said in my house probably once
every day. I got it. From the time I was born to like 2010. My mom complained
about Hillary more even before the 2016 like even before Benghazi and stuff like
my mom was saying that Hillary Clinton is a lesbo bitch. She was a stuff like
that whom Abedin saying like she hates her and Bill Clinton. I didn't know why I
still don't really know why my mom hates her that much, but I get it. Well, she's
a pedophile. Yeah. No, I know why your mom's a pedophile. Yeah, she doesn't and
She doesn't like Democrats. That's the other. It's not really why she doesn't
like her, but yeah, your mom is a pedophile. My mom's a complete
pedophile, which I feel like her and Hillary would have got along then.
Yeah.
Yeah, my mom, the thing was that my parents would make fun of Al Gore all
the time. Like South Park. Well, it was maybe South Park. Yeah, but also like
if I would, if my mom was like, "Hey, did you do the dishes?" I'd be like,
she'd be like yeah and Al Gore invented the internet. I guess he claimed that he invented
the internet or some shit. I never even learned what she was talking about. Like I'm the Queen
of England. Yeah that was a new update. Well we didn't know about the Queen of England
when I was a kid. We were in North Carolina. Yeah. You know. They don't teach you about
that there. Fuck no. I just picked up my Canadian friend. He handed me a piece of money to show
me how weird it was. First of all. The Looney and the Tooney. First of all it's plastic.
weird. Second of all, the Queen's on it. It's because they were a territory of Canada until
the 80s or the early 90s. I think I think Canada was a territory of the UK. I think
we should put Sacagawea on ours. Yep. Don't they have her on some of the coins? A gold
one. Then they changed all the gold. No, it was a gold coin. The gold was a dollar. Yeah,
the gold dollar was Sacagawea and then they changed it from Sacagawea to all of the presidents,
it just fucked up because then you got to put you put Andrew Jackson in there.
You know what they should do the kings of comedy. I agree. Bernie Mac, Bernie.
That's not a bad idea. It's the entertainer bands in the world. That's a
good idea to put breaking Benjamin on one breaking Benjamin. It should be
breaking the rock. The rock core either. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Finger 11. I mean, not stricken. That's a song. Finger 11. 11 is good. Flip
front side of the coin. A photo of them on like a like a moody, moody photo of
them on a rooftop, you know, like every rock band in the early two thousand
had back of the coin picture of the single. Oh, no, I'm saying one coin
with every rock band in America to make up a coin in my perfect world. All the
presidents, they can do all the rock bands. Yeah, but they all the presidents
get their own coins or my back by doing this, then we should respect the rock
bands by giving them each their own. Can you imagine how excited you would be if
you got a coin with all the rock bands on it? It's not our job to figure out
how to fit the bands on there to be bands. I don't like government to make
the band's coin and they make it and then you get it. And guess what? All the
toilet paper should have wrappers on it.
Oh, wrapper. I thought you meant wrappers like it should be wrapped up.
No, it should have little Wayne and all this bull crap. I understand now you
want to wipe your ass with it. Wipe my ass with little Wayne. Little Wayne.
All the, I should have every single member of the DNC. And all my food should
have chocolates on it. And all my food should have whipped cream on the side.
And all my food, the sauce on the side should be free. In my perfect world and
our perfect economy instead of dollar bills and money, we'd have album
albums, LPs, and we'd trade each other. You'd say, Hey, here's this Bob Seger
album. I go, Okay, I'll trade you for
I'll trade you for the Leonard Skinner album. Yeah, what would the what would
the number one? Well, dude, obviously, the number one would be the Beatles.
You'd be so pissed off, bro, if you're working as a cashier in the store and
someone came in and they were buying a cliff bar and they're one of those guys
that comes in and they dig by cliff bar. They pay with five hundred Justin
Bieber. Oh, they've been collecting in a jar in their house, bro, or they say
hey dude, I'm not counting that for you. Take it. I only have the mollusk on
LP. Do you have a change for it?
Yeah, yeah, dude, here's fucking for Justin Bieber albums and usher album.
Yeah, whatever take it to the Bank of Music, take it to the Bank of Music,
roll it up into a
put it in the mute thing. I'm wondering what the convert like what all the
dollars would be djs and they spin the albums when you yeah deposit the how
much
it's record movie music country music.
How much would okay, okay, how much would like just a loaf of bread cost what
album would that be a loaf of bread would probably be
and how much is a loaf of bread cost three bucks, yeah, something like that,
depending on the bread, though, like a baseline loaf like what would a three
three dollar bill be yeah. What would what would three dollars dollar bill
we all by limp biscuit? Oh, that's three a three dollar bill. Anything that's
good.
Anything under five would have to be either a full album from some piece of
crap pop star or maybe just a single with a radio with it with a yeah, I think
three dollar a single. I think that's part that would be so ignition and
ignition remix on one thing. Yeah, I guess this would all the five would have
to be like
would be the all music reviews or like the pitchforks course. No, it's yeah.
It'd be how good it is. Yeah. I mean reviews. Somebody's got to be a
standard. Nobody's reviewing. You don't review money, man. You do. There's a lot
of people who do review money. I like this money, but it's not enough. Ben
Stein, Ben Stein, he doesn't review money. He has money and you can win it.
Oh yeah. You know, he was my mom's professor. Have I told you that before?
No. Yeah, he taught like that. Well, that's what that's how we got. No, this
this was after this after Buehler. He was a professor at Pepperdine and he was
then he did he made a movie about intelligent design. I don't even know
who that is inside. He's a guy who says anybody anybody Buehler Buehler. Oh
really yeah, that was my mom's professor. Yeah, he was an actor. He was
an actor and then also an economics professor. Yeah, he's like what's his
deal. He's like he's a he thinks that poor people should be grounded. A
Asian Jewish guy, yeah, who's libertarian and
thinks that he got kicked out of working in academia because he believes that God
created the world and not some monkey
or whatever evolution. So actually he aligns with all of my views. Yeah, he's
cool man. Yeah, he did and he did a movie called No Intelligence Allowed, I
believe is what it was called. Yeah, and it's
and it was about how no professors are allowed to say that God
invented the world. Yeah, that's crazy. Yeah, speaking of world,
what did you guys know? Here's something I learned music world. Pluto
was only discovered in 1930. Yeah, it's new as fuck. It's the newest.
It's really new and what came first, the dog or the planet. The dog
was named after the planet, but very shortly after. Yeah, it was new.
It was a new discovery and Walt Disney was excited about it and named
with the dog after that's like if we named a cartoon character ebay right
well ebay is not very new. He's been around for a minute. It wasn't really
discovered. That'd be like if it was one thousand nine hundred and ninety nine
and we named a cartoon character ebay.
Yeah, you're saying yeah, okay, what year is
two thousand and twenty three. Oh yeah, so then that'd be like if we named a
cartoon character x yeah, okay, I would do that yeah.
that's a good idea. That's a good name for a character. There's a good chunk of
you to find a decent, but I guess what happened with Pluto and this is this is
what maybe where I can see the scientist argument for Pluto, which I don't agree
with okay, but it only was discovered in one thousand and thirty and basically
they discovered it and announced it and then all the public was like, Oh my God,
the ninth planet and all those signs are like, oh no, it's not it's actually it's
different and everyone's like no, it's a not planet right. You and I it's and I
put it and then they were like, okay, I guess they were and you can't go back on
that that's what I'm saying. You guys fucked up in one thousand and thirty
please don't tell the nerd man. You gave it to us. We got it. You can't say
never mind. I was actually lying. I don't know the science nerds. Of course
they weren't going to like
okay, nineteen thirties as science. Well, that's the thing they just
glass just discovered football and then the nerds had to strike back exactly and
they said all right. You know what we got another planet. It's called Pluto.
It's way out there and you can't actually see it because it's so small.
Yeah, we like that planet. Actually, it's a dwarf planet. We like that planet.
Yeah. I miss those old time bullies that talk out of the side of their mouth,
man. They knew this. Yeah. 1930 to 2010, bro. You almost never see...
When was it? 1930 to 2008. That was 2010. 2008? The book came out? 2008, yeah.
I was in middle... I think I was in sixth grade, so probably 2008, 2009.
How old am I? Yeah, 2008, 2009, somewhere in there. What happened to people
talking out of the side of their mouth. You almost never see that anymore.
2006. I think it's because there's less lead in stuff.
Everybody's talking out of the side of their mouth because of these vaccines.
They're all getting Bell's palsy. Well, Bell's palsy for sure.
But that's... That too. There was also a lot of more vaccines back then.
Sorry. Sorry. I have Bell's palsy. Or the new vaccines back then.
I just got the COVID vaccine. I just got the COVID vaccine.
What you getting, Moderna? What happened to that?
People used to do that and then they started talking out of both sides of their mouth.
Oh, they would have cigars. Is that why? Yeah.
yeah to back mouth would would and they were eating sticky jellos and aspects
and it was
that makes sense to nowadays. We don't have much sticky food anymore. It's all
dry or wet. We don't really have any more nowadays. It's aspects from an only
fans model. Yeah, and only and spicy food is mostly the norm. And even then a lot
of times they put an emoji.
that's become very normal. Yeah, I see food has become normalized. I had some
hot sauce earlier that put me in the dirt, man. Yeah. Put me in the dirt. I
hate that. When you eat, when you... You took a gamble on a new hot sauce that
they had at the restaurant and it looked, it had a woman on it. You think you
know your spice level? Yeah. You think you know your Scoville line? I sit in
there hacking up a fucking
I feel like maybe I kinda wanna do one of the challenges just so I can feel
the upper limit, 'cause I've never liked spicy. I mean, I don't mind spicy
stuff, but I never seeked sorted out before. I think you might find it
orgasmic. I think I might find it horrible and it might completely ruin my
life for a couple of days, but I feel like I need to I need to I need to be
able to understand. We should do a spicy episode. Yeah,
oh my God,
a whole Jesus Christ of spicy episode yeah and we should look at spicy pics.
We should do the death nut challenge. The death nut is there a death nut.
Yeah, it's a kill the kid. Where does that grow? It grows. I think it's a
normal nut that they put spice put yeah they death up a nut.
It's so funny that all the spicy challenges you buy is like it looks
like a fucking like like Hot Wheels package where it's like the paper and
like a blister pack and it's like one thing that's like not a spicy food and
then somehow infused with chemicals. Cover it and so much like what it's
called like the one chip challenge or the
I know that yeah just it's always just you buy it. It's just a fucking little
We were at, I think we were at Gordo's and I got the birria tacos there and they had one
of those little ancho chilies.
And I don't know why, like it was like a dried pepper that was in the sauce and I bit the
whole thing because I've had those before and I've been fine but that was, I guess the
one that they put in there was the spiciest one ever because I had to go in the bathroom.
I went in the bathroom and almost threw up because I was spicy. I almost threw up
last night because the ham was too spicy. This happens with peppers often.
Some jalapenos, like every tenth jalapeno is like ten times. There's a
jalapeno my dad still talks about. He ate it ten years ago. I swear to God.
That's how I feel about this little ancho chili, dude. Every time I go home,
my dad, if my dad sees a jalapeno, he's like, "Remember that one time, that one
summer when I made cheeseburgers and we had jalapenos on the side, and there was
that one that was so spicy that everybody took a bite and everyone had to
go run water under their mouth. He's obsessed with this hell of a thing.
There was one time we were doing the same thing, little ancho chilis at a taco truck.
It was like me, you, and Mike. Same shit. I overestimated, I think I ate two or three,
overestimated my spice level and was on the side of the street trying to throw up.
From chili.
From a little dry to chili.
This spicy food ain't right. They went too far with this spicy food.
I have white ass.
become part of life. Keep that shit in Thailand to do with the Thai spice.
Julio, can you handle spicy stuff? No, not really. I do. I like that bow tie
spice. What do you think of Thanksgiving food, by the way? Yeah, first time ever.
I thought it was delicious.
Had a great, great day. I even tried to, I tried to, you know,
spruce up the mac and cheese a little bit, put the chipotle in it. That's
unusual, man. The spiciness of the mac and cheese? It wasn't even spicy, but it
something in it. It had a bit of a thing. It had a red flavor. Yeah, yeah. I know
what you mean. I noticed it. I added red stuff. To what? The mac and cheese.
And guess what? Guess what mix I used at the grocery store? Mac and cheese mix.
Quesadilla. Oh. That mac and cheese was fuego. Yeah, dude. We all, we all, everyone popped off.
Bro, we tore. Everyone popped off. We ate and left no crumbs, man.
man. We I had pressed even the tiny amount of cauliflower that I did bring
because you said last year I pulled up with a poultry option. You did, but this
year I completely redeemed myself. The biggest thing of Brussels, you pulled up
with enough Brussels sprouts to feed a family and we had family meal. We did.
We had the biggest thing of Brussels sprouts of and all I brought the drinks
and he brought the drink and they were given to me by a miracle. Do you guys
know what happened? No, what happened? Well, I got some. I got some of the
white claws and I was going to go get a big thirty rack and then when I went
outside and I was opening the windows when we were going to go buy the beer,
I was opening the window gates here at the office and in our trash area, there
was a twenty dollar bill on the ground. You're kidding. Yeah, so we got free
beer. God subsidized our drinks. Oh my God, he blessed us from the sky and I
had to do it.
The planets God knew about the five weeks of plans has been changing
shined upon in some way that is not normal, dude.
- No. - We were getting scared.
- Neptune, we were like, kind of like, you know,
kind of, we felt like maybe, we were saying like,
oh, this kind of sucks, whatever, this is kind of crap.
- But Pluto's back and I have proof, man.
- But Pluto brought us back.
- Do you guys wanna see my painting?
- Yeah. - Yes.
- What do we know about Pluto?
- Tiny, smallest planet. - Small.
- Bingo.
- Mercury, Mercury, second smallest planet.
- Look at this painting.
- It's so gorgeous. - Oh my God.
the world. You record an Instagram reel of you painting that night. I wish you
had it go viral. It would go so viral. I'm going to get up and show this. I'm
going to show Cameron's camera how small this is.
That is a small planet picture I've ever seen. It looks like a purse, too,
because of the handle. I like the handle. Give me the loose thumb tack over
there. I got to hang this shit up. Oh, it's it stuck to me and rip my thumb
off. Is that what the super glue is for? How did you get it in your mouth? I opened it
with my fucking mouth because I ain't no bitch. This looks amazing. That is a great painting.
Wow. Looks great. Pluto y'all. Reminds you of anything? Planet. So that's my amazing painting
for today. That was amazing. I think that art is going to be a really big that's a
thing. I mean we've talked about it before, but this this five weeks of
planet shit has opened our minds to different avenues once this whole
podcast that we know once everything's over once this turns to dust once the
ceiling over there finally collapses. Yeah what's going on with that? I can't
tell if it grew or not it kind of was browning me. It's just brown. It's sagging quite badly.
It is sagging, but there's a family up there or something. Are they made out of water?
there. Maybe it's the water. They might be making water or they have a hot tub. Are
they fish? They could have a hot tub in their apartment. I don't believe that.
Could be. I can see that. It's just a it's practically a bath. Maybe they have. It's not so
strange to have. Maybe they're like they're on a permanent honeymoon. Oh lovers. And they have a heart shaped tub.
Oh yeah. That has a jacuzzi jacuzzi. Renting the honeymoon apartment.
Honeymoon apartment in Ridgewood, Queens. Yeah. Wow. This would be an amazing place to
That does sound wonderful. A balcony, a hot tub.
Where would you guys go on a honeymoon to?
Bridgewood Queens. Right above this office.
I want to go to China.
I want to go underground.
I would love to go underground.
Oh, I want to go to Vietnam and see the underground tunnels.
And make love in the honeymoon tunnel.
Oh my god, dude.
With a grenade wire above me and a bunch of razor blades everywhere.
That sounds so fucking awesome.
In a spike pit?
Yeah, some of that shit.
What is that thing called? Is it Puka Pit?
No, you're thinking of a necklace.
But what's the word?
Well, they had a lot. They had the ones where...
Pungi?
They were kind of playing Pungi.
Pungi Pit?
That's what they called it in Tony Hawk's Frozen Skater 2.
A Spike Pit?
They called it a Spike Pit, but in the first game they called it by the name,
and I think it starts with a P.
We'll figure it out later. It's not of any importance.
it's okay. Well, that's fine. We'll figure it out. You guys think you'd be any good
at guerrilla warfare or do you think you're the only type of warfare? I'd be
good. Yeah, me too. I feel like I'm much more built for this line shit. I don't
think so walking out line. I still fight like that. Get well, if I get in a fight
with somebody at the bar, I say you get eight friends, I'll get eight friends.
Let's walk at each other play Red Rover. Yeah, we're about to walk at each other,
get eight friends and get a kid and put him he's going to give him a guitar or
something. Yeah, he can play. Let it rock and let's walk at each other with our
hands out. He's probably going to play smoke on the water. Play smoke on the water? He's
probably only going to play smoke on the water. Yeah, I guess you're right. It's the first
song he learned. I would have been getting it as a little drummer boy, man. It would
be so scary to be in one of those lines because they were using the muskets that would misfire
like 60% of the time and they didn't have rifling inside it, so the shots didn't go
straight. They would just go out in random directions. So you'd just be standing with
two lines facing each other and you'd just be shooting at each other. I feel like everyone's
was missing like eighty percent of the time. I feel like and you're really
learning and we're just standing there and it's a loud banks going off and
nobody's die.
The fuck is going to die first Jesus Christ yeah, you might like it's like a
game at the fair or something. It's like you're playing a egg spoon.
Imagine
a really bad
yeah,
that to be so scary man. I would imagine trying that shit now with like an air
it's like rows of guys with fucking AR 15s. Yeah, just everyone is me dead.
Everyone would know it was a fight would last two seconds. I would definitely if I
was on the front lines, I bet we'd be marching, you know,
you're a high flying flag. Yeah, that's playing dad dad dad dad dad dad dad dad
dad. And then I would I would say, Oh, fuck my shoes on tide man. Hold on, give
second but then I slowly the entire every line kind of passes me now I'm at the
back of the line and now I'm the chef general guess we're making grits nice
okay now I just now was thinking about you know the Looney Tunes short where
Bunker Hill Bunny or Bugs Bunny is in the Battle of Bunker Hill and it's him
and Yosemite Sam and they're shooting cannons at each other no it sounds fun
really I guess I kind of just assumed everyone's seen that because I saw it
probably 500 times did you watch it in school but as a Bunker Hill no I watched
watched it at home because of my love for bugs bunny, but I just did where I
guess this doesn't make any sense. If you guys haven't seen it, but in that
it's two forts that are built right next to each other and they're shooting
cannons at each other. You think they ever actually do they just feel like
okay, we're going to build our fort here and you guys build your fort right here.
It's a while to one of the forts blows. We should make you guys chill. While we
build our fort, you build your fort chill everybody chill. We're just going
we're going to go away to forts next to each other so that we can have a we can
have the war. If the forts are too far apart from each other, we're going to
we're not going to be able to battle will not work. The battle will not work.
The guns aren't good yet. We don't have enough gunpowder to shoot the cannon
balls. That for neither of us want to go do the line. We don't want to line
anymore. We both want to shoot from inside the fort, so let's just shake on
this. We're not going to fight. What was the country that in World War One? They
thought it was still the line. Was it Poland? No, it wasn't Poland. It was I
think it was like
Luxembourg. It was something weird and they pulled up and like all the regalia
and they're like Cray and they were like, let's do this. Let's make the line
I think
I think it was Poland. I don't think so. There's nerve gas and trenches yeah. It
was literally like a guy was like, okay, I guess we're going to start the war.
Let's line up from shortest to tallest and then his head just
like that must have been crazy man. That must have been we're pulling up on
horses, yeah, like horses like it was bush gardens pulling up on like giant
ass horses with like they put their horses in clothes and they're like,
yeah, let's go to war man. That must do that. I mean that AK forty seven,
yeah, that was suck being the general or whatever that was like yeah, trust me,
they're gonna line up. It's still a line. I know dude that's what that's what it
is and that's what you as in Vietnam, bro. We all we put yeah, we're gonna
fuck you up like get ready. You get you come out. We're going to fight you bro
and we're going to fucking get we're coming there and we're going to shoot
and we got second. We see you we're going to shoot. Yeah,
we got beat by dental floss, yeah, walking around ringing a bell.
Yeah,
where are you getting?
The tiger trap to just a fucking just a spike that fell out of a literally
walking into Jurassic Park, right? Oh, here we go. It's like it's like a bully
school being like going up to the nerd me like hey as soon as school's out like
at two thirty, I'm going to beat your ass and the kid just goes home at two
o'clock
walking around like what the
that shit must have sucked so bad. I think almost every war has been
basically shit yeah, but like
even more because it's like they already had like
it's like I can't imagine going to
before after rock and roll has been invented,
like all you'd want to do is just go home and listen to rock and roll the
whole time. You finally had something to live for. Yeah, exactly. All these
other there's a music or the world war one and two. What are you gonna go
back?
Fuck that. No,
I'm a fucking little trumpet ass. Yeah, but I gotta go sit in a club and
dress up and listen to music. Fuck that man, right? Don't even have a cell
phone, got a fucking telegram and shit.
there's somebody back home writing a song about how he just fucked your
girlfriend. Yeah, exactly, and you can't you don't know yet. Yeah, we don't have
the computer. You come home and your your your family is now living in a
house of straw. We had three little pigs because they stripped every piece of
metal and wood out of your house to to invent a new guitar
to send you a box of spikes. Yeah, dude, imagine they need more spikes.
say your mom gets a job building spikes because it's a war. They need spy and
that
when rock came out, you're sitting there and your white your wife is back home
getting fucked by a ninety pound guy who looks exactly like it most looks like
the most beautiful woman of all time and it's from bloody London right God damn
yeah, no going to Vietnam. Fuck that all these all the you know I would have
England involved in that war. I think that if a war came up in Vietnam, it's
Luckily, we're nowhere close. Us and Iran are going to patch things up pretty fast, I
think. As long as I turn 27 before that shit happens, I'm good. But if I was draft, I think
that I would straight up say, "Dude, I can't do it. I can't do it, man. I'm not built for
this war shit."
They didn't let you in if you had flat feet, right?
Dude, I'm doing jump training.
I feel like flat feet was the thing that's like the stereotypical draft dodger thing.
You can't let me in if I have flat feet.
I have no arch. I have no arch either. You're not special bro. Yeah, I know, but we're both
going to have a high arch. I don't know. I have a few of high arches. I'm going to be
real. My feet are fucking made for straight up. Yeah. Oh yeah. Yeah. He's got high arches.
because I knew he got high arches. I think you and I were not going to war.
He is going what is going to be the bones you do of the next war. If you
it's anxiety, it has to be right, it's going to be as I mean that you have to
just be full of the something that we have over the people in the in the past
generation, they're getting drafted and yeah, they're trying to be like, oh, I
have bone spurs. My hips are they hurt when I lie down now. They're going to
move. I can't dance now. I said they come to me. They're trying to they're
trying to get me in the army. I say, listen, buddy, you can do if you want to.
in fact, I want you to because the second you put a gun in my hands, I'm going to
slay every member
of my company. They're all going to be dead because I'm a psycho zoomer and I
have PTS. I have PTSD from a bad interaction at McDonald's. Yeah, I have
PTSD from a interaction where I was kind of weird. One time I thought that the
computer screen was a person at the McDonald's straight up. Yeah. Back then,
if they tried to be like, oh, I can't be in the army because I'm crazy, they
they would take your clipboard and they would take a big red marker and they
just write gay on it. Yeah. And you would not be able to get a job for the rest of
your life. No, no. They change your last name. You don't have to go to war, but you also have to live in a hole now.
Yeah. You're going to live in an apartment that has a big arrow pointing to it that says gay guy inside.
Nowadays, they say, if you try to get out of the army by saying you're gay, they say,
please, we need you. Yeah, we need you, man. We need you to whip the other men into shape.
Yeah, we need you and we need you to, I mean, you're already good at the computer.
Get behind the like, the drone thing.
I could probably be content creator for the army or something.
Yeah.
Some kind of streamer.
I would love to work social media for the army right now.
I could do that shit, I think.
Oh my god, I would love to go to PAX East with the pull-up bar.
I'd be the guy that stands next to the pull-up bar at PAX East.
I could be a recruiter for sure.
It's not the pull-up bar at PAX East, but it is VR pull-ups.
you guys are you're talking about the being the recruiter who goes to Paxos.
That's that's the one that's your that's your like that's your pizza party.
That's your once your your day to day job is you are texting fifteen year old
and say
you finish your homework. Oh shit, my bad. You still in school. I'll text
back. I thought that's literally all they do. They take they text high
schoolers and I was friends with this army recruiter on Facebook when I was in
high school because I would just add like any friend request that came in. I
to accept it, bitch and it was funny to do that because you so funny. I have
thousands of friends on Facebook. A lot of people fucking kill for that. Okay,
well, there's one guy, the friend cap, this one guy, no, I didn't
yeah, I probably have twice as many. I deleted it, I deleted it, but there's
one guy that like my Facebook group has been popping off, y'all. Yeah, my man,
but there's this one army recruiter I was friends with that would try to make
memes about why you should join. And there's this one that was stuck in my
brain forever. It was like, "TB12 is throwing touchdown passes while you're
passing your opportunity to join the US Army." Damn, dude. That shit worked in
New Hampshire, too. Bro, that probably worked. That got three kids. He probably
got the biggest meathead in the school. That and then the Dodge Charger,
obviously. The Dodge Charger's always gonna get people. These days, all you'd
have to say is, "Do you guys wanna... Do you wanna go shoot a Draco or a
yet. Join the army man. And avoid student debt. You want to avoid student loan debt and go
shoot a glizzy man? Go straight up to fucking go to Iran right now. You need to, we need
you to go over there and instill a phantom tax on Iran. You need to go jump out of where
the battle bus is leaving. You better get your spot man. If I was a recruiter I would
just be telling people like you have to sign this right now or you're going to jail. Yeah.
it's just been a you're being sued. Yep, I pretend everything to drop the soup. If
you if you sign right here, if you know, I don't tell them they're joining me, I
just say your name and Tokyo drift style situation. Yeah, what happened? Why did
he have to go to Japan and who knows? Have we talked about it before? Yeah, I
never seen it. You ever seen Tokyo drift? We've talked about this. He gets in big
Bantha Pudu and then he fucking has to go to Japan.
yeah, he said he gets in Bantha Pudu
shit, a Star Wars fan. I know I know that well. I didn't expect him. I know
what a Bantha is, but I wouldn't expect him to say who do is poop in the Star
Wars.
I say that quite quite often. Yeah, I never heard you say that before. Well,
you don't hang out with me when I cussed it.
I don't I say I say that kind of stuff. That's true. I say alternative cusses.
Yeah, alternative cussing is good again earlier instead of Dick. I said prick
brick. That's funny. Brick is always good instead of a but how much time do
we have left on the holly relax bro? Well, there's a
the hell's that there's a new jay so that's why I thought you're trying to
get out of here. I was no, no, no, I have to show this new song. I forgot
about so I want to preface this by saying that I didn't know we were
acknowledging Pluto as a planet, so I had to make this one really quick. I
need to push back against this because we've we listed the plants are doing so
20 times on the episode. There's audio evidence. Okay, that's not an excuse.
Well, I think what you'll hear in this song
is lyrics. Is lyrics. And a beat. And a beat. And maybe a chorus, man. And I
think you're gonna be pretty impressed. Alright, let me hear this shit. What's
it called? Remember. Damn. It's actually his deepest song yet.
Man,
I don't know what I've been doing, man.
I'm so confused.
I gotta talk to my best friend Pluto about this.
Oh, OJ the alien.
I'm spinning in this cosmic confusion.
I'm lost in love, caught in grand illusion.
Neptune's allured like a magnetic pull.
My thoughts scattered like stardust in the pool.
I love the pool, man, the pool is cool.
Summertime, go there right after school.
We'd all go there playing fish out of water.
That was the game that I used to slaughter.
fifth
the
*Rap music*
*Demonic laughter*
(laughing)
- This is plutonium rapping.
Cookie Monster?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Okay,
that's a really good one. That was great. The beat was amazing, a little bit of
you know some kind of padding, maybe at the end. What do you mean? For the
length
we do do we
Tony and his speaking plutonium. It makes sense yeah, but then he had the
adlibs that exponent for the well, the Adler English. Oh, so that was saying
what he said yeah, okay, he said lives were done in English. So we do it. It
He was talking about how he remembers Bill Nye the Science Guy and Cat Dog and Toonami
and how much he misses playing in the pool. See, because every good rapper has a song
about the 90s. Every single good rapper has a song about the 90s. Yeah, I'm from the 90s.
Boy, I'm from the 90s. Do you guys consider yourselves from the 90s, man? I don't think
I don't know because we're told all the time that I feel like I'm from right now.
Yeah, I feel like I just now I'm hitting on the pulse.
Yeah, I got I'm not my finger.
My whole body's my whole I live on the pole.
It's my I'm in the I am the pulse.
We're Gen Z, right?
Did they change the definition again?
Dude, I think I really I think we're cusp.
I think this I think we are literally Gen Z.
I'm not going to lie to you.
I think we're elders.
Z lineals, man.
I literally we are.
Yeah, fuck my life.
by elders Ellen you doesn't have between one thousand nine hundred and
ninety six and twenty two. I was born ninety seven barely made ninety eight
bro. I was born in two thousand nine. I'm barely made it.
I'm right on the cusp.
Wow. What's the new generation of these alpha
generation alpha? You say what? Yeah. These thirteen year olds are alpha
generation. My nephew speaking of gen alphas, his birthday yesterday, I called
them on the phone to say happy birthday. The same happy birthday immediately
takes the phone from me or from his mom and goes up to his brother and starts
doing, he started doing POV like Call of Duty and was just walking around the
house shooting stuff and there's, I just, I have a video of him just shooting his
brother like that and his brother's just standing still trying to do stuff with a
paper turkey they were making. I think he's gone... Do stuff with a paper turkey?
I think he's gone... What the hell kind of perverted shit is your nephew doing?
I think my nephew's gone completely insane. You think he finally lost it, Slim
I think that this phone generation is truly fucking up the younger generation
because why the hell is he shooting?
You didn't walk around with like a...
Yeah, every kid shot.
He's doing COV...
What was your favorite gun when you were a kid?
P90?
No, like a fake gun.
Oh, fake.
Oh, a stick?
Bro, I had this really good...
Nerf gun, I guess.
I had this amazing stick, dude.
I used anything.
That had like a handle.
It was like this crazy, like it had a natural handle in it.
It had a good, yeah.
And it looked huge like a Halo gun.
Sick.
I kept it for a long time in my parents basement.
You know those long chip clips that you used to like seal?
I would use that as a gun. I killed my dad thousands of times.
I also had a very realistic General Grievous' blaster that I got for Christmas one year.
That's cheating.
That is cheating. That's why I used the stick more.
I don't think I was allowed to have gun toys for quite some time.
We were allowed to have lightsabers and that was a bad mistake.
I was allowed to have lightsabers for sure.
I don't know. Lightsabers is the worst mistake that you can make for your child.
We had a potato gun, a real one that shot a potato. That's cool.
Yeah, it was sick. Like the PVC. Yeah, the PVC hairspray. Yeah, hairspray. That shit would launch.
Why were you allowed to have that? Did your brother just make it? Science vibes. Yeah,
how are you going to stop someone from inventing something? It's not possible.
What, I can't have a potato? I can't have a potato in a PVC pipe? Yeah, what do you want
for dinner tonight? Potato again. I'm actually really hungry for potato and I want it served
on a PVC pipe in the middle. And also I need a new hairdo. It worked, man. I need a new
hairdo. It worked every time.
Well, I tried to look up how to make those, and I learned, like early YouTube, there was
like tutorials on how to make zip guns.
You can kill somebody with anything.
My friend's older brother made a like magnet gun that shot a nail.
What the hell?
300 milligrams a can.
300?
Yeah.
That's too much, dude.
That's why I didn't want to take a sip. I know that G Fuel has 300.
I drank the whole thing.
I thought it was 200, dude. Well, I'm done.
Yeah, you're going to have heart problems constantly.
I got to go to the gym. Bye.
Bye.
Is there anything we need to talk about?
I don't think so. I guess it's the...
Oh my God.
That's the end of week four, week five, the final week.
Get ready.
This is coming up next.
Big shit plan.
Oh, and then if you're in New York, we're on a show with Girl God for the holidays.
Oh yeah, we're going to be...
- Yeah, what day is it? - An amazing choir.
- You can find it on their social media. - Yeah, December 10th, I believe.
- December 10th. - I'm still in New York. Come find me.
- Oh yeah, Jubio's in New York. - Oh yeah.
- Look for him, man. - Yep.
- All right. - Bye, mate. - Bye.
This is the story of Neptune, a planet report by Cameron Fetter.
Once upon a time, 30 astronomical units away from the sun,
There was a blue and icy planet named Neptune.
One orbit, Neptune woke up and felt depressed.
"What makes me special?" asked Neptune.
"I feel so average."
"Don't worry, Neptune," said the sun.
"You're very special.
For example, you're an ice giant.
Your distance from me means that you're dark and cold,
covered by frozen, icy materials."
"Big whoop," replied Neptune.
"That doesn't make me unique.
Uranus is an ice giant as well."
"Well, maybe your surface doesn't matter.
It's what you're like on the inside that counts.
You have a rocky core," the sun said.
"Yeah, right.
So does Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Uranus,
and probably Jupiter and Saturn too.
I knew I wasn't special.
You're just making me feel worse.
I think I'm going to kill myself."
No.
Neptune opened its desk drawer with its hand, where it kept its revolver and used its hand
to put the gun to its atmosphere.
"No!"
"I'm done doing this with you!" screamed the sun in anguish.
"It seems like every rotation you threaten to kill yourself.
You think you have it bad?
Look at Pluto, the poor guy isn't even a planet anymore!"
"Even my suffering isn't unique," sighed Neptune.
"I think I get it now.
I was so concerned with being special, but what's actually special is that I'm so similar
to everyone else in my solar system.
It's about togetherness and family.
That's right, said the sun.
I'm glad you came around.
Coming around the sun.
Yeah, coming around me, I mean.
The me.
Let's eat.
And the planets all started in on their Thanksgiving dinner.
Moral.
The moral of the story.
Okay.
There is nothing interesting about Neptune.
[BARKING]