I
You guys it's officially the five
The five weeks of planets are coming to a
Please I don't want it to come to an end. I don't want us. No, don't do that. Keep it
keep it going. That's not right. Keep it going right invent another planet right
now. Right. I do is that we're doing a plan here today. We should have invented
another one. We have a full planet in front of us. Okay, well, just invent one
more the moon, the planet of the earth, planet of the moon, but just invent one
more. There's billions of planets in the solar. I mean, the galaxy one in our
solar system. I've said there's right now man, billions of planets in the
solar system. Just name a planet Sedna Sedna. All right, Ares,
that one sounded fake. Those are the two exoplanets. I know in the solar
system. What is an XO? Paris is the one that here's what I'm saying every minute.
Do we have to add another week of some people? Some people ain't never paid
attention to the planet reports and it shows do we have to add a bit of
attention? It's Alpha Centauri. Yes, that's exactly on man. Planet dingbat.
I know all about all this shit from every planner. One hundred and fifty
million from one hundred and fifty one moons by which one had that planet
dingbat that was Venus. Maybe no, it doesn't have a hundred and fifty moons.
that had to be one of the gas giants, bro. That's my Jupiter. That was Jupiter man. I
had probably hundred and fifty one moons, including Titan. Well, that's in the original generation.
It's a different generation of planets and the second generation. They added more. Now
that's in Jupiter, gold and silver. What the fuck are we going to do after this? But we're
all at ideas. We have the five for the boy for the planet report. Oh crap. I spilled
a little bit of water onto my hand. This is one drop. Well, it doesn't seem so. Oh, that's
not a deal. Can we start over now? We can start the whole episode a little bit.
Look, my hand's shiny now.
Cameron's got a wet hand.
This is not going to be a viral video called shiny hand.
Shiny hand white boy. I'm giving my hand under the table the rest of the
episode. But then it looks like it don't do that man. Then it looks like you
got wet from something else bro. It looks like it's wet from Jess.
Your hand looks odder now that you're putting it so front and center on the
you need to learn what to do with your hand. It is a little bit more. Put it on
here, put it on there and then it'll look like you're DJing and the sweat
will be. Now this looks like you're a thinker. Don't think like this man. This
pisses me off. Yeah. What's wrong with thinking? Well, it just is too much. I
feel like anti intellectual. I feel like you might outsmart me at any second
here. I already have. We're doing what? You got spilled water on your damn
hand, you fucking fool. He spilled water in a Machiavellian way. If you guys
didn't realize I basically made the episode funny just now. Wow, wow, you
got us a good thing to start with up, man. You got us an amazing people. So
realize that sometimes the class clown has a lot going on inside his head.
Yeah, sometime the class clown actually does all that shit on purpose. Yeah,
instead of a bad home life. All right, let's go through the outfits. Okay,
well, you're looking at mine and I assume you guys probably are like what
the hell I'm thinking. Well, my initial impression is well, you're right. It's
it's what the hell yeah. So what you guys assume you guys don't know is that this
is an album cover and it's an album by they might be giants and if you look at
the back of my shirt, you'll see the name of this album. It will say that you
can read it off for everybody to hear
the might Apollo 18 tour Apollo 18. There was the last mission to the moon
was Apollo 17. That was the last time this in demand mission to the moon
today folks. We're doing Apollo. Where did you get this shirt from my dad? Oh
yeah, I can tell because this is an old this is a man is a shirt is a older
album. That's a single stitch that you can tell that's how you know it's a
real true because they stopped doing single stitch in like that's a good
shirt. Ninety-four. I think something around there. Okay. All right. So
that's a little bit of your shirt, but I'm still saying what the hell to your
hat, man, bro is bro. Does this blow up on the shirt? It's a circle like a
moon. Yeah, and there's yellow and there's a man in the moon. Yeah, or a
rabbit or Chinese believe there's a rabbit in the moon and is close to a
a rabbit. I read that is a rabbit. I think he's a he's not a he's a beaver yeah.
Yeah, beavers and beavers, a subset of rabbit or a type of that's true. It's
got buck teeth like one yeah.
How many different animals can there be with buck does it besides nerds and
beavers and rabbits, nerds, beavers, rabbits, they're all in the same genius.
Oh, because you guys know did you guys see that there was a kid who was
protesting the nerd emoji because it looks exactly like him. Yes, now I have
I have news to break about that. So there was a kid. He was a ten year old
kid. He looked just like the nerd emoji. So he said, please apple change the
nerd emoji and he drew a new one where it has a little smile, but what I noticed a
long time ago here, Julio pulled it up for us. I noticed this a while ago. If
you you know how you when you type on your phone, it will it sometimes gives
the option to to replace to replace the words with an emoji. I know predict
air. Yeah, yeah, when you type the word nerd, the emoji does not come up. You
have to type glasses. They're so woke that that is not even a nerd.
I owe you anymore. It's a show me that emoji and tell me that's not a
fucking nerd. I know bro. It's got buck teeth man. It's crazy that you can't
that who would type glasses to get that instead of nerd right. Nobody talking
about yeah, you're not it's not. I mean who wears glasses is cool. Well,
nobody Harry Potter, Harry Potter, not cool. Jerry Potter is a nerd. Now Jeff
Goldbloom's a nerd Jeff Jeff Jeff Goldbloom's a nerd. Yeah, Potter's a
nerd. Everybody who's wears glasses is a nerd. I'm doing it ironically in which
because there's a loser there. A hipster yeah, they're a hipster and they want to
they want to wear glasses before it's cool. Anyway, sorry to derail the
the like an emoji to yeah, it does look a bit. It does look like the Bucky's
emoji, Bucky's emoji, yeah, the yellow shining. It was a big shining moon
to last night. It was a waning. I may be three quarters crescent. It was really
scary. I thought that it was bright, bright moon last night. Do you know that
the moon cycle controls why your girlfriend is mad at you? I heard this
Apparently, girls' bodies get attracted...
Okay, what do girls like more than anything?
The moon.
White balls.
White balls, depending.
So they look up at the moon, they see a big white ball,
and their downstairs starts getting all hairy and crazy,
like a werewolf.
They grow...
That's where their pubes come from.
Yeah.
So if you want to make sure that your girl has no pubes,
block that moon out, man.
Block the moon from your house.
Inside at night.
Do not open the shades.
Do not let her out, or else she will grow.
- A fro down below. - Movie night.
- Movie night. - Yeah.
- Wow. - Yeah, I just came up with that shit.
- Oh my God, I wish I had you on today's song.
- Yeah, you do, man. - Yeah.
- Yeah, I'm really excellent at rapping.
- I know, I wish I had you on today's song
that we will play in a little bit
after we're done going through our outfits.
- I think that only happens if women
are away from telephones or something.
- What do you mean?
- I think I saw this on Rogan some years ago.
That women, if they're away from telephones
for a certain amount of time,
when they're in a gaggle a group, they start will think up with the moon.
Yeah in a rhythmic. Well, what I was wondering is it true? Is it true?
People always say that, you know, when there's full moon animals behave crazy
and that humans are committing more crimes and acting more crazy. Is that
actually true? I know I was thinking about this last night. I don't know if
that's scientifically true or not. If the moon affects people's mood, yeah,
or their behaviour and animals, not just people, but animals to the moon.
people are animals. My Luna Luna see you guys know about that. Yes, Luna see wow.
I never thought about you didn't know that yeah. Holy that's like how dementia
and demented have the are the same thing. Well, that's the same word yeah. Yeah, I
didn't know that till a couple of weeks ago right, but that's literally the same
word. Yeah, well, that was a pretty you know, it's not like Luna means the moon
that's like the same that's not really at all. I did know etymology wise
running is like ran
is what you said. I didn't know that a Cornish game hen was a chicken. I
thought it was a completely new type of animal. How often are you thinking about
a Cornish game hen that that matters? I also until right now thought a Cornish
game hen was like a like a bird. I thought it was a completely different
bird, like how a turkey is different. I guess I could have thought that, but I'm
not. I can't say that I've thought about a Cornish game hen. You have never been
that's the craziest name for a fucking bird. Of course you think about that all
the time. I don't. That's the bird for like the one that was a fancy.
tiny bird food. I think the bird the the thing that you use in a restaurant
sketch quail, a Cornish, you see, I thought I would game hen was closer to a
quail. I thought it was a tiny bird, just a chicken is a Cape on a chicken
two. Is that a different bird Cape on? What the hell are you talking about? Oh,
it's a Cape on that's you bitch got you, you got your way. I'm sensing lunacy. I
am between you two right now. This kind of crazy is a Cape on adversarial nature.
I don't know what a small is I've never heard also a small food bird. Okay,
well, there's one that only you knew at this table. How do you guys not know a
capon? I've never had it. I never had it either. I know it. I know what is
though. C A P O N let's look it up. Maybe it's the same thing as a cap on
this shit. Yeah, ain't no such thing as a shit. Whoa, a capon is a male
chicken that has been castrated or neutered
and that makes it taste different. I guess capons cost more than hens,
because they're expensive to feed and not mass produce, which is why you won't see
them sold at a chain supermarket. Yeah. Why is it better to eat? I guess that's
why I've never seen one fattened for eating, so it's actually a bigger
chicken, like a wagyu chicken. Yeah, that's cool. All right, walk us through
your outfit, Pat. Well, I am some kind of a werewolf. I think I really tried my
best on this. I kind of just look like Howard Stern right now. You do look a
lot like Howard Stern. Yeah, kind of, kind of just look like Howard Stern. If
he got bit by a wolf. Howard Stern does have a bit of a, he does have an apish
kind of hair configuration. He is set up to
be in a movie where he takes off his sunglasses and there's some kind of
crazy animal eye underneath, like a werewolf like bloodshot eye. Like a
thriller. Yeah, exactly. Or a Judge Doom, who framed Roger Rabbit, some pop out
eyes. He has some silly eyes. But I could see him, he's like probably the
perfect specimen to be a werewolf. He has silly eyes under his glasses. He pops
them off whenever a woman gets on the Sibium. Yep, and he goes, oh, he takes
him off and he's got binocular. Wow. Wow. I'm looking at your butt. We need
to do more stuff like this on this show. Stern, just like having his voice
is because now that we have video, we need to get a Sibium is what you're
saying. Not a Sibium. It's outplayed, man. Yeah, we get a new thing. The
Sibium's washed. We have Juvio sit on. Let's just put an obstacle course over
there. Yeah, that's not a bad idea. A sexual obstacle course where it's like
wipe out, but you're jumping on the bad dragon thing. It's like a pit in the
pendulum, but there's a dildo on the- Why did he make the women ride the
Sibiu? He didn't make them, they wanted to fucking- Well, yeah, but why was that
his thing? 'Cause it was- It was a shock jock. Yeah, it was something different.
I guess they would make, I guess, yeah, but that's like, you know, that's just
the sound of vibration, really. And also this.
Yeah, I have to say that's more the draw than the vibration. You think he ever got
on that thing. How it's a turn. You think he ever sat on that thing? He loved that
shit. Think he ever sat on that and put the whole thing up his rear? Hell yeah.
I would have shaken up his balls like a can of soda. Yeah. Yeah, then would have
shot a spray. Yeah, it'd be foaming out everywhere. Yeah. Coming out through the
cracks in his zipper. I just shot a huge rope. But I think they probably- No,
that's Alan Alda. I lost the- Why do you want to do this impression so bad?
Because I'm dressed up like him. You're not dressed- you're dressed up like a
monkey was sung. You're dressed up like like
don't feel like doing anything.
I'm Howard Stern.
No, this is the lazy song.
Okay, should I dress like Bruno Mars then?
I don't know how he talks.
Filipino-y?
You are so yeah, you're whole because the mic is also covering your mouth.
You're like a shadow. Yeah, yeah, you look evil. I do and also you chose to
have a grim reaper. Yeah, I thought this would work better. No, it's not working
informing that much. Now you're resting your boob table. You look like a magic
trick. Yeah, yeah, you don't wait. All right, enough of your fucking outfit.
Yeah, let's let's hear we can talk about the show. I think I have a guess about
yours. What's the guess man that it's coloured like the moon? It's coloured
like the
yeah, it's not that deep for me man. It's coloured like the moon and the fit the
man in the moon, the face in the moon. I kind of just look like one of the Abu
Grey prisoners. Now
I don't really look like a monkey anymore. That's because the monkey
because you covered the monkey mask.
Yeah.
You can't do it.
I mean, of course you don't.
Yeah, you put a hood over your entire head.
Yeah,
I was stepping behind a wall and saying I don't look like anything now.
I'd look like nothing.
I don't even look like I'm here.
Yeah, we should get one of those.
Have you guys seen the invisibility panels?
No, I can imagine what it might be.
I think I've seen a camera through the...
No, man.
It's crazy.
it's like a piece of plastic that bends light in like from two directions into
the middle so that it just basically like you can if you sit in the middle of
it it looks like there you don't exist and you're invisible oh is that what
they use for that like have you ever seen that public toilet that's all like
what's it called is it invisibility panels or is it the two-way mirrors I'm
I'm trying to think I don't know mirrors probably yeah, this thing's expensive.
Would you put that I'd poop anywhere? Yeah, I'd poop in a probably wouldn't
want to pee in. I poop in our bathrooms pretty often man. I just do that.
Somebody told me that the fuck is the problem with that man? I don't toilet.
That's what I'm told me. They got yelled at. I think it was Neil. Neil went
into a bar into a bar bathroom was shitting in there and the bartender ran
over said he was in there for too long. I guess it was one of those ones that
you got to fight. It's a fucking turd. I guess they thought he was in there.
He was banging on the wall and going,
I guess they thought that he was shooting up, which is why they like
banged on the door at him, and then when he got out and said,
"Sorry, I was shitting," the lady went, "Well, you don't do that in a
bar."
That's one of those social norms that needs to be eliminated. It doesn't make
any sense. I've shitted in so many bars. Don't install a toilet in your
bar if you don't want people to use it. You have food at your bar.
I'm gonna crap. Yeah, and I digest food instantly.
I have I have I have your bells the thing, though you know how we can we
can prove show all these these evil bartenders, how that they're wrong,
yeah, how they're I just remember there's a curb your enthusiasm episode
where Larry is opening his coffee shop and he wants to have a bathroom. I
remember where there's no pooping allowed and you shows you show somebody
that they're doing what Larry David did in an episode. They're going to turn
around. They're liable to kill themselves. What if they say that he's
their spirit animal, though,
but he's supposed to be the kind of spirit animal where you like secretly are like, I
want to be like that. But in real life, you're like, oh my God, he's so me. He he acts like
me. But then you're like, oh, thank you so much. Like how people want to like, oh, thank
you so much. That's you. And this is Larry. I want a box of bear. It's honestly no worry,
but worries like if not, but like seriously, thank you so much. It's like a spirit animal
in the sense that like like oh, like say like a bear is your spirit animal. But like, you
know, you always have a thought like as a man, you're walking around acting like a bear.
a man you always have a thought like I could get in a boxing ring with a bear.
This fucking Larry the David guy, nobody needs to be acting like him. He's a scumbag.
He teaches you how not to act. Yeah. Isn't that fascinating? I think he has
actually sociopathic tendencies. I think I'm somewhat agreeing with you. I think that
we have an essay that we could make video wise. Here's what I noticed about
video essays yesterday. Why do they always have this parentheses at the end?
Like one about Larry David would be like, "Why Larry David acts like an asshole."
double and then princes and why he's right yeah. Why get that parenthesis
out of it's because of the argument that shit they want to hook it on yeah. Why
does it work? I want to hook you. I'm watching all these fucking videos man no,
but I know I know exactly what you're talking about. Shit man. I'm trying to
watch NBA highlights, not why Josh Giddy what he did was wrong princes or right. I
don't want to watch this shit. This is a fucking for all right. If you live in a
country where the age of consent is different now, they got him on some
bullshit man. What do you mean? Apparently the woman had a fake ID.
Oh.
So? Was he supposed to hire a private investigator? Maybe. I mean, if he's
got the money to do that. How old was she? 12? She was fucking four years
old, man. She's a four year old child, yeah. Well, I guess if she's that
young, maybe. And the fake ID said she was 65 years old. You're telling me
that a man named Josh Kitty was...
Yeah, big surprise. Yeah.
You're telling me that Josh Kitty
was hitting up kids. Here's the thing man, Josh, do you realize how much of a
fucking privilege it is to be a fucking just corn-fed white boy in the NBA? Is he
Australian? He's Australian. Yeah. Yeah. I don't think he's corn-fed, I think he's kangaroo-fed.
To be a roo-fed white boy in the NBA, that is such a such a mistake, a universal
just just crazy stroke of luck that you're in there. Don't fuck it up for us.
You're ruining the reputation of guys like Bryant "Big Country" Reeves or the other
guy Jokic.
Jokic?
Jokic.
I don't know how to spell any of that fucking Polish shit.
Well, you're not spelling, you're talking.
Or speaking it.
You put a J and it's supposed to make a different sound, I'm done with that.
I'm out of there.
That's any other language except ours pretty much.
Every single Balkan style language where you got the Y with the shit on top of it.
I don't like that shit. I don't know how to get that shit on top of the Y unless it's a
Zivic. I like those, but that got the Y with the shit on it. You just basically destroyed
your entire position. You're making a convincing argument and then you said you liked the most
insane one. Yeah, I know. I don't agree with you anymore. The most impossible to pronounce.
Well I'm a hypocrite and I'm a double crosser. Don't say you're a double crosser. Because
I'm in business with you. I don't want that shit. I'm a complete double crosser.
Don't say that. You're not a double crosser.
Yep. And well, how do you know I'm telling the truth? How do you know that
my double agent status is even... Who would you be a double agent for, man?
Probably Poland. Maybe I'm spreading anti-Poland shit. There's no... You would
not be a double agent for Poland and podcasts about Lyft. That would not be...
You don't know that. We're not in any kind of conflict with any country.
We're about to be. You could be a double agent for... We're about to be the
Call of Duty five weeks of war
with Poland.
Oh, no war with you want to invade Poland. No, that's reminding me of
something that's reminding where you learn that as well. Where'd you learn
how to do that? Call of Duty five.
I learned it in Call of Duty five from playing the bad team, but the call
of Duty five is about invading Poland. I think so. I don't think so. No, I
never played. No, it's actually mostly about Japan. I just realized you're
World War Two in real life. Yes, that's what he's thinking. Yeah. Okay, so maybe we're not
going to invade Poland, but we are going to go to war with some country. I don't want
to go to war, man. We're not ready for this fucking disgusting war. We're going to go
to war with a country. We already finished the war, man. We literally appeased the Nazis
of Brooklyn. We literally lost a war. No, no, no, no. We appeased them. Yeah. I would
say that we appeased them like they appeased the Nazis. We waved a white flag and the Nazis
have taken over the trash Nazis have taken over everything. Yeah. Which in my opinion,
all Nazis are fucking trash. Holy shit. I just fucking amazing. Play Zombie Nation after that.
Say it again. In my opinion, every fucking Nazi on this planet Earth is trash to me. I
missed it so much. Yep. And it's back. We could not, I don't know why we haven't even
touched it in the five weeks of planets. I think every single... Because we're on a different
wavelength man. Yeah, but that's the best sound. That's an Earth song. That song was
was written on earth. Yeah, that's songs that were written on other planets.
Speaking of man, yeah, speaking of you guys,
this is the one to close it all out. The last song, the last OJ the alien song.
Unless,
I don't know, unless we discover a new planet, I don't know,
which we could. I guess we could. Unless there's a discovery of a new planet.
We could discover it.
Maybe there's gonna be a discovery of a new planet. You guys can't,
you can't be setting stuff up in the plan. You don't know what's in it.
You're going to disappoint everybody. There's no new plan in the plan report.
It's not right. You're setting expectations that can't be met. It's not
fair. I was supposed to maybe I guys. I think the painting is going to be a
hundred feet tall. It's actually way taller. It's way taller. Yeah, people
are going to be disappointed. Now I'm excited to see it. I was supposed to
make another song with Rupert, but Rupert was busy, so I had to make this
in under an hour before the episode. So what I further ado,
Nothing Looks The Same by OJ the Alien
Nothing looks the same.
This is a song about my dreams y'all.
He looks fucking sad.
I guess it's more like my nightmares actually.
OJ the Alien!
Old man, water bear, rabbit or hare
These the creatures in my nightmare
I tried to run but I don't know where
Damn this shit has got me scared
I once had a dream that everybody hated me
They called me names like Pooh Head and Pee Wee
They wanted me dead, tried to hit me with a piece of tree
Until I showed them the Infinity Pea
Infinity Pea brought a bountiful harvest
I planted it and they said I'm the smartest
Had a portrait done by an artist
Till they realized what I had started
The pea grew wings and started flying like crazy
I was alive, the pea ate a baby
Then it maimed a sweet old lady
Then I woke up and I was doing 80
Behind the wheel of my Flora Explorer
I rammed into an old Toyota
This all happened in Minnesota
I killed a man and his name was Dakota
Wasn't the impact, it was the fire that killed him
The car was cracked and it broke all of his limbs
It was all fucked up, it left me feeling very grim
When I drove away, it was me or him
Every single day, I still see his face
I think of his blood all over the place
And how my car was the coup de grace
I ended his life with my car from space
Wait, that was a dream? This is all okay.
Okay.
We learned.
We learned that the moon controls all nightmares.
Whoa.
When did we learn that?
And moon creatures like the werewolf or the water bear.
We learned that you can have a dream while you're driving.
But we shouldn't let the dream world control the real world.
*laughs*
When did we learn-
behind the wheel of my car is a dream and it didn't happen. Don't look up the case of
Epona Wellman from Minnesota, okay? Nothing happened. And if you're from his family and
you're listening, leave me the fuck alone. There's no reason for me to be penalized for
what happened in the dream world.
This is OJ the alien signing off.
Five weeks of planets, y'all.
Peace.
The fuck was that?
I had to make it in an hour.
What the fuck?
What the?
I mean,
why?
What did that have to do with the moon, man?
There is different kinds of lichen throat creatures that he says.
A werewolf?
A werewolf, a water bear.
A water bear is a real animal.
Microscopic.
But it's powered by the moon?
No. I guess it lives in the water so the tides could...
They found a water bear on the moon.
That's not true.
Is that true?
Look it up.
They found a creature from earth on the moon?
What the hell they stop see that shit it's small as fuck. They say I don't
know what kind of telescope they use and see this fucking bullshit. This is
I'm pissed off. You're pissed off about the song? I'm pissed off about this
song. It's about the moon is at night time. So this song is about dreams.
Yeah, no shit.
It's all about dreams? The song is about how the moon controls dreams.
Talk about that, dude, there's so much amazing shit to talk about on the
moon. First of all, the fake, the fake, the fake landing. The flag. The flag
that's on there. There's been a lot of creators, the people who you can see on
the moon, the tides, the tides man talk about any of that shit. Don't say I was
first of all one thing that did come out of this. It was good dreaming and
driving. That's good. I like that yeah. That's a good well dreaming and you
weren't even going for that. That's what I put together watching the song yeah
dreaming and driving. I'll never forget that fifth of dreams dare me to drive. I
just had a
I just had a five second dream.
I had a dream last night. I was hanging out with Taylor Swift. Really yeah, I
had a dream that I was at a party and Taylor Swift was there and I was
talking to a bunch of people and everyone kind of left and I was just me
and Taylor Swift and I was like this is really awkward. I don't want to be
talking to Taylor Swift, so I was going to try and find my fiance to be like
oh, you guys should talk.
I don't have to talk to Taylor Swift and you just talk to her man. Leave your
fiance fucking. I was having so awkwardness with Taylor Swift and we
had nothing to talk about. I was like, oh, I heard you set a record with your
latest concert or something and she's like oh yeah, that is honestly every
guy's worst nightmares being in a one on one conversation with Taylor Swift,
having no idea what she expects you to know everything about you getting
that's literally what I said. She expects everything from you and you're
just like
so I heard yeah. I guess you're really popular right now, so
really I have no I have no idea what I would even talk to that lady about
out. That's what I'm saying, but I think in the world of dreams, my dream self
we would have nothing in common. You know, the only thing the only thing that I
think that I guess we both may be Travis Kelsey. Yeah, the only thing that I
think I could maybe say, but I know that it would end the conversation
immediately is are the four chain rumors true. Are you really a beat hard? Did
you write that? She was on four chan and then she would go. She would walk
away. These these rumors, T swizzle was on four chance. That's what people
that's a claim, a claim, racial memes and shit like that. People claim that
she was on there on the random forum.
Mm-hmm.
That, why would she be on there?
I don't know.
When you're famous and you got nothing else to do, you might as well go on the internet,
I guess.
Yeah.
Why?
I guess you're fucking right.
You can't go talk about random crap with people in real life.
But why would you go on there?
You'd have to go on an image board.
Because it's completely anonymous.
But I would get, but obviously not if people found out that she was on the fucking website.
Well, she was sloppy.
Well, yeah, she was sloppy.
What'd she say?
There's evidence.
It was something about, I don't remember.
There was something she...
cats and they're like a like yeah, my cat's name or some shit. It's nothing.
It's nothing. It's not a real thing. It's not real. It's all fake. But why
do you say it then? If it was fake? I think it's a hoax, but it could be true.
That's why that's the only thing that I would want to ask her about. Let's get
into it, bro. Guys, what's the big elephant in the room with? I think that
they filmed the moon landing.
There actually is a lot of stuff. I think they filmed it, man. I think they
I filmed it, man. Yeah. I think it was more than just a bunch of images strung
together. It was actual film that they used on this ship. I don't get how that
got back into the atmosphere without completely exploding. Isn't there a
radiation plane that you can't pass?
Yep.
Yeah, but should spaceships have radiation shielding? But that doesn't
really do anything. That's a myth. That's also a myth. Yeah, I guess that
probably doesn't do anything. It doesn't do anything. It doesn't do anything at
Oh, that's all crap. Okay. Well, let's break this down, though. Okay. What are
the arguments for it being real? Because that's what I'm working on. Obviously,
there are no or no. There are some arguments. The footage is crazy. It is
crazy, crazy footage. Yeah, that's not an argument for it being real. That's
just I think that's a middle thing. Argument for it being fake is that why
haven't we gone back? Right? That's what I feel like. Okay, I get the and the
argument people always say for not going back is that they say, well, it costs a
a lot of money and we already saw it's just rocks yeah, but that's stupid
something could have happened since then yeah could have changed up there. Well,
first of all the flat you guys know I was reading about this. The flags that
they put up on the moon, they weren't like special space flags. There's normal
flag yeah they're done. So they're done yeah they're gone. We gone as fuck, so
we need to go back and put more flags up there. We should put a new flag for the
five weeks of planets flag. Yes, these days, I probably put the LGBTQIA two
plus yeah yeah flag put that probably there. You can't you can't call them
guys. No, I'm no. They put said it in such a way. I was saying me and
Patrick both thought that that's not what I was saying at all. You said it
the way you I was the way you said that into me both of our minds that
simultaneously put that banner up there. You're going to ban them. You're
going to ban them from the moon. Sure, who cares you want to ban her days
from the moon. I don't care who goes to the moon. I want to ban her chaise
for shays no more. You shouldn't be able to. I agree. I agree. You shouldn't be
able to. No chocolate on the moon. No. We should have done a cheese tasting for
today's episode. Oh, my God, we're so stupid. We're so stupid. And I should
have dressed up like motherfucking Wallace. Yeah, you should have dressed up
like that. Wallace the dog. Wallace is the guy. Don't even try to start. I'll
mute you for the rest of the episode. We're not doing that again. I don't know
which is which, y'all.
I actually do know.
Okay, go ahead, talk whatever you know. No, I don't want to talk. We okay. Now
you just made me a bad. So yeah, I'm getting mad now because it's it's the
end of the five weeks of planets. Okay, and we're getting mad at me because I
got mad at your song where because yeah, I flopped and then what next is like
let me guess like your painting is like going to be digital to you already. You
already knew it was digital asshole. Yeah, you have a digital painting. You
can't even do a water. I was taller than a hundred feet. It was taller than a
hundred feet could be it because it's digital. It's not so I
mention okay. I know the song and then there's no to the painting. The
painting has no dimension. We're going out with a flop. We're not going out
with a bang. It's the end of the five guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys,
guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys,
Joe, the pressures, the lunacy, the pressure, where we're completely
where we're where we'll think not only that tunes, but I think I'm realizing
right now that this has been, I think for all three of us,
like the most fucking unbelievable experience I've ever had with this show.
Yes. You know, I think I speak for all of us when I say that. I learned music
production. This has opened our eyes to so many new things, and I think that the
fact that it's ending
is ticking us off. Alright, let's not start crying yet, 'cause we still have
half the episode to go. Okay, man. Yeah. So, here's my theory about the moon
thing. I think that the moon landing was real. They really did film it, but here's
my, my thing. I think that 2001, a space odyssey was actually filmed in space. I
agree with that. I think it's the other way around. People say that Stanley
Kubrick did the moon landing. And they were both fake. Because he knew about how
to do it from 2001. No, they were both real. Yeah. He really was on that
spaceship and he really went to the future. And he really had a computer. So
the year 2001. I believe that shit. Yeah, I believe it, too. But I think that, I
think that that was film in space. No doubt how did he do a loop de loop on
the ship and are you going to build a fake moon can rocks it's too big. What
a giant run a bunch of rocks in a sound stage. What you put I don't get is how
they got the footage of the moon landing.
They brought it back. They don't just leave it there. I thought that there
was a I guess they also trend. They did transmit it didn't they well. I guess
they had that work well. They can also can't be far away. They can transmit
their voice as well, because they can say Houston. We have a problem, so it
must not be that hard. How it must be the same as TV, I guess. Okay, here's the
so they want you to believe. Here's the argument for it being. Wow, I can't my
dad was born before humans landed on the moon. He only land on the moon. Nineteen
sixty nine. So it was my dad. Isn't that crazy that your my dad was my dad
watch that on TV, bro? My dad probably watched that to my dad. Isn't that crazy?
Oh my God, my dad was three. My dad was eight years old. It's my uncle. I bet he
I should ask him about that today. Yeah, my mom apparently she heard dad put her in front
of the TV and said even though she was like two years old, it was like you have to watch
you have to be in front of the TV for it's so funny how many and then he and then my
grandpa did the exact same thing with me with 9/11. Wow, he put me in front of the TV and
was like you got to remember this shit. My dad has to remember the moon landing because
he told me he remembered when Martin Luther King got assassinated. That was what 1968
something like that.
Yeah, I mean I guess it's true.
It is funny though putting your kid in front of the TV like that, I don't know.
Why?
Just like a stupid 60's thing.
Put him in front of the tube.
Just putting him in front of there for some kind of significant, yeah.
Here's the argument for why we didn't go back, okay?
So say 20 years ago you went and climbed Mount Everest and it was the hardest fucking shit
that you ever did right and you had all sorts of amazing Chinese food that you
never had before at the bottom of the thing right and it was great, but it's
very expensive. You're not going to do it again, but then you get a go pro for
Christmas and somebody's like why don't you go back to fucking Mount Everest and
kind of with the go pro. You get a go pro. Yeah, well here's a every no
yeah, here's what it is. You know it's because that's basically we invented the
go pro and they're like go do a go pro commercial, an apple commercial for an
eye. Yeah shot on iPhone on the moon suck on it.
but America is the only country that of where people walked on the moon. So
it's more like so here's what I think if ever you can imagine every country in
the world is brothers and sisters in a family. I like to think that yeah your
brother goes and walks. It goes and climbs Mount Everest yeah and then your
fam everyone you why does nobody else do it? Aren't you jealous? Well, your
brother be the only guy who did it because you're kind of been coasting off
the being the moon people right. Can you imagine that? I think that's it. I
I think when China lands on the moon, it's over for us. Yeah, it's absolutely over.
Well, because they're going to put cool stuff up. They're going to build some
shit up. They're going to change everything. They're going to eat a crab
up there or something. They're going to bring back moon rocks and then they're
going to use them as a source of fuel. Have you guys ever seen the fucking
spaceship part at the Air and Space Museum? No, I've never been. Maybe.
Where is that? DC. I did not go. I'm sure I saw it, but I don't remember.
their lander yeah, the lunar lander it's really small man. You know it's not. I
thought that it would be as big as a palace, but these guys they landed on the
moon as poppers yeah, it's crazy. It's really is unbelievable that you could do
that. I think I fully understand people who think we didn't land on the moon,
because how could you do that? I can't do that shit yeah, bro. I think it was a
six man think about their cars exactly. I'd be up there trying to hold my
breath. Think about the airplanes, the cars and how come every single spaceship
has looked the same since the they did not have Mario yet. No Mario was not
even invented, not even close. Nobody even had an idea of Mario in their head
at that point. Maybe they had an idea. Maybe one guy had an idea. I had an
idea. It was probably only one guy, one guy, one guy had an idea for Mario,
but then was was hit by one of those big 1960s like Chevys and was immediately
just just decimated. Yeah, well, it would have been the Japanese guy.
Okay,
so he wouldn't gotten hit by. He's saying like an alternate thing. I had an idea
from Mario and then he didn't get to you, but I was saying yeah, maybe it was
whoever who's that Jigoro Miyamoto.
Is that that's exactly who it is? I don't know. I don't know if that I know
that's just a Nintendo guy in general. I don't know if it was a different guy
from now. He made up Mario and Donkey Kong. Well, then it was him as a child.
I guess he's probably born at that point. That's an and that's an idea you have
as a kid and then you grow up and you oh yeah, you think you refine it. Yeah, I
guess I should make this thing that I drew on a piece of paper when I was
all right years old. Speaking of drawing on a piece of paper, I have to show my
painting. Okay, even though it was not drawn on a piece of paper, it was drawn
on wood. It was not drawn on wood. Stopped hyping it up in a way that I
can't. It was burned into wood. You guys are going to like this shit man and you
spend ten hours on this. I spent a long time on it. Okay, I spent a really long
time on it. Wow, so guys, this is the moon right and this is this is Caleb
that's twenty twenty three digital. Here's the moon right here and from left to right
OJ the alien Cameron Patrick me and Julio and at the very top at the very top. I love you
five weeks of planets. That's I like that font to that's so sweet. It's very like kind
of loving font. Well, it's a digital very, very futuristic font. That's what I'll find
you're going to look like in the future. True it's true as fuck, but that's us
three. It works just like I did different head shapes for me and Patrick.
First, I'm saying detail on my hair man. Yeah, the hair looks that's insane.
You're welcome to how do you do that? Dude, I'm an amazing artist. What do you
mean? That's the most impressive piece of art you've done yet. No shading on
that hair. Is it beautiful? It's great. It's wonderful painting. I mean, I
wanted to nail it. You know, it's the last painting, so I told you I spent a
of time on it man. Our eyebrows, I gave Pat his mustache. And a hat and I guess some type
of hat. It's a beanie. It looks like me. It does look like me. It's just a beanie. Julio
is kind of looking like a chip. I like how you made Julio pale and white. He's white
man. He's as white as a ghost. He's whiter than any of us and he's got his favorite hat
on. He's the whitest guy I know. And I made OJ green. Classic. Everyone's smiling. Classic
OJ green. Yep. The moon, didn't spend that much time on the moon I'm going to be honest.
which is mostly about my friends faces looks good, though it kind of looks like
a close up of a hairy ball sack. This is a
microscope
exactly like a my
germs under a microscope on a ball. So
doesn't really look like this is a this is a dead guy's balls yeah and then
yeah dude. I love you five weeks of planets. This has been the pleasure of
my professional career, ten episodes, ten episodes, episodes, a complete
mastery. Exclusively about planets. I mean, it's been amazing, guys, and I
can't wait to continue my artistic endeavours into the future, whatever,
into the future, that future. For the future planet. Whatever comes next for
us, 'cause I don't know what comes next. I don't know if there's another planet
that maybe is gonna... Cameron's the leader, he decides this kind of thing,
man. I don't know why you guys are doing this. He's the leader and... If there's
maybe an extra day of planets that could happen, maybe, who knows? Maybe for a
planet called Poonam or something who no more cent or cent or something like that
cent or never. I'm never telling you guys that I'm doing something at the end
of the episode ever again. Okay, why as you're trying so hard to put build up
false expectations? I don't know. I don't know. I literally already told you
point blank. There's no other planet in the plan about it. Think about it,
though. What if there is a planet called cent that had a moon called Poonam could
like a day because I said a instead of something,
which is how planets get name. I guess it could be somewhere. It happens with
the universe is infinite. The universe,
the first universe
we could go. It can look into that. I guess we could look into that. Do you
guys ever? I just don't want it to end. I just don't want the five weeks of
planets to end. Let's talk. Let's get real about space. This space fucking
terrify you every second you think of it.
Yes. This month has made me...
I'm fascinated by...
I think that humans, I think our brains... I was thinking about this yesterday when I
was walking my dog. I was seeing so many people and I was like, "I don't think that people
were meant to see this many people."
No, we were not meant to see this many people. I don't...
You're meant to know like 15 people.
Everything that I've learned about planets this whole month has fucked me up beyond all
repair.
I think that it's made me really happy I don't smoke weed anymore. If I was smoking weed and
doing five weeks of planets, this would be an entirely different. I'd be in the
mental hospital. Dude, I was watching a video of going inside of
Neptune and it's unbelievable. How'd they go in? They went inside? It's gas.
I mean it's... They sent a thing? No, no, no, it was like CGI. Oh, okay.
But they have... There is footage of Neptune where they fly by it and
that shit is... I mean, just any actual footage of flying by a planet is
actually so fucking crazy. I get why people want... I get why these millionaires
want to go to space. I wouldn't. I don't want to go up there, man. I want to go
there pretty badly. You know the thing where like everybody... I think that's
the... I mean to be real about it, I think that's how you have a... You
transcend. I think I agree. I would change into a completely different person.
I would shed my... I guess it would feel like the first time you do acid
in college. Was it Mr. Armstrong? Neil? Neil Armstrong that said that he thinks
that anytime somebody's elected president, they should send them up into
spaceships so that they have to see Earth from very far away.
I think, didn't SpaceX send like William Shatner up into space and he like had a nervous breakdown
in his life?
Oh yeah, he had a nervous breakdown and then, or no, it was Bezos.
He went up to space with Bezos and Bezos, like he's telling everybody like, "Jesus fucking
Christ, this is so scary."
And then Bezos is just like, "Hahaha, Captain Kirk!"
Yeah.
Really?
It's a really good clip.
It like destroyed his brain.
Yeah.
is having like a real like moment and then Bezos is just like, "Who cares?" I get that
with the backgrounds of YouTube videos. Yeah. If somebody's talking and they decide to put
a space video behind it, I'd fucking close the tab, dude. I don't want to see space.
I want to see space. I want to see the planets individually and learn about them and what
kind of creatures they are. I want to hear raps from every planet. Yeah. I don't want
to see this space shit. It's too scary. I want to go to the South Pole. I want to wear
some South Pole and be a gangsta. Is that a type of clothing? I guess it is. You don't
remember the South Pole? No. It was like a brand from the early 2000s. Coca-Cola Polar
Bear. No, no, no. South Pole. You never wore South Pole? Coca-Cola Polar Bear. Coca-Cola
Polar Bear. Yep. We got to make a new wrap. We can use that in the next wrap. We got to
make a new one. No, but I think that this final one was such a flop that we got to make
the last like when we went to the Grand Canyon, I was attacked by large.
That's why I want to go to space.
But I think it would. I think I'm right.
I would read my humanity to the brink man brought me to my knees.
It brought me to the brink is too big.
That's what I mean. Don't you want to don't you?
Wouldn't you like to seek something greater?
Hell no, no.
Find it something new.
Actually don't I don't want to but have your brain destroyed.
My brain's already been my brain wasn't destroyed by the great
of existence. I saw the Grand Canyon and I was just like, well that's nice. You're built
for space. I don't want to think about it. You're built for space, man. Well, I think
that I was making myself not think about it hard. Because it's too scary and big. Yeah.
I think I'm good at that. I think I'm good at shutting off my brain to not think about
big things. Imagine seeing space. I would come back and I would start a cult. Imagine
missing Lizzo in real life.
Celebrities have a glow to them. They do you can tell why they're famous. Once
you see him in person, some of them have been taking Adam Scott in real life and
I was like this
yeah, you bit your no, it was hot as fuck yeah. Apparently, Paul Rudd came
into my fucking wife's work again. Paul Rudd stay away from my fucking wife. I
swear to fucking God, if you ever do this shit again, I will kill you
sorry
don't bring your kids around either and make my wife think this look at my
amazing family you would plug in as a perfect step mom don't do this shit man
don't make me divorce don't make me hurt you I love wet hot American summer I
love Ant-Man don't do this is he divorced Oh speaking of Ant-Man here's a
funny here's a funny space thing okay I've been I've been reading the
Fantastic Four comics from the beginning the originals and do you guys know the
origin of the Fantastic Four yes they're all four friends and they go up into a
their spaceship together and they get blasted by cosmic rays and it mutates
them yeah and then they come down and they land and and they all get their
powers. They got and they're all like okay. We should become a team and the
human torch is like well. I can I can make myself go on fire, so I'll call
myself the human torch and then the invisible girl says well. I can turn
invisible. I guess I'll call myself the invisible girl and then the thing he's
become a mutant monster. He's like I'm not even human anymore. I guess I'll be
called the thing and then the last guy says and I'll call myself Mr.
Fantastic
and we're going to be the fantastic for wait. Wait, this is what we need to do.
We go up in space. We come back and stretch, so I guess I'll be
four of us will be fantastic for wasn't there. He wanted to be the leader so
bad. There is like a what if I think like a marvel, what if that was like if
they went up to space, but like their powers just like killed them.
that's a pretty short comic. That sounds like a boring. What is yeah?
What if someone died as soon as the story started? I don't know it's like
over a long period of time that they're like powers or like they just got like
radiation sickness or something. No, I don't remember exactly what it was, but
I think it couldn't have been that they just got it. Yeah, one there is one
and we're dead. There is one yeah. I think that might have been what it was.
I don't know. I don't really remember it that well, but we need to go up to
space, come back, become the thoughtful three. Yes, I was oh my God, yes, the
thankful three, the thankful three. What would your powers be in the thankful?
Well, I'd be I'd be Mr. Thankful
okay, and I would be a stretching ability. Oh man,
whatever I have stretch. I can't have a new power. Okay, I would have
acrobatic powers. Okay, that's pretty good and I would be Mr. Thankful. Could
I be late have laser beams? Yeah, where from where my hands, my fingers, ten
laser beams who and they come in ten fingers. That's too many ten figures,
mister ten finger finger
is good. Okay, I'll just shoot to from I'll okay. The thing I'll just do you do
this yeah just yeah you're the finger yeah, and I do this and it shoots it out
of my ring finger or it's lightning bolts yeah, and it's the shocker that
the shockers are real. I'm sure right, so the thing I would be is real. I would
I have like the like like the human torch, I would have water powers and I
would be the human drop
and that would be
the human job and I would I would turn into water. I do water guy. I'd be the
human drop. I'd be a water guy. I walk around
that's my whole power.
Basically, my power is that I give people cups of water. He's a super
still in in that doctor doom. Okay, so doctor doom comes up right, mister
thankful, I'm acrobatic, so I do a bunch of back flips to distract him and then I
finger him to death. You finger him to death and the human drop gets him wet
and what wets him. I just I put a puddle. You get him wet, you finger him and I
amaze or I could make I could just make a wave or something. I don't know. I
think, you know, the human torch can only just turn into fire. He can turn
into fire and shoot shit out of his hands fire, but the human drop can't do
the drop. You know, like when the Brita is like a little bit empty and you have
to tilt it to get the water out, that's basically what I can do with my hands. I
just do that tilt water. It just kind of falls out. It falls. I understand. Yeah,
I can mostly fill up cups. Yeah, I can mostly do the human drop filling. Is
your water need to be boiled before you drink it? Yes,
water. It is not. It is not potable. No potable. Potable. No, it's definitely
potable.
Well, it's not potable water. It's mostly like it's mostly rain water. I think you
drink rain water. You can drink rain water after you clean it. Depends on
what it hit more like river water. I feel like I think mostly what my power
would be for is helping people make ramen, helping people make tea. I can
boil it with my finger and you had a pasta and I could do a back flip in
front of them. Yeah, or I guess I could fight with it and we'd be wearing the
jumpsuits, the stretchy jumpsuits with a big three. I would I would basically be
we would be more of a Vegas act than really a super hero and we'd always just
be like we're so so thankful that everybody for supporting us. Thank you
so putting us in jail. Yes, well, he would for being criminal. I would turn
into a drop of water. I would back flip out of jail. He would escape. You would
cut the bars of every old superhero comic from the sixties always has at least like
five different issues where they are the whole plot of the issue is just that
they are going to Hollywood and starring in a movie and the director turns out
to be evil. So we would do that would be fully are the only thing for three
would only do that.
Only villains are always movie directors who are always going to star in
different movies. Well, who's that? Who's that guy who
that one director that Roman Polanski? Yeah, we go and it's Roman Polanski man
and he starts telling us he starts getting a little locker room talk with
us yeah and then we and then I
anger
that's our that's our thing. I was saying like a vendors assemble. I say
get him wet and finger him, get him wet, figure him a back flip right in front
of him.
Yeah, you wish you never fucked with the thankful three
bitch ass Roman. We have a we have a rap at the end of the movie. Yeah, yeah,
Thankful Three and I'm here to say we are the Thankful Three. I've been thinking about...
Get 'em wet in finger! We are the Thankful Three. Why is it you know all these rappers are getting
in trouble because they rapped about doing killings in their songs. How come that never
happened with Grandmaster Flash? I don't know. And that that is only a new thing. Nobody,
there was no attorney in the 80s that was like your honor Grandmaster Flash said that he was
not only not only here to say, but he was also wrapping in a thankful way and then
they put him in jail. He said that he broke glass everywhere. Exactly.
This should have been prison for life. He saw somebody peeing and didn't report it.
Straight up. I got in trouble for that as a kid. My cousin just started peeing on
his bedroom floor. My cousin just started peeing on the carpet on his
bedroom floor and then I just said stop doing that, stop doing that and then my
my aunt came downstairs, put him in time out and also put me in time out for not
telling her. Here's a what if what if the thankful three came up? What if the
way your cousin stopped that fingered him? Yeah, backflow,
wet him, finger him, back flip, wet him, finger him, back flip. Well, that's how
you stop all crime. Yeah, yeah. I mean, who's going to be able to power through
getting wetted, fingered and back flip? Oh my God, it's not Dr. Doom. It's the
it's Dr. Soon, ungrateful, all rich and he's he's not a doctor. He's not
thankful. Well, I don't think we're going to so grateful urologist.
That's a doctor. You're the urologist is a doctor, like a lot doctor doom, but
why are we going to what about us wedding him fingering him and back flipping is
going to make him? We're just called a thankful three because we're thankful
for our powers and yeah everyone support. Okay powers, but wouldn't the
wouldn't the natural enemy public? That's what we say every time we thank
you public.
Thank you mayor. Thank you. We get the key to the and now the thankful three have to comment about defeating the ungrateful urologist.
Thank you.
Thank you everybody.
Thank you everybody for watching.
Thank you for letting us put on like a little show and getting everybody wet.
And I'm all my God hundred backflips in a row.
We get to throw out the first pitch at a game.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, that would be amazing.
Wow.
But then we but then dude we turn evil.
Oh God.
Yeah, like
like Magneto thankless three thankless three or that's a villain. That is a
copycat of us, so yeah, the evil version, the thankless three and they do the toe.
They get them hot,
yeah, they faced them, the human torch, the human, the toe, they told him and
mister thank you mister front flip is very inflexible, so you can't do it
yourself all the time.
So he'd be mister front flip, not mister thankless, but he can't even do a front
front flip yeah because he has why that's his villain or is a back. It's his real
name, Mr front. Yep, it's really just kind of born with that name is front
flip yeah and it just he's really mad at his parents and he's taking it out on
the world. That's what he does try to front flip a lot, but he got in a car
accident a long time ago. Dreaming, a wheelchair, it's just a guy in a
wheelchair. It's just not pretty mad about it.
That is a villain. That's a villain and unbreakable yeah. Oh yeah, I wanted to
that movie the other day, but I feel like it might suck. No, it's fire. It's really good.
You need to stop taking these. Why? You are not built for Zen. What do you mean? You spit
them out instantly. I didn't spit it out instantly. I was in there for like 15 minutes. But yesterday
you had to leave Phil's birthday party. Yes, because I had a few. Yeah, I had a birthday
party for my dog, okay? You had to leave because you had one. I had one and yes, after a couple
I'm not. You don't need this shit. This is not good for you. You don't know that. I do
know that. I'm saying you spit it out in pain and run away from obligations. You didn't
even sing Happy Birthday to Phil. Did you guys sing when I left? Yeah, man. Yeah, dude.
You missed out on an amazing moment of reverie. Damn. And music. There was music? And revelry.
And revelry. That's what I meant to say. You need to lift my spirits with maybe a planet
report reverie is like chill bro. You don't control the planet report. That's
not your business. Yeah, stay the fuck out of that reverie is music.
There's a bunch of songs called reverie in whatever a minor that kind of thing.
I believe reverie is like sitting around being like, oh, this is amazing.
Yeah, that kind of thing. So I suppose it was reverie as well. I think it was,
but I wasn't trying to correct you. I thought that that was what I did mean
revelry. Okay. I was just adding revel rebel. They got rid of it. Revel is
gone. There's no more mopeds. Really? They're getting rid of every cool thing
in New York. No more Airbnbs. Yeah. Oh, I mean, Airbnb sucks shit. All right, let's
get back to the moon. But we don't have any... Oh, yeah, okay. Sorry. Back to the
moon. So the Thankful Three were sitting on the moon. Yeah. Oh, a werewolf would
be a good villain for the moon. Yes. For a moon-based group. So the... Yeah. Because
a werewolf would always be a werewolf on the moon. I've never thought of that
before. Because of the rays. If you sent a werewolf to the moon, it'd be a zoo.
blue. Yeah, well, no, it'd be a werewolf.
Oh, would he be wearing a suit, a space suit? You can wear a space suit.
That's cool. That's really cool. A werewolf in a... I was imagining a
were... I always thought it'd be cool to have a werewolf and he's wearing
some type of glasses where the moon is like painted on or he has some
kind of like VR headset where like he's always sees the full moon. So
we always... And if you take it off, he turns back. Like Cyclops. So wait,
it's just a picture of the moon can do it. I thought he's a physical moon rays
and it's like a real that's what I mean. It's like Vr, so it's realistic enough
yeah, is it like influence? It tricks the psychology, the rays of the moon that
makes them werewolves. You know about them full moon, you know about monsters,
it's the full moon, so even a picture could do it, though, I think it probably
the jury's out because well it's not real. I'd have to test it. Oh yeah, it's
not real, so it's no, but why is nobody? Why is Robert Rodriguez never made a
movie about about a bunch of astronauts sitting on the moon and then they
become werewolves. I'm almost certain there's a movie about werewolves on the
moon. That's that's that has to be like
probably I'm sure that a million guys who love sharknado have come up with that.
Oh yeah, I feel like they definitely want to watch that movie. Yeah, I feel
like it probably isn't good. I'm sure there's at least three movies about
that. Whatever that was just the type wasn't that nazi werewolves on the moon.
They probably did that. They definitely did nazis on the moon. I remember that
Yeah, is that where they got off to dinosaurs on? No, that is a thing.
Where did those bloody Nazis get off to? There was a million of them.
Hell, hollow, your seat, oh, hollow earth between me and Pat. Oh, God,
yeah, kill him.
The hollow earth, the hollow. I think that's one that I would really on the
hollow. I would really like to believe in the hollow earth. Yeah, it's easy to
believe in. You just have to think about it's called faith. Yeah, well, now I
believe faith is about believing, even despite evidence to the contrary.
Okay, well then I'll do it then.
Alright. I suppose. There we go.
But how do they get sunlight in the Hall of Worth?
There's another sun in the center.
You're kidding. I'm not kidding. That's the theory.
That's what they said back when they thought that was it.
Oh, the molten magma core is actually a sun.
They thought it was a sun, yeah. And then it was like
the sun was, you know, it's all like
So is everything topsy-turvy? Yeah, I think so.
Is it reverse me?
I think there's, they said there were different layers.
I think there's also a bunch of different
people had different ideas.
ideas. There's different ideas there. Yeah, it was all based on a guy who
wrote a book. There was a science fiction book and then the Nazis did a
bunch of research in it to be like, well, let's see if this is real. They
were some fools. Let's take this book and let's see if
weren't they trying to summon the devil to yeah, they were all types of strange
stuff. They also were trying to murder thousands of millions.
I did not mean to say that. Oh, my God,
millions of people. Wow yeah
Oh God,
that's an honest that's
no. If you said hundreds, if you said millions of thousands, there we go
thousands of hundreds, thousands of hours, time, a still hundreds, a
hundred thousand
hundred thousand times millions man, I'm done talking on a million, two
million, millions, millions,
kajillion okay.
Something else to stop talking about I don't want to talk about this. I made a
mistake man. I just said you should have said kajillion.
No, that's not true either. It's not true, but it's less bad. Just so
excited to jump in. I said the word murder and you went yeah thousands. I
falling ill.
I'm falling completely ill.
you're sick of what you said. I'm sick of myself for making that kind of
historical
inaccurate statement, man. I'm sick of myself. Yeah, it's just well, it's good
that you're sick. I'm glad that you're setting the record straight. Yeah, it's
not right to say things that are false about history. I agree. It's bad to
miss a historical bullshit.
That's right. You know, gingus slash gingus con whatever his name may be.
People say Genghis, people say Genghis.
Dan Carlin says Genghis.
- Genghis is crazy.
- It's cool.
It's kind of cooler.
- Yeah, a little bit.
- Genghis.
- Yeah, it is cool.
- Hey, I'm Genghis.
- I'm walking the other way.
Genghis, what are you, a plant with a face?
- Dr. Stephen Brewell style Jesus.
- Genghis.
- Yeah.
- But apparently he didn't kill as many people
as people say he did.
He was a propagandist, not unlike Donald Trump.
- Propagengist.
So he wanted people to walk around and say,
Oh Genghis Khan's killing all these people and shit and he was killing some
people sure,
wasn't that crazy back then you everybody was killing people yeah. It
really seemed like people didn't matter that much. No, no, what is that about
isn't it funny to there's way less people way less. He won't be like I just
fucking kill whatever who cares cut cut him into a trillion pieces. Let's just
do that yeah nowadays you can't even kill one guy. Go to jail. You go to jail
immediately for one for one back in the day for half of one for half of a
the fucking guy could injure somebody and go to go to jail. You can go to jail. A
guy recently went to jail for shooting other people who were trying to rob his
weed store. Oh,
doesn't seem like that big of a deal to me.
Shooting shooting it's not shooting and not even killing. I mean what he shot
him with what a BB gun right yeah, a BB gun that killed them instantly. No, I
didn't kill anyone dude. He was just shooting at him. Can you imagine you get
in front you shot somebody you killed them and you get in front of the judge
and the judges like gathering papers and he's like okay you and you shot them
with a BB gun right,
yeah,
yes, clerical air, yeah, actually, he's and then he's trying to catch you. He
says lying, you just lied, perjury, double time in jail. You guys got to
watch brawl on cell block. Ninety nine. Do you guys want to watch that tonight?
I'm now that movie's fucking fire, all right, well
give us a report. Join us. One yes, on a five week galactic. There's a big one
So this is the report not about the moon.
What the fuck are you talking about?
I'm just going to go ahead and read it starting with the title.
Five weeks a friendship report by Cameron Fetter.
Five weeks, ten episodes, the greatest experience of our lives.
We've done it all guys.
Met up on Mercury, vanquished violent varmints on Venus, made love on Mars, jumped for joy
on Jupiter, said silly stuff on Saturn, yelled yippee into Uranus or on Uranus, needed nourishment
on Neptune, partied on Pluto, sang songs in the sunshine, but as much as the sun shined,
there was one thing that shined twice as bright, and that was the three of us.
We connected with each other by dressing in outlandish yet stylish outfits.
We found points of similarity we never even considered before, our opinions on planets.
Patrick blossomed into a talented musician before our very eyes,
writing several of the catchiest songs that have ever been heard in our galaxy.
Caleb revealed his hidden art skills,
turning out some paintings that seriously belonged in the Louvre,
and some haikus that belonged in the Haiku Museum in Japan.
And I hit it big on the Powerball.
Even Julio felt the love of the Five Weeks of Planets.
He traveled to New York City all the way from his home planet of Mexico
just to talk about the solar system with us.
Our friendship is a lot like the planets.
We built it off a strong terrestrial core,
surrounded by the stormy, wild gases of mad romantic love
and blanketed in an atmosphere of normal pleasantness.
We stand strong for each other on our rotational axes.
We all orbit each other at a speed of one smile per minute.
And we all have moons, which represent our hobbies.
Well, now it's time to return to Earth after our long space journey.
I know I learned a lot, and I loved a lot too.
I can only hope everybody else did as well.
I wish the five weeks of planets could last forever, but there's a reason it can't.
because it's five weeks long. Planets for every everybody. And now it's time for the four
weeks of Christmas.
YAY!
I don't want a lot for Christmas There is just one thing I need and that's
Santa Claus will make me happy With a toy on Christmas day
[Music]
10th at the bell house with Girl God.
If you like us singing, scrap the fuck in,
because we're going to be the crier.
The choir, rather.
We are going to be actually elves.
Elves.
And that's the Five Weeks of Planets, everybody.
And get ready for the Four Weeks of Christmas.
This has been an amazing journey, you guys.
It really has changed everything.
[applause]
*singing*
I wanna take the mask off
Take it off man
*singing*
Woah
Woah man
I'll change your whole vibe up man
Alright, alright, that's the episode
A sandwich I ate the other day gave me indigestion so bad that my whole chest felt like it was
jumping out of my chest.
I feel like I can't even eat turkey ham anymore without the nitrates going into my system
and just totally bubbling me.
I feel like I got bubbles in my stomach and chest almost every day I wake up.
Walking to the train station I feel this gulp gulp gulp gulp gulp gulp.
I shouldn't be eating that turkey or that ham man or the turkey ham.
This stuff is destroying our planet.
I'm not going to eat it.
and this stuff is destroying our men and our women.
- I've developed-- - Mostly men,
men usually eat more cold cuts than women.
- On average, on average, okay.
I've developed an adult gluten allergy.
I never thought it would happen, but here I am,
close to 27 years old,
and the only bread that I can eat is sourdough.
Sourdough's good for breakfast, and it's good for sandwiches.
I can't eat Hawaiian rolls anymore.
Just the other day man I was cleaning out my humidifier, it had a heavy mineral scaling.
Mineral scales were collecting onto the humidifier's heating element.
I soaked it in a solution of vinegar and water for about 15-20 minutes and I started to scrub
it with a soft brush so as not to damage the element.
I was rinsing the brush under the sink so it wouldn't just have vinegar residue and minerals
in it.
I flicked back the bristle.
The vinegar shot straight into my eye.
And you know, when you think about how men are treated in society nowadays, every single...
The way that women make us feel is like we always have to act like Howie Mandel.
We always gotta be thinking about putting a rubber glove on our heads and doing Bobby's World impressions and talking like Gizmo.
is
Graham.
(Bowser roaring)