(upbeat music)
- Now recording.
- We're back.
- I miss Craig, man.
What happened to him?
- Yeah, I heard him for, and I haven't--
- The Discord bot that we used to use to record, man.
- And that never worked.
- Every time we do this remote shit,
which we're doing today because Cameron appears
to be stuck in a Wes Anderson movie, you guys.
- Oh, shit. - With his 4x3 ass
and the paintings on the wall behind him.
(laughing)
Did I say painting?
- Bro, I don't want-- - Those are paintings.
- I don't want my damn armchair and my bookcase
to be in my shot, man.
I cut that shit out. - Yep, yep.
You basically-- - You have to symmetricalize
your department. - There we go.
There we go, see now, oh, now he's in tangerine, y'all.
Look at him. - Damn.
Damn, now he's in fucking,
I don't even know what that would be.
Anyway, we are remote today.
Sad but true.
- I'm deathly ill.
- Cameron is falling deathly ill.
And you know why?
- We had to unlock an episode, which sucks ass.
- Yep, and now we have to do this.
There we go, now he's completely wide.
What, Pat?
- Can you hear me?
- Yeah, man.
- Okay, everything, all right.
Okay, thank God, 'cause I have to,
I'm using the Zoom H6 into my computer,
and I tried to use it for FL and it made a bunch of crazy sounds.
A while ago.
Cam, this is a much better look for you.
And you know what?
You may notice that now we're all synced up
in terms of wideness
because guys, me and Patrick are going
to the gym together, new gym buddies!
Mhm.
Snap it up, y'all.
I was on you, I got killed, man.
Cameron's falling behind because of illness.
Well, Cameron doesn't even want to get gigantic.
Gigantic what the fuck are you talking about bro? I ought to come over there and fucking kill you. What's your problem, bro?
I'm gonna get gigantic a million years before you were you're talking about bitch. You're talking about
Look at you. You're just wide you're not even trying to get gigantic bitch bitch-ass
You pulled up to the gym, and then you ran and then ran away
Bro, I pulled up to the gym and God struck me down for a little go for a run and literally the run
- Run is the thing that caused this.
- Yeah.
- See, you should have gotten under the barbell, my friend.
- Yeah, I know.
- Everything's been cured in one session under the barbell.
- Why are you doing cardio?
That's not what this is about.
It's, you're not supposed to try
and keep your heart healthy.
It's not.
You're supposed to actively fight against your heart.
- He treats the gym like a joke, y'all.
- You're supposed to actively--
- I will say, he's doing it so he can get a real lock, y'all.
- No, I'm not treating the gym like that at all.
- As someone who's worked out with Pat,
Nobody has less fun in the gym than Patrick.
(laughing)
He fucking, he is, he's the only person I've ever known
to start going to the gym and you instantly got that
by, during every set, the last couple reps,
you should be making one of the ugliest faces of all time.
You're locked in.
- No, I'm completely locked in.
I'm taking it--
- He's locked the fuck in.
- Uh-huh.
I know what's up now.
I know that, I mean, for a long time,
I have just been a guy who sits around the house and drinks beer.
Basically, I lived like Andy Kap for a long time, and I don't want to live like Andy Kap
anymore.
You don't want to live like, what's that guy, Popeye?
Burt Wimpy.
Oh, Wimpy.
Exactly.
I thought his name was Burger or something.
He likes burgers.
That's his hobby.
No, he likes burgers.
His special interest is burgers.
Are you sure his name is Wimpy?
Yeah.
His name is Wimpy.
fifty percent sure fit that the look of a muscle it doesn't matter about it fits
him very well has a big I would be no he's when people are just talking about
him as you're comparing him to someone not going to the gym is yours his name's
would be yeah and I think it was a bit perfect analogy is the literally the
perfect analogy but he just has a he looks like a burger can we admit that
yeah you want to do is we burger is out you're saying he wants his on one
- His name was Burger or Hammy or something.
But I guess it's Wimpy.
- Yeah, his name is Wimpy.
His name is Jay Wellington Wimpy.
- That's a good one.
- I have been going through life as Jay Wellington Wimpy.
I've been asking people for money for a burger.
- But now Popeye brought you to the gym, man.
- Uh-huh, that's true.
- And now you're about to turn into the guy
who's bigger than Popeye, whose name is Burger.
- There's photos of his burger.
- I think it's Ludo, bro.
You don't know any of these.
- You don't know shit about Popeye.
- Oh yeah, the girl's name is Oil.
- There's a photo of him with a mustache
that does look like me, a little bit.
- What, Popeye?
- Wimpy.
- Oh, Wimpy?
- Yeah, of course.
- I'll gladly pay you next Tuesday
for a hamburger today.
- I see your eyes moving back and forth
as you read the sentence,
"I'd gladly pay you Tuesday for a hamburger."
- I'll gladly pay you never for a hamburger right now.
What the hell, that's a terrible deal.
- I see your eyes moving like you're reading
a cute card. - Stop reading, man.
- We're doing live radio straight to the ears.
- Vintage air, wimpy, Popeye the Sailor Man,
I gotta stop looking at wimpy.
- You need to stop looking.
You need to stop looking.
Which is something he can't help himself
from doing at the gym, I've noticed that too.
- What?
- Oh yeah, makes sense.
- He looks at every single woman.
- No I don't.
- Just look, just look.
- Gets right up in front of him.
- I'm not looking at any women.
- That's how many sets they have left.
- No, I'm looking at--
- You're not looking at any women?
- I'm looking at every single old ass man
that pulls up there in a t-shirt that is way, way too long.
- Pat has some of the best gym fits so far.
He's on a legendary run.
Every single day, he pulls up in a thermal shirt
and a bathing suit.
And this is a, this is when you know somebody's serious
only about getting big, is when they are wearing--
- That's what I'm trying to do.
- Fucked up outfits possible.
And he always wears this hat.
This is his gym hat now.
yeah
was on my skating had to do
is look at how to get a crusty it is used
you know that's what i was on and that's that's came up with a mf lardman you
think that's what
that's the case
that looks like jimbo that's disgusting
i got a wash it soon but is on your head
how do you get to that point
of and i have never heard a piece of clothing that that happens to me
without me spilling a dessert onto it or jizzing into it
seeping out of your skin into the hat that it's calcified?
that is fucking disgusting man
that's crazy dude
it's a crust cap
you've never had a crust cap?
what the hell are you talking about?
so much sweat that it's turned into hard
hardness?
yeah
no I've never had that
that's just a thing that people have
wash your damn hat
I know I have to wash it soon
it soon. Why are you wearing it? No, not soon! You had to wash it soon. You shouldn't be
wearing it bro. You told us you have 40 hats. Yeah, but I'd like to wear this one to the
gym. You're not at the gym. Well, I just got back from the gym. Caleb and I went to the
gym before this. You guys didn't even text me? You are sick! You're sick, you bitch.
You're dying. You are on death's door. Wow. I know you well enough that I know that if
you even like go near a germ, you're going to sit there and just make like a dog noise.
Why are you being so mean to me? I've had the worst week of my entire life.
You're saying he doesn't want to get big, first of all. Now you're saying that he has
a dog's body.
If you think one germ could do this to me, you don't know anything about my immune system.
I don't wash my hands. I lick poop. I do a trillion things every day to get myself safe.
This is Caleb's immune system.
Caleb is sick probably.
I'm a strong motherfucker.
Caleb is probably sick.
But this season has done me in.
They're developing something new.
I've been telling, I've been.
I think the allergies are getting.
Caleb is sick nine times out of ten.
I've been spreading this gospel all, all, every time.
Man, they're developing, the new disease is gonna be in the news soon.
And I think I'm, they gave it to me because I've been calling it out.
Okay, the first one came from probably some type of lab leak.
Mm-hmm somebody was eating, but I still think it was food, but I think somebody was taking their lunch break at the lab
They ate the soup and then it got out right
Covet yeah, I don't have kovat bro. I tested. No. What is the next one coming from I'm wondering oh, it's from me
Probably still soup
It's for me and my body you think your patient zero on this I think
patient zero
I would hate it if you were patient zero of something I
I hate it if either of you is patient zero.
I would hate it because then I could live or die.
I don't care.
I could be here or die.
Well it's not about the living or dying.
Patient zero is about the crushing guilt.
Yeah, it's your fault.
Of all the millions of casualties being falling on our shoulders.
Because your one body made the disease so much worse.
You were the only...
Yeah, but I wouldn't feel bad about being patient zero for anything.
But you're the only vehicle that this disease can be transferred through.
I wouldn't feel bad.
I would feel like God is slighting me somehow.
I've been having the most insane evil fever dreams, guys, last night.
I was trying to sleep, I couldn't fall asleep because I was so freezing cold.
I haven't been able to get warm for days on end.
I have no matter what I wear or how many blankets I put on myself, I'm shivering, freezing cold.
Last night I fell asleep and I dreamed for six hours straight about playing a made up
video game.
What was in the game, man?
It was like Among Us, but it was with real people and to kill people you had to throw
them into holes.
I played it for a long time.
- That sounds fucking amazing.
- It was fun.
- It's kind of like the Mormon YouTube channel
that does Among Us in real life.
- It was crazy.
And I also had another one about bugs the other night.
It's been, I've been having a strange existence.
I'm sorry to hear that, man.
- I had a dream that I saw one of my childhood friends,
but he was the Statue of Liberty last night.
- Wait, sorry.
You saw him, you like were coming in on Ellis Island
and you saw your friend big and green.
- No, I saw him, I saw him after--
- But he was walking around as--
- He was dressed as-- - As Lady Liberty.
- Yeah, small or big? - Dressed as the
Statue of Liberty, and it might have been implied
that it was Halloween in my dream, but I don't know.
But I didn't wanna talk to him because he was dressed up
like the Statue of Liberty.
I just kinda cold-shouldered him.
- 'Cause you thought that
this was a cringe outfit. - Oh, hey, what's up?
I thought that being the Statue of Liberty was so cringe
that I just straight up just was like,
oh, good seeing you, and then walked away.
I had a dream that my favorite pair of pants went missing.
No!
Which was more of a nightmare, I think,
than anything else.
That's horrible. God damn it!
It was really, really, really bad.
I'm sorry that you're feeling bad, Cameron.
You know what we can do with this episode, man?
I need healing prayers.
Here's what we need, okay?
We're already doing remote, right?
We're all at our homes.
Look at Pat's home, looks wonderfully decorated.
This needs to be the audio equivalent
of cuddling up in a big blanket
with a big glass of hot tea,
a big mug of hot tea with honey, lemon, ginger.
- Ginger, turmeric. - Yes, all sorts of things.
Medicinal, cozy, this is what we're doing this episode.
- Cayenne pepper.
- No, not cayenne pepper.
I think that would make you sneeze.
no it's not is that some of the impurities of the not if you drink it
guys
let's talk about grant that dot o
it's going to work
how did it go to the woke empire has seized it and first of all under their
leather high-heeled okay
okay i i i i i think that you have a lot of it is that why and use it much as a
mother
and by the way you zoom up and uh...
the boot is worn by a hairy man's leg actually a hairy woman's leg
And are people saying it's woke because it's got black women in it is it woke to be a dominatrix
No, is why I think that's the opposite of BD BDSM woke
I think that is not pain is BDSM woke wokey. You're afraid of pain. I think it is woke
How's I think I don't know? I'm just letting the feeling that it's woke
I think what he's loved that crap is it like how woke ease hate they hate beautiful strippers
but they love fatty burlesques. They love Miss Andrie. And Polly Emery. Yeah. So GTA,
you play as a woke burlesque agent. Yeah. And you do what? You live in
Florida, so what do we know about Florida? Unwoke. One of the wokest places in the
country. One of the wokest places in the world. No, no, no. Yeah, one of the wokest places in the world. It's so woke that
transgender people get their own bathroom that's how woke it is in
Florida man that's interesting I didn't know that I thought that Ron DeSantis
ruled that with an iron fist Ron DeSantis is woke bro he's woke man he's
woke yeah literally a Santa in his name yeah did he become woke it's woke
Christmas is woke as well now Ron DeSantis just became woke I'm reading
that right now. Stop reading! Oh my god yeah yeah you guys I just saw a photo of Ron DeSantis
wearing a mask. No. Uh huh. Wait my ass hearing that and being like wait why do I hate masks
now? Yes. My ass hearing that and being like why am I never gonna wear a mask again? I
I had to wear a mask, I felt so woke the other day.
Guys, the car troubles continue for Caleb.
- Yeah.
- I don't know if I, did I say this already?
I went to go fucking, I went to go replace
the side view mirror on my car,
which has no license plate and is sitting
in a parking lot behind the post office.
And I went to go fix the mirror
and the entire car was filled with green mold
all over every seat.
He told us that.
Yeah, I don't know if he said it on the show, but.
So then I went and I wore a mask to go fix it, and this is the wokest I've felt in my
entire life.
You gotta wear a mask to clean mold.
It's woke.
I know, so this is also woke now.
So now everything, even growths are woke.
Spores can become woke.
Even your car, your car has become woke.
Exactly, now I'm not supposed to wear a mask.
GTA well guess what a GTA is theft auto grand grandly stolen your car mold has
green woke mold has stolen your car green haired woke yeah green haired woke mold
is completely stolen your car from you it's true and now it's making me wear a
mask. Green haired woke mold has grown over all my dishes in the sink. Even my fucking car is woke.
- The kitchen has gone woke because my wife
will not wash my dishes.
The woman won't wash the dishes, the kitchen goes woke.
- The Thanksgiving leftovers have gone completely woke
in my pantry where I drunkenly put them up.
(laughing)
On Thanksgiving night, my mac and cheese has green hair
and it stares at me.
And it makes me sick to even eat this mac and cheese.
- But guys, can I tell you the truth?
I think that God is punishing me deeply and I think the reason is because he wants to
take me out of commission because I'm one of the number one soldiers of Christmas and
in this woke world even God doesn't want Christmas to be around anymore.
So that's the truth man.
Has God gone woke?
God has gone woke first of all, second of all, we don't know.
We have zero contact with God.
He's abandoned us.
But here's the truth.
God has abandoned us, yes.
We were obviously we had giant Christmas plans for this week. Yeah for the show. Four weeks
of Christmas. We literally ended the last thing we have. And now one week is obliterated.
Literally a week of Christmas is destroyed. By some woke mind virus that Cameron has got.
I got the virus. The woke virus. I don't even know if there's going to be a week two. I
got AIDS bro. I mean I didn't get AIDS but. They gave Cameron HIV/AIDS one of the most
Horrifically killing diseases that ever has walked the face of the planet Earth. Well, you just make sure you're out of your eyeballs
That you just take 1 million pills and it's cured
I'm taking them 1 million pills of cereal every morning for breakfast
Cereal is pills cereal is a box of pills. Yeah, and it's been healing me pretty well you guys
Can I tell you the actual truth? That's actually the truth that but what I said was also true, but this is also yeah
We're true. Yeah, tell me that's I
since start hitting record and since sitting down with you guys I genuinely
feel better than I felt in days on end. Yeah. You see this is literally healing
me in real time. It's because of the friendship. It's the friendship and it's
the idea that Christmas isn't ruined. We're giving you we're giving you the
gift. And it's honestly shitting on woke too. Yeah. That also. Shitting on woke. Shitting on woke is the gift that keeps on giving.
that keeps on giving.
- Shitting on woke is the greatest medicine, they say.
- Laughter.
- It's the gift that never fails.
- Laughter in the face of woke.
- It's the gift you give somebody that has everything.
- So now that you two are getting a gem.
- I got you shitting on woke this year.
- Oh baby!
- I don't know what to get my dad, man.
I got him a Blu-ray of the Godfather trilogy already.
(laughing)
I got him a Blu-ray player the next year so he could watch it because he didn't have a
Blu-ray player.
God, I'm out of ideas.
I don't know what to do.
Fuck, I guess I'll get him shitting on woke this year.
I don't know if my dad would like that or not.
I can't tell if my dad...
I'm too scared to ask.
My dad is the one elderly person in my life that I really don't want to know his political
opinions about anything.
Yeah.
You know, I feel like...
At least your dad doesn't talk to you about the...
You know who my dad hates the most?
Who?
besides Donald Trump, probably Donald Trump the most you know who else, George
Santos. Wow that's an interesting combination. He despises George Santos. I love George Santos.
I love George Santos too. Hey, give us all that money. Isn't that crazy that you can't
even, when you hit a certain age you can't even appreciate a guy like
George Santos anymore. Yeah. All you can think about is taxes. The only thing
that, the only thing my dad has ever done that has clued me into his political
ideology at all is that one time I told you this before that one time for
Halloween he dressed up as Caitlyn Jenner on a box of Wheaties and that's it
that's the only political thing he's ever done the only like statement he's
ever made and well it's not so little it's on Halloween well yeah and also I
asked him about it he was like I was like why did you do that he was like I
was just funny so even that he didn't really seem all that gung-ho about it
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I don't know. I think my there's definitely some a branch of my
family that's pretty anti-woke that I could probably get shitting on woke for
Christmas. Yeah, I could get my whole family besides my siblings probably the
roast of woke. The roast of woke on DVD. Probably the most probably I could get that for
every single one of my aunts, uncles, parents. Wait, we should make that. The roast of
I could get the roast of woke.
I'm selling on DVD for as a Christmas man.
And release a Christmas gift guide.
I could give that to them.
The only problem is that...
I guess I have a big family so
probably I would say maybe the majority of my family
I could probably get the roast of woke for Christmas.
Oh yeah, not my Aunt Joanne.
Not the ones I interact with very much.
Not my Aunt Joanne. She would probably
be at the roast of woke protesting.
But isn't a roast...
Protesting the roast?
- Yeah, so the roast of the roast of woke almost.
- But isn't a roast supposed to be the roasting?
- Don't you love, at the end of your roast don't you say,
"Also I love you so much."
- This isn't the roast, but listen woke,
all that stuff aside, we love you man.
(laughing)
- You're so important to our society.
- Not.
- Would we need to get somebody to actually sit in and--
- Adam Carolla is the host.
but we need somebody to sit and be woke.
- Oh, JVN.
- Oh, perfect.
- That's not bad. - That's perfect.
Yeah, JVN would be great.
- I think they would walk out immediately, though.
- Or woke Patrick Doran.
- They would woke out.
- Look, I'll bite the bullet.
I'll bite the bullet.
I'll put on a blue wig.
- Dude, I'd sit there. - Anything for a paycheck.
I'd be woke for the Roast of Woke.
- Wait, what is he doing?
- He's going to take his clothes off.
- Do we have an SJW wig?
We have a Karen wig, I think.
So that's going to be the opposite. That's part of the dais, the Karen.
The Karen is obviously going to roast you.
Karen is an anti-woke warrior.
Yeah.
So this wig is not going to work at all.
I know he's right next to the wig.
Until I organize the wigs.
Yeah, okay.
Alright, so I'm going to explain to this...
Pat, Pat, this is not wokeness, man. This is a Karen wig.
No, this isn't a Karen. This is a...
This is a woman with a male haircut.
Which is woke.
- But it's the wrong color, blood.
- No, okay, can I, I don't have a webcam.
Actually I do, hold up.
I'm gonna change the color right now, okay?
- Okay. - And then you'll see.
- And then we could do,
- Whoa. - Okay, so that's red.
That's more. - Oh my God.
- Red skin, I mean completely purple skin
could also be part of wokeness.
And piercing blue eyes and a black shirt.
- This is looking, I guess, a little woke.
- If this person-- - I am woke!
I wish I had a voice changer.
- If this person walked down the street,
I would probably assume they were woke.
I'm gonna be honest.
- This is a full body tattoo?
- A full of redness. - Of red.
And black eyes except for blue pupils.
- Blue contact lenses?
They call them contact lenses because of eye contact?
- Yes.
- I think so.
Okay, if someone walked down the street
with red skin and blue teeth,
I probably would say that is certainly a woke warrior.
Yeah, that is really a scary,
wokey walking down the street and blue eyebrows.
See, on the other hand,
this is God's most anti-woke man of all time.
It really is.
Yeah, you need to stop scaring me, Pat.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Well, I don't know.
Oh, there we go.
- Yeah, now it's normal.
- Yeah.
Did I tell you, speaking of parents' political beliefs,
Did I tell you, maybe I shouldn't say this, but--
- Let it fly, dude, it's a premium.
- All right, yeah, whatever.
My mom likes to send me funny-ass memes from facebook.com.
And we might have been hanging out
when I got this text, Cameron.
I think I might have shown you this.
But my mother sent me, it was a picture of,
okay, my webcam's frozen.
My mother sends me a funny-ass Nicolas Cage Photoshop meme,
right? - Yes.
- And it is Nicolas Cage as Prince,
and it says Prince, right?
So then I open up the screenshot,
look up a little bit, look at the page that it's posted to.
The page was called Transvestigations 2.0.
(laughing)
and i asked her
what she was doing in that group
and she told me i don't know my friend shared it it's not i didn't join that
group it's not a fact it was on my feet and believe it
i don't believe her at all i think that my mom has might have become a
transvesta gator
and the funniest part about that to me is the guy
who posted that i mean it's nicolas cages like the first prince album so it's like
nick cage with like a long hair yeah long womanly hair great okay so there's no way
that a guy
did that all of the guy posted in the group like
all my god
my transvestite gator homies need this laugh right now we are fighting the
clear fighting this war
and we need to work we need a good laugh
check this out we gotta raise morale where we are a spiral here's a nicolas
cage me
from fucking two thousand eleven
or you know maybe maybe he's trying to maybe was trying to uncover some truth
there
maybe use cage yeah well yeah that means a lot of class cage and nicholas cage is
uh... true is
actually a female
who is disguised herself as a male
to make it in hollywood right and that's when it was case goes in every day and
movie to put it in the donor throats
to push the trans agenda why else would you go in that many movies unless you
had a little bit of political escape she wants to put all men in the chastity
cages so that we can't reproduce
and that every single and every single man becomes the masculine aid
and uh... national treasure more like national treason
yeah and against our society
and systems
Fast times at Ridgemont High more like fast guys
turn into fast guys, girls into guys.
- 'Cause you're fasting the guys into girls.
- Into girls and guys.
- Girls don't eat as much as guys do.
- Fast guys into girls, guys.
- Yeah, so that makes not that much sense.
- No.
Raising Arizona more like transing all the men,
all those old and all the while the sons of the world yet
there we go away i got it national treasure more like irrational pleasures
movement yeah
how do they use it
and vampires case more like trans all the kids
wall
a wall
the and i
bearable weight
of massive jugs of masculine oh yeah there we go because you got them put on
yeah that works uh ghost rider hmm
go go go girls guys they're girls guys
the girls guys yeah the girls geyser
there could be a squirting movie yeah girls into guys
Gone in 60 seconds. Yeah, what's that about? Men's genitalia?
It takes really quick.
It's actually really quick and easy. It's actually not really a big deal and it goes right back on too.
Yeah, it's like a piece of Lego. Yeah.
I wish that, I think that we'll get to that point soon where we can hot swap everything.
Yeah.
pretty soon. Yeah, pretty. We're gonna get there. We're getting there basically instantaneously.
Let's see. It's crazy that there's like, like those trans, the transvestigation thing
110% started with the Michelle Obama rumors, right? Rumors is a strong word for truth.
Or a weak word. It's a strong word. Or a strong, yeah, a weak word. No. For truth.
- Rumors is a weaker word for truth.
- Rumors is a fleet word for music.
- No, I think rumors is, I think that made sense.
- Well, no, I know, I'm just kind of building off of it.
It's more like in the direction,
rumors kind of less truthful than a truth,
which you would imagine would be, might be weaker.
- I guess you're, oh, I mean,
so you're thinking more of like a really good t-shirt
that would say like rumors are a strong word for truth.
Like a sentence in a novel.
Rumors are a weak replacement for the truth.
That would work really well.
That could be good, yeah.
But yeah, Michelle Obama definitely is a man.
Yeah.
That's why she was putting food in schools
that have a lot of testosterone.
What woman on earth would marry Barack Obama?
Exactly, he's disgusting.
He's actually hot.
Yeah, he looks good.
I'm gonna be fuckin' honest.
You guys know he's a war criminal, right?
Yeah.
Wait, what do you mean?
That's what makes him kind of bad though.
Apparently he uses drones to blow up, basically,
I guess, apparently it's either children
in one of these countries.
I use fucking drones to record soccer games.
Yeah. Who cares?
You know who else uses drones?
I use drones.
Who? The Queen Bee of the hive.
Yeah, what, so the Queen Bee is some kind of
serial monster?
No.
I don't fuck with the Queen Bee.
- Have you guys watched any of this lady who,
she went on Rogan like maybe six months ago,
but her whole thing is that she's like a bee expert
and she makes videos where she like moves colonies of hives
from wherever to wherever.
- I've seen the mushroom guy.
- But there's a bunch of guys who do this online,
but it's clear that Rogan just had her on
'cause she's like crazy hot
and he just wants to like talk to her
and then as she's,
and you can tell he gets a little bit bored
of the bee stuff like 90 minutes in.
(laughing)
And she just keeps talking about how the bees work.
And he's like, "Oh, okay, so where are you from?"
- Oh.
- Does he put his arm around her?
Like fear factor style?
- Well, she sits on his--
- It's the first time in Rogan history
that he sat on the other side of the table.
- She sits on his lap.
(laughing)
- Yeah, she sits next to him.
- I don't think I've ever watched the video
for a Joe Rogan episode.
And I also don't think I've ever watched
Joe Rogan episode with a girl in it.
Why the hell has Santa not been on?
But he was fully, he was on that tip in
Fear Factor. He was all up on the ladies.
That's part of what makes it so fun to
watch. Is he still like that or does he
mellow it out?
I think he's mellowed out.
I don't think he has women on his podcast
that often.
Me and Eric talk all the time at the gym
about how funny it is that he
talks about whenever he works out.
Oh yeah.
The thing that gets him through like a
really hard rep at the gym is that he
imagines his entire, his like
wife and his daughters getting raped and the only thing that can stop it from happening
is if he does a squat.
Oh dude you never know.
They could be on a spaceship and some half alien hybrid bandit landed on the ship and
is trying to rape his entire family in the other room and the airlock button is directly
under his butt and his arms are atrophied from being in cryo sleep.
- So he's basically like squatting four points.
- Yeah, exactly.
The gravity generator is running haywire.
- Yeah.
- I mean his body weight has quadrupled.
- There's certainly--
- There's scenarios, man.
We've thought about these scenarios before.
- It's crazy that he thinks of that
'cause to get myself to work harder in the gym,
I think about Joe Rogan getting assaulted.
(laughing)
- And me having to stop it.
- Yeah, and not being the only one who can stop it.
- I'm in the gym lifting,
I'm thinking I need to get strong enough to kill Joe Rogan's wife.
I need to get strong enough so that Rogan is never put in that position again.
So that aliens use me instead of him.
Yeah.
I squat so much that my butt becomes huge and then every single alien is just like, "Well,
we gotta probe that one."
That would be a really bad accidentally saying like, "Yeah, me too, man."
he explained that to you. I imagine my wife and daughter's getting attacked. Yeah, me
too. Yeah, dude, I imagine your wife and daughter
getting attacked as well. Oh, fuck. I fucked it up with Rogan. Oh, shit.
Yeah. He's never going to have me back on to promote
my peanut butter. Telling him to keep the peanut butter.
To the movie theater ticket taker. Yeah. Just zoning out on Rogan. He says that shit.
You're like, "Oh, yeah, me too." Can you imagine my wife getting raped?
No, no, no, no. I imagine you getting attacked, bro. I imagine you getting attacked and I have
to stop you. Alright guys, this has been a bit long. This is our first 30 minute episode
of Joe Rogan. Dude, Joe Rogan starts talking about that 5 minutes into the episode. I do
think I would have a hard time paying attention for that long to do one of those things. I
I can't believe he does that for two hours.
It's fucking crazy.
- I'd start playing with the table.
- Dude, I'd be playing with his foot under the table.
You kidding me?
I'd be sitting there, taking my shoe off, rubbing his toes.
- I'd be trying to flip the interview on him.
- Dude, I got those Betty Boop socks
that each toe got a finger-like type thing.
I got fingerless socks on and I'm rubbing his feet
with my toes under the table.
- The table's too big now.
It's too big now?
- He made the table bigger because Mike Tyson scared him.
(laughing)
It's true.
The table used to be like three feet across
and they made it like seven feet across because--
- What, did Mike Tyson try to like fight him?
- Not even a little bit.
He just said that Mike Tyson was sitting across from him
and he was like, "I'm way too close to Mike Tyson
"and I'm really scared of him."
- Oh my God.
Yeah, but then like what, he's had like
fucking Edward Snowden on after that.
Like all these like--
through edward all the other will mother fucking kill your ass
and through the power of information
yeah a lot of people don't answer them
he's a a cyber assassin
they got that word snowed in still alive
yet was his address and can i get 'em
i believe he's a little bit of a road some he ruined everything for us
i know i don't want to know about it that's if that
the phone is on the
care and i don't care about we know bro
We know. I know my phone is weird.
I know it. Leave it alone, man.
I wanna be playing on miniclip.com
and know that it's taking my RuneScape password
and not care.
Yeah, man, we don't need Edward Snowden
to know about this shit, man.
I text my girlfriend and say,
"I'm gonna poop right now, I'm pooping,"
and then I get five Instagram ads for toilet paper.
It's obvious.
Yeah, they couldn't make it more obvious, man.
Pat, have you started getting gym ads
or like work stuff?
No, not yet?
No.
Then you're not going hard enough.
What do you mean I'm not going hard?
I just don't talk about it in front of my phone.
Talk about it right now.
Take your phone.
We have talked about it right now.
You should be getting it from your credit card.
Bro, I have been--
They should have, if you signed up,
they should be getting you, man.
I have been eating so crazy.
Pat's been getting into protein, guys.
Bro, I have been eating--
That's the other thing.
He's been going after it with the diet,
also more than anybody I've ever seen.
He pulls up to the gym, he's eating 70 grams of protein
before he goes to the gym.
Completely arbitrary number he just decided
he wants to hit every day.
- It was easy.
- I never told him to do this.
- Is that too little?
- No, it's more than enough.
- Okay.
- For one meal.
- Well, that's 'cause it's just,
I just did the math the first time I ever did it
and then it felt good.
- What math? - And I was like, okay.
Well, I had the one protein bar that was 30 grams
and then the protein shake was 40.
And I was like, oh, I feel really good right now,
so I should just do this every day.
- Yeah, just get it in the-- - Every single time
I go to the gym.
- Fuck it, whatever works for you, bro.
But now that you two are both in the gym,
we have to decide which one of us
is gonna start using gear first, I think.
- I have the strongest liver out of all of us.
- I would say that you probably have the weakest liver
out of all of us.
- What are you talking about?
- It's been abused the most.
- Years. - That doesn't mean
it gets strong.
- Livers don't get experience points.
They don't level up.
- Yeah, they don't get better with drinking.
- Oh, I have an iron liver.
- My liver. - No, man,
it's like a sponge.
It's like a kitchen sponge.
- Your liver's definitely insanely fatty and--
- No, I got that tested last time I went to the doctor.
- At 26, you got your liver tested?
- That probably means there's nothing
to worry about. I thought that I thought that that's what the blood work was but I'm realizing
I'm just lying. I'm just lying to get on steroids. They have to give you they have to like do
imaging or something. It's like stick a camera up you or some shit. Well I don't have like
a fucking. Have you seen that photo of Bert Kreischer where you can see his liver through
his belly. That's OK. He looks good man he lost a bunch of weight. Yeah. Why do you think
- Why did he, bro, why did he take that photo with the towel?
That was so fucked.
- I've been meaning to say this for a little bit.
- I get he's trying to show his V-lines or whatever, but.
- Guys, if you are losing weight
and you want to take progress photos,
I do not need to see your trunk, man.
Keep the trunk back in your draws.
I do not want to see your fucking trunk.
Get that shit out of here.
- People get so excited about the trunk, man.
- I don't wanna see it, man.
No one likes the trunk.
The trunk is...
Nobody's getting into the trunk, dude.
The only thing people like is the arms and the chest.
Yeah, I don't need to see the top of the thing.
The only people who like the trunk
is a really scary gay guy who attacks your life online.
Yeah, exactly.
And who wants to get to the...
They wanna get to the bottom of this.
I'm gonna get to the bottom of that.
They wanna get to that root.
They wanna get to the root.
I don't wanna see that shit, personally.
This is the only guy, the only type of person who likes the trunk is the gay guy who also
would think it was really hot if you posted a picture of all the veins in your body.
Yeah.
If you somehow posted an x-ray of every vein.
Yeah, a body's ears, man.
They would go, "Oh my god."
A circulatory system.
Just your spine and all.
Just your whole Dr. Manhattan eyeballs and circulatory system.
They would go, "Oh my god."
Everybody else doesn't want to see that shit, man.
It's anatomical, bro.
Those are like the gay guys that are obsessed with the gay guy.
Would you post a picture of your body?
Yeah.
I would.
It's a ball hanging out of your Patagonia baggies. I don't think so
Yeah, that is funny, but those are the type of gay guys that are obsessed with us
It's crazy. Those are the gay guys that ask us for like armpit pictures and stuff you get armpit asks
I don't know anything man. Nobody likes me. I like you know
I'd see your one of the few trunks. I'd like to investigate show it show us
I just it's not doing well right now. I'm unhealthy on dude. It's discolored. It has good days and bad days for sure
Today
Yeah, you got a bright purple trunk now. It looks like you've been like it looks I bet it looks horrible right now
I bet it's like photo of Jerry Su after he took that butt slam what who's that?
And is this does that mean? Oh
One or two listeners will know
Okay, it's a skating thing sometimes. I only speak for the listener
You should always be doing that yeah
Well, where are you guys you're entering another dimension?
No, I'm just good. He's got Jim. You're looking down into the corner of your eyes like a cartoon
I'm looking at you guys in the camera
Look at you guys on my screen. Okay, all right that makes a little more sense. Yeah
But I think that I've now gotten
Five people in the gym and for each and every one of them. It's changed their entire. It's so funny
I was talking to patches about this to be fully in there. I've been I've been really happy doing all the running this past year
I'm ready to stop with the damn running and do some better stuff
I was talking to patches about this the second you put Caleb in charge of something. He becomes like Scoutmaster
It's like your leader, man. I don't know it's you you built his PC with him
and he was like, yeah, I got him because I asked him
how to do it because I know that he would like
tell me exactly everything that I have to do,
which is why I started going to the gym with you
like day one, you were like, so this is called this
and what you're gonna wanna do is this, this and this.
- I was teaching him about eccentric
and concentric movement.
Dude, the thing is, man, I don't know what to do there.
I don't know what to do there.
I just have to sit there and listen to what you say
and then I'll just be a little worker drone
until I become gigantic.
- Exactly, man, you follow everything that I have to say.
I just think I'd be an amazing dictator.
I'm just good at giving people complete orders
and especially in one-on-one situations,
I think I could definitely become a personal trainer.
I'd love to be, there's a, oh dude,
you haven't seen him yet. - Dude, I'll be, oh my God,
I'll be your first, I'll be your first example
that you can use.
- Yes, you'll go on all the brochures.
There's a guy at our gym, you haven't met him yet.
His name is Bluebeard because he--
- Oh, you were telling me about Bluebeard!
- Dude, Bluebeard is a fucking legend.
He's this like, kinda fatter, older guy
who has completely blue hair and a giant blue beard,
like blueberry blue, like as blue as,
like it has, it's probably hours to his--
- Can I say something without everyone getting mad?
- What? - He's kinda sounding
kinda woke to me.
- Dude, he looks woke, but then you hear
the way that he talks to these guys,
he trains. He's a trainer and he's training like bodybuilders, like giant guys. And at
first I thought that he was some kind of freak, weirdo, wokey, SJW.
A guy with blue beard? You thought he was weird?
But it turns out this guy knows way more about working out than I could ever know. And we
have to hire him to train you, dude.
This would be an amazing training partner for you.
I mean, I want to look like a 1920s strong man at this point in my life.
You want to get that, the curled wrist fighting look?
I want to hold a barbell with my finger.
Oh yeah, one of the ones that has the big ball weights on either side.
And it's a bend-in.
I want to do this.
And have a big barbell right there.
You want to look like the gold gym logo.
Yep.
That's what I'm trying, that's what's going to happen for me in the next year.
I don't care about any of that. I just want to be a monster. I
Like what I'm saying?
All these guys you want to know we're not going for health
I'm not trying to be skinny at all
100 fuck you
I truly would just like to gain some weight for the first time in my entire life besides growing from a baby
Cameron if you wanted to gain weight you could have come to my weight gaining classes
Oh, you're saying come to growing up from the time you're a baby
I thought you were implying that you had been pregnant before and you got wife off of that
I don't remember what I said one second ago, so I can't remember you said growing from a baby
Yeah, I grew from a baby. Yeah like a plant grows from a seed
Yeah, or a guy grows out of a baby or grows from it's not
From Cameron what here okay listen, and I don't think I've gained weight since no no no no
I'm about to put you on to something.
Okay.
Two words, three words.
- Okay.
- Okay, I'm getting excited.
- Social.
- Ice cream soup.
Social, four words.
- I have ice cream every once in a while.
- You're gonna have an ice cream soup.
Uh-uh, you're gonna eat ice cream soup every single day.
You're gonna melt down that ice cream in your microwave
until it gets completely melted
and it's a little bit hot, kind of bubbling,
kind of looking like clam chowder,
you're gonna eat two bowls of that with every single meal.
- It's true, people do this to gain weight.
Why is it that we've lived in New York
for years and years? - Ice cream soup
plus Taco Bell fat fucking idiot meals.
- That's how Mac got fat on always sunny men.
- You need to eat, it's a T10 combo,
so that's two tacos plus a gordita
plus a Crunchwrap Supreme. - It's too much money
- I'm trying to gain weight, man.
I wanna spend $10 on food a week.
I'm not about this shit, man.
- He is the cereal and sandwich man, dude.
- Yeah.
- You and me, we like decadent dinners.
- I don't fuck with meals.
- He doesn't like these giant expensive meals like you and me.
- You know what I made last night?
- I do like it, but I just can't, I can't make it work, man.
- Roasted delicata squash with pistachios and goat cheese.
- Roasted Dan Licata squash?
(laughing)
- It does sound like his name.
- Sounds good as hell.
I love that. I roasted Dan Licata for dinner. That does sound, I've never... I could see
him all bundled up. Roast like a turkey. Roast up with the twine or whatever it is when you
get a rotisserie chicken. Just this most scared face ever frozen on his face as he burned
alive in the oven. I wouldn't eat you Dan. I would never eat Dan. No. But I'd roast you.
I'd roast you man but I'd roast anybody man I'm a fucking I'm a crazy roast I'm
an equal opportunity offender yeah people always say that and they don't
seem all that equal opportunity yeah then they have that one thing that they
get really really upset at like if you made fun of Jeff Ross for dating a child
yeah if you try to roast the Roastmaster General for dating that 15 year old girl
I think me thinks that me thinks that he would put pull out the roast extinguisher
He dated a kid right I don't think it was a kid I think it was a young girl tails
I don't think it was a person of younger age
But I'm not so sure it was a child
Yeah, I don't think that's a pretty it's a pretty big accusation I don't I mean a child
Well, you know, I think it was probably a 20 year old but again, I'm just oh
- Oh, well. - Right.
- Then it is all a legend.
- But if you ask me, I don't think that Jeff,
what's his name?
- Dunham?
- No.
- Jeff Ross, man. - Jeff Ross.
I don't think that Jeff Ross should be dating anybody.
- Yeah.
- He was disgusting. - So if he's Justin 8,
- I will say I'd like to hear that dirty talk,
'cause I bet that shit's funny as hell.
- You look like a slut.
Yeah, you look like a stupid...
Your shit is, your ass looks...
What if you're dating a girl you find out
years into the relationship her ex was Jeff Ross?
That would suck.
I think that honestly,
would probably be better. That might be
one of the celebrity,
no, I'm not gonna say the only one,
that'd be exaggerating.
That would definitely be a celebrity
that like, if it had been a previous relationship
of my wife, I would not have gotten married.
Yeah, you would just think that you're
the ugliest guy of all time.
No, it's just, it's not bad at all.
It has nothing to do with,
it's just anybody who would want to date him
obviously has something completely wrong with them.
Right.
I think there's a lot of these.
It's kind of like, well, can you imagine,
what if back in the--
It's kind of like who?
What?
Who did you say it's kind of like?
Caleb?
I didn't say it was like anybody.
Oh, I thought you said it's kind of like
dating somebody specific.
No, I was gonna say it's kind of like--
It's kind of like it's kind of like Walton Goggins.
And I was like, what are you talking about?
The other one would be if somebody if my wife had dated anybody
who's Urkel, who was taller than if your Steve Urkel would have
also been a bit of a red flag.
Yeah.
Imagine how hard it would be.
How hard it would be to be dating if you were if you're alive
back in the 40s, you had dated Hitler.
Yeah. That if and then you're trying to walk if you're a girl.
Yeah, and you, well yeah, you dated Hitler.
Maybe you dated Hitler back when he was an art student.
You know, maybe he was probably still pretty nasty,
but you know, he wasn't full Hitler yet.
And then all this stuff goes down,
you're kind of trying to just live your normal life.
Yeah, and then people are asking,
you're on your first date on Hinge,
back when Hinge was in the newspaper.
And then you're on your first Hinge date,
and they're like, so what was your last relationship like?
Like, oh, it was a celebrity.
(laughing)
- You might know him.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, he was,
he had a funny mustache.
- Yeah.
- You dated Charlie Chaplin?
Oh my God.
- No.
(laughing)
- Let's just say in a long, long time,
he's gonna be in a funnily epic rap battle.
He's gonna be in a very funny, epic rap battle.
- Let's just say in a long time.
Let's just say in a very, very long, long time,
he's gonna be in the funniest epic rap battle of history.
- This is the 1940s, somebody's saying this.
- Yes, and somebody--
- And they go, oh, Hitler.
Oh, funny rap battle, yeah, it's gotta be Hitler.
- Funny epic rap battle, then you find out
that bitch from the time traveler machine.
- That bitch from the time traveler machine.
What the hell is going on with you, man?
- I think I'm winded.
i think you might actually be
i think maybe i should record after going to the gym my brain is on shit
time all my god
he said himself
fix it
haha explosively louds well i'm sorry i feel like normally i can maybe pick up
some slack here but i'd
guys there's something wrong with me
last night when i was lying in bed i had days of who of having some kind of
massive epiphany about the world from the night before that i couldn't
remember all i could think about was that
well 'cause both of them the reason i had the deja vu 'cause both times i was just
feverish lying in bed in the same position and i was it was because i
turned over onto one side and i remembered oh my god i think the night
before i was lying on my side like this and i was shivering
and i was thinking about some kind of giant
oval machine
filled with wires and cables i can't remember what it was or what it meant but
it was really i thought it was really important
you were thinking of the ooyah? i literally invented something and lived
You invented the OUYA in your head.
It was completely, no, bigger. Bigger than the OUYA.
I think that, no, if you have a fever, if you have a really high fever, at some point you invent the OUYA.
At some point you think to yourself, what if games could be streamed directly to my TV?
It was a good idea. It was before its time, I'll say that much.
Yeah.
Wasn't the point of the OUYA that all the games were like iPhone games?
Well, that was the problem.
- No, I thought that was the point of it.
- No, you want to be able to do--
- They tried to do it later with Stadia,
but none of that shit worked out,
'cause nothing is fast enough.
- And that was Google.
- Yeah, that was Google.
- And why, who even care, who wants to do that?
- I kind of want to do that.
- Why not just sit on your couch?
- Well, you kidding, that's the thing, Cameron,
you do sit on your couch when you use it.
- Yeah. - But why?
- What do you mean, but why?
- Not just have it on your game console.
- But then you have to go download
and wait and all this crap.
And it'd be nicer to just have it all streamed directly.
I had an episode last night.
- What?
- I've been painting my brick wall.
This one's white,
I've been painting the one in the living room white as well.
Finally.
And I got up on a ladder.
Have you guys been on a ladder in the last couple of years?
- Yeah.
The electrician has not been in my house for weeks,
this electrician, and he has left the ladder.
He called me two weeks ago
'cause his dad has been doing all the work.
And I guess his dad almost died from COVID.
- Okay.
- And that's why there is still a ladder
and multiple holes in the wall.
- And you get up on it every once in a while?
- Oh, good, yeah.
I get up there, I open it up, I stand on it.
It's fun.
- You had a ladder in your last apartment too.
- I also, oh yeah.
I do, oh my God.
- So last night, I got on this ladder.
- Mo likes to get up there
so I have to get on it to get him off.
- I got on this ladder and I started painting
and then I finished painting.
And I looked down and guys,
I refused to get down from this ladder for about an hour.
I sat on the ladder and I watched TV
because it felt so amazing to be that tall.
And so my new goal in life is to be nine feet tall
because I had my wife,
I refused to get off the ladder
until my wife brought me a tape measurer
and then I measured myself
and I was almost exactly nine feet in the air on my head.
- Yeah, but that's like Robert Wadlow stuff.
Like he couldn't even like--
- I think I would have really enjoyed being Robert Wadlow.
now you wouldn't have a wife
well you never have a lot to do to use to a doctor young girls like back and i
back in
robert wadlow times it with women didn't like tall guys to the eat more food
so you have to return to jobs as a woman was a little bit of zero
nowadays women like tall guys
because it woke means that women should have two to three jobs in the mention of
one
exactly and those women don't even realize that you're gonna have to be
making that much food. They think that men can just eat McDonald's every day. No! McDonald's
is a snack. That's true. It makes you more hungry I've heard because of the sugars. Yeah.
But I'm not kidding man, I really, is that what life is like for you Cameron as a person
over 6 feet tall? What? Being tall? Everything looked so small to me man. It was amazing.
- Yeah, I guess people look pretty,
you guys look pretty small.
- I was looking around and I thought I was better than,
I mean, it was only my wife in there.
- I mean, to tell you the truth,
I look in the, when it comes to tallness,
anybody who's taller than me,
and my brain is really tall,
anybody who's shorter,
I couldn't draw any distinguishment really,
unless they're insanely short.
I don't think I think about how tall I am very much.
- All I'm gonna say is you, Caleb,
you're lucky you weren't in that world's biggest army promo vid
'cause now everyone thinks i'm the shortest fucking guy in the world
'cause there's one clip where i'm in between
pierce isn't in it at all
all you can see
is me, cameron, joe and alex and i look like a baby
i look like their little brother
i look like both their uncle and their little brother simultaneously
i guess to answer your question, no i take it for granted
you clearly experience any sense of this is all the patrick ever think about is
this every single tall person takes it for when you walk by this happens i will
i will say i will say though you guys really i mean maybe
now at this phase in our lives were not taking so much public transport or
anything
there were any type of seat
in a public area is a complete nightmare just in terms of
we either leg room on a plow or a bus or something like that
or having to just be touching people on all sides because your legs are too long on the subway
and i know you're gonna go i'm okay with that but yeah it does suck and it's i'm perfectly built for
public transit i have a big ass i experience this i have time no ass and tiny ass legs but but the
upside the upside to being tall on a plane or train or a bus like on the amtrak or whatever
you can be really rude. Like people, because my body is just too big for the Amtrak seats,
if somebody tries to lean their seat back, I just start hitting their seat.
And you get to use the women's bathroom.
And I just go like, "Fuck you," and I start hitting them.
Yeah, see, that's cool, because you have a physical, basically disability on a plane or a bus.
Yeah, which is, that's, I wish I had something more, kind of, I wish that's,
I guess that's the thing everybody says.
- You wish you had a disability.
- I wish I had a new take on this height issue.
- I don't think about my height too much,
but if I was going to a really high powered
job opportunity, business opportunity,
interview style pow wow, right?
- Putting some lifts in?
- If I had, no, no, no, no.
- Or a run to San Francisco?
- I'm not doing any of that shit,
'cause that's compensating.
What I would do, or I guess that's fixing.
What I would do is there's no way
that I'm taking the train to something like that
where I need to be at my highest level of confidence
because the prospect of walking by
like a 50 year old woman who is taller than me,
which happens probably once every three days,
on my way to something like that,
that would ruin me, man.
- My first girlfriend was, - I'm taking a limo.
- My first girlfriend, like my ex was like,
- Way taller than you. - Six foot one.
- Way, way taller. - My ex was like six foot one.
- I wonder why it didn't work out, man.
- Something like that. - Don't do that shit.
That's not for us. I don't think that's why it didn't work out.
That's the only reason, man. The only thing, the only time
when you should be dating somebody who's taller than you, as a man,
you should be dating someone who's, is if you're very short and they're very tall.
There's something adorable about that. Well, I was very short compared to her. If somebody's like, if a guy's like
5'6" and his wife is like 6'2", first of all,
this guy's cock is, this guy has a absolute
Giantly fruitcake log cock mm-hmm, right
Do you guys get stuff off of shelves I have to get stuff off of shelves
Are you one time are you forced to get stuff off of shelves that you don't even when you're sitting down on the couch?
No, I would I am but here's the worst part 90% of the time. I can't reach it
So then I have to climb up on the counter
Step stool man. There was one time that I did I put something on top of the cabinets like in my in my apartment in Boston
and I did get I
Did like have to ask my ex to get it if you're tall you can hide stuff on top of cabinets
Yeah shelves that nobody will ever see can be up that you can put anything you want up there
Your own can top of on top of things. Oh
See us us five foot nine guys. We have to make a burrow in the house exactly we have to dig into the wood
Pull up a plank and Walter white all of our Reese's pieces
Into the floorboards and we don't even get to put them in like they don't even get to keep them in the bag
It has to be loose Reese's pieces under the floorboard
Yeah, exactly because the bag would make too much noise when you walk over exactly
Yeah, crinkle and then the floorboard is already making too much noise. We can't hide two noises exactly should get wise
Uh-huh. I want to have a tunnel in my house to go somewhere. I wish. I want a tunnel from my
Room to the bathroom so I don't have to walk through the living room and that's called the hallway
No, but I want it to lead
directly there I
Want to have a house where I can press button at the door and it switches to whatever room
Like you know what I mean you know it goes like yeah, and it's like it is the order of the rooms
Like in like monsters honored to I never play it builds a new room. I think that's the game
I haven't played it either, but I saw I wish that I had a big hamster water bottle next to my bed
I wish I had a big hamster
Big hamster and a cat that are connected to my I was had a hamster that was a size of a German Shepherd
Yeah, I
Said did you see I kept in a cage in my room? I never let it
Shaking the bars. I throw a blanket over it whenever I'm home because it hears me walking around.
It's trying to kill me. It hates me so much. I just drop mealworms in through the bars.
That's how you're feeding?
And I'm like, yeah, I can't get rid of it. Like, it was my uncle's pet and he died so I have to take care of it.
A disgusting hamster monster? With human eyes?
a quarter of the space in my bedroom.
- Yeah.
- I have to get rid of my bed and get a twin bed.
- I think you'd like that.
- It would be nice to be beholden to a demon.
- Yeah, I think so too.
Yeah, I think it would be nice to have--
- That's the experience of at least 50% of dog owners,
I would say.
- That's my life.
I'm beholden to a demon.
- Is what I just described.
Yeah.
- A rattling cage that any time I want to not be
want to not be babysitting something,
it just screams at me in the most agonizingly terrible,
and every time I leave, it just has actual human cries
that I swear to God he's saying,
"Stop, stop, stop, no, no, no."
- Who, Phil?
- Yeah, Phil, whenever I leave the house.
- No, no, his slave.
- No, my slave.
- Yeah, I know, that's why I was asking.
- Rupert.
- It's Rupert?
- My friend Rupert?
- Yeah.
- My friend Rupert is living in your house.
Well, guys, Christmas is coming up and the four weeks of Christmas, you know what we're
going to do? Executive decision. The four weeks of Christmas is being extended beyond Christmas.
Just to make up for this week of atheistic laugh.
I'll take some of the blame for this. I'm sorry for letting my body become weakened,
but I can tell you guys I feel better already and we're going to have Christmas fun all
month.
- Christmas is, you're not going to fucking believe
the Christmas shit we have planned.
- And I'm not letting the devil take me down this year.
- No way. - No, no, no.
- No way, no how.
- And can we do a quick prayer for you?
Just to get this out of here. - Please, I really do like it.
- Dear God. - Lay your hands up.
- Dear God. - Do I have to do it?
- No, you just need to take it. - Who art in heaven?
- Just shut up. - Hallowed be thy name.
There is a sick, sick boy in our presence.
- Sick little boy, God.
- Thank you, Jesus. - He has some kind
of rare disease that is turning him into a cube.
- Yes, Father. - And is making him stretch,
and we need him to become himself again.
We need him to turn into just the best he can be.
We need, and you can do this.
You're the one who made him sick because of his attitude.
He had a bad attitude. - Forgive him, Father.
- Forgive him for his bad attitude.
He didn't know. - Don't say I had
Attitude don't interrupt the prayer you that's clear you have a bad attitude you're interrupting a Caleb prayer
I don't want to pray anymore you take this dear God this
Poor sick stupid little boy has turned into a complete monster exercise this demon out of his body Lord in your holy name
We pray please get this demon out. We want to celebrate Christmas with our buddies in real life, please God
We have to decorate the entire office and have a Christmas party dear God
Oh, God mighty in heaven in your hallowed be thy name Jesus Christ
- Woo!
Woo!
I caught the holy ghost at the end there.
- Dude, I know how to pray, man.
I learned how to do that in school.
- Guys, that looks so scary.
- Yeah, you look like an evil goblin.
- You look like a painting. - All right, guys.
- God bless you and may Christmas start next week.
- Yep, and tomorrow night we are at the bell house
with Girl God.
- Oh, shit.
- Oh, true. - Get your tickets.
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
- And never misses. - And I have a special thing
I'm doing next week that I won't say yet.
- But you'll see it. - Okay.
Bye.
Jesus Christ, you look weird.
If you couldn't tell, we're dressed up like Venus today.
Although we had some amount of disagreement, I guess, over what color Venus is.
That's okay, I got both going on.
You do have both, but what's this black wig about, man?
Well, we'll go down.
You want me to start with my costume?
Are you dressed up as Coraline?
No.
I'm dressed up as Venus.
No, I'm just up as be any if I walked out on the street right now, any person who
knows literally who attended at first grade would know I'm just as it would be
some people.
People think that you were Coraline.
No, a first grader would look at me and say that's Venus.
No, they would a child who was into science and into movies who would have
seen movies in a movie.
Why did you say movies?
Of course, they'd say Coraline man.
Well, if it was movies around Halloween time, if they saw me in a costume like
this, they would say Venus.
They would say that's Coraline.
She's very pretty today.
No, they wouldn't say that.
They would say I like Coraline's mustache.
Jumping off of pretty here,
Venus is actually the name of
the goddess, Venus is named after the goddess
of beauty and of love.
So I elected to put on a
beautiful wig today.
To show my
beautiful hair.
Now we're asking about the yellow raincoat.
So let me explain this to you. Venus,
the color can be, some people say it's
yellow, some people say yellowish white,
Some people say beige.
This raincoat is yellow.
Definitely too yellow for Venus.
Some people at this table would say beige.
I think two people would.
Two people would say beige.
But Venus has...
It's surrounded by sulfuric clouds.
It has a sulfurous atmosphere,
which is why it's that color.
And in the upper atmosphere,
constantly acid rain.
Oh.
Wow.
Wait.
So you dressed up like Coraline
because of rain.
So that's the yellow.
It's the yellow acid rain.
And then I have a yellowish white shirt here.
Uh-huh.
This is kind of closer to the color I feel.
You're dressed up like Cora Lane.
Dude, chill. I'm dressed up as Venus.
I don't know why you guys are stuck on this.
I don't look anything like Coraline.
You pull up a picture of Coraline, it's going to look completely different from what I'm wearing right now.
I said Coraline though.
That's not, then you said a nonsense word and you're proud of that.
You're proud of making up a word.
(Laughter)
That's you, man.
I don't know what you're talking about, guys.
talking about. I didn't try to dress up like this. Oh, no, wait, no. She has
blue hair.
(Mario sound effects)