(upbeat music)
- You look nice today.
You look all dressed up for Christmas.
- I am all dressed up for Christmas.
- You have your green.
- I wore a big Christmas outfit.
- You have a green hat part on.
You have a red jacket on.
- I look like Mr. Rogers.
- You do, you have a button up shirt on.
I haven't seen you wear a button up shirt that many times.
- I haven't seen the episode right now.
This is a bad start.
what talking about your outfit? No, I think I did the thing where I drink too
much caffeine that it makes me tired. Do you know that? You know, when you do
that happens to me. Yeah. What is that about? I don't know. Why is it not
linear? You know what it was? I'm trying to write the perfect Christmas song for
Christmas and it's I know you've been ignoring me. We don't have to worry
about how much about you don't know make any excuses for the badness when we
haven't even started yet. That's true.
It's very quiet. Most quiet. Boom. Quiet. Most quiet ever made. God damn it.
That's a bomb that could kill nobody. That's an ant bomb. That was somebody
breathing in their sleep. That's what the electrician that's been in my apartment
sounds like when he breathes. Really? Have you told him about a CPAP machine?
Dude, I haven't even fucking called that guy back. You haven't talked about him
in a long time. I haven't talked about him in a long time. It's been a pretty
good string of episodes. No, I've heard a boyfriend hearing about him. But
remember how long ago it was since I last talked about him, right? Uh huh.
You talked about him yesterday. This was a job. Oh yeah, you did. But I think
You and me both just kind of ignored it as he was talking about it so that we
could just get he's supposed to install five outlets in my apartment.
We really can't do this. I swear.
We can't talk about this. I haven't talked about it on the show.
He's supposed to install five outlets in my apartment.
He almost died of COVID cause he's like 400 pounds and 69 years old
and he can't install it without bending over and doing this.
When he's in my apartment, it sounds like this.
- Nothing. - It's silence.
- You hear-- - Dead silence.
- You hear like a drill going into the wall.
(imitates drill)
From his body.
- That's one breath he makes?
- Yeah. - That's an exploding--
- And then his son is watching TikToks
on our front stoop.
- I know. - And he gets paid.
- I know.
- And he gets paid.
- And that's the electrician's corner.
- Guys, I've made a terrible mistake.
- What happened?
- Maybe a marriage destroying mistake.
- Oh no. - Yeah, last night.
- What happened?
- Me and my wife have decided to start doing
a budget right to do it's that season man. It's that season on the budget,
too, and it's been ruining my not good dude. It's not
not good. The moment you realize how much money you actually yeah and your
wife makes you've actually double the amount of money. It's still not that
much money,
and then and then she's like is this really how much money you make and I go
yeah, but we have an office
I actually seeing the exact number of money I'm putting into savings every
month. Yes,
sorry, more than two digits sometimes
only sometime yeah, but I last night we did we went over this budget spent
hours doing this yeah. We set up a joint bank account took us weeks. We
finally got it. We're doing got a man together had to go to had to go to Bank
of America, set up the joint bank account, had to do it took days. I'm
going to need your advice on this, because we have no idea how to do. He
said that this is marriage ending. I don't think you need his advice. I know
he's getting he's working up to the mistake making them. I made the mistake
okay, so last night, so we set up the entire thing right and then and and in
my checking account, not that much money, but we agreed that like our joint
checking account is going to be groceries and yeah like yeah, stuff that
will both do right so last night
she goes to bed and I stay up so I can do the dishes like a good guy right yeah
And I'm sitting there and I'm watching YouTube videos and I get this ad, man.
I get this ad for something called Alpine Butcher that sells A5--
Oh, no.
Oh, wait, no, I know.
Yes, you were saying you were going to buy it last night after the gym.
Oh, my God.
Did you put it on the fucking joint bank account?
I accidentally bought it with the joint bank account card, A5, marbling score 12, Wagyu,
New York Street Steak.
is a hundred and thirty dollars
and for one
you go to fucking Costco, go anywhere,
go anywhere, but buying a
line. There's butcher shops all over. How the fuck are you buying
something off a YouTube ad? What I'm
with you?
That's that's a dude that's like swiping up on an Instagram ad and by
sweat pants. What are you talking about? It's a built in that it's a
built in a
for that's in the video of the creator that I like. Oh, it's the one where he
says he says click the link in the description. You butter yeah, and I
use by it off a Guga
did you get Warby Parker to
maybe
maybe anyway, if you get five percent off, I have not told her and I'm not
going to until she takes one bite of the
as the stake is in her mouth, I'm going to say you better not fuck it up dude.
I'm going to be the rarest. I'm going to be the medium. Well, you got to cook
that shit rare as hell. That's going to be the juiciest medium. Well, fuck you
and
well and slow fuck brother. I'm going to send you this put in the tray, this
steak in a manila envelope. Yeah, you're going to get it. It's going to be a
five wag you media. I don't know. I'm going to leave you right. I immediately
even an email. It was like I'd like to cancel my order and they were like we
don't cancel orders because we we process them immediately. All right,
well, you got got yeah. Well, sometimes you make ginormous mistakes and
hopefully she by the time this comes out, she probably will have already
eaten and will have already forgiven me. So it's not here's the thing you don't
even it's not even that she has to forgive you or eat and be convinced that
it's great. If she eats it, it's a joint expense. Yeah, exactly that's exactly
the truth before she sees the bill exactly where she sees the statement for
the account. Yeah, it'd be so funny in one or two bites of you say, Oh, well, I
knew you were both going to eat it and was it more for both was it about seventeen
percent of our monthly entire food budget on one single steak? Yeah, that
would be so funny if you get the call, like right in the middle of this
fucking episode that I have to go pick it up.
Hey, I was looking through the joint bank account. I was looking through the
Bank of America app. I saw one hundred and thirty dollars on state. You know
I'd probably do man. I probably lie blame it on a say say that you were on a
website. I would probably say
jacking on probably say was a dent. We put my credit card. It was a cam web
right yeah. She would probably how many how many servings is this day? This is
literally this is one meal. This is half a meal for each of us. It's one eleven
ounce steak.
It's not even a pound of meat. You fucking
what's wrong with you.
I told you like how many butcher shops there are in this neighborhood.
It still would have been an absurd expense.
You can go to Costco and buy A5 Wagyu there.
I mean, it's not like the best, but I wanted the best, man.
Even then you go there, you get a fucking Costco membership out of that.
This is why, you know what, man, these women need to stay the fuck out of my money.
Yeah, it's that simple.
If I want to spend all my money on Valorant skins, how much is it at Costco?
that's a lot. Well, that's twelve pounds. That's twelve pounds and that's nine
hundred dollars. Yeah. And it comes with a big yellow pepper.
That's good. Nothing goes better with a five wagyu than a big, raw, yellow bell
pepper.
That's the craziest garnish they could have.
That's it's Costco, man.
Whatever.
It looks good. It looks
vegetable.
I don't understand what's going on. I mean, he's right that you would never
eat a bell pepper.
What would you choose?
The least attractive bell pepper, too. Not even a green one.
You just put a carrot next to it.
A carrot would have made a little... I mean, really, any vegetable, one carrot.
Why did they even need to put the vegetable next to the...
It's a garnish, man. It makes it look like it's a part of a kitchen.
Was it for scale? Maybe that makes a little sense.
I guess it's for scale, yeah.
But bell peppers vary widely.
They should have put someone's hand to that.
Yeah, exactly.
But then you definitely say...
The butcher's hand with a knife.
Oh, that's smart.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
See, fucking Costco hire me for your fucking photo shoot.
You look like you work at Costco to be fair.
Yeah, I know.
Like a Costco manager.
I'm wearing... This is a... If you can see right there, I don't know, that's the jacket.
Hi, my name is Ivan. I could see that.
Hi, my name is Eduardo.
Whatever company, I haven't been able to get this sticker off of it.
I couldn't read it.
You've always reminded me of Eduardo from Foster's Home for Imaginary Friends.
That's crazy because that's...
And I can't tell if you're real or not.
That's what my sister said that too.
What if he was you and me's joint imaginary friend?
That would be great for the IRS, you could claim that.
You can't be worse for us. That would be good for me. Where the hell would our money be going?
You can just tell the IRS that I'm an imaginary friend and that they don't have to...
That'd be a dependent. They don't have to make me pay any more taxes.
That'd be amazing. That'd be smart. You can't make me pay taxes.
I'm an imaginary friend. You wouldn't have been paying taxes to begin with because you wouldn't be real.
You don't exist. You wouldn't have existed. There would be no concept of what's good or bad for you.
You don't know about the bank of imagination. You wouldn't appear in the world.
take a USD. They take ISD. Imaginary State Dollars. Did you guys have imaginary friends
growing up? Yes I did. Who? I had a lot just because man I don't even remember. I don't
remember the name of my imaginary friend or what his power was, but I had an imaginary
friend who had a power who is pretty much the same as like blue or whatever from
Foster's home a blue guy a bullet he might have been blue but talk about it
might have been blue but red he was a bullet no he was a teardrop bullet blue
was a fucking bullet he was a teardrop because of how sad that makes for not
having real friends oh that's actually sad yeah my imaginary friend was a big
hand and then my brother's was a guy who lived on Mars but he had it way long yet
got it into like ten eleven years old. Okay, he was saying I'm going to go to
Mars today and they started my way. His imaginary friend was Mars. His imaginary
friend lived on Mars. I don't remember his name and his he his mom would drive
drop him off in a red Corvette from Mars and my grandma thought for some years
that my younger brother was demonically possessed because
imaginary friend is weird. I never had an imaginary friend. I was I had an active
imagination as a child. I never had an imaginary friend. I guess I imagined
that I was a monster.
You were the imaginary friend. I became the creature. I used to ride the vacuum
and say that I was a superhero named Oak Man. Used to ride the vacuum? When I
was a little boy. Used to ride that shit? You know the vacuums that have the...
You ride enough of that shit, bro? They have the... Face hitting the vacuum?
They have the thing right there, like the big part of it that goes to the
wall, and then they have like the thing right there. The big cord? You know
what I'm talking about? No, no, no, no, no, no, no. There's the vacuum that's
there's two parts, right? There's like the thing with the tank and then
there's the suction thing that's like the cord that goes up. The hose?
Okay. The hose, yes. That's the word you're... The thing that goes to the
wall? The thing that goes to the wall is the cord, but I'm not talking
about a one piece vacuum, I'm talking about a two piece vacuum. I know
these are old. Yes, I used to sit on that and I would hold the thing on
my back and I said that I was moat man. I don't know what moat was.
Moat of dust. Moat of dust.
Maybe that's what the word means. My grandma had a, have you guys ever encountered this?
A central vacuum? Yes. Where it's in the wall. We had one of those and then my parents shut
it off. It's literally a hole in the wall and you plug a tube into it. That's crazy.
Isn't that crazy? And it all goes to like some place in your house. I want that. It
was amazing. We had one in our house. That must be the one that's the best to fuck. It
was like a big thing in the 80s and 90s. It's definitely the best to fuck. I put an action
figure in that silly you and I lost your action figure. Yeah, I think my old
brother definitely put his nutsack on it. Yeah, I you guys had that my
grandma. Yeah, I want to have that. We had one in our house, but it didn't
work. They shut it off when I worked at the liquor store. I do use one of
those really old commercial ones where it's got the big like cloth bag like
a full like nineteen fifties. Yeah, I haven't ever used one of those. That's
the one way we have an oric in our house. We used to have that as
glass shop that I worked at. Clean up all the glass man. And it would cut holes in the bag.
Yeah, that's what happened. And then it would fly out and it would kill every single person
in the whole building. No, that didn't happen. I witnessed a crime today. I saw a lady get
hit by a car. Oh, that kind of trumps my thing. I think she passed away. Sorry, continue. I didn't
say anything. What crime did you see? I was at the lot less over by on Fresh Pond. I know it.
and there was a guy stealing what looked like a bunch of hair gel in his jacket.
Did he look like Elvis?
No, I wish.
But he had like four or five things and then the owner...
I heard like a scuffle start. I heard like a scuffle happen.
The sound of a scuffle starting.
A sound of a scuffle.
And then I heard, "Leave me alone."
"Alright, here we go!"
"And it's time to start!"
"Here we go!"
The fists winding up.
you
somebody doing a giant falcon
charging it up,
but the manager I could hear them like rest like rustling around and then like
one of the things falls out. It's like either hair Joe's either hair gel or
skin cream or something. I don't know what, but he was stealing a fuck ton of
it and the manager of the store like is like he was like grabbing him like I
I don't think that he should have been hitting him as much as he was. I think
that like... He's got his hair gel. I think that he broke the barrier between
like subduing... Managers always do. Yeah, but then I hear him go like, like
they're, like the guy's just like, "I'll drop everything if you just let me go.
You don't have to call the police," which I was like, "Yeah, that's fair if I
can let him do that," and then, you know, I chimed in.
Well, that's... Yeah, sorry. I'd like to say... That seems fair.
talking up well
sir. I mean he said he's going to put it down. We just let him go. I just
don't need to involve the police here yeah, but then so then that happens and
then the guy is like moving him around and everything and he's the I hear the
manager go. He's just like you broke my arm. You just broke my arm, but I look
and the guys already has the cast of
that's true
He already had a fucking sign.
He had a cast on.
Yeah, you know he had signatures.
He had a baby.
He was like, "Where are my other three?"
And everybody here signed my cast because they support me and not you.
Everybody saw you break my arm and I put the cast on so fast.
That is a pretty, that's a layup for the cops when the cops get there.
You say, "Well, he broke my arm, obviously."
So then I'm waiting outside and the guy's like gone.
I was waiting for my girlfriend to leave because she like went to the back of the store for
some reason.
Probably to steal something else.
Probably, yeah.
probably going to fucking steal some makeup, too. And this old woman did
exactly what I was joking about doing, where she looked at the guy and went,
"You shouldn't have done that. When the police come, they're going to arrest
you."
It was, like, so fucking crazy. This little old Polish woman going, "Uh-uh,
you should not have done that. You should not have hit him." If you're a
manager, though, if you're a manager, you got to risk it for the biscuit, man.
do there. You know, do this is a lot less. This is where, like products go to die.
This is like they have a
going to get fucking
promotion shit there that you didn't think would exist like they have like
this guy, he has to be an action figures, US Army branded, no under
every every single, you know, under guitar, so every every manager at a
place like that is their entire existence. Is there have boiling evil
rage? Oh yeah surface, they're just they dude his
every day you can only you can only vent so much amount of steam on your
employees. You can only get you can only get out so much by like yelling at
your employees to go rearrange the shelves so that when someone picks up a
thing of hair gel and walks out by accident, you're ready to just voles
over the counter. Teen things of air yeah, see that's a felony like yeah. It
was like a lot of people shoplift because they're starving, they're
hungry and they need it. This guy probably had a family of fifteen babies
to care
giant that he needed to style so they could get jobs as child models, but he
is not easy to survive. That's true. It was so crazy. It's pretty much the only
way out. Oh, absolutely, but he like grabbed the guy, the guy spun around
because he was trying to get out the door and then like as he dropped one,
he's like that's all of it and the guy was like I know you have more and then
he like spun and then
it's so funny for one to fall like that's all of it. I expect to be like
Okay,
bye dude. It was like Sonic's rings like
that the fucking every single time that the manager hit him another thing of
hair
jacket that he was wearing. That's awesome man. Dude, you know that, you
know that man, all these poor teenagers who work at that store about to get so
old women. Oh really? Yeah. So like the old women were like pushing customers
away so that they could fight and like the old women were kind of like,
like I don't even know it was like they were like Praetorian guards like
they were
standing there.
They were full. Like blocking?
Like blocking. Yeah, like they had a...
You should have ran them over, man.
Dude, it was like a... It's like they set up a fucking boxing ring to
like keep everybody, like keep all the customers watching this guy get the
shit kicked out of him. It was insane. I think that more... I'm so pro
fighting like that. I think that that should happen. Anytime that... If you
have a disagreement with somebody who works at a place or they have a
disagreement with you. They should do that. They should be fighting. Yeah,
especially at that lot less. You shouldn't be complaining, sending a survey
and all this shit. Fuck that, man. Kill each other. Yeah. The weirdest part
was all the old... Everyone gathered around, right? And all the older women
who shop there, they're buying weird Mitsubishi toothpaste or whatever.
They're all
excited to watch this. It's the most amazing thing I've ever had. They don't
I have anything to Chris. So like there's like the one the one old woman who is
saying like you should have done that you're going to go to jail to and then
like these other women like I would have done way worse.
I would have fucking killed the guy respect to them. I scared a guy this
morning. I just oh yeah, you popped out of your apartment and jumped on him. No,
that's a lie. I was walking. I went to the grocery store and I was walking back
and I was holding on my groceries. It's just a straight line walk back. I don't
turn or anything. So I was walking. I just walking behind a guy. I was just
walking in front of me for like many blocks. I was walking behind him and
then
when I we cross the street, cross the street and then knows we cross the
street. He turned around. He like kind of like like I could see he was doing
the thing where he's trying to look over his shoulder a little bit without
looking and then he did turn around like all the way to look and he started to
turn back and then he went like
full like double take job. He got scared. He's got scared of me and then it may
be made me like because you immediately after he did that I'd turn the other way
and he kept walking. So it's like he noticed me and I was like Oh,
I gotta go.
I can feel you in his wind bro. Yeah, I guess so. I guess I was kind of your
aura was too strong. Sometimes I do I do try and send messages to the people I'm
walking behind. I think I walk by and so on for a while and I just think like
nothing for a block. I just think I'm going to kill you. I'm going to kill
you. I'm going to
turn around, see if they clock it, start walking, fellas, every many people
not sensitive to this time. I must have accidentally sent something out. I was
probably thinking something like can't wait to get these groceries home. Yeah,
he may be he thought he thought he was a
head. Yeah, oh my God, is there a grocery here? I can't wait to blow up
his home. Yeah, yeah, there's a can't wait to take this gross man home.
Yeah, that's I'm like a really, really fast Walker too, which is like my
girlfriend hates it. It's a full brag. No, it's also not true.
One of the slowest walkers I've ever watched.
Insanely slow walker. Okay, I'm faster than my girlfriend and I'm usually...
Congrats, she's three feet tall. My girlfriend's not three feet tall. One
time we were talking about how long it takes to walk somewhere. And she's
young too. One time we were talking, I remember this. Here's my evidence I'll
represent twenty she's twenty one man. She's just turned nineteen.
We're talking about how long it took to walk somewhere and he was looking at
the Google Maps time and he said it would take him longer than the Google
Maps time to walk somewhere. What are you talking about? When was that? I
don't remember when it was. I remember it happening. Okay, well, I'm faster
than my girlfriend because girls walk slow man. Yeah, I was literally the
girl walk time yeah, but sometimes I'm like two or three blocks ahead of not
blocks. What's your bad boyfriend walking three blocks?
I mean, for some reason in my head, I thought that for a split second here, I
thought that blocks meant like, like a Minecraft block. Yes, yes. And you know,
on the sidewalk where it divides, right? Right. The sidewalk tiles, the sidewalk
tiles. Yeah, I'll be like three tiles of a head of her. How far is it? I don't
you know it's pretty close about four hundred and fifty blocks that way.
Yeah, the thing is I have I have the thing to where I've walked pretty fast.
If I'm on but and I all but I also if I'm walking behind somebody, I have to
pass them. I can't be walking behind people and this today was a day where
I'm still like you know I'm recovering from my illness and I carry a bunch of
groceries. So I was like you know what I you normally would pass this guy, but
I'll let it ride today. I'll walk behind him for a while and look what happened.
I ruined his day. No, I always scared his the daylights out of because of how
because of how like you like we probably walk around the same speed. Nope, but I
mean we are both we are both in the upper the upper percentile of walkers, the
upper half, keep reaching buddy, because you're both you're five foot five. Yeah,
yeah, I am five foot five. I don't I'm not ashamed of that.
Look it up. I'm five foot five, five foot five inches tall. So when I stand
up, when I stand up, it's not going to be much different than this. You get
disorder. When you yeah, look, you're in a booster chair.
That's it. That's how tall I am, but we're like like we walk behind people
and people always look behind because we are weird and walking way too fast.
Yeah, we're walking faster than a normal person. I'm walking with it when I walk
behind someone when I'm walking within twelve inches of them. Yeah,
dude, it's the worst at night. It's like an old woman who keeps turning around
and chasing her way. Yeah, I have a big butcher's knife. That's because I'm
going home. I just watched Babish. I want to make a you just got it in the
from adventure brothers or whatever,
and I just got this big cleaver in the man. I'm heading home to cook bitch.
I'm looking behind you like I'm going to kill you. I might kill you because
you're annoying me. You know what I'm doing like little like I'm walking fast
and I'm doing little jogging style workout. What I do in that situation if
I'm walking down if I'm yeah walking home from the train and it's dead of
night, you know, middle of the night and there's nobody on the street. It's just
me and there's a woman walking in front of me. I I'm on the ground like a
spider. I'm not going to cross the street because I need to be on one side
of the street for efficiency, because if I turn to turn right and be on the
right side of the street, I'm not going to cross over and cross back. That's
I'm going to barrel through. So what I do yeah is I just want to start walking
away.
Dude, I'm on which usually I think makes people really uncomfortable. He's just
a speed up all for his backwards style, like this walking towards her. Usually
I crank my head all the way around. What you have to do what you got actually got
you got on your left and that voice exactly yes, you have to do that yeah,
then I think you got a little bit of thing is to yeah. I'm not so bad. I'm
not so invest. I'm sorry that you're an untrusting person, but I'm going to blow
by you and you're going to hole. There's nothing. Are you supposed to walk behind
or pass? I'm going to run so fast that there's just going to be a right behind
my clothes. There's gonna be a cloud. I'm gonna be nude running home. Are you
supposed to pass by them like just kind of speed up and overtake them, which can
be very scary, because it's like you're chasing them down or are you supposed to
more courteously just walk directly behind them for eight to ten blocks and
then realize you forget you forgot where you're going. Sometimes get confused
think maybe you're walking with someone you know for a couple of blocks. Yeah,
yeah, well, it's directly yeah yeah, here's what I do man. You got to get
right up to them because it's it's the middle of the night. You don't want to
make a scene or be loud to be alarming, so you get right behind them and then
you get really close to their ear and go, "On your left." And then you pass.
Then you do the Hannibal Lecter.
"I'm right here. I'm behind you. I'm here."
Hannibal Lecter.
Yeah, because the gum's falling out of my mouth. I'm trying to get it back in.
I had an experience one time where, I think I might have talked about it, but I was the
guy who kept looking behind because I think I was going to meet you guys at a restaurant
and I ended up, there's like that cemetery near Stanhope and there's this old Indian man
man who creeped up behind me, tap me on the shoulder and made me take my air
pods out to tell me that my air pods are giving me radiation poison. Oh yeah,
stop listening to music. He's right man. Oh fuck him. I need my tunes tunes. I
mean I need tunes every single day. Have fun enjoying tunes when you're on
chemotherapy. I would rather that's probably the only thing you can enjoy on
can imagine how amazing music sounds when you're on chemotherapy. Actually,
you can't eat any food brain being stimulated by radiation, evolve into a
form of music-based consciousness.
Just listening to Pink Floyd in the fucking bed.
What's that Josh Brobin song?
The "Horty Volare"
Dude, I would just get super into like...
From Step Brothers actually?
I would just get super into noise and Mers-Bow and stuff
so that when I got put in the MRI
I'd feel like I was at a concert.
Zone out.
A new type of enjoyment.
Take some Molly, man.
Take some Molly for the MRI.
Dude, that sounds great.
Sounds fun as fuck.
That'd be so scary.
just yeah to have cancer yeah, no to be in an M. R. I machine on molly just
like how you'd be feeling the most fun time as long as you get a glass of
water. I feel like I would just feel the iron in my body moving, bro having
sex in the M. R. I. Oh, my people have done that man. They do that, but
they're not allowed to thrust it all. They have to just sit there. Mormon
style just soaking in there. I just said that, but you seem to know a fact who's
having sex in an M. R. When they do have like M. R. I sex things like when they
they M. R. I sex, they have they they they took an M. R. I of two people
having sex, but it wasn't sex. It was literally science. Why they do this to
see to see what it would be like to see what I feel like they should have all
the stuff like that. They should have gotten that done back in like one thousand
and ten. Well, they didn't have any more. How many more questions we need to
answer of like what is the X ray look like of a guy's penis? Yeah, what is the
extra different now? No, they're not. Yeah, penis cocks have changed. No, not
since 19.
I've changed their last hairy because we have made
expert. That's true. Yeah, you do seem like an expert. I'm 1910. The hair
grows up all the way at my shaft.
Yeah, I guess I'm on search. I get straight. No, I get stray hairs that go
all the way up to the border. Yeah, yeah, right where the meat meets the tip.
Yeah, that's where I get it. There's a way the rubber meets the road man.
That's like Frank Zappa down there. Yeah,
yeah, I've had I've had ingrown hairs on my shaft. Oh, that's the worst. You
think you got herpes or something and then you're like, wait a minute. I don't
I don't fuck around. Yeah,
wait, I'm a virgin. I'm fifteen.
I guess I'll just pop this into my mouth.
One hundred percent. I told you guys about this, but I had an ingrown hair on
my balls, thought that I had cancer and have my dad look at it. Really? Yeah,
Give a little have your doctor look at it because I was asking my dad to take me
to the hospital.
His dad is a doctor.
I begged his dad to look at it.
I begged my dad to take me to the hospital and he said, I bet it's not
cancer.
I bet it's an ingrown hair.
And I said, well, I don't know what that looks like.
Don't tell me he reached his fingers out and went.
No, he didn't touch it, but he did look at it.
He looked with a jealous look.
He got down on his knees and looked at it.
Are you for real?
Your dad got down on his knees in front of you and unzipped your pants and
looked at your balls?
I had my balls out over the top like it was like I was holding like you did the
reverse. You know when you put the dick underneath the balls? That's funny.
Yeah, I did that to show my... 'cause I didn't want my dad to see my penis,
obviously. How old were you? I was 16 years old. Okay. And I showed my father
my nutsack through my jeans and he
kneeled down.
That is gross, man. That's not a right thing to do. And he said,
once he looked at it, he went, "Oh, come the fuck on," and left the
bathroom.
really that's how bad of a hypo.
He went into the bathroom.
The funniest thing is something like that. You guys both know that this is
not right to do. This is not okay, so you have to go into a smaller room.
This is not something that can be in an open air. This is even in a bedroom.
What did you see? Did you lock the door? No,
also like most of my family was in the kitchen. Anyway, I came back home, so
you couldn't have done anything.
and I was I was that's how I mean you guys met me like just God, just the
knowledge of like
we need to do this in a in a little light room. Yeah, this can't. This is a
medical procedure. Yeah, this needs to be in the room where I where I shit. I
can't do this in the room where I sleep and have dreams. We're getting out of
the the love suite. We have to leave the the hot tub. The I should have done in
the basement. Yeah, that would have been good, but you guys you guys knew like
when when you first met me just how bad of a hypochondriac I was and just like
like COVID changed my whole life. It made me realize I don't care.
It made you lose your twenties. You lost your twenties to COVID. Yeah. And your girlfriend
lost her teen years. Oh, because your girlfriend's like 15 or 16. My girlfriend's not 15. She's
24 years old or 25. She just turned 25 on Thanksgiving. That's none of my business,
man. Why are you boring me? I told you my girlfriend turned 25 on Thanksgiving. Shut
up, dude. I'm going to look at this snow. Don't look at the snow. Oh, I could have.
I probably got the worst tree of all time.
- Yeah, you did.
- 'Cause it's just, it's--
- I told, dude, we should have went to Home Depot
and got the mouse.
- The mouse would have been an amazing mouse.
- The mouse would have been so--
- I still don't even know what the mouse is.
- There's still time.
- You haven't seen the mouse?
- There's one of those--
- I'll show you later.
- You got a photo on your phone of it.
You could show that.
- I'll find it.
- Actually, Julio, look up Home Depot Christmas Mouse.
- That's not gonna come up, I promise.
- It'll come up immediately.
- It'll probably come up immediately.
- There's basically no world where that comes up.
- Christmas Mouse.
Oh, there is. Yeah, that's him.
There he is right there. What is his name again? He had an amazing name.
Oh, he's called customers also viewed. Oh, man. Wait, is he sold? No,
30 inch Christmas mouse. 30 inch Christmas mouse. Look at him.
He has got some cookies and he's got a candle. He's so cute. He's standing
on a cookie, too. And he also lives on a cookie. He lives on a
cookie and he's as small as a mouse. He's got his tail draped around his
foot in kind of a weird way that I don't like. It looks like poop,
man. Yeah, it actually looks like a white poop. I want to say his name was like
cherish or something. Click the product details. He's so adorable and he's
pretty big. I need to scroll up and click the product. Whoa, look at all
these pictures where people have put him. Oh yeah, he's got lights.
Makes me made my day. I absolutely love my new Christmas rodent.
Whoa!
LED's did not last two weeks. Well, it doesn't matter. You still have a little
mouse. Say hello to my little friend. My little friend works well and not pricey.
Love the size and the coloration. Me too. My grandchildren love them.
Love Our Mouse. Scroll up to the product details real quick. Love My Christmas
Rodent. Exactly. That's the top review. Down a little bit. I love my Christmas
Rodent. Love My Christmas Rodent. It's an episode name. Yeah, it is. Whoa!
Oh, it's... Oh, my God. What? What are you talking about? Oh, there's all these
cubes. Oh, that's what you were surprised by? Yes. You were amazed at? Yes.
Yeah, I don't remember what the exact name of it is. Did you guys as families
ever do Christmas decorations outside grandmas? No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
decorations outside growing up? Yeah. Like did you guys go crazy? I mean, you've seen
you've seen like a wreath on the door. My child's decorated inside. Do you do lights?
Not like I did some lights outside, but probably just to read. I mean, if we did, that was
definitely over early in childhood. I feel like we never did any inflatables or anything
like that. I could see my son definitely had a bunch of shit like that. And my my family
kind of hated it. I think I love lights on the back porch. But that was it. Like we couldn't
I mean, I don't know we had like
well, you're going to have a front yeah. We had like no roof access and like
like you weren't allowed to like we couldn't put like like lights and shit
on the roof.
I think that I could see myself getting older and being one of the
Christmas lights, Christmas lights, peoples that's the may freak me out. I
can't think I like the the Halloween ones. There's somebody in ones are
better than the Christmas. There's one near our near our know the place where
you take the dog that is like they go all out for every fucking holiday. They do
go all out for Thanksgiving, Halloween, Christmas and now Halloween. They had a
big banner that said the Ridgewood Coven, and when you walked by, they had it,
they had like a screen that was built into the window and like a big pot, a
boiling pot with like fog, and you would walk by and a witch would go.
That's got to be a business. I don't know. No, no, no, it's a bunch of fat
ladies. Oh,
There's a house near my mom's old house where they had a for Halloween one year.
They put up a skeleton with like a carriage like a skeleton with a skeleton
horse and a carrot and a carriage and then they just left it up forever and
now every holiday.
They just decorate the skeleton in the carriage with whatever the different
holiday.
That's cool.
Isn't that fun?
They put like that's what I'm saying as an idea like that's maybe that's a fun
year-round thing like for when it was September.
They put like back to school stuff.
My mom's neighbors.
Yeah, my mom's neighbor had
actually my mom's neighbor had a skeleton.
There's a sign that says I died.
No, they were my mom's neighbor has a skeleton where they do that. It's
Halloween skeleton that sits on the front porch on the on the bench and then
at Christmas they put us and put a Santa yeah, yeah, it's that simple man.
That's like
yeah, that was like I thought that was a sign of pure redneckness because of
that Gretchen Wilson song redneck woman.
The chorus says something about leaving her Christmas lights.
No, it's "We'll have Halloween on Christmas," Blink-182.
No, I'm thinking of the "Country and Females" song.
"We'll have Halloween on Christmas."
Why do you want double Halloween, you sick fuck?
It's because they're gothic.
Blink-182 is the most goth band I've ever heard.
That's their only gothic song.
Their whole discography is goth.
It's not gothic, it's more skater-pump type.
No, it's not as goth as fuck. Adam's Song.
Adam's Song is not goth.
(singing)
the songs are goth. They're not goth. You guys don't know. Damn it. It's a swear.
Damn it. I'm too god. We went to the coffin club and you guys weren't even
educated on gothic behavior. I know everything about goth stuff because I've
been a joiner since my life. A joiner? You've been a joiner, Lucas. Been a
member since my life. Oh, no, wait. But what do members do? They join. So I've
been a joiner. You joined your member with a guy. Yeah. That'd be fine in
goth culture. Goth culture... No, it wouldn't, my friend. Yeah, goth...
We actually, in the goth world, we actually celebrate homosexuality.
For some reason in the 80s, it's like ancient Rome.
Good chunk of the goths also kind of like fascist, like Nazi types.
It's industrial.
It's the spikes, man.
It must be the spikes.
It's the industrial stuff, right?
Isn't it, I feel like?
I think so.
As all the industrial people, there was like, what if we made music that sounded like a
toaster and we dressed as if we were Nazis?
Well, it's also like, what was that guy, Death in June?
That's a Nazi guy that made...
death in June is Nazi status. Yeah, not so you didn't know that I don't even
really know what that is. I never listen. I don't even really know all I know
about death and do is that it's Nazi status. Yeah, I heard one song and I
like sure it's good. I heard
I liked it. I made a man. I think about these Nazis and they make amazing
music. Some Nazis do. I hate to say it. I'm Kanye West.
Burzum, I never listened to Burzum. It doesn't seem like I don't care about
Burzum, but some of the other bands that he was in those ones are good mayhem.
Mmm, him's good. I fuck with mayhem. See I'd rather just listen to
Especially this time of year frankly Christmas music frankly Sinatra frankly Sinatra who has been you know
Kind of what happened him when did he die? He died in the 1990
Really, I think look that he was around forever. Yeah. Yeah, it's rumored that he is one of those guys. He thought would be around forever
forever.
It's a rumor. It's a rumor that he's Eddie Murphy's father.
Yeah, I think I remember him at the beginning of Raw when he's doing the flashback to him
as a kid.
Yeah, it's Frank Sinatra sitting on the chair.
Yeah.
Watching Little Eddie.
Yeah, it's crazy. It's crazy that that's his father.
Who do you guys think, do you guys think that you, it's possible you have a celebrity father
are long lost out there. Sometimes I look at my dad and I'm like, there's no way I'm related
to you. My mom told me that I look exactly like my father. He told me a few times that
Evan Dando from the Lemonheads, you know, that is. Oh yeah. He followed him. He followed
her around at a party in high school that could leave her alone. Lemonheads is it's
a shame about Ray. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Fire as a part bit part of your life. That's a good
good song. Good fucking there. Yeah, I think they really only have one Boston
baby album. Yeah, their other stuff has a like a few good songs. Yeah, they did
they were they did they were punk. They had one album there. They had a few
stuff where they were punk first and they changed to be indie rock and their
indie rock stuff is way better. But there are a few good songs from anyway. It
doesn't matter. They went crud. They went crunk went indie unfortunately, but it
is it's good as Punk went into streets hip hop, but that's crank man. They're
Massachusetts status, but yeah and that's all we like that's all. I like
here a podcast about my mom dated a football player that passed away
jealous. I think my mom went on a date with Roger Clemens or she won a dinner
with him.
Really one a dinner was the inspiration for friend.
What
was the friend? Wait, what do you mean? What's the who's Roger Clemens is Roger
Clemens? Roger Clemens is a Red Sox picture. I thought Roger Clemens, the guy
wrote a frindle. Oh no, and then I believed it because he said it. No,
the guy wrote frindle. I don't know. Roger Clemens was on the Red Sox, then
he got traded to the Yankees. My mom, I wish that was I wish you'd most said
that your mom did the guy wrote frindle. That's fully what I thought.
He said that crazy. I think she won like a dinner date with him, but it
wasn't a date because I think she was with my dad at the time, but there's
like photos of my mom with Roger Clemens, and when I was a kid, I thought
I thought that she bragged about it to me because Roger Clemens, I think, was still on the Red
Sox at the time.
And then I was like, "Well, what if he's actually my father and I'm actually destined for baseball
greatness?"
Oh, and it would be like, maybe you would have lived your whole life and then you get
onto the field.
Yeah.
And it just clicks Henry Rowan.
And you just feel like you've lived part of your life.
Yeah, not like 85 or 90 years old.
Yeah, but maybe like 28.
Yeah.
So some part of your life.
your life. Just part fully you never know when you'll die. I didn't really mean
all of your life. My mom dated Joe Coy for about twenty five years.
Yeah,
so it could be my dad man straight up. I could see that
why
because I'm Vietnamese, your name, what he's not Vietnamese, he's Philippine
because I'm Filipino. You're you were going to be or no, I'm not I'm being to
me. You were going to be named Joseph. I was going to be Joseph like his stand up
especially yeah. I am Caleb with all the fill guys. I oh yes, it's always a
Caleb yeah. That was a really bad shot Caleb. I got
who's Caleb. I want to kill this guy. He's you thought it was someone else. I
thought he was talking to somebody else, but it turns out I was the one. He was
really the praise. No, he's a bad shot. Oh bad. I thought he said good. No, it's
this guy Frankie. He's a really good pool player. Oh Frankie was good. Frankie
was really, really good. He had like he had like ten kids in the grand Philippines
Frankie Cosgrave. You were playing pool with Frankie Cosgrave and you thought he was a Filipino
guy because of his outfit. And because of his last name.
Who did you get Frankie Grande down here? We could get Frankie Grande on here. I was
talking to somebody, I think I was talking to Eric the other day about, I was like, I
really want to get celebrities on the show. That's his whole podcast thing. No, no, no,
I was like we need I want to get like a booker to get like oh yeah, we were and
me and him were talking about what would be our podcast dream celebrity guests
and I don't know because I think it would need to be somebody that is just
so it needs to be completely out. I mean, I don't want to do the be list.
This I've said this to you guys before. I think that it has to be somebody who
is so completely out of reach and out of sphere that it is not even fun or
interesting to have them on because there's nothing in common. There's no
so they don't they don't want to be here. They don't like us at all.
There's not they're not promoting it to any no, we don't pay ourselves for one
month. Like I fall behind on rent and like and we get every one of my
papers, a fee for like like Dacre Montgomery from Stranger Things. Who's
that? The older brother in one season? I don't know who that is. Yeah, he was
also in the Mighty Morphin Power Rangers movie. He played the Red Ranger.
Okay, maybe this isn't a big enough celebrity to you guys. Sounds like a
I'm all so I like a celebrity for kids to my face. I like Finn Wolfhard or
then, but they sell them or no
we can get no snap. No,
no snap doing yeah, and that's all the old dude. He's busy. He's busy man.
He's enlisted. That's true. He's fighting the idea for Israel one sticker
at a time, man. We can get Finn Wolfhard. I had him on super mega some
years ago. Oh, they did. Yeah, we can get him to Finn Wolfhard. If you're
listening to the show, Finn Wolfhard's too old.
What age do we want to go for celebrities?
Finn Wolfhard, once you get young again,
we're rocking with you, man.
You can come on the show.
We respect you as an artist.
We respect you as...
I like everything you've ever done, dude.
Pretty much. Stranger Things, love that.
It was fire.
Part 2 was okay, too, but you weren't fully in that as you were on the first one.
Yeah, but you were in that stuff.
Oh, you were in a Pup music video?
that don't like that song so much, but like some of their other side, I think
he was on yeah, but still or I think him and Brandon just hung out. All right, I
think we're not so interested anymore.
Then seems like you're kind of ran through when it comes to
yeah, if you're so low that you're doing Brandon's podcast, then we don't
really have any interest man. You seem desperate bro straight up
Leonardo DiCaprio. I do that. That
I would do that.
extremely and just put them right now. Dude, we got just not even talking.
Well, the idea we want to do sitting right there. I remember in the old
studio what we wanted to do because it's such a shitty basement space and we
didn't have much room at the table. We wanted to get a big guest and then have
a separate camera that was pointed at them and they had a really tiny chair.
They have they're like really like a chair. I can still do that. We can do
that in a better way and we just have to cut to them, but this is like them use
my computer. This is like a somewhat nice space. It'd be it wouldn't fit in
that well to have that nice of space. It is not that nice. It's better than the
old one, but it's this is a nice space. Are you crazy? This was supposed to be
nice. I don't know if the state of it is so
over there, but it was a lot funnier when there were pipes, exposed pipes
over and there was always a flood and put them in the corner with the
collapsing ceiling. Yeah, we could do that.
This space was supposed to be our landlord's son's Disney perfume business
headquarter. Oh yeah, he's going to resell Disney perfume right
like souvenir novel, funny business that could have been in anywhere could
have been a poop. Rest Disney Disney perfume resale. Speaking of spaces,
bringing up of spaces and basements, I had an idea when I was walking here.
This was today. I don't you know when you have a basement apartment and you
get the windows that are kind of just out onto the sidewalk.
yeah, you know, yeah, I think that the instead of having those types of
windows on basement apartments, they should extend the basement out to be
under the sidewalk and they should have skylights that are like plexiglass that
people walk over and you look up and the show and you just see people, you see
the sky. First of all, yeah, and you can see people walk. Oh, that would this
would be an up skirt
yeah, this would be an up skirters paradise. This is a night at the
box, but you could style up kill. So sure you could do up kilton people and people
so you first of all you probably have to go through a background check to get the
apartment to make sure you wouldn't do that. Yeah, but I have no eyes and you're
blind, so you could have the apartment if you're just a kind guy who doesn't do
that kind of thing.
But you know if you look up at somebody, they don't like it, then they can put
they can pour shit on your window. Do you think that there's like a part of the
public sidewalk, a gay Scottish ups kilt fan? Yeah, for sure there has to be
that probably was one of the first fetishes developed in the
eleven hundred. What was public transportation?
They got a mirror underneath the guy. Yeah, man, mirrors are old.
They have a big easel on their arm and they're trying to paint
whatever the guy's balls look like. Yeah, they've got watercolors. A quill?
No, no, no. Back then, back then, man, well, upskirters, upskirters back in
the olden days, they lived in the moment. They didn't need to
cheapen it with pictures
jack off right then and there, then kill the girl and dumper in the woods. It
was that simple.
That fucking simple you didn't have to have all this
my Nokia phone,
none of that shit existed. Yeah, you just fucking kill somebody. Yeah, you
don't have to you don't have to worry about what you're getting under them to
look up the skirt. You just grab them and you just say that they're a witch or
something. This is how it was back in the sixteen hundred. That's how it was,
and it was sad man. It was terrible. Things are better now. Things are way
much, much better now. We have this now. We have a big mouth Billy Bass.
You wouldn't have... If you saw a big mouth Billy Bass in the 1600s, if you
showed this to somebody in the 1600s, they would think that you have done some
Evil Dead 2 type of Necronomicon shit to it. True. Yeah. And you have... That
would be a holy item. That item would make you king. Oh yeah. I have a
talking fish.
you would be the advisor to the king. I'll be like pretty. What does the fish
say about the movements of my rock and around the
here? What's he? What's he say?
He's casting a spell. I can't stop this feeling that he that means we're going
to have a good harvest. That'd be amazing to oh my God, I'm a
cute my queen. Yes,
yeah,
that's actually an amazing idea for the best movie ever. Yeah, kind of a time
to hear that's a pretty funny. Yes, I know sketch you know, no, no, no, no,
this is a feature. This is a feature army of darkness reboot. You've where he
has a big in the fully for the first part of the movie. It's primer. It's a
very weird kind of kind of you're thinking it's scientifically accurate
version of time travel right. It's like two guys building this thing for a long
time and then they test it and they're like well, let's throw just anything in
there. They throw in a big mouth billy bass right yeah and then they're like
okay, well it's gone. So it has to be the thing and then they get in that shit and
then they go back to wherever what time I mean actually it'd be maybe that you
ever see the gods must be crazy. Yes, yeah, we watch that at Neil's house and
we watch it on mute for like most of it. Oh, I think I remember yeah and then
and somebody was saying it was the most racist movie ever made or something
yeah, it's about I mean I couldn't really tell because it was muted. Yeah,
I don't I mean I guess I saw it as a kid. My dad showed it to me, so I
don't I don't it's a doc. It's a my I feel like it's pretty pretty racist.
It's a mockumentary about a bunch of like a bunch of bottle falls out of the
guy from a plane and an African tribe and tribes and they believe that it's
sent from the gods. So they go to return it to civilization. That's cool thing.
They showed, but it's a social studies. I showed me that in sixth grade. I think
there's two of them. I think there's a sequel. I just saw the first one. I
watched both of them. I think my dad showed me both. I don't remember much
about it. It reminds me of the magic conch, but anyway, it reminds me of that.
That's what your idea reminds me of. This is kind of like an update to take
out, to turn it from an African tribe to maybe a bunch of white, a bunch of
Nordic yeah, who are and we really are overcompensating and we make them
really, really stupid. Yeah, yeah, and big mouth Billy Bass has a lot of
people can be stupid too. We'll say that I'm a big
it's a great name. That is a good name. And the big mouth Billy Bass will just
say he has a lot of soul, if you know what I mean.
What does that mean? He's gonna be the, 'cause it's the movie about how the
white people are stupid, the big mouth Billy Bass is smarter, but he's also
so it's a machine. He's also got a smart. He's a battery. He's got a very
deep voice that he's singing in, which reminds you of what kind of for your
reasons.
Okay, yeah, I think this is an amazing movie and I think this is going to get
sold instantly sold
to the movie. We get
you know we should do. We should have an auction where people come and they
raise their hand and they stand up and they just say an idea. Everyone bids
sold to the movies sold as a book. That's what the blacklist is for a song. We
should do, but it should go for everywhere. Okay, not just for me. I've
been wanting to make a movie or a TV show for years. Yeah, and it's so hard
because nobody likes us and we are not very good at it. He is and our agents
don't talk to us, but what if we tried to what if we sold a movie to like the
like Ben Shapiro's thing that he's doing daily wire. So we could do that so
fucking easily. Oh my God, we would just trick them into thinking that it's
like a movie of a gender critical movie. Yeah, we just make that. I think that's
not a problem. That's what s Craig's allard does. I think he's the he made
bone tomahawk and and and brawn cell blocks ninety nine and all that stuff. I
think that he gets his money from these guys into thinking the movie is gonna
be like, oh, people are weird. He could be an evil guy. I don't think he's maybe
seem like he could have hold some evil beliefs, but I do think that he
leverages it, but daily wire. Let's just make a movie. I think one of his
movies might be daily wire. Let's make a movie about a gay basketball and yeah
and it's in it's stuck in the sports section of a Dick sporting goods, but
it's called a no Dick sporting a chop your Dick's off sporting goods. Yeah
right and the best good and bad. The basketball is gay and a big strong white
guy comes in and blows it up and it's
and baseball them's it's no baseball them's sure yeah and well okay, we got to
I think that you got what about okay? What about it's a it's an anti woke
version of that Seth Rogan sex hot dog movie okay, okay, called buns out that
one anti woke already. No, it was an anti food was anti or was pro food. It
was telling the message. It was the story. It wasn't a doing. I didn't ever
saw that movie, but I remember it came out and I was like why does all the food
rape each other a hundred times? Yeah,
it gives a fuck of a hot dog. It's not the food. It's not the food raping.
It's a douche bag that is raping food. What? It's Nick Kroll as a douche bag,
like an enema. Oh, he's raping food.
One of the best ideas ever, man. Yeah, I'm glad that those animators were
starved. Yeah, that's good, man. I'm glad they're working 80,000 hours a week
to...
No time off. That's right. That's right. Nick Kroll raping food as a bag.
That's good.
Thank God that thank God nowadays to those animators hit crunch and they
got to work twenty six hours a day. There can do it in service of Spider
Man. Thank you. Thank you for giving me my hero.
I love Spider Man. I need more. It's all worth it when they see the looks
on those kids faces. Yeah, like this. Yeah, because they're all make a wish
kids coming to the animation studio and they're dead. Dad, I want to watch
SpongeBob instead. I want to watch another movie on my iPad while this movie is
going. Yeah.
Steward, you've been destroyed, children.
Children, you've been fucking destroyed.
Children, never come for us again.
Uh-huh. Don't even--
Let that be a reminder.
Uh-uh. This is a message--
Don't play with adults. We'll fuck you up. We're smarter.
This is a message to my niece and my nephews, okay? I'm not poopy, okay? You're
the only three children that I know that I can direct them-- actually, to all
all children. You are poopy man. None of us are poopy. We're not poopy and hey,
my
but my niece and nephews, I'm never going to get your names right. So stop
having your parents send me texts about what they're going to give me for
Christmas and my to my to my nephew learn how to spell turd. I heard what
happened. He said t e r d. He spelled t r d t r d. My sister sent me a voice
demo of him trying to spell turd and it was a minute long of him saying TRD and
she said no and then it was him going turd. You can't blame him though
phonetically that makes the most way that a kid learns letters. You could
understand that. It was a minute long of him saying TRD.
Turd. Why would you add "oo" into that?
exactly
tired tired to our road. Yeah, all right. We need another movie idea
daily wire wire for so okay, so they're going they want doing what they're
doing that
every single thing that comes out of daily wire is they're trying to make
some like right now they're focusing on so that their only projects have been
school shooter movie. Yeah, movie about trans people, TV show about trans people
inadvertently, TV show about a woodshop teacher who hates trans people. What
have we not done? What have they not done? Just a normal family... Illegal
immigrant. We haven't done a legal immigrant. That's true. Well, hold on.
We can do a Mumble Corps movie called Juno.
Juno Diaz? Juno. Juno. Juno. But they have not done just a family program,
right? They have got where we are going to make the daily wires Barney
because you want to target the kids directly. They're already well,
they're already complaining that every single program, Sesame Street and
everything is all be there. They're pushing their agenda. Yes. So we make
the most anti woke children's performer. And it's in a bar. It's in a
bar. It's called army. It's called army. He's an army guy. He's a played
by army hammer. Yes, who was canceled by the
unrightly for being a liar, six foot tall,
black hair, blue eyed army soldier yeah and we never say what army he's a part
of no, no, no, we don't specifically say that he's in the US or you know what
maybe maybe it's just because it was in my direct line of vision. What if the
thing is a Christmas tree? What if the character is a Christmas tree because
they're trying to get Christmas out of school? I don't think that been what's
his name and like that. Okay, then it's a okay and start. Well, Patrick committed
a
it will be funny when it cuts. The cut is just a
can you cut right before what he says
so you can hear all the lead up to it. So don't beep it out.
The beeps makes it seem way worse. Yeah, it does anyway. I just think that we
to be there's so many opportunities and we've just been looking at the old school Hollywood
avenues.
Can I tell you guys this is kind of outside of Daily Wire. I had an idea for a character.
I was thinking about well so there was a crossword clue about a cartoon character who sucks his
thumb and I just realized I haven't heard about anybody sucking their thumb in quite
a long time.
That's facts.
So I thought maybe a character who's an adult who still sucks his thumb could be funny.
Well that could be.
When he gets stressed out he starts sucking his thumb.
he could be an SJW yeah, I mean yeah, but he could be, but just the idea to me, I
guess it's kind of funny of maybe a guy who you he's at work, he's in his he's
in his polo shirt, he's like he's working on the spreadsheet. His boss comes in
and says, you know, I need that by two o'clock right and the guy's like two
o'clock. I thought you said next week, the boss says no two o'clock, he's like
all right, I'll get to work.
He doesn't smoke cigarettes or anything like that. He goes outside. Can I take a
thumb break, you know, stuff like that. It's interesting that you haven't thought about
that considering we some of our most listened to episodes are the diaper forums, right?
Well, people don't really talk about sucking their thumbs when they well, here's a new
thing that we can look up next time. We do a diaper talk. I'm so stuck in thumb war.
Yeah, I do feel like I'm sucker for thumb war. One, two, three, four. I declare it.
No more. What you didn't dance your finger around Pat. Wait, he has the most amazing
strategy I've ever seen. Whoa, he has a fucking cobra of a thumb. That's why they call me the
cobra. That was a dirty match. You tried to coach me. You guys should have put your hands
out on the table. Okay, you know what, Cameron? Still quiet, man. That was a good one. You
stopped it. Yeah, you are so technologically illiterate, man. I'm not technologically illiterate.
my watch to the right time because I accidentally set it to the wrong time
yesterday. It's a stopwatch right now.
You didn't set it to anything. You set it to stopwatch.
Is it 3.13 right now? No, it's not. Yeah, it is. Oh, hey, my watch is fixed.
Oh, it is 3.13. Wait, I'm a genius.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
What the fuck else is going on, guys?
I have to give my cat a bunch of gabapentin because he kept trying to bite the...
I had a dream last night. I had a dream last night that I had to go to the
bathroom and there was an I was in. I was in a house that had two bathrooms
and one of the bathrooms that I went to was the one bathroom was normal. I
didn't go to it, but I knew in my head it was normal for some reason. I chose
to go to this other bathroom. I dream, which is it was like off from the
living room and it was like down a few steps so that it was on. It was directly
and at the corner of the house and on street level and that was to wall to
wall windows, but with a really like thin sheer curtains. I could see
everybody walking by and but I was like I was there's like Oh God damn it and
then I really had to go to the bathroom, but there was two kids that were
walking by. I was like I can't start being while these kids can see through
this.
I started trying to scare them.
Did it work? Did they leave? Oh my God
I wasn't working and I was like
I'm just remember this. I don't know my dream. I was like I was like what am I
doing in the bath to scare these kids and my cover probably hears me yelling
I'm yelling and banging on
oh my God, that's crazy. That really glad I don't have that bathroom yeah. I
I think now we have an idea for a movie. That's an amazing idea for a movie.
Kind of like a buried... It's called Glass House. It's like buried or 127 hours.
Glass House and the only thing, the only real conflict in the movie is the bathroom.
But all the scaring is doing is attracting more kids. Right.
Oh, what's this? Kids like being scared. This is more of a Black Mirror episode.
What? This is more of a Black Mirror episode. This is not really a movie.
So that's what movies go to die is black mirror episodes. Those telephones
it's a smart glass.
That might work, but then the kids wouldn't be real and the kids are
tapping. You have to pee so bad, but the kids are tapping. You're stuck in
an iPad as the background. I'm talking Ben. Yeah, you're talking about. You
have to piss so bad.
Get away from me! That's a great idea. That's a great idea. Talking Ben.
Talking Ben. Talking Ben. Oh my God. Do you remember back in the day,
people would say that like talking Tom, I was watching the other screen. I
were a web that would also be a good black mirror. Episode is that already a
black mirror episode? I don't know. I never watched a single episode of
everything a single up. I saw the one where they were the Star Trek one. That
one's cool. I think I was really, really high when I watched. What is that one
about? It's they're about start so basically the plot that as I remember it
was a Jesse Plemons. Yeah, Jesse Plemons plays a fat guy. He's in Star Trek and
it turns out that all along the women were his slaves. He basically uploaded
his friends or his employees that he thought were hot into Star Trek, so that
he could finger. So get this he was creating Star Trek yeah all along, so it
was so the whole episode is that he basically played the Sims. It's like
imagine
you were he basically it's a guy from Star Trek. Yeah, he works at an office
Jesse Plymouth and all and he looked around one day and he said all these
fucking people I work with are such NPCs bro and I also he created them I'm
gonna make them a litter on PCs in a video he did like face scan yeah
like a beetle, Stephen Hawking beetle.
- Black Mirror voice that I'm starting to do.
- Why do you have a Stephen Hawking mouth?
- I don't have Stephen Hawking.
- Why don't you just be retracted now?
- I don't have Stephen Hawking mouth.
- He didn't talk with his mouth.
- I don't, I don't want to go to Stephen Hawking right now.
- Why are you looking,
this is the most offensive he's ever been today.
You are going crazy.
- What, he's a pedophile.
What am I, you can make fun of him.
- Stephen Hawking wasn't a pedophile.
- He went on Epstein's Island.
- Yeah.
- You can make fun of him all you want now.
I think you are an island with adults, though. I think he was on there to fuck
a wheelchair.
You wouldn't need to go to an island to do that.
You gotta go to an island to do that. I don't want to watch that. I've ever
being disabled just because he did that. I'm not making fun of him for being
disabled. I'm making fun of his computer for having a funny voice. You think
that you think they could have his computer could have had a better voice.
You're gonna make fun of Chris Tucker for being black because he went to
the island. It's okay. He went to the Epstein Island. No, no, but you know I
see the error of my ways. Thank you, man. Why am I all of a sudden the SJW of the
show? Now he's just running off the leash. I don't know the hell's wrong
with you, man. I hate being a woky SJW. You know me. I hate this crap, but
somebody's going to put you in line. Somebody's got to put me in line. I
was going to speak truth to power. You resurface. What did I just say? Oh, my
God,
you're tired of me punching down. Is that what you're saying? Straight up,
dude, yes. Here's a snowflake for you. This is me. This is me. I'm that. I'm a
snowflake. That is you. Oh my God. The snowflake dust is rubbing off of you from
the Christmas tree. That's what it is. I'm covered in snowflake dust. All right.
I'm going to go get a shower, clean myself up. All right. We don't have
anything to plug, I think. Bye, bitches. Except for... Well, this is the Patreon,
and the YouTube is probably... I mean, hopefully, if everything went well, we
have 10K subscribers. Bye. Bye.
This is also from a little one.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, aw, how sweet is that?
It seems like we've taken a lot of these from kids.
Yeah, it's weird that we didn't get that many adults in our literature.
It's kind of weird, right?
Yeah, I feel like mostly kids.
I guess it makes sense.
This is from Little Ben.
Hello Santa. This year, the only thing I want for Christmas is world peace.
Aww, little Ben.
Oh my god, that's so cute.
War, disease, social disorder. How could I sit here and wish for big red fire trucks
or super powered action figures when some people are struggling just to afford basic human
needs? What a smart little kid.
It would just be selfish. And that's the problem with this world. Selfishness. Selfish
corporate CEOs and money hungry politicians hogging all the wealth up top and leaving the
little guy with nothing.
Little Ben?
All the way at the bottom.
He's probably referring to himself.
Yeah.
Or his family as well at least.
Is he related to Big Ben?
He could be a clock.
All the way at the bottom.
I just wish I could do something about it.
You know what Santa?
I finally decided what I want for Christmas.
I want a voice.
I want a say in what direction the winds of change blow.
A say in the future that I'm inheriting.
When I grow up, I'm going to run for president.
And I'll make sure that never again does another immigrant enter this country illegally to impregnate
a white woman.
Little Ben!
Little Ben, what the hell are you saying?
Right now I'm 31, so I should be able to run for president by 2028.
And when I'm president, every border of this country will be protected by nuclear bombs
and big red fire trucks to put an end to you illegally flying over the border. Go back
to your igloo, you disgusting red snow pig. Holy shit. Little Ben, what the fuck? I thought
you were a little ass kid. What a turn little Ben has made. I didn't know you were a grown
man going by little Ben. I mean, his first name could be little, I guess. Little John.
Little John. Little Richard. Little Wayne. Actually, there might be more little men than
- Yeah, a little hole in her heart.
(upbeat music)