they told I'm recording okay wait let me record to hold on ready hold on and clap
and we're back with amazing Brandon Wardell California man all the way
let's see what is Holly Holly weird you hear a lot of this over there in Los
Angeles huh mm-hmm yeah we got a soundboard today I'm on the soundboard I
I always do it loud and if you're near the oh my God,
Oh no, let's see. I got to turn this off.
No, this is good. This is raw.
Okay.
I will, if unless Julio cuts it out, I will come clean.
We need to talk about this. I became the Spiller again. And maybe, no, not even
maybe, for sure the worst spill of all time on the entire show. Oh, absolutely.
You have been famous for being the Spiller. I don't know if that's why I'm
famous.
You're famous on the show for being the Spiller. I think I'm famous as maybe the
host, the number one host, the better guy on the show. Maybe, maybe, maybe,
maybe, but... But if you wanna say that's why. No, the Spiller was your
nickname. The Spiller was your nickname. Coca-Cola all over the mixer. The
The Spiller used to be his nickname.
I used to be the Spiller because I would spill droplets.
You would spill droplets.
Every once in a while.
Yeah.
The past month I have become the Spiller.
And I spilled on the mixer.
You poured a two liter of Coca-Cola.
A catastrophic amount of Coca-Cola.
All over the goddamn mixer.
The Christmas fool over here.
The actual Christmas dunce.
But there is a Christmas miracle.
The mixer still works.
The mixer does still work.
Please, I'm not even kidding.
Nobody tell Cameron what just happened.
he can never know. He can never know. He would freak out. He would do some very, very bad
things at Patrick. So we're going to avoid that completely. And we're going to have to
put this whole thing in rice pretty soon. That's a lot of rice. I saw a big bag of rice
the other day. I'm still wiping Coke off my pants. No, it's fine. I have to go to a dinner
after this, but I'll show up smelling like Coca-Cola. It'll smell sweet. Yeah, no, it's
fine. It'll smell like a baseball game for my wife. Your wife will like it. Yeah, I know.
I'll probably like that a lot. Brandon,
great to be back. Buddy, how are you? I'm well. I didn't get I'm I was not
affected by the soda incident. You were not affected. No, but would that if it
did spill on you with this? Would you have had some kind of diabetic attack
from just skin contact touching me? Yeah, that would scare me. I wouldn't
know what to do in a medical emergency. No, me neither. No, we'll find out. Is
Is there a world where because you're maybe the only person I know who has any
kind of medical problem at all? I really tend to keep people away from me who
have issues like that. So if you had some kind of attack, what I have to pulp
fiction insulin directly into your chest isn't the right or the depends it's
what what it depends what kind of incident we're talking okay.
Get this
I spills he spills all the soda into my mouth directly in your mouth over
40,000, not 40,000, over, say a gallon of soda somehow made it into your mouth.
Powerpuff girl style, I'm making a big jungle juice.
Yeah, he doesn't tell you what's in it.
And then I...
You take one sip.
My elbow hits you.
And then maybe he lies and says that it's Splenda or Stevia, which I imagine you can
have as much as you'd like.
I can have soda in an emergency if I...
That's so awesome.
That's amazing.
I gave you some fruit snacks prior to this.
They made me feel amazing.
I really need some sugar.
I need the carbs.
that I'm medically required to have fruit snacks on me.
- That is the most amazing fucking diagnosis.
- No, I took it way too well when I found out about it.
- How old were you?
- I don't know, I was like in middle school.
- Oh, dude.
- And so I was like, oh cool, so if I have an incident,
I just have to drink soda and eat candy.
- Sounds amazing to me.
- I was like, that sounds awesome.
- So you were in the middle of class
eating candy all you'd like.
- Yeah, it's basically what, I don't know how,
I don't know how interesting this is for people, but I'll talk about it.
For candy fans.
Please, we have a fully candy fan audience.
This would be for a candy holic.
I still like candy.
I would fucking hope so.
I still eat candy.
Your heart still beats.
Absolutely.
Yeah, so you like candy, man.
I'm a red-blooded American male.
What's your favorite candy?
A hundred grand, probably.
Wow, that's a bit of a curve ball.
That's a bit of a low-tier Halloween chocolate.
This is a part about lipstick exclusive.
- You actually, 100 breaking news, 100 grand.
- 100 grand. - My favorite candy bar.
- What was that Canadian one you showed me?
- Wunderbar.
- Wunderbar. - Wunderbar.
All my Canadians in the chat sound off.
- That is a good-- - It's about Wunderbar?
- Good ass candy store. - What's so good
about this candy?
- Just like a really good texture.
It's like peanut butter and then it's like,
there's a caramel center.
- It sounds like a Snickers.
- It's-- - No, no, no, no, no.
- Sounds like a fucking Snickers to me, man.
No, no, no, no, no. I feel like you're not listening to me in good faith right
now. Okay, go ahead. You know, pop off about your wunderbar, which sounds to
me German, but I guess it's Canadian. It's good. It's really good. It's really
good. It's kind of crispy on the outside, but it's soft in the middle. Yeah.
It's a texture that you don't see with American candy so much. There it is.
That's what it looks like. That's wunderbar. Oh, yeah, there it is. Oh,
I'm so glad we can do this now.
- It has, you know what?
I'll keep it a buck, man.
That is too much peanut butter in that box.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
- That's too much for me.
- It's a very tasteful amount.
- It's the perfect amount.
And that looks like it's, that's like the computer version.
- I don't know what that is.
- That's what a robot would eat.
- Okay.
- That's not.
- So this is what you're eating?
- I did not eat that.
- That's your favorite candy?
- No, go back.
- What the fuck is wrong with you?
You are a robot.
- No, that's robot candy.
- Yeah, don't show robot candy.
- No, that's true. - There we go.
- That's the shit I'm talking about.
- It kinda looks like a hot dog in the middle.
- The peanut butter's just too dense for me, man.
I'd have a hard time working my way through all that.
- No, you can work through it really well.
- You'll see.
- I'd be mining with my teeth trying to get through that.
- You know what I saw the other day
that I haven't seen in a long time,
speaking of candy, a Fifth Avenue?
- What the fuck is that?
- I haven't had that. - Those are good.
Those are good.
- Some of those old candies.
- It's an old person candy.
- Like a Werther's?
- No, not like a Werther's.
It's like a full peanut butter chocolate bar, but the texture on the inside,
like the peanut butter texture is kind of like a Butterfinger, but a little bit
crispier.
Okay. Which Butterfinger has what kind of thing in it?
You know like the...
Yeah, but what's that shit called?
Peanut butter.
No, it has that other shit, the flake.
Brittle?
No, what is the flake in the...
Are you thinking...
Beating a Butterfinger, the flakiness.
Crispy?
The crispiness of it.
That's a Butterfinger crisp.
No, the normal Butterfinger has an ability to be Chris. Does it have an
ability? It has a
call it. Oh, those are good.
Great stuff. You're missing out. If you want to talk
shitty candy right now,
recently
a friend of mine
fucking
whipped out, whipped out some Neko wafers. I knew
I knew you were going to say that they're the worst candy in the fucking
worst candy in the world and worst name to I don't like saying that name
nickel wafers. No, no, no, no, no, I mean yeah, New England, we fucked up, we
fucked up creating the necco wafer. My granddad loves those. This is it's
it's like no, it's like you should only that if you're a granddad, this was it's
great depression food and this was millionaire comedian Stavros Stav Stavi
baby.
I mean, I think that if you're fat enough, you eat anything yeah, yeah, but
he well, he was just testing the waters. He never it was a the whole sleeve. No,
he was a he put him away, not put him away like that. That's how he did. He
did like boy. He put him away. No, he he left it on the table. He he tried one.
He but he went to the he was at the candy store. Yeah, he said, Do you want
anything at the candy store?
Sour patch, please. And then he comes back. He comes back from the candy store.
did he have an assortment? Did he have a he bought the whole trial? I think he
had some like
chocolate frogs, some like seasonal Reese's. I think it was like a Reese's
Christmas tree. Yeah, those are good and the sour patch and then he had like a
roll of neck a wafers. I said stave, what is what is that? What is that man?
He's just trying to he's like I don't I just saw this yeah chalky it's chalky.
The texture is bad. It tastes bad. Can't I would say candy in the probably nineties
had a meteoric rise in quality where before the 90s the candies were those
fucking wax bottles.
Ew!
Wax lips was considered a candy?
Ew! Fuck the wax bottles!
Wax, fuck the wax lips!
Keep wax away from my mouth!
Those are actually, depending on which one...
They're funny, they're not edible.
Depending on the one, if it's the one with the gum on the inside...
I'd rather eat regular cigarettes.
The ones that look real.
That's up way too loud, you gotta turn that down.
What's the tastiest cigarette?
Or maybe my headphones.
The tastiest cigarette?
When you hit a like a Turkish Royal, that is nice coffee. I think I never shut up
about these, but Marlboro NXT's, there was a lot of like international students
from Dubai and like China on our college campus and they would have these
Marlboros that had a it was like two different flavor things like two
different like camel crush, but it was like menthol, but also grape or yes, I
- Watermelon. - No, they have.
- Flavored cigarettes from Asia.
- I have seen those, I've seen--
- They have these in other countries.
- The grape flavored one? - A friend came back
with those from Mexico.
- Yeah, the Winston's?
The Winston's with the grapes?
- I don't know who made it.
- I want these. - They got those in Mexico.
- I want these skinny Chinese cigarettes
that these skinny Chinese guys smoke.
- I want those too. - I want to smoke this--
- The really long ones? - So bad, I don't think,
there's a full language barrier, can't ask for one.
I want one so fucking badly.
Every time I see one. You can pantomime. You can pantomime this?
This is... But I don't know.
That's such a crass word. You do this, if you want a cigarette from somebody
that doesn't speak English or whatever language you speak, you point at them,
you go, "You," okay, puff, and then you, "Joyous happiness."
Okay. But again, maybe in China, that could be the most disrespectful possible
thing. That's true. I think like this. Is this bad in China to do a pinky?
You never heard that as a kid that this is the Chinese. I know we didn't hear
anything about the Chinese in North Carolina. Yeah, that's a good point.
We didn't know one thing. They might have been telling you a tale out of
school. Maybe. I don't know. That's what I was told. This is the middle finger
there? People would say... So what's this? Kids would say... This is the
pinky... This is what you do when you drink tea? This is, yeah,
when you're drinking a drink, you do that. Can we look this up? But it
was a thing, it was like a little rumor around my school. The rumor was
going around? A rumor that was that this is the Chinese version of the
middle finger. I'm trying to think of what I heard about other countries.
Okay, apparently it's this.
Yeah, bad.
Bad?
Yeah, pull up that picture.
Mmm, what is it?
Well, yeah, there it is.
Proof is in the goddamn pudding.
It says it right there.
On Quora, they have people, oh man, that looks--
This?
The thumb through the fingers is also a bad thing.
I guess this is kinda, 'cause it kinda looks like
your dick through your shorts.
What is the connotation behind that in China?
If you have your dick through your shorts?
That you're being rude.
that's rudeness. Rudeness, that's peak disrespect. Oh yeah, dude, if somebody,
okay, like if you see like somebody walking around even in their house with
the no bottoms t shirt on. Pooh bear, that's what I do. Pooh bear, and if
you're pooh bearing. I do that a lot. If you're pooh bearing while you got
people over, that's the most disrespectful thing you can do. Pooh bearing
with guests in the house, it depends on who the guests are, I guess. If it's
your beautiful girlfriend or your lovely wife, that's okay, but if it's your
boys, you can't pooh, you don't pooh bear around your boys. If your brother's
gonna have to poo bear now because he has soda all over his god.
Exactly. My pants are complete. I'm going to be walking.
He's going to be at the restaurant completely.
Pooh bear. Now he's at the goddamn pizza restaurant.
Yeah. Pooh bearing because of your ass.
And I was already by the way, I was already planning to get the fucking
the pizza with honey on it.
And now I'm going to look like I'm doing some kind of entire thing.
So this is going to be a really bad night for me.
Thanks for that red shirt.
Yeah, it's
smelling like complete sugar.
No, those are the his two choices right now are to either Pooh Bear or just this
is the worst beautiful wife. Do this is a smelling like for him to pick up a
catchphrase. Oh bother
everything is lining up in a really bad way. You've been saying that all month
to yeah, it's a fucking that was just a happenstance. Yeah, that just was it's
a thing going around. It's like Grizz or any of these
father. Oh father is hitting every all the middle schoolers are saying, oh
bother on the street. Yeah, no, it's a lot of yeah, W Riz Ohio. Oh bother.
Yeah, you got to say it like Pooh Bear too. It's the hardest part. And if you
don't say it right, kids won't do the Fortnite L dance at you.
Rishio, why be better, oh bother. Why be better, oh bother. That wasn't Pooh, man.
That was Mickey, bro. Oh, that is a little Mickey. That's full Mickey. Oh,
bother. Now I forget which one's Pooh Bear. Can you do Stitch? A little bit.
maybe that was me watch it off right now. Okay,
really? What? Yeah, me what and me one stitcher kind of
whoa. Okay, wait. I thought that was pretty good. I thought that was stitched
man. Pretty good stuff. You have a meat wad that turns stitch.
That's it. That is
no, that was you. I think you have a tenor. This is like this is like
watching Mel Blanc. This is what I know. I tried. I did this for Lauren.
I can
here's me and
talking to each other. Okay, this is me. One of those is me what which by the
way, if you haven't seen a teen hunger force,
this did remind me that one of the one of like the worst
functions I have I've been to what I guess one of the worst hangs. Tell me
about these celebrity parties. This is not this. It's not it's not a
the last part. I'm a man of the people I had. It's that so that is so apparent to
me, but I'm a man of the people. Tell me about this party, but I'm you know I'm
yipped up, okay, cocaine, oh shit, and I
had the sensor yeah sorry.
This is this old me, but then
then the other guy in the room, one of the third party you're in a two person
party. I'm at a it's like three people. It's like three. It's more of a
kickback. This is more of a kickback. All right,
and then this third person is like, oh wait, oh Peter, you haven't seen
aqua teen hunger force. Oh dude, you gotta watch aqua teen hunger force, and
so I'm on stimulants. You're on drugs and then this guy's forcing me to watch
aqua teen hunger force. We're not look I had I had my phase with that show in
like sixth grade. When I was like damn, this is holy crap. That is like
McDonald's come to life,
but to be you know in your thirties, you don't want to be you don't want to be
around any sort of situation where people are like
dude, you got to watch awkward.
That when I was in college, I we had this like literature project where it
was like do a
write something that is in the same form as something that already exists. So it
was a very broad thing and I got paired up with these two guys and they were
with like let's write an episode of Rick and Morty and but the guy said you have
to go do six hours of logged research and everybody else just like faked it. Wait
is this is in college? Yeah. Okay. And everybody else just faked it just wrote
down like read this for six hours. Which college? The one we went to? In Boston.
Yeah. Okay. And these guys were like yeah at Emerson and these guys were like we
have to wait let's see let's use this opportunity to watch six hours of Rick
and Morty in the middle of a Wednesday. So I went over to his house and just
just watch Rick and Morty for six hours and they were like taking notes like
okay. So Rick is Rick has blue hair. Rick is a bit of a bastard and Morty's
kind of a pus just doing that the entire time. It was really, really did they
figure it out by the end. We wrote probably one of the better
Rick and Morty specs grips of that class. Are you trying to like turn it
in? I mean I've submitted it to pretty much everybody. I mean I showed it to
Dan Harmon. He loved it. Hopefully, we'll move forward with it pretty soon.
left it in his mail box. Yep, I just put it there a little seal it with a kiss
and whatever else he likes probably a
condom with a hole poked in it or whatever.
I don't really know what he does,
but he seems like a normal guy. Jared Leto was yeah, all that kind of thing.
Yeah, I mean Dan Harmon, if you're putting together a gift package for him,
you do the condom, you do maybe fifty to sixty tiny bottles of Jack Daniels and
maybe a picture of your mom and then I don't know if he did he quit drinking or
no, I don't know. I don't quit Rick and Morty. He was he's still he's still
there. He's still there. He still does. Rick and Morty. You can tell based on
the story structure that he's still behind the story circle of it all. You
can tell that he's behind it. He was a very functional alcoholic. He was yeah,
I mean. Rick perhaps something of a self insert. Oh my god. Wait a fucking
And he's got blue hair just like Dan Harmon.
So which one is Justin's?
Which character is Justin Roiland's self-insert then?
The dog.
Brian?
Yeah, Brian.
For sure it's Brian.
It's gotta be Brian.
Why do they never do a collab?
There's no, there is a dog, there is a dog, oh I thought you were just asking why don't
they ever have a dog in the family.
I did just remember, I do like when in one of the Justin Roiland DMs, when he's doing,
he's being a pedophile and doing Chinese voice. Yeah, yeah, doing Chinese typing.
Yeah, he's like
he's
I think he, I think he did like jare bait or something. Yeah, he said
something like to that extent. That is like he told he's yeah, he was like,
you know, he said me so horny to a child
to a child who has no frame of reference for what that is, doesn't know what
that is from this is like this guy's not that good at typing for a writer. He's
not that
this is the I'm Atlanta drunk. Yeah, yeah, all with one kid. Yeah, one little
kid. He said, Oh yeah, that's right. He said, I'm Atlanta drunk. I'm Atlanta
drunk.
With that actually
Drake said that if he said, I'm Atlanta drunk. Oh my God, we'd be saying that
It's way different if that's a DM from Champagne Poppy.
That is true. I mean, nobody would get mad at Drake for those exact messages, I don't think.
I think he'd be fine. People would have been like, "Oh, he's so cringe."
Oh, ew.
"Oh, he's so desperate."
He's giving me the ick.
He's seriously giving me the ick.
This pedophile is giving me the ick.
But Marvin's room is just so good.
Yeah, being a pedophile is a red flag.
Yeah.
When are we going to link you up with Drake? I feel like he'd love your ass.
I know, I was definitely trying.
Drake, if you're listening right now.
I was trying in my early 20s.
Oh, yeah.
It was a lot of...
Mmm, yeah.
That was definitely...
Despicable Me era brand.
Yeah, oh, yeah.
Yeah, I remember that, man.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, it grew it out.
Yeah, you were pretty...
You had to have been close to getting with Drake.
Who knows?
Who knows what was going on at the...
Imagine if you did at that age, though.
At the YOLO estate.
Would you?
The timeline would have been way to if Drake if Drake I don't think
wise you out.
Yeah, if Drake flies you out and just flies you out to his house and you guys
just like play basketball for one day, is that a little bit insulting that he
doesn't try to have sex with you? Maybe yeah, a little bit just a tiny bit. He
gives you that that what's that drink he's always talking about on the have you
heard of that? This he has a drink that he invented or his friend invented and
it's tequila and passion fruit and it's called Anda.
And it comes in a big wine glass and he always swirls with it.
And he says he's... Someone asked him how many he's drank in his life.
He said probably close to a million, which is an amazing, amazing line.
He's had a million drinks.
Did you see that video today?
No. What came out with him?
He was like... It's something like, this is all the underachievers tweeting
leaders, you know, make me sick to my stomach.
Nobody hates fake people more than fucking Drake.
Nobody. Nobody.
Nobody hates fake people more than Drake.
I think he's being, I don't think that he invented this drink.
I think that some...
His fucking friend invented it. I said he invented it.
His friend invented it. He says my friend invented it.
There's definitely an old Mexican guy that made this millions of years ago.
They didn't have passion fruit millions of years ago,
especially not in God damn Mexico. Sorry to say God damn Mexico, Jimmy.
Yeah. Sorry Julio.
Yeah. That's, that's...
Maybe Julio invented it.
You're like a, you're actually, you're a Drake guy.
I'm a Drake guy?
You like Drake.
Yeah.
Patrick hadn't listened to Drake and then you were like,
you got to take care of him.
Yeah, we talked about this, I think the
second to last time.
I showed you take care in our 20s?
Yeah.
That's crazy.
Yeah, when I was like 20, 21.
I had a breakup.
I was living at 22 star.
You were opening at
Laff Boston.
Oh, yeah.
And then you and Cameron came.
We had a fun weekend.
With Gavin.
Yeah, Gavin, Matt.
Very fun weekend.
And I remember that weekend, you were like,
"Wow, I just listened to Take Care of Me."
I just started listening to Drake at that time.
Had you just gone through a breakup?
I think so.
Because that's why I liked that album when I was a kid.
I think that's why.
Because I went through a breakup.
I was with this girl for two and a half months.
And we broke up.
And I started listening to Drake.
I always thought Drake was a homo thug.
that we used to call him. I thought Drake was a homo, and so I didn't like him
because he sang about his feelings and about what he was eating. I was like,
"Shut up, man. Sing about killing people or math." Yeah, they were at the press
and play and you were saying pause. Yes, well, we didn't have pause back then.
If we did, we definitely had pause back then. We, I didn't. Whites had no
pause. They didn't know. Whites had not heard a pause. We had no homo. They
didn't know about Cameron saying it ten years ago. No, I mean, I guess I knew
about camera, but just like purple haze. That was the no homo era.
This was no homo. This was fully no homo. So if you said anything,
you'd have to say no homo or else you wouldn't get paused, but you would
go, you would get a what the fuck? You'd say, "What the hell? You're being
gay." That's what we used to say instead of pause. You sound like a gay
wad. We used to have, "What the bloody hell? You're acting like a gay guy."
You've lost the plot, mate. You've lost the plot, you turned gay. You've
absolutely lost the plot. Yeah, we used to have that. Yeah, it's giving gay
got it. Nowadays, they probably do that. They say that now, but yeah, the only
rap I listened to before Drake, it was all about either
crime or math, math and science. I would listen to, I was into that kind of. Were
you listening to MC Chris?
No, he liked MC Chris. I did. Oh yeah. I thought MC Chris was wack, dude. I, oh,
it was a way worse nerdcore rapper. It was MC, too. Name, I can't remember. MC
- No, dude, it was a different guy.
- Yeah, I remember.
- MC, oh my God, MC front a lot.
You remember him?
- Why was it always MC?
- Was he sort of in,
'cause I remember MC Chris had some sort of
ties to Aqua Teen Hunger Force.
- Yeah, MC Chris was the baby character,
the one that's like, I like candy.
- The Moon and I.
- You know that one, remember that one?
It's like the-- - One of the Moon and I.
- No, no, it was the episode where it's like,
or MC Pee Pants, right?
- Mm, yes.
- Isn't that MC Chris?
I remember he has a song with Childish Gambino, Mystery Team soundtrack.
Wow.
Yes.
Filmed in my hometown.
This is something that me and, I feel like me and Patrick really connected early on via
like this fucking useless media ephemera.
Trivia stuff that you both know.
Do you also know every actor's name from every movie and what other movies they've been in?
Not so much.
So what do you tell them to?
It was mostly me and him saying, "Do you remember that Childish Gambino song where he raps over
two weeks by Grizzly Bears?"
Oh, okay.
Member Berries.
Oh, did you watch a lot of Wonder Shows?
We were fully Member Berries.
You guys did Member Berries back and forth with each other.
Well, that's good.
Member Berries.
Yeah.
Yeah, it was us talking about Wonder Shows and that fucking I Am Not a Rapper by Childish
Gambino.
Crazy, yeah.
That is an amazing list.
I have that on my family desktop.
Oh, yeah.
to this day. I wonder if he scrubbed that from the internet. No, because it's definitely
that shit that he was rapping over. It's like, yeah, man, I can tell you're not a rapper.
You're not even using any boom bap beats. You're not even using boom bap. You're not
even you don't sound like a mortal technique to me. No. Yeah. You're like this doesn't
have any of the core elements. Where are the five pillars in this? What the hell is this
crap? Five pillars. I'm barely even hearing him seeing. Let alone knowledge. There's no
no no emcee breaking graffiti graffiti be buying. That's the one I that's I think
that's the pillar. I put my most points and a lot logic and reason, logic and
reason knowledge. Let's see there's got to be more
Islam is long. Well, that's that would be wrapped in a knowledge. Yeah, that's
true. You wouldn't know about that. What was the name of the guy who came up with
these Africa Bombada? Yeah, which is an amazing last name wasn't he and an even
better first name Africa Bombada. Was he a diddler or is that but it was guys?
Oh, okay, so it's like
who know so it's worse yeah, because men are
persecuted and our lives are ruined. What is it like being a man in sunny Los
Angeles where the feminists are rain rain supreme? They destroy your life. I got a
phone call yesterday that I ignored from my old teacher or my my old not teacher,
old boss from when I used to work at the UCB on Sunset.
Amy Poehler? Oh, wow.
She called me and I'm really, really scared that she's going to leave me a
voicemail or something.
Wait, what was the... You don't know what it was?
I didn't answer. It scared me so bad.
What if it was a congratulatory call?
I have a strong feeling it wouldn't be.
By the way, UCB Sunset, have you guys talked about this?
No. Not to get too in the weeds about it.
A little bit, not too much.
But it was like, it no longer exists.
Yeah, it's gone.
But it was like in like an old hospital.
Yeah.
No way.
No, like felt super sterile. It was a very bizarre place.
I didn't go there. The setup was bad. I never went there.
I think that we walked by it and like we walked by it on the way to El Pollo
Loco, which I was like, Oh,
El Pollo Loco was right next door. El Pollo Loco, pretty good. Yeah.
I used to go there. I used to go to UCB every single day.
I worked there behind the desk. I would sign people up for classes.
It really felt awful. You'd send the lambs out.
to know that they're going to get hurt. Yeah, some kind of way. Yeah, just
in order to play. They're about to get in the worst two year relationship with an
older man. It's just going to be so fucking taught them. Yeah, exactly. It's
going to be just a bad, bad situation. And then I would go and I would go to
subway and I would eat a rotisserie chicken sandwich every single day.
Did that rotisserie chicken rotisserie chicken at subway. The rotisserie chicken
had just come out, man. I didn't know this was on the menu. I think it's gone now. I would
go no cheese, rotisserie chicken, tons of veggies, veg it up. Oh my god. Sometimes I
haven't scooped the bread. They hated me for that. Yeah. Can I get it scooped? Not at Subway,
man. Not at fucking Subway. No, come on, man. I don't know. I feel like when you walk into
a Subway, all the employees are at your whim. Me? Yeah. You think I have Subway King? You,
I've seen you in Subway before, bro. You have seen me. I run, I've, oh my god. The way that
you asked for bell peppers. I've never seen it's like it's like when a
Rottweiler see somebody they don't like. Yeah I'm growing.
"SATCH BELL PEPPERS!"
Bell peppers please.
Did you know about Quiznos?
Yes.
There's only 150 of them.
I know dude they went away.
That was the first time I ever had guacamole guys.
Really?
It was Quiznos?
Quiznos man.
Wow.
Guacamole.
The first experience I ever had with guacamole was at Quiznos.
And people, I mean we had never heard of this shit.
I forget about the fucking... There's one person on this sound effect that is
screaming so loud. On the applause thing? I forget about it every single time.
Yeah! Yeah, it's so good. Yeah, that was the first time I had... Nobody had
ever heard of guacamole. What was it on? It was on a sandwich, man.
A turkey sandwich. No, what was the sandwich? A veggie sandwich. Wait,
then it was in the... Do you line up? At Quiznos? Yeah. Is it the same
- You've never been to one?
- It's been years.
- So the Quiznos experience,
the reason why Quiznos isn't around anymore,
they were the first people to do toasted subs.
Subway used to not have toasted subs.
Now, they're trying to toast my fucking tuna sandwich.
I'm about to shit holes.
- That was the key difference.
- They were the only ones, that was their motto.
- And then Subway, once they started toasting,
it was the game changed.
- It was fucking over.
- And they had the sponge monkeys.
- What's that?
You don't remember that? We like the moon, we like the subs.
Uh-huh. They had those.
Yeah, those are funny guys.
Those are really funny.
What the hell is a sponge monkey?
Yeah, it was a video.
It was a viral video back in the day.
They did this in the same time as Jared.
They were doing sponge monkey?
That was, this was their competitor to Jared for a second.
Well, yeah, Patrick does this thing where every time I'm in town, he's always like,
"Dude, you got to come over.
We're going to hit a sprite gravity bong.
I'm going to show you all of the Quiznos sponge monkeys."
there's only one. I believe that. There's only one, but I keep it on a loop
because I like it so much. He's cracking up. He's losing his shit every time.
They like the subs. They love the subs almost as much as the moon. A couple
of weeks ago, me and Cameron at Pat's house, we were- what were we watching
that you were loudly playing bass guitar through the entire thing? We were
watching some TV show. We were watching- we were watching
Family Guy, Most Racist Moments compilation. Oh, that's enough. Family Guy,
Most Racist Moments compilation. You guys just like came over my... I think we
got lunch. Pat amp in the amp on, turns on the amp, plugs it in, sits next to
us,
what's louder than the TV?
No, I was playing... That's not what I was playing. You tried. I did. And failed.
I tried to play... I tried to play Tool. I tried to play Tool,
Schism for you guys.
I do wanna...
just speaking of Family Guy, I don't know if I ever showed you that.
I've showed you my old my old like forum post from when I was like, I've seen
the one. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Grinch alert. I genuinely I was in a shiver down my spine.
I was thinking that you were going to show me just like like, oh yeah, I made
this on the train on the way over and it's like Family Guy yourself.
Like one of those things.
This is kind of a line.
Yeah. But this does this is my first ever post on that website.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Toonzone.net, I was 13 years old.
And this is a subject line,
"I went to the carnival recently, dot, dot, dot."
- Wow, I like it already.
- So, Family Guy does come up.
Yesterday, I went to the carnival.
While I was walking around, I saw plenty of games.
At those games, many character-based stuff toys were there,
including cartoon characters such as SpongeBob,
Superman, Nemo, Batman, and a few of the Simpsons.
But the character with the most toys was,
that that that Stewie Griffin
they're an adult animation. Yeah, I know. I was like bitch. I was really
concerned about this. They range from massive to very small. Brian, Peter, Meg,
Chris and Lois also had toys. I even saw- Lois? I even saw plenty of toddlers
with Brian dolls, which there's no way. No. That's- You lied. There's no way.
You lied. I had to have been lying. Yeah. You had to- I've never seen a Lois
I've seen one. I understand that many adults and teens go to the carnival too, so I was
not very surprised. However, many of the games with the Griffin Clan...
The Griffin Clan is crazy! I love when, like, it still gets me every single
time when somebody talks about the
Family Guy characters as if they're
like, like family friends, you
know?
You're an amazing writer as a
child.
Oh, because I also wanted people to
think I was older than I was.
That comes across.
Yeah.
Had a sign saying 12 and under.
I was somewhat surprised by this.
I also recently saw an action figure
featuring Jasper, which I forgot
about Jasper.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yeah. Replacement Brian.
With the message on the package eight
and up. I know that Family Guy gets
wonderful ratings from the nine to fourteen demographic, but wouldn't Fox
want to hide that fact rather than embracing it? Oh, my God, that's crazy.
So no, I somebody you're trying to sound older in those posts, but you sound
subject matter. You accidentally you you were trying to sound like ten years
older, but you accidentally like sounded thirty years older. You sound like a
Christian. No, I there's like one there's one post where I'm talking about
24 and I was like, wow, like I love 24. It's a great topic to discuss at your
job.
That's what you thought.
Water cooler talk.
Jack
got up to last night. You see the enhanced interrogation? Jack
No, these like old forum posts of mine. I looked, I was like, I was looking
through them and I feel like I beat autism. Yeah, I think maybe I just, I
I mean, you at least...
You zipped right past it.
Well, I don't know if zipped right past it is exactly what we're...
Zipped or dived right in.
Yeah, you dove right in. And maybe you've gone to the shallow end of the pool.
Right, exactly.
But yeah, but you were definitely high diving into the 30 foot.
I wish that there were still my forum posts.
I found another one real good where I was talking about the new episode of American
Dad.
Okay.
And there's one part where I'm like, "It airs at 8.30 right after Seth's other baby, Family
funny guy. What am I talking? Seth's other baby. Those are his babies.
It's crazy, man.
It was really disappointing for me as a
Seth's other baby. It is, dude. Yeah, it's unmistakably his baby.
That's his baby.
His only baby is Stewie or Rallo. When I was a kid being, I remember being a
little bit disappointed when I found out that Seth MacFarlane was not like a
fat guy. Well, not like an ugly libertarian like the South Park guys.
Yeah. Like finding out that he was like a theater kid, made me a little like,
"Oh, well, fuck this guy." You can see yourself... That's the thing,
it's like you can see yourself hanging out with Matt and Trey. You can envision
it... It's all I think about. And it's all...
Oh my God, I can't even tell you the dreams where I just... I wow them
with my Cartman every night. Every night I fall asleep to a dream where I am. I'm
hanging out with Matt and Trey and I wake up to a nightmare where I'm not or
you're not even in the same state of my bed. Well, they, that's, you know, but
Seth, it is funny, it is funny that Seth MacFarlane, who was like, you know,
prior to Family Guy, he was, you know, he's working, he's like a storyboarder
on Johnny Bravo, whatever. He gets on, he gets, he gets on Family Guy, he gets
the, you know, once he got the Family Guy back, he was like, "Finally, my excuse
to be a lounge singer.
Finally, my excuse to
get real. Do this snap. To do it like Frank. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah, that really
is an interesting
next step. Yeah. That's not what I would think if I had done that. I mean,
they were pushing him front of camera hard. He did the fucking Goldies. He was
the roast master. He hosted the Oscars. Oh, is that what it was? He was the
roast master for a lot of different roasts. Yeah. He hosted SNL. Frank Ocean
as the musical guest.
- Oh yeah.
- But Seth, you know, you talk Frank with Seth,
he's more of a Sinatra man than an Ocean man.
- Yeah.
- You know, that's the thing about Seth.
- That's right.
Ocean blue eyes Sinatra, that's what he likes.
Not so much Frank.
- And yeah, I remember he hosted the Oscars
and he did that, he got in trouble
'cause he did that song that was like,
"We Saw Your Boobs."
- Yep.
- He did a what?
- He did a song where he named every actress in the room
that had a nude scene that year.
I was like, we saw your boobs.
- That's borderline disrespectful.
- You know?
- Mm-hmm.
- But--
- Strike one, Seth.
- You know, Seth, you get tired of it.
- Strike one.
- Strike two, you killed Brian.
What the hell was that?
- Three strikes, you're out, buddy.
- You fucking stupid bastard.
- You better not fuck up the Orville this season.
- We got him back.
- You better not fuck up the Orville.
- You fuck up the Orville?
- Yeah.
- I'ma kill you, man.
- We're coming, we're coming for you.
We're coming for you.
- That's how it is.
- I did want to make sure that you guys know
they did, they brought Brian back. Yeah. What? We know they brought Brian back.
I know. Yeah, they brought him back. I know they brought him back, but
that's a prank you don't pull. Yeah. That's a prank you do not pull. You
wouldn't do that with my own mother, would you, Seth McFarland? You wouldn't
beat her to death with a car and then say, "Just kidding, she's here.
Here's a time machine that brings your mom back." And I would say Brian was
magnitude's greater importance in my life than my mother growing up. Oh,
Everyone says that.
That's where I got all my jokes from and my outfits.
And my love for dirty martinis.
Yeah, it's where I learned what a martini was and fell in love.
I'm constantly doing this.
I'm imagining a martini in my head.
That's the Seth self insert.
Oh my God.
He is the...
You're right.
Brian is like, he's the one voice of reason in the room.
He's a smart guy.
He doesn't have a fucking one of these dog shit New England accents.
He's well read.
Yep.
And he fucks hot chicks.
sex and he wants to fuck his own mom.
He only has sex with white women though.
And that's a problem Seth.
And that's another thing I want to talk to you about.
Strike three. Strike three Seth.
Hook up Brian with a black queen my friend.
We're gonna need some sisters.
Please surround Brian.
Seth.
Seth. Seth come on.
Seth you're neglecting your babies.
Come on Seth.
Your baby is failing man.
Tell me what is it like to be back in the greatest city in the world and away from
the worst? Yes, I love dude. I know. Yeah, I got in today earlier. Yeah, but and I
came straight here. Isn't it amazing? I took a blade helicopter right to the
bottom. I was Tom. I want to take one of those so bad. I've Yeah, but I can't do.
I know that I will die like Kobe the exact same way with your daughter in tow.
No, come on. Talk about them. Well, you're done. I can't. It's not talking
talking about his daughter you fucking bastard.
I don't have a daughter.
You're talking about the goat and
talking about his dead daughter.
Kobe Bryant.
Los Angeles Lakers.
Colby.
You're crazy.
Can you turn my headphones up?
Which one are you?
That's me. That was way too loud.
Is this you?
You have hearing issues.
I do because I thought you said Colby.
just had a fucking problem, but it's nice being here. Yes, it is nice being here.
I don't it's L A is the L A. Thank you. It's bad. It got bad. What are you doing
every day? Yes, you wake up, you go to air one by of what the crap is wrong
with the price of the smoothie. There is a new fifty dollar rotisserie chicken
Olivia Rodrigo smoothie at air. What the heck? Let me guess. It's pink. Yeah,
no, it's purple. Oh shit. Well, it's the same. Somebody's not keeping up with
the lore. I have a in it at all. No, is that the fellow half Filipino?
Yeah.
Ube. I like the Ube pie. Oh,
Jollibee. I like. Oh, yeah. Oh, the in the little. Yeah. The hollow hollow.
Yeah. The pie. It's the pie. It's like a fast. That's a mango pie. They have
an Ube one. They have an Ube. Yeah, bitch. They do. It's I haven't. I
really haven't been back there in so long because the only one that I know
of is in Times Square. Yeah, it's not worth it. I think there's more. There's
probably more the chicken sand. What huge, huge, huge fan of the chicken.
Oh, it's so good. It's oftentimes left out of that is a really good chicken
sandwich. They put chicken sandwich. It's not pickles. It's jalapenos. And so
you hit, you hit the air one. Yeah. Next thing, let me guess, 10 to 12
auditions. You're going out for the new, the office reboot. They have you
playing Jim. Obviously, you're doing reads kind of silent mug into the camera.
they say it's a pass for now, but you might have a chance. You might have a
chance. You might be the AI stand in for John Crusier. You are our favorite, but
the producers won't like it. One day we might get you in that late season
Clark Duke. Yes. I was thinking about Clark Duke earlier because I saw a
Clark Duke type of guy and you don't see them as often anymore. I would say
I've only ever seen one on TV. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No, but you know the type,
you know the type, the Clark Duke, like think about Clark Duke, think about a
Clark Duke clone with like a guy with glass. He looked like glasses.
Like a guy who looks almost exactly like Clark. Like a not that like a kind of
fat guy with glasses. Kind of fat guy with glasses and like the long swept
bangs. You don't see it's like a guy it was like a it was like a man in. You
don't see that anymore. It was like a man from 2012 perfectly preserved in
amber is what I mean. That's interesting. A guy with glasses. A guy with thick
glasses. You know you know what I'm trying to say. Like guy like Weezer
looking at. It's a Weezer looking type of guy.
I would say you see that all the time.
I see these guys every day.
I think I've been in this damn city too long that
I don't see them. Well, because it's all like Carhartt.
Yeah. It's all Carhartt guys.
It's all these hipsters.
These Carhartt guys jumping up on roofs.
Who knows what the fuck they're doing. They're using
hammers and nails, looking like assholes.
You don't see too many of the
guy who exclusively shops at Old Navy
in this neighborhood.
The other thing about these Carhartt guys
in Bushwick. Yeah, talk about it. They can't work a toolbox, but it's a bunch
of tools looking for box. You know, that's my observation about all that.
If you ask me...
Yeah, body. Today, I don't really use Twitter anymore, so... So you gotta get
it out now. I'm gonna go through my drafts. The drafts.
I like that. That's what this show is for. Yeah. Today, I was wearing... I
I had to go change my sister in law's tire. She had a fire had to put a spare
on it, miss the gym because of that. I'm so sorry. He's a fucking tool box. I
know a little bit. I was changing the tire, though, and I got maybe one second
into even putting the jack up yeah and a guy runs over me, grabs my shoulders and
goes you're going to fuck up the car man. You put the jack in the wrong place and
I was like I know I'm not I'm just starting the jack and he was like you're
fuck the whole thing up man fucking up badly, and I was like I know what I'm
doing man get away from here, and then I looked and I was wearing this outfit and
I realized Dickey double knee, the clogs, the clogs with no laces on this guy
thought that I
was a hip stuff. Hell no and I not this guy dude and I wanted to say no bro. I
he was already long gone, but I wanted to chase after him on his Uber. Each
I'm not a hipster. I'm not a hipster. I know how to hang a painting. I just
saw the TV, you bastard. I hate passion. But luckily, he doesn't make very much
money
'cause he's an Uber Eats driver. So I win in the end. You got him. Yeah. So in
the end, "Okay, change all the tires you want, buddy. You're not getting paid
for 'em. Fuck you." That is funny that he just instinctively was like,
"You're gonna ruin this." He didn't even see what I was doing. He just ran
open up to me, touched me and wanted to tell me that I saw that's an assault. I
could have sued him. I could have ruined his entire family. I should have killed
him. He's crossing a boundary. You should have taken the fucking handle out of the
jack. If we were in a better state, I would have. Yeah, but all of a sudden,
you should have taken the jack, put him on top of it, get him real tall, right?
And then made him and then tipped it over or maybe wait for a bird or a bird
that hit him. Bird of prey to come by. You guys see the thing Eric Adams said
today that was so funny? I did not see. Well, this is going to be so dated when
that comes up. Eric Adams, this is come out, it's backlogs of probably
sometime like January. We've got he'll say something funny. He'll say something
funny. It's okay. Eric Adams said he did some interview today and they were like
what what is what is it like being the mayor of New York and he's like it's a
most amazing city in the world. Every day you could wake up and a plane could fly
into the World Trade Center or you can have the best slice of pizza of your
life. This city is truly something he said every day you could wake up and a
he could fly into our trade center.
(laughing)
That is so, he is such a fucking beast, dude.
- Dude, it's so sick.
- He has to run for president, please.
- Please.
- Please, Eric Adams, if you're listening, please run.
- That video of him, where I think it's him
like showing off places in your house
to look for like weapons that your kids could be hiding.
- I haven't seen that one.
- Oh my God, it's so good.
- Where does he posit that you could find them?
- It's like--
- Why do they make all these--
How many kids are around? I think if your kid had a gun, you'd know you'd be
suspicious.
Could you pull that up?
They'd make it known.
Because it's like, how the hell is a kid gonna like, it's like, like they're
hiding it behind like picture frames and stuff. And it's like him just putting
a picture frame down. Look up like, it's called like Eric Adams weapons. Yeah,
gun safety.
Behind a like a fucking haunted house.
Yeah, it's like, it's like his house is a haunted house.
Here's where your kids could be hiding ghosts.
Oh yeah, this is him.
well yeah wait what does he have there?
a bag? a book? on a bookshelf?
yeah that was pretty much all like that
I'm asking you to join me in this crusade
you may be using an illegal drug
or carrying an illegal gun
but you also have to protect
the members of the household
I love his setup here this fucking tiny ass
little Michael Scott style
flat screen TV
yeah this is a bad TV and you're the mayor
you're the fucking mayor
doors, your house is open to inspection by your house and the members of your house.
The message is, I may be hiding. For instance, a gun could be hidden inside a jewelry box.
Look at the various colognes, perfumes, and photos and pictures. In addition to a book,
something simple as a crack pipe
*laughter*
something very simple
it's so fucking sick
yeah
cameras try to determine what's
taking place
behind a picture frame you can find bullets
*laughter*
doesn't mean the child is carrying a gun
no
where there's smoke there's possible fire
where there's a bullet there's possibly
a gun
That's real shit. Bullets are kind of the breadcrumb. Oh, absolutely. That's what you know a gun is around. Oh, it's the doll, right.
What the f-
Oh, well.
(laughter)
Yeah, he's got weed hidden in the baby doll.
Yeah, this is all, this all would be a problem in my house. Oh, absolutely. My kids will own nothing.
Mm-hmm. No, did you guys- Well, you have, you said, you said that if, if your son comes home with a jewelry box, he's gonna have a different, a different problem.
he's going to have some real problems. He said there better be a gun in that.
I would be better not be any so happy if my son brought home a jewelry box. I
went, oh my God, now open it up. Oh, twenty sixteen. Yeah, okay, all right.
You know what? Now you're speaking my language. You put your hand in full AR
fifteen and pull it. And then I sit him down and I'm like, listen, son, you
don't have to hide this kind of thing from me, okay? Look, I got one myself.
You pull it out of your pocket. Yeah, I carry. AR. Yeah, mine's not in a
fucking jewelry box, you freak cake.
- My son, my jewelry wearing son.
Did you guys, when you were growing up,
did you guys have a locked door policy?
- No, I shared a bedroom with my two brothers.
- Oh, I did, I did.
I did have, well, oh, like that you couldn't lock the door.
No, well, yes, yes until I got to a certain age.
But then-- - Jack off time.
- Yeah, but once it was jack off time,
the problem was that I had two doors.
I was like in the I was in the I was in the basement.
You have a warning. I was in the basement.
And then I had like I had one door here and one door there.
And so if if the knock is coming from both, it's hard to it was hard to jack.
Oh, you had two doors not to get into your room, but a door on either.
No, like two separate doors.
So yeah, this bedroom got it.
But yeah, no, we I do remember,
especially in the computer room, they were like, keep.
Yeah, we had a I had a.
Oh, fuck. What was it called? I had a program on my computer. It was called
Safe Eyes, and it blocked out pornography, PG rated R movies,
everything that was bad for children. And there was no way around this. It
was the most strong firewall known to man, and I could only watch porn on my
mom's iPod Touch.
For years, I would ask my mom if I could listen to some music, bring the
iPod Touch into my bedroom and shoot jizz on it.
And then I would hand it right back to her and I say, enjoy your run.
Enjoy your run.
Yeah. Spill some ropes.
I would blast just pitiful child ropes just directly. She wouldn't even notice.
Was it down? Did somebody spill Sprite on my phone?
Oh, the iPod touch had internet.
It had wifi. So you could go on the, was there a browser on the iPod touch?
Yeah. Oh, cause it's just an iPhone without the phone. Right.
Because actually, no, I do remember Jamel, my co-host, one of my best friends, he
used to have an iPod Touch with Wi-Fi instead of a phone.
So you could only contact him if he was like at a McDonald's.
Adam told me that the other day.
He didn't have a phone for like 10 years.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
What the fuck? That's crazy.
Walking around. He was like, he would just take the bus everywhere.
You couldn't get in touch with him.
And then he once he was in inside of a McDonald's, then it was communication
time. But yeah, so back to your Jack off journey, you would get on your mom's iPod Touch and
then just like watch porno.
Just watch everything man, everything under the sun.
I do remember, I feel like, well I'm like 5 years older than you guys right?
I think so, something like that.
5 or 6? AOL at all?
Yeah, I was at the tail end of it, or I got on the computer pretty young. I think I was
I was using like AOL instant messenger when I was like six.
We there was I had parental controls, but I remember that I could see AOL
keyword swimsuit.
And so I could see, you know, Heidi Klum.
Oh my God.
Whoa.
Pull this up.
Pull this up right now.
Heidi Klum. What's the other big breasted lady with a large bust?
What is her name?
Who jumped around in a bikini?
Kate Upton.
Upton this think I've talked about I ever seen in my life when I was a kid. I
think I talked about it before, but there was a boy in my
jubilee. Can you Google Kate Upton hot, please? There was a there's a boy in my
class named Ed
porno. You're getting pranked man. I like that. It's called gay male tube
tube.
Tube is
tube is a pretty gay word for penis. I think a gay males to
oh, okay. So you're saying it's a penis only. It's it's also it's a it's kind of
a genius name for a gay porn website because tube is a double entendre. I
would say if a vagina is much closer to a tube than a penis. Yeah. A tube has an
inside. A penis has no inside. Yeah. Well, it has a very small one. I'm glad
I'm making you think. That's what I try to do. Oh, but the speak I was talking
I was in this like study lab class that I got a credit for because I had adult
a d or child, HD, ADHD, because I was a child, HD, I had child. That's your
website. You like going on.
I had
hold on.
There's this boy in my class named Ed Upton and my buddy one day was like Hey
Ed, look, it's a picture of your sister and pulled up like a picture of Kate
Upton in a magazine and he's like she's not my sister,
thought I wish she was my
I remember
yeah,
little boys are awesome. Why do you wish the g is your sister ed? Just kind of
just made everyone make fun of him more
like oh you want to have sex with your fucking sister. Okay, to be fair,
no, you don't want to have sex with your sister in let I mean bit of your
sister's Kate Upton. You might
you her brother definitely wanted to have sex with her. Yeah, there's no
down my mind. Well what if her brother looks exactly like her with short hair
and I'm saying with the boobs? Then I'd have sex with him too.
Yeah, was that the question? That's the question. David Upton is Kate Upton's
brother. So this guy... Do you know... wait is that true? This is him. If that's her brother right there, the third one...
one. He's a dead ringer gave for twenty seven years
when he quit. Wait, he became a wait. Did they give him the outfit?
The veteran decorated? Wait, I like that. He is wearing a Navy outfit.
That's funny.
Gay.
Jesus. Oh my God, John. Yeah, he did quit. Oh my God. Yeah, thank you.
Well, that's your John fifteen rocks. What's John is John fifteen like a
passage in the Bible that says don't be gay
because there's a whole section of LGBTQ on this website.
Home Philippines. Let's see. Philippines is very Christian, yes?
Yeah, yeah, Catholic. Catholic, yeah, that's what it is. Bare fruit,
confession. Well, this is just a bunch of
news stories. Well, it looks like there's lists on this website.
"Panoi Atheists Doing..."
Have you ever been to the Philippines, Brandon? No, not yet.
I need to go before you pass. I gotta go. I gotta go before I pass. I feel like you need to go while you're young, man.
I know. You think you may fall in love with a bride while you're in the Philippines and come home make your parents very happy?
Could.
Another fun thought experiment.
Yeah, wait, I actually am liking the sound of this. I think that you would blend in. I mean
culturally, I feel like
You're already there pretty much
Lakes like are you referring to like swagger? Pino? Thank you. Just you said so over there
I what's that is that still going on over there? I hope it
California the guys I play pool with we're like these guys were not rich and all of them had like a Rolex
Crazy outfits. Yeah, they still were into belt buckles. Were you playing were you doing like Pinot exclusive?
It was me and my brother and eight Filipino guys on a pool team, on a billiards team.
And we played eight ball, nine ball, APA.
It was Rob Schneider.
Rob Schneider vibes, yeah.
Joe Coy.
Joe Coy, of course, the GOAT.
The Hollywood.
That's the OG, man.
That's my daddy.
That's the OG.
That's my movie daddy.
That's your father.
There's a scene in that film where he does, for whatever, the pastor of the church is
he's like come up here and do some stand up. That happens a lot of your and then
he like just does stand up at the church. Is he being dirty? No, no, no, hell, no,
thank fuck. It is he doing Joseph. This is a family film. He's doing Joseph and
the movie made well over its budget. No, it was yeah. This is a this movie was
not successful commercially or critically, but critic, but Lord knows my
you know the but with your family, my mom, my mom's family loved it and that's
That's what counts.
That is important.
We talked about him.
You got the mommy Oscar.
It can't all be, you know, a lot of the stuff I'm doing is for guys like us.
You know, you gotta do something for your mom.
Mommy and daddy.
One for her.
You gotta do something for your mom.
I mean, did you bring her the red carpet premiere?
I did, actually.
Really?
That's adorable.
No, this is actually, yeah, she was really excited to meet Joe Koy.
And my dad got to meet Adam Carolla.
- Oh, hell yeah.
- That is the white guy, Joe Coy.
- Yeah, well, 'cause he was,
'cause my dad, you know,
I remember my dad would watch "The Man Show"
when I was a kid and then flip the channel real quick
when I would walk in the room.
The juggies are--
- You don't want--
- They're all trampling, he's gotta change the channel.
And then I finally got the opportunity to say,
Father, allow me to introduce you to Mr. Adam Carolla.
My movie uncle.
Wait, why was he in the movie?
No, he's just hanging out.
He's hanging out.
I don't know Adam Carolla, but he was there that night.
I think a lot about what showbiz thing
I could either take my dad to
or person I could introduce him to
that he would care about at all.
And I think it would have to be
some kind of celebrity golf game.
I could maybe, if I could become a massive movie star
and then introduce him to John Daly,
I think that would be massive.
I think that might be the only guy.
I think my dad would not be impressed
by anybody that I could show him.
- I think that my mom and dad--
- You've had your dad on here, right?
- No, I had my uncle on.
- You had your uncle on.
- Yeah, my uncle, Matthew DeVita, yeah.
- My parents, I think, would get excited
about any celebrity they would meet.
- Really?
- I mean, Colin Connor was on here.
he told the story of like, like my mom was backstage in Boston and was like, I'm
surprised that I laughed.
You took that as her being impressed.
She was,
she was so just excited to meet somebody that has been on TV that she was like
shaking his hand and stuff.
At midnight.
They're bringing it back.
They're bringing it back. I'm trying to get,
I'm trying to get those points again, man.
You should email, do my points carry over?
When you guys were in diapers. I've been doing this a long time, man.
Did you win at midnight?
No.
Oh.
Who'd you lose to, man?
I think Esther did.
Really?
I think Esther won.
Damn.
Or, I don't know. It might have been Ryan. I don't know who won that night.
We need to have...
I just know I lost.
Nobody won.
Nobody won. That's why you're coming. That's why they're bringing it back so you can go there.
Yep.
This is the sudden death episode.
You could do the at midnight tournament of champions.
And you could be...
Give me back in there.
Yeah, they're bringing it back.
CBS.
That's amazing.
It's on CBS?
It's on CBS now.
The new cordon spot is at midnight.
After midnight?
Is it Hardwick?
After midnight.
Oh yeah, it's not Hardwick.
It's Taylor Tomlinson.
Who the fuck is that?
Huge.
Yeah, she's a big star.
Somebody really big.
I don't know who this is.
Yeah, well, no, she's massive.
Huge theater act.
Both of us, same season of Adam and Divine's House Party.
She's since become a theater act.
I have plateaued. Plateau. I've plateaued, but I've it's a healthy plateau. How are the
road tickets selling? Tell me, you know, it's amazing. Austin. Look, Austin. Great. You
look at Austin. You did the mother's Austin, Seattle Creek. No mothership. That's not the
you know, this is pre this is pre mothership. Maybe maybe I'll maybe I'll go to the mothership
next please. But look, we need to get you on. This is you know, it's a real it's a mixed
next bag. You know, I go to Austin, Seattle,
your name in the
be one of the guys. Yeah, I should yeah,
yeah, awesome. Yeah,
if you tell
you promote yourself, you're like going to be doing a show in Austin.
Everybody, it's just
I'm moving to Austin and I'm making myself work for
Garden at the bottom, I like that.
Yeah, what was I saying about... Oh, road days.
Road's going good.
You know, certain cities, it's, you know, feeling good about an Austin, Seattle, D.C., you know?
But I did do a show in Cleveland recently where I was like, "Nah."
Oh, I heard about this.
Not a draw in Cleveland.
Yeah, there's...
You should have done your whole set about Skyline Chili and all that stuff.
You know, this is the most normal set in Ohio. I could have said that. You could
have said that. I could have said most normal set in Ohio. Would have done really
well. Yeah, that is the big lesson of doing stand up around the country is
that there's only about six cities that are worth going to. Yeah, you learn
quickly
how much demand there actually is. Yeah. Yeah. Well, that was like when me and
Adam did Pittsburgh at the beginning of the year. We, it's like the biggest
comedy club I've ever seen. It was like 650, 700 seater. Yeah. And it was like,
used to be a Dave and Buster's. Yeah. And then, and we sold, you know, through
five, through, it was awesome, through five shows, sold maybe 250 tickets.
Right. And then... You could have just done Bottle Rocket Social Hall, that's
a hundred cap and... Could have easily done that. That's right. Could have
easily done that. I opened for Grace and April there, that place is awesome.
And then we were leaving and we were like, "Who you guys got coming up?"
And they were like, "Matt Reif's coming up. He's doing 10 shows.
All of them are already sold out." Yes. This guy sold like 7,000 tickets.
No, dude. It's very... Well, it's... And then I realized it's not the
stand up to man, it's us. We suck. Yeah. That's the thing is it's like
he's from a different world, right? But he's from a world that is bigger
than ours. That is true. It's a world that is like... There's no
Irony, it's just people that are...
Fucking love irony.
It's people that...
You love it, you love it.
Don't even get me started.
You guys love that stuff.
Oh, I love that crap so much.
You guys love that stuff,
you're addicted to that stuff.
I love that shit.
I don't mean to get you guys started.
But that's a...
You go over there, it's people that...
It's people that unironically are like,
"I hate fake friends."
Yeah.
Like, "I hate haters."
People are still using Facebook.
They're happier people than anyone we know.
They're happier and there's way more of them.
And he is like, he's so like when I was doing this, I was doing a, like a one nighter in
Cleveland. I'm like in this small room, I'm like, God damn it. Like this in the big room
next door, man, right. I swear to God that next, it was like five days later, Matt Rife's
doing a weekend sold out months in advance in the main room, like so many shows, probably
every comic on the road has had this experience. But it's like, it's for me, it's, it's a funny
thing because we had our whole we had we had a public. We had a first beef with
that. We had a public beef and when I was got involved twenty three years old, I
I just I posted a couple of pictures of the guy was like how look at how's this
guy? Look at this guy. Look how just like you know DSL selfies or whatever,
and then he was like come fight me at the park. You show me them right now.
Just look up Matt Reif selfie. Matt Reif stuns and you know he wanted to fight
Yes, but then what's weird is years later.
Hell yeah.
Yeah, there it is.
There it is, baby.
This guy wanted to kick your ass, man.
Did he look like this when you started the fight?
Yeah, he did.
Bro, what the hell were you thinking?
What were you even thinking?
I was cyber bullying the guy.
I was trolling.
Holy cow.
And Twitter figures turned to,
regrettably trigger fingers and he told you to pull up and park at the time. I
remember people being like damn, do you want the internet? You know, fast
forward years later,
one of the rich, one of the richest comedians alive, one of the richest
comedians in this industry and I have maintained a certain level of like, you
know,
but that's the thing. All credibility. You've got diehards bro, but now, but
Now when I go to alt shows and there's like younger people there, they're like, "Oh, this
guy is like an elder statesman of being weird in front of a hundred people."
Yeah, it's funny.
So years later, now that he's one of the most famous people alive, there's people who...
There was some like Nicki Swift video or something.
of these like YouTube accounts that's like the shady side of man.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, I watch these all day.
They posted some video where it's they say that I posted old tweets of his to
like hold him accountable where they were like, they're like in 2016 Brandon
Wardell got on Twitter to hold Matt Reif accountable.
And I was like, that's not that that was never.
There's a lot of things from like when I was like young and like new in comedy,
whatever, where I regret it. But at no point was I ever like, "Guys, look."
Yeah. "You guys, we need to do something about this."
"We need to do..."
"Let's unpack this."
No, I was literally just like, "Ha ha, this guy... Look at these fucking gay
selfies. Ha ha ha."
If anything, you made the tweet that gets brought up later.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I was cyber-bullied.
Yeah.
And then years... So that day, other people started pulling up old tweets
where he's saying the N-word at 13 or whatever.
Yeah, but through whatever gave it to him, he's not gonna not say it.
I mean, he's a black man. He's one of the best black comics. Yeah,
he's but he's, it's very, it's like, it's funny. Like, so years later,
there's these videos, there's this one video and I think I saw like some
click bait, like listicle article, whatever, that said that I was pulling
up old tweets of his. And so now I had, I had like a couple of
they're only using photos of you with glasses. Yeah, they're only using
like looking photos that I'm not proud of. Yeah, so it's like it's all these
people
and I say all these people. There's like five. I got like five dms about it,
but I got like five dms in my in my message requests that are like dude. I
can't believe you tried to cancel matt right. I was like I never that's not I
didn't do that. Oh, they're saying that millennials are trying to cancel matt
right. One of them was
I one of them was like a like a landscaping service.
I could actually find it. I actually
I
need to fucking see because this is this is like he said this from his
landscape.
He from he said this like from his business. You fucking gay guy, you
will cancel, Mara. Yeah, so this is from Green Shield tree on its a check him
Green, she underscore tree and he sent me this message. He sent me this message
at four. Nineteen AM. So he's like he's drunk as shit. He just watched like he
just watched like some video about that right. I guess
I'm the victim of misinformation and so now this guy, this tree, this tree
account, green, chill tree,
the emc in the middle of the fucking night,
just
imagine that he was like really early on a he's watching it on his riding. Oh
yeah, I feel like he maybe yeah that's the maybe he wasn't. Maybe he wasn't
drunk and late. This is a clarity. He was waking up super early to the cut
trees yeah
for nineteen AM. He goes you're a fucking pussy
wait. Is that one message or is that how it's that's how it starts and then
there's like a paragraph he goes like what kind of pussy ass comedian tries to
get others cancelled. I never did that you know I never you know he goes and
then you make jokes about drunk driving. Maybe karma will make some drunk drivers
drive near you and your family. One that you scum bag piece of shit. Whoa
suicide is legal in Oregon, just saying J, which I do like that. He's like go to
look. You should kill yourself, but do it in order
Go to Portland you fucking hipster!
Go to Portland you fucking hipster gay guy!
Yeah, it's like on his business account.
That is badass.
That is so beast.
Well, speaking of Matt Rife, I'm going to have a mad wife if I'm late to my dinner.
So, do you have any dates you'd like to plan?
Yeah, check out Matt Rife on Netflix.
I guess I'll just do crowd work, right?
No, look, I wish him well.
God damn, he looks so good.
He did break bread. We broke bread once.
Yeah, I like that.
We did break bread once because he saw me at the Laugh Factory and I said, "Look, we can
talk about it."
Comic to comic, there's nothing like those conversations, bro.
That's the thing about it.
Y'all did WTF with the cameras off. I like that.
I like that shit.
There it is.
It's like that Dane Cook episode of Louie.
I don't know when that was. It was so Dane Cook episode of Louie.
It was actually so Dane Cook episode of Louie.
so the thing is man. We can't have our legends fighting like that. I can't have
no, no, no, no, I can't well, I guess, oh, I guess I don't know when this comes
out, but just listen to the brand and Jamel show tap in this comes out the
brand of the beginning of January. I think well in that case, Nashville,
Atlanta, Athens, you have a website that you could maybe plug to see all these
things. I've got a fucking link tree check them out. I don't I haven't
updated the look
click the link San Francisco. You'll have it on. I'm going to be in San
Francisco, San Francisco. Here it is. Yeah, there it is. Look at that. Oh,
look at all the amazing dates. You guys come to his show.
Last minute intimate one. Oh, the Earl. I love that place. And then it oh
yeah, yeah, that's a great venue. That's where we did. Well, yeah, thank you.
Thank you guys for coming, Brandon. Bye, my friends. Bye. Goodbye, bye.
(static)
- Remember the reason for the season?
Hmm.
- Christ presents.
- No, no, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong.
- Christ's present.
- It's about Christ's birthday.
It is not about commercialism.
That's the complete opposite actually.
It is not about, unless you're buying black coffee company.
- Anti-capitalist commercialism.
- No, none of that.
And then Mrs. Claus is white.
I'm sick and tired of all these different races of Mrs. Claus.
It's just not true.
I mean, listen, I'm fine with people being from all sorts of
worst countries than the one that we're in, right, but I'm not
fine with rewriting history.
I am a Christmas fan.
I'm a supporter of Santa Claus, but also commercialism.
I like the presents and the stockings and I don't care who
as long as they are fun.
I just like Christmas.
I couldn't see that TV is too far away.
And I am a I'm a woke iconoclast.
So I want to destroy the icons of Christmas.
I believe Jesus Christ belongs in jail.
Whoa, not in Christmas.
You shut your fucking mouth.
He's only a baby.
He literally manipulated a group of 12 people to do his bidding.
He was a cult leader.
To hang out with him?
What, are you manipulating me and Patrick to hang out with him?
I think that on Christmas Eve...
I'm Cameron?
Why am I saying your Cameron all so many times today?
Sorry, continue.
I believe on Christmas Eve we should be leaving out gluten-free cookies and oat milk.
Shut your trap, you bastard.
And if my kid asks for Harry Potter books for Christmas, I'm hitting them.
Did you just say them?
I said them.
I'm gonna shoot you to death with my fucking gun and then punch the hole.
I think we have one more position to look at too.
I don't know if there's...
We have one more member of the debate.
If someone wants to read this.
It says, "Jubio, he's a white Mexican," which I've been dreaming of.
It says, "Amo la Navidad.
Amo a mi papa.
Amo a mi mama.
Amo a Papa Noel."
(monkey screeching)