(upbeat music)
- Wow, man.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- We're doing Orthodox Ristmas this year,
celebrating it a little bit late.
- More like Dork-th-Ducks with the--
- Dork-th-Ducks.
- Guys I'm seeing in this call right now.
- Yeah, I mean, that's fair to say.
- I should've worn my fucking glasses,
I feel so fucking embarrassed.
- We got, who do we got over here?
A caveman, you know, that you kind of look like a caveman.
- Yeah, and an army guy, look his hat, his camouflage.
- Yeah, a punk rock army guy and Daria,
you could be Daria over there.
- Amir Perales.
- The male Daria, Dario.
- Male Daria, male Dario.
- Maybe the best of the three,
I'm happy to be the male Daria.
- Yeah, I'd hate to be a giant buff caveman,
that would be pretty embarrassing to be called that.
I'm not buff.
Wait, is I the caveman?
Are you buff?
I think of you as a buff.
I'm not really buff.
I'm large.
But what--
Not really toned.
It's just a lot of stuff.
Well, can I see it?
Can you take his shirt off?
Can you take off your shirt?
Yeah, give me some posing.
Give me some posing.
He's getting up.
Holy shit.
OK.
He's shaking the entire room around.
Oh my god.
Whoa.
You are the bodybuilding sage at the Olympia.
Branson, can you smile for us?
You look so pretty when you smile.
That's how you hit it from the back?
That's the first gump.
That's the gump.
He's such a piece of ass.
I have a question now that you've panned up.
Why do you have a TV mounting
bracket and no TV?
Cause uh, well we
just moved in two months ago. We haven't got around
to it cause we gotta paint the room.
Cause this used to be a little girls room and it's all painted.
TV there though cuz it's opposite from your computer so you'd have to sit backwards
Should do is he should put a TV there that's playing like screw tube behind them
I mean you can watch it when we record e1 Andrew. We'll just watch yeah
You can put a mirror on top of this
Yeah, and the Brad's can see it. It'll be reversed or just paint the room in mirror
Oh, you could just use mirror paint. Yeah. Yeah, I really do like this setup of you're going to paint the room
So you already put the bracket up?
Take it off to paint it. Okay, it was already there
Because the bracket came with it like was that an up charge kind of thing. I don't think at that point
They're really worried about that. I think they charge you more. I don't think they did
We do have big fake like a like two huge fake fireplaces
that uh
Don't really know what to do with in here. So, you know warm yourself up man
We're not real fireplaces or fake a cast-iron pot. I'll ever get a big stew going
Screen. Oh, it's like an electro
It's it says it's a heater too, but it hasn't you know
I don't think it really gets hot that doesn't mean you can't put a cast-iron pot and get a stew going
sous-vide
He made a cast-iron pizza. That was crazy
pizza yeah that actually worked. Andrew was just here for new years eve and the day. Really?
I went to the casino and won big. Yeah we hit big. Well you're an amazing gambler man every
time that I've been over there I think we've gone to the casino and you've always dominated.
Yeah money fraud helps me. I think Branson said he ended up about $15 up. That's huge.
Money moves. We were about to leave because we were so sleepy at 12.15 and we had like
$19 left on our vouchers and so we decided to blast them which made a blast them you
put them in the nearest slot machine and you bet the highest amount you can't be
a man all gone yeah and then I won $55 I was blessed by money frog you got a
blast him it was six I think it was six bucks each time I won the mini jackpot
it was $14 look at that cat what do you guys want to see your podcast ratings go
up you gotta put a fucking cat on there mm-hmm we don't want to be else in house
no we used to I had no idea that you were the size of a cat yeah I'm already
looking at five pussies in Patrick in that means I'm one of the pussies that
No, that's a button that's for your bed.
Four chairs back there.
What's up, pussy?
There's not people in there.
Because Patrick's got that dog in him.
There's not people on these chairs.
Patrick, did no one want to join you at the studio?
Did they not like to spend time with you?
No, I just didn't want to record it at home.
We'd have to all sit around and...
Well, you don't have a way to record at home.
No, I do now.
I have that shitty laptop that I found at home.
Pat has a genius setup.
Pat has a genius setup of he brings...
He put his computer at work so that when he's playing video games,
he can be saying that he's at work,
which is the biggest, highest IQ thing of all time.
- Yeah, that's pretty good.
- I go home, my girlfriend asks me what I'm playing.
- It's any DLC a business expense, right?
- Pretty much.
- Yeah, I buy all the Arkham.
- Eight hours a day.
- Playing Bubble Popper for six hours.
- Cookie Clicker.
- Booby Booby Panic 2, the porno games on Steam.
- Dead or Alive, Extreme Volleyball.
I've been here playing that.
Oh, I've been playing Leisure Suit Larry.
I've been playing, what was that one that I bought,
Julio, on stream, do you remember?
- Oh, was it the?
- It was a cuckolding fantasy 3D--
- Cuckold simulator?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Called Petra Simulator? - Cuckold Simulator.
No!
- Oh, dang. - Ha ha!
All right, that's the episode, I gotta go.
I'll see you guys later.
(laughing)
- It was, I didn't realize how many porn games are on Steam.
There was one, my friend Rex got mad at me.
Tell me if you think this is weird.
- There was a porn game called like Vampires Molestation
or something like this.
- Oh, I know that one.
- And you, yeah, it's really good.
And you, it's like $4 and I bought it
and me and Julio played it for a little while
and I made, you create a character
that you basically can put in different poses as a vampire.
And I made my buddy Rex
and took a bunch of screenshots of it
without telling him.
And then one day I was streaming it in Discord to Julio,
and he joined and just saw a version of him
with his ankles tied to his wrists
and giant bat wings coming off and huge tits.
And he got all mad at me.
He thought that was weird that I did that.
- How's that weird?
- That's what I'm saying, man.
I thought it was-- - It's a celebration.
- Did he know it wasn't real?
That's not real.
- Yeah.
- Well, I had to explain that to him.
- He doesn't have big boobies, right?
- Yeah, I had to explain that to him.
One time on Steam, I also think this is why they advertise a lot of porn games to me.
One time I gifted Ben from Eat Chain Pregnancy the game.
What's Pregnancy?
It's just a game where you're pregnant, but he didn't accept it.
So you just have it in your inventory.
Sounds like a bad friend.
Do you just eat nickels when you get a craving?
I think it's like a visual novel, like emotional.
Like there's no, like it's just emotional or something.
It's not fetishistical.
No.
I hate emotional.
I think that every game should have porn in it and zero emotions and only guys and then
one girl.
That's kind of like what we were talking about on E1 recently.
They need to make a horny version of 2K where you have the dick-sized slider, you can date
other players.
It's like Harvest Moon or something.
Isn't that Cyberpunk, basically?
They need to have 2K with Baldur's Gate level of relationships.
Yeah, you still play basketball in 2K.
You just are in a relationship.
Well, they have all those games like Football Manager.
You can have like, only fans manager.
It's like a guy with like, two like, bad tattoos and slick back hair and sunglasses.
This is how we reboot Leisure Suit Larry.
Oh yeah.
Leisure Suit Larry is now an only fans manager.
I don't think it's about, I don't think it should be that every game should just have
the option to be fucking everybody.
I mean, I think it's like, it's exactly I think the lesson that we take from Baldur's
Gate 3 that was so successful is, oh every game you should be able to on the side fuck
a squid.
That should always be an option.
I'm a total pussy when I'm playing a video game and somebody's throwing their video game pussy at me. Get out of here!
You think every single game? You think Ernie's adventures in space? You think Elmo's shape adventure?
No, your favorite games don't have to have that in them, I guess.
Because you get scared when you see that stuff, I forgot.
Elmo and Ernie are kids though. I think they're adults.
It's okay, there's nothing wrong with that. They are adults.
Bert and Ernie are adults?
I think so.
They live together.
They're roommates.
- Their fan base are children, but they're adults.
They can do whatever sexually they want.
- They're made out of clothes.
They're not adults or kids.
They don't, it doesn't matter if they,
I mean, I don't want to see them have sex.
- I'll say that.
- If they have sex, also they're puppets,
so it'd just be two guys' hands going like this.
- Exactly.
- It's fine.
- There's already videos of that that you can see.
- Yeah, I can watch that anywhere.
I can watch that on the fucking street corner over here.
- I can do that for myself.
- You just saw that shit on the evening news.
- Right now.
- Just say to a guy on the sidewalk,
"Hey, dude, you ever see one of these?"
(laughing)
Oh, which street corner is that Patrick?
Which street corner is that?
New York City, baby.
It is 34th and 42nd.
Hmm.
You guys hang out at Times Square a lot?
Yeah, sometimes.
You know it, guys.
Honestly, more than you would think.
You do hang out there a lot.
I go there any time someone comes into the city,
any time somebody visits, I go to Times Square
and we always do the M&M's store.
But you gotta do the M&M scan.
- Well, you're a hip hopper, so you gotta go there.
- You gotta scan, whenever someone visits,
you have to take them to the M&M store
and scan them to see what color M&M they are.
- You gotta hail a yellow taxi cab,
be like, "If we don't make it to Lady Liberty
"in 15 minutes, we're finished, we gotta get there,
"we gotta see everything."
- I always have something I gotta do at Lady Liberty.
There's always some kind of big,
hot shot style meeting there.
- Don't forget the Empire State Building.
- Last time I was in Times Square,
we went to Margaritaville.
- Ooh. - Oh, congrats.
- They gave us a Christmas card for free.
I've never had a bad time at Times Square.
- Oh my God.
Everybody cheats on Times Square.
- Was it December or what time of year was it?
- Well, Times Square is just short for good times square.
- Exactly.
- It was January, that might've been a leftover card.
- It was the end of November, man.
They were starting to share early.
- It's a card that they take your photo.
It's like, wait, Julio, are you about to show it?
'Cause it's hanging up on my fridge.
- I have one on my fridge too, man.
- Yeah, Julio, it's a photo of Julio,
My roommate Noah, Caleb, and two other guys.
We have lightning blue jerseys.
But wait, what were their names?
Brian and Alex.
Yep, thanks Pat.
It's a photo where their legs are tied up
and they have big titties.
There it is guys.
Oh, wow.
So this is the kind of fun that you have
when you go to Times Square, you become completely blurry
and you have a purple and blue drink.
Look at that, dude.
I mean, these guys are having the most fun
they've ever had. It does look amazing and once I saw the photo on my fridge I
became very jealous that I wasn't there. What were you guys drinking that day?
What were you drinking in that photo? Gatorade. I was drinking something called oh yeah it
was just Gatorade Andrew. Yeah. Don't worry about me man. Sex on the beach. You guys going to Margaritaville
drinking Gatorade? I think it was called sex on the beach. I think it would have been nicer for Christmas
especially they should have given you a photo of all the workers there. Yes.
- Yes.
- Not of yourself.
- Yeah.
- It's so egotistical to have a picture of yourself.
- I think it'd be really funny to have a place
that just has really aggressive names.
There's places I've seen that have like
aggressive cocktail names,
but it's just called like butt sex on the beach.
Like what the fuck, why do you just call it that?
I don't wanna drink that.
(laughing)
- What milk based drink named mother slut?
- Why is it that sex on the beach,
it sounds so good, but butt sex on the beach?
(laughing)
- Wait, I can't figure it out.
Why is that?
- Brown drink.
- Why is that?
- What's wrong with it?
Maybe it's 'cause it does make me think of the sand
that would go in your butt.
- Could it be poop?
No, there's poop in butt. - You're thinking
about sand mostly when you think about butt sex
on the beach.
- Sand in your pussy. - Sand is kind
of your first thought.
- Sand in yo hole.
- Nasty fucking sex on the beach is my cocktail.
- I'm a bit sick.
Are you guys, I'm sick of when I go to a restaurant
or a bar or something and they have a cuss word
on the menu.
- I don't need to see this shit, man.
- Do not show me swearing at a restaurant.
- The best fucking wings ever.
Shut up, man. - Yeah, what the chill?
Chill on that. - And I don't care.
And by the way, you're not fooling me with these little asterisks.
No, I know.
I know those are buttholes.
It makes me not believe them, because why do you
have to show off so much?
Right?
Don't even tell me you have wings on the menu.
Then I'll just intuit that you should have them,
and then I'll try them.
You know, restaurants don't serve you stuff in buckets anymore.
Yes.
Right?
What happened to the buckets?
You get drinks.
You can get beers in buckets.
Sometimes you get a whole bucket of food.
There's a few places around here that you can still
get beer in a bucket.
I feel like Branson lives off of maybe like a bowling alley food diet exclusively.
No, I've been getting better.
You would think that he was like because he's a Missouri giant, but he cooks better than
anyone I know.
Really?
Besides like CJ, yeah.
Whoa.
So you're making pasta?
Duck a la ronge.
Coq a vin?
La ronge.
I love coq a vin.
Really?
Coq a vin.
Oh, I'm a big coq a vin guy.
Whoa.
Crimper Lays a lot.
My wife hates it.
What the hell is coq a vin?
He got really into French omelets for a minute.
a
- Bread, wine, omelet.
- Omelet, yeah.
- With beets and...
(laughing)
- You eat this every day in Paris.
- Bread, wine, omelet, and beets,
with a raspberry garnish.
- Mm-hmm, and tuna salad right in the middle,
and I wrap it up, put some fried rice on it,
and then cut it down the middle,
and a bunch of tuna spills out,
and everybody goes, "What the fuck is this?"
- Ooh, that sounds so good.
(laughing)
- Tuna, fish, omu rice.
That sounds amazing, man.
- It's easy.
- You guys think I should drink this soda?
- Yes.
- Buddy, that's not soda.
- Do you want me to drink?
- No.
- I don't want to drink this.
- Don't do it, man.
- You can tell how--
- Oh, I don't want to drink this.
- It's like 4 p.m.
- Yeah, you can tell how evil the Dickel White
overproof whiskey is by the tiny, tiny amount
that is left in it.
Look how little is left in there
that nobody has wanted to even touch.
- That's what my wife does with chips
when she doesn't want to throw away the bag
and she'll just eat until there's like three chips.
There's just barely any left.
- That's the whiskey crumbs.
- Just throw it away.
Nobody's gonna make a drink of that little bit
of
a prank drink I think. You're supposed to mix it with like, yeah. Speaking of food, my wife
yesterday ate a slice of pizza and she was in the other room, she ate the slice of pizza,
she put her dirty dish on the counter. Get this, I walk out to the counter, I see the
dish and I'm thinking this is gonna have a piece of crust on it because I saw something
on the dish. I get closer, it is literally she ate a circle around the entire slice of
pizza ate the crust and left one piece of cheese pizza with pepperoni sitting on her plate.
Not for you.
That's not a saving it for you.
I'm so sorry.
That's like the reverse of what Charles did with the cheesecake.
Isn't that the most psychotic thing you've ever heard?
What did you do with the cheesecake?
Man, I don't want to get into the cheesecake.
The cheesecake has already been litigated in the past.
It's yeah, it was litigated.
I was sitting there with the cheesecake, he eats the middle of the cheesecake.
Well, no, you gotta explain why though. It's because it was a frozen cheesecake.
That's just some dick joke, Charles.
No, no, no, you don't have to explain this.
I was recording, he walks in and goes "Mmm!"
He makes this fucking stupid Charles "Mmm!" sound like he's fucking Mr. Lou Berry.
Well, it looks good. Cheesecake tastes very good when you...
And then I can't say anything because I'm in the middle of recording.
He just starts eating the middle of the fucking cheesecake.
He goes for the middle of the cheesecake.
I wanted to check if it was still frozen. I was doing him a favor. He couldn't eat it because he was recording.
But I wanted to know if it was room temperature yet.
right in the middle the best spot to check if the temperature is usable you
will try to whistle your way out of anything yeah you have no dignity what
some people would say I ruined every single slice in a single bite but I
would say I was checking for my friend if the Charles also doesn't use pizza
crust doesn't use it unless it doesn't eat it this is good like Detroit style
pizza you got it you got to eat the pizza Chris
- How can it be bad, it is bread.
How can bread be bad?
- Okay, here's my thing.
If you had a really good pizza,
you were eating a really good pizza,
and you tell your friend you should try this pizza.
If they ate just the crust,
would they have tried the pizza?
No, because crust does not constitute pizza.
- That's an insane argument, such a dumb motherfucker.
- No, if they tried a pepperoni, would it be?
No, it's part of it though.
- It's part of it.
- You can try a pizza without eating any of the crust.
- Dude, Caleb, you're not gonna win.
- If you don't get a pepperoni, I think you missed out.
- If you did a deconstructed pizza
and you ate every ingredient one at a time,
is that the pizza?
- That's actually-- - Whoa.
- Well, this is getting too philosophical.
- Yeah. - Holy shit.
- That just blew my mind real quick.
- I'm not gonna be able to sleep tonight, y'all.
- Yeah, I'm gonna be thinking about deconstructed pizza
all night. - The pizza.
- Patrick's already posting on Reddit right now.
Have you guys ever heard of deconstructed pizza?
- Yeah, it's a new hamster style pizza.
Deconstructed. (laughing)
- That's Nashua style.
- Yeah. - Still have not had the--
Also real quick Charles, I I can't agree with you on this
But I do think that you're a piece of shit and you should be in prison for your entire life for taking this if you don't
eat
Pizza crust it's like not even half of them, right? You gotta eat some
40 slices and 20 crusts. You should not be letting pizza. Here's the great thing about America
You can do things that should put you in jail and you don't have to go to jail
I think we can agree on that. Well, I don't agree with that. I think people who do illegal things should go to jail
Why I didn't do anything illegal, I just did things that people like Caleb think should
put me in jail.
You also bitch about tomatoes.
Well we can't, we don't know if you've done anything illegal until you see your day in
court.
He said shrimp isn't good, he said shrimp isn't that good.
Woah!
What the fuck?
Shrimp isn't that good.
Shut your mouth right now, you should be in prison.
This is disgusting.
This is some weird bug.
That's my number one food of all time.
Oh my god.
Yesterday, yesterday me and...
Charles, tell them what your favorite food is.
His favorite food is his Cheerios.
His favorite food is Cheerios and eats them out of his hands like a baby.
They get stuck to his arm.
My favorite food is chicken tikka masala because it tastes so good.
That's not the answer he gave last time I asked.
What did he give?
He said his favorite food is water soup.
My favorite food is a sandwich.
A sandwich is what he said.
It's not bad.
I mean it's up there for sure.
A good sandwich is what he said to the question of what's your favorite food.
It's like basically saying like, "Hey Andrew, what's your favorite food?"
And I go, "Yummy, yummy food."
The delicious kind.
I prefer yummy food over non-yummy.
But it's not do you prefer good food or bad food, it's what's your favorite food.
And a food is what can fit on one plate.
And it's gotta be specific.
A food has ingredients.
A sandwich does not.
What's your favorite ingredient?
A sandwich has ingredients.
Do you eat the crust of your sandwich or no?
I feel like you don't, right?
Of course I eat the crust.
You eat them out of the middle and then leave the crust.
Let me say this about crust on pizza too.
Here's another thing I gotta say about pizza.
I know about that.
The crust is the bones of the pizza.
It's your fault.
eat a chicken bone.
- Crust is not the bones and I've eaten chicken,
parts of a chicken bone before.
- I've eaten crust before.
- He's a crust before but I'm not proud of it.
- The whole reason you eat pizza
is because it doesn't have bones.
- Everyone came up with that answer.
- That's why it's popular.
- What I said, sometimes when you eat ribs,
they're cooked so, they're cooked so much
you can sometimes eat parts of the bone of ribs.
- I eat parts of the bones of ribs too.
- He just likes bones.
- I clean the fuck out of ribs.
- I was gonna say, he just likes eating bones.
- He's eating bones and this is okay.
- Also bone marrow is delicious.
boner is a best foods of the world on their own just like it is she's on the
inside of the crust
who is the best she's on the pizza
so i think i was not there's no now we're talking so it is like a lot of this
was coming out here so it's not about the courage to say that you won't eat
it would you really have a little bit if the crust had no bread and it was only
at the end of the pizza just solid cheese
would you eat that activity
Yeah. Okay. So Detroit style is
a style. You don't like
bread. Got you.
Well, the crust is kind of just
like straight up.
OK. Going out, you know, that's
why it's.
It's a well, you bite instead of a
disgusting breadstick.
You know, I grew up eating
New England style Greek pizzas
where the crust is like super fluffy
and big. And then it's basically you
get a big dipping stick at the end
of the New England.
You dip it into it.
Yeah, you dip it into the sauce.
It's a thing.
New England, Greek pizza.
It's a thing, but it's completely
fake and it doesn't matter. It's not a fake thing. People from New England will tell you
about it and they'll say, "Oh my God, the Greek style pizza is not fake." It's not a fake thing.
The Greek style pizza is really good. It just sounds like it's Neapolitan pizza and they say
it's Greek. No, it's literally normal pizza. It's normal pizza pretty much, but if you go to a place
in New England that has... It's basically pizza that's flat. Yeah, Nashua. If you go to Nashua
and the place is called something house of pizza, that's going to be owned by Greeks. Yeah, it's
It's house style pizza.
Yeah.
It's not real.
It's basically pizza that's a circle and flat and they cut it into triangles.
So if you put it that type of pizza...
It's very fluffy.
What's the funny thing about the crust?
The crust on the end is made of bread and fluffy.
I think cheeseburger pizza is very funny.
My mom loves cheeseburger pizza and it's so gross.
They'd be putting that hot lettuce on that shit.
Yeah.
Put some cold lettuce on there.
Casey's General Store, the taco pizza was something that I saw ordered multiple times in Columbia, Missouri.
Missouri and that's just a pizza they put shredded lettuce and Doritos on.
Well you have St. Louis pizza which is not even close to pizza. St. Louis is the worst kind of pizza that exists.
I love St. Louis pizza but I won't defend it.
It is insane.
Did you guys ever go to Cici's pizza? Do you guys have that?
Yeah.
In college we would pay like four bucks for the buffet.
Yeah I used to go and I would eat the artichoke dip pizza and I would ask them to make another one because I would eat so much of it.
I had a buddy when he was my buddy would show up to that place when he was broke
with big ziplocks and he'd pay for the buffet then just fill ziplocks for the
week. Oh yeah. And then leave. This just looks like Domino's Thin Crust this
St. Louis style pizza. It's got a different cheese. It's the cheese that tastes like revolting.
It's Provel cheese which is a processed cheese made to have the lowest melt
point possible
So you cook it in like and and they cut it into squares
They cut it into yeah, like squares like Chicago Tavern style. I love Chicago Tavern style. It's better than looking like yeah dominoes thin crust
Gotta say I think my least favorite style of pizza would probably be pu poop style pizza from
pizza
- Indian poop style pizza from the bathroom.
- It's in the acquired taste.
- Invite us on your podcast,
you can start talking about eating poop, man.
Come on, man.
- I'm not talking about, I'm talking about not eating poop.
You're the one bringing eating it into it.
- How are you guys still on the air
when you talk about poop so much?
- What'd you say?
- Talking about--
- How are you still on the air
and all you do is talk about cheese?
- How are you still broadcasting?
- We're not on the air, man.
We're underground, we're in the earth.
- That's true.
- We're indie.
- If you search Prevail cheese on Google,
the first thing that people also ask is,
is Prevail legally cheese?
(laughing)
See, that's what I'm saying.
It's not the answer is.
It's oh my God.
Charles, Charles, if I eat the
crust, they put prevail on it.
You know, put stuff in it to
to get it good, to get it more good.
Trying to think of disgusting
regional food that we have back in
North Korea. Oh, dude, in New
England, they got the the chop
suey sandwich.
Oh, yeah, that is fucking that's
fine. That is I never knew
what that was because it's like
silly thing.
That's like a North Shore thing.
But like I didn't fucking I never
encountered it until
I only ever heard about it.
They shot cabbage on a sandwich?
Yeah.
Yeah, dude.
In Sedalia, Missouri, they put peanut butter on a cheeseburger and called it a goober burger.
Oh yeah, I've seen that.
I've seen that done.
Peanut butter burger, peanut butter hot dog, peanut butter banana hot dog, I've seen.
You know, in Miami, they put peanut butter in a fruit and sell it for $127.
I've heard that.
Peanut butter fruit, and it tastes like PB&J.
Wait, wait, wait.
Are you talking about Miami Fruit?
Miami Fruit.
- MiamiFruit.com which redirects to MiamiFruit.org.
- Miami Fruit is like my go-to.
- Yeah, that's where I'm getting all my fruit.
- MiamiFruit.com is the best.
It's where I get my shit.
- I'm getting the banana variety box.
I get the Gak fruit that is $92 and has no flavor.
I get the ice cream bean.
- I do all my grocery shopping on there.
- And my clothing shopping as well.
- My clothing, I'm supposed to get,
I started about two and a half years ago.
First set of groceries should be coming in about six months.
I really, really like it.
The price is--
- It's pretty cheap too, yeah.
- I can't wait to eat a big piece of exotic fruit,
get a huge headache and have to throw up.
Three years for it.
- I was about to say that it's nice to shop
from miamifruit.com 'cause they have a variety box
and most grocery stores don't have variety boxes of fruit,
but I just remembered that the grocery store near my house
has a variety box of fruit called Box of Fruitopia
and it's just a cardboard box that has six apples in it.
- Yeah, it was mostly, it's advertised as a variety pack
fruit they have nothing but apples in it. Are they different kinds of apples though? No,
the box has pictures of different fruits on it and then they all of them just have apples in them.
It's like a mix and match six pack. You know the mix and match six packs that you can buy
for beer? Oh no, it is different types of apples actually. Oh it is? This one at least was.
Yeah but look at all the fruits. Yeah look at the picture. Look at all the fruits on the
- That's from the Fruitopia, dude.
They got oranges. - It's a chronicopia.
- What do they got, pomegranate on there?
But that's all apples.
It's just apples, man.
- That one in the middle could be a pomegranate
in the middle, look at that.
- Yeah.
- It looks like it could be a red delicious though.
- Oh no, that is a pomegranate, guys.
- Wait, it is?
- I thought I spotted that, see that?
- Oh my God.
- You got fruit vision.
- We got the fruit master right here.
- I think Cameron knows someone's storing an apology.
- Yeah.
- Takes one or no one.
- All right, I'm gonna go and buy
the box of Fruitopia right now.
I feel so bad.
thought it was just eight apples. It turns out it's eight apples and one
pomegranate. What's your go-to? I think Honey Crisp are real good and Fiji.
Those are real good. Honey Crisp is amazing. I fuck with those. I like any of the very hard ones.
Yeah, when you bite into it, but then it's all juicy on the inside.
That's the crispy ones. That's what I like. I hate that. When I could eat apples.
Granny Smith is good because it's like the Sour Patch Kids of apples.
I like a Granny Smith. It's amazing with peanut butter. I'm looking on
Miami fruit dot com and they sell recipe books and one of them is smoothie inspo
and just imagine ordering $800 worth of fruit and then putting it into a
fucking smoothie. Oh this Gak fruit sucks I better blend it. Yeah maybe I maybe it's
just a texturizer for smoothies maybe that's the whole. Hey baby you want to try this the
smoothie what is it just try it it's like durian and like mint and kiwi yeah
- Come on.
- I wanna try durian so badly, man.
- I get, yeah, just, I mentioned the Gakfruit before.
I just want everybody who's listening to know
the Gakfruit is called a Gakfruit, G-A-C fruit.
It costs $97 for one Gakfruit, which fits in your hand.
It's a spiky orange fruit,
and the inside looks like an animal's lung.
And it says on the page, flavor profile,
Gakfruit has little to no flavor.
But you're paying $97 for a--
- It's the ultimate flex, though.
- The ugliest, the ultimate flex, yeah.
They're making new fruits.
That shit's from Monster Hunter.
That's not real.
That's not a real fruit.
And it's only been harvested between November and January.
It's a Christmas fruit.
You guys, we're getting all hung up on all the fruits and stuff.
You guys, they have a news section on Miami fruit.
That's where I get all my fruit news.
Yeah, it's all fruit news.
I thought that they were going to have articles and stuff.
Do they have a picture of you?
Dude, Miami fruit's getting too political.
What the hell?
Yeah, see, "Eggfruit is in season" is one article, and then the next article is...
Eggfruit?!
"Is Donald Trump fit to be president?"
Eggfruit is another one that has little to no flavor according to their website, and
just says it has the texture of eating an egg.
I mean, it's the fruit of an eggplant.
I wish that it had flavor.
Do you guys know that black sapote season has arrived?
That's huge.
Wow.
I heard about that.
Oh, I just clicked on the same page as you, Charles.
How many do you guys want me to put you down for?
Fresh rambutan for sale?
A lot.
16 to 20 pounds.
16 to 20 pounds, please.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- I'm so scared of having too much fruit
'cause you can't eat all that quickly enough.
It's just gonna rot.
- Just blend it up.
- That's why you gotta buy the,
that's why you gotta pre-order the tree, man.
Then you don't have to worry about it.
- Just trying to blow through all that fruit,
just having diarrhea every day.
- Amazing news, there was a banana bonanza.
- Really? - Back in 2017.
- Was it?
You're kidding me.
- That's unbelievable.
- That's the greatest news I've ever heard.
- Isn't there a thing where bananas used to taste better?
Like genetically?
- Yeah, well there used to be a different kind of banana.
- Kind of banana, right, right.
- There used to be a different kind of banana.
- It's like Brussels sprouts used to be like a joke
where they tasted bad.
- Which one is it?
- And then the Dutch guys, those Dutch scientists
changed them genetically so now they taste good.
- Yeah, I was gonna bring that up.
I was gonna try to homeschool you
before you could homeschool us,
but I lost to the master here.
- I'm on miamifruit.zendesk.com
where they keep all of their FAQ and the support tickets
if you have a tech issue.
And I'm on a page right now,
there's a Zendesk that's just called,
I don't like the fruit, can I get a refund?
(laughs)
And it just says no.
- Can you ask if they can make six T-Rex fruits for us?
- I'll submit a request right now.
- Do they make custom fruit for your request?
- Yeah.
- Your email address.
- Tell them you just got kicked out of a--
- Custom fruit description.
Can you please make a custom fruit
called the T-Rex fruit for me and my--
Five male friends.
We want the fruit to look cool and to taste like anybody?
- It should be cinnamon.
- It should be big cinnamon.
- Tastes like anybody.
- Big and scary.
- Tastes like T-Rex.
- Can you attach a photo of a dinosaur
just so they know what we're talking about?
- They do actually do have an attachment section.
I'm gonna say we want the fruit to look cool
and to taste like a dream come true.
- Okay.
- The fruit will need to come--
- Can I send you the dinosaur I want it to look like?
- Yeah, send it over.
This fruit will need to come in sets of six.
And the color of the fruit will be awesome.
- Can they send it in a case?
- Awesome.
- And six keys to open it so we can all open it together?
- Yes.
It needs to taste awesome with a blend of tropical.
- The season of the fruit will be summer.
- That's what I want it to look like.
just making up a neopets fruit like can you make us a sneo pets for all this
incredible I need this dinosaur fruit yeah let me let me save this to my
downloads folder and attach it your co-worker like what's your co-worker is
over there eating something like what the fuck is he eating oh he's eating his
t-rex fruit I'll say always pretty so soon I've attached a picture if you want
find that picture and just search "lizard man selfie" and it's the first one.
Really? I'll say "thank you so much Miami Fruit, me and my friends, love you"
We'll put "love" at the end and put all of our names. Yeah, I will love you and we wear all your shirts year round.
Oh my god. I mean now you'll get to see that as a piece of fruit that you get to eat every day.
Charles. I mean, it's his PFP and discord. It's been that forever.
That's amazing. Oh, that's what that is. I see now.
I love that he's just in that parking lot, like outside of a stadium.
He works the night shift at the airport. He's just like,
I've gone ahead and submitted our request guys. I'll let you know if we get a
response. It'll take 24 years for us to get,
we're gonna be all men shivering when we get these first he rexford but it'll be
worth it
it'll be so we're all going to take one bite and i i really i want to taste the
orange meet cinnamon meets awesome flavor meets dream like a dream
oh yeah i haven't had in any exotic fruit but i definitely want to try
durian but that's a stank they're really expensive man
yeah that's a fucking stink but i feel like it'd be funny to bring them to to
Movie theaters and stuff yeah, I mean you should just like walk in with a kit like a little bottle of liquid ass and spill it
Just leave it in there. You could like probably get charged with terrorism for doing that bringing the
Video about a durian yesterday that was called if you bring this to the hotel you will be asked to leave
whoa
Got my durian videos about durians every day. I will yes
Every day or 40 videos about durians. This is a thing that I think about a lot
Apparently it tastes better if you eat it frozen
So my just because you can't smell it. I'm eating I mean durian and stir strum on at the movie
Oh, that's the existing old fish fish
I'm eating that I mean that ever in the in the movie theater. I'm watching salt burn
Yo, we me and cam and Pat did smelling salts recently. Did you guys talk about this on the other day?
Yeah, we did you missed it buddy. You should have been you should have been sick
they wake you up you could say that yeah it was awesome they make you wake up
like a mummy where you go like if you get like if you get like a big can of
like 100% ammonia it kind of does the same thing you just huff that why would
they do that what it is a can of a hundred percent ammonia I mean
Sometimes you have that around the house. We can put one right here to wake up
Yeah, oh wait. We could put one next to this duffel bag that my dad. Let me show you what's in this duffel bag
You already have one isn't that good enough for you? Yeah? I love what you guys haven't done with the place
Hey, yo
Yeah, put up some beautiful. It's thinking about the - it's Pat about to take out a gun. It's his everyday carry
That's gonna be TOS on pot about list. We have no T. Oh, I read you guys
Is it 20 pounds of pussy and ass guys pretty much what do we got here? It's all Hawaiian punch
Fucking gumdrop ass life do you I know dude it's sure this kind of thing shows up at the office a giant bag of candy a
Dump someone does someone just think so all one person always for Hawaiian punches in a duffel bag
Like there were way more than four. That's four is that's the leftover
Yeah, guys I'm sending you 400 feet of bubble issues hubba bubba chewing gum
In the office for years somebody always one person buys something to make something to do something funny
And then thinks that nobody will notice if they leave it inside a duffel bag in the middle of the floor for weeks
And it works every time I leave that in an airport, and they think it's a bomb and everyone's freaking out
They just find Hawaiian punch we had when we when we moved into this office. We got rid of
probably two hundred and fifty toys.
Literally toys. Not an exaggeration. We got rid of a doll house. More.
More. Genuinely more than 250 toys. We had the toys for D&D. That sounds so fun.
We still kept about a hundred.
But we did have to get rid of quite a few, man. And we gave them away.
My wife's calling me in the middle of the thing like, "Oh, the dog's freaking out."
I'm at work, bitch!
I'm not doing any toys! I'm not doing any toys right now! I'm deciding which toys we want
and which toys were gonna give away.
one
you guys got blocks?
you guys got socks?
it's so neat that you play your little games Patrick, that's neat
you guys have the coolest carpet
those carpets that have roads on them
didn't we have one at one point?
we did
did we? those are sick
I could have swore we actually had one of those
that's awesome
I bet you guys have so much fun there with all your toys
dude look at this toy
how do you get any work done?
look at this one
goes jolly be that knuckles show-and-tell for Patrick he's getting sturdy oh yeah
he is Wow well the hat comes off or no it's
fascinating my bed that's really interesting pet anything else man
PlayStation. Oh my god. Regal cinema cup.
You know what I have? I got my buffalo flavored soda. I got something that
nobody has. Look at this. Look at this little whale. That's sick. I got paint.
Everyone brought their shit to show and tell I'm gonna truck oh
That's a cool truck. Oh, I found it guys
My race is a piece of art from Joe
Rotary Club chip. This is my green rat car - these are from kinder. Oh, I do have a toy look I got
Luffy from one piece as a cat. Oh, that's a vampire
Nope, he's got the head on
We can all play with toys
I don't have any toys. Yeah, well you don't even have a
I have what Branson sent me for Christmas. What's that? Oh you mean?
No, this is wonderful. What does that say?
It's a black rose preserved wow way that's a little beautiful. I know isn't that stunning
Wow
This would go so well with your decor - you're keeping it in a box. You should be displaying it. I have this from Yugoslavia
No, it's a it's a
Golden man given to Joseph Rose Tito's Admiral
My favorite Felix sent me this. I thought you said that looks amazing
You play love that toy that is a good toy. I had I put on the ET mask and whoever wore this last
Got it really stinky in there
It was you're last
What did I wear it last? I'm certain that you wore it last
I'm gonna go get all my berserk tomes and show you my berserk tomes. Maybe I were I
Right now you need stuff dude you need stuff in my house. I don't have any kind of stuff
I have a shoebox filled with stuff at my feet right now.
That's where all my stuff is.
That's satanic.
L demons.
Yeah.
L demons Branson.
I'm not rocking with this demon Branson.
I'm not rocking with the bad energy.
I'm just going to write some bad energy cameras on your show so you can show off your toys every once in a while.
Yeah.
This is podcaster of the year.
Whoa!
I did not know you got that.
Yeah.
2021.
Black Knight from Dark Souls.
Well they have...
- Wait, Charles, you also won him 2021?
- They have podcaster of the year
and then you just have a toy.
- Well, he didn't win one.
- I'm the one who sent them those, that's why.
- I thought these came from some official academy.
- You didn't get one for yourself?
- I have the academy.
- Oh, okay.
- I'm the movie guy, so I also do a podcast.
- This is the kind of shit that I have in my house.
Look at this stupid thing.
- Are you sneaking around in your sleep cap at night?
- Okay, this gets worse.
do you think that i'm going to a corridor right now you got a talented
but it's a hard a look at it and i'm older is what you have in the peace
as he's a resistance
this candle holders of my wife asked for for christmas
this is her christmas gift for me it was a hundred and thirty dollars
wow i think a candle holder
you know you gotta go you gotta go and get that it is it's a bad ass can older
you know you know what i'm talking about the thing on the wall away i'll be right
back sconce
No, you guys aren't going to believe this.
You guys got to see this.
This has been on his wall since he moved in there in 2020.
Check this out.
It makes him...
Whoa!
Okay.
Chill.
Chill on that.
Stop it!
Oh my god.
Stop!
I can feel that.
I cut myself on a...
I have a pocket knife that says the Freemasons on it.
It's got the Freemasons logo and everything.
That's just a chef knife.
I actually won an award.
I have some kind of crazy knife that I can't remember what it says.
Check it out.
I got a contesting award.
award show and tell I feel so fucking dumb let me turn off my show and tell
episode is good this is a good idea for an episode is the show and tell because
then it forces them to watch the video mm-hmm I cut my thumb last night on my
Freemason pocketknife oh all right guys are we you have a free missing in
pocket knife. Woah! Is that a witch's broom? Oh my god. He's got a corn broom. It's been
sitting on his wall since he moved in. Woah, what is that? Wait, you have one too Branson?
What is that? Gandalf staff. Woah! It's kind of the same thing. They do look similar. Branson,
You look amazing right now.
Don't do magic to me.
You really do amazing, look amazing with that man.
That is so awesome.
You need like a robe and stuff.
My mother made me a wizard staff out of copper wire.
That is so amazing.
That is badass man.
Oh my god.
I want one of those.
See I need more shit like this.
All I have is all this fucking.
Oh Patrick I sent Felix a Russian, a vintage Russian mason watch.
Anyone need some fungi?
Oh hell yeah.
I found the Freemasons, we were in Texas, we were like driving to I think LA or something.
we went to this giant mall in Amarillo and there was a big knife store in there.
And I found the free, it's a blue pocket knife that just has the Freemasons on it with the
logo.
I thought that was in North Carolina.
No, no, no.
That's where I bought the Trump 2020 lighter.
If you're going through North Carolina, you're going to want one of these to play your guitar
down there in the south.
Oh yeah.
I'm in Nashville, North Carolina.
You gotta get a resonator too.
That's right.
I know about instruments.
Yeah, I'm trying to think of what I would-
You're gonna run into one of those indie rock bands down there, they're gonna want one of
these damn ebos.
Whoa.
What the hell's an ebo?
You are in a musician's paradise right now.
Well, Charles lives in Guitar Center.
Yeah, that's right.
He did have a lot of guitars.
Got electrical tape?
What do you know about that?
That's for electrical equipment.
I have an alligator's head but I don't feel like getting it.
That's a lot of stuff.
I had an alligator's head when I was a kid but bugs came out of it and made me throw it away.
I have the studio right here.
This is not your house, bitch.
This is not your fucking house.
I could live here at some point.
If everything goes wrong for me.
If you crash sure enough it becomes your house.
Are you planning on something going wrong?
Something is going to happen very bad in my life.
Can you tell us what?
I wouldn't worry too much about the future in two days.
I wouldn't worry too much about the future.
In two days, there's gonna be, well,
me and a couple of my friends are gonna make a big splash.
- On January 6th?
- Why?
- When this comes out?
- It's going to be amazing.
- Oh my God, wait, this comes out on January 6th, guys.
- Oh, we should have planned something.
- Me and my friends are gonna finish
what we should have started.
- What you should have started?
What you should have but didn't start?
- Yeah, we couldn't start 'cause of something
that was happening this time.
- 'Cause of woke, 'cause of woke.
We're going to start and finish what we haven't even thought about.
I think everyone's going to be a lot happier and everyone's going to thank us.
You guys are going to do a 24 hour movie festival, aren't you?
24 hour film festival. It's going to be awesome.
Almost anything gets so much more fucking awesome when you do it for 24 hours.
Francis, I finally acquired an actual film,
35 millimeter Francis Ha.
I call him Barbie Francis ha ha ha because I laugh at how bad it is.
His favorite film that he always watches.
Those little women, they're so fucking small.
Yeah dude.
You could pick them up.
She's pretty big man.
They're this big.
In the movie.
Listen, why did she make, why did she call it Barbie and not Little Women 2?
Yeah.
Oh shit.
It's true.
Well because the Barbies are this small.
They were the same size though.
They're normal size actually Andrew.
I didn't see it.
Alright well.
Because of woke, it's woke.
I didn't watch that shit.
It's actually not that woke.
You'd think it was woke but I watched it.
actually not that woke. It's actually pretty anti-woke. Yeah, it's pretty much anti-woke.
I was gonna say Barbie 2 that I'm writing is gonna be very anti-woke. Oh really? I'm
interested. So what's gonna happen in Barbie 2? Barbie 2 is, well yeah, it's
about January 6th. Barbie's gonna go to the insurrection. She's a big, like a
blonde Republican woman who does FaceApp too much, or Facetune. This sounds woke.
It sounds like it makes her really fucking woke. No, it's just I'm talking about the type of woman.
Yeah, yeah, she looks like a rescue hero type woman
Well, I'm getting there I'm just describing what the woman looks like
She's on the carnivore diet she has a great Dane named Piper who's like
Already died never
It's an XL bully mixed with a great Dane and it's one of the biggest scariest dogs in the world
I'm just named the West Korea bully
It's named West Korea.
And yeah, she's planning on going to January 6th and she sees like, you know, trans people
and goes like, "What the hell is that?"
And stuff, and like she goes around.
She sees trans people at January 6th?
Well, they're protesting.
They're counter-protesters.
Why are they there?
Oh, okay.
Yeah, there were counter-protests on November 6th.
The message of your movie is very muddled.
It's getting a little muddled.
were counter protests on a message of your movie is very muddled. It's getting a little
muddled. Barbie Toost begins with Barbie driving towards the Capitol and running over climate
protesters. Yeah. Yeah. She's mowing down. If you want to make Barbie too un-woke, just
a big protest for climate or gayness or whatever and just Barbie just unloading a rocket launcher
directly into the crowd. And she says, it zooms in really close on her face and she
says fuck woke yes that's a good movie I'd watch awesome hi there guys guys guys
guys guys guys guys guys guys guys guys guys guys guys guys guys guys you get a
reply Elizabeth Miami fruit no way hi there your correspondence is deeply
valued and appreciated we do not offer t-rex fruit at this time the best thing
to do would be to stay tuned to our newsletter on our website as we'll share
updates there if we begin to offer this fruit in the future.
Here's the thing, if it's on their website, then everyone else can see it.
They're saying it like T-Rex fruit is a real fruit. They're saying it like it's real but they just don't have it.
Yeah, that's a good point. T-Rex fruit could be real.
They probably just don't offer it at this time, but they might in the future.
Wait, but some-- OK, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I found a T-Rex fruit.
You guys, look at this.
Oh, wow.
Look at this one.
Whoa.
Oh, no.
Oh, my god.
Well, I think that's just a watermelon.
Yeah, it looks just like a watermelon.
Yeah, that's a watermelon.
It's real, though.
That's a watermelon shaped like a T-Rex,
with the one up top.
It says the T-Rex fruit is a mythical beast-type blocks
fruit.
I see blocks fruits.
OK, so here's what I'm thinking, man.
There must have been an email where someone asked,
can you invent an ice cream bean?
Can you invent a ice cream peanut butter bean?
We can't at this time, but stay tuned to the newsletter.
Oh wait, there's a T-Rex devil fruit?
Whoa.
Those are the two scariest things ever.
Model Tyrannosaurus Rex is the ancient,
so untitled by God.
Scariest shit I've ever heard of.
Charles should know this, he's the One Piece guy.
There's a devil fruit named, like called Model T-Rex.
Yeah, they call him the One Piece guy
'cause he's sure got one too.
Anything about that
What thing the microphone my weapon I don't really do violence I'm more kind of doing violence to fools on the on the microphone
Right Charles damn
You know crust acid and bitch
How you not gonna eat the crust of a cheese crusty
Let's be real here if I'm out and about at a pizza place
I'm gonna be shamed into eating about half the crust cuz it looks weird for a grown man to have like four pizza crust on
His plate you're right
So you admit it shamefully disgust well, it's shameful to eat crust, but society doesn't see it that way
So I have to conform to these fucked up backwards ass conservative ass societal values.
It's shameful to murder people, but society says to not murder people.
And if you were if you existed back in the Neolithic times,
they would cast you out of the community and you would be eaten by a panther
because you need to learn to think like the group.
Conformity is how you survive. It's part of human evolution.
And then there would never have been crust on pizza if I invented it.
So then it would be the best food ever.
And they only had crust back then. They didn't invent the pizza part yet.
It was just circles of crust.
They had the wheel, they said, let's make this out of bread.
They mostly had, they mostly had crust.
And the crust comes from the earth.
It comes from the grains and they smash them up so that you can bake it with water.
Exactly.
Crust comes from the earth.
Cheese does not come from the earth.
Have you guys ever noticed how crust is wheel shaped and cheese comes in a wheel
shape, but the sauce doesn't?
What's up with that?
Do you see the sauce in a wheel shape?
Tomato is wheel shaped.
Yeah.
Tomato is a wheel shape.
Tomato is a wheel shape and so is the tomato sauce can.
And pepperonis, pepperonis too.
It's so is the can that the tomato sauce is in.
- Will you guys let Caleb talk?
He's raising his hand.
- I just wanna make a point.
I'm not raising my hand.
Oh, you can't even see it, and I just dropped it.
Hold on.
Do you see this tiny little O-ring, Charles?
I wanna talk to you about food waste.
Do you see this?
- No, I don't.
- No, this-- - Now I see it.
- This is the size of a pizza in Africa,
and this can feed 30 families for 30 nights.
And you're throwing away probably 50 of these every--
- It's like a menorah of pizza.
crust every single time that you don't need my crust to them to Africa
To Africa
Caleb said that their kid there people starving africa. You said okay. I'll send them my shit
(laughter)
- Yeah, crust, crust, I meant crust.
- Imagine the crusty shit.
- For his life right now.
- The crusty shit.
- Not even the whole shit, just the crust of it.
- The pizza crust, you guys are so juvenile
and immature on this show.
- You want to insult a starving African child,
distended belly, who opens up the only thing they've ever,
only package of meal they've ever had, they open it up,
it's not only your shit, it's just part of it?
- They can tell it's scooped out.
- This is, I've been so misrepresented here.
- And also, like your shit's gonna be crazy
- Because you don't eat,
all you're eating is cheese and pepperonis,
your shit's gonna be all,
it's gonna be liquid when they get there.
- Exactly.
- Well, I'm eating the bread underneath.
- 'Cause I can tell by your face
that you are lactose intolerant.
- I'm eating the bread that's underneath the toppings.
I'm not just pulling the cheese off.
- You're just sending like a KolaGuard box to Africa
and they're just opening it up and going,
is this shit?
- Well, what did you guys do to help?
- I said, I said this was--
- That's true.
- I was born there.
- That's true, that's true.
I haven't done anything to help.
Not anything about it.
- Cameron was raised in--
I was raised in Africa. I was literally part of a warrior tribe.
Yeah. Which warrior tribe? I might know it.
The Cameron tribe. Have you ever worn any of their outfits?
Oh yeah. But not anymore. Not since I moved.
There's a lot of photos of him. Not since I moved when I was seven years old
to America. And he assimilated very well. A lot of people
can't even tell, but he still has that African accent.
And he still has that warrior mentality. Sometimes you've got to calm this guy down.
Oh, you have to. You have to remind him that there's no war.
Yeah. And he still throws spears around too as well.
Wait, is there no war? There's no war anymore.
Oh, thank God. Yeah, we're all done with that.
I mean, I'm sure. I'm reading right here on CNN,
war. We're all done with that. War's been outlawed.
Wow. War, somebody, I think it was. Why hasn't everybody done that before? I think it was
President Biden, but he did one of those 2024 in and out lists, and on
on the out was war. So now it's all gone. But you know what was in? Jelly shoes.
Jelly shoes. Oh those are comfortable. Yeah, jelly shoes are very much in for 20.
You wear jelly shoes all the time. Like Dr. Scholl's? No, no, no. Imagine never hearing of something and
someone says you wear it all the time. You wear those brown jelly shoes all the time.
Those are clogs, they're not made of jelly man. What is a jelly shoe? I don't know what a jelly shoe is.
It looks like a type of jelly. Yeah, it's a plastic type of jelly.
Plastic is jelly.
The metaphor he's saying and what he's saying.
Charles is talking about shipping people who's crusty poop and Brant's talking about eating jelly plastic.
No, let's talk about Charles.
Let's talk about Charles.
They talk about all this nasty stuff on here.
You're eating a peanut butter and plastic sandwich? Come on.
Nowadays, that's basically the only option.
Yeah, Mike.
Plastic isn't everything.
Can you ask Elizabeth or whatever if we can have a plastic fruit?
It's like in Crimes of the Future.
OK, I'll reply to the email right now and I'll say, OK, and what about plastic fruit?
- Yeah, plastic fruit because plastic is a type of,
and specify that plastic is a type of jelly.
- Yeah.
- Can you send the picture again too?
- Also, plastic is so easy to make,
they could make it for us right now.
- Say, okay.
- Ask her if she has another email
where you can send her bigger files.
- Plastic fruit, and then I'll do two line breaks,
say plastic is a type of jelly.
- I need to send you a jelly video.
- Google tab, and I'm gonna go to Google Images,
and I'm gonna search plastic clip art.
- That's for a whale. - Franken-sum-fruit.
- You want a bubble berry.
- Franken-sum-fruit. - You guys, you guys,
I found a website called dudejellies.com
that has male jelly sandal.
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, this is a website where you can just
dress up like the dude.
This is a website that gives you stuff
to dress up like the dude from Big Lebowski.
- That's a very specific niche.
- Charles, what was the exotic meat website
we were looking at.
- Oh fuck, what was that called?
Where they have, you can get one pound of lion meat
for like $20,000.
- Oh, here we go. - What?
- Whoa. - Here we go.
Exotic meat market.
- That's it. - Yeah, that's it.
- You guys are gonna go crazy with this.
I can't believe Branson dropped his bombshell
at the end of the episode.
- Yeah, I know.
- Oh, my bad.
I just remembered it. - We're close to the end.
- Holy crap. - Now we've got another
20 minutes. - Bluefoot chicken.
- Oh, goose meat.
- Bobcat meat. - With eggs.
- The site's not that good 'cause they don't have people.
- Yeah, they don't have people and they don't have swan
and I wanted to see if they had swan.
- They have muskrat.
- This is fucking awesome, man.
Silky chicken.
- This is unbelievable.
I like they have, okay, I'll read a selection here.
They got raccoon meat, rattlesnake meat,
reindeer meat, and salami pepperoni.
(laughing)
- Yeah, they just have normal steak and then they have yak.
- Antelope meat.
- You can get a yak filet mignon.
- Ooh, you can eat a--
- If I don't cook it right, I'm gonna yak.
You can get donkey milk.
Lionfish.
Oh, you can get a shank of shark.
Shank of shark, really?
Donkey milk powder, 50 bucks.
Look at the picture on the shank of shark page.
Wow, you can get a lot of donkey milk.
You can get five pounds of otter stew meat for $249.
Shark meat is only $30 a pound.
Guys, you can get 20--
That's not bad.
Shark's pretty common though, right?
You can get 20 kilos of donkey milk powder for $7,999.
(laughing)
That's amazing.
- We split that six ways.
- Yeah, we split that six ways.
That's such a, oh my God.
- What if you ate caiman meat and you became a caiman?
- What's a caiman? - Oh my God.
- It's like a little alligator.
- They sell nutria meat.
Can you guys imagine eating a nutria?
Do you know what a nutria looks like?
- No. - They're swamp rats.
- No, it says, they're big old rats,
but here's what it says on the nutria page.
It says, "Nutria are not rats," in all capitals.
So you guys are wrong there.
But can you imagine eating one of these things?
- You get some rattlesnake bones
for rattlesnake bone broth.
- I think I will just, I think I'm not that hungry
and I'm just gonna go for a suckling pig
between 5.1 and seven pounds.
- Wait, 10 pounds of iguana heads is $150.
- Holy shit. - Oh yeah, they are.
- 10 pounds of the heads. - Look at this piece.
- I'm good on that.
- Skin on iguana heads ready to cook.
- I'm good on all that, I don't need that.
I'm just gonna eat a peacock heart.
- A whole groundhog costs $200.
- Bobcat smoked sausage for $30.
- What?
- Look at the picture for Silky Chicken in the chat.
Look at that chicken.
That's a blue chicken.
- Oh my God.
- That's stealth chicken.
- It's commonly used to brew tonic?
Is that what that says?
- Ew.
- I'm eating stealth chicken tonight.
- Exotic sausage of the month club.
You can join the exotic sausage of the month club.
January's rattlesnake and rabbit sausage.
I think the best thing to get somebody from this website, unless they...
Oh, wait a minute, no.
I was going to say the best thing to get is the gift certificate, but no, the best thing
to get is the exotic hot dog of the month club.
You guys, this month is venison hot dog, followed by bison hot dog, axis deer hot dog, elk hot
dog. Those are all llama hot dog, goat hot dog, alpaca hot dog,
alligator hot dog, also antelope hot dog, beaver hot dog, camel
hot dog, and wild boar hot dog. Is the beaver in season? They
also have those are when they're in season for a whole section
for exotic meat for pets. Whoa, rabbit meat for pets. Oh, they
got halal ostrich meat for pets. Python meat. Boneless meat.
Isn't it? This is the most incredible website I've ever
seen in my life. Yeah, I mean, exotic meat market and Miami fruits dot org.
Both ends of the
of the hell else could you ever fucking need?
And you fill in the gaps of this little CVS trip.
All I need is a website now for crazy breads.
Yeah, exotic strange breads dot com.
Not me. They're going to send me pizza crust.
Yeah, we got red bread. We got blue bread.
We got green bread. We got yellow bread.
We got blue bread. We got red bread. We got yellow bread.
I want to go to that bread.
That's all I want. I need a rice place with different colors, a bread place.
Chevron bread.
Yeah. Bingo. Hot bread kitchen.
Have you guys noticed that food isn't enough colors lately?
It's not.
Good point.
It's really not, except for Sour Patch Kids. The number one candy.
You're biased because it's on your screen and you have a hat of them.
Where's your hat? Why didn't you wear the Sour Patch Kids hat?
That's what GBB stands for.
If Cam really cared, he'd be eating Sour Patch watermelons and supporting Palestine.
That's real shit.
Damn.
That's real motherfucking shit.
Alright guys, Riffmas, another one in the bag.
We'll see you next year.
My dog, I think my dog has shit, diarrhea in his crate
in the last 10 minutes, so I think I have to go clean that up.
- That's huge. - So this is an amazing,
amazing end to the episode for me personally.
- Maybe you should get a better diet. - Thanks for sharing your toys.
- Just throw a towel on it. - Eat some exotic meat.
I gave him an exotic bone, which was a not a bone from an animal,
but instead a... I wasn't fucking my dog!
Come on dude, don't fuck your dog man.
No I wasn't.
Your dog's got diarrhea.
And your bone's not exotic.
It is, it's red.
Oh that's cool.
You would think it'd be white as snow.
It's red.
It's red like an animal's.
Thank you to the good people of E1.
Thanks for having us.
Except for Charles.
You're very very stupid.
You're very stupid.
Is this about the pizza?
Yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah.
And you said shrimp was mid.
You said shrimp was and you said some crazy stuff about Africa as well that we're not okay
I said that you want to shit to Africa which is
Almost worse than say you don't like it's an act of literal terrorism. Yeah, I feel like I've been mister
I feel attacked and misrepresented, and this is the worst appearance on this show we ever made sounds like
His toys which was very nice
Okay, and wait just remember this before you go
This time for Africa fuck you Charles
1992. That would be a good year because you can get put in the
nines, but you wouldn't see these people have 1991. Oh, they
were patented in 1992. That's exactly what I said. 1992 would
be a good year. Yeah. Yeah. The 90s make sense. But this is
this is this is complicated. This is fussy like this is too
much going on. You know what? Here's my thing. I think the
night these these 1991 1992. Wait, they said they were
invented in 1992. This woman's wearing 1991. That woman is a
a time traveler. That's
I believe that that is
but here's what I'm saying. The
1991 1992 glasses have had to
have been invented by either a
time traveler or a schizophrenic
person because who looks at the
number 1992 and says, oh glasses.
Yeah, I want to make glad 2000.
You're like, oh glasses glasses
or handcuffs or bubble wrap
would be great to merge this off
of but a 1992 is a psycho number
to look at him. Look at this guy.
We're in the 1998.
That's Jerry Lewis right there.
That's Jerry Lewis.
But look at this.
This to 2024.
This is like when you like you're like, like, you know, somebody
that's got a dog that should be dead, you know, like it's like,
oh, yeah, that dog's been alive.
One hours.
Yeah, that dog is like, it's like, oh, yeah, this is my 34
year old dog.
Yeah, that's what these glasses are.
We got to put them down.
It's time to put them down until it's time for them to come
back to work in a feed.
We're going to feed the dog a Big Mac with the we're going to
feed these glasses of Big Mac and then they're gonna pass away.
Why is there liquid all over this?
Oh, don't worry about it.
What the fuck happened?
Nothing happened.
What did you guys do?
Come on, man.
It's disgusting.
Nothing bad happened.
And we're back with amazing Brandon Wardell from Los Angeles.
All the way from Los Angeles, California, man.
All the way from Los Angeles.
Holly, Holly, weird.
You hear a lot of this over there in Los Angeles, huh?
Yeah, we got Caleb on the soundboard today.
I'm on the soundboard.
I always do it loud and proud.
And if you're near the...
Oh my God.
Yep.
Spill the entire...
Oh no.
Let's see.
I got to turn this off.
No, this is...
Nothing bad happened.
Were you not here?
I was not here for whatever happened here.
Patrick, what happened?
I...
There...
Don't worry about it.
Who did it?
It was you did it, didn't you?
Patrick Spiller.
Could have been Caleb, the famous Spiller.
(Bowser's theme)