Well, on the way here is what is what I saw. So we were talking about now.
Well, you were gone Caleb, but the ridiculousness of these twenty twenty
four glasses. They don't know where to put the circles. I mean the holes well
like circle. It seems like they figured it out that no. I saw the craziest
twenty twenty four glasses on the way here, sitting on someone sitting on
someone's
dashboard, dashboard, so basically it was imagine it was it said the circles.
It was two circles for the eyes, two o's, so it's two zeros, two zero zero
right all on one line and then above off to the right of the other zero of the
second zero. It said twenty four, so it's two hundred to the twenty four
two hundred to the twenty fourth power. Holy well, how do you know that they're
got a geek or a dork and or they're from the future. Yeah, I think twenty
thousand and twenty four person, but it was crazy to put the extra zero and
then put the twenty four off to the side. That's the craziest solution I've
seen yet. Yeah, that's the like this. I just felt like I have to share,
because we talked about this at length before, but it's just I just saw. He
said that this was a dying puppy and you got to feed it the Big Mac and put
it to sleep. Why do people do that with their dogs? Feed them a big man, but
they're not going to remember they're dead. You know who I was thinking about
it last night in bed, Liz Warren, letting her dog eat a cold burrito off the
floor for its birthday. Yeah. What the hell? Why do people do... You don't
remember this? Fed on the floor. Did everybody fucking... Fed the dog on the
floor. Did Liz Warren get a fucking memory hold, y'all? She got a fucking
memory hold, bro. Not the memory hole. She... But she put... Don't throw me in
the memory hole. She put a cold burrito on the floor, on the rug.
she's not going to heat it. A rug is a crazy move. It's on the road.
From across the room. When you say
you're getting heated, it's a weird video. You're getting heated about a
thing to do, but it also you can do that with a big dog. It doesn't matter.
A big dog dog is not on the rug. Put it on the hardwood. It
reaches. She has a cleaning lady buys another
wood for even then it's the principle. She has a fully carpeted house. She's
the day principle. She looks like the principle. That's like my principle.
that's fire and I'll pound that shit out. We almost pulled a prank on you guys
today, me and Jonah. Yeah. 'Cause I went to this thing, did this work for him
and most of it was taking up all this carpet. He said, "What if we go to the
office and we put 300 square feet of carpet down in every single part of the
office?" Oh, I brought a rug. I got a rug. I know, I saw that. But I said no
because I thought that you would... I thought you would think it was funny and
I thought you would be really mad. I wouldn't be mad at all. I thought you'd
be really just carpeting the office, just carpeting the entire office and then
imagine this you get here. Oh, I was at the gym all day and I'm so tired. Open
the door, me and Jonah sitting there
holding our faces like this going
and you see you at first again. I site is at a head level, so you're seeing me
and Jonah were two different heights. So you look at Jonah's very tall. Then you
look at me and then you look down carpet all over the floor. I don't think I
would even be mad at. I'm not sure I would react. I would be like oh, that's
kind of weird. I don't think I would like it, but I think that I wouldn't like it.
I guess I could tell you're mad. Maybe I have another question. Do you guys
fucking hate me?
You guys fucking hate me. Wish I was fucking dead. Bad prank. That is a bad
prank. I'm not good at pranks, man. I'm famously bad. I don't have a prank face.
I haven't is this. I haven't done pranks since when I was a kid. I did the
bucket of water on the door to my brother and he cried. You do this when
you're my older brother, six years old. You have no poker face for pranks is
when you do a prank, you have a little you have like a bobble head thing. I
don't bobble my
this you go.
I don't double it
all my head the other day. I got a fake poop and I put it on my kitchen
counter as soon as I got it. I zero planning put it on my kitchen counter
and my wife walked in got home from work and I said I'm so bad at pranks. I
said Hey baby, can you get me a glass of water and I was closer to the kitchen
when she was I was doing nothing. I was just sitting in the hallway. Can you get
me a glass of water?
It didn't work man. She walked in and she was like yeah, there's there's a fake
poop on the yeah. I'm also pretty bad. We were talking about the master troll
the other day. I remember I was trying to think of of trolling I had done in
the past, and I remember something I did in college that I completely forgot
about the people got mad at me for what which was you remember how college it
was like they had the it was like a TV net like a school TV network where you
get shows and there's like they have a staff and you make like you know,
however many episodes or whatever, and I never did any of that, but on Facebook I
posted I made a fake poster for a show for that call. I remember this shit
fucks and I said
I'm excited to announce I'm making one of these shows.
Please message them on Facebook and ask to be if you want to be on the crew
and like we're going to have a meeting in this room on this day at this time,
and it was completely not true and fake and a bunch of people messaged the like
the school organization and be like hey. Can I work on this shit fucks and
everyone got really mad at me because it wasn't real. We used to be more into
trolling and back row. My God, that was how I think that's how we how we all
started hanging out sign that said. If you see something in appropriate of
trolling, yeah, we did, we did, but the master trolls, yeah, the master troll.
Do you submit to him? I did a prank in college where I stole somebody's
headphones, very expensive headphones. I remember that prank. I remember that
That's a prank. That's not a prank. I you know, it's a prank that we did in college.
Someone pranked me today. I stole my wallet. What? Yeah. Oh, yeah. I fucking I was coming
back from that thing. I stop in the smoke shop. This this is why I know this is why
I drop my wallet. I walk in the smoke shop. I hand the guy my or I walk up to the thing
and there's nobody behind the counter and I am like hello and I see movement in the
at the corner of my eye and they have a the door to the bathroom is open and the
mirror is
like I can see in the mirror. The guy who's supposed to be running the front
is wiping his ass and running off the toilet. He's like taking a shit
actively and then he comes in and I was like okay man. I just want to pack us
in and he like walks up to me and he goes like this
and he fits he wants a fist bump. So I gave him the limpest least contact
I'm why did you want a fist bump for because I saw him take a shit that made
no sense. I've never fist bumped anybody at any cash register ever a prank do
and then you have this guy or something theory and then, so I was so flustered
that I guess I dropped my wallet on the way back. I got a call from a barber
shop. They googled me and found my phone number and called me. Oh, my God,
that's crazy. That crazy. I don't even know I had lost my wallet. They saw
your crazy videos. They saw all my videos exactly. I walked in and they
said, are you the master? Trey, you the master, they would not know he's the
master troll. He's not the master troll. Also, I used to be. I don't you don't
at all, bro. You're a zero. You literally you're a little trolled in
the wire dot com. Look at me in the wire dot com has been completely trolled.
I'm looking at you. You're a zero. You're I troll you're trolling me right
now. You're attempting you're failing. I'm looking at you. I'm looking at
doesn't troll at all. Oh, you are not a troll. You know, I am the man. I'm the
name name five trolls. You've done five right now. I told okay speaking of the
same thing, the same group on Facebook. I told all of them that I would I would
buy. I pretended that I was going to buy every single kid at school
menthol jewel pods because I said I commute from New Hampshire and I'll buy
them for you. Even if you're under age, I don't care and I put it in the group
and every people got mad at much, much closer. People got by the way. I got
messages that said I think you shouldn't do this much closer to a
crime than a troll. That's most much closer to a master troll knows that
crime not eater on so trollers on crime years on crimes. I would say yes,
that's what I just said. I rolled in that scenario. The trolled yourself.
Seems like you trolled yourself. Congratulations. You told you troll the
admins of the group. Thank you very much. That was the master troll at
work. They have a way that admins leave alone. I rather what else out. What
leave out the admins from the troll.
What else
there was one okay, but there was a very there was a comment from I remember
sending this to you guys, because they sent this one really long paragraph about
how they said, like he
he's so deeply irony
they seem like you got this. I got this. I got this. I still listening the
first, all the one troll. No, so you still have one more seven years ago.
What else did I do? Four more trolls to describe. Four more trolls, okay.
One of my master troll things I did in high school where I made a folder on
the computer at the school, it was all the same JPEG,
and it was two gigabytes big and it said, "Important documents," and the
computer teacher went through every single one to make sure that there was
no important documents is what he told me. You stole this from like a
green text screenshot. That is not a green text. No, that is not a
master troll. That's no. You're just jealous. I'm not jealous. I'm
you're jealous of you. You haven't trolled in years. And I'm not saying
I put that I put those days behind me. So you're not the man. You're not the
best.
You're terrible. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
because I put the it's like when a cowboy hangs up his gun, we have some
meaning. He's done. He's not a cowboy.
like John Mars, Cowboys, go. It's like when Cowboys Cowboys and then they have
one. That's my only real. So your one last thing about Cowboys, by the way,
in context, I gotta be honest with you. That was not a troll. They just find
tweets that are in
a relation. I wrote for the Golden Globes. They put funny thing. They don't
think, they never said, and writer Patrick Doran. No, no, and the bottom,
at the bottom of it, at the bottom of it, it said, "He threw his writers
to the wolves."
but you read the article, but it didn't say anything about you being a writer.
Yeah, the tweet said that I was a writer on the Golden Globe. They just put that
in because they thought it was funny. I don't think so. You're the master of
funny. Yeah, we can agree with that. Yeah, you're the master of the master
jokester. You're the master jokester. Okay, maybe I'm less of a troll and more
of a jester, I guess. You're the master jester. Master jester. I'll accept master
jester, but do you submit to the master jester? Yes, I submit to the master
jester. Why do I have to submit? But sure I do. Okay, alright, that's all I
wanted to know all week is do you submit to the master troll, but now it's
Master Jester. Master Jester is a really cool name. Master Jester is a better name.
Master Jester. Kind of hard to say. Damn, Master Jester. I think there's a secret troll
among us though. And who disses? Who is the actual master troll, Kaiser Soze style.
Aye. And he's sitting behind the production computer right now. He barely
trolls. He doesn't troll that much often. DJ Jubio, by the way. DJ Jubio? DJ Jubio.
I like DJ Jubio. DJ Jubio does not troll. Well, what's going on? He could troll us
right now and we don't know. He could make the episode really fast.
A troll is not a troll if nobody knows. Interesting. That's true. But what if it's the long troll?
What? What if it's the long troll? Well then someone will eventually know and then it becomes
a troll. It's just what I think. This is a trolling 101. Trolling 101. Trolling 102.
This is a troll like 102. An advanced troll, 201. Let's be real. This is a major one. Speaking
of getting, of trolling yourself, last night I finally learned you put the zins in the
top lip, not the bottom. It's called an upper decker for a reason. Yeah, but it says it
on the tin. It says it on the tin, put it on your top lip. Really? Because if you put
it on the bottom, there's too much saliva. You put it on your lip? That ain't gonna work,
man. You put it right here. I was putting it right there. You put it on your lip. You're
You're kissing the zin. I'm kissing the zins. Yes, I am. You're not supposed to do that.
Oh, I need to. Why? Because I love them. Well, that's sweet. Well, that's actually very sweet.
I actually completely love them. Guys, can I tell you something? Yes. I'm sick of birthday
parties. Wow. That's the wrong one. Wrong one. Thank you. I'm sick of birthday parties.
and here's why
what yeah you're sick of birthday parties. Oh
and it's not the people's parties. I'm sick of the what has become recently a
birthday party. So I've been getting these emails, these messages, these text
part of all nestles party fall. I'm sick of party for I do not need to RSVP to a
birthday party. It's that simple. Here's what used to happen. Okay, you get a text
used to people used to throw birthday parties when you're a little kid.
people would say it's your it's my birthday. It's your birthday. I'm
throwing a party. It's my birthday. I'm throwing a party. They would invite
people and then they don't know if people are coming until the day of the
party, and then either people would show up, you'd have a grand time. Right,
this is before telephones. Nobody would show up and then that's good because
kids are losers and that's what they deserve. If you don't have any friends,
you shouldn't have a birthday party. You learn from that. So that's what I
think is so disgusting about this is the fact that I have to say, and I always
maybe yeah, I know and then you feel bad because you hit maybe and then I never
go and then you see the comments on it. Yeah, the comment thing and this is
everyone else. I'm gonna be there ever and I'm bringing a million beers. Many
things should have stayed analog in this world and should not have gotten
technology involved in it. Are you about to pull your tooth out? Oh God, why
did I just have a fear? You think that my teeth are that bad? Yes, yeah, I saw
him earlier when you're showing me your lip and I was like any any second one of
these could pop out. These are the hippo game where you touch the teeth. That's
it's not a hippo. It's a crocodile. It's a crocodile, though. I played the hip over
the hippo is the hungry one. Yeah, he's hungry for your finger. Yeah. Well, no,
he's not. I told you to scare me so bad.
I was going to bring
why did they invent this startling game that game? That's the fun of the game
and that game, I think, is the reason why we're afraid of crocodiles in this
country. I would think it was more of dentists. Maybe that's the fear that I
got from that you're afraid of dentists because
because of the game because of this crocodile dentist, I think that is
afraid of powering to the dentist user because you bite that you can just bite
well when you play when you play as the evil dentist to this lowly crocodile,
you realize how evil the dentist is.
He's so mad at you that he's biting you, but he's not even but you're not trying
to help the crocodile. You're not trying to help him. You're trying to touch his
teeth. I could see dentists being the next thing like clowns where it just
becomes full evil pedophile vibes. Yeah, I think dentist what's that thing about
dentists that they kill themselves more than anything? That's toll booth
operators.
Toll, but I don't think there's that many of those around. Yeah, but they have
the highest suicide rate. Oh yeah, that seems like the absolute, that's why
they're not around. Worst job of all time. My sister told me that, my sister
told me that toll booth operators have the highest suicide rate. But isn't that
just because? Oh no, I think it's... You're supposed to say more than eleven
towards to them so that they don't feel bad. I think the high suicide rate is
depressed people. Yeah, well, that's what I was gonna say.
Tobu's operators skew probably pretty stupid and stupid people kill themselves.
You can't even go to the bathroom. You can, but it's not pretty. Yeah. You
can't go. Do they just have a little toilet in there? I think you're supposed
to pee out one molecule at a time and wipe it on the dollars.
So you get pee on your fingers. Just little tiny amounts. Is there, I guess,
Can we go to a toll booth real quick?
No.
Can we go check one out?
And do what?
Just to see if they have a bathroom on site.
You want to go to the toll house, Fatso?
What the hell?
I'm going to the gym, I'm working on myself.
You didn't go to the...
Well, I just had to say that.
You didn't have to say Fatso.
It would not have made sense if I said skinny, Mr. Thin.
Mr. Sweet Tooth.
I've had a bit of a sweet tooth recently.
Me too.
And I've been eating a candy...
I had a Rice Krispies this morning.
Haven't had those in forever.
That's what I eat sometimes before I go to the gym.
That's what I started because Noah said that's good.
I learned this from Sam Sulek that you're supposed to eat Rice Krispie.
Oh, interesting.
A Rice Krispie treat before the gym because it's carbohydrates that is fastly available.
So says a 21 year old on YouTube.
Yeah, he's the smartest 21 year old I've ever seen.
There's absolutely no discussion about that. It's completely true.
Oh yeah, he's incredible.
We should start making gym vlogs.
Yeah.
Speaking of vlogs, you know what I have is our Applebee's vlog that I never edited.
I never edited. Do you remember this? We made an Applebee's. No, I don't know. It
was a video of us. We went to Applebee's in Astoria because you were going to get
a TV for Black Friday and we filmed ourselves. It was the worst Black Friday
ever. Yeah, it was. It was the worst Black Friday on record, but we filmed
this vlog and I just have all the footage on my phone of us eating the food
and going,
"I don't remember this at all." We filmed it. I remember going to Applebee's,
but not filming the vlog. I'll put it together after this. I'm getting on my
PC after this and I'm editing together our Applebee's vlog. We're hitting the
six month mark where I need to go to one of these restaurants again. Oh yeah,
Olive Garden, Cracker Barrel, Carrabba's, Applebee's, TGI Friday's, Red Lobster.
There's a... You know what we could do? We could get on the Q58,
go to the
Olive Garden at the mall. You're 58 and you're Q. Q anon. Guess what that
Q stands for. Q.
What the hell? What?
It's not that strange. You think that we're... He said, "Do you guys hate
my guts?" I think he thinks we're mad at him. Are you mad at me?
Are you mad at us? Yeah,
I just woke up on the wrong side of the fucking you did. I woke up on the wrong
side of the truck bed this morning. You did not wake up on a truck bed, woke up
in a truck shut up. Oh, you didn't work a work up on a truck. Lady kicked me
out.
Shut up. My old lady came on. I was drinking and and sleeping and drinking
and drooling. That was drinking and drooling. You got a
you got a rule if you drink because then you get the liquid out of you and you
can drink more. I liquid is not supposed to stay. No liquid is not supposed to
stay in your body. Get all the liquid. Get that shit out out of liquid equals
time as fast as you know. It is a way you can die liquid in your lungs.
Yeah, yeah, you can die from this scared. That's going to happen to me. I
think it happened. I think I have you ever
the stuff there's some stuff that gets in your lungs. Maybe breathe in a
the yeah, I imagine just getting something really small and you're like
small, not small enough, not big enough to choke you, but you can just breathe
and it just goes in. If you breathe in a cheerio, does it just stay there for
your entire life? I was literally thinking about this yesterday, really,
because I was trying to get a tonsil stone out of my throat. You have a
tonsil stone? Oh, not anymore. I got it out. Whoa, you got that little poker.
You know, my girlfriend's got those. My girlfriend's got a tonsil stone poker.
Really? I don't use a poker. I just like it's a little piece of metal. You lick
You lick the tonsil stone until it comes out?
Yeah, I push it with my tongue and I don't lick it.
Wait, you have amazing tongue dexterity.
We were all talking about this last night at dinner.
I don't know why I didn't know it was crazy to be able to do that.
He left. He left when we talked about tongue stuff.
Oh. My bad bitch.
You missed out on big tongue conversation.
Big tongue conversation.
But you can't do that? You can't?
I can't do that. All the way back?
Kind of.
I'm worried that will happen too when I do it.
I'm worried because it's so small and I'm like I'm not going to choke on this,
but if it comes out and I breathe it in, is it there? I don't think you
breathe it. I think when you breathe in something, it still goes down your like
your throat. I don't think it goes to your lungs, but air goes to your lungs
air goes to your lungs, but I don't think that food goes in your lungs. I
think that the the lung hole is too small. I think maybe if you like so
little, I think maybe a sprinkle could get in there. That's what I'm scared of
man. A toss of stones is like the size of a sprinkle, but I think a sprinkle is
small enough that I think there's probably something a fail safe in the
lungs to the puzzle zone is a body sprinkle. It's just food and oh my God,
you know they call sprinkles a silent killer. Yeah,
thousands of people every year. One
that's why people, you know people, you
you're more likely to be killed by a sprinkle than a shark attack. Absolutely
have
something. You used to put sprinkles on mashed potatoes. Yeah,
one one called chives subreddit. I always like to look at on reddit.
is very funny to look at our slash, our slash sharks, because it's all is it
ante or pro it's mostly pro right. The the majority is people who are like you
know they like sharks even too much. They're like sharks. If you kill get
killed by a shark, you were doing something stupid. You shouldn't be out
in that far out in the ocean. Stop making excuses for these fucking sharks
man like and they're they're they're front. They're basically dogs is that
ever they run defense, but every single every single day somebody comes into the
a bread it who's like twelve years old or thirteen years old and
link that is like someone got killed by a shark. So it's like look at this
this guy got killed by a shark. Sharks are evil and every you fucking idiot.
You're probably twelve years old. Get the fuck out of here. The trucks are
not even they're saying they constantly that's all it is is just people
fighting about. I'll be like like saying like how do you how can you explode a
shark? If it tries to attack you get the fuck out of
I'm not rocking with sharks. No, I love sharks, but I think a distance yeah to
look at in a video, you love sharks the same way you love a celeb and I love
the sun from my distance with the celebs you're up in. I don't I doesn't know
any sharks. He knows plenty of so yeah, as a rule, I do not watch celeb videos,
because it makes me gives me FOMO yeah, yeah, fuck I can't wait for fucking
Friday night. You see if I had a text, I would have been there. Well, no, it's
it's like Golden Globe. I'm going to be up with all rolling with all these
these people on Friday nights. So I don't I'm not going to watch on a
Tuesday. I think they had a lot of random people at the Golden Globes this
year. I think you could have gone. I was at the Golden Globes. They whoa really
did you see the sandwich guy from the Instagram? He went there. Yeah. I saw
the sandwich guy from Instagram. Oh, and on the fat Jewish. I saw the fat.
He's still around. He's still around.
No, he got deployed.
that is really getting you that much. The fat Jewish is in Israel fighting a
horrible war. This is making you die laughing. Okay, imagine him with his
big Pikmin ass haircut. Imagine him being hung by Hamas by his giant fucking
rat tail somewhere in the street, Old West style. Is he has a tail like a
rat? Yeah, what the hell? Just because he's Jewish? No, because he's fat.
He's more fat than he is Jewish, if you ask me. What if the fat Jewish
got on... Fat Jewish, stay away from Ozempic, okay? Yeah. You are not...
you will lose everything about you and I'm sick of Osempic and what govy.
This is actually to have friend pics in baloney
Osempic and bulgogi. Well, govy, that's the other one. It's what govy you
have the same man. You've been good. No, this is my friend was on what govy
what govy
I didn't Google it. I didn't Google. I had no no, he's ever heard. Yeah,
govy. You never heard of that. No, I know two people. That's a Harry.
that's a Harry Potter. I know somebody who overdosed on will go be and had to go
to the hospital and eat food. That was the cure.
I'm not kidding. You had to eat food. Oh, my God. This is an article that I
would click on from Facebook, a click bait article. It would say, you know,
top ten celebrities from the seventies if they were on Ozempic
Dom Delos through the power of AI. We've worse in Wales. Yeah, exact Orson
Wells is good. Dom Delos
Chris Farley, Chris Farley, Farley is a great that's the name. I was trying to
norma from tears, John Candy, John Dandy yeah, he should have been John Kale,
John to save his life yeah. Well, that was already taken yeah. You can't have
to John Kales. I found out they would fight to the dude, John Candy and John
killer kind of opposites, aren't
I
amazing wow
we're going to write a book about this called the kale and the candy
the kale and the
by I never seen John Candy pick up a violin. Maybe that would have changed
his life.
Yeah, no, no, no, no, no, no, he lived a sad life. Did you want to be? I found a
crazy, I found a crazy, very funny. I found out a crazy name thing was the guy
who made Gary's mod his name Gary Gary Newman, Gary Newman, his last name's
Newman, but suppose it different fucking Gary Newman, the singers and you
whatever asshole ruin my old day, ruin my whole life. No, no, since you ruined my
day, I'd like for you to go ahead and ruin my entire life.
Yeah, go ahead and just go and get ten steps ahead of me wherever I go and
just ruin it. Just throw things anybody I'm about to talk to hurt them, abuse me,
ruin my life, throw away my shoes, throw away everything, throwing away your
shoes. I guess I have a life that would ruin your life. Unless you don't have
another ruin your life. Speaking of I okay, well, you don't live in
Taktown. We are we live in a total shoe desert. Yeah, we do. Actually, there's
a shoe store near me and a shoe repair. There's a trillion shoe stores here.
Yeah, yeah, so nice try Cameron, but a shoe desert just means they're more
expensive. They have become more expensive. Is that is that what what is
Food desert really food desert means that there's only cheetos around.
You only have delicious food around.
There's only snack foods, no meal foods.
So they have to ship in the meal foods so they get more expensive.
Got it, got it.
Okay.
So spaghetti would be expensive.
Spaghetti would be expensive.
In a food desert, hypothetically.
I'm learning about food deserts now.
But also a food desert, a normal desert is also a food desert.
I was just about to say that because we're going to eat.
A scorpion, a viper, some sand.
Oh wait, what's that?
it's a
lobster. You know, I can eat that giant cheeseburger. Oh, let me just get closer
no man. Mirage Yeah, have you ever experienced a full on Mirage where you
thought that there was something so amazing in front of you, but then you got
closer completely. I've only been only puddles of water. What if that happened
in your house water Mirage? You see that yeah, of course, yeah on the end of the
road, yeah, yeah, wow, I really cool to realize that it's real. It is real. It's
lot of cartoon. It's completely a true thing. I don't know what this is. I've
never experienced. Are you serious? You'll drive and you've never been in a
car. I guess you've never been in a car. I've been in a car, but not in the
summer.
It's crazy to me that you don't know, you don't, you know, you haven't
experienced this. No, I don't know what it is. Sometimes over yonder, you will,
because of the heat, the shimmer, the shimmer of the concrete, the stuff that's
like when the, like when the, when this it's so hot out that it looks like the
whole world is boiling, you know. Yeah, so that's the same thing. Yeah, like a
water. It looks like water. It's shimmer, heat shimmer. Oh, oh, that's a mirage.
That's what a mirage is. All right, I guess I get that. Yeah, I've seen that
before. Yeah, I used to think on the cicadas would make that sound. I used to
think that that those were correlated, and I used to think that that, that that
was the street boiling. The, the boiling was, yeah, like it was like a lobster and
the, like the shimmer, because it's kind of sinks up. What are you fucking talking
about? It sinks up. It doesn't happen all the time. The cicada sound and then the,
Well, I guess it's because whenever you see them cicadas in a minute, thank God,
I think they're disgusting. I hate all big. They are very discussed. I had a
dead cicada that I collected. Wow, you need to be hospitalized for odd. I
don't have it anymore.
Why not?
Probably somewhere in my old house. Yeah, it's mummified. One time, one time my
wife got me when we were in high school, one of these
boxes, frames, they call them, but it was deep box style, glass pane on the
front bunch of fucking disgusting bugs all in it and I had to pretend I liked
it. My dad got me
framed dead scorpions like that when I was a kid and it scared me. I didn't
want it in my room. I was like it's going to come to life, come out of it.
My ex had a death's head hawks moth in a frame. That's the one from
when you're a kid. That hanging up on the wall in the house.
Fight Ants of the Lambs?
Fight Ants of the Lambs.
Reboot it.
Ian, if you're watching.
Reboot it with Ian right now, man.
It puts the lotion in the basket.
Please, God, make that movie.
That was the best idea we've ever had on the show.
That is so perfect.
Holy fucking shit.
Okay.
That's funny.
Yeah.
I've never experienced a mirage, though, but that would be sad as fuck.
We used to put our face in elements of the movie.
fucking shit. Okay, that's funny. Yeah, I
never experienced a mirage, though, but that would be sad is to put our face in
elementary school used to put our the side of our face against the brick wall
and you could see the the heat shimmer. You and I also I've never experienced
how I think about it.
Desert Island with one tree. I've seen that way. I've never experienced the
coconut for lunch either a coke. Well, that you get trapped on the Desert Island
one tree. Here comes the coconut and also there's a treasure chest there, but
what the fuck you gonna do with treasure? Yeah, you're on an island.
Nobody's coming to get the you. They want, they're gonna get the treasure,
even if they show up, they're gonna get the treasure, they're hauling it back
back way over. The saddest part about treasure is it brings out man's worst.
If you were on the desert island with the one tree and you were trying to
spell out a word with the sticks to make the plane see you,
but... Swag. But, but...
but
you only have enough sticks for two letters. So you can't say help and you
can't say s o s me me
I'm on this. I'm
well, could
couldn't you just like use the sticks to if you are in the sand, if you use the
sticks to draw in the sand, the wind will pick up and blow it away. It's a
Windy Island. You can only write two letters using this. It's an island
outside of Seattle. If you try to break the sticks to make smaller letters,
they won't be visible from the plane. Chicago, yeah. What did I think Seattle
was the windy city? It's the rainy city. 'Cause that's the rainy city. Yeah.
Son of a bitch. So if I was stuck on an island in Lake Michigan... I would do
O. Yo. Yo. Yo is good. Yo is good. Yo is good, but they would think that you
would be... They would also think that you were a pirate because of Yo Ho
Ho. True. Two letters is so fucking hard, 'cause if it's three, SOS,
it's so obvious, but with two, what do you say? So so because then they're just
gonna be like, oh, the guy doesn't even want to get off. He's like, yeah, I'm on
the island, so
who cares?
Fucking get out of here, leave me here. What if you did F law law would be good
because they go, wait, there's an amazing singer on the
drop down the parachute, the reverse parachute. Don't put F you, they would
not, but they come down, they come down there.
We gotta give this guy a piece of our fucking mind.
Let's get this
oh my God, it work. I need to get off. You fucking stupid bastard
P, you have you
flying the plane all the way yeah.
Fuck you,
fly back
you can do P you they would be you. They would want to rest. I mean, because
it smells bad and pick up yeah, the smells bad they're not going to come to
the island. You could do okay, here's another one T, Y and it's like thanks in
advance. So they feel pressure like when you put that in an email, you know
six and a bass. I have to do it. I also could think why you're like being
passive aggressive. That's good. You want if they then again, they'll do it.
Yeah, I guess it's kind of that's why you're you're so afraid of being
passive aggressive. You put NP yeah, no, it's not a big problem. Don't worry
about you. I'm on you know what I do. I put
maybe like some famous persons initials like with
TC Tom Cruise Cruise TC.
Wait, I think Tom Cruise is on this island!
Oh God.
JT, John Travolta.
It's Terry Caleb.
JT could be Justin Timberlake too.
Yeah.
JT would be a good one.
JT would be a lot of different people.
Exactly.
So even if they say Justin Timberlake, I said Justin Timberlake, Justin Theroux.
Holy crap.
Whoa.
It might be him.
Yeah, PP.
Doesn't he own that, he owns that bar, Rays, with the guy from Succession, Cousin Greg?
I don't fucking know.
I actually don't even know who Justin Theroux is now that I say this.
He's in Mulholland Drive and I think he was married to Jennifer Aniston.
Lucky bastard.
I have a new fucking stupid enemy that I hate.
Well hey, there's a bar you can find him.
Jennifer Aniston, he's been married to her since she had jigglies out on TV?
Yes.
Wow.
You can go to his bar and you can give him a piece of your mind.
I'm gonna go in there and say, "Cousin Greg, Justin, stop the sex at this bar."
the same up stop the set of twenty one year old. I pick it their bar with a
son. It says stop the stocks, stop the sex. Y'all I've been thinking recently of
going in it because the thing is there's all these problems. The mailman wants me
so
speaking of the mailman, I got a I got a package right. Yeah, I got a found that
out big ass dick ass on you fucking hung like a horse. Yeah, that was loud. That's
loud, very loud as a I got a package that was supposed to be delivered. I go to
tracking I've been looking at this because I did 10 day shipping because I
was like I want to save a little. I'm looking at this I'm getting it's 10
days that's today is day 10. I look at the tracking and it says some kind
of error happened. I didn't answer I was out doing errands. I didn't answer
the door but it's the parcel service that my father works for so I
call him up and I say you need to sort your fucking company out or I'm gonna
I'm going to take it down from the inside. You said I'm going to pretend to
be I'm texting him all day. I'm saying I'm taking down your company. Really?
He said you're going to have to pay my rent and I said fuck you. No, I'm
pretending to be you. I'm going to go on your LinkedIn. I'm going to post
the ASCII middle finger shit. I just remember it is something. I just
remember something that made me feel even crazier that you were trying to
claim to be the master troll. You were too even afraid to do a prank call.
Oh, this guy calls. It just made me remember that this guy is not a prank
Trolls aren't trolling. It's breaking bro and also I already rescinded my my
throne as the master troll. I am the master. I'm just putting in context. I
make the troll last. You make the you calm the troll.
The troll's about to do something bad yeah, he's about to cross the line and
you kind of make light of it. Yes, I make light of trolling get off of that
yeah, what you troll, but sometimes I go the troll.
Don't do that. That's a that's a bad idea. You don't that's a very dangerous
doomed to many greater man than you have died playing that game. That's how not
me, because I'm the master jester. That's how Harry Houdini died. Yeah,
yeah, exactly, but that the other yeah,
we were talking he died because someone punched him in the stomach. So funny
way, yeah, and then a guy who locked himself into a bomb every day.
When we were talking about it before, I was telling you how there's like a
museum. There's like a magic shop. That's like also is like a few like
magnesium items or whatever in mid town, and I went to it. My family was here
like a year or two ago and they have this. I just I was talking to you and I
didn't realize how ridiculous this sounds, but but now I was thinking about
it. It's very funny. What the like main attraction, the main thing they have
there is that it's a bathtub that Houdini escaped from
lame as fucking stuff. What are you doing? Where you escape from a bat? I'll
now escape from my bed, even though it's very comfortable.
so that early in the morning, I really escape like well when we see I will
escape from this bath. I'm now escaping from the pantry.
Here I go. Was he around when taft was president because maybe everyone
thought that like I was like Oh, my God, the president got stuck in the
bathtub. Is that maybe that's the classic taft? Did he fatly die there?
He fatly got stuck in die, but he just got stuck and it was a story. I
they had to cover him in lard to get him out. Well, doing some math in my head.
How do you get into the bathtub if you're that fat versus he got fatter?
It's easy to get in. He got in, it was fine. They handed him one donut,
stuck forever. Well, you can kind of just jump in, you can just jump in and
you'll just... He took his corset off. There's the force of gravity will push
you in. Yeah, like you can put a bunch of kimchi into a jar,
but you can't shake it out. Exactly. Well, I've been defeated and I'm back
thinking you two hate me. You know who else hates me? My dad, I found out.
Because you didn't call him to tell him you were going home for Christmas?
No, no, no. I talked to him about that. In the past four days, my phone screen has been
crazy wigging out and I've butt-dialed my dad six times. He hasn't answered a single
time, but I've been waiting. I was waiting for the call. I was like, "Fuck it. He's going
to call me and then he's going to be like, 'Hey, what'd you call me?' six times, whatever."
But way worse than that, he has not made contact with me about this at all. And then I texted
I was like, hey, I but dialed you again zero contact. So he doesn't even care
that I but dialed him or he doesn't even he didn't even think that this or
something. Maybe your dad got stuck in the bathtub.
He is not fat. My dad did P90X. So did my dad, my dad and your dad. Same
shadow. Yeah, same exact silhouette. Yeah, they look like my poor character
design. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Very copied and pasted. Yeah, guys. My dad was
younger. My dad looked like human Shrek. Human Shrek? Yeah. The good looking Shrek? When
Shrek turns into a human in Shrek 2, that's what my dad looked like. What a doll. He's
a good looking guy. Let's get him. Let's go get him. Well yeah, I'm getting him. I'm at
war with his company. I don't think you could escalate. And by the way. He's given me a
lot of free merch from his company. So and you're going to betray that? Well I'm going
to impersonate with all this merch, I'm going to wear the socks that he gave me from the
company.
They're not going to be like, "Hey, you, do you work here?"
Oh wait, you have the socks on.
You have the socks on.
You only get those if you're an employee.
Of where?
Of FedEx.
Is it FedEx?
I thought he was a UPS guy.
No, no, he used to be.
Then he switched teams.
Wow.
That is crazy.
Yeah, that's a double crosser.
That is some crazy shit.
That is spineless.
That is Babe Ruth from the Red Sox and the Yankees.
Go to a minor, go to a DHL.
He was about to. That was actually.
He wanted to switch again.
No, no, no.
This guy's the biggest snake ever.
No wonder he was your dad.
He was a free agent.
What are you talking about?
You fucking snake.
I'm not a snake.
Yeah, you are.
Snake.
I'm not a snake.
You're going to hop ship.
I'm not going to hop ship.
Or jump ship.
What do you think? I'm going to join.
You're going to turn tail.
I'm going to join some different podcast.
Turn coat. I mean, turn coat.
Yep. Being Ian with Jordan and Patrick.
I'm going to become Ian now.
Yeah. Or no, you're going to go join that.
Yeah.
I have them on my mind.
I have them on my mind. I love him. Yeah, me too.
He was a free agent for a little bit in all these... And they're throwing
contracts at him. He was having meetings with the executives. He's so good at
shipping and logistics. He's so good at shipping and logistics, bro. Did he do
like a DeAndre Jordan in Dallas situation where he told, he maybe told
UPS like, "Yeah, I'm gonna resign with you. Yeah, yeah, 10 year, $50 million
exactly what it was, but I remember when I was a kid. And then the UPS guys
driving around. And when they see him. New Hampshire, looking for him. Well,
he worked at a UPS in Massachusetts, so. Oh, boy. He actually just probably
moved to a little closer to home. Not even loyal to a location. And let me
guess, let me guess, your dad doesn't stay in the same place all the time.
He doesn't just sit there. He betrays his area by going by walking around.
Betrays his chair for the couch. Oh, my God, your dad's an ultimate piece
- You have not moved from this chair.
This has been your chair.
- No, and you know what?
And you know what?
Maybe FedEx deserves to be taken down from the inside.
- I think that is a bad beef to make
because I think that they could get things to you.
I'm just saying FedEx--
- They can get anything to you.
- You might think that you're not,
but FedEx could get you touched.
- We could all get--
- They know your address, bro.
- We could all switch up to Green Mountain Express,
which is a local personal service
in New Hampshire and Vermont.
Sounds like coffee to me.
So he's not even putting on for his city by working for the local companies, working for
this big disgusting national change.
Change?
Change.
This is Good Burger.
Remember Good Burger?
This is Barbershop.
I remember genuinely when I was a kid when he told me he was leaving UPS to go to FedEx,
in my head that was as big as like the Alex Rodriguez trade.
He didn't even like...
I mean it's the same thing.
I was like rumored that a rod was probably going to go to the Red Sox and then he went to the
Yankees. I was like, this is like pretty much the same thing as my dad switching shipping
company. Yes, a huge fucking backstabbing snake betrayal. It's not a snake betrayal. Benedict
Arnold. This is like a snake. Benedict Arnold is crazy. Full Benedict. Complete Benedict.
That's crazy to call my dad Benedict Arnold for switching up shipping. Okay, Benny Doran.
Full hollandaise bro. You hear Benny Dor is switching sides? Who's Benny Dor? That's your
Ben Doren, Ben Dick Doren, like a rod be door.
What like a rod? That's not his name is not Benny Bennett. Are you dumb?
Ben, as in Benedict Arnold,
which he would have been being old, being old, being old. Yeah, being old.
You can't call it a barn. I feel like I've given away too much information
about my father's. Okay, well, give and he could probably fake stuff in there.
My dad is five foot one, ninety pounds. Red herrings. Okay, five foot one. What
else about him? He's sixteen.
Okay, yeah, I know that about him. I'm helping you out. Yeah. My dad is five
foot one. No, but you have to sprinkle in real fact to make it so that people
can't tell his address. He's been married to my mom since 1995. Something
more personal about his body.
What's his shoe? Grower.
That's awesome, man. That'd be a little bit of a disappointment to find out my dad was a grower.
Yeah? For you?
Let me see it in the gym shorts. I don't want it to be gone when you're walking out into the living room.
Right.
Let me see that, Dad.
I guess.
Have you ever, have you seen your father's penis as an adult? Because I mean, you see it as a kid.
He was an adult when I saw it.
Well, yeah, same.
He was, that's, well, no, when you're a kid and you see your dad's penis, it's like, you know.
"Whoa!" "Oh my gosh!" It's awesome, right? That's what you're saying.
It's not exactly like the Hearthstone announcer when you open a booster
pack. "Whoa!"
Legendary. I used to... I just feel like if you see
your dad's penis when you're a grown man and he's also grown... You have.
What's the limit that you have? I never have. I never have. I think
the limit is... But I feel like you would be seeing an old friend.
The limit is exactly this. The limit is if the kid gets to the height where
potentially without jumping, it could hit his head,
that's time to put it away.
Yeah. No, but I'm just saying... If he can't clear under your legs,
just walk under, you're not even real, it's completely oblivious. There's a
dick on his... That's when you can't show it anymore. But once,
as soon as it touches his head...
Enough. I'll say it, when you touch your kid's head with your penis,
you should start wearing clothes.
That's what I think, man. I don't know if that's crazy. That's the line that I
think should be established. Don't touch your head of your child with your
penis. Don't touch your child with your penis. Yeah. And that's a... And you can...
And you take that to the bank. Yeah, that's a... We'll put that on a shirt.
Yeah. We're gonna put that... No, not don't do it, but like when it happens.
Wait until it happens. Wait until it happens. Because... That's how you know.
that's how you know it's when it happens. That's how you
not a big deal. It's just a sign and you can and you can let your
kid walk through your legs. If you have pants on yeah, yeah,
of course, everybody does that yeah, yeah, come on walk through
yeah, go ahead and this you know what this does. I'm playing
London Bridge. This is going this this
punishes
dads with large ones. Yeah, or short dads or short dad short
dad dads with maybe short legs and I don't like short. That
should be taller than some. Dad should be taller than some. With a small thing.
With a small thing. Yeah, tall, big and lanky. Your dad should be a grower.
It keeps him humble. Your dad should be a samer. Exactly. Yeah, you should have
the same penis as your father. A samer is a small shower. Yes. Your father and
you have to have... It doesn't move at all. It doesn't change. Completely
identical penises that you could not even tell in a line up that they're any
different. Is it true that skinny guys have the biggest rods? No. No, I think
with guys with the biggest rods? No, because I was thin in high school.
Are surgically changed to have that? Yeah. Guys with giant penises have
probably short legs, longer legs. Well, I guess what they always say is if you're
fat and then you lose weight, it makes your dick look bigger because there's
like less fat around your groin. What was the name of that porn star that had
the fake penis? OG Mudbone. Was that OG Mudbone? Yes. That was so funny,
man. That was so fucking funny. Speaking of a troll, this wasn't... That is a
huge troll as a troll, but also as a troll to the school, my friend's
dodgeball team,
they named themselves OG Mudbone. Yes, yes, yes, and then the assistant
principal looked it up in her office and almost and almost came yeah, and
almost and I was a to the picture of almost completely jizzed, but who
they also put fake nut in that yeah, but do they have I mean who's is I
am building this prop for him. Yeah, that's got to be a fun thing to
invent because the guy I'm willing to bet the person who invented that that
machine is a millionaire is not only a millionaire, but was not trying to
probably not yeah yeah, and then a
porno company trying to build like it was like you've done what we're looking
for trying to build a new like
exactly
you know the push catch up dispenser that they started. It was around the
same time. It probably was the same technology
and he had a very Oppenheimer type thing where he was like looking he's looking
on the barrel of it needs just going like my God, it was
like cake decorators like a frosting mechanical piping bag and for some
reason this kind of looks like a nut that they were putting in. That was not
convincing man now and also by the way, if I was a female porn star and I was
drinking nut all day and night right, I'm used to it at this point. If I get
to a porn shoot and they're saying this time it's fucking yogurt now,
you know, that's what they put real in it. It's not real. I feel with the real
not maybe they tried that cold real not that why well that probably better to
have it's all this stuff. They like they would still like some sperm banks,
which is let like little ug knots go in and just little what's an ug not not as
a star wars creature. Okay, sounded like a slur. Can you just when I guess it
okay, when you when you start what's the slur for ugly people, because I'm not
this kind of sounds like ugly. Now, what is it? What kind of star wars creature
is it? You know the little guys on Bespin that take apart C-3PO and Star Wars
5? I don't know the names of the planets. Cloud City. When you go into this
Star Wars shit, can you please... I have not talked about it in a long time
because I'm a grown man now. I'm asking about it. Can you just stick to the
things that we would know, John? Okay, Star Wars Episode 5, they go... C-3PO
gets taken... Which movie is that? Which movie is that? Empire Strikes Back.
Okay, thank you. Empire Strikes Back, C-3PO gets taken... The Vampire Strikes
back. He gets taken into the Empire bites back will be a good. That's a good
parody.
He gets taken into that room. Let's go to you to the 2007 taken apart. Remember
what do the guys look like? They're little tiny guys. He said this man's
receding gray hairlines. They look like humans and they have the bulldog faces.
Okay, I don't do it. A bulldog. Did you guys know this about bulldogs? Bulldogs
have the attributes of a real bull. Really? The other day I was walking. Phil,
we see a bulldog. Are you just going to say that it charged it literally charge
didn't try to bite charged it into the side. It has the attributes of a real
bull. Yeah, you think that's funny
the
of a real bull. Is it right? It charged him and did not try to bite did not try
to jump. Not normal dog stuff rammed him in the side and knocked him over for zero
reason completely unprompted. It's because he's red. I just realized they
probably thought he was a skateboard. They probably thought that he was one of
these flags that are red. That too. You know what I would do an amazing
protest about? What? Or not a protest, just some kind of art piece.
I would go out into the bull pit, bull pen,
that's baseball. The bull zone. I think it's called the bull pen in baseball
because of... The ring, it's a bull ring. And I would pull out the red
flag, he comes, he shreds it apart, destroys it, there goes red. Yeah. I'd
pull out
the American flag, it's got red on it, here it comes,
ripped apart. You let it get ripped apart. Well, first, I will get to the
part. Listen, I do that the bowl rips or the American flag. I obviously cry
patriotic. Okay, and I pledge of allegiance real quick, but then I pull
out the LGBTQ plus. There's red on it. I cover up the red, but not in a way
where I'm disrespecting the red. What does the red mean on the flag? Red
stands for red, ready or not. We hear we're here.
And then I would hold it and then the bull would do nothing. And I would say,
"That's what the American people need to be like with these bulls."
Destroy America.
With these LGBT people.
But do not destroy the LGBTQ community.
Rip down America built by...
But leave the LGBTQ out of it.
And bulls, stop charging.
And I would hold up the asexual pride flag to this bull and the bull would just
get confused.
It's never seen...
The bull would say, "What? Do they have sex? Do they not have sex? Do they have
sex that they're in relationships. If I was I would just have his head would
explode. I would have a shot gun and I would just shoot the bowl if it came
after my would you kill you don't want to you don't want to eat. So it doesn't
hit me. I'm calling bull shit. The point is that the bull doesn't get you.
The point is to go. The point is to wait is to zone out to the clowns come out.
You just yeah. So if I the master, I blow its head up. It's not I can just
wait.
I don't like this plant is killing a wild animal. I really kill it. This
plan makes the shot gun
in the head. Maybe it will live in what were resident evil. It's got a
bones on its head. You think that it would wipe away all the skin in the
re sound bones on its head. Maybe I could just bring in a video of a
bull. It's no, you know what I would bring in one of those files from jail
and I would file its horns down. That's all I weren't sharp
This is a video of a donkey getting hit by a train on a Pakistan railway.
This is a video of a Chinese factory worker getting flayed to ribbons.
Yeah, I would like to see, do they still do the bowl thing or is that illegal now?
Yeah, they still do it. They have it on Pluto TV, man.
Oh, I forgot you told me about this.
Oh, yeah, they do.
Which America, though?
Native America.
Well, I respect that.
reservation. Do they both?
Bullfighter shoes are
like really weird like cowboy boot meet sneakers, right?
Is this something that I just saw?
You said meat sneaker?
Cowboy X sneaker.
Oh. I don't pay attention to
fashion so much. I more pay attention
to the athleticism. Fashion's a
big part of bullfighting. It is.
Well that is true. It's probably one of the bigger
fashion sports. Bullfighting is
essentially ice skating. We talked about it before.
Their fashion is crazy. They have
crazy style fashion. They starch their pants. Monster Energy cowboy clown
combination three-way combo. You ever seen how they do these pants?
I don't watch videos about how they make pants. They take their jeans,
these cowboy guys, they take their jeans. They take their jeans, give them back!
They take their jeans off, put it on the ironing board, pour out like a whole
bottle of spray starch on it, then iron them so that when they walk around
they're stiff as hell. I saw a video of a guy doing this the other day of
I'm gonna start starching up the jeans and I really want to try that actually.
I have it at home now. I bought it after I saw it.
You bought it? Really? Do you want to borrow it?
Fuck yes. Borrow it. You use it.
We can bring, I can bring the starch here.
We can turn this into an ironing board.
We can do the clothing episode.
That's gotta be the first episode.
I need those smelling salts so bad man.
What do you got going on the rest of the day? You gotta be all piped up for it.
No I just need them. I have no...
Will to live? I have no electricity in my brain.
You can smell my...
You can smell my finger. That's him.
yet he reacts to scares. I'm going to scares me. I don't he's the scare. I'm
not going to scream, but I don't like it. Yeah,
okay.
Well, there was an attempt made to be a better. I do think that I have a
big
way.
You're back, man. You're way back. You're back. Did I get away? We're scared
of you. I don't want to go against you, so I'm going to go ahead and stop
talking talk. You need to talk. Why man? I have nothing. Don't say there's nothing
coming from me.
It's because you went to the gym before this. You used up all of your energy. We
had a big pasta dinner last night. You used up all that. I didn't have time to
have my leftovers before this. I was already gonna be late. I didn't have time
to eat. You made a crazy move to me at the pasta restaurant. What? You got the
fettuccine alfredo with broccoli instead of chicken. I saw that. I wanted the
veggie. I didn't want chicken. Also, chicken was a little more expensive. I
I didn't want both. I wanted to have I just have them don't eat that much
veggie. So I always try to get something green, even if it's simply a broccoli
and I'm not both adding both the broccoli and the chicken was like
twelve dollars or so. Now that I'm not going to do that now that you are in
the gym, I am going to have to put you through a full. We're going to break
down your diet. We're going to go to you eating zero things, eating nothing,
going days without food, days without back up and then slowly build it back
reintroducing things like beef jerky until you have a fully protein rich diet with iron.
Have you ever made a steak at your house? No. I'm going to get you making some of the most
disgusting well done steaks ever. Don't make much meat because I'm the only person who
eats meat. Here's what you do. Oh yeah, that's a good reason. You can eat tofu. Tofu's good.
I eat a lot of tofu. I like tofu, fair amounts. If you can make it in all different styles.
I know a way to make tofu. I eat a lot of tofu and a lot of fish. There's a way to make tofu
feel exactly like McDonald's chicken nuggets. I like putting it, we bread it with panko
and we do all the types of things and it's nice and crispy and good. If you want to know
my chicken nugget secret, I'll tell you after the show. Send it over. They're chicken C-H-I-K-N.
Back in my day, there was a C and an E and no apostrophe in the word chicken. And they
and they also do what's his company, Gardein, they do that with every single
type of meat, B, E, apostrophe, S, F, S, S, S, Bs, listen, Gardein, you better
Bs, Bs, you bring it home and you open the bag and all the Bs fly out of
you.
So what you get for not eating meat? Gardein, you better be Gardein your
headquarters, because I'm coming after you for you bastardizing the flesh of
our animals. That's right. You better have a sniper on a turret. A sniper,
apostrophe are no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
it's a snipe apostrophe are a K apostrophe forty seven yeah, yeah, instead
of the instead of the dash.
They have F F F apostrophe. This apostrophe is flustering me. That's okay.
I can't even think about what even the spelling is because it's light rhyme F
apostrophe S H. When you get the fish fillet really B E apostrophe F P
apostrophe RK wait. They went for the funniest one to me is F, but F B
apostrophe F really you haven't seen that F. It's so funny. Yeah, but I go
for B. F. It's funny F, but F go for maybe make it out of beats. Call it
beat. Beat is good. You can use beet roots to mimic the look of blood and
fake meat. But this is exactly the point I'm making. I used to watch my
exes vegan, so I'd make vegan food. Now we had watch a lot of this cool shit
when I was young and vegan food videos. It's crazy how far it's come. It's all
it all basically tastes pretty close to what it is. But I think being in fish is
like spot on. I am a little bit. Vegan fish is like so good at being the worst
fish you've ever eaten. I am a little bit convinced that the fake meat stuff is
really bad for you. It tastes a little bit good. He's went like this. He said
vegan fish is spot on. I was like, oh cool. And then he said it's spot on at
being the worst fish you ever tasted. And then he I said what? And he said it's
okay, master troll master, what are these people doing? Kaleb go kill them
their little kids. They're just sitting there. We're the go kill them. I'm not
gonna kill up, kill them.
Okay, I guess I'll kill the chill go kill them. No, it's making me laugh to
say that when there's kids.
Why do they do that? I don't know. I think it's because it's the only cultural
thing in New York. All these kids who live in New York, literally think the
work. Well, they just think that every building is their house. They think of
the city belongs to them. Oh, I hate the children of New York. I think I agree. I
don't think that it's possible to have a good child. No, yeah, I went to Wendy's
after the gym
on we, we, we went to the gym at two, got out at three. I can't go anywhere. You
can't go, you cannot go to Wendy's at three PM. They're infesting the streets.
They're too many of them. It was literally, it was so, I was the only one
in there. I'm at the kiosk, I'm waiting, I order, I wait for my food, I turn
around whole fucking school in there. Yeah, it was like a field trip to
Wendy's. It was fucked up.
The thing about kids in New York is none of them are the silent loner nerd
types. No, no, they're all, they're all, they're all like a public library.
They're all adventurous. Having the most fun day ever. Shut up, you fucking
kid. They all have 12 friends. It's crazy. I'm sick of these kids having
friends. I hate it. I don't want them to live here. They all have these
cliques, they call them. And so basically the jocks. Some are goths, some
more jobs, the gods, the teacher, the lunch, this is what the world is like
which is different from the nerds, the wolves, the wolverines,
the farmers and the red coats, the red
they were so fucking the red coats in school were so fucked. The king's guard,
their slang was all weird. They'd already hard pack the teacher's guard
for the teacher
my
so
decking
just a bunch of thirteen year old kids holding Spears
I've been obsessed with those videos. Neil Neil before the teacher
now he's such a teacher's guard, a fucking guard at looking garden,
teacher, but that kids such a teacher's guard even guards a substitute. Do you
always have a patrol or hall not call monitor. He said pop patrol yeah that
Bob patrol on your teeth. We didn't have a hall monitor. No, no, it was just
well. If it was it was an adult. We had a hall monitor in my middle school man.
Why don't they give a kid that middle school? I went to middle school asshole
stop trying to monitor at your home school. Yeah, it was a disgusting robot
tentacles. He was running around named Ethan. I we had a hall monitor and it
was of course the biggest nerd in the entire school. Of course, why is me and
I don't remember his name, but I think it was one of those guy girl names. If I
ever saw Leslie back, I literally think it was Les back when I was in school or
Cameron back when I was in school, if I ever saw a nerd, I'd fucking slap them
in the face and stomp on their head and just fucking straight the fuck up. I
used to kill nerds. I've fucking killed them. I used to fucking I used to hide
behind shit and assassins. I thought you were pointing at somebody. I would
stand inside. I would wait inside my locker for two to three hours at a time,
skipping class and when I heard somebody walking by saying the approximate
quadratic
door door open arm around the neck pull them in close, shut the door, put the
lock on from the inside, change the combination really fast, reset it to a
different number and then you're in there sweating with that kid and then I
be I kill the kid. I kill the kid bloody body and I say
bite him a little bit and then I say the jocks in their regards
Jack's know you're planning and that yeah it would be it's like a full mortal
combat. If I tell he was with his little nerd click three friends, I pull him in.
He doesn't know where he's in the darkness, the inky blackness, I'm
strangling him, I'm biting him, I'm eating, I'm snapping his legs backwards,
I'm doing all types. I'm giving it to him. I blown his back out and then is
and then is and then isn't his friends. I just see they see, but they're
saying us to the locker. They see the door
from inside. They hear, but they hear
man, the door slowly swings on
skeleton. You ripped you picked him clean. Oh my God, full bone white yep
a skeleton as white as a bone. I they should do a hit man game. They should do
a as white brittle and bony as a clean bone as a clean bone of all. They
should do a hit man style game for school where you are in school and you
have to kill every nerve and by the way you go to a school that has piran.
that's a good idea or you're the jock yeah, you're the jock, you're the jock
or you're the nerd getting back at the job. No, it would be. I don't want to
have nerds. It would be so cool video game programmers or nerds. It's the
only way not to make a hit man called the human piranha and you're like
trademark is that you to completely clean them off the book takes so long.
It takes a full day every time yeah, this one looks like the work of the
human piranha. I was one of the or other or it could, I guess, be normal again
piranhas. This is a work of a copycat. It's messy. He didn't clean the plate
and he cleaned the bones. Look, there's still there's still part of a leg on
this. Yeah, there's still mostly leg. He left the grizzly bit at the nails on
yeah, the real human brown eats to toenails to toenails is technically
bones. That's not true. It's not technically hair jinx. What the hell the
other day, Pat Patrick said jinx after I just said something and he didn't say
anything. I said I'm on my way and he said jinx and I saw you replied and I
said double jinks. I knew it. I still on double. I understood what it meant, but
it made me laugh. Someone says something and he's like jinx, but I said double
jinx and so you're still on double jinx. You've never got my double. You can't
talk and you can't talk as much as I want. Well, plus that was a jinx over
text, so I just can't text. You know every word is another coke that you owe
him. No, it's not you'll be still. It's a how many words per hour does he
usually speak thousands. I mean, I wish I have a soda party. You're gonna have a
full so to have a soda party. Do you are never having a so? Oh my God, I'm gonna
have a my water party. Not on my watch. You're having a soda party, but we're
not bringing cups. That's the and you gotta you have to waterfall. Uh huh.
Every single one having any so soda party, little kid, you guys aren't gonna
fill up the pool with every single type of soda and it's gonna be the ultimate
soda. Diet doctor, diet, doctor, lemon, coke tea. That's what we used to call
that diet, doctor lemon Coke, tea, because you hit all the bubbles on the
top of the thing and it reads diet, doctor, lemon, tea, their bubbles.
What else are they? They're bubbles. You pop every bubble for every selection
and there's different styles of bubble on it to
remember. Not sure what that means. There's different types of bubble.
There's the round one for Dr Pepper. There's the star one for diet. There's
you went to a fancy cup. McDonald's has those. I didn't go to no make that. We
didn't have McDonald. I didn't go to another Donald. I didn't go to make no
McDonald's where I'm from. We don't have McDonald's where I was from.
I'm done sounding like that. I'm Kylo Pets. We didn't have McDonald's while I was from.
What accent is that? Why is it so alluring? I don't know. I'm trying to remember too.
It's a little old. Like old. Some part of the South that I came from. It's a guy from
Pet Sematary. Oh, it's John Lithgow? You don't want to go off that road. That does sound
like John Lithgow more than I think about it. Well, I think the guy from Pet Sematary
is John Lithgow. No, that's not John Lithgow. I thought it was. No, the old is maybe the
the new one, but the old one, the guy what's his name? Judd Crandall
Judd. Whoa, big time. All right, we need to end.
I'm having fun, but we do need to end.
What do we plug the Patreon right now? No, we're on the Patreon.
Oh, we're on the Patreon. Just keep your eyes to the ground. Keep your eyes
peeled, and by the way, we got... Oh, we get... Oh, Junior Associate. A short
film that we were all in is coming out on the 2nd of February on Home
- Planet's YouTube channel.
And I'm gonna be in Tampa, Florida,
the 19th and 20th, opening for Mr. Adam Friedland,
who recently went on Hassan Piker's stream, guys.
He just told me that.
- Wow.
- So, if you're a big Hassan fan,
I'm sure we'll be doing that kind of political stuff.
- Yeah, political material.
- Yep.
- And keep your eye out in the movie "Junior Associate" for--
- An Easter egg.
- An Easter egg-stra that you may remember from this show.
maybe an episode of the show. I forgot we met him there. I met him there. Yep.
Somebody at this table and he's not you guys his friend at all. He wasn't our
friend. No, Alan, Alan. It was Alan. It was Alan from the focus group. We
discovered him. Cameron discovered him on the shoot. Full scouted. We is the
man. We love. We should have a premiere and have Alan do a speech before that
would be. That's a really good idea. He would kill it. He would fucking kill. He
that kills everything. I sat at the table. He's a monster. I pretended to eat.
Here is
the Junior Associates.
All right, bye guys.
Higher life. Oh, I just remembered something. Caleb, you died in my dream
the other night. What?
A big piece of debris hit you in the head and you died. They should make
technology where I can go into your dream and stop that. That's a bad omen
there's that big puddle thing that's forming over there. I had a dream that New York City was being
nuclear bombed and there's explosions happening and I was hugging my fiancée and saying "I love you so
much, oh my god, I can't believe this is happening, I'll always love you, I'm so sorry this world is
ending like this" and I look over and Caleb gets hit in the head with a giant rock. Was I in the
dream or was I implied to be dead for years? Just Caleb was in the dream getting killed for one
second. At least I wasn't killed. I had a dream where I was a very bad guy and here's how you can
tell. Number one I was involved in serial killing. Which is not that big of a deal.
The only dream I've ever had like this. Yes. But number two, get my partner in
crime Ellen Degeneres. Wow. And she, you and Ellen were just in love. I would bait people into this room and
then she would murder them with a chainsaw. That's crazy. And that was my dream. Isn't that a crazy
dream? I did have a crazy, not crazy dream, but last night I had a dream and it
was you guys were both there.
Whoa.
And it was me remembering the time that we went to New York City for the first time we were at that Burger King.
I remember that.
But the weird thing in my dream, it was basically the exact same, exactly how both like we all remember it.
But I went up to buy onion rings at the Burger King on that bus.
You know, the bus would stop at the Burger King.
Yes.
I went there and I just wanted to get onion rings and zesty sauce.
And the guy said, "One large onion ring, that'll be $18."
This is such a funny dream.
I said to him, I said, what the hell?
$18 for onion rings.
How big is the how big is the thing?
And he shows me the size of the thing is like that big.
And I was like, oh, I'll just get the medium.
Then he said, oh, then that'll be $8.
And he said, it's $8 for medium, but it's $18 for the large.
Oh, my God. Inception.
It's about dreams.
But all Christopher Nolan could think about was a building spinning around.
I would rather be a- die a von Ehrich style brother suicide death
where I lose all my limbs and then I kill myself
than be your therapist.
[Music]