(farting)
- See I'm getting better at making fake farts.
- So listen to one sound, listen to a sound right now.
(farting)
- Yeah, that one was, that one was very mouthful.
- I'm gonna close my eyes.
You're gonna do one fake one and one real one
and I won't know which one is which.
- No I shouldn't, I think it's 'cause I ate
vegan meatballs last night and I think that's making my gains.
So you decided to ruin my fun last night for dinner?
That one was... wait, give me the next one.
They both sound real to me.
They were both my mouth.
They were both fake?
Uh-huh.
Well, then you broke the rule of the game.
I thought at least one was real.
No.
But I thought you broke it the other way.
I thought you said both...
or you did both. What do you think I was going to pick up the mic and put it up
to my butt? I would have to smell that. I'm not a scientist. I don't I can't
figure out how you might do stuff. I you weren't in the room. Okay, thank God,
but you were over there and you walked in after I had farted
and I said to myself, Oh, my goodness,
you said out loud. Oh, my God, you open the door. I've been farting nasty to
what do we eat? I don't know the other day. I've been having some of my stomach
wishes. The other day I took a shit that took that was so violent and horrible
and wet that when I got up off the toilet and I looked in the bathroom
mirror, I was two inches shorter.
This is good.
A minute, a minute, twenty nine, you were the poop talker podcast. I was
going to go this early in the maybe, maybe somebody
on listener, a new, a new
now. I wonder if they talk about anything different on the Patreon. I
we did it and farted so good, disgustingly. I did the full poop.
This is the poop. That's all I do.
The only stories I have in my life are times that I farted or I should at
every other day. I don't we sit. We watch movies, eat a banana and I walk
back and forth twenty five times. That's why we are not good artists. No,
because we if we were if we we need something trouble, we don't get in
we don't push any kind of boundary. I'm pushing the boundaries, you pushing the
boundaries, how so pushing the boundaries of how bored I can get. That's right. I
get so bored. I get so far last night. I was so bored that the idea of playing a
video game was disgusting to me. Yeah, I was like that. It sounds like so much
work to I know I hit the I hit the yeah. I hit the the boredom peak because I
decided to play a resident evil game. You guys have all been talking about
resident evil. It's been in my brain. I don't even like it, but it's all I can
think about and all I can do all I can play fifteen minutes a day of this game.
I every time I get to the fifteen minute mark, I go
all I can do in resident. I tried to play it on stream before and everyone got mad
at every decision I made, so I cannot play. I make a lot of this. Yes, what are
the decisions like a brain, every decision I made, though every choice that
I made when I played that made people upset, walk like our choices, though.
It's like you go through you just in the joint. You just find keys, you find
keys you back track you put the key in and then you find the next one. I was
doing that
shaped like an eagle. Oh, this is like a so it's so easy and I was doing it so
wrong that people got upset. Where are these? It's not even in all these
resident, not easy. No, it's hard. No, it's pretty hard. There's all in all
these resident evil games. You're going into these houses where every key is a
fucking every every door has some has some crazy colitis. I was I'm playing
resident evil seven and it's so funny to me that it's like a it's supposed to be
like a dilapidated like Texas chainsaw house. It's a house that you find in the
swamp in Louisiana and it's like okay. We have a door that only opens. If you
project the shadow of a spider on to this paint, exactly that's what they
became zombies, but before where they were the fucks my eagle key.
I can't get to the Scorpio
fuck. I like my scorpion key behind the spider door. Oh fuck me man. We are
I got back tracked out of the bad. I put that eagle disc God damn it man. I
never finished any of those games. I think I know that there's like a tofu
character that you can unlock right or is that silent hill tofu character?
There's a piece of that. Oh, you can unlock
that's Resident Evil two. That's Resident Evil. You can be tofu in this
game. I'm playing a tofu man.
You okay if you're going to be the expert, you got to chime in. You have to
like give some yeah. What do you mean you can be a making me sound like a
fucking crazy person like
like a new game plus plus type of thing. I don't like this shit. I think that
you should only have to play games one time. Yeah, I don't think you should
that's what I was reading. I don't be actually fun. If you play, I was
reading about Resident Evil games and they're like yeah Resident Evil seven's
fun, but it has like no replayability. Yeah, why what why are you replaying
this man? You did it yeah story over monsters and you got out of the house
your story. You want to go back in you must hear yourself again. You must be
psycho. Once you know what's actually in the house, which, by the way, are you
kidding me? Zombies at the beginning of the game, you only go into the house
because you're looking for your wife. If you go in again and you know that she's
evil, are you local? You must be a moron. Exactly. It's not safe in there.
That's how I ever looking mama. You put the video you once you're done with the
game, you sell it. Yes, these are disposable items. That's why digital has
ruined digitaling. I agree. You gotta play the game on a disc. Same with songs.
Give it to your friend afterward. Same with albums. Once you're done listening
to it, give it away. I don't want to hear this stupid shit again. I know what
happens on this album. Yeah, the song gets loud at the end. The song, yeah,
and then it slowly fades away. I've heard this song before, man. I want to
enjoy this song, but it's like from the first second, I know how it's going to
end. I know it's going to fade out. I got spoiled. It's so predictable. I got
spoiled that it's three minutes and thirty seven seconds long. Oh, and let me
I saw it by and let me guess. I
accidentally read the book on the back. Well, it's actually I like to read the
books before the songs, because then I can kind of imagine my own music. Then I
listen to the song and I go one second, two seconds, three seconds, because if
you listen to the song before you read the book, it's like you just already
have it imagined for you exactly lose a lot, and I also like to read the book
before I eat the food. Yes, I read the recipe before I eat the food.
imagine how it might taste. I look at all the ingredients and I think how
could this possibly tell you like that spaghetti and meatballs? Yeah, there's
the cardamom. Oh, you like eating the spaghetti and the meatballs. That's
there's the ketchup. I actually
I actually like
the recipe much more. I actually read the recipe before anybody even made
recipe was a lot better. I actually like the recipe way, way more. It had
way more like I get why people like the food. There's actually ingredients.
people had like read the recipe before they ate the food. I feel like they
would be under well and there's actually ingredients they left out of the
that were
and meal. So
the recipe is different than the food in the recipe. They actually have to
mix the ingredients together and the yeah they're just you didn't even see
that in the final for yeah and that's it sucks. It sucks at the fucking recipes
being remade and rebooted every year. Yeah, that's true by J Kenji Lopez and
kind of Muguse rebooting recipes. They're rebooting it. They're making them fucking woke. They
literally are. They literally are. They're making chicken marsala. Oh yeah, we're making
a Philly cheesesteak with bulgogi from Korea. What the hell? Get out of here. They woke-ified
a sandwich. I'm sick of them woke-ifying recipes. I didn't think it was fucking possible. Oh
my God. They used an international palette and applied it to my recipe. Jesus Christ.
It's not so messed up disgusting fusion. What was that fusion restaurant fusion
belongs in a power plant exactly and keep it the fuck away from my food in a
frenzy on xbox or in a or in a power up.
What was that fusion restaurant idea you had
text text text text and sushi text max in a or Korean. I was forget what it was
yeah, yeah, that's a guy that's what Eric would look like a manager of a text
Tex-Mex Korean. No executive chef, executive chef, executive chef at the
Tex-Mex Korean fusion restaurant. Yeah, yeah, yeah, where they make different
they make. They need to start getting to the three, the three fusion, the
try fusion, try fusion, but that's right. I'd be doing too much. Okay,
what would you know? Because it's like we've done you, you don't get surprised
anymore. When you see the fusion, you go, you see the craziest fusion of all
time and you go like, oh, okay, sure, whatever. Here we go back to your
hometown and someone you know has opened up a terrible fusion restaurant. No,
and it's always like hot sushi like they make like steak and fries sushi
sandwiches. No, no, I can't say I've experienced everybody from my church
started making disgusting fusion restaurants in the last couple of years.
The only restaurant I know that we made a fried fried chicken egg roll.
That's some that's like that's an applebee's appetizer. That's what I'm
saying man.
Try fusion. We need a third a third flavor.
most of them is it's like so just think of okay. Give me give me a classic
fusion here. Well, in a classic here, it's always American. You're always
adding American to it. It's always no. Let me just give me a class. He let him
work. Give me a classic fusion. Okay, man, what is a classic fusion? What is
a classic fusion? What fuse? What's the last fusion? I've been trying a lot of
Thai soul food places. Okay, so yeah, Korean fried chicken, that kind of thing,
soul food,
and let's think here
Macedonian adding Indian food into it. Okay, so what that would be butter pad
chicken exactly interesting. Well, chicken is in tie and soul food, but
okay, let's see
let's see here, maybe a side dish of Mac and cheese that's pad tie Mac and
cheese
with peanut with he not Mac. He not
you know Mac and cheese. That's really listen. I'm no I'm no chef. Well,
recipe developer. Yes, no no recipe scientist recipe side of research. I'm
just I'm provided. I'm the concept. I'm the person they hired to redesign the
logo type, but what if I give them the idea? I say listen, you got to add a
try. This has to be tri fusion. I'll give you a third. You have to figure out
how it works. I can't yeah. You're just drawing the big blue and pink. I'm doing
this. I'm doing a Venn diagram and a triangle you're doing the pink lady that
on the front of the that what faces that you know, you know the the the
corporate Memphis. That's
Petford. Smelling the bowl.
I closed my eyes.
Yeah, why do you have to close the smell?
Don't say you know what I'm talking about.
You always close your eyes to smell something really good,
especially in soup commercials.
No, I see it and smell it.
Alright, well, I've stepped on a rake.
I want to be the recipe.
I want to be the
Julia, what's her name? Julia
Julia Childs.
Julia Childs fellow at the recipe. She's leaking recipes.
She's leaking recipes that we're not supposed to see the public line soup
from above yeah
that's dude they're working on tri fusion. It's a secret tri fusion, yeah,
but maybe they could do met in something beyond food
with the third. The third thing is not food like being like oh, like more of a
maybe a drink culture. Oh my God. Yes, man. They kind of do that here.
Yeah, they do everything in this. Yeah, it's pretty easy. I saw I saw a bar.
You go to a punk bar and they're like, Oh, we have a vegan Korean fried. I got
an ad on my Instagram this morning
and piercings. Yeah, they put little bonito flakes on the top. This is
that's actually a good idea. I got an ad for a I got an ad for a gym today on
instagram.
No, this is I just this is fusion
and watch. I guarantee you that there's already a restaurant in New York called
punk rock dump.
Wait, there's a play. There's a vegan place called like fuck you burger,
stinky slit burger. There's not a stinky slit burger, stinky slit burger,
stinky slit.
No, it's got searching with quotes, searching punk rock. No, it's somewhere
in like Green Point or some or no in in like Fort Green. They have like I've
been to it before I haven't been into it. It's not called fuck you slit. It's
called slut. Fuck your slut. Fuck your slug. No, no, it's not egg slit. It's
say stink slut burger. It's not stinky and although everything on the menu is
called like the fuck you burger. Is it did you got a dick last resort? No,
no
they don't cuss there. Yeah, they do that's a fusion where not when I go
rudeness yeah true and crad and rudeness disrespect food and rudeness
rude. We're the first people to mix food and rude fruit. Yeah, Dix last
resort. It's more of a food,
restaurant and rudeness.
I saw an amazing fusion today, an instagram ad for a gym. I don't remember
it was called, but it was like have you ever been at the gym and wondered why
nobody there wants to party come to this gym in Manhattan. It is a it is a gym in
a nightclub setting and after the after the classes, it's an open bar and the
bartender was hot and he took his shirt off. I think I remember something like
this. It's like a dance for people drinking and goes like can you imagine
like what the hell and working out? Why are people doing this crazy? It was
called like booze club with no vowels,
easy CLB some shit like that. Yeah, I would be worried. I was a bee busy,
busy club, busy club. I was I'd be worried to be a club for be. I think now
that you guys are
now that you guys are. I think beekeepers probably should stick to their
own kind. Yeah, I don't really want to spend. We can't have a beekeeper fusion
place honey. They're going to put bees in everything. Bee food is honey. Is that
their food
tea, a cup of tea is kind of like British bee fusion. If you put honey in it, don't
put that there. Put that on the ground, please. That's disgusting. Bee. When you
use a zen, you're supposed to put it in your pocket and then try to pay for
groceries and then 50 of them fall out. That's what you do? Yeah. I want to put a
wet object in my pocket. Every fucking time I go to the grocery store and I'm
buying a banana and they say, okay, that'll be eight dollars. Well, how many
zens do you think you could buy a banana with? Used? Very few. Used, but I think
stuff like you know you're at the bodega, you pull this in out of your pocket and
maybe the bodega. They already have them there. They already have them there.
Yeah, I know, but what if you... Now that you guys are in the gym and we have been in
the gym, I'm sure that people can tell. I know that we're all wearing long sleeves
right now, but if we were wearing... Check me out. If we were wearing micro bikinis,
you'd see a very big difference in our bodies. Yeah. I think that it is time for
us to join a high-end Equinox style gym with towels and smells. Maybe. That would
would be nice, but I can't do it me neither, but why not
money yeah, it's only an hour away.
I guess I have time, but I don't have the money. It's only an hour time is
money. So my God wow yeah, if you do a little bit of online work from home
style work on the way there, it pays for itself
right or if they pay you to go to the gym that it does literally pays for
it's okay for itself. Speaking of the gym, we found out yesterday that my left
side of my body is shorter than my right side. Oh yeah, you weren't...
You said that I was looking at his body and... Yeah. You thought you were
looking at my breasts. You were looking at his body and... Well, Pat was
literally standing like this doing hands over nipples, kind of Monty Python
style. He has a horn. And then Caleb was full leaning hand on chin inspection.
I didn't have my hand on my chin. You were stroking your chin. This thing
makes my like rib cage kind of slanted. So we thought that it was that, but then I
said, you know what?
If you notice, I don't know if you, it's kind of, it's very subtle. You always
exaggerate it when you think about it. Yeah, this is what he was doing yesterday.
He was like, look, one shoulder's higher than the other.
One of my shoulders is bigger than the other.
But I found out yesterday, one of his legs is way longer than the other leg.
Wow, his knees are like this. That's why I got to go to the tailor all the time to
get my pants fixed because you have one leg that is one leg. That is a little
yeah leg. It follows the same thing.
You know, I like pant one leg short one leg pant one leg short. Maybe that's
what I got to do. That is a pants fusion. Yeah, pants fusion fusion shortness and
longness.
That's an incredible idea. The shortness culture of pants meets the longest
culture of pants. They clash. What do you think came first? He's shortness or
longness shorts or because back the you see photos,
there's a
cloth right. It's definitely got shorts was first here's well. I
think that shorts were first because yeah, you have a loin
cloth and then you also have the kind of like caveman leopard
skin toga or it's a slung over the shoulder. Yeah, and that's
completely a romper and a romper is shorts romper is shorts.
So I think it's shorts first and you look at all these photos
of people in like the seventeen hundreds and they're wearing
like shorts and then the high-ass socks.
True, they didn't even think to extend the shorts down to the longs for some time.
They wanted a combination.
Combination?
Combination.
Of longs, longs socks, shorts, shorts.
And that is a huge tenet of being a cholo as well.
Is longs shorts.
Longs shorts, longs socks, which is I think maybe...
Longs shorts and longs socks is kind of beautiful because it's about two things kind of reaching
and bridging the gap to each other, reaching across the void.
it's an other fusion. It's like it's like a we we don't have anything to cover the
knees. We're just shorts and socks, but we're going to make up for it. You know
what I mean? It's like a family making ends meet when a family member dies.
Have you ever had ends me?
It sucks
from an ends
the ends me. It's so fucking
disgusting. You know you grew up poor. If you were eating ends me,
you know, making ends meet. Oh my goodness,
come on, can't we have the beginnings meet? I'd rather have means yeah
certainly
you know, I fucking hated in me, especially well when it's braised. It's
okay. What was your guys's? Did you guys have this experience? I don't have
this had scrapings of by did you have
Did you get of this experience growing up? You both had siblings. You wake up
in the morning, you sit down at the
desk where you eat, AKA the dinner table, breakfast table, breakfast table. Oh
okay, I have two tables, one for each meal. No, it changes based on the time
of day. It's only two meals, you're saying? Yeah, dude, we did two mad,
two meals a day.
Anyway, moving on,
you sit down, you're waking up. Oh God, I ate my crust out of my eyes.
your plop biggest, most disgusting bowl of disgusting scrambled eggs of all time
plopped right in front of you, family style, and you wanted to vomit every
time you looked at the eggs. My dad made eggs good. My mom would make this like
fully brown eggs that she was scraping the Teflon pan into and then just put
them in a big bowl. Fuck. I think I said that at friends houses. Serve yourself.
Serve yourself. Yeah, I never had to serve yourself. Oh, you were served. Oh,
Okay, you were sure served. I mean it's only two kids. I don't think there's a
yeah, we were only three. Yeah, that's the more where you would start doing
serve yourself is where you do the serve yourself. I mean, I guess I'm trying to
think we would. I don't think we are typically made breakfast very often. I
guess we're a little, but I don't think we're my family's making us eggs. I
think we're having cereal and my dad was making eggs and hash browns on the
weekend and sausage pancakes and yeah, that serve yourself and tell me tell me
this. Did dad make the pancakes? My dad did. Why is it that moms make everything and dads
can make pancakes and burgers and grilled cheese? My dad made grilled cheese. Anytime
my mom was out of town, my mom would go on work trips for five days. For five nights
in a row, we'd eat grilled cheese and tomato soup, and it was so damn good, man. My dad
was the chef in the house. I don't think I've ever really seen my mom cook besides some
kind of chicken thing that she used to make. The only thing that I remember that she would
make is the Planet Hollywood Captain Crunch breaded chicken. It was actually good.
actually really good. Your mom made that? She would make copycat recipes. From Planet Hollywood?
That's a fusion. Yeah, that one breakfast and dinner. Restaurant and celebrity. Breakfast
for dinner was one of my faves. Breakfast for dinner is a classic. I still do breakfast
for dinner. I'll make some protein pancakes, a couple of fried eggs. I don't think I liked
breakfast for dinner because I was not a breakfast person. You're still not a breakfast person.
I have become, by the way, you've been fully vindicated by me. I haven't eaten breakfast
in maybe like regularly years. I am a lunch, dinner man now. I will eat breakfast foods
at lunch or dinner. But at breakfast, I fast until 2 or 3 p.m.
Yeah, that's what I do. That's what I've always done.
It's wrong. It's the most important meal of the day.
It's not. It's the least important meal of the day. You've been lied to.
I'm not by nobody told me this. I just the doctor told this. I don't listen to
the doctor. He hates the doctor more than anybody. Oh yeah, you hate the
doctor. I hate the dentist. I think the doctor told me breakfast is the most
important meal of the day and I said, okay, yes, you think I'm that kind of
guy. Hell no, I don't do what the doctor told you this. No man, first of all, my
teacher told me and second of all listens to the teacher.
Uh oh, you have been destroyed feeling sluggish and getting high headaches all
No, it actually fasting turns you into a full caveman. Yes, when you wake up, oh
for some hours, yeah, it's good. Yeah, it's really good. It gives you super
human strength. I've been doing this for years. I fast, but then I'll drink
probably 200 mg of caffeine in the morning. Paragon of okay, so yeah,
exactly. I'm sorry to tell you this, that's breakfast breakfast. Drink a
sugar potion in the morning.
There's no sugar in breakfast. There's no sugar in Celsius.
okay, sorry, an aspartame,
potion, but there's no sugar. It's a milkshake bro. It's not a mill or a
starbucks. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, drink an energy drink every morning.
If you drink a I'm sorry, you cannot be talking shit on breakfast. If you drink
a if you drink a thick in the morning, that's breakfast. If you drink a thin
that is almost similar in texture and shape to water or coffee, that is not
similar in flavor to a starburst or maybe a lollipop. It's similar in
flavor to actually a warhead. If you drink the ghost exhibit a
skittles, this is my fasting the skittles see for but that's a
bacon eggs skittles. I want to it's a thin. This is why you're
like yeah. I don't eat breakfast because in your mind breakfast is
like five eggs and a plate of bacon breakfast. You can just
eat a piece of toast and that's breakfast. That's an empty meal.
Do you remember when we were we were at your house in October
for twenty twenty and I made a lion breakfast made Hawaiian breakfast. I
know you talk about it all the time, so it was a great so good, but then I felt
I ate them in the morning and then felt so sick that day that I thought that I
had contracted the Covid-Nineteen.
Oh, I do remember that, but I think you were just hung over. I think it was a
combination of a lot of things. I'm gonna a shun combination. I like I think
everybody's gripe with breakfast always comes from people that have no self
control and think oh when you have to eat breakfast, that means every day I'm
eating a diner breakfast. Well, that's no, but that's the only thing that is
appealing. That's exactly my man in the morning is breakfast. That's not great.
That's a snack. That's a snack breakfast. You eat it when you wake up. It's
breakfast is a meal. Breakfast is a meal. You're eating a snack. It's barely a
meal. Okay, not if it's a meal, then I'm not eating breakfast, bro, because
that's okay. Then this thing is solved. Then why are we even talking? Let's turn
the cameras off. What are we doing? The episode we decided cut. Nobody likes
breakfast, all the cameras, I was like yeah whenever I break I can't break it,
because I eat in the morning. I feel so sick and it's because they're in
chocolate chip pancakes, a can a
obvious everything,
yeah, you don't need you. I also that stuff also not a big fan of pancakes
because of the chocolate chips pancakes. You have to because of what is it you
think it's on chocolate chips. I never it's a
very man. It's a big wet disk of bread covered in shit with sugar and we're all
we're all monkeys on a flying rock and space. You eat that crap gay.
You're lashing out at me. I don't fucking out of pancakes anymore, but you know
what I fuck with waffles? Yes, I've always been. I've always been. You know
what I put on the waffles? What? Butter and syrup. Zero, but I like I like
peanut butter on waffles. New Hampshire syrup is better than Vermont's.
They're the same shit. They're not the same. You know what? Oh, you know what
I'm done with? I've been meaning to talk about these. Vermonters are so proud of
done syrup. I'm done with maple syrup. I'm done with for any I'm done with
pretending it's better than
stupid
with you.
He's a complete idiot.
Maple syrup. That's probably the most the easiest thing to tell the difference
between
so much obviously, but no, no, no, Mrs. Buttersworth. Oh, you're talking,
you're talking to it's candy. You're talking to the you're preaching to the
opposite of the choir to men.
Titanic choir, the syrup capital of the world's
it's so sucks. I'm not even saying that the fake syrup is bad. I would I eat
it, but to say that maple syrup is worse than that is it's worry. Maple
syrup as an ingredient is amazing. It's not no. Oh, well, maybe as an ingredient
sure it's amazing and everything who pulling it as an ingredient. I love
ingredients, but okay, at least at least you said that at least you said you
love ingredients. I think that for my waffle I'm going peanut butter and with
peanut butter. I don't want a butter and syrup yeah bitch. Why to make the flavor
good? This is what this is. You got your
that argument to make a good flavor. You don't have restraint when it comes to
breakfast food. It's a I'm diagnosing you right now. That's not a good time.
Here's your person next time. I've met one topping
you wait. You're saying just put p that be the driest thing ever peanut butter
only on a wall. It's up to you. You don't choose what this is. You're just
siding with it. You would put the syrup on. I know he doesn't like breakfast on
waffles. Yes, I always put syrup on one and peanut butter. That's no, I would
not see anybody do that before. This is the most common thing in the world.
That's what Waffle House does. Waffle House does this peanut butter and syrup.
Yes, it's on the menu. Maybe a waffle with peanut butter chips in it. That's
worse because that's that's that's chocolate chips, but they're peanuts.
Yeah, but that's at least at least that's not a topping. That's an
ingredient. I can accept peanut butter as an ingredient, but as a topping
peanut butter and maple. It's just it's not about the flavor. It's just the
practice is bizarre. Yeah, you think that you you're saying it's bizarre.
Imagine
you're filling the holes of the waffle with the peanut butter. So you're
blocking the hole. It's not incorporating with the waffle. It's
incorporating with the peanut butter. So why don't you just let's get into it
then? Because listen, I have a system for this. It's called checkerboard.
every
you do not do that. Yes, I put a little bit of peanut butter. Okay,
every other square. That's a fucking lie. I'm mediating this. I'm mediating this.
What if you take the peanut butter and you mix it with the maple syrup before
I've done that too? Okay, then why don't you just do that all the time? That
makes more sense. What do you mix it? It gives the peanut butter viscosity. You
get a bowl and you mix the peanut butter and maple syrup. Yeah, it's good, man.
I bet that's really good. I really get a butter maple syrup is very good being
magnetized to my fucking amazing ideas, but you can't you can't put peanut
butter
first. I can do whatever I want maple syrup after that's weird. It's on top.
Weird. It is weird. It's weird because then it's nothing I do is fucking weird.
Everything you do is weird. Okay, how about this guys? You soak the waffle in
the syrup. It takes up all the syrup, sponges it, and then the peanut butter
goes on top. Okay, I can accept that. Okay, well, I'm just missing one. I just
No, I wouldn't put both of those things on. That's too much for me. Do you guys
get weird about your foods touching? No, no, I'm not like that. That's why I
don't like. I mix everything together. That's why I don't like a full...
Not 'cause it's all touching together. That's why you don't like breakfast,
man. The best part of breakfast is mixing all the foods together. Actually,
wait a minute, full English is separated. Yeah. Yeah, but it's like if
you get a side salad for
like spaghetti and meatballs. I mix everything. I save the bread at an
Italian restaurant, save the salad, put everything in a big bowl, mix it up
of spaghetti. That's weird. You don't want your salad to touch your spaghetti.
I don't want salad to touch spaghetti sauce. Yeah. And when I was younger,
they would put it all in the same plate, like the spaghetti and the salad.
I wouldn't eat it together, but if it touches... The salad's gotta be on a
separate plate, but I don't want lettuce touching a red sauce.
Well, how about... Give me a red sauce. Oh, there's gotta be some type
of... Maybe chili crisp can touch lettuce. Oh, what about any... But that's
different. There's a bunch of red sauces in Korean food. You know a lot
about Korean food, is there any lettuce in there?
- Gochujang.
- Well that depends.
If it's a salad that has a gochujang vinaigrette.
- You have been destroyed.
- We got 'em.
- Did you guys eat raspberry vinaigrette growing up?
- No.
- This is what we had with every salad,
raspberry vinaigrette 'cause it was sweet like candy.
- It is good, I've had raspberry vinaigrette made homemade.
- It tasted exactly like can we get Newman's own.
- There was a long time this summer
where I was making my own vinaigrettes and salad dressings.
you should try it. It's really good. Get anchovy paste from the store, make your own Caesar
dressing.
But I don't eat so much salad.
I don't either, but it's good to have on hand. Then you can force yourself to eat salads
by having all this dressing.
I don't need to force myself to do anything. I like hamburgers. I'll eat a hamburger every
damn day. I much, much, much care for hamburgers.
Making your own Caesar dressing at home.
It sounds nice. It sounds fun.
It's good. It's fun. You can put it in a jar and just shake the shit out of it.
I'll do that.
Yeah, try it.
to do it. Go get anchovy paste at the store. I need to buy a fucking microwave, man. For
real. You don't have a microwave? I don't have one either. I haven't had one since college.
The microwave is basically my number one friend in the world. I actually hate the microwave
so much. I don't like it very much either. I actually don't want one in my house. This
is something where once I... But it would be convenient to melt butter. If you have
an air fryer, you... It's a microwave? Yeah. I mean, anything you warm up in the microwave,
you can warm up in the air fryer and it won't be soggy. Except for a fucking hungry man.
Well, yeah, but how much are you eating those, though? Not that often. Without a microwave?
four or five days. Yeah. You eat a Hungry Man every four or five days? No. I don't think
you need a microwave in today's world. Yeah, you don't. Especially guys like you who make
food. Yeah. Yeah, but I'm kind of sick of making food. I want to get... I am too. Oh
my God, I hate doing the dishes so much. I kind of like doing the dishes. I hate the
dishes. I love to cook. That's time to listen to Stumpthing. Stumpthing, yeah. Stumpthing.
You put Stumpthing in. I love to cue up my... I go on my big playlist, I press shuffle and
and then I cue it up, I delete all the songs I don't want.
- And I do the dishes to the music.
- Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Sometimes do a YouTube video about the history of spiders.
(humming)
- History of spiders?
- Yeah, that was one I watched the other day.
- That's good, yeah, see, I watch all these horrible videos.
- Spiders are mentioned in the Bible, you know.
Did you know spiders used to be synonymous
with being fragile and weak because of their webs?
- Really?
- That's in the Bible, every time they're mentioned,
it's like, and they would walk through them
like a spider's web.
- Little do they know the tensile strength of a spider web.
- I think spiders are moving crazy,
the spiders read the Bible and they're like we got to step it up. We got to get
poisonous. Well, it's interesting because you know there's no poisonous spiders in
or venomous should say in like England. So the the folklore of a spider is very
different from where from other places where they're actually dangerous spiders
like a brown recluse. What do they talk about spiders in England like?
Well, they were seeing well here, I guess the interesting thing that was in
this video was that some of there are still things about like people getting
sick from spider bites and like cures to use for a spider bite, but it wouldn't
have made sense necessarily because there probably weren't spiders that made
people really sick. So it was probably from somewhere else that they got like
handed these like remedies that they would use for sicknesses that they didn't
exist.
Very interesting.
What else do they not have in the bloody UK? Bears. No bears. What? That's crazy.
Not many snakes either, I think. Imagine what it was like coming over to the US.
Wait, we have the most fucked up... We're like... Yeah, we're second to Australia,
I feel the most fucked up shit here. You go into the woods, you're going to die a
mountain lion, a mountain lion, bears,
a panther,
I hung out with destiny. I had a dream.
I
took a nap and right before I took a nap, I saw some picture of him cut to my
dream, me and my cousin Matthew hanging out with destiny and he was trying to
fuck my aunt. Wow yeah, you know the dreams you know when you're falling
asleep and you feel like you're falling and you jolt awake yeah every that was
almost every night that I had every almost be almost every night that I was
falling asleep this week. I've had a version of that where, instead of a
falling, I slip on ice and I I'm like whoa and I wake up like I hate that
feeling. It's terrible. I it happens to me probably once a week, but it's because
it got so damn snowy and cold out that now I'm it has been I'm getting ice
versions. They don't they don't salt or shovel in this neighborhood. Do they
thought they do people everybody except us did yeah yeah, well, there's no
My neighborhood, my neck of the woods. I bet we're liable if someone falls and
breaks their head open. Oh crap. Not my problem. No, not mine either.
We'll put it on Pat. I don't know what liable means. So that is not going on me.
Well, that's liable if someone says that we did that shit. Yeah, it's not true.
And they're able to lie. It's Lionel who fell on the ground. Lionel.
Well, that would be sad because Lionel sounds like a little kid. Lionel does
sound like a child. Not anymore. No, I think Lionel's an old man name.
name. Well, I don't know those old names that's coming back. Really? They've been
given little kids old man. Would you guys think I was good? Would you think I was
a whack if I had a kid and I named my daughter Gertrude? That was my great
grandmother's name. So you'd like it? I know. I would think it was weird. I guess
I know that you were naming your daughter Gertrude. So she looks normal
holding that damn corn broom back to the corn. It's always all about the corn
I have a broom that I never use. It just sits up just in case of whatever, just as a way
to ward off bad spirits.
Chekhov's broom.
Chekhov's broom, yeah.
Did you guys grow up, well you didn't grow up Christian.
No.
I think my mom tried to convert.
We moved recently.
No, no, no. When Passion came out.
We moved a lot. I lived in like 18 or 19 different houses when I was growing up and every time
time we moved, my mom would take a full day and anoint the entire house with
I do drawing crosses above every single doorway. That is interesting, you know
that is guess what
nothing bad ever happened to us. I believe it for the moving around for the
moving, getting kicked out of every house, divorce, brothers running away,
but besides all of that, nothing bad happened to the house. Now the house,
no house ever was destroyed or burned, nothing ever burned down. That's good.
Nobody ever passed away one heart attack, but no passing away right just trouble
Yeah, so just a little just like getting in trouble in the road, yeah, but
nothing demonic for sure. No, no negative energies. Yeah, it's not like when you
grow up Irish Catholic, you just believe that anything that is bad is happening to
you is a curse from God, because you did something you said to swear.
I thought they like swearing and they like swearing, but that's the thing
that's why they're constantly felt basically the guilt. Let me explain
because I know you didn't grow up. You didn't grow up Catholic, so let me
I'll explain it to you. The basically the way it works is your entire life from
age zero to age about, let's say, sixty five. Okay, you do whatever you want.
You hurt everybody in your life. You act like an asshole. You beat women. You
drink to excess. Okay, you may commit assault. That's fun. You steal, you lie,
you send it at the age around age sixty five. You go like this. Oh my God,
look at your hands. I go to hell yeah. I feel so guilty because my mom raised me
bad.
You raised me into a doctor, which is that's crazy, because every one of my
done every single member I cussed of my mom's Irish. Oh my God, I watched R rated
movies at the age of fifteen, spend all day beating up every single person in
your family. Oh my God, I cussed and I watched bad movies. This is my fault. I
have to go to a booth and talk. I have to talk to some guy to a pedophile right
no, please, oh God, it's crazy. You said sixty five because it's around every
single like old person on my mom's side passed away before they reach seven.
They all went to hell yeah, they think well sixty five. It's because it's
because as soon as you retire, you finally think for the first time in your
life yeah, a person finally yeah yeah and finally finally sits down and thinks
about something. Oh my God, then I should have a drink and drove busy,
it's busy this season man rats rats. Oh dress my family's screaming again yeah
wait. I'm going too fast. I'm driving to a right now.
The screaming was my fault because I didn't make dinner. I listened to the
other night, the
podcast episode with the nerdist, the Chris Hardwick episode where he
interviews norm. McDonald came up on my YouTube thing and I bet that just like
It just said like comedy interview Norm MacDonald, it was two hours long and I was like I wonder
if I've heard this and I played it and it was the nerdiest and I turned it off because
ten minutes in Norm tells some story about how he like went to, he like went and did,
tried to get on The Tonight Show with Johnny Carson and the Tonight Show guy was like,
"Yeah, you're just not really like a Johnny Carson comedian."
And then he ended up having his first late night appearance with David Letterman and
and it was this like great thing for his career, changed his entire life. He
tells a story very like seriously and then Chris Hardwick goes, yeah, it
sounds like you were sorted into the right house.
This was like the second to last interview this guy ever did and that's
what he's getting from Chris
you know and norm just goes like, oh yeah,
he has no idea. Yeah, he's never, I don't think he knows what Harry Potter
is.
Sounds like you were sorted into the right house. Chris Hardwick, if you ever
try to come back. Yeah, no, no, I will set you up. First of all, I will set you up
with so many honey pots of just
every woman I know I'll be hiring to walk around you covered in bandages, just so
that you can rip them off.
Second of all, if you'd like to come on the show, you're always welcome. We'd
like, we'd love to talk to you about sketch shows from the 90s that didn't
exist for more than one season, like the Ben Stiller show, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
or the Dana Carvey show.
- I could see you kind of growing
into a Chris Hardwick type of career.
- Why would you say that?
- He wore suits, it was badass.
- Oh, you could see me wearing a suit.
- He wore suits, he did like three comedy specials.
I think you could do that.
- He did, Jesus Christ.
- He did one where he wore like a--
- I thought he was just a talk show host.
- No, he wore like a $10,000 suit in the special
and it was called like Da Nerd.
And he's wearing like a giant,
like Chris Rock golden suit or some shit.
- That's actually--
- It was badass.
I think that these comedy interviews are the reason why everything in the world is really bad.
Yeah, it's always bad. It's never good.
Why did Mark Maron do this to us?
Why did he decide that people need to hear Patton Oswalt talk about...
Like, that's the worst idea ever.
Yeah, they should crack down on it and kind of limit free speech.
They should want an episode or a radio show or a TV interview or something is filmed, the
government should literally send a SWAT team and come and seize the tape.
100%.
Put it in a vault that only opens after 99% of the world is scoured in nuclear flame.
There's no reason why anyone should know about what fucking Bill Burr was doing at Open Mic's
in the 80s.
Oh snap, Bo Burnham has trauma y'all.
I don't need to know about that.
No, no one needs to know that.
I could tell you had trauma.
I could tell because of his art was so affected for art. Yeah.
What? How could you make art like this without trauma? No, this guy's full of
trauma and guess what? Literally, literally, you can tell because he raps
rap is literally a genre born out of strife. He
gets what he even says it. He even says it in the end of his
special. He writes a whole thing about how George Carlin would hate him. Wait,
did he grow up in the ghetto? He grew up in the ghetto. Yeah, and he
grew up in the get the streets of
St. John's prep. I wonder what I think he's from. I'm pretty. I think he's from
Boston. I wonder what's a box from. I think he's from
locking in a guess here. My guess is my guess. My guess is hold on before you
say. I won't look it up. My guess is
mass. Beth
okay. That's not Boston. Oh yeah, that's I'm going Brookline. I'm going. I was
gonna say
I'll go Brookline as well. Okay, and copier. Okay, I got all Burnham. Where from? I know
that he went to Hamilton, Mass. I know he went to the same Catholic boys school that my cousin
did. So did you did your cousin chill with him? No, my cousins my age, my cousin Patrick
who how old is Bo Burnham? He's older. Bo Burnham is 33 years old from my cousin Patrick
who is a year or two weeks older than me.
And he's from Hamilton. No, he's from he's from Somerville.
Whatever man, it's old fucking States. Hamilton is near Wayland.
Hamilton is in the North Shore Essex County.
He was a North Shore kid on the weekends and then went down to
yeah, the parted style. Hamilton also has a rich equestrian heritage.
Oh shit, which remains strong due to the influence.
blasted you strong due to the influence of the many horse farms and of myopia
hunt club, which holds frequent equestrian events. Myopia also holds a
thanksgiving day fox hunt each year that the public may attend. Why not a turkey
hunt? Crazy man, Hamilton neighbours, win them, win them. We're done with one
names. We're done with Massachusetts. We had you know what in North Carolina.
Yeah, of course, yeah, it's right next to Manchester by the sea. It's bordered by
by six only by the sea, no short place. We can are allowed to talk about twelve
miles south of Newburyport where it's tough. Now we fuck with we fuck with
Plastel Plastel. Yep, New Hampshire. Yeah, Plastel, New Hampshire, New
Hampshire is my number one in New England. What is Plastel just the town?
Yeah, and the beat. I got a shoe barn. They got a really good savers. They used
to have a trump store closed. Why? What is Plastel next to Plastel's next? I
I think it's next to ports near Portsmouth. I know it's near Merrimack
and Haverhill and all that. Oh, then it's way closer to where I'm from.
Portsmouth has my favorite hamburger store. Yeah, it's right by, I think it's
right by, I think that where, yeah.
Portsmouth is what? Has my favorite hamburger store. What place? I don't
remember the name. I've been trying to remember the name for like four years.
There's only like six restaurants in Portsmouth. I've been like three times
and I always leave and I'm like, I'm going to remember the name this time.
Yeah. How often do you go to Portsmouth? I've been, when I lived in Boston, I
go a lot. Oh, I didn't know that. Because it was close and it was like a nice place to go
for a day. Yeah, it is a nice place. I do love Portsmouth. It's basically cute. It is basically
cute. And it's also next to the Kiddery Trading Post in Maine. I love all that stuff, man.
We need to take you guys to the Appalachian Mountains. No, we gotta go to... Appalachian
Mountains are fire. We gotta go to New Hampshire, we gotta go to Salem, we gotta go to Canobie
Lake Park. No, you know, we gotta hit the... we do have to hit Canobie Lake Park. You still
never went there, right? Still never been. We gotta get... we don't have to close. We
I close to the Berkshires. What's the Berkshires in Western Mass? Is this a
Norman range, Florida, Massachusetts?
There's also beautiful, beautiful out there, North Adams, Massachusetts. It's
where DJ Lucas is from. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay, I'll go to the
Berkshires. The most beautiful part of Massachusetts. Really? Besides the water,
beautiful part of Massachusetts, East and West are both so beautiful in mass
and the middle. It's shite for me. It's the Gucci store at the Prudential is
beautiful part of Massachusetts, a golden store. Oh man, the all tired golden
store. Yeah, the all there's a warby parker there is beautiful. Oh my God,
don't even get me started in the fucking made well store. Oh my God, made well jay
crew. That is where that is basically where I grew up in massages and we're
going to a high noon pop up. Oh yeah, we're going to the june shine bar. We
should do a I've been I have had this idea for some time. David port noy will
go on. He'll go to any pizza place. Yeah, he went to the pizza place that up. My
family went to our entire lives. Really? My dad sent me the video. What'd he give
it?
He gave it a bad rating because, because they just got the management, like
change. They just, like, got completely, but it used to be good. It used to be
fire and, like, even in the video, is it Greek? He tries the, he tries to,
it's not house of, I don't know what style you would call it. I'm not a pizza
style. Like, Boston style, Italian. You're just a normal style. They were, they
were like Italian. It was like an Italian family. I'm a normal guy. I
had a very strong Italian accent, but even in the video that people like see
him trying it and they're like you just like if you had come a week ago, it
would have been good like they were like yeah yeah crazy, but I want to get him
to review a pizza that we make yeah. It's not a bad idea. Oh, my God, but I
heard the thing is I'm serious. We could we could put a dominoes pizza in a box,
pretend this was a pizza store, get all of our we do a fake a Google thing and
he just says we're close or whatever. He will come. If we tag enough
comments that say David, please come. He goes to every one of these places.
He's been to Pizza Hut, he goes to all these shitty... The only problem is...
Has he been to Papageno's? He probably doesn't give you a warning that he's
coming. We probably just have to be here with the pizza. It's not a problem.
Yeah, we can just order it and go out the other side. We'll order one pizza
and if he doesn't show up, we eat it. What a fucking tragedy that is. Not a
imagine that is yeah. We make our own box. Oh my God, we put we put some
live box out of wood. You know we do we put the wooden pizza box. Damn, that's
a good place gets us. We only get a seven because of presentation because the
presentation is so good. Exactly. We put a four or five flies in the box and
then close it for this
or yeah, a seven would be a ten for us for this. I don't care what the rating
is. No, I just want to get the rating is important and I want to get in a fight
with him and yeah, I want to walk down and be like a fucker. So you don't like
pizza yeah okay all right David Portnoy.
Lick him up and down yeah. I'm gonna start at your toes David Portnoy.
Portnoy's complaint is gonna be that he's too wet from my licking. Yeah
this guy's licking my entire body. Okay so that's something. I like the ones where
I've been watching all these pizza review videos. Didn't think you're a
I'm a Philip Roth fan. I only know the title.
I know.
We could also, we could plant homeless people, because he always has interactions with homeless people who walk by and they say, "Let me get a slice of this pizza."
Wasn't one of them a crazy murderer?
Well, he did the, there was a guy with no arms.
That's what it was, wasn't it? A guy with no arms killed somebody or something?
I don't know if he killed, he got in some kind of trouble.
There was some trouble he got in.
yeah, but he did one where a guy with no arms walked up and was like I don't
know what he did. He probably not not in at a place. I think all he can do
only rude thing a guy with no arms can do is shake your head and kill
somebody apparently or hurt somebody. It's not like there's something that
that guy did, but I don't know what it is, but then he was like slander this
man's name. Well, he'll unless he did something very bad, the guy without arms.
Yeah, the guy without arms. You don't want to slander one slander, even though
apparently an assault or murderer. Yeah, but we don't know. We don't remember what
he did. We don't know who we killed. Yeah, you know, is the truth. We could be
a full family. Hey, that that bread Dave's killer bread. Did he kill? Yeah,
because it says he's an ex inmate, right? But then he went back to jail
recently. Oh, shit. And his name is the name. Why? If you have your whole thing
is that you name the bread killer bread. God, if I was working at like some
some shitty insider trading, horrible click bait online news website yeah and
I got wind of a story of a scoop of somebody choking to death on Dave's
killer bread. I would be like literally my family is we're going on a month
long vacation yeah by literally we are getting a tire hitting one hundred
billion clicks on this one. This is going to be the biggest right the
headline as if we I don't think it's funny. I want to pass tweets in the
vertical yeah, yep, say New York man chokes to death on Dave's on piece of
Dave's killer bread. Yeah, would that be what's the great roll in as people say
seriously yeah seriously seriously you could even make this the country
seriously dot dot dot seriously
my grandma loves that bread, but she said she doesn't care for the packaging.
I don't like how many seeds there are in it. I'm done with this healthy bread.
Oh, my God, I hate seeds and bread. You know what the only bread people should
be eating is sourdough. I like I've had sourdough or peasant bread. I want to
get some I was just thinking about this. I want to get some bread from a bakery
instead of the grocery store. You got it, but then you got to get home. You
slice it yourself and your whole house becomes crumbs. No, it doesn't matter.
Just clean the crumbs. Yeah, but that's another slice it on the on the cutting
board. So I'm not slicing like on the floor. Yeah, my cutting board is ten by
ten, because that's where the crumbs are getting. You're getting ten by ten
pieces of bread. I'm a very dull loaf. No, the crumbs are going to a ten by ten
area. Why? How are you? Are you cutting with a chainsaw? Ten feet by ten feet?
Yeah, ten feet by ten feet. How are you throwing these crumbs around? What is
this? Because I am really strong. Are you just blowing? Are you going? Yeah, to
get them out of the way. That's a crazy way to cut bread. I think it's fucking
normal. Also, I don't have an ability to cut a really thin slice of bread, which
when I get it pre sliced at the store, it's pretty easy to cut bread thin. Are
not even that serrated blade. How thin do you need it? Do you need it? Yeah, the
thing is, I'll cut a giant lettuce burger, so he probably wants to cut it
so thin it's not even again again. I get attacked for just living my life,
just living a normal life in a weird way. A lettuce hamburger, a lettuce by
the way, when I say let us hamburger, the burgers, not let us the buns are.
We don't know that you can be chopping. You'll be chopping up lettuce, putting
and maybe you do like an eighty twenty twenty eighty romaine twenty
iceberg
eighty romaine twenty iceberg, twenty meat and then twenty pieces of lettuce
on each side of the burger. No, I don't do that
chunks of lettuce in the burger
salad burger. That's fusion. That's a
salad. That's fusion. You guys like salad. Oh my God. Wait. A burger is
literally tri fusion between meat, cheese and bread. Holy fuck and tomato.
yeah well you can and stop you. Toppings don't get included in top things.
It can be. I think it is
I think they could who invented the salad. What region does the sound or
so let's think Salad France
has to be France. It's got to be France. Who else would invent such a
disgusting food? That's right. A gross green food. It's a way from you know
it's fucked up is when you realize like Caesar salad is an eighty year old
convention right. So I would say that this is kind of that's kind of a
thing that it's been around all that you're driving right now forever. This
is kind of air so interesting dot com yeah. Call you when you read the
recipes. They have the article before the rest of you read the recipe for
Caesar, Caesar salad dressing, Caesar salad dressing, and you read the
article. I read a little bit of it.
Yeah, I like some of them. Some of them are nice
the story at the beginning at the beginning
but Caesar salad that's crazy man. There's a story at the beginning. I'm
like what the fuck are they going to say about Caesar salad and then you learn a
little fact and you're like oh that's what they have to say about Caesar.
Every one of those articles is just my
my husband's. My husband is picky. My husband is addicted to Caesar salad
right now. He will only eat Caesar salad. I'm a job, no chicken. I jumped to the
recipe. I jump to the recipe every time. I go on reader mode on my phone, man. I
jump to that
I jump to the recipe every time, but I wanted to see what these people had to
say was different about Caesar salad. So who invented the Caesar salad if it
wasn't a- Caesar. Caesar who? I don't remember, but it's Caesar and he was
working at some restaurant in,
was it Baja California or somewhere in California? Was it Baja California or
somewhere? It was somewhere in California, but it made me realise that
the Caesar salad, Caesar salad is a Mexican, is Mexican food. Is Baja California
in California? I thought it wasn't. It's in Mexico. Yeah, but it's Mexican food,
Caesar salad is Mexican food. I didn't realize that.
Why do they serve it at an Italiano restaurant?
Exactly. What the hell is going on?
Caesar is Italian.
Caesar is an Italian name.
Italianos are so...
I'm pretty sure, I might be misremembering this, but I'm sure the Caesar salad is a Mexican invention
and it was served at a Mexican restaurant and they would make it table side food.
I guess salad is probably...
I mean, because we were hunters first and then we started getting the plants.
gathering, Neolithic era type vibe.
Jumiel, can you pull up the history of Caesar salad?
The first salad was probably berries and animal skin instead of leaves.
I'm sure they didn't invent dressing for some time after.
Yeah, that was probably a long time.
Because hunter-gatherer and dressinger.
Dressinger, chef-er.
Yeah, we didn't...
Is that a gatherer job?
Dressing?
Dressing.
Well, if you find dressing, that can be a gathering.
That's a combination, a combiner.
That'd be great.
a bottle of cans out behind a dinosaur's cave. Well, they probably just used blood.
Blood was the original dressing for sure. Monkey blood, monkey blood. Would you
get a monkey brain? What? Yeah, I would. I would really want to know it was
prepared right because that you can get some fucked up disease. I'm watching
some very strange videos last night of people eating. We're watching porno
together. We're not watching porno. I have to do or you don't even say that
We're watching porno together on discord alone. What videos
pussy destruction. We didn't watch. This is not a tab. She is dressing. You can't
click on pussy destruction on a
right. Can you pull up two things for me? Can you pull up the history Caesar salad
and pussy destruction? Don't pull up either of these men or just maybe you
could fusion them and look up pussy Caesar salad. It already has anchovies
in it.
Down low, down low, down low. Okay, thank you.
Yeah, and that's another thing I want to talk about. Women, wash your
pussies. This shit is starting to taste like disgusting fish and smell like it
too. I can smell you at the movie theater and it makes me want to leave.
I'm trying to watch, I'm trying to watch poor things. I'm getting enough of
that on the screen. I'm trying to watch Wonka and think of sweet candy. All I
smell is your fucking disgusting thing. The nose was a damn 4D movie.
I walked into a fish farm over there. I'm watching the Meg to
that's
no, no, you know, you know every showing of the Meg to every matinee. They got
the four D yeah yeah didn't take a shower after the gym. I understand it
happens to guys all the time. The difference is, but the different is for
us. We's on our balls. We smell like cool animals. Yeah, we smell like bulls
wolf in here. We smell like a dog. Is there an alpha dog wolf in here? We
smell like a dog that has never had its teeth brushed. Yep, not washing my
balls, people walking around, thinking there's a- it's on the news. There's a
wild animal wolf around. We can't see him, but we're sure he's here. Everyone
can smell him all over the city. Scaring everybody in the city. People think
that something happened at the zoo. Somebody has smelled a wolf downtown.
Somebody has smelled a wolf downtown. Women are losing their minds, going
crazy. This is what- this is what news reports were like back in the B.C.
sometimes yeah that's true back went before we had nobody could really hear
them. Yeah it wasn't that effective. There was a guy to a I smelled a bear.
They had a one rock on a pile of rocks. They pick up a break in rock camcorder
breaking rocks. There is no they would call breaking old
the old
breaking old. I was watching the old smell the breaking old. There is a new
cave painting of a fish. We found something in the water and we decided
to paint it
old is a good idea. This would be an entire sketch video. This is a
sketch right here. The old old old and you would have the instead of the
weather man you would have WBC. There we go WBC. Well, that would be woke.
Let's just go WBC yeah, but it's not enough letters to sound like it that
launch is for is for entertainment or just bct entertainment portion. Bctv is
good because then we don't have the wokeness and then it has for what the
for the
bc thing is so funny because they try to make it woke, but it's still they
didn't change anything. It's the Christian era. Well, it's common era.
Yeah, I thought it's still like well, you know we're going to change the name,
so it's not I know Domini yeah, but it's still going to be all centered around
Jesus. Yeah,
also, we're going to say that after Jesus born of stuff started being common
yeah, I was told growing up that which makes a common Jesus W. The B. C. Was
before Christ and A. D. Was after death. No, that's what I was told. I know
Domini. I know Domini year of our Lord. My education was not good after death.
He was boy died in 33 man.
He was born in zero.
So there would have been a kind of no man's land zone in the middle there.
Well,
that was before Christ was killed. Can you imagine how lit that shit was? Him
is there a birth from zero to thirty three
wait. Can you imagine how lit it was the the night of one BC yeah, that's
like God, like for it's like nine to nine and damn I heard all our our
scrolls are going to break
all of our abacus is can't handle zero, zero, zero, yeah, I wish we were on a
BC type type year schedule right now. We were just counting down to something I
like of right now. If it was like imagine right now, it's like twenty five
be X. That before so and it's like X is like a mystery because then you do the
let's do that X, then you go five. This is kind of like the variable
five, four, three, two, one zero
people throwing sand in the air. Oh my God, no fireworks yeah yeah, maybe
fireworks, maybe throwing throwing flint. So when it falls, another than
the fireworks, trying to hit another piece of flint in the air to make just
one tiny spark. They had dragons back then, so fireworks weren't as impressive. I
guess that's a need to invent. I don't really care so much about fireworks at
all. I don't like fireworks. Dude, I saw there's this, maybe I shouldn't talk
about this. What? It's kind of sad. Okay, alright, don't talk about it. Oh, I
say it. It was a, I was at the, at the dog park with my dog, and these kids
start, like, gathering up, and I'm like, 'Oh, they're going to try to run around
or something. My dog's going to chase one and eat one.' And then they started,
Saturday and then they launched a firework and I was like fuck I got out
of here because the dogs gonna go crazy. Yeah, so he's like trying to run to the
fireworks, kill himself, Kirk a band shotgun directly to the head and we run
away and I was like what are they even celebrating and they were seemed so so
happy they were having like the time of their lives. I saw them setting something
up come back the next day. It was like they set up a memorial photo for like a
dead kid who passed on. It's fireworks for it was fine. I was like this is not
not appropriate. That's not yeah. That's an excuse. That's a clever excuse.
None of these kids knew this this kid probably and they were like there's
probably that's probably the friend who's alive. Yeah, true. Are you doing
it as an excuse to launch fire? They just wanted to launch fireworks and now
there's a candle
that's on or lit. It's not probably not lit for long. It's cold out. That's
what I thought, but then I went yesterday. It's fucking still lit and
invincible candle probably too cold for the one of these prank birthday cake
candles that shoots by the way you guys ever try to get me with that shit. The
one you blow out it comes back. I will blow. I will be the first to blow it out
first try. I won't even know I have to do a spit on it. Yeah. Well, I spit on
everything yeah, yeah, that's true. So I make my mark on different things,
especially my birthday. I'm going to spit on my birthday cake. So you can
have my brother did that my brother did that my aunt yelled at him. Your aunt
seems like a bit of a party pooper. She is
Fuck you. Fuck you so much. Okay, so tonight I'm going to be in Tampa with a couple more
shows. We've already done the first two. I'm sure they went so poorly. Hopefully I spent
the day at Busch Gardens today, Saturday. What else? What else? What's going on?
What else do we got?
Let's see. The shareholder meeting is what, the 28th?
Yes. It's a Sunday this time, right?
Sunday night, the twenty eighth, I think is what we said and Julio will correct me
right now if I'm wrong, but if not, he'll I guess stay silent because he doesn't
like talking and guys let's let's recruit probably ten to fifty people each
person who listens to this. Yeah, I just want everyone to send out a blast sign
of text to ten to fifteen of your guys. Yo, what's up? We set a goal a long time
ago. They removed patron goals. We it took us two years to not hit it of
$20,000 to make a movie and we will honor this. Yes?
Yes. Sure, we'll honor it, I guess.
You don't sound excited to be making an amazing movie.
Well, just keep your eyes on the news.
When you get kicked all the time
by people who don't want to see your goals,
and people who take money away,
and people who kick you proverbially
and treat you like absolute ass and shit.
Who?
The fans.
my fans. They kick all three of us and
I never get kicked. Well, when they people just say down, they keep you down
by not letting you fulfill your dream by not by withholding money by withholding
money,
literally my money,
my money that you
what are you doing? You guys are just holding my money. Give it all your
telly text your friends right now. Say you have Caleb's money.
please return it at patreon.com forwards on the on the for real talk, though, basically
big things as fuck will happen this year, but we can only do if we get $100,000 at the
very minimum. Yeah, I'm sorry to say that, but it's true. Okay, thank you. Bye.
Well, here's another fast food one. Can I sue McDonald's over there being snot like
substance in my drink? I don't know if intentional or not still unacceptable during COVID.
just was getting some hot acts and hot chocolate to start of my morning.
I've never had any problems before at any other locations till this
morning. I order hot chocolate with my meal, but when I drank it,
it tasted like a slimy gooby
like a slimy
dude.
That is such an amazing line to be given. I just need to go to court. It
taste it like a slimy gooby. Your honor, it tasted like a slimy gooby.
The gooby, please bring out the slimy gooby. The taste was completely
off and had gooey substance all over it. Really don't have words to
describe texture. It was same texture like snot, used my fork and scraped
up lots from the inside. I have photos I can provide if needed,
just need place to send them. I'm never usually that guy, but this is
my first time ever actually feeling like I have to leave a report.
I'm open to being tested or whatever to prove it's not my own.
He kept the slimy gooby?
He kept the gooby, man.
He took a photo, but how are you gonna test it?
Yeah, he's keeping it, man.
He kept it.
I had so many of this type of thing of finding slime or gooby.
This should be a gooby.
You looked up gooby?
No, I didn't.
It's gooby, you know, the material.
This is not a one for the...
Everyone keeps it, is what I'm saying.
I still have it.
I put it in my fridge.
I don't think that this is a problem for the United States court system.
This is a problem for Maury.
This is a more even...
It is not your gooby!
*laughter*
It's not your gooby?
Ladies and gentlemen, it's not my fucking gooby!
He does the backflip, yeah.
50 backflips in a row, not my gooby.
The gooby does not belong to you!
*laughter*
*outro*