you guys mark norman was attacked by the devil at the new york comedy club and
everybody saw it was caught on video. The video is crazy. It was the spirit of
a ghost. So guys, if you haven't seen this video, yeah, basically mark norman
is doing his set. He's going
comedy yeah.
I'd like to get everybody's uproarious laughter throughout the venue. Yeah, you
can see the click was abound people enjoying the show. Yeah, I turn mine up
to yeah. I don't know what happens just a slight bit. Yeah, it's a little bit,
but there's there's people laughing their friggin heads off in this. There
are people rolling in the aisles. This New York comedy club. Yeah, was it in
New York? It was in New York. According to the sign behind him, it was in the
New York Comedy Club. No fucking way being funny. I'm not being for I wasn't
being funny. You didn't read the sign on the back of the I'm typically when I'm
watching a video of a comedy show, I pay more attention to the jokes than the
sign in the back, but it shows how you are a clout hound and hungry for you.
You're saying, oh, what venue is that? Can I perform? I wasn't a clown, but if
you haven't seen the video, I guess I haven't even heard of New York Comedy
Club. That's how the opposite of a clout hound. You're you're my I feel like my
headphones feel crazy to me to what's going on. What have maybe we're getting
attacked by the same ghost? It wasn't a ghost. It wasn't a ghost. Basically,
what happens guys is that somebody jumps on stage wearing a beanie and looks
very like that looks like this jumps on stage like you looking scared. Mark
Norman goes like this. Oh,
basically, if you were there and you were blind, you would not be able to tell
that anything different had happened. Yeah, and then he says a crazy. I think
which is like what's is a migrant and then he says this is a swinger sex party
thing and the guy runs. Someone comes up, takes the guy by the hand, runs out a
door and then he said mark norman says somebody just got tased yeah and then
everybody goes what the hell and you see everyone filming and then some people
from the venue come in. They reach for mark normans mike and he goes like yeah,
okay, he's making the craziest noises as they escort him and that's a
changes pay. Well, you can just hear the microphone go away from his mouth to
see first you hear is really like oh and then yeah
and then he fucking and then a lady comes on stage. You looks like do that
lady. She looks like she's a back a cry. Yeah, it looks unbelievable. She's
like fully about to cry. She's confused. She's like having talking like a
stroke victim. It's like everything's fine, but but it's really you have to
run. I mean stay where you are, stay where you are, but you have to go and so
the
context that I saw this video and then wait we're not at the end of the end.
She
she's up there for like you know, twenty seconds doing the being like guys,
nothing is wrong. It's all okay. You have to leave, but stay in your seat and
then someone has a guy is so great and then another guy comes up and he gets a
second microphone. It's also there and he goes guys. I'm a producer. I'm part
of the taping tonight. You all have to go. You need you to get out of here
right now and then everyone goes what the what okay and then somebody asked. Why
are you recording? It's like because this is awesome. Yeah, what do you mean?
Why are you recording? I have to record that there has to be on the
intimidate theories. First, let's get into what does the government say this
is so being okay sure we so government being Robert Kelly, Robert Kelly said
that that he was just he was discussed
he looked at Sam with disgust,
and I tried to tell him because I saw from a reputable source, some
Twitter user using cigarettes said that there was
an attack from a paranormal. So this is my
I want to read the official one before we get into the theories, because this
is ridiculous. This is bullshit. This is clearly this is
a cover. This is we need to read this so that we understand, so we know how
I debunk this this is from NY comedy club, then one of the most famous comedy
clubs in the world, New York, New York, it's a New York City, it's under the KGB.
Oh my God, we've received a handful of inquiries regarding a viral clip of our
club being evacuated last night. First and foremost, nobody was harmed or
injured. The disruption was part of a filming by at high high, the producers
that rented out our venue for the night. So since this took on a bit of a wild
narrative. If you were in attendance for this taping, we'd love to host you for
an actual show for free. Please pls email us at info at new york comedy club dot
com and we'll throw that email address up on the screen and this is what
Robert Kelly said
something about
Norman
Robert Kelly, Robert Kelly, newly appointed to the bonfire after Dan
Soder left. Oh interesting, I didn't even know that mean either for Robert
Kelly. Yeah, people hate him.
I looked at their reddit the other day and it was just like when is blobby going
to shut the
blobby? My dad used to work with him at a restaurant. I know so I back him yeah
yes, he's he's a he used to drink shots of whiskey with I'm a blob. I'm a blobby
kelly to big shoes to fill Dan Soder
probably size sixteen or something as tall as fuck. He filled up with a big
shirt. Yeah,
Robert Kelly says told you as a great at not Sam once said to me when I asked if
beef between two wrestlers was real. What are you and mark then looked at me
with disgust, disgust as in they discussed it looked at me with disgust.
He was disgusted by so apparently they have a beef. We're getting too much into
the the blobby. Yeah, yeah, this part doesn't what I want to do with this
episode is do a full on investigation investigation. Maybe we should make a
diorama of the New York comedy club, yeah, and do like a JFK thing and have
let it be here's this thing happened here. Here's where we felt there was a
pocket. We have this to do calculations on the spiritual
why
because it's not like you're trying to change the top. I'm not trying to change
the top. Are you in this way? I'm not involved. You know what he's not
involved. Blue is low too early. He said paranormal and now we have nowhere to go.
You should have waited to say paranormal and then we could be now. That was the
only thing the only thing I knew about it was somebody saying that there was a
a paranormal occurrence. That was the only thing you knew. I didn't see any
other clip. I didn't see any other clip except for what Robert Kelly said, and
I'm going to take those two, those two people's statements as bond. Okay, this
is why you would literally never make it in the Lone Gunman or the X-Files or
any of those organisations. No, I wouldn't. I'd be the guy that I put my
suit jacket behind my badge and I say, "Well, it's the damnedest thing." Do you
guys want to hear, see my, this is my impression of a character that's only in
his first three minutes of the X files episode. Okay,
hello,
oh that's him. That would be me. That's you he's he's hello and then night
warrants long as flashlight yeah, two foot long, but it's like working in a
museum looking into the room with all the sculptures of the apes. Hello, would
I at least going back? Hello, cut to black, would I at least tell them the
investigators that it's the damnedest thing or no you'd be dead. You're
completely or the guy who dies or a you'd be disappeared and then they would
find you your head implanted into a giant blob monster because he like he
took you in and you're part of and you would be talking in unison with a bunch
of other yeah, you'd becomes part of this giant board thing. Okay, so then
you be would be the guy that says it's the damnedest thing we can't make heads
or tails. Let me tell you where I was yesterday when I watch this video and
why it was so let's get I'm sorry I'm getting too into this X files. Why it
was so affecting to me yesterday I decided on a whim I left the gym as a
rainy day and my wife had had her siblings over and they smoked a joint
and a joint was sitting on my kitchen window sill. Disgusting. And I said,
"You know what? I haven't smoked weed in a very long time, like six months.
I'm going to hit this weed two times
and play Assassin's Creed Valhalla, okay?" Which is on Game Pass now.
I sit on the couch. I know you guys hate me for this. I sit on
my couch. It's disgusting. I open up Assassin's Creed Valhalla. As soon as I
open it, I get bored and I open my phone and I look, I look at this video and
this video made me so, that's the video, fucking scared. This video made me so
fucking scared. I was freaking out. I put on my Apple watch and checked my heart
rate. It was a hundred and twenty seven BPM sitting on my couch. That's a like a
watching a song. You could I know could get down to a house song to a heart
like that. This video was killed. See woman by Chris. I saw where I was where
I was when I saw this video is I it popped up on my reddit feed, our
slash stand up, which I do not subscribe to. I started frequently popping up
into my reddit feed due to me looking at some posts on there. Yes, and
this popped up. I watched it with no sound because what it was was it was it
it wasn't a video like post. It was like a text post that said and the thing
just said anybody know what the hell happened at Mark Norman set last night.
It's like well, I got you got to see what happened here. Maybe yelled at
somebody yeah, maybe he went so you made a yelling yeah, maybe he said
something, maybe he said, told a joke. He does that to yells and I click on
it. I watch the video without sound. I go whatever what do I care it pops up
again on my twitter this time. I watch it with sound and I am entranced. It
took over my day. I watch it probably twenty times. Oh yeah, the energy that
this woman has when she comes up. Can you pull this up? It's full. I'll send
you the video right now, so you can pull up the video and we'll watch it one
time and then we'll stop. We won't do any more. She has it. She has a need to
everyone needs to hear this woman's voice. The way she's talking. She has a
full the energy that she brings into this video is the same as the lady who
as the who like starts speaking gibberish on the news broadcast that
one time where she just looks so scared. She doesn't know where she is
instantly. She's looks actually so terrified. Well, I wonder what happened.
It's fucking chill because all that Norman said was some shit got fucked up,
which means... What does that mean, man? That's what the government says when
you're covering something up. It is a full cover up. Yes. And the fact that
we have not had a play by play. Here, we'll play the audio of this
video. We have a migrant here. I don't know what that means. Who are these people? See
these are security for the venue maybe? But then there's a cut right here. By the way,
he's bombing. Yeah. What do you mean? He's killing right now. He was bombing before this.
I think everyone's too scared to laugh at that.
And he just, he waddles like a penguin out of the fucking thing.
Why is he walking like that?
He does the walk you do after you're really embarrassed.
Everybody's getting up, they're switching seats, they're playing musical chairs.
Look at this.
Harry, no, this is a little bit...
Interruption.
Um, just stay, get up, get out, the taping, um, can we get out or what?
Yeah, I'm one of the producers of the show.
Um, yeah, we just need everybody.
Why is he wearing a lanyard with a...
Nice and slow, nice and slow, everything's fine, but...
If anyone's got any photos or video of what just happened...
what you have any father video of what just happened cut out their true actual
cover. It's actually
fully sober is even scary, believable. It is
I watch this multiple times. I never I only just caught just now the part we
said. If you have any photos or videos of this incident and it cut out, that's
crazy, that's actual X files yeah dude. I government cover and here's the second
theory we've heard the paranormal theory. This is the other theory that I've seen
people
posting in the in the twitter replies. I think you sent so one of these guys. I
think this is the shot heard around the world very soon. Comedy will be illegal.
Somebody said pretty legal to make no jokes. Yes,
there's a last time starting with Norman. They're starting with the most
powerful and they're going to work their way down. They're going to work. I
first came for Norman and I didn't say anything yeah because because I don't
care.
dude that and they came for me and then I still didn't care that much. I just got
a
guys. This is the beginning of the stand up bubble popping yeah. You think this
is it? I think this is this
the text, but that is so they're going to put this one great social studies.
They're going to be studying this video, the Norman Jesus Christ dude. It really
scared me and it's crazy and I've been worried for days. She goes like just
they sit down, get up and stay and you have to leave. Yeah, taping she
doesn't know what to say. She's completely lost. I love that how how
like flustered and how much evil energy do you have to be giving off to be on
stage, trying to inform people about an emergency and someone in the audience
goes. What the fuck are you talking about? Yeah, yeah, but I read it.
Any situation where someone is on stage doing that, like everybody in the
the audience is dead silent. Oh my God, which I'm of course, yeah,
all instructions, let's go. What the fuck? What the fuck are you talking about? I
read another theory and I think this one could be also true is that those
security guards are the men in black and that man was a time travel alien event
uh-huh and that man was a time. I traveled from like four years ago,
though, yeah, time travel man that's still pretty impressive. Time travel
that doesn't really impress me.
it impresses you. I'm not impressed by forward time travel. I'm if I could go
bro. If I could go four years back in the past and future, you can only go
future.
Okay, okay, what would you do? I'm not it's fine. No, no, I would go. We can
only go in the day that they
go four years into the future. I'd probably go to I would say January
twenty twenty eight. Most likely is where I go. If that's what I could do to
see who's been who's the president, just see whatever happens. I messed up. I
messed up by shutting down your idea where what would you do if you go for
years, not a good enough idea. Now you have to justify. You may tell me what
you would make a stink about. I made a second joke. I made a
inauguration bringing it back. Would you go to the inauguration? Would you go to
just somewhere like you can't go far back enough? I guess of four years to get
to January six.
Okay, or what year was that? Was that four years ago? That was three years ago.
Okay, then I go to January six and I'd be there. You know you could kill. I was
at the dentist that day. Take a bullet for Ashley. I would invest in sourdough
sourdough starter, though yes, that's what I was a good idea to invest in the
like yeah, just in the entire in the entire thing. Okay, invest in sourdough
starter that you're not selling is what you're saying invest in it like on the
stock market. I'd go to the stock market with ten million dollars and I'd find
whatever stock code is closest. I'd just type in s r d h and I just put a ten
you know. I just watched the wolf of wall street or not. No, I walk in
Wall Street and I watched the big short yeah. I re watch both these movies and
in the big short they they they do that, though they walked they go to Wall
Street. They're like we want to put money on something that doesn't exist and
they're like oh okay, we'll do that. So you can do that yeah. You can definitely
walk in. Well, maybe you can't do that anymore because they did that.
So you think you can't walk in and say I'd like to put my money on bubble gum
yeah and do you think now if you've done it because two thousand and five
whatever it's the fucking little. Do they know bubble gum going way up chewing
tobacco going way down in the major league baseball and then you make money.
Yeah, I think because of the big because of the big short the event mentioned in
the movie, the big short I'd rather watch the shorts big yeah, we about
death runs.
The big shorts,
shorts big
shorts big.
It's a documentary about new metal. It's kind of more an artistic name. It's
like saying like the brothers three, then big shorts. No, the short big. I
don't like this name. I like them big shorts or the big shorts better than
big shorts. The big shorts is too close to the big short. You'd be but it was a
alien style sequel. It's supposed to be close. It's a reverser. You know that
guy's pet is, but it budding he's budding money again. No, I don't know.
I never saw the short. You never saw the big short. No, it's pretty fun man.
They got Margot Robbie in the tub. Margot Robbie gets in the two. I thought
that happened in the Wolf of Wall Street. No, she gets in the well, she gets in
her nudity both now. Yeah, but then in the big short, she sits in a tub and
she tries to explain stuff and I still why she's as she really must be so
obsessed with money to be in both of these movies and Barbie as well. This
money made more movie than any movie ever. It makes so much movie. This money
made a two hour made a long movie. Yeah, I made a very long movie guys. Have
you seen Barbie? Have you guys either? Yeah, I saw Barbie. I saw I did too. I
I liked it. It was fun. Yeah, I thought it was funny. I saw Oppenheimer. I
thought that Ken Gosling was so my brain is melting today. Yeah, what's going on?
He was so fucking funny and I think we're affected. I think that when he
says, can I please go to your house? Can I come to your house today?
It still makes me laugh. That's cute when he says he goes, please, do you
want to hang out tonight, Barbie?
Yep, and that makes me laugh. That makes me laugh. I haven't seen it. I don't
know you. That was the first clip they released from the movie. I haven't seen
I find a look at anything from it. Why did nobody here's why did nobody ever
take the barbie and the can in that movie and go
and make them do it and make them fight now you all may they fight in the movie,
but they don't they fight in the movie yeah. They have a big they get it. They
have a civil war disagreement. They have a basically a class divide civil war
interesting, so it's like Dark Knight Rises kind of did Ryan. It's a lot like
get a and Oscar Oscar nod. Maybe I don't remember it. If he did he get an Oscar
nod Ryan Gosling for Barbie because I'm only just now processing how funny that
is. Yeah, you got yeah best supporting actor God that is really everyone
pissed off that Greta Gerwig and Margot Robbie didn't get into guys. I mean
to be fair,
out of the movie he does deserve the best guy. Yeah, but then, but then let
him steal that movie. America Ferrara still got nominated for best supporting
and everyone's just like oh fucking the the two that I like didn't get it.
America Ferrara the she's the one who gives the model. She's the mom. She's
mom barbie. No, she's a mom of humans. She's a mom of a human woman. Why is she
there? It's just see
the most simple movie of all time. Speaking of movies, man, couple of new
camera yeah, so if they look like if the colors are off, they'll be fixed soon.
So don't believe it is. I know you guys are going to leave some fucking comments.
good news. We don't like the therapy gecko. Well, guess what? How would you
feel afforded this? How guys I saw a lot of people. I saw a lot of people
upset about the episode we did with therapy gecko. They said they didn't
like that guest and they thought they didn't like him. Now, how would you
feel if I told you that five minutes after he left the studio, he got hit by
a car? He didn't, but how would you how would you feel if that happened?
Probably feel and you'd probably feel terrible. You would feel terrible and
I'm talking to you, Draven. That's the only guest. That's the only person I
remember we've said your name on the show. We are going to be having so we I
mean what are the what is a new paradigm of guests guys? What are the chances
that we're going to be back next week? He's back. I was just about to say
he's on this episode. He's
he's sitting in the corner. He's over there. We are going to have so many
guests that none of you know who they are. We don't know who they are. Well,
just to be on the show. I think it's not even I guess maybe this is over the
line, but maybe
it's the funny part here is not that it's nobody knew who the guest was.
It's that everybody knew who the guest was and we did and we didn't know
very nice guy. He's a very nice guy, yeah, very kind, but but apparently all
of you guys,
I mean all again and what are the odds that we have a giant guest on in the
next episode? No and don't we don't know who we don't know who he is in the
next episode we have new cameras. So next week we're gonna have on Kate Blanchett
and then we're gonna have on post Malone. They call post my God post one
of the posty moms got twenty brain tumors. Oh, I saw that
you sent us that text. He's in a group chat with post Malone moms. They're
what the moms, the posty moms yeah, twenty
she got twenty brain tumors in her brain talk about post the mom.
Is a Facebook group for moms who are obsessed with post Malone and they post
pictures of my my husband got me tickets to a post Malone concert. I wish I could
suck post Malone's dick. My son, they're getting their post Malone and I came
into the room and started dancing. They're buying their husband's tattoos.
They have the most violent crushes on post Malone that it's possible for a
forty or fifty year old woman to have and one of them posted the other day.
Well guys bad news. I this is like and it was the name of someone else in a
group just got this message from this like other posty mom and she has twenty
tumors in her brain.
twenty twenty. Can you imagine you're living your life? You're dedicating
your entire life to this disgusting smelling raccoon man with with tattoos
covering his entire body. You're you're snubbing your husband for sex because
you're a man. You're imagining you're you're in a trash can with a stinky
you're drawing your little you're doodling you're doodling your name
when barb wire, Gertrude Malone, yeah, you're a kid, you're Gertrude Malone,
your your your children are embarrassed. They don't want you to drop them off at
school anymore. Say Mom, stop listening to this music. Please listen to
something normal like Roy Orbison
and then you find out all along the reason that you've had this crush is
because you have twenty two.
Like when they cut open a pedophiles and they find that they have a giant to
they're like the doctors yeah, the doctor's like all right and that's
seventeen eighteen.
I'll go here. I
sat of a and you know you know the gallows, you're opening your phone and
just leaving the group. Yeah,
what have I been doing with my back to the gallows humor that these surgeons
have. They're going to look at this lady and go, Hey lady, you got some brains on
your tumor. Yeah, classic, classic surgeon. You know what this this woman
should do, though, is literally she should
she should take these twenty brain tumors and to auction them off and give
so yeah, auction them off to other members of the group who are not so
serious about post Malone and completely put them in their head. These are post
Malone tumours. It's the tumour that does it. You put the tumour and how many
times is he going to go crazy? Twenty. Have you guys heard? I was going to ask
as a twenty times. I think we talked about this with Rex at some point. You
have you heard that he has an aunt that is like fully being catfish by somebody
pretending to be post Malone. No, that's exactly the the demographic. There is
front is like going like flying across the country, flew to Vegas for for like a
VIP, because Post Malone was like yeah, I'll put you on the list and then she
got there and they were like these tickets don't exist.
It's crazy. That is a very funny person for older women to get involved. Yeah,
it's really funny yeah, because he talks about he likes. I mean, I mean, I guess
that's the only that's that's the type of bad boy, the younger bad, because they
don't have a real
anymore. There is a no no. What do we got? But he doesn't make music.
Jacob, a bad boy. He wears a leather jacket in the trailer for the movie
where he plays a biker. Oh, that does look cool. He's playing Elvis in a
movie.
He's the closest thing I could imagine to the type of bad boy that an older
woman might want to get involved. That shit where Austin Butler did the Elvis
movie and then couldn't lose the voice. That is funny as fuck. So fucking sick.
And everybody's saying, oh, it's a stunt. We lived it, guys. We know. This
We got stuck in Donald Trump voice. We did. We did that for months. Genuinely.
Yeah, the whole month of the 2022 tour? Was that the year? Yeah. Way too late.
Six years after he was in the election. Six years after it was funny. Yeah.
And we did that for a long time. And we were obsessed.
And this happens to a lot of great men, I think. You put yourself too far deep into the role.
Heath Ledger, Us. Heath Ledger did it in The Joker. That's the only two.
22. Well, he fledger Austin Butler, but I could see that me doing this with other
roles as well. Oh, yeah, percent like what what rules
well, what do you think I'd be up for in my future? Mr. Hit man, hit man. I think
I could become silent. Mr. Clean. I think he doesn't talk much either. Blue
Caillou blue. Okay, so this is a really bad idea for me to bring this up. If we
put it, if yeah, if we put a big thing on your nose, you could do in this shirt,
you could do a perfect Squidward. No, because I'd still need to do the
Squidward. I would still take... Can you just do your best...
Do your best to talk... Oh my God. It's not that good. It's pretty good.
Why do they give humans Squidward hair? Yeah, that's fucked up. It actually
does kinda look like me if I had no hair. The first picture looks a
lot like you. Well, that looks a lot like me. Click that first one,
the first drawing.
That does look like Caleb. Wait, what? That's the hat you always wear too.
But he would never say K star LL me. What does that mean?
He would if he was human. He doesn't know about death. Yeah, he would say, "I'm
gonna kelp myself." He'd say that. He'd say, "Eeeh." Dolphin noise. He's a squid.
But dude, someone... No, that's the swearing. Thank you. A man of culture.
Yeah. I know the most about squidward at this table, probably. Broskies, I'm
sorry as fuck. Have you guys seen the video where they... I don't know if it's
real, but I saw it when I was a kid where it was like you... It's the uncensored
version of that episode. Oh, yeah. Where they actually say the cussing. Is it
real. They did you guys see the
leak? Did you guys see all the
leak? A disgruntled employee. That
one is that's not real. I think
if I remember correctly, but
recently there was a bunch of
there was a bunch of production
drawing sketches and drawings that
did leak of like all the sponge
Bob characters with giant dicks
fucking each other. And why is
this one? Why is this? You guys
haven't seen this? Hold it up.
We're on Patreon. You can show it.
This is real. I'm serious. There
it's a bunch of the characters all
saying insane stuff and getting
and getting fucked. Why are they
fudging violently fucking because that's just what cartoonists do. They have fun.
You know what I mean? That is how and then and it's so funny. I got I was
looking at them on Twitter and it's all the like it's like, you know, 12 year
old SpongeBob stands on there all like I can't watch SpongeBob anymore. This is
the most evil thing I've ever seen in my life. Speaking of just like kids
animation stands. Have you seen the children who are obsessed with a family
got or South Park. Yeah, that are like what I mean. They've never really watched the show
for it's for adults. It's not for kids. Yeah, I know, but there's these children who are
obsessed with South Park so much that they have like Cartman X the Yowie. Yeah, South
Park Yowie. It's the only cartoon that has a warning on the front of the cartoon. That's
not like cigarettes drawn together. Well drawn together as well, but they stole it off South
Park. Well, they I think they had to legally what is Yowie. That's when two boys two boys
is kiss. Kiss on a comic. This is called yaoi. Yeah, comically kiss. It's Japanese. To kiss
boys have it called yaoi. Well, it's gayness. It's gay boys kissing. Okay, so they're doing
it. You never heard of this? You're probably the number one guy I would have expected to
know about this, man. Yeah, why? Because I play Persona? Yeah, it kind of honestly shows
a huge gap in your cultural research. Persona has no gay stuff in it. You were talking about
tsundere and stuff like that, and you don't know yaoi. Well, because I played one game.
but what's in dairy? I don't remember now. It was a long one of them is about
yeah. I don't know which is which and one of them is about stupid you idiot
and it's a various one yeah. You go you idiot don't fuck me. I hate you don't
even try to, but they're being me, but they're being yeah fake to be a fake
about it. It's about being fake and the other one's like
yonder. I know, please, which one's that I'm telling you. I don't remember the
difference. I think that's the end area. One is one and one is the other. Well,
I don't get involved with this. No, you're going to get involved. I'm not
going to get I'm going to drop you in the middle of the Japanese. This is
you doing Sundari on me. I can try
wait, which okay, Sundari is we'll say that Google it. We'll say that's the
shy one. Okay, so now try to go, which is which
hold up. Whoa, that's the
I'd like to rewind. Sundari is the yelling, but yeah, let's do this again.
I try to fuck me and Pat went
that is not how you do that is not okay. So that's how you try to fuck me. The
mean here let me hear
your hand. Put your hands on the table like you're just like sitting there.
Okay, wait me or him
nice hand. You fucking fat ass
and dairy exactly in dairy and now hit me with it. I'll now do yonder. A
exactly yeah. So now I know the wait, wait, wait, actually this do it again.
So I've been doing that to him, the can slowly comes back. I've been doing that
to Caleb forever because he tries to do that to me. You are yeah, constantly
yours. I'm yandere to you because you sit there and you say I'm going to get
your butt. I'm going to get your you say I said, I said stuff like that, but
never get your butt and then that's not this is I guess if we're talking with
there was a romantic dynamics here. I feel like I'm always trying to get
Jubio. He always he he kind of what's the one where he just basically coldly
ignores me and doesn't say a word when I text him things like I want love or I
love you or I want to hold your hand. He doesn't say I love you back. He doesn't
say that I've told him I love you. You have to
drop you at the airport. I say I love you and you say, well, maybe you don't
know. Maybe you're saying Teyama to be he's not saying he doesn't he doesn't
love us. I have a text not from yesterday. I said I want love and this
is what he sent me. Oh well, that's actually myself. He's telling you to
love yourself. He's sending a picture of me back. Speaking of shot, I art of
you speaking of a shops, somebody had to submit to the master troll two days
ago. I heard about that. I got I got some I got owned. You had to submit to
the master, the master jester. I'll say explain what happened. I will explain
happened. So our friend Connor kept texting us and asking us to make AI voice of Too Lazy
to Try. And you did it. So I did. I didn't know this. I had the file on the computer.
I already had the AI voice. If you don't know who Too Lazy to Try is, he is a drama YouTuber.
He probably will watch this Mark Norman thing. Maybe. After we finish this story, we need
to get back to the Mark Norman thing. Dark Mormon. More theories to drop. Yeah, I have
theories. So he does these videos. He's basically like Real Housewives for the Roganverse. And
we are obsessed. We are completely obsessed with him. We're obsessed. We love him so much.
So I did an AI voice of his and then I texted Caleb and I said to him, "LOL, too lazy to
try. Just made a video about your Tampa shows with Adam." Not my Tampa shows. On his Patreon.
You said on the Patreon. On his Patreon and you said, "LOL, what's he saying?" and I said,
"Hold up, I'll screen record it for you." And then, do you have the video on hand? Because
my phone's charging. I think I sent it in the group chat. But... Will you find the video?
So this is... So I sent this to Caleb and he fully... He said he'd screen record. I fully
believed it for the first 10 seconds. This is not... And then I got pretty mad. Jubio,
This is not the text.
That is a good text though for Patrick.
He says, "Ironic racism is still racism."
And there's a picture of him.
This is not the text I was talking about.
Okay.
All right, so recently I went and saw Adam Friedland in Tampa and my God, what a fucking
mess that show was.
First, he had this opener, which seemed like he might have worked for the club.
I don't really know.
but then this other comment came out and I think his name was Caleb Phipps. I
don't really know. He told this embarrassing joke about getting his wife
taxidermied or something. Okay, so burning my material at the crowd,
which wasn't cool because I'm afraid of screaming. Then he announced he is gay.
Yeah. So at what point, what point did you honestly, honestly, I'm not even
maybe kidding FIPS. I believed it fully until FIPS at Caleb FIPS. I was like
hmm. I don't think that that
is real
and then I
submitted to the master trial. So here's what I don't like. Can I tell you? I
feel pretty proud of this. I thought it was fake as soon as the first like
weird pause when he says what a fucking mess.
that's how we talk. So what a fucking mess sounded really, but I've never I've
never watched this guy's video, so I don't know. You got to get in. Yeah, you
need to buy that was where I was like. Oh, I think this is fake yeah yeah and
even after that it it I still was would say I was only ninety percent
even when he said that I said I was I still was like yeah, I don't know it's
possible,
but it did scare me yeah. You got me good, the mark normand thing. I believe
here's a couple other theories. Okay, I think that one possible thing it could
be
a
bad smell
of who fart it could have been a poo. This guy farted and the lady behind
jumped up, jumped up on stage because it smelled so bad
and
are that you, but the lady in the back, the lady in the back that was trying
so you guys can stay and then smelled it right get out right now. Everybody in
the seats doesn't know what's going on, because the smell was localized to the
stage, because this is farts moving in patterns like wind yeah yeah for
torioles coriolis effect, coriolis effect, so it's moving across people.
There's different different temperatures that it's weaving in and out. People
had big hot buffalo wings plates of buffalo wings. It was causing it to
sandwich between two buffalo wings between the seats, not hitting anybody
exactly this guy and maybe it didn't even run because of smell. Maybe it was
was powerful. It pushed him on stage. It blew him away. I mean, pull up the video
again, because it does, he does jump,
and then he's getting dragged out. It's like, "You don't understand! You gotta
get everybody out of there! The fart's too big!" Here's another theory I have,
is that I believe it also could have been that guy who jumps on stage,
I believe. See, okay, he's bent over, right, and this woman is chasing after
him, so maybe... He's looking, he's seeing if he can smell, he can smell it
anywhere, but maybe he crop dusted her right and he she is so mad or maybe she
tickled him. Maybe she
and that's the start of all this. It could have been a tickle monster. Oh my
God, the tickle monster was loose in the New York comedy club in the New York
comedy club. Oh my God, I think that is a terrifying sight. Also, he could be
trying to get this guy who jumped on stage. The beanie guy could be trying to
get an Instagram real stand-up clip because this is a clever trick here. He
jumps up on stage. He just uses premiere to crop out Mark Norman from the side
that be really funny. That would be really funny. We should do that. We
should go to the stand and just jump up on stage and start doing it.
What if this... And have your captions and have no captions for what the
other person is saying? Yeah, get off stage. Get off... What the fuck are
you doing? You're getting dragged off stage. What if this is like a
reoccurring problem now that people... Like maybe this is the new streaking.
Theory three, this guy was wearing a bomb vest, he was trying to kill Mark
Norman yeah, his detonator did not go off. So then he's looking around,
he's looking around like go press the or someone else is holding the detonator
also similar clothing.
Maybe that's his long lost brother and he's kind of trying to sit next to him
so that people go wait, go sit wait a second. There's two marks. I can't tell
who's who here's another theory that I've seen this one is not one. I came up
with but one that I saw that it was fully staged for whatever this taping was. I
Mark Norman was doing a joke where he was maybe because he was bombing. He
wanted to look like everyone was getting evacuated. I how bad he was. I also saw
this theory that it was stage. This is why I think actors are bullshit. No
actor could pull off that performance of that lady did on stage. Yeah, the best
actor in the world could not do that. That was so fucking real. It's also like
if it is if it's completely staged, that's fully like evil to do yeah. Oh
really evil. That's if I was in that crowd, I would believe I was going to die.
Yeah, no question the way that that lady came up on stage, the way they grabbed
that guy, I would have thought that there was five guys converging on the
theater with a are fifteens. I I agree. I like yeah, it was being surrounded.
Yeah, fully it's like you have to get out right now or stay.
I'm my I'm so fascinated by I need to
okay. We should go to an investigate anybody. We need to go do an
investigation, but also if anybody was there or knows any mark Norman fans who
we have been there that night. We want to interview you. We need to put together a
documentary. I just decided right now there's going to be a normal
investigation into this. We're going to do at least a twenty five minute.
Oh, my God, we need to go to the
comedy club. Yeah, they'll let us in. Here's what we do. Look under all
these. Oh, my God, here's what we do. Okay, we tell New York Comedy Club,
hey, we want to do a live show at New York Comedy Club
and that's how we get to
that's how we get it's under cover investigation. We all are walking in
wearing spy glasses, and we record everything. Oh my God, we just want to
look right at the museum to yeah and then
we get you so right. We get mad up here and we do a full. We have here. We see
if there's any paranormal it in this. We somehow try to sell it as part of the
show, yes, but it's not it's not
part of the show. We have Matt walking around using his BVP, the EVP reader
trying to find hot spots and cold spots. Guys, can I tell you something right
now? Yes, well, as since we started discussing this, there's a man standing
out the office door staring at us and has been for the past five minutes. Oh
my God, we are literally getting men in black right now. I'm not kidding. He's
literally just staring at us. He looked at me and then I looked up at him and he
nodded.
What should we pause right now and see what he wants? I don't think so. Did
anybody remember to lock the door? Because I don't think I did when I came
I think I did. I hope that I did because I don't really, really he's leaving. I
think he's waiting for the bus. He's been made. I think we're on to home.
Mike, you don't know. He's just kind of casually walking away. Rose up in a
crazy fucking way. We got a wait a minute. Norman. We got fucking Norman.
Oh, we got Norman just like him. Yep. A man who's that man jumped on what could
to be technically our stage. Yeah, front step. Our front step is a stage.
That's crazy. Holy cow. There's a guy with a beanie.
Oh my God, an orange beanie. No, it's a red. It's well, he's wearing red.
Yeah, it's a red beanie. It's not the same guy. It's when the similarities
stack up. I mean, that was why was he? He looked at the nod that he gave
and he looks, he has a scary. He just walked by again. He's wearing a
and for everyone, he was wearing a hoodie in all black. Yeah, and he only
he was coming to eliminate. It was a nod. It was a nod like I know he nodded and
he left after we stopped talking about the incident. We started talking about
him. Let's see if we talk about it again and he comes back. What if a
different person
I'm getting really scared? What if we've stumbled on to the greatest? What is it
really is? This is a completely saying he that nod was. I know you're talking
about you were never really here. This is where we're fully in we're in it. Now
there's no way out. We're under the Silver Lake. The only way to get out
under the New York comedy because we gotta go through yeah. Oh here's another
thing we could do you're right. There is a bar above New York, New York City
comedy club or New York comedy club KGB. We go up there saw
we wait to Jerry Tom and Jerry saw down into the club after closing hours. I
don't really know why they'd let us in a KGB, but not New York comedy club,
but we could find out a way to get in and then we saw up and
and then we just patch it on up when we leave nobody yet. No, no, no, the wiser
and we leave with the truth. We have to make this investigation. Doc, I bet we
get a new to New York comedy club. We go do our show. We get into the green room
and then straight up Resident Evil style. There's an eagle medallion on a say that
you have to find like that just for last mascot. Yes, that weird bug thing. Yes,
the green guy. I don't know his name bug or whatever. Not muzzy some no. It's got
the
rap world, a glizzy is slang for a glock handgun. The evolution of the word to include hot dog
dog comes from the extended magazine of a pistol, which is about the length of a
hot dog more. What happens inside an eater's body after the Nathan's hot dog
eating contest? Do not test me on hot dog knowledge and what happens inside an
eater's body,
probably digestion, most likely digestion, but I mean we could I can't
believe there's another man outside is the right there moving stuff. Don't
worry about okay, maybe he's a mover, maybe that's what the guy van is
literally the number one surveillance type van. I'm not. Oh my God, you're
right. If it the only way this could be more suspicious is if it was flowers,
the van has flower delivery on the side. I've never seen flowers get delivered
like no and as soon as you've big white van with no window, I'm running like a
drug operation. I'm a hacker. I've got like a trillion terabytes of like
sensitive government information on the hard drive and I look at them. We're
I guess my neighbor's getting flowers delivered. I mean I'm in I'm in
completely the slums. Oh,
it looks like he's getting an edible arrangement.
I have binoculars. They're probably trying to see where in the house the
flowers would look the best. Yeah, what's the what's the place of the most
sunlight in the apartment? Yeah, exactly. They're trying to do all this
sort of measurement. That's okay.
Oh, my God,
you need to stop being. Yeah, I know I'm
that glass door is now metal. We got to get frosted glass stuff for it. We could
you know we could glass sticker. We could just move this whole operation to the
New York Comedy Club to know we need to move this shit to Texas right now. Yeah,
we need to move this operation to Texas or Florida. We got to start going to the
mothership. Did you guys see that is my only safe mother ship is somebody's
gonna save space. They're trying to invade Texas or some shit. Yeah, what's
What's going on with that? I did not see what any of that was. I don't really know either.
Who's trying to invade Texas? The federal government is trying to run around Texas.
They're trying to run around? I guess Greg Abbott, who I just found out is in a wheelchair.
I didn't know that. He's very famously in a wheelchair. Not for me. He's very famously
a rightoid scumbag, if you ask me. That's what he's famous for. For me, he's most famous
for being named Greg. That's pretty much all I knew about him. And Abbott. And every time
I think Abbott Elementary, this TV show, but I think that he's a character in that.
He's not in elementary school.
I get him confused far from it.
No, no, he's graduated high school and college.
There was some baseball player who had one arm and his last name was Abbott, I think.
And you think that that's Greg.
I get them confused because there's some physical disability that they both have.
Well, here's an easy way to do it.
I don't think many baseball players are in wheelchairs.
Kenny Kawaguchi.
Well, maybe after.
Kenny Kawaguchi from Backyard Baseball.
true. Yeah. Yeah. How'd you buy that was a crazy pull? You know the name of all the all
I know is Pedro Pablo Pablo.
But yeah, I guess Greg Abbott wanted to put up razor wire to kill pregnant women when
they try to cross the border and Biden was like screw you man and now he's sending people
to take up the razor wire and I think that there's going to be a clash at the border
Clash of Clans. Yeah, it's gonna be a year the Texas succeeds. I did. I don't want to
lose Texas. I love Texas. I like Texas. I love Texas. What? I don't want to lose Texas. I
saw a really funny picture on Facebook. Yeah, this is non Texas. Okay. All right. It was
one of those things where they say Simpsons predicted everything. Yeah. And this was, you
know, this that most epic selfie ever. Yes. Bradley Cooper, Ellen, Kevin Spacey, Julia
the Roberts. This was a completely this is from a serious conspiracy page. This
was not a jokely. It was probably someone made it as a joke and then this serious
conspiracy page posted it thinking it was real and it was the top. It said
Simpsons predicted everything. It was the picture of the most epic selfie ever and
then it was a picture of a Simpsons fide at the most epic selfie ever. That was
captured in one
and it had Ellen and
whoa
We need to look to see if the Simpsons predicted this Norman ship.
I think there's a strong possibility.
The McBain stand up clip?
That could be it.
That could be fully.
Or it could be Krusty the Clown.
Krusty the Clown and Sideshow Bob.
And Sideshow Bob jumps on.
What color is Sideshow Bob's hair?
Reddish.
What color is that guy's jacket?
What color is his hat?
Don't remember.
Fashion brain.
Simpsons yellow.
Scanned the outfit.
Well, it's because he's wearing the same outfit as Norman.
I couldn't have told you either of them.
You're the only person who saw this because you have a fashion brain.
Okay.
So, I bet you know what I'm wearing right now.
Yes.
Fashion brain.
You're wearing a Squidward colored shirt.
I look at you and I just see crap.
You see crap?
I just know if an outfit is good or bad and that one is bad.
How is this bad?
It's similar to stuff that you wear.
wearing diarrhea colors. I'm not wearing diarrhea colors. Brown and dark green. You wear the
same thing. Yeah, I stopped though today. You stopped though today because you thought that
it was diarrhea colors? That reminds people of diarrhea. No, you know what it could remind
people of? It could remind people of beef and broccoli. That could be food. No. If broccoli
was that color and beef was that brown, I would not be eating Chinese food once every
other day. Why did the guy who jumped on stage not even say anything? Maybe he was about to.
He just jumped on stage and he just stood there. He wasn't trying to heckle. He wasn't
he was trying to get away from something, the ultimate heckle, but even getting
away from something he didn't even he wasn't even like he didn't point at
anything. He wasn't like whoa, he was completely up there. He got up there to
get a better view of what was happening in the club. He gets up there just so
that he can look around because you can't see everything from the dark.
Only place you can see the only vantage point and he gets up there and he's
looking around and now that I see a look a little closer, he's wearing a chain.
man. So he could be a gangsta yeah or he could be an escape. He could be
escaped from like a facility where they chained him up. That's true. He could
have been chained up to a wall like this, trying to break away,
and then he ends up in this thing, because I was thinking yeah, maybe he
is a time traveler is trying to warn something and he, but then he didn't
say anything.
It really is upsetting to me. It's this whole thing is fucking me up in a
crazy way. I need to and you know what the worst part is. You know that this
minute is going to get memory hold within a week. You did
remember the Norman. I what I want to promise everybody who's watching this
episode. We will never forget about. We will never let this story die. What if
this becomes our this episode and I don't care if you don't really find this
very because the new intro, the new intro is a full the full, the full video
every single time show becomes called the Norman files, the Norman files. We
we'll get to the bottom of this. We started the museum to the norm into
five. I'm going to take somebody right now and ask if they have Norman's phone
number yeah. This is where this is going to give him a call yeah. Oh my phone is
dead. God damn it man. Okay, this is where that by next episode we're going
to be. I will have a full prank call. I phones coming back on Holy shit. I have
a full prank call attacking Mark Norman, but where I ask him what hell what he
did, why yeah well, we just need to interview say because we need to
interview him. Yeah, we literally need to interview him to get to the bottom of
this, because if he spews some of that bullshit, we can pick it apart. You know,
he's going to be talking about this on every single podcast that he goes on.
Well, I know that, yeah, but that's the thing, I want to scoop him, because now
he has time to think up a cover. He's probably-,
here's what he's probably going to say. I mean, he's probably on a plane back to
the Bahamas. Exactly, where he's from. He's probably going to say,
Yeah, there was a fucking SJW in the crowd and jumped up on stage.
He was triggered.
Got mad at me because he was triggered.
I guess that's comedy.
And that's comedy these days.
And thanks for asking about it.
And Mark, I'm going to see through your fucking bullshit.
That's right.
X-ray vision.
The man with the x-ray eyes.
You are lying.
The worst part about this is, to me, as a comedy fan, he didn't get to say when he was getting
pulled off the stage, "Thank you, I've been Kevin Hart."
he didn't get to say.
Fuck me, I didn't even think about that.
That's incredible.
He didn't even get to say thank you.
He didn't even get to do his funny.
He said op op op op op.
Right now he...
Maybe that'll be his new...
Oh, hey.
That is the best part of the video is that he cannot shut up for some reason.
He can't shut up.
Oh, okay.
And then he walks like this.
The walk is fully the walk that you do after you like, you go up.
That's a walk you do if you're up on karaoke and you fart loud enough it gets picked up
by the mic.
he's trying to serpentine his way out in case there's fire gun fire. Look at
his arms. Look he's holding his hands in front of him like he's doing like a
dance.
You can see just his head go back and forth as he wobbles out of the hallway.
He just goes his head has like a full there's a foot between each side where
he wobbles his head. He's walking like a South Park character, but at what point
is he when he okay when he gets off stage and he's walking away and he does
that walk full sprint yeah. At what point is he doesn't walk like a normal
person? How long do you think that's his normal walk? That is not no. He does
that when people are looking yeah. When he gets back onto the street, he walks
like a normal person. I'm sure he's not waddling around. He doesn't waddle in
the subway. Okay, you be right now. I want to we need a practice here. Okay,
you be mark normand mark normand is coming on the podcast. We're asking
what I want to show you how I would drill mark norman to get the truth out
because you're about to spew the bullshit, right?
We have to lull him into obscurity.
So first, we'll be like, "Oh, hey, Mark. Nice to see you."
"Oh, what are you going to call this podcast about math?"
Yeah, we actually...
It's close. Thanks for doing the show.
What's going on around here?
It's a video podcast.
You should call it "Podcast about fish."
There's a fish on the wall.
Comedy.
What are you going to call this podcast about water?
Because they've got a water bottle here.
It's an empty water bottle, Mark.
I just went to a comedy show the other night, and it was like...
huh comedy. It went really. It was kind of like everyone was bombing and that
was really awkward. So I was wondering like what's the craziest show you've
done recently? Oh well, the craziest show I've done recently is oh
oh oh wait. Where you going mark? Oh my watch this now stay now.
Mark sit down.
Sit down mark. Now I'm going to show you. I'm going to show you my man. No
this is how I would break his spirit. Okay,
so Mark, what happened at that one show?
I'm not Mark, I'm Kevin Hart. Oh, hello, Kevin. Hey, Kevin, did you hear about
Mark Normans?
What do you think?
Kevin Hart, will you wear a dress for us, please? No, no, no, that is the
funniest shit ever. Do you see that in the Cat Williams? Oh yeah, where he's
like yeah, I'm like the only comedian that they didn't get to wear a dress and
he's like Kevin or the dress. Yeah and he thinks the entire Illuminati is about
getting comedians to wear dresses. It's really, really awesome. Yeah, I'm
surprised we didn't talk about the Cat Williams thing either. Well, it was just
everybody. What do you think Cat Williams thinks of Mark Norman? Probably
loves him, man. Yeah. I mean maybe not after this, he's gonna say this is a
the full Illuminati. Yeah, it's going to say this is Illuminati for sure. It is
full Illuminati. And I'm with him. I mean, he was right about it. The guy who
jumped on stage is a clone of Norman, who was in the early gestation phases. He's
still kind of his body still adapting to become the reason he got up on stage and
stood next to Norman's like that was because the Illuminati was standing in
the back of the room and needed to get a good look, saying take a pick so they
can compare features and see what they need to tweak. It's like it's like
something it's like doing a me and you making a me on the we and you you make
a me on the we and you hold up your phone and you're looking at what's that
potion in Harry Potter that turns you in a poly juice, poly just potion where
your skin is bubbling yeah and you're kind of slowly transform. That's exactly
what I saw a skin bubble. Yes, I think I saw the skin bubble on God. I still
can't believe if you have any pictures or videos of this event, please, please
don't use them. Yeah God damn it man. I mean I'm willing to
spend
three years invest three years and forty thousand dollars
to get
right. I'm actually willing to ruin my life. My wife comes home. I have a big
the big pin board in the red. Exactly going everywhere. So the act full
killer, full, full mind.
I
live in your car,
bottle of Jack Daniels, just just drink, counting it. She knows that I don't
didn't care about the story that much. I just wanted to drink and leave her and
I'm just kind of pounding it doing one string back and forth between mark
Norman, New York comedy club. That's all I have doing a string between New York
and comedy club.
The only thing in the middle is three years,
then there's one really long red string that's going like all the way across
the room. There's a frame photo of Jim Gaffigan. I know he has something to do
with this.
Oh my God, his alternate personality.
you think that was Jim Gaffigan turned around. I was going to get a
Potter the head on the back.
That's why we're the beanie to cover up Jim's face in the front. This is
exactly. I didn't say anything. Oh my God, can I tell you guys what happened
when Mark Norman walked out? He walks out of the theater, he goes, he's
freaking out, he speed walks down the street, he sits, he gets in his car,
he sits down in the driver's seat, turns it on, lights go on silhouette in
the back seat.
he's driving his car. He's trying to start his car. Can you take it to
mcdonald's? Mark, he doesn't know a bomb will go off as soon as the
ignition.
The heck
he still doesn't realize. Well, I think that we're losing track of who the who
doesn't probably set this up on who probably set this up is Robert Kelly. I
think Bobby Kelly said, yeah, Bobby, Bobby, Kelly, Bobby, Kelly from the
bond, likely he's trying to dispel it to he's saying like this was he said it
this bullshit. Well, it really doesn't make any sense. I tried to tell him
boy. The first post he made was like I told you this was bullshit or
something, which wait a second. I told you this was hold on. I'm going to pull
up this first post you made and I'm going to read it because he says I told
you this is blind. I told him in the replies. I was trying to tell him about
the theory that is going around that is a paranormal. I think he did not
respond. I think that it is paranormal. I think that there was some kind of
air Norman comedy. Yes, see thank you. He said I love that everyone stayed like
cattle this bullshit. Anyways, this bullshit anyways, this bullshit
anyways, and then in the other post ready starts it with told you what I
mean stayed like cattle, because they don't understand cattle stays cattle.
Just one of the main things about cattle is they stay. Usually it's not
usually when people are making a metaphor about cattle, it's like oh and
they all stayed. It wasn't that they all did the same thing or went somewhere or
did something to say it wasn't that they could be all stayed, which cattle, by
the way famously cannot be moved or heard it right. I always just stay what
when people say they're like cattle. They mean that they're not listening to
what someone's telling them and that they're staying yeah and it's not and
the cattle are hearing the farmer and they stay. We do you think he could
have been the I'm sorry, I'm just thinking more. I know it's more acts
axes, more ways we could approach this problem.
This show certainly had an opener. Yes, right, there's no way it was straight
Mark Norman jumping on stage. Certainly at a host, certainly at an opener.
We could look at the lineup.
And I'm sure if it's like the kind of person who just does host spots at New York Comedy
Club, that they are a friend of a friend. We could find out what happened there.
Let's pull up the lineup. Let's figure out.
I don't know if it'll be posted.
It's @hihi.
How many days ago was it?
This was...
Two days, one day ago.
It was not last night, but the night before.
Yeah. Well, the post was yesterday.
The post was yesterday, but in the morning, they weren't doing a show.
The show was at night.
Yeah, the show must have been on the... Wait, what is today?
26th.
It must have been on the 24th.
Okay, let me try.
And this is going to be a legendary date that you're going to need to remember. 1/24/24.
Yeah, because it... Oh my God, 24/24.
Exactly, yeah.
Wait, wait. Okay, so that's another thing.
Oh, here's an article about it from USA Today.
Oh my God.
A comedian was escorted off stage during a stand-up show in New York on Wednesday
in a strange incident he now says was a planned surprise that he was not involved in.
That's bullshit! That is a cover-up! We know!
That is such bullshit, dude! We know that that is a cover-up, Norman!
A planned surprise? In a statement provided to USA Today,
Norman said no one was harmed or injured during his performance
and that the disruption was part of a planned surprise activity by show producers.
but Norman said he had no prior knowledge that this was going to
happen in an earlier post on his Instagram story. Norman said his
team was still trying to put together the details.
Planned surprise.
A plant just tell us what the fuck you're talking about adding
to the intrigue.
Donald Glover shared several of high highs posts on his Instagram
story, including a screenshot of a TMZ article about the Norman
incident high high available.
Now one of Glover's posts said a Vanity Fair report published
Thursday said Glover's upcoming show Mr. And Mrs. Smith features a mysterious entity nicknamed
Hi-Hi.
USA Today reached out to representatives for Glover.
The Hi-Hi Instagram account also shared videos of Tyra Banks being surrounded by two people
in furry costumes at an NBA game this week, clips of which also went viral.
Wait, is he saying, so Mark is-
This is all a global conspiracy.
He's claiming this is a prank-
This is a Glover conspiracy.
Involving, he's saying that this is, they're saying this is Childish Gambino's fault.
They're saying that this is all marketing. That Childish Gambino orchestrated this.
And this is all marketing for a new show. That is not true. That is not true.
That is not fucking true at all. No. We reject your reality. That is such an...
People are so used to this shit of like, "Oh, this thing happened at a thing and it turns out
it's Sacha Baron Cohen." Mark Normand. They set up this fake show that is going to be in production
fiction forever, so that they can always say, oh, that was happening because we
were doing a prank for the show, but it's bullshit. Mark Norman is back at
New York Comedy Club on Wednesday. We have to come back in town. We'll go. We
will have to go. I will be there. No, I think it's a weekly show. They matter
mark norman what and I will be charging the stage. We will be rushing, rushing
and picking him up and kidnapping him, bringing him back here. Okay, take a
kidnapping and bring him here, sitting him down and interviewing him. I
don't have
yeah, and he will immediately because he's such a showman right. He's going
to have no choice but to sit here and broadcast with us for a couple hours,
and I will play him in skate. It won't let me view the past date, so I can't
see who was on the show. Fuck, there's no way. We'll find out. I'm going to put
out. I'm going to put out my feelers. Yeah, and I'm going to get a trench coat
right at the museum to the Norman incident. The Norman files right at the
New York comedy incident. This is
well, I mean, parent is right there. Paranormal and he likes
laughter. He loves
para norman left. Tivity that's good coming coming soon. Don't worry. We're
on the light at the
delight right at the delight of the light at the para normand delight at
that. No, we're like and you see him delight when you see the light when you
see her norman to laugh.
Paranormal life to light when you see a pair of Norman's leftivity and
there's the episode title yeah, a pair of Norman light at the mark. ZM all
right, there we go. What's going on mark? ZM, we have anything going on
besides
holder meeting is tomorrow. I think the from the day that this comes out and I
want to say again, if you have any info messages, literally yeah, please anybody
who has any connection at all, you want to just make something out. Yeah, we
will use all of it in our investigation. What else do we I mean yeah subscribe to
the higher tier. If you want to do the shareholder meeting, that's will be
discord job. The play. Yep, job. February 1st, buy a ticket to that and
we're doing a Q and a after that play, which
we don't know how it's gonna go either. So just come out and we'll see
what it means. Really? So we it's trying to get you out to the
theater. Wait, wait, wait. What if somebody what a guy? Oh my God.
What if this is part of it? What if this was the plan all
long. This is their status up and being if I see an or if I'm holding the
smoking gun, they're going to say it was our they're going to find me because
oh my God, they better not. If you're the beanie guy, do not come to that
show. Do not message. Don't come to any of our shows. Do not come. Well, I
mean, I like I mean, this is we I still can't believe we got completely
actually. Okay, we need that scared. We need some of you to come to the show.
We need a lot of you to come to the show. Yeah, and I guess just
keep keep stay tuned. There's a big announcement coming up soon, so just
oh yeah to the ground and check the news. Yeah, also junior associate
February second. Oh yeah, sure yeah, coming on, but watch out for January
thirty first. Why watch out
there? Like I said, watch the news. I don't think we're making it to January
for thirty first after this.
Oh and
don't be playing donkey kong with Cameron. Okay, I won't be happening
more
And so I'm like, alright, maybe the first step is to not drink Yoo-Hoo's at 3am.
And then I'm like, how do I- alright, now I'm trying to get into that, uh, you know, so-
The sugar rush.
Yeah, so I'm on a bit of a spiritual journey.
These days, that-
Indian sugar makes you happy, though.
These days, that whole-
They do.
That's the premise of Willy Wonka.
Well, that's true.
Did you guys see the Wonka movie?
Not yet.
No, my wife did.
Okay, it sucked.
Yeah, I heard it was terrible.
It was terrible.
I rewatched the 2006 Willy Wonka movie. It rocks.
With depth.
Really?
Yeah, with depth.
I mean also by the way, they don't give a fuck about it.
I like that Willy Wonka because he,
like the new Willy Wonka is kind of like a dope,
but this, the Johnny Depp one, he hates children.
- Yeah.
- And he's mean to all the kids and his wife.
- Well this is his origin.
- I hear the new one is Woker.
- Oh shit.
- No way.
- Willy Woka or something.
- Oh my God.
- They drop a slur in the fucking, in the 2006 one.
- Oh yeah, sure.
They were cussing up the story.
It's funny when they're Wokifying the new Willy Wonka,
they're like, "How do we fix the Oompa Loompas?
How do we make this not Willy Wonka having a bunch of jungle slaves?"
Yeah.
And then it's that they put Hugh Grant small and he's like,
"Oh my God, I can't believe you fucking enslaved me."
It's just that he still has a slave, but now it's a quippy British smug slave.
Isn't it, well he has multiples of Hugh Grant in the movie?
I don't know man, I didn't see it.
Do we have a Wonka expert that can call in?
I just remember in the trailer that he catches Hugh Grant in a glass thing like a cockroach.
He catches him?
Yeah, yeah, he catches him.
Yeah, he catches him.
What the fuck?
There's only one of them.
I think the thing about the Oompa Loompas that's cool is that they're a bunch of little
guys.
I don't care that there's just one.
He only had one Oompa Loompa in the sequel?
Only one Oompa Loompa.
Sometime between the prequel and the original, the Hugh Grant Oompa Loompa is fucking, is
He's asexually reproducing.
He's putting a pipe down.
What is it like when a person is asexually laying pipe on themselves?
Isn't it strange that uh...
They're like...
They're all guys.
All guys.
[MUSIC PLAYING]