Hello, hello, hello, Cameron. What is something amazing for you? Okay, I have
a gift for you. Oh my God. He's been giving out so many gifts. There was an
incredible. We'll get into the gift from yesterday in a minute as I'm too
excited to think about anybody else's gift right now. Close your eyes. Okay,
Do I close them too? Hold on, keep your eyes closed. Do I hold up my hands?
Cameron, I don't want to spoil it, but it's exciting. Do I hold up my hands yet?
Yeah, hold your hands out. Well, it's not that big. That's a classic joke. Okay, you
could probably just do one hand actually. Okay, that actually worked. I think this
is because I'm so proud of you in the gym. Oh my god. I got you this very, very
special gift. Wow. And tell the people what that is. This is a free Junior
Frosty for a year with any purchase from Wendy's for the Dave Thomas Foundation
for adoption. Yeah, and this is a Christmas special. Oops, that Wendy's
runs every year. Guys, I can't believe it either. I can't. I really can't.
Thank you so much. I also got the same gift last night.
It's don't tell him that, but he was there. I was there because I saw I saw
the blatant disrespect. There was a disrespect. Yeah, I have a problem with
and here's why I can put it on my keys and by the way, here's why I wanted to
give this to you, Cameron one because I'm proud of you this year. You've been
getting into the gym. You give it your all you're getting you're really you're
becoming
you're becoming an amazing man and it's amazing to see you blossom in front of
me right as your eldest as your eldest brother. This is an amazing amazing
thing that I've been seeing out of you great is just it's really incredible and
the number two reason is Patrick didn't say thank you when I gave him the same
gift yeah and refused to say thank you and I kept asking to say thank you and I
said no. Thank you. He just kept saying no. Thank you, because he just doesn't
and I'd like to understand why that I don't know why that is. I mean I do have
a problem accepting gifts and both compliments and gifts. You know this
about me, but why couldn't you just say okay?
I gave you ice cream. I said okay therapy
frankly, have a problem with. Okay, I gave you ice unlimited ice cream. Yes,
it's crazy. It is the best gift. It is the best possibly get I limited ice
cream. I just and it's a don't know why even after it goes on your runs out. I
don't even know why I don't even know why that so I'd like you to say it now.
Thank you, Caleb for the unlimited junior frosties for a year.
It is going to make me so fat for only okay. So now he's already saying that
yeah. First of all, he said only a year. I'm not yeah for a year. It's going to
make me fat. You're already like a junior for us.
That you don't have self control. Just because I gave you a limited ice cream.
I'm not blaming you. I'm saying that this is a good thing. You're not even
getting fat yet and you're already, you're getting, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm saying fat when I mean I'm bulking. You pre blamed me for your, I'm not
blaming, I'm not blaming, I'm thanking you for helping me with my bulk.
So when I get, when I look, look at me now.
yep, you can go wide. Now I can go wider. He can go wider now, but I have a
bicep dimple now that you pointed out.
You I think I was just check attention to his friend's bodies very much this
one.
We were at the gym and I did this and you went, oh, bicep dimple. Yep. He was
so more excited than I was. You started, you brought it up again. You're way more
excited. I don't even remember this moment. You said this, you pointed at me
what we were doing. He was more yeah
well. It made me excited. It made me excited. It got me that yeah, the beauty
of accepting it is yeah gifts from your and that is my that is actually it was
my new year's resolution. Really what a bicep dimple, no learning to learning to
accept compliments and stuff all right. Mine was get a new car. I didn't have
any this year. No, I didn't have time to think of it in time. I don't think I've
I'm living like I made a bunch of resolutions, but I didn't make any that
is really powerful. I've been going to bed early, waking up early, reading
every night, going to the gym. Well, those are resolutions, but I didn't
resolve to do any of this stuff. I'm just randomly doing it. He has zero
resolve. I'm just doing it on accident. I'm just I literally
I just happen to do it. He's actually slipped into the most healthy. If you
were watching my life out from outside like a movie, you'd think that I made a
big list on a piece of paper and things I had to do this year, but you I have
zero goals. Yeah, you don't give a fuck about any of this shit. I hope I end
this year in the same way I ended last year on the couch on my bed yeah on the
bed. Well, it's night time. I just sleep is true midnight yeah. What are you
going to do? Stay up? I don't say past midnight. What you have one you have one
resolution me, which is what is it play play all games play all games.
It is a resolution. I don't make the ring a tuxedo all games. In fact, I
girl. If I made any resolution, it was playing no games, but I didn't make
that he didn't make that even if I did, I would be failing it because I'm
playing all games. Yeah, well, so it's a reverse resolution. The reverse
resolution is a good idea. You said it reverse unsolution, an unsolution so
that
so when you don't do it, so if you don't do it, you did actually complete a
guess. A desolution would just be something like don't eat candy. Don't
don't stop this. Stop that. Yeah, good one. Don't eat poop is a good one that
I have trouble with.
I have a little every year. I've never completed it. It's always it always
like I get through January fine, and then you eat one. I'm like
now I can do it. I got a power through here. Come say Margerie,
here comes a day. There's all the people, just one crumb, one dingleberry,
yeah, all the people eating shepherds pie and cottage pie and you're just in
the bathroom locked under one of the stalls trying to eat their shit. Yeah,
this is a because what can hurt just once just one. I made it through two months.
Everybody's Irish on St. Patrick's Day. You gotta eat it. Yeah, I deserve this
shit. Literally. Yeah, literally. Oh, I went home. Everybody's saying, "Where's
Caleb on the last episode?" I went home for a bad news type of situation, but I
took a plane there, guys.
And here's what I've noticed about planes. Here we go. Yeah, so go ahead and
buckle up. Here we go. And another thing about going home, I got a Columbia zip up
that I stole from my stepdad. I saw this is my new type of look. I saw this. I
now... You guys both are wearing new things. I now... He has a what? A
heather gray hoodie. He noticed that buckles. You know why I noticed this?
'Cause this is something my dad would wear. So I... What a gray hoodie? Well,
this exact type of... We got the same damn pants on, motherfucker. No, yours
are... Yours are Carhartt's. What's this kind of fabric design called? Damn.
This is called the... Heather. Heather gray. Heather gray. Yeah, heather gray.
but this is what a beautiful name for a woman. It is so it is a hot. If I was
married to a woman,
I would take her long legs, so I become Patrick Gray, Heather,
Patrick Gray. I forgot about him. Oh yeah, that's her buddy.
I haven't seen him in years. So
what was I saying? Oh, playing my plane observation right. Have you guys know
well, maybe this is just me whenever I go on a plane and I don't really like
planes that much. I pretend I am fine with them, but I get pretty scared on
them sometimes yeah, and I think the
people the plane people know this, and so they decide to seat me. It doesn't
matter if I'm number eight or number twenty eight. If I open my window, I
look directly at the wavering yeah, that is is about to yeah off the plane,
and I don't know how this is possible on the plan on the ride up there. I sat
like eleven F and on the ride back. They move the wings yeah. They
moving to wherever I am. How big is the fucking wing? Maybe it's the cheapest
seat. They just put you in the wing yeah, so that you get that nobody wants
we
can't change the wings every flight because they know that nobody wants are
the ones where you are responsible for everyone's safety on the plane. If
there's a right, I let that is a really good or air marshal those seats. The
worst seats, I hate it when they come up to are you they say, hey, are you
are you come to the plane?
Are you comfortable flying the plane and landing? I hate it when I fly spirit
airlines and you know that they are barely they're holding that plane
together with duct tape. I suppose spirit they come up to me. They come up
to me with a badge and a gun and they say are you you are you prepared to be
the air? Are you comfortable being the air marshal on this flight today guys?
It's coming. What
the big the big commercial airplane crash is coming? I think I think that
every time I've been
almost two years. We're going on tour. I know we're going to die. Don't we don't
serious the giant commercial airplane crash that will completely redefine the
airline industry forever. That's a change, change the regulation. Everything
will change things. Maybe we'll get safer, maybe not it's coming. So here's
my valance big bopper buddy Holly.
I really really really is coming. I think so to I almost don't want to get on a
plane for the next five years. Not going to be in the States. It is going to be
in the state. What are you talking about? That's the only way anything all
the time everywhere, everywhere else. It will be in Canada. They will be in
Canada. Well, that's still it'll be on air. Still the United States, it'll be
on air, not Canada, but it'll be a plane from it'll be an air lingus plane from
Canada. I don't like that. It's going to happen in the US, though, because I'm
talking about I think so. U. S. Airline, I think I think it will crash.
hmm. I think two planes are going to are going to collide when they're landing
breaking bad. Wow, I think it's going to be an air traffic issue. You saw the
video the other day where the pilot was chewing out the air traffic control
person because they were about to collide into each other. They do it
happens all the time. It happens literally six hundred times a year that
play passenger planes almost collide into each other. So one of these times
somebody's going to get. I thought I'm saying bro it's going to happen. It's
crazy and you guys see this Boeing stuff. What's happening with bone? You guys
haven't you know when the entire side of the plane blew off and they had to land
did you guys not see this? Maybe this is your prediction. You're serious. You
didn't see this. I did not there was a there was a fucking I don't remember
which airline it was, but they took off they're flying and then Julio look this
up. They they want it fucking the one of the windows, you know how it's like a
window like segment yeah. It came, it blew off oh that's bad and and it was
just it was completely depressurized. They had to land and nobody was in that
seat, but if it happened, they would have just been so
instantly and then they check the plate and they're like yeah. All the bolts on
this plane were loose.
They hadn't tightened the bolts in like ten years. I always and it's bow. It's
Boeing plans. You see look at this is your air. This is your no no no no
everybody's going to die yeah. I mean I just can't happen. This is they need to
fix this.
Please tell me they at least fixed it. I don't tell you that they're not still
flying this play.
Seems like a recipe. This is Caleb's plan. You just duct tape over that damn
spot and start flying it around. Am I right? You don't I don't strike you as
that kind of person. You do that all the time with your car, yeah tape stuff you
duct tape. You've had like five duct tape situations on your okay one time.
Yes, I did have a pink kids hand mirror that replaced the side view mirror and
yes it was duct tape, but that was only for for what about your car window.
What about the hood of your car? The car window is saran wrap by the way, not
duct tape, asshole dumb ass and that was only for a month and a half. Why would
they break into your car with how it looked someone broke it in his air
they didn't break into the car. They just threw a beer bottle through the window.
Okay, it was a terrorist. You know why it was your Bernie sticker. It was fully
the Bernie sticker and it was a Heineken, which is a conservative conservative
right wing style beer. Yeah, I saw somebody put up
like some flyers around the neighborhood for like it was like communist meeting
or whatever you got to organize or yeah, I was like pictures of Karl Marx or
something and like something made me laugh was like someone went by and like
tore down part of it and scribbled over it with sharpie and like wrote a bunch
like USA forever long live USA and it's so funny to me to be like a full like
USA, USA guy living in Ridgewood.
So yeah, just there is a guy I see him on the walk over sometimes and he'll have
his garage door open, whole garage trumped out like big like yeah, I guess
also that is like that's why this neighborhood still cool because you
don't have it's not all
the hippie the hipsters. I bet also the people like that are like so much more.
They dig their heels in so much more because of all the communists and they
see me walk around them. Exactly. You guys should see me walk around this
neighbourhood, big hoop earrings, a shirt that goes to my nipples on the
downwards way, just right above them. Yeah, yeah, fishnet. I have a fishnet. I
fishnet shoes. Everyone sees your arca tattoo on your belly. Yeah, yeah,
the arca tummy rocker.
you have a big portrait of Arca on your I do
I look good, but a lot of people don't like it, and so I think that that's the
other thing that's coming as a retaliation against me. I walk around
with an under bite. So people don't talk to me. That's smart. That's really smart
when they ask you stuff. You just go. Nobody asked me stuff. You walk around
with an under. I don't want to talk to anybody. Say under board to you. Oh,
hell no guarantee it, because I don't want to know that voice sounds like no
people got a little bit of spit in it. Yeah, exactly and showing your teeth
like an angler fish to not just in the job. Just yeah, I'm afraid they'll bite
but I'm not doing that walking up to the game in contact.
So when you walk you walk up to the bouncer and just go hello, you walk
into a bar walking fully like like knuckles dragging on the ground until
you get to the bouncer. So they style just yeah. Hello. Hello. That movie
scared me when I was a kid because I thought usual suspect anybody who has a
disability could be faking it
and could be
isn't that scary. Yeah, that's a scary idea. Did anybody that's really fucking
scary. Someone pops out of the wheelchair and now listen, they got
Ganondorf powers. Get the fuck away from me man. Stay back. Stay down.
Yeah, say a pig get back down or don't become the pig. Stay a pig. Stay a pig
Ganondorf a pig.
you're saying so it stands up out of their wheelchair. You say stay down and
I got no Ganondorf the man and then Ganon you're always getting confused in
offensive ways. Yeah,
you are easily. Yeah, this is like I step on the real you type of I step on
rakes confused. You is the real you know
the confused me is yeah that the really you really pops out when you get
confused. I don't call disabled people pig. You literally just did about thirty
I was saying that Gannon is a pig. It's always something crazy and new to or
I've never heard in my entire life. Anybody say something like that, it
sounds awful. It comes out and I'm like that is a horrible. That's crazy. That
is horrifying. What have I said? What have I said like that besides pig? I'm
sure that somebody can make a super cut there. Yeah, there could easily be a
super cut of all the times that you've actually said something horribly
offensive as a confusion.
I thought we were talking about something else. You get confused for one second and you go
just Doug Stanhope instantly. It's a very interesting quality to your body. Interesting. So what's
going on? We, last night, did our Q&A. We did a Q&A for Job the Play. We had three old
women walk out. No, I saw you. I saw you posting about this and you're wrong. No, no, no, there
there was an old woman who walked out and stared at us. He did not see her.
We took that look at the strike, but you're saying you're here to touch it
too, because then he will
it's strong the strength. So he's distracted by my strength. It's it's
I didn't see the first person walk out, but the majority of people who walked
out and this is you're trying to give false info to make it seem like we
bombed when we didn't we didn't bomb. I'm not saying we bombed. I'm just
saying that there was a little lady, the old ladies who walked out, walked out
after we finished our portion and we said okay, now we're going to take
questions from the audience. That's when they left. They were like if these guys
aren't talking anymore, I'm fucking off. They love us. They hate the audience.
All right, well, I thought that that was a failure and on us to the old
community, but no actually they don't have a they hate each other. It's like
it's like when you go to a concert, you leave after the opener. You that's
because you just like the opener. It's not because opener was so bad. You can't
even handle the main event anymore. Yeah, exactly. That would be a silly. There
because my friend told me that the woman he was sitting next to
scoffed and said stupid after our first question. She was probably my first
question. Yeah, I actually
what was do you remember it was not does. Oh, I remember what it was. It
won't make any sense because nobody's seen the play, so it doesn't matter. Go
see the play. It's very good thing. It probably sold that lady was probably
chilling dude. She's probably moaning, one jilling you ever heard. She called
She called her vagina stupid?
Yeah, she was calling herself, she was dirty talking herself in the middle of the chair,
giggling because we were on stage, and moaning, and...
Stupid, stupid, stupid.
That'd be kind of cool. Has anybody got in trouble...
Cool?
If a fucking hot old milf was gilling in the audience?
And calling herself stupid? You'd feel bad.
Why would I feel bad? She's getting a nut.
Hmm.
To me.
Okay, you're weird.
How's that weird?
You're a little weird.
How is that weird?
a little bit weird. If you're saying if a guy did it, it'd be okay, it'd be weird.
If anyone was jacking off and calling themselves stupid, it wouldn't be. I
don't think that's that crazy. It would be weird. It's been done. You witness
somebody, you witness somebody masturbating and they're going. I'm so
stupid, I'm so dumb. Oh, I'm a piece of crap and they're there in public one
because you're witnessing. I'm
would it be better if they're going? I'm awesome. If I'm the best
way, because that is a that is a psychopath sex criminal. The other one
is also a sex criminal, but they're ready to go to jail yeah. They want you
to say buddy. You have to stop doing that and they go okay yeah you're
right. They're remorseful. This other guy thinks he's God yeah, this thing
I'm awesome. He thinks he's in a time loop. Has there ever been a peewee
Herman at a play? No, yes, Lauren Bobert, oh yeah, oh she's she got she got she
did a two person Herman Yep at the play
P P. We we she did a P P. We Herman
Herman P P. We Herman Herman Herman Herman, she P, she did a P. She took her
man okay wait. I got her man. She took her is we P we out she P weed her man
yeah she
yeah exactly yeah, so yeah, I guess that it wasn't a play. What play was that at
Beetlejuice that's why I said until his beetle juiced. I thought he that was his
his face. He made booty. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
he didn't get he didn't get to not he nutted so hard his head shrank. He has
a
they kicked him out for he could not that's a bullshit. That's a man nut.
Let him know let him fucking let that boy nut let her not or him let him let
it off at Beetlejuice. You know what I'll say this about her. She is midi to me
really is it because of her political views, I have a hard time separating
women from their political views, so yeah, I think it is that okay.
Also, would you ever date like a Nazi woman?
If she was like really ugly, yeah, she was really ugly, say more things about
her, and she's a really ugly. Her hair is
she doesn't have hair. Her hair is milk white. She has she has green
She's green spots on her skin. Okay, they look like liver spots, but they're
actually from a different part of their stomach spots. Yeah, she's dressed a
new. It's a new type of she's dressed in a paper bag, a trader, a trader,
revealing. It's a big one. It's a trader Joe's bag from a giant trader Joe's
that's what's the sized up was the body like she has one tooth that's long and
and one tooth that's very yeah arms on the bottom toothpick arms in terms of
thinness and also no joint straight and straight arm arm body trapezoidal and i
know right now you're thinking either broad shoulders or broad hips but no
trapezoid on it like sideways yeah so tall on one side short on the other side
so one long leg that's very strong and one shorter leg that's made of wood so
so she balance does she balance out or she's always falling over. She's the
trap, standing like this. She has to hang on a rope yeah, so we have to bring so
she has two people who bring a rope everywhere. You know that do you know
the the thing that they use to realign baby's spines where they put it on
their head and they spin around. They have that she has that okay yeah dater
okay, but that's settled because
people would like shit is she like really loud about her political. She
can't speak. Oh well, then yeah, I don't care if she's silently she's she's
written five hundred. Are you going to say we're going to say it's we're going
to say it's like when people have like a dog that's got a wheelchair? No, but
I'm sick of that, too.
I'm sick of that. How many dogs do you see with wheelchair? I see you. How can
you be sick of that? How can you be sick of it? I saw there was a dog in my
neighborhood. Oh, wait, sorry. Do you have a woman in your life who sends you
these videos every fucking day? Because I do I don't see disabled animals from
here. You get pictures of dogs in wheelchairs, dogs in where they have the
back legs are replaced by wheels. I got them chopped off. You get videos of
those every day pretty often. Okay, this is your wife wants to do that to fill.
Here's what I don't like with dogs. She wants to take Phil's back. I'm done.
I'm done with the three legged dog. Don't show me this dog anymore. I don't
want to see this dog and everybody is and nobody's paying attention to my dog
because they're so obsessed with this fucking dog that has three legs. You're
My dog is better than the three-legged dog.
Your dog bite is not better than the three-legged dog.
It is better than the three-legged dog.
Your dog bited Cameron.
Your dog bited me all over my whole body.
That's fine.
I trained him to do that.
I don't care that much about it.
I trained him to attack you.
Here's the other thing I'm done with dogs.
You don't like Phil?
I don't fuck with him anymore.
That's fine.
We fell out.
You fell out?
He's still rocking with me.
Was it money?
No, it was his barking.
It was too loud.
It hurt your ears?
No, but it startled me a couple of times.
Oh, I'm sorry about that.
hurtled me a couple times. Oh, I'm sorry about that. I'm also done with dogs that
have two different colors of eyes. Border collies. I don't give a fuck and
people who have that to heterochromia is out for 2024. Get a contact. I'm
throwing that shit away. Make your eyes match. I don't want to see two different
colors of eyes and then I'm trying to pick which one to look at. I'm honestly
done with any color of eye that's stranger or catches your eye or
interesting in any way. Enough of the purple. Even a color, even a blue that is
too pale, very bright, brown that has too many flecks of green. When the sun
shines into a hazel, a hazel that's too hazel, it needs to all be muted and
gray, gray eyes, brown eyes. No, just gray, just just as gray as what I'm
nothing, just nothing too crazy with the eye color, but especially these two
different colors of eyes. I'm sick of that shit and no hair too long or short.
Yep, have a perfect length, have it in between. Yeah, well, except for me.
Well, you don't have any. Yeah, you not that it's too short. I do have hair.
Well, you don't just don't have it. I don't grow it out. Yeah, you have it
doesn't grow. It doesn't have hair on my head. It does. It's not on your head.
I have hair in your bathroom drain. Yeah, because I shave it off
into my drain.
Right. So the play we did the we did the Q and a last night for the play and
also last night was the drop of the release of junior associate.
We were all in short film, short film done by the home planet guy.
And you may have heard a song at the end of the movie.
And I just want to say right now that was not the first song
that was supposed to be in it.
They went behind my back and they changed the song.
I actually wrote a song for the end of the movie and it was not used
like a credit song, like a song in the credits.
Yes. Do you want to show it?
Yes, I would like to. Julio, can you pull this up? I sent it to you earlier.
There is a... This is my... This was supposed to be the song at the end of the
movie. Why didn't they use it? And Joe and Alex, if you're listening,
what the hell? Why the hell didn't... This is not it. You're opening up
AO Technology again. It's a file. You're opening up me singing AO Technology.
Don't play this. Don't play this. Well, maybe mute this and then play
the song under it. No, I think you can just probably play the song.
Okay.
Yep. So there's a play button.
All right. So this is your
song.
was a purple fish inside of Alex's suitcase when there was supposed to be a bunch of papers
and documents.
Then Alex and Patrick, they get a call from Caleb from the phone in the house.
The house has a phone on the wall and then they go to the parking lot where they meet
Caleb and Caleb shoots at them and then Caleb goes to his uncle and he meets his, I think
it's actually his grandpa, then he meets his grandpa at the restaurant and his grandpa's
He's disappointed, then he tells him about New York.
And then from New York they go to back to the restaurant where he is on roller skates.
And when he's on the roller skates, he sees Alex and Patrick.
And then he sees them, and then they see the owner of the restaurant.
That is Caleb's grandpa.
Remember, that's Caleb's grandpa, 'cause it comes up later in the movie.
Then the movie ends, and it is, they end up eating fish.
and they have a good time in the end of the movie.
So that was the original. I am getting men in black Adams family, deep blue sea
vibes from this heavy. Yeah, it was supposed to be. It was supposed to be
that song at the end of junior associate. This has all the traits to me of a good
credit song, which is that if you just listen to the song, you don't have to
watch the movie exactly and I get everything you need. What I would have
I liked from you as some kind of spoiler alert type of thing. Maybe that was the
entire movie. I don't think it's... There's some stuff I didn't say. It says
everything. You said everything. I left out a few things, left out a few
details. Okay, so that's why people are watching movies. Oh, I can't wait to see
the details in this movie. Yeah, people... If you're a cinephile, you love
details in movies. I guess that is true. Yeah. I guess that is true. So, I left
out some details so that cinephiles could watch. This is a song that's not
certainly great for cine files, but it's also great for audio files. So I just
want to say about this song, it's for files of all types. Yep,
blank a file, you know, you'll like this song. A file. And it was made by a
blank a file. A file. Exactly. An audio file. Well, come on, it's a mix of
files. All types of files. A file, probably some other ones. No. Yeah. No,
no, no. But they did use this song and they made it, they used some song, it
just some guy saying purple, purple fish, some fucking guy, some guy. I don't know
it is bullshit. Why? Yeah. Why did they use my song or at least the Patrick cut?
Really? Yes, that's a good idea. We should black and white five hours long.
We should get a recut of the movie. Five hours long, black and white. Yeah, the
ending song has changed. Let me get into that editing booth. Yeah, let me turn
those knobs. I want to splice film. This is what I want to be doing. I don't want
to be in the movie. Even I just want to be I don't want to be in it anymore,
deciding which shots go into this shit and making sure that there's cameos from
everybody that I like. And let me tell you what, Cameron, if I was in charge of
this movie, right, we would have seen the front of your fucking head. Thank you.
Yeah, the back of your head is not enough, bro. We will show the back of my
head doesn't look good. The back of your head looks like shit. It's a bad and I
said that on set. I said this head looks like fucking shit. Can we get? That's
why they changed it. Can we have him eating at the restaurant backwards so
that we can at least see the front and not even because I like the front all
that right. No, I'm not saying I'm not saying the front of my head is that
great, but the back really is the worst part of you know what I would love.
There's nothing to see it's completely nothing. There's nothing loved in that
moment right before they cut to us
two hours. My dinner with Andre style you and Alan talking. Oh my God, or
without you guys, I mean dinner without no idea how deep we got. Oh, what do
you guys get on? I know mostly talked
well. I can't was the extra that Cameron sat next to who then did our focus
group episode. We really like we were fast friends.
We talked about my engagement to be married. Is he engaged? I didn't learn
any facts about him at all. That is you were talking about
yourself. He basically did not even really answer many questions or volunteer
much information
and more. Most of the conversation was silence, but he did enter a top ten in
your life? He was it was very fun and it was kind of
it was me and him and and Sean Bay and Sam and we were all sitting and
we all kind of were having the conversation with him and we all thought
that he was great. And he really was fine. You know when you feel when
you can kind of feel that somebody in a friend group is destined for greatness.
Yes, yes, he was kind of holding court over all y'all.
And he doesn't need to share that much about his life. Yeah, a silent but
strong tie. Yeah, he's kind of an outlaw and one of the and if you go back and
watch junior associate again, you pay close attention to him. One of the goats
when it comes to mannerisms for a dinner conversation. Yes, I mean he's doing
this.
Well, he's thrown in some of these. What's that? What is this? I don't know.
You'd have to ask him. I don't think I've ever been in a conversation at a
restaurant. Well, I've done this with my hands. Well, he's showing off different
He was showing you a spec?
He was showing you a thing. I mean, I don't know, understand what you have to just watch it and see.
Okay. I haven't watched it.
I want to see my dinner with Alan so bad. I need to see my dinner with Alan.
I don't think that you... I honestly can't imagine you having a one-on-one dinner with somebody.
Me? I have one-on-one dinners constantly.
With who?
My girlfriend.
But girlfriends, you sit there, you look at your phone, that's easy.
I mean, my dinner with Andre style, let's talk about life.
I've done it before with some people.
You've gone deep?
I think it's mostly, it's not dinners, it's mostly lunch.
You have a luncher type of vibe.
I get lunch, but I don't think dinner.
The kind of conversations you have over a lunch are very different from a dinner style
conversation.
Dinner is when you're allowed to drink wine.
So the wine comes out, the wine is pouring out of the sheepskin.
and you just I mean anything is on the table at a dinner conversation. Oh yeah,
I'll talk about it. O's steak well, besides the food, even asparagus spare
besides the food, Sam well, not the lemon, not just like candles and all
that kind of lemon, lemon, lemon, you don't eat lemon at dinner. No, you
lemon on you put lemon on stuff. I call lemon limb. Well, that you call lime
must be a regional thing. Okay,
really
You call lime, lye? You're not even saving a syllable there.
What about salt?
Sal.
You call it s...
Pepper is pep?
Pep.
Okay.
Okay, that one makes sense. I've heard pep before.
I've heard pep. I've heard pep.
What do you call ketchup?
Chup.
Chup is good.
I like chup.
Chup is very good.
What do you call mayonnaise?
Mayo.
He came up with that one.
That's universal.
Oh yeah.
That is universal.
What do you call mustard?
Yeah.
Don't say it.
I know.
I know what you're going for.
I actually call it empty
two syllables. Okay, all right, you'll pass the empty. What do you would you
call sauerkraut? Oh, that's tough, because I can't I can't actually our
because that's what I call sour. It's actually easy. It's a crowd is a bad
word. No, it's not. If it's a bad word, I don't know. I thought kraut meant
German. Yeah, isn't that bad? It's not bad. I don't think so. They have kraut
raw. I guess what I'm thinking of is that they would just is that in all the
war movies. They call them krauts and I mean, they're the bad guys in those
movies. It's true, but it still sounds like a rude word. They should just suck
it. Does it just mean I think you can call germans whatever I always
assumed it was that ending. I mean, I'm not either, but but I mean, I was just
saying, I think you're do you think enough time has passed though that
they're like that it's like all right, we've had our fun with germans yeah.
I think you're saying it's time to forgive and forget the hall. No, no, no,
no again. He's walked into a confusion. It is a confusion situation, but you
think
that was fully, but do you think enough time has passed
not to forgive and forget, but to stop calling the crowd time has passed is a
crazy thing to say not even a hundred years man. All right, well, once we hit
the a hundred years, I guess we can stop calling them crowds and stuff
and stuff.
I mean to stop, we can keep I guess
that whole thing, you call them Nazis or the I don't call German people Nazi. I
knew that they're rude. I call bisexual cashier's. I want to I call people who
does like my videos on line Nazis and techno yeah. I hate that techno crap.
You like it. What are you talking about techno sex? You need techno at the gym?
No, I don't yeah. You do I did a here that's I did a fully no techno work out
that is not German style. That's not a yeah. That's a talion that's trance and
hero dance. That is Italian. They did not get any heat at all for World War II. You don't
see anyone making fun of Italians for that. Italians. That's because they... They kind
of fucked up their whole government. I don't think the people who were in Italy even knew
that they were in a war. Yeah. That's a good point. They were just fucking bumbling around
walking into each other. They were just fighting over pizza stuff. The funniest one is Japan
because people got pretty mad at them of course, but they kind of just roll with it. It's so
so far you're watching an anime from the two thousands and they'll be dressing up
as Nazis in it. Yeah, I started playing Persona three and everybody's got a big
red armband and they're just, they look like full Nazis style swastika. Japan has
a very interesting, very interesting ideas about World War Two still is very
funny. Do you think there's a guy that can kind of just get away with it?
Because people are farther away, because we're like, oh, they don't understand.
Yeah. Do you think there's a guy on one of those islands that still thinks the
wars happening, probably not. Yeah, I think the last guy was there, the guy
like the last guy that didn't know the war ended probably on an island. Yeah,
no, no, no. When do you think? Oh, what do you think? People were like a chill
dude. Imagine I don't know what's the latest like. Do you think like maybe
like one thousand nine hundred and eighty one there's still a guy there
and then they come over and they're like isn't there a famous case of this?
Look at this. This is called Donkey Kong. Did that ever actually happen or is
that's something that for a long period of time, though, besides just being like
the 50s.
Was it the 50s?
Yeah.
Was it the 50s where all that they were like, "Hey, we got black and white TV now"?
Imagine us three, we get trapped on a stranded island.
A stranded island.
And we're sitting there and we see a galleon coming across the horizon, and we start readying
our arms because we're thinking, "Is this guy going to be an SJW or is he going to be
be right based guy like us and then they show up and they say guys, the war on
woke is over. We lost you guys have been fighting this war on woke your
prisoners of war. Now yeah,
that would be a woke lost woke lost. So we woke never. I thought you were
saying
I thought you said we lost no woke law, then who then great say well, the more
interesting thing is they come by. They say the war on woke is over and woke one
and then you're like do first of all do I believe them yeah and second of all,
what the fuck do I do? I'm doing that's the more that's I mean that's a movie,
the banana to my head, pull that's a that's a novel. That's an eighteen
hundred's novel right there is that's a beautiful. You are now a prisoner of
prisoner of war, and we are going to we've all been prisoners of woke. You
were going to put you in a bra yeah coconut bra that we made on the island
exactly and there's going to be the Abu grade picture of us getting
electrified, but instead of a bag over our head, Cove, a nineteen mask in
ninety five.
Now it's not going to be that is going to be one of the cloth ones and it's
to say like wear a fucking wear a fucking mask, Nike or Nike, it's gonna be a Nike
branded mask. So that's a really scary kind of being a prisoner of war must be
very scary. It doesn't seem that bad. It depends on the war, but like when you're
a prisoner of especially, I guess what I want I'm thinking of is is when you're
not even like a soldier. I guys read this book about
history of whaling and I forgot which war it was, but like the whaling wars,
but you know people would just be out whaling like up in the Arctic and then
ship the whatever war was the other country would just come and capture them
all and like sink their ships and take them all as prisoner. It's like they're
working man chill out. I would switch sides yeah. They wouldn't let you I'd
make them feel bad for me. I do the I do the best cry ever from the video and
did you guys know really bad? They let me go. This is something insane that I
learned from the from the
from this book in the eighteen sixties they were using. They were using literal
miss exploding missiles to kill way.
They're used. They had like harpoons for a while and then they invented in
eighteen sixty. They literally had a like is like a giant like rifle that
shot out an exploding missile. They would shoot it into the whale and it
would go into the well to be on a delayed views. They would shoot in and
that would just explode. Just to shit eighteen sixties. Why were they doing
that to because it can't even get like the you can't even get the blubber or
anything or you can
are big. You you shoot the whale, you hold the plate out and it lands
perfectly on your okay well yeah, and then so there was another guy who was
trying to invent a shoulder mounted one and he could never do it and he blew his
entire hand off. Try to like conservative patriot. Have you seen that video?
Coolest thing is that video never seen that guy conservative patriot where he
fires an RPG and it burns his entire face. Oh my God, no awesome. He put it
on YouTube and it goes it's it's me. It's called like my RPG exploded my face
parenthesis slow motion and slow mo video of it burning his face. That's
insane. It's really, really bad, like a really bad burner. It's probably fine. I
think it was quite bad. Yeah, yeah, like it's not like like he doesn't look like
Indiana Jones opening up the Ark of the Covenant. Well, Indiana Jones or I'm
sorry, Nazis and Indiana Jones opening up the really look like that. When it
melts, if it was like plastic and wax, it was made of candle. Yeah, if you have
a candle face, yeah, I guess so, but if you have a normal skin, I think it would
probably just burn and curdle. Yeah, it would just flake away. Yeah, was it
doing that because of the Ark of the Covenant? Did it look like that or does
it do that? Because that's what a human face would look like if it was burned
the Ark. The Ark is the Ark. Okay, so it was a horror that we couldn't
understand right. Well, we under I mean Spielberg or you're asking if the arc
physically burned their face or if it was super natural. If it was super, it
wasn't super natural at all. Okay, it was a big fire. Oh yeah, and it just
burned them for no reason. Oh all right. Well, there was a reason. There's a
laser beam. Is there anybody currently on the search for
the great cup, the holy grail? Yeah, probably I bet there is. I mean, I think
it's also one of the I bet it's also one of those things where, if you look it up,
I bet that, like
you know, twelve to fifteen archaeologists have been like we found the
grail that the Holy Grail was based on. Yes, fuck that fuck that right. I want
to see I want an extra arm. Yeah, this is the shit I want. What did the Holy
Grail do you drink from it and you become? I think it's eternal life. I
I believe it's eternal life. The when we when I was a kid, a big news story
broken my church that they had found Noah's Ark. Oh wow in laid into a
that's pretty incredible in somewhere in the Middle East and
guys, it turns out it's not true. Yeah, yeah, I know what he probably did was
took all the pieces of the Ark and made like his own like mansion. The Ark
wasn't even that big. It was like yeah, I know, but you can still make us pretty
sizable house. What's a piece of that? It was some cubits. That's the
you know, like a cubit is a cubit is your is your elbow to the tip of your
middle finger. So it's a unit of measurement is different based on who
is so maybe no one that's a big able. Yeah, he could yeah. So how big you
said the arc was a cubit? No, it was quite some of it. It was quite some
cubits, but it wasn't so many that you think you could fit every animal on
this motherfucker, but I had you're supposed to kind of understand the
spirit of the rather follow the spirit of the story rather than the letter of
it. It's not literally that there was two animals. There's probably one of
each animal. Okay, so you are a heretic,
so you believe your believe the love this is the I believe this is this. Yes,
you said my beliefs exactly. I believe this is this. I think that God was
in the sky. No man, you're not supposed to read it and go. I literally took
seven days to
to create one. You're probably what you're supposed to read and be like it
probably took like six to eight. I do remember one of the five, one of the
early atheistic owns I had on my mom,
which there were many of was oh yeah, God created in seven days. Interesting,
because he didn't make the sun until day two or three, which the sun is how you
determine the day. So tell me how many fucking days that was you fucking bitch.
Well, he made the son to correspond to the nine years old. Did she say that
back to you?
No, I think she told me to go to my room, which is how moms moms should be on
every debate stage for every presidential debate. They'd win every
time.
Why do you want to raise that? Go to your room, go to your room right now, go
to your room,
what
go go three to go to your room is so funny. It's so funny to send a what
did you see your fucking sorry? I used to go to my room all the time. I know
it's just very it's really funny. It's not even it's completely it's just
something that's just like I just can't do this right now. I don't want you here.
I wish I didn't have a t right now. Punishment, but I don't want to see
you're here. I can't stand looking at my child. Just go to your room, like
go away, go like go to your room and don't come out. Yeah, just go go to your
room. I never got to go to your room. I just got go away. I feel like go away is
hard. You didn't have a room. Oh yeah, damn I did have a room, but I shared it
my two brothers, so it was not mine. Oh yeah, I'll go hang out with my brothers
and fucking think about football with them. Yeah, what a punishment. Yeah, I'll
go to my room where the PlayStation One is. Yeah, stupid. No, I would go to my
room and I had a chair I would masturbate in. In the chair? Yeah. Does it change it?
What kind of chair was it? It was one of these big circle ones. Oh. And I'd go in
there. What, like an armchair? You would wipe it on the chair? Hell no.
Treat it like gym equipment. It was a big leather chair. You'd fucking finish
and just get a wipe down for the next person.
No, it was one of the, what do they call, I don't know what those are called.
They're like the clamshell chairs. Yeah, it's a loveseat, right? No, not a loveseat.
It was like a crappy, it was a... It was a loveseat, but you got it in a circle?
It's not a full circle. It was just like a,
I don't know how to describe this. I don't understand. I'm not so good with
language, but it was like a,
it was like me doing this, and if you sat on it...
I guess I can imagine maybe. Not really, but I'll give it to you. So it was a chair
that was shaped like a hand.
No, I'm moving on from the
I'd like to move on to the, but it wasn't cushioned. It was cushion. Oh yeah,
but it was one. It sounded like it wasn't. It was a cushion that sat on
top of it. It wasn't like made out of cushions like couches. It was plastic.
It was wood or bamboo or something that bamboo is wood. What's that called
wicker wicker?
You're jacking off in a wicker chair. I'm old school baby. That's I'm old
school. There's no way your mom didn't know there's no way your mom didn't
hear
like all moms always know that their kids are jacking. Dude, that is the
biggest terrifier of getting a kid. Yeah, is there gonna jay know if it's
way too early? That's bad if it's way too late. Yeah. If your son is going to
college the next day, you hear him jack up. You hear him in the bathroom. I
guess
yeah, I guess what would happen is you're kind of like
that's bad. Well, you are
I made butter. I made boogers at the front. You would be kind of surprised
because you would think he you know he would be going through the ages,
thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen, and you never kind of you never catch him
or notice any signs that he is jacking off and you think oh well great. I
mean he's I guess he's just a very secretive kid. I always thought I was a
parent. I would know, but I guess I guess he's just a screet. That's good
for me. I mean, yeah, which great yeah and then eighteen rolls around eighteen
and he starts he's allowed to realize all what will you just realize all along you
thought he was being so conscientious and discreet. No, he just didn't know how
he's touched in the head. He didn't know how your son has been touched. Well,
what if what if your son was just such a you, you raised him so right that every
single rule he sees that web, that porno website and says you must be eighteen
plus to enter any porno websites to check off. I'm not going to use your brain to
think a different did you watch it first time you jacked off to do jack off to a
website. Yeah. Internet poisoned. I jacked off to a bath tub that I was in. That's what
you were supposed to do when you were a kid. If you want me to be honest, it was a DVD
that I stole when my uncle lived in my house. You fucked a DVD through the hole. I used to
think about that all the time. That's what I did. I saw the lady on the DVD and I said,
"Well, I'm just going to put it right through the hole in the center of the disc." No, my
My uncles, I had like all three of my uncles lived in my house at some point because they
needed a place to stay.
An addict porno DVD?
My uncle Kevin had the most porno in the house and he put it in storage in the basement and
we found it all and my older brother, he had a, it was a photographed version of the Kama
Sutra.
So it was like these artistic photos of like people fucking in different positions, you
can have that and my older brother stole it and then showed me that he hit it and
I got in trouble at a family cookout that we were having and like it was like
the there's the porch in the backyard and then our like the window from our
bedroom looking down. So I got sent to my room and I said, Oh yeah, you guys are
getting me in trouble. Well, Paul has this and I threw the book out the window
to get him in trouble as well. I was taking him down with me because he was
the one that got me sent to my room and I threw the comma sutra down and then
he ran upstairs and beat the shit out of me and then he got in the most trouble.
You just reminded me of a time when my mom was having her wedding rehearsal in
our backyard and I didn't want to be involved with it. So I went upstairs and
I opened up all the windows and I had some speakers and I played jizz in my
pants at like maximum volume and like ruined her
and that was probably most trouble I was ever in. But man, it was fun. I
avoided trouble completely for doing that because my mom, my mom said,
I'll deal with you later. And then they had to sit my brother down and be
like, you can't be, you can't be jacking off because the Lord does not want
you to do it. Really?
They said that and they also told us that we can't be looking up porno on the
computer because one the Lord and to every website that as porno on it has a
virus. That's still true. I think yeah, that is I still still true. If it's not
one of the big three, then I've told the fake taxing on here. It's how your dad
was watching fake taxi all day. My dad was watching fake taxi off the website.
He's trying to call one. He was off. He was off the website, watching the
trailers to calling one of the like cab services and being like yeah and send me
to go. I need to go to the airport tomorrow morning at like five thirty
am. See you then. Could you send me the fake?
Oh, by the way,
send me the fake text and I want to do and I only need five minutes when you
wake up to go to the airport at four AM. You have like an early flight. You like
yellow cab you get in. Oh Fuck, it's a
let's get this over with come here.
I'm in a fucking run. Did they ever do a fake ambulance where someone's in a neck
brace and getting their butt fucked? Eric, I did really yep. I remember that
wasn't an Eric. I was an Eric Andre one. Remember watching that being like Jesus
because that was the one where he was that's one of the most of the Eric Andre
show completely left my mind. I can't even remember a single episode of it.
come on craft this one or whatever upset me so much. Well, I guess you're right
this upset, but I mean the pranks this upset me so much because it's he's like
the it's the one where the person it's like a passed out woman, like in a
getting loaded into an ambulance and he starts fucking her.
Nice
so I saw an amazing. I saw that in real life. I would kill myself. I try to kill
him and then I would kill my I saw an amazing post today. I opened up reddit to
look at the Ridgewood subreddit, which I'm a
really good one from it that I showed you. I have I love this subreddit. I
open up reddit and it says recommended post and it's a post on the Eric Andre
subreddit and it said is this show real?
That was a god damn. I wish I thought of that.
I'm going to send you a pic that you have to show. I do love the Ridgewood
subreddit because it's mostly just neighborhood. If you have if you live
in a neighborhood that has a subreddit, it's incredibly recommend or a
neighborhood or a better than next door for sure, because it's go on this
website, go on. Well, it's all it's all search your town who are like
they're all just it's either people who are who are posting like what the hell
happened to this restaurant? Yeah, or people who are like anybody noticed that
like it's just the most inconsequential. Anybody noticed that there was a bug?
Yeah, the other day, what the hell is that about? Has someone noticed more
at this our slash Ridgewood post that I painted a tribute to the Grand
View right. Oh my God. Wow. We need to buy this from this person.
We need to buy this.
Wow. We used to go there all the time. This is kind of right in
between, I would say,
earnestly trying to paint something and painting something shitty on purpose,
so you know that it was earnest. Yeah, it's not trying to be funny
enough, it feels like. The Grand View Rite Aid is closed. I know.
so that's why that's why that's what the tribute is yeah. This trip we need to
buy that paint. If you listen to the show and you made that painting, we will
give you twenty dollars. Oh wow, they even they looked it up off Google. Oh my
God, that was that's how we go put the side by side of the right and the
painting. If you saw a drink, look at that, I literally looked up that it's
got the same tree. If you saw a tree is only there in the show from May
2023 to August 2023, nine times out of ten, it was purchased from that rated
not for me. It was a little far. Not me either. Probably a little far. I guess
closer to I don't really I don't like right. I didn't like that. I just like
that right. It because nobody went to it and it's on the way from my house to
wherever I ride it in Walgreens. These for these chain pharmacies, I don't like
them because I always feel like I'm being accused of stealing. Yeah, the I and I
don't like to have a security guard yeah and if you're going to have a security
guard, I think that you should have to I would feel better if they checked my
receipt yeah, because I was saying I'm going to walk out and they're going to
be. I feel the way yeah, I totally agree. I will say, though I have any if I like
a if I'm got if I'm buying over the counter medicine or like so if I
anything that I need to go to a place like that for I can't ever. I feel a
thousand times less comfortable and like a small like bodega style one just
because I don't know. I just grew up going to CVS all the time. I think
they have the wrong medicine. I just well, I just yeah, I'm always like only
CVS is going to have what I need. Yeah, yeah, I it took me a while to get
used to going to a right at or a Walgreens. I went to brand loyal. There's
there's one there's a pharmacy closer to my apartment and I went to it and I
needed the pain medication for my my wisdom tooth surgery. Yeah, and the guy
was like
listen, that's on back order. I won't have twelve until Monday.
like can I just give you six and then you can ask the doctor to send me
another prescription, and I was like what you haggled with a pharmacist. I
well, I got that's always what it is yeah yeah, you're like do you have do
you have this do you have do you have zyrtec and they're like no, we have
our flax yeah. I don't want our it's also the same color. We have our flax.
It's the same color and it's a little weaker and it costs seven hundred
Yeah, with insurance.
Alright, that sounds good to me.
Yeah, I'll take it. I'll take Zarflex.
I haven't taken prescription medication in a very long time.
I was on Adderall for a little bit, then I stopped because it was making me crazy.
You know I want to take one of these, what are they called?
The antibiotic pack?
Where you have to take every single one every day?
Oh yeah.
The antibiotic advent calendar?
If you have the advent calendar version, it means that the pharmacist or doctor thinks that you have a brain of a 12 year old.
Okay, well, I haven't taken it in years. Yeah, but because antibiotics did you
guys know this antibiotics are good or bad and I can't remember which type
it's bad not for you, but it's bad in the grand scheme of things because the
grand scheme. Well, the more antibiotics that people take the more that
viruses and stuff adapts to them. You know, it was fine. I know it's take
them the less that they're come up with a new biotic as a species. I was taking
when I got the wisdom tooth out again, I was taking antibiotics and then I was
eating yogurt because there was a stitch in my mouth, but the yogurt I was eating
was probiotic. Right, so you think maybe it cancelled out? I think that maybe my
mouth is infected. Why the damn antibiotics so big? The pills, they're
gigantic. I have a hard time swallowing those. It might as well fill up my butt.
The biotics you're getting, the biotics you're getting rid of. My mom put it in
my ass. The bacterias,
a suppository? Yeah, when I was like kind of too old to
I probably could have done it myself, but my mom was like, "You're going to mess
it up. I'll put it in your ass." I was like nine years old,
and I will never forget that. I was sitting on the bed sideways,
and I was sitting there thinking like, "I think that I'm ten and I could
do this myself."
And she was like, "That wasn't so bad, right?" And I just ran away.
And I don't, it only, it wasn't, it was like one pill that she had put
up there. It might have been a tracking device. Yeah, I think it was a
right? You got fat bastard. That's the thing that sucks about having babies is
you have to do that kind of tracking device. It's all this disgusting stuff.
When I was a kid there, I don't know if it was flu shot or some other type of
vaccine where they were like,
"Oh, you can either get, like, the shot or you can get, like,
mist." A hamburger.
Like some kind of, like, you breathe it in, right? And I was still young enough
that I was like, "I really didn't want to get a shot." And it was just scary.
And I was like, "Okay, I want to get the mist. I don't want to get the shot."
and they were like, "Oh, you can't get the mist because you have asthma,
so you can't have it. You have to get the shot." And ever since then,
I always feel like there's gonna be some scenario where, yeah, they're gonna
be like, "Okay, you can either take... You can get the pill or you can
get the suppository." And I'll be like, "Okay, please, I can have the
pill." And they're gonna be like, "You can't. Actually, there's something
wrong with your mouth and you can't have it." They see you turn around
for one second, "You gotta take the suppository," and we have to do
an on site application. How is a suppository better than just taking it
by the mouth. It's a mucous membrane in your asshole. Oh yeah, it's the same
reason. I imagine it's the same reason that if you pour a beer up your butt,
you get drunker. Oh, and you can put cocaine in your ass. Yeah, okay,
'cause what's his name? Did that who? Scott Storch? Oh,
never heard about that. No, that's a different. That was way far. It's way
farther away from Steveo than I got. Steveo Scott Storch used to blow.
That's what he is now. The damn vegan cocaine up Mariah Carey's asshole.
yeah, it's called a Miami blizzard. You never heard about this. No, why do you
do it to Mariah Carey? She was just a very nice your assholes out
walking around with her ass out, and he shot it like a dart like Ace Ventura
directly
and
yeah, Kobe
Kobe.
Yeah, the
you can do all sorts of drugs in your ass. I don't know about it, but isn't
there's always a little bit of poop in your butt. Maybe you're what I imagine
and there's always a little bit of poop. You don't finger your ass with the
white to try to clear out at least like a like a you know you you've said this
so many times and every single time yeah, I don't say no do that, then you
have nasty asses whiteys. I don't really care.
I don't care if you're nasty ass on the inside. No, it's sides of part where
people might have access soon. No one is having access anytime soon. You don't
know that I don't know that you could get in trouble, then that's on them. If
they if they find out it's dirty in there, but first of all, I don't want
them in there. It's a deterrent, but you can get people. You can get yourself out
of trouble. I keep I keep it a little dirty like a poison dart frog. Exactly
it's like a biologic. There's a reason that there's a biological reason that
shit stays inside your butt, even when you wipe yeah to get it out.
What yeah it's like power washing the reason it stays inside is to get it out
yeah, so you can get so you have so you can get a satisfaction. I understand
satisfying. I cleaned out one finger one like nail
as I am like up to your nail. You have a coke nail for poop. No, it's a normal.
My nails are all short, but you just go to the nail bed.
You create a glove of baby white. So I've never he's Julio's your flesh and
baby wipes in your apartment. Now here's my question. I that's another thing.
Let me flush that not in this city. Fuck all that. Maybe maybe some new style
plumbing and listen, I'll pay the fine in some I'll pay the fine, but I'm let me
let know that's terrible for plumbing. I don't give a my brother's a plumber. He
told me how bad it is. I hope he fucking not the
not the plumber
and don't throw away. I don't care. The plumbing is the most important part of
your house, because I've seen those videos. The part of your house where the
videos where people get their plumbing backs up and then their toilet starts
shit doing shit, but they let me tell you like it's like not my problem. I'm
I'm renting I'm flushing the wipes. I'm putting aerosol cans in the trash
flushing on batteries, olive oil directly
olive oil. When I'm done with it, my shit is literally seventy five percent
olive oil and that's going in the fucking pipes. Yeah, okay, what am I
supposed to do sift through and throw the olive oil? I'm pretty sure I'm
pretty sure I did that well yeah. So here's a question if we can't flush the
baby wipes yeah. What the hell am I supposed to do reach into the toilet and
grab the white covered in shit. Yeah, because the other option with a
flushable with the other option is throwing it out in the trash and I
don't know how often I clean the I don't know how often I empty the
bathroom. What if I put it in a nasty bullet and I believe don't do it.
Get my girlfriend does it
wait misogynist bala. You make your girlfriend throw away your shit. I
don't make her throw with the shit. You put the shit wipe in the trash. No,
I flush him
my man.
I'm just sick. No, no, I'm it's regular toilet paper. I don't like rules. I
don't like regulations and I'm gonna be watch my shit baby wipes in the toilet
regular wipe trash. I
put oil and grease down the sink. I put large chunks of food down the sink. I
or when I was living in Boston, I have we have the thing on our drain that has
little holes in it. So you try to try that away. I don't it's it's completely
attached on. I can't throw it away. I jam stuff through it. Oh yeah, yeah,
I put a chicken bone. Really yeah, no disposal. I don't have a disposal by
bone.
It just goes away. I it's gone. I'm never going to think about this fucking
bone again. I don't care what I'm saying man. I'm renting yeah. What's going to
get stuck sideways in the plum the plumbers? Oh, no water can't get by
water. You want me to feel bad for water? It's ninety percent of the earth
and my body. When I was living in Boston, I poured a hole. I had a
it was like a late crusade thing filled with
vegetable oil and I was deep frying something and I didn't know what to do
with the oil. I just poured it down the sink. Yeah, I do it whole like three
court thing. Well, it was probably it was probably one and a half quarts of
olive oil or vegetable oil straight down the drain. Yeah,
what am I going to do with it? But we had a disposal, so I think that if you
turn it on, it cuts up the yeah, I'm supposed to make an a only in your this
is a this is a tip for renters. If you have a garbage disposal, pour that oil
directly in your little bit of lemon juice. Yeah, a little bit of lemon juice.
I would turn the garbage disposal on. There goes a mayonnaise and that's a
really high speed thing because it's supposed to cut up chicken. Well, you
need an egg. You need to put one egg. Yeah, not with how fast this is going
to blend whatever. All you have to do is you just reach past the blades, put a
plug in under there, put in all your ingredients, flip the switch, blend it up.
He's been abbreviated and then you take a straw and you can either drink it
right out of the sink drain or you can do a little siphon action. You put your cup
on the ground long straw. When the plumber shows up, you open the door, you're
wearing a leather jacket. He's not going to fuck with you. No, you got a bunch of
chains all over
leather jacket with the chains. You're looking like Robert Halford. Do something
basically like Robert Kelly. I ate 4000 doughnuts right before I opened the door
powder all over my face. What the fuck is up plumber? Well, you're mad at me
because I made a I made a baby wipe mayonnaise.
I
fucking
you should have got a real job. I mean all you have to do to the plumber is say
it wasn't me. It was my neighbor. Yeah, I the guy before me. Yeah, I'm renting. I
don't know anything about this shit man. I'm renting. This was the person that
just make this face. I don't know shrug and you wide eyes. Oh or or make a
here's how you let him how you make them. Let you flush make the plumber laugh.
The plumber comes, he's doing a routine. He routine he's just trying to fix your
sink. You have a leaky faucet or something, and then he's leaving. He's
like, yeah, I'm finishing up. He said, oh, before you go, I have something for
you. I know I'm not supposed to throw these away. Giant bucket of all my
shitty baby wipes with all my diarrheas from a year. Yeah, I can't say here you
go. I know that you don't want me to flush these, so I figured here you go,
and here's all my oil, and here's also all my oil, my bacon grease and my bones
and many, many bones that I did not want to flush or yeah, you can make a stew
of these. Yeah, so go ahead, knock yourself out. Yeah, you're gonna knock
yourself out with the smell of these. What the smell of my apartment has been
bad because of the chloroforming the plumber. It's just shit. Yeah, stinky
duty.
Oh, you
three miles in the face. Terrible. There was a kid that was telling me about in
high school. This kid was telling me about jencom and how poop if you
ferment it is like it could get you high. And he told me in the same vein is
chloroform if you take it to your fingers and put it on your taint and you put it
up to your nose it can knock you out. I heard that too actually. That could have
might have done this might be a repeat story. That might be a repeat story. I smelled
pretty bad. After a hit session, throwing that ball on the ground. Oh yeah.
That's a good workout. I love that one. You hate it. I love it. He begs not to do it every time.
I beg not to do it every time, but then when I'm in the middle of it, the rush
of adrenaline, I guess, like throw a ball. Tell them about the workout that
he likes and what it looks like.
So we do dips on chest day and there's a machine that does yeah, it's the so
we're all doing the dips, the standing dip where you're just lifting your body
up. If you don't know exercising, yeah, you're lifting your body up with with
your arms and I did the scene. The dip is where you sit down and you hold two
the bars that extend behind you and you you do this same motion like this
and it completely looks. I would say pat only likes to see to dip. He doesn't
like the standing one do this. He won't do the sending one. He only does the
one working my way up to it and the it looks exactly like he's. I was saying he
only does the seated dip because it's genetic memory of being an Irish peasant
carrying a wheelbarrow full of potatoes across a bumpy road. I want to get a
video of it because it looks that even the posture you use for it is unlike
anybody I've ever seen. Use that yeah
a ride. Yeah, it's also it's a face while you do it, it's bumpy dirt road
with a wheelbarrow of
cabbage and then it's also it's also an Irish indentured servant in America,
like
carrying a rickshaw with the American times for the first millionaire in
America, the slave of
Rockefeller, I've done I've done research on my ancestry. No there. I
think some people on my mom's side came over from the potato famine. Yeah, so
there's no way that that is not a genetic memory. This I think you've
unlocked. Yeah, you needed to look up documents to find out that your Irish
heritage maybe had experience being peasants.
What do you mean by that
peasant race. Yeah, fully all three of us. It's okay. All right, we're going on
tour. Yeah,
with with world's biggest army. It's us home planet and Pierce Campion going to
be super fun. We're going to Boston. We're going to Atlanta. We're going to
Toronto. We are going to Philadelphia and we are going to did you say Chicago
Chicago and I'm serious guys. I said it last time and I feel like people didn't
take it to heart. Keep just keep just keep your eyes open, because you never
know
there could be more shows added and there will be a giant plane crash. It kills
hundreds and we will be on the plane and here are the tickets. Julio showing them
right now swag poop dot com slash shows. You can see all the beautiful poster of
us being targeted, beautiful poster of us targeted for death,
and you can have links to tickets to all these different shows. It's going to be
a huge blast. The plane is the blast that we all it's going to be a huge blast.
if you know what I mean.
- All right, thank you.
- But yeah.
- All right.
- Bye.
(static)
- I do love mustard.
- Me too.
- I like spicy mustard.
- I like different types of mustard as well.
- I like pretty much all.
- Mustard.
- Yellow, brown, pink.
- Oh, man.
- Oh, fucking, oh my God, I love mustard.
(laughing)
I'm a
so grab crazy.
I fucking love different kinds of mustard. I'm imagining hearing this
voice, hearing this voice saying you getting this, you had a call. I was
gonna say I wouldn't know when you pull up to the
my scenario is you imagine being a ketchup lover and yeah getting that
mustard.
My scenario is you pull up to the McDonald's, you pull up to the
McDonald's drive through, you say hey yeah, can I get
burger and I'll get some ketchup on it and you know it all get some mustard
too.
You have
yeah, okay, you want a big you want a big Mac yeah, mustard and some mustard
mustard.
This is the this is the cashier who's talking to you through the speaker and
and that's actually pretty funny. I guess I'm playing the guy in the
restaurant. Okay, cool you so just get ready for your big your big moment
because it's coming up again, but it was very funny for that to happen for
someone for you. Pull out you pull up to the to the drive through and you're
saying like yeah. I want a burger and then say oh yeah, I bet you do want a
burger on and then you pull it. They're like okay, next one. Don't you pull up
and it's just the guy you just there for the looking very stupid. You're like
sorry about that
the window. I forgot about this part of it. I'm new here. I forgot you were
going to see me. He's my first day on the job yeah, he's like
he ducks down really quick and then he throws the bag in the car like a
grenade. The restaurant is like
and then the guy in the restaurant is like
This is so much better than McDonald's in Paris.
[Laughter]
(Sonic the Hedgehog theme)