Super Bowl tomorrow. Yeah. How you guys preparing your bodies to play in this
game? I'm hitting myself a lot. I'm cutting myself thinking, thinking,
thinking will get you nowhere in this game. You got to start. You got to sell
fledgling. You think that man, that's what you say. But consider this. If
if that's the case, then how come none of these football players on the field ever
look completely gigantic like a body builder or like an orc? It's because they
have to put some points into intelligence, not just in the strengths.
Cameron, Cameron, Cameron, Cameron.
It depends on the position. It depends on the position. You have no clue. You
don't know anything about sports because you're the nerd side of sports. You
probably watch Moneyball and you say, 'Oh, that's my favourite athlete, the guy
with the pencil.' I don't watch Moneyball, first of all. You watch Moneyball all
the time. You definitely watch Moneyball at least five times in your life. I've
playing it three times twice with my dad and once on my nerd side of sports,
Mr. R slash basketball.
I like
so crazy what
that's because we're doing a joke at the beginning of the thing. You don't have
to bring personal stuff into it. I was just a guess. I guess okay. Well, what
do I know?
Wait, what do I know about you? We know things about Cameron. I got it. It's not
embarrassing to go on hard slash basketball. His tummy hurts all the time. Guys, my tummy
actually did hurt this morning because I had my first free junior frosty yesterday. I thought
I could handle the lactose, but it lactosed me out. No, no. Yeah, but it was worth it.
It was worth it. It was delicious. So you like the gift? I haven't had, I loved the
gift. I haven't had a full, I've been eating the lactate ice cream. Really? Or the lactose
first free ice cream and I thought I liked it. I got kind of brainwashed,
but then here the thing I like I have the junior for us. He literally instant
deprogramming yeah. I need it frosty. I had this experience. I've been drinking
fair life milk and then I had this and I've been like yeah, it's fine. You can
put it in smoothies and whatever isn't isn't on or you're you think of a light
life. No, I'm thinking of fair life. I drink it all the time. It's a you get
this. It's a milk made by Coca Cola. It comes in plastic. It's very good. It
comes in a certain type of square plastic. Yes, and I would say it's a
curvy, beautiful woman shape. Actually, now I think about it, is that kind of
shaped like a it shaped like a sexy
it's shaped like they're reusing a bottle from something else. You say
we ran out of
it. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
run of detergents. Yeah, but you said curvy beautiful and I thought that you
I'm talking about that beard, beautiful purple cow that's on the milk. You know
it's a bottle. I've always wanted to fuck palm wonderful. Don't know what that is
the pomegranate juice. Yeah, it looks like to it looks like to boobs or two
balls, but I thought boobs until today and when I thought boobs, I wanted to
have sex with that bottle.
The so I thought fair life milk. This is fine and dandy whatever it says like on
the thing it says like ultra processed, but it's like it's a good thing right
and then I had I made a bolognese. It's hard to make ultra sound like a bad
thing. That's right. I always think I'm like, oh, okay, and let's say ultra bad.
Yeah, even then I'm like, oh, ultra, ultra, cool, ultra, for sure,
acrid
yeah,
I would eat that, too, and you need an ultra, but that's what I'm saying.
Ultra putrid, ultra putrid, wow, ultra putrid, say that five times fast. It's
hard. If there's two bottles next to each other at the at the at the at the
store and it's one of them labeled putrid and one of them ultra putrid.
I'm going for ultra yeah, if you have it, yeah, it's no contest. If you're going
if you're trying to make somebody sick, you want the ultra putrid. I putrid I
had a glass of whole milk because I had to use whole milk for this bolognese
dude. Whole milk is amazing. Oh yeah, I forgot how good whole milk is dude. What
was that? Why was everyone saying that two percent milk is the best because
it's the classic yeah, this is the mom mill yeah. This is what comes out of
as well. What even is the percent? Of breast milk? A hundred. A hundred
percent. No, of milk. Why is it called percent? Because it's milk, two percent
fat. Oh. So they take out the whole milk is like... Whole. Four or five percent
fat. No, a hundred percent. That's a hundred percent fat. Okay. It's butter.
Yeah. So they take out the butter from the milk. Milk can make, like,
ten things. Yeah. Milk is like the Swiss Army knife of the cows. But apparently
people are now allergic to milk, lactose intolerance, which come, but only
certain populations are like and tolerant, because it depends on where I
think it's also here's. The thing also is that it fully is
you. I mean you can get over it. You can't you become like if you're not
eating enough lactose, your body reverts to being lactose intolerant and then the
more you eat, the more you build up. I think you can get over any other. I'm
aiming to get over my lactose intolerance with which I've always
literally with frosty because I've always been a little lactose intolerant,
not enough that it ever affected my life in any way. But then my fiancé is more lactose
intolerant than me, so we always get dairy-free stuff. So I have a lot less dairy, so then
I've become more lactose intolerant lately. It's time to fight back.
I don't think I could be. If I was lactose intolerant, that would ruin so much for me.
There's stuff you can still have. You can still have some cheeses.
No, I know. Just like in terms of the—I would have to pull out the fucking index card
of allergies at restaurants if I was also—
It's not an allergy, though.
No, but imagine—
you make your stomach up. You've you've smelled my farts in the van when we were
on tour. I tell people imagine the van tell people I've smelled your farts. I
don't want people knowing that she smelled my fart on people to tell people.
I buried my face and you buried your face in my by disguise myself as like
doesn't I would fart in the seat and then I would get out at a go. I think I
left something in the car.
I've got lactose intolerance is not an allergy. It's the same level of like a
food issue where it's like oh, I can't eat
live hamburgers in a row because it will make my stomach upset. Noah said the
craziest thing to me last night. He said, "Yeah, dude, my spice intolerance is so
low. I went to Popeye's and in five minutes I ate two spicy chicken sandwiches
and I was like sweating walking out of there." I was like, "Yeah, you ate two
fucking fried chicken sandwiches in five minutes? That had nothing to do with the
spice. That's just a hog's behaviour." That's 'cause you put your body into
challenge mode. Yeah, you said, "I'm man, I'm gonna verse this food in the middle
the Popeye's at a three PM type of time. I miss doing walk around. I miss doing
man versus food challenges by myself. When did, when's the last man versus food
you did? Not like man. They should reboot this show with you, because that guy's,
what was that guy's whole problem? He cared about his body. Yeah. This dude,
you'll go forever. I have acid reflux currently, just because. You'll go
forever. Yeah, I'll just. You'll never pussy out like Adam. No, no, no. What was
it? Adam something? Adam Rich. Adam Rich. Rich. Fuck you, Adam Rich. Yeah, he
definitely got rich after that show. The food was made a lot of money. That's a
good point. Adam first man. Yeah to do a show. It's true. He really heard his
word for man and also the first man in the Bible where it comes from. Yeah,
wasn't the first man God. No, he was not a man. God is a corporeal. Do you say
to me he's more than a man. Thank you. God has both parts and he fucks him and
that's how you made Adam and Eve.
the chair is a fight outside. There's not a fight outside. Oh, you think
everything is a fight or you wish there was another fight. Well, that's enough.
That's a okay. We're waiting for the bus. What that amount of Children is
constitutes a fight. What? What? Like after school, if that many kids are
going somewhere, this guy never had friends. Yeah, this guy doesn't for
doesn't ever walk about. You have no friends. You have no fucking friends.
You suck. Nobody wants to hang out with you after school. That's not true
because you fucking smell at school. I don't smell it's yeah. You smell after
school. You smell in regards. You smell fine during school, but then at the end
of school, you start smelling. I've seen you're a pencil chewer. I'm not a
pencil pusher. You're a pencil pusher as well. You work at the school. That's
why no one wants to hang out with you. You smell back to the janitor. You're
the kid. That's why I'm a janitor. That's my new job. They should have let
kids be janitors for X. I hung out with the janitor and they actually the janitor
should pick an apprentice every year. I agree. Just my friends can damn a kid to
the worst fully ever
and
they have to wear the full
jumpsuit to where you shall be. It should be like the Dalai Lama yeah,
where you pick a
new janitor when you'd pass on that is such a thing. That is such an
incredible idea for a young adult novel series. I became the janitor. It's
like I mean, okay, it doesn't have to be chills already. Basically, a Harry
Potter situation, but it doesn't have to be like it can be a school for like
really gifted magical abilities, X men or Harry Potter or something like that.
so I'm listening and one of the kids he has no powers. Yes, his power, but he
learns he is going to the school because he has to become the janitors of and it's
called learn
it's called the janitor's apprentice. He learns that his power is a resource
on this and cleanliness exactly to clean up. He cleans up after these all these
people with powers, they're careless and by the six about other people, yes, by
the book by the six book, they revealed to him like you thought you didn't have
your power, but you had a power all along your power was that you were so good at
cleaning rose. You were the greatest cleaner of all time, bro.
I have bad news, though this is community. No, it's not this happens to
childish gambino in community. He becomes the plumber. That's a plumber.
That's a different thing. You're kind of right. I guess God is community, but
this is on everything. This is better. This is a different idea. First of all,
I was about to get up and leave. First of all, it's high school yeah. Second of
should be high school or middle school. It has children with powers and stuff.
This could be like an X men, like an X men one shot. Yeah, okay, yeah, it's a
sky high school. It's a six issue, six issue X men run. Well, no, it's not
even that he doesn't know why he came. He knows he's knows why he came and he's
like ashamed of it. Like he doesn't see the value in it. Like he's like he's
one of an underclass, but he doesn't know it's only like one yeah, only like
point five percent of the human population in America have no powers and
they're called dirties, the dirties, that's a movie already chosen. There's a
movie called the dirties yeah by who matt johnson. Is that a british movie?
It's a movie about a school shooting. Oh, it's called the dirties yeah. It's
actually really really good. Well, if you understood you watch it, the
shitties that's a better name for the shitties shitties fuck the shitties, but
then what happens a flood of poop, dirt and a villain comes in dirt. So yeah,
well, that's just in the first book. Now that's like you know how in Harry
Potter it's like oh the first four books they're kind of fucking around at
school, the fifth stuff fifth book and on it gets real. They're fighting for
the fate of the world and to stop another global holocaust. They do stop
a holocaust or there were they
they don't stop it got to wonder where they were with the first one. It's
revealed that they zoom back. That's basically what happens in Harry Potter.
anyway. It took place in 1942. I think that happens in the Fantastic Beast
movies. I think those are set in the Holocaust. Really? And Dumbledore did
nothing. They are, yeah.
Grindelwald. They're set before. The Crimes of Grindelwald. Yeah. And they
set it there and they... Well, I didn't see the movies. I didn't see them
either. I can only assume what this crime is. I know. I saw the first two
in the theaters, and I think the angriest I've ever been leaving a movie
in my life was leaving the second Grindelwald movie. I think it was Crimes
of Grindelwald. I think I was just like that. My ex was a big Harry Potter fan.
Well, anyway, this the janitor's apprentice right, the first four books,
they're all it's all kind of just cleaning and cleaning really like like
the first one, it's like oh, maybe it's like we have to clean it. There was they
had prom and their solo cups everywhere and that's the big like climax, you know,
and then it gradually ramps up. It's like oh, a villain is coming. He becomes
friends with the jock because he cleans up the jocks party. Yes, and he's
gradually to understand it's starting to bridge the class divide between the
cities and the powerfuls, oh my, which is ninety nine point five percent of
the population has got the powerfuls. Well, so the cities are really small.
Well, there's barely any of them because it's I mean if there's too many of them,
they'll rise up yeah. Oh, so we may be a find out they're even being sterilized.
Oh my God, and that's why there's such a small portion of the population,
obviously, and so now the shitties have to clean the world of the powerfuls
kill every last power. That's that's kind of like they're doing that's when
we do kind of an i carly reboot type thing where it's like the series ends
and it comes back twenty years later, back twenty years later, exactly like i
carly twenty years and twenty years have passed since i carly for now it's for
adults and now the good guys do the holocaust.
Okay, yeah, this is a pretty good idea. I think
like
they're doing an i carly reboot, but it's for adults.
Yeah, and then someone asked them at comic on like so. Why did you decide to
do this reboot where it's the holocaust? Have you seen i carly? It was all
currently. It was all hinting towards this. It's all an i carly style show.
Yeah, I didn't see the new i carly. Did you that you were saying like like the
i carly reboot? Well, I didn't see that it could be like that. I carly reboot
because it's like zone of interest or
I didn't see zone of interest. I hear it's good, but it seems like to scary.
She's doing random dancing and you just hear one scream in the back.
Yeah, the
Carly studio was above. It was like on the upper floor of a building
or it's like in the same neighborhood as the move bombing. Yeah, some awful
thing that happened is happening right outside. I
they're just barely like you can hear it in the background. If you want to get
seventy million views on YouTube, you can make a creepy pasta about this right
now, where you edit this stuff happening outside of outside of the window of the
i carly studio zoom into it. You can literally make bank. Oh my God, yeah,
because there's like that's a free idea and we're not going to use it. We're
not going to do i carly in the holocaust. That's all you a lot of our
ideas that we have on this show are most of them. I think probably five percent
of them. We hold dear ninety five percent. You can open source reverse
that. No, I'm I'm very possessive. Everything I've ever said on this show.
It's mine. Okay, okay, well, then the five percent that are open source, you
are allowed to do whatever you want with them and that's one of them and then
but but the ninety five percent you can apply for a license. Yeah, we'll give
you a license. It's pretty cheap. Honestly, yeah, we don't have that many
good ideas, hot sodas and cold dogs that we can you can buy a license for that.
yeah, when you can have that one for free, okay, that's a but you are not
fucking licensing janitor's apprentice. No, this is getting written. This is a
book series. Okay, so it's ninety four percent, five percent and then one
percent of things that we are going to license and create
like janitor's apprentice where they should have a different name.
Why the shitters the it was the was the shitties and now it's the janitor's
apprentice janitor's apprentice is a good. That's the perfect. I guess the
janitor's apprentice is the name of the first book series and then the series
is called something else. What's the boy the boy's name shitly shitly shit,
shitly, shitly, piston, shitly, piston is shitly, piston, colon, the janitor's
appreciate right now. The first one is just called the janitor's apprentice. I
can visualize the cover. It's a mop leaning up in a closet, no like people on
the cover. The right class shadow, the
my crab. Why villain? There's no villains in the first one. It's just cleaning
okay, maybe a few villains
or maybe that's one of the superpower. No, it's the font. It's like it's like
kind of like a thin, like the kind of font you'd see on a scroll. You know the
pirate's apprentice and then as the of course three author names yeah down in
the and then it's got and then it's got a circle. It's got a seal of like it
won some type of a word like some fake young adult award, the duke, the
the
the podcast about list. They won the why a choice twenty four and yeah the cover
is the mop is in the closet and there's an open door with a with a beam or of
some light coming from outside the door and we see a
shadow of the of the so what's yeah silhouette shadow, but then the second
book and we make it so that the mop stick looks like his dong and that's a
Easter. We have to later there like did you guys know that this was actually an
Easter egg for adults. Yeah, that will pop up in a YouTube video called ten
Easter sexual Easter eggs in book covers. Why don't they do? Why is it they do
that with all the kids movies? They never do it. They sneak up. Why is it
you're never reading a kid's book and then it says book and then you keep
moving? Why is that or like a footnote like maybe like a tell me you didn't
read books as a kid without telling me you're doing a playboy trifold that's
like just like a between the thing like a number at the top, like a little foot
note and then you read the at the bottom of the page and said this is this is
only for adults and in parentheses and then just says penis penis sex. So tell
me you never read Captain Underpants before I read it. I did flip around
because that is all for adults. Yeah, yeah, because for kids and for kids it's
it's school superheroes, principals, et cetera, but then all these secrets are
hidden in there for adults underpants, professor poopy pants, toilet, toilet,
George, booger, monsters, George, a lot of around a lot of children named George.
yeah, I guess that's you ever see somebody on the street. You're
a little bit of a
type of thing. Yep,
the crop I used to skip right to the flip around me to
go to the flip around and then read from the flip and be like I
can't wait for that to show back up. Yeah, exactly. I can't wait
for that. Hey, go to your friends. Hey guys. I made this
they think you made this book. Yeah,
I don't name is Dave quickly. My name is Dave. Ikely, Ike,
Pilky Pilky man come on. That's your thing of pleakly. I am thinking of
pleakly who's pleakly from you don't know pleakly. Pleakly will also be doing a
crossover appearance.
I feel like a fucking douche bag. Who the hell is pleakly? You know pleakly
can make this is pick. Oh pleakly pleakly man, Mcdonald. If you're
listening, please, pleakly always dressing like a woman. He has but one
eye Cyclops
Cyclops that's what they call that if I saw a woman with one eye like this in
public, I would just I'd probably just shout and three fingers. If you saw a
woman with one eye, you'd shout at her.
That's what you said. Stop it.
I know, I know, I know you're in disguise. Yep. I know. Okay, please.
Clearly, I know you're an alien. Hello, please.
Anybody with one eye, you ever known anybody with one eye? No, my cousin had
one eye or my he's like my second cousin had one eye. So he got another one later.
No, I think he passed.
I'm sorry. Yeah, it's okay. He was much older than me and he lost his eye in a
motorcycle accident.
But he nobody
he wouldn't tell anybody that I had two family members who had one. I actually my
great grandpa had one eye from shooting a tree with another pirate gun and the BB
gun came back and took his eye. Your grandpa, I've been black. I'm from a long
a lineage of pirates. I've been deeply obsessed and with forming a connection
with my great great grandfather, Peter Fetter. How are we going to do this? I
have been, I listen to music and I look at a picture of him.
That's some cloud, whatever I'm listening to at the time, but I want to
meet him. Cloud Atlas. Do you want to see him? We have a Ouija board, don't we?
Did I show you one before? Show me that picture. Peter Fetter. Show me Peter
Fetter. Oh wait, we do have a Ouija board. Isn't that a great name? We do
have a Ouija board. Peter Fetter. It'd be better if it was Petter Fetter. Ouija
forward is like what I wanted to want him turned to a demon or something.
Yeah, it doesn't turn you into it. He's either a demon or he's not. You get you
get sucked up, but I could be a demon that pretend you're thinking of you.
Don't you think that me and him would sash so hard? Yeah, God, Danny, Peter
better doesn't he look good as fuck God damn show the camera. He looks like the
Pringles.
You're the heir to the Pringle. Oh, my God,
that's why you're so rich. Wait a minute. He has think of an energy to him. He
because he I will say name ship is this what got you in the gym as you saw how
wide he was now. He said I need to be this with he. I think it looks like he
is blown up with air. That's that's more than yeah from eating potato. It does
look like he has fake arms on this. This is the this is the basis for the
Pringles guy, his wife listen, no disrespect, she's a dog.
Your great great great great grandma was a complete dog.
Well Peter Fetter, if I ever do get to meet you in a dream or in some type of
vortex, I think that
you really would like me. Can I see your grandma? What I would do was doing with
my life and why it's normal to be like I am. I didn't get a good show him show
him your grandma one more time. Why are you scared to show?
I was in the middle of talking to my Graham great great grandpa. He has a
coconut head.
This haircut,
what's wrong with the haircut?
that's my great great grandma. You're talking about watch it dude. I mean I
don't know what else to say about you mean she's beautiful. I
you see the resemblance
that's horrible.
She's passed on. She looks like they were about to put plan of the apes
make up on
you can't say this. That's my great great grandma looks like she's halfway
through a plan of the apes. Yes, she looks like an anamorph second to last
anamorph
she does not look good man. You're trying to tell me that your grandma was fire,
your great great grandma, you're trying to tell me she's fire. You know she
kicked Peter Fetter to the curb day. He was a womanizer. I would hope so with
that fucking wife at home used to he used to blow his entire paycheck on is
that way and food and women is that why she looks like that he womanized her. He
womanized her. Oh my God, I was probably trying to he probably just used her hair
as storage. She was probably just using her. Yes, he thought that he thought that
he was a bowl. Yeah, you know guys in a hundred years, people are going to look
back at us and think the same
the same thing. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's so funny to imagine going to
the salon and getting that haircut. Get it, give me give me the give me the
rumple stilt skin from Shrek for
there. This is like the hot haircut. This is like this is like the the bus and
zoomer haircut of the the nine tens, just a big just putting like the stickiest
it like pine tar in your hair. So it all stays in a job. Have you ever thought
about your kids, your grandkids, your great great grandkids? This will be
available to them. Yeah, yeah, I think about that more about my kids than my
great great grand. Luckily, they were my great great kids. I'll be speaking
Spanish yeah, and so they will understand any of this. What I'm just
thinking about now about this picture to about this hairstyle is that picture
they, especially since you're saying this to pick pictures are they're not
just like taking a picture. This is like a they're like this is a once in a
lifetime. It's like we're taking our fifty cents. It's like this is our
picture, so this that what they're they're get up that's like they're like
they're like prepping that for like a week. This is the best we need to get my
hair done for this picture. I need to get these clothes. I need to need to
and essentially I forgot to smile. The only reason why you would get a picture
was to prove that you existed. Yeah, I knew that the picture came out and it
was just proof that you used to exist. So they didn't there was no reason to
mile. Yeah, they were from Latvia,
immigrants from Latvia, okay, reminder to never go to Latvia, because the ugly
women,
she literally does look
you're not even looking at her. How can I know that a perfect mental? What if
you look again and you forgot when you were you again and you can't believe
how beautiful she is. I'll show you what she looks like.
She looks really, really as we're not that white. No, her. She really didn't
look like she could see like this. She had a teacher type of yeah, look yeah, you
know she looks like the wayside teacher from wayside school, the evil one looks
like she weighs the same as a side of an apple. This is gorgia, this is gorgia.
That's crazy. You remember Mrs. Gordon and how did she pass crazy? You remember
her to I remember the one who brought her attributes. I don't remember her
name. Mrs. Gorf. It's frog backwards. Oh my God, you're right turns into a frog.
How did she pass away?
I don't know.
Jack the Ripper.
They're not buried together.
Whoa!
But they lived in...
Whose choice was that?
Probably hers, because like I said, she kicked him in the curb.
And how did he fare on the curb?
He probably lived outside on the curb.
Just sitting there.
You had a hobo grandpa?
Kick to the curb is an expression.
I do like the idea that he did live
did live on the curb just like that right outside the house. Just like well,
well,
back then you could fully live
on the on the curb. Yeah, you could live a hobo. That was like a normal. That
was the golden era. That was before that. Oh yeah. Back then hobos would walk
around wearing suits. Yeah, actually,
it's so funny. Most hobos were better dressed than most CEOs now. Yeah, shoes
say could I bother you to come in and eat a meal with your family, please well
sure well sure sure I don't see why not honk honk your hobo. They all had like
the wooden sole shoes to like no shoes back then were comfortable. West
Shocks, wooden shoes are actually supposedly very comfortable clogs,
wooden clogs. I don't agree with it. Okay, let's wear them some doctor until
doctor shoal came around. He is a doctor wood. He is buried in Ros or his
girlfriend is from Roslindale. Where's Roslindale in Massachusetts and they
lived in, I think West Roxbury. Whoa wait, what if you find out that deep roots
yeah, but you find out that his like
like great great grandson or something is like Maurice star, the guy who found
new great greats on me. No, no guy before you got two guys before you, so
his dad, my dad, I don't understand what you're saying, okay, but he got kicked
to the curb right right. Oh, you're saying I have like a half you're like I
a Herbert Powell. Oh, you might have a I watched that episode last night,
actually, I have and I was thinking about having about how incredible it
would be to have a half half brother that you don't know about. You could you
could have I want a long lost brother so badly. Man crazy. Wouldn't it be insane?
I was thinking about the can you imagine I feel like my brain would
instantly break to meet somebody who I've never met before my life who looks
like me and you instantly love them. I know and you hug them. How amazing is
that wouldn't it suck to not fuck with them at all? I know that's like and it's
like yeah, you meet them and you don't fuck with them at all. They suck and
then you're like oh this guy's walking around with my face. Yeah, I've been
with like some second cousins on my dad's side that you don't like. Well, I
think I got along with them, but like my older brother just did not fuck with
them at all. Like we like met it like some family reunion thing when I was
eight. My older brother was just like I don't like these guys. They have a
different favorite color than you. Yeah, exactly. That would hurt my heart. More
toys. Yeah, more toys, the richer. More toys, damn. I think it's possible that I'm not my
father's son. Yeah? Yeah, my brothers both look like him and it's possible that my mom
philandered and found her way into having intercourse with some kind of great man and
produced me. Trixie Mattel. Trixie Mattel, who else? Mr. Clean. Mr. Clean, some of the
the most amazing men who've ever lived that changed the world forever, more so
than anybody in your family ever has. So
on my mom's side, I'm related to the woman who invented Christian science.
Really? Yeah, that's an odd or what's that? What it's called? What's the one
where they don't go to the doctor? Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's an interesting
religion, because they have a whole they have like a whole tower in Boston. Yeah,
they're very cool, yeah, and they don't believe died, I think, because she broke
a leg and didn't go to the doctor. I think that's why our boy from Top Gun is going so
badly. Who? What's his name? Tom Cruise? No, the other guy. Can't talk anymore. Oh, Val
Kilmer. Val Kilmer's Christian Science. Oh, no way. Is he still alive? Yeah, he's still
alive. I thought he was dead. No, he got the Ebert thing going on. Yeah, he got no mouth.
He looks fucked up in the Top Gun movie. He's got a mouth, but it don't work. Yeah. It's
straight up don't work. He's Christian Scientist? Yeah, he's Christian Scientist. I should hit
I did not know that hit him up and say what's up, what's up? He just says dot
dot dot every time
can't speak or type.
I would love to have a conversation with him where he does the typing thing like
a top gun Maverick. Yeah, like hey man, what's up and he's like and also he's
not much. He's so fucking old that it's you know it's just not in Peck all the
time. He did not learn. Well, he was in that movie in the 80s where he plays a
scientist. I can't believe he did that with his religion being that I know
That's really surprising.
He, um, in 2013 he was doing this like one man play where he plays Mark Twain and he wore
this like crazy prosthetic.
I saw that picture.
Yeah, he came to my hometown.
Really?
And he did the Mark Twain show.
Val Kilmer came to the one man show in, uh.
Well he did one town over, it was in Derry.
In Derry, New Hampshire?
I almost went and saw it because I was just like, why the fuck is he doing that?
I bet it was awesome.
I bet it was sick.
I bet it was a once in a lifetime experience.
And he just missed out on it because now he can't do it anymore.
No, now he can't.
he didn't he's going to do it again. Wait, but he wrote he wrote. Oh my goodness.
Why was he dressing up like Mark Twain for the play? Yeah,
what kind of question is why? What is his leg? I don't understand. Why was he
doing that? Like no, that's not a very marginal thing creative. Yeah, I guess I
guess it's all your hearters exercise. I would listen if I was if I if I got had
brain damage, yeah, from you know, taking one antibiotic once deciding that I'm
never going to take it again and it you know viruses and bacteria ravage my
system because they don't take the full course. It infects my brain, half of my
brain decays. There you go. I would also completely be doing tours around the
country where I'm doing plays about American authors yeah and I would also
be going on stage at American authors concert. I'd be doing one singing a lot.
I'd be I would be doing a musical called American authors. That is about mark
Mark Twain and the band of Melville and all the other one all the music is
American authors music. That's a good idea. That's another good idea. It's a
five act play. It's five authors and five new original. This is it's cloud
atlas.
Oh, my God, all authors are related. Who are the authors Herman Melville and
Mark Twain, Dave peakly pickly
play
so
Dave, and then we have to have one a we have to have one that is a comic book
writer to like that's like the last one where it's like a or a blogger where
it's developed. I guess that's mad wall.
Yeah, yeah,
Stanley Stanley and then
Stanley is like in the middle. It goes like a Herman Melville Stanley and then
mark
that's a wonderful idea yeah. It's a good ideas day. I think that I would do a
one man show about the real life of the actual Peter Parker, the historical
Peter. Yeah, that's a really good idea, the true story, not the fictional
isation. You actually, I think, could make so much money doing that. If do
you know how the way you do it is what is you do it as a Stan Lee biopic and
you like do it as like a Meta fiction thing and he's meeting all the real
people. I think you could actually make a hundred million dollars
like all the inspiration. Oh my God, Peter Parker, it's so the idea that he
like meets just like a homeless guy. That's like what's up, bub? I've been
alive.
The way you do it, you literally do it so that you don't buy the licenses to
any of the marvel characters at all and you just have stuff that like suggests
it and you have moments where he looks at something and you can tell what he's
he meets a water found. He's like
and then about fifty percent of the movie is him whipping Jack Kirby with a
belt. Yeah,
drar it, drar it, you fucker yeah, Jack Kirby is the guy who is accused of
killing JFK yeah, Jack Ruby, the guy who killed Lee Harvey Oswald. So Jack Kirby
is a second guy involved. He drew he drew all the X man, created basically
all the marvel stuff and Stanley took credit for all of it. He was the he was
the artist he's you know the guy better made you did the guy who made a
Stanley's real Stanley's real name is Stanley Lieberman and he took the name
Stanley. He went by first name only a let yeah, but the the same situate
situation happens
to watch the same situation,
same situation happened to one Bob finger yep, Bill Kane and Bob Bill Kane
and Bob I'd fucking
yeah,
finger, bill finger, you are, I would walk all over you on the cover. No, no,
no, who's bill finger? He's the guy who stole Batman yeah from bill finger bill
finger, a bat man and then bill dude, you're his name's bill finger.
Everyone's just going to bully him.
I'm still a guy named bill finger. I'm bill finger. It's so funny to steal
credit from bill finger. I mean listen, even if they believe you, they're not
kind of want to put your name back on. We would not have that man. There would
be no dc no dc anything yeah. If bob cain big daddy cain didn't step up yeah
daddy
things through a little pinky finger. Yeah, exactly there you go. You got all
the that you got. Oh, okay pointer yeah, stop calling me point dexter okay,
all right, middle middle. No one thinks about you because you're so middle.
You're middle ring a ding ding ring a ding ding okay, thumb pinky thumb okay,
I'm Thumpsy. Thumpsy would be good. Thumpsy Whumpsy. And then you have to go
to it. Then you'd have to say left hand finger. Who made Vertigo? Who's the
genius who invented Vertigo, the dark comics for adults? Wasn't that part of
DC and they broke off? Yeah.
That was like... Wasn't that fucking like Rob... Wasn't Rob Leefield involved
or something? Or is Rob Leefield Vertigo or Image? Might have been Image.
And then I bet that... And then also is which one is fucking
Todd McFarland. Oh, that's a God. What is that? I know. Is that Vertigo?
It might be Vertigo. He has his own. No, he has like his own thing.
Oh, yeah. He has his own thing now, but he might have been the... That might...
I forget. That might have been one of the first Vertigos. One of the first,
yeah, one of the things... I remember seeing a... Going to some comic book
store, and I never really liked comics, but I bought a bunch of Vertigo comics
and... They was all like... 'Cause they just looked so awesome and sexual and
violent. They was all try hard shit, though. Yeah, it was awesome. I was so
fire. It would always be like a bunny that smoke cigarettes,
yeah, and everybody everybody else is human and the bunny has a has a human
girlfriend who's like really, really hot and they do like a I felt the same way
reading those comics at the at the comic book shop that I do did looking at porn.
Yeah, I'm in trouble when you're like someone well, it's like hole in your
stomach on your neck. Yeah, I hope this guy's made of blood. Oh my God, a guy
made of blood and his best friend is made of knives. Oh fuck that's so dark
that's the darkest thing. I can imagine grittiness, all the grittiness. Oh my
God, this guy has yeah reading, I yeah go buying it would be like you go and
you buy the comic about the guy made of blood and his name is is gut gut yeah
gut and he has an he has an imaginary friend. That's a unicorn that swears and
they use they do stars and bombs and yes, and you'll be buying those and you'll
be like yeah. I just like comics that are kind of like dark and realistic yeah
really like gritty realism
four arms and he has a K forty seven and eat like have you played that game, the
wolf among us, the telltale game, I think it's based on a comic or some
shit. I think it's a it's about the if fairy tales were real and they were,
but it was a way of a yeah. I have seen this yeah.
Oh actually yeah, that is where like what's his name? Ichabod crane is like
bad like evil rich guy. You can tell how every everybody who writes comic books
has their have their brains completely broken. They were all they all live the
worst childhoods of all time, because every single one of them when they set
out they're like all right. I want to write a comic book that's it's going to
be gritty and realistic, so we're going to cover like real world stuff. We're
going to take a look at issues. It's like okay, well, first of all, Batman
gets raped one thousand times yeah. I know
that's like the killing joke. It's literally all that. It's so crazy.
That's like all, that's what happens to Batgirl in the killing joke. Dude,
the wife finally made me throw away the killing joke copy I had since I was
twelve. No. Well, they made me throw it away, but she asked if I wanted it,
and I said, I don't think so. I still have mine. I don't think I need that
for anything. Yeah. Yeah. I think that they need to reboot a gritty version
of the Stinky Cheese Man now. That'd be a good, well, the Stinky Cheese Man
supposed to be a great version of those like fairy. Yeah, but we need to go
gritty. That's I think that is so prime for like one of those public domain
horror movie. The Stinky Cheese movie. Absolutely.
Horror movie. That shit sucks so bad. Yeah, it's terrible. Oh, oh, what did
they do recently? The banana splits. Yeah. I heard that one was kind of fun,
but it's the same idea. Yeah.
That's always the most... What are they gonna do when we go into public domain?
it's going to happen. When we start the podcast twenty nineteen, I think
honestly, I think right now we are in public domain. I don't think we have
any really
never thought in anything, but don't we have is in which we might have creative
commons yeah. So that's got to run out soon. Probably that's a five year thing,
so we're probably coming up on us. Be creative commons can't work. That can't
be real. It can't be like okay. If I put this, if I put a JPEG in the
description of my deviant art post, it's copyrighted yeah. I can't hold up man.
There's no way that's not holding up. I don't believe you can copy and paste
everything. It says this is covered by creative commons. Yeah, it's like oh
okay. Well, I guess I won't steal it. Sorry. I was thinking of stealing it.
Yeah, I thought that creative commons meant that it was public domain. I
thought that that was another word levels of creative common. There's
different licenses, but that's the funniest creative commons license is
creative common zero, where the license is you can do whatever you want with
Yes,
okay, cool.
Thanks for taking the time to put that into your thing to say that I think we
may have that one.
I had something that flew away from my brain to talk about what a fly. It was
a fly that was
opened up my brain to look at my thoughts and like an empty wallet, a fly
buzzed around it out. You're talking about a movie idea that's dark and
gritty. Oh no, are they doing one with with Mickey Mouse? Yeah, he's the
steam.
Yeah, they've already done a trillion of them. I think I think literally the day
that it went into public domain, there was a thousand. So where's our idea? I
want to get some money really see boat Willie. I think you got to go. I think
I ship has sailed
the steam.
I forgot about that. I think that the way to go is, you know, everybody's
doing well. First of all, everyone's doing horror. Yeah, because obviously
he's a cartoon. So we should also doing violent funniest of her shooters.
romantic. Oh, that's an even better. Nobody is going to do that. Well,
there's romance. A woman falls in love with steamboat willy isn't that isn't
that a human woman? Oh okay, in real action, live action, I was going to say
doesn't, but we're going to call it real action. Taylor Swift, Taylor,
Taylor's, not public. She's not she's public. She is not public. She belongs
to she belongs to trap. No, she doesn't the trap, the T for the entire public.
No bro. She is loyal. She is not for the public super. Take it back. Actually,
I'll take it back. I'm not dude. What if she does the half time show as a
surprise?
I'm doing the half that would never happen. I sure I think it's usher. Oh,
isn't that funny? Well, but then that would be funny. She can't do that
because what if she does the halftime show and the Chiefs are down thirty six
to three, it will power motivation. Yeah, I don't think so. I think there's
another team this year. The forty niners is it yeah, I'm looking to you. I don't
no, actually I'm not like if I know that before Caleb man card
don't take my man, bro. You're going to be oh snap way. You're actually in
francisco bro. I'm I pains me to do this. I'm rooting for Kansas. This is
tough for me because I like Taylor swift and I like san francisco because I'm
gay. I like both. Let's let's let's let's I don't know which one the like
on here. Okay, san francisco gay,
Kansas City, probably straight yeah. She is the straight versus gay. Yes, but
not
she's racist name true forty niners cool name. Yes, very cool. Also Kansas kind of
white because they have a big state in what way owner because forty niners were
real white people. Yeah, I guess you're right. So you never thought about that
yeah minor forty nine. So
Kansas City's gay. They have a big statue of a boner in the middle of the
city, the big arch. I don't know anything about Kansas. That's not about a boner.
That's a boner. So but okay, so a Volvo Kansas City has has has has Travis and
Taylor. Yeah. Who does San Francisco have? Oh, they have boner. They have
Travis and Taylor. But it's a guy's guy.
Got him and Steve.
I don't know. Okay. I don't really know who's involved in. So I think it's
stacking up on the side of of Kansas. Okay, well, let's do a full analysis of
for this yeah San Francisco. What is what do they have in their corner right now?
The apple vision home has just been really and plus a homeless Ryan. There
will be homeless people sitting in their mansions watching this
who are going to absolutely riot if the nine or forty nine imagine if Taylor
Swift was from San Francisco.
Where's she from she's from she's supposed to be southern she's supposed
to be. It is like trying to to understand a fictional care. You use to
story southern, but now she's from the internet Pennsylvania. That can't be
what that's crazy. That's fucking that's so crazy as
she's never claimed Pennsylvania at least once. Where does she live? I thought
she was a she like was she born there and then she like immediately how close
is reading to like Philly
whyo missing what the fuck is whyo missing? What is whyo fuck you whyo
if you live in a town called why I'm missing, you are not going to make it
why you're missing. Okay, I'm right now. Okay, wait, well, Philly,
Philadelphia is kind of southern, though yeah, it's not enough. It's not enough
for what she's rocking. That's yeah, it's not that it's not horse flannel
t. No, no, yeah, but it's kind of it can be country, but it's she wears
short skirts. I wear t shirts. It's a concern. What happened in Pennsylvania?
Yeah, that happens a lot of Pennsylvania. I've heard I didn't realize
she was a I guess they have a
tenancy or some doors in pencil. Yeah, I thought she was well. I guess I had I
haven't she hasn't been pretending to be southern for quite a while now. Yeah,
yeah, I think she got over that. I think even if she was southern, I would still
consider it pretending to be southern. She's pretending to be christian.
She may not be pretending. She's having sex on the night. I let now don't I
don't want to listen everybody listening this right now. I you can't spread this
okay. What this is exclusive. I haven't told this to anybody else. It this is it
think you could consider it Super Bowl gossip. I Taylor gossip exclusive. I was
at church now this past weekend and I was bowing my head in prayer and I hear a
noise next to me.
Someone's phone buzz. I look over to scream at them and say, turn your phone
off off all the way, leave it at the door. Who is it Taylor Swift and Travis
Kelsey holding hands and this was in New York and what kind of this was in New
York. This was a Latino church really. So they go to a that I go to church.
What's the name of it? Iglesia
Iglesia, okay, Iglesia Jesucristo. Okay, wow, I believe this now. So they go
to a fully Spanish speaking church and they and I saw they had Google translate
open on their phone. They share a phone. That's adorable. They share a
it's a Samsung Galaxy. It's one of the they have a Facebook, they have a
Facebook account that is called Travis and Tei. Wow! Travis Tei, I sent a
request, not accepted yet, but okay, I think I might Travis Taylor and that's
really hard to find because there's so many Travis Taylor's in the world, but
they were on their phone, they were running Google Translate and they were
reading the
translation, which is even harder because it's like it's a lot of the songs are in
Latin and she and he was dressed up nice to the nines. She was wearing a T shirt
my sweat pants like she just rolled out of bed. Wow, so what you're telling me is
these celebs that I idolize are actually just real people walking. Yeah, except
for Travis Kelsey, who dresses up yeah. Did he dress up like a when you say
dress in the night, the forty nines, he's a football player. He was no, he was in a
he was in a full tux and a top hat to church church on Sunday. Wow, top hat,
the top hat, well, the whole the whole thing was lilac and did he have
coattails? Lilacs a really beautiful color. I couldn't tell if he had
coat tails, because he did not move his butt enough for me to see against the
pew and I believe me. I was trying to check
trying to get him to lean forward a little bit. I said
I said, Oop, you dropped your pencil and he said what pencil and you when you
take
when you take notes on in church, no, but it's easy to see some of these
coat tails when they're sitting down and I also heard that he was praying. He
uttered a secret prayer. He thought he was doing it quite enough that no one
could hear, but his phone picked it up when they were using the translation. I
put it off the Spanish. He said, Dear God, please slaughter and eliminate the
family members of every man, woman and child in San Francisco. Wow, so that
doesn't strike me as so loving into God. No, no, so he wants God to do nefarious
things for him. He wants God to do his bidding. He thinks he can move heaven
and earth just because he's famous. So this is a battle.
This is Sodom and Gomorrah versus Bethlehem. This is angel versus
Pennsylvania. Pretty close to wow. We're Taylor Swift is so again that's a
Sodom and Gomorrah Kansas.
I like
Sodom and Gomorrah sounds amazing and it's a Twin Cities. It sounds amazing.
I'm gonna go more like imagine you go to Sodom and you're like, oh, well, I
really I'm loving the vibe. The more is like and they're like just go, oh, just
go to Gomorrah. It's right over the bridge, go over there, whole new type of
vibe, different music, different coffee. When you live it, when you live in
Samora and your friend text you and goes yo I'm going to be in your area next
week. Let's hang out. We cut rolls around. Hey man, where you stand? Oh,
I'm just in Sodom. Oh
I that kills me man, bro. It's literally an hour away to my train. It's two
hours. Yeah, it takes forever. It's on horse. I mean I have to get it and if
you look back, you turn into a pillar. Yes, I can't even I don't even know how
far I am from home.
It's bullshit man.
yeah, we need a I mean San Francisco. Why is there not a high speed line
between Sodom and
perfect
my dream transit map Sodom to Gomorrah one line, the brown line
right there.
Yeah, I
guess it is a bit of it fails a little bit because San Francisco wait, Oakland
yeah, Oakland is Gomorrah
Because Sodom was kind of the main one.
- Yeah.
- The cool one where all the artists live.
- No, Oakland's the one where all the artists live.
- Okay, well Gamora, the artists wanted,
they used to live in Sodom.
- Then it got too hipster-y.
- And then it got too hipster-y,
and yuppies moved in with their tech jobs
doing abacus work, and they kicked out
all the hipsters and artists who then had to live in Gamora.
And now it's a commuter city, and that's bullshit.
- Yeah, it's true.
It would be funny to be living back in biblical times and you're pushed out
there. All the tech bros start coming to your city and they're inventing carts.
Yeah, new car push carts. They're inventing slaves. The idea of having a
slave. This is an iron. Imagine a guy who can do it for you. Okay, Steve,
Steve Jobs presentation of a guy just like this showing he starts with. He has
the same progression as the iphone reveal where it's like a dog, a horse and
than like an outline of a guy and then they show that it's a human. Oh yeah,
they're doing he's doing the yearly keynote, the Steve jobs way back from way
back when and he's like well up to now we've been able we've been able to paint
things red. We've been able to paint things yellow yep and but now, thanks to
these flowers, I found guys we can paint things blue and one more thing
and one more thing. Blue is a color now.
Oh my God,
everybody yeah. You see everyone waiting in line to get their first blue rocks,
yeah
bunch of pictures in the tablet. The next day it's crazy that this this this
ancient this biblical time, Steve jobs and Steve jobs probably both died trying
to cure their shit with juice.
True, a very similar life from a medical stand. I just need to drink a bunch more
confused by cancers, Steve Toiles,
Steve
yeah, but he didn't do the Flintstones invention. He did actual stuff that
they used, but yeah, he had real concrete stuff exact like concrete,
yeah.
I think I wish I think if I could go back in time anywhere, it would be Bible
times just to see if it all really happened to them. Yeah. Yeah, I would
watch this is kind of a completely different branch off of what we were just
talking about, but I would watch a keynote of if they did
if they did a keynote for every single industry. One like can you imagine how
incredible it would be to watch a keynote for like construction workers? Don't
think we have a new tool. Yeah, they do that, but I don't I would like it. I
want it on the same scale. Yeah, I don't record the same production value. Yeah,
I mean I would watch the last conferences. This is the kind of thing I
Yeah, elevator repairman go to like...
Yeah, I know, but I'm saying I want the keynote.
I want them to do it up.
You want some...
Well, that would mean that there needs to be an Apple-type head of their industry for
that type of stuff, for manual labor.
Or they could all work together to make a good presentation.
That's not very...
It's like a music festival.
Isn't that what they...
That's what they do in Paul Bart Mall Cop 2.
I have a convenient Apple keynote thing, but for security guards at the mall.
Wait, this already exists. Yeah, that's got to be real too, though. They've got
to have some. I'm sure they do. There's conferences for every job. Why do we not
have a I mean, we'll do it. The podcasters keynote will do it. The
podcaster summit. Yeah, if I definitely do, but it's for the people who do like
and this year we present. Yeah, and this and one more thing. That's right. We
we have cameras. We don't know how to use that kind of thing every single year.
Yeah, it's a good idea. We bought more equipment that we have no idea what the
fuck to do with,
but it feels like we're supposed to have it. It is like it is fucked up that
they're like
like I think I'm think about how much work we put into that. We don't know how
to use the cameras. We barely know how to do this. Sometimes there's like people
who like have you maybe you barely know. I barely know how to do it. You we have
a guy that knows how to do one part of every hole of this thing. I guess that's
kind of true and there's podcast out there. When you say to somebody like,
oh yeah, like my job is a podcast, there's podcasts that have like they're
edited and they have music to them. Should we just start? I would. How the
hell is that? I would really like to think that part of the reason people
like us is because we don't know what we're doing and maybe that's part of the
charm of it because otherwise it hurts, it hurts my soul. Yeah. Do you think
that we could start telling people we're a part of your mom's house studios and
you might believe us easily. Well, they might not know what that is. So yeah,
well, if they know what it is, I think they could we do inspect element and
change their website on one end and you can see great just start posting all
the time. You can bring your cousin. No, I want to prank millions of people.
Yeah, because nobody's gonna check. Nobody inspect element. Yes, I can.
All right, I just did it to prove and it's back to your element.
Mustache
brackets must dash you're doing really good brackets. Yeah, can you believe
that people another must? Can you guys believe that you have your pubes shaved
into a mustache? That's odd. That's a cool idea. That is cool. It's actually
cool eyebrows, a goatee,
a goatee above. I wish I had just like a circle. I wish that my pubes were more
easily shaved like that. Yeah, maybe I'll shave him into an X. No out get out
of here. Just the word out
Fuck off. If you're reading this, the bitch fell off.
Fuck off.
If you're reading this, the bitch fell off would be good.
Yeah, it'd be a little hard.
Yeah, the bitch was sitting on my pubes.
Big pubic area. Pubis.
Ew.
It's funny, it's area is called a pubis.
Do men have that too?
You should have a button that you can press and it says pubis.
Ketchup.
That's better.
That's a similar enough type of thing.
Are we going to watch the Nickelodeon Super Bowl?
That's the plan?
Yes, we are.
I like to watch the Nickelodeon coverage, but Joe did kind of stab at my heart
when he said that the commercials are going to be for kids. Joe immediately
like the Joe's over time shows going to be so good man sweet or the they're
doing sweet victory before the whole game. They're not even doing his half
time, so we could even catch that and then switch to the normal. It's going
to be imagine the I mean honestly, I would really like to in giant platform
coming out from the middle of the bubble. Who is Bob Doug
Doug he's pass who does Nickelodeon is over. He's barely even got out by
Disney. I thought okay, Doug comes up, goes right back into the ground because
he doesn't belong to Nick and he that would be an incredible.
If they brought somebody up like they're going to perform in the spring,
they should have done that with remember last year when fifty cent was hanging
from the ceiling like a fire, he should have just immediately gone back up. It
just he comes down. Why did he do that? It was cool. It was kind of cool. It
was awesome. Yeah, it was actually really. I love that last year's musical
artist. It wasn't like one person. It was just the hip hop. All that's
there was Rihanna, right? West. Yeah, it was. It was. Yeah, it was two years
ago. I'm thinking two years ago. Yeah, yeah, and it was and the Rihanna
performance was she announced she was pregnant. She danced with her
pregnant eye popping. I saw her body. It was belly popping. I know my belly.
I felt like it was jiggling for days afterward. I forgot that we've been
together for two Super Bowls. Yeah, yeah, that's crazy. Then we go to my old
apartment last year for it. We watch it in my part. I made wings that I made
wings and there was a black mold problem. Yes, and then it was one of the two
years ago was the best one. Yeah, that was the best one. The big apartment.
Yes, yeah, with all the millions of foods. That was amazing. This is going to
be probably the worst one because we're in the office. Yeah, we have no couch.
no chairs, no couch. We have chairs. This is the type of chairs we're all going to
be sitting for for the entire for the Super Bowl man. Yeah, we have we have a
Herman Miller around. I guess we have one or two Herman Miller's. Yeah, so you
got to come to the office early and secure the seat. I'm going to bring I
think I might go pick up a whole couch. You should you honestly really need to
do that. Go pick up a can we get rid of those camp chairs? Yeah, yeah, no, no,
no, there's still there's still two good ones, but it's fine either way. That's
not that great. Oh, I think I want to become I think that I'm going to quit
the podcast and become a fire watch. I watch the fire watch. It's a guy. I
watch this guy on YouTube. Oh, they stand up. He stands up in that big
tower. There was a woman who did that on Jeopardy. Really? Yeah, it's not
really a full time job. It's just you do it for a summer, but apparently you
get swarmed by ants. Yeah, I can imagine. But I want that responsibility. How
amazing would that be to just let the fire go? I'd be swarmed by ants up and
I think I'd have all my snacks with me.
you bringing a bunch of sugar water, sugar water,
maple syrup, water and that's very shallow. He bonds
my favorite yummy midnight snack, a bowl of sugar water. Oh yeah, and a sugar
cube. Oh, I love a sugar and a vinegar trap.
That's amazing. Oh my God, but I if you did a job like that, do you think you'd
get lonely? Yeah, I would love to do a lonely job for a while and then I had
one. I had I worked at the gym in my community college and no one knew I'm
talking about like a like you work on top of a mountain. Yeah, nobody. This is
a different. You have to be helicopter. I worked on. I worked on top of the on
top of the building. It was on the top. That's not on top of the building.
Jim was not on top of the building. It was for elevation. I would love to be
like I would love to like be, you know, I'm somehow contracted to like I they're
you're like there's an island off the coast of Greenland and you are the only
person who can maintain its wild life for two years. All those kinds of jobs
are always in a lighthouse. All those kinds of jobs are always just like make
sure that this button doesn't get yeah, make sure nothing happens yeah. Go there
and make sure nothing ever happens. Nothing sounds exciting. It's very
you're you're really, really want to go to Antarctica. I don't actually I've
I'm watching a lot of north and are to go south and are so Antarctica is the
south one, so south Antarctica, yeah, so the south one. Okay, what's the top
one called? Arctic? There is no
up there north. There's not nothing. There's not nothing, but there's not a
continent. Oh yeah, but who decides this the UN the ocean fuck all that right?
I'm not listening to it. Of course, there's stuff in the Arctic circle, but
there's not a there's no
there's not a come. Tell me that
is just ice. There's no land make it. I know what that is. That's white. I
ice okay now pick up now bring a picture of Antarctica. Give me a glass of
water yeah. I want some land and show us a picture of Antarctica
huh this is looking mighty familiar giant ice cubes. I've been watching all
of these videos of so what's that lately? Oh, what's that right there? Oh
everybody knows what black ice is they did a key and peel sketch about this,
but I really would like to go to Antarctica yeah. I don't think that you
like that. I don't think you'd last a day there. You wouldn't in a bikini.
Why are you realize going to Antarctica just like going to a shitty hotel?
so the way you can't go outside, you just can't go outside. You just go to you
just go and you live in a cafeteria hotel in a bad neighborhood, Flint,
Michigan. Yeah, it's no
can't go outside.
It's that's what just what it is. You just go to a place. You go to the back
rooms and then whenever you look out the window, you're like, oh my God, why
would you want to go? I want to go to Hawaii or something. Well, you can go
there, too. You don't have to only go one place. Okay, I'm going to go there
instead. We're going to go to Hawaii and be alone. You go to Antarctica. We're
going to go to Hawaii. That's fine and we're going to fuck flowers to see us. I
I want to I want to see a seal in person. I want to see I've watching these videos
of seals. I do not want to see a polar bear or maybe you don't see you. You
don't want one to see you man. Yeah, I want to see one. I don't want to be
yeah. You want to see what you don't want to get eaten by one kill by one
though. Do you? I know that your opposer, you don't want to get to shreds.
Haven't you seen that movie polar bear TV show? I mean the terror. No, I
haven't. I was thinking about watching. Is it good now? Is that the way I
thought I figured that I figured that there's no way it could be good, but I
saw a picture of it a couple of days ago and I saw it had it was set on a ship.
It's based on a true expedition, but then they say
I don't remember Shackleton. I don't know Ernest Shackleton. Who the hell
you only watch is the guy who went to Antarctica or the north. I think
there's some of them. They were a bunch of people went to different places all
across history. Yeah, that's true, but do you have any interest in going
somewhere that nobody's ever been untouched by man? I think that would be
pretty cool to do. I think I would have to I think it would be make me freak out.
I would not want to go. I would love to do that. I want to go to a place where
somebody has already set up a resort. You could probably do it in America. I'm
sure that there's somewhere that probably one square foot of land. There's probably
more than that. I mean, America is huge. It is crazy big. They probably in the
middle of the woods or like a desert or something. I feel like I want to go back
to Wyoming. I spent one night there is amazing. I love I watch a movie Wyoming,
Montana, all of these. This is where we belong. I belong in Montana. We don't
belong in this wretched city. I love Montana, man. I need to go back so badly.
I don't know. I think I belong here. You belong here because... I don't know how
to drive. Well, you can't drive up and down the mountain. I don't need to. I
don't know how to drive, but I will ride a horse. I'm a hiker type. Yeah, that's
a good idea. I'm not a hiker. I am a hiker type. I want a backpack. I have to
be around stuff. There's so much stuff out there. There's butterflies. Yeah, but
I gotta be around buildings. I have to be around stuff, but I like to be not
around stuff for a little while. Is this true? I have the opposite impulse.
The buildings are disgusting to me. Yeah, I'm the opposite. You like the
buildings. I like being around big buildings, yeah. Yeah, I don't like it
either. You have a bad soul, then. I don't think I have a bad soul. I think
greenery. Well, you have a newer soul. I was an old reincarnated soul that has
now been... Yeah. You're a brand new one. I don't think I was ever... I don't
think that I could have existed at any other point in time. I think one of my
past lives I could have been on an expedition. I don't think I had any
past life. I think you were a prairie dog that was eaten by a hawk. Yeah,
something like that. Maybe like an animal that had no life. Yeah,
like an animal that was a fucking door animal that had no life.
Yeah, like a prairie dog that got eaten by a hawk or like a fly that lived on
a piece of shit
or like a praying mantis that got ate by his bitch. You should definitely not
they'll ever have a past life reading.
I would
and they just sit there just like, should we go? This is our sequel to a race
off the past life reading life reading. That is an amazing, that is fucking
idea. The past life reading we have. There's so many psychics around here.
Okay, let's
really in psychics around here. We can easily go to them. Do you think they'd
let us record them? We can, we can just, I mean, there's literally so many
psychics that we can go and ask each one if they
find one cause like a couple bucks more. My mom would go to psychics all the
time growing up.
All cold call.
You should see if we if we can, they can do the reading, but not tell us
personally and then talk to a camera talking head style. That is such a good
and then because then we don't know until we record that is and then we can
play the clip. Yeah, because I already have guesses as to my past life. Yeah,
we have to have a bunch of guesses. We have to oh my God, this is a great idea
race up to life.
The life
off who had who had the best life. My guess is and then we'll get Julio to do
the thing again with a chart of all the different, all every possible like
occupation. Yeah, we'll rank them. Oh, my God. So how do we do this again?
What
I'm gonna let kill do not the dude. If that shit happens again to me, it is
gonna happen.
Fuck man, I think my you're gonna find out that you were like the psychic is
gonna say something like yeah, you were a lounger yeah.
I
already don't know, or you were like a like in your past life. You were like a
flapper.
I could I could see that actually I could see you being a flat. I think I
think you're one of your past lives. You were the
teenage girl that fatty Arbuckle sat on or whatever or in the past life. I was
like my dad and then before that I was my grandpa. I'm so boring.
All right, I can't imagine I had a good I'm definitely some Irish peasant or
to some kind of like no. See this is you have to dog that lived in a dog that or
a chicken nugget chicken. You have to have the chickens that turned into
chicken. The one you were one of the ones who was hatched out of the egg.
They saw it was a man and they immediately threw it into the blender.
Yeah, you have to uncouple this past life from from from your your ancestry,
because listen your whole family. Yeah, they were Irish peasants worthless. They
were worthless slaves, twenty IQ. That doesn't mean that that's what you were.
that was just what your entire family and everything leading up to your DNA was
this is mysticism. Yes, you could have been Arabian,
maybe
turban. You could have worn a turban, a turban and lived in the desert. You
could have been a Lawrence of Arabia. Yeah, that's what I'm saying man. You
have to dream bit. I mean you could have been a robot or no, that's a future
life.
Yeah, it's something big like maybe like a
like an elephant that got shot on a teacher.
just
like a poached elephant in every single like you were captured,
always captured and held in captivity. Yeah, I was a giraffe that got its neck
cut off. Oh, my God,
I guess we somehow subconsciously have cloud atlas in our brain. Yeah, I don't
know why this is in the movie. I never saw the movie. I read the cloud atlas,
but I just keep I'm like a chimp that got hit with a rock
head. Yeah, you were the one yeah, the space odyssey. Yeah, when the bone came
down and the first thing ever die, cloud swag list.
That's your ass and I'm cloud ass list 'cause I was
a gay guy. No, speaking of gay motor, the leather guy in the village people,
only one of them that wasn't gay. What? Yeah.
The cop was gay? Yeah, every single other one, the leather guy. The rest of
them were gay. The rest of them were gay. Yeah. What the hell? Yeah, I learned this
the other. The leather guy. Well, that guy's funny then. Yeah, he went, he went,
he went way too. He did way too much. Dude, the one straight guy in the village
people that had to be so awesome. I bet he was getting laid. Yeah. And he got to
watch all them change. Yeah. You get to watch all the other guys change. He'd
look at them and he'd go, "Uh uh, not for me." That would have been awesome to be
in the village people get to watch each other change. Yeah.
All right, we are going on tour. We are going to Minneapolis, Detroit and
Carborough, and we are also going on tour with world's biggest army
to
Toronto,
then Boston, then
Philadelphia, then
in Chicago, Atlanta and not a matter. We have a secret show planned for
Bar Harbor, Maine.
Really? I didn't know that. It's a secret from all of you. Bar Harbor,
Maine. I don't even know where that is. I booked a show in Bar Harbor
at a lobster place. Sounds cool. Is this a show or a dinner that we're
having? It's maybe a dinner. Okay, well then don't come to that. Tickets
are at swag poop dot com slash shows buy them up because my intel is telling me
that the Boston show is more than halfway sold out. Boston show is pretty much
sold out, so don't buy it. That's not true. It's getting there though, so you
better buy it. If you want your ticket, you better buy it because you can go
look to see if we have any left, but I'm telling you, you're not. You can do that,
but there are so buy. There are so buy. And then maybe we'll add ten more shows
if we sell it out. Maybe. Is that what we're gonna say? Alright, my friends, I
will see you at one of those shows, I think. And what will I do the rest of
the day?
I'm gonna go to Orchard. What's Orchard? It's in the north end.
It's a place in the north end of New York. North end is Harlem. You're talking
about what you're gonna do a different. I'm saying today. No, in Boston, I'm
gonna go to Orchard. I'm gonna go hit that up and then I'm gonna go to
Filibuster in Boston. Oh, we can go. Yes, Filibuster. Please tell me that
restaurant's still around. I hope it's still around. If I fucking, if it's not
there, I'm going to actually die. That's where that photo, the famous Caleb photo
is from. I want a $5 breakfast combo so bad. I bet they raised their prices with
the remember how sweet the coffee was struck by inflation. Remember you had to
get a coffee. They put so much sugar in it. Oh my God. I loved that. I love that
place. I'm going to go to this place. I used to go to all the time. Haymarket
station. Oh, it closes soon. Ah, fuck in 20 minutes. Well, we have very little
time. Let's go then. Well, bye bye.
This is an item on the next slide here that is called dog mating.
This is on Timo and I have to censor some stuff on this sleep.
Estrus dog toy simulation mating toy plush poodle vent fire.
Estrus partner mating sexual companion venting fidget dog toy.
Let's look at some more pictures here.
Next slide.
The features it has are simulate appearance, which is again censored.
That is a fleshlight hole for a dog pussy, simulated rabbit hair and a
suction cup base. Yeah. Now let's go to the next slide here. Let me
read you the description. Here's some more pictures
of it in use. Here's the description. Note, lubricants is not included.
One, dogs with estrous behavior at home, holding legs, riding over dolls,
making love to the air, etc. Only chasing female dogs outside and not
estrous behavior at home are not recommended to buy.
Two, dog cannot be too stupid.
If your dog belongs to what cannot teach, a few years will not be fixed
to the kind of toilet. Do not recommend to buy.
Okay. Three, the host needs to be patient. Dogs are emotional creatures
too and mating doesn't happen all the time.
It may not be used on the spot, but dogs with estrous behavior will use
it sooner or later under the patient guidance of their owners.
And now to the thing you spoke about about a cover-up.
I'd like to this next slide.
I'd like to read a review from this four stars color khaki.
The one of the photo looks bigger than the one I got might be a
little too small for my dog as he is bigger than this.
This is really truly fine guys.
I'm going to tell you also this is this I'm going to tell you
what the it's on sale.
It's on sale 68% off.
So you're looking for the current the sale price.
I think that this is also one thing on this is I think this
might be a new leader for number one worst thing to be reincarnated as in your next life
if you wake up and you're you can't move and you have four limbs and they're suction cups
to the ground you're in for a very rough one this is gonna be this is a $10 item on sale
from $70 original price was 200 current price is 84 or no 30 you said 68 off yeah okay then
and