Excellent. Hello. Hello all. Welcome. We are doing a Halloween spooktacular campaign, or
one-shot, I should say. And it's going to be based on Child's Play, the movie starring
Brad Dorff as Chucky the doll. And we're going to be doing a little bit of us getting the
characters together. You know, I feel like last time I just sort of shoved those
Pokemon down your throats and I feel like... Pause. ...we could benefit. Pause. Pause. Right. No, I yeah I get it.
I feel like we could benefit from together building these characters out.
Now some of us have already given me some ideas, some of us have given me
nothing I'm open to all of it who gave you nothing his name rhymes with
Shmaleb Schmitz I gave an idea in the chat but I'll do I'll come up with
another idea right now I will be actually maybe just didn't see it then I
will be a Hot Wheels car that wants gasoline okay that's not a good idea but
Yeah, that was a good idea and that was just right off the top of my head.
That was... you just thought of that now?
I kind of like that idea.
Yeah, I'm a hot wheels car.
I'm a hot wheels car.
And I want gasoline.
[laughter]
So, we're gonna put you guys now...
Oh, does this...
Did they... did they... did they fuck this up?
Did they... did Roll20...
So they have folder...
They have a folder structure,
but you have to move the players to the room.
to the room.
So this doesn't sound important,
but it's actually super fucking annoying.
There we go, I fixed it.
Awesome.
- Okay, so on the character sheet,
do I want to use the character manser?
- Yeah, use character manser.
So for those listening at home
and for anyone curious about Roll20.
- What is this?
- So there's ways where you can edit the sheet directly.
I usually do that because that allows me
to put in all kinds of weird stats
and weird things to go on.
For you guys, use the character manser.
Just follow the drop downs, make your character level 2
for any class you want or you think fits your character
and then we will add in our own sort of custom abilities after the fact.
Because you are all things that are possessing toys or objects of some kind
you will all have the ability to briefly possess an inanimate object
similar to the ability I give every other Caleb character I feel like.
But and you'll only be able to do it for a short amount of time, though,
and then you'll inevitably be sucked back into your toy
as is the curse that Chucky is under.
Would you say that's so sad that a possessed car
would be a dragon born?
I already put that.
So you already the same thing, be the same thing, it's true.
Oh, OK. Well, no, I'm not going to copy.
I would say a car just from like, like, I guess like
- Because there's no war forged in there,
you know, which is kind of an automaton in D&D lore.
I would say dragon born.
Me, I'd say a gnome 'cause they tinker with stuff
or you could say a dragon born because they skin wise,
it's more car like maybe.
- I will be a gnome, I think.
- I like that.
It could also be based on who you were.
- And I'll be a rock gnome.
- It could also be based on who you, nice,
who you were before you possessed the doll.
What kind of class is a lawyer?
Is a lawyer a bard?
It's a background, I believe,
but a lawyer.
But my guy is a lawyer.
What should I make my speech?
A bar?
Would that make him a bard?
You think maybe probably bard is good.
Yeah, that makes sense to me.
He talks.
Yeah, like you know, you a bar
College of Eloquence would be
something that a lawyer would.
OK, and skill proficiency is deception.
Yeah, first of all, yeah,
Intimidation and persuasion.
Nice.
No way.
I like that.
No way it's that perfect.
And then tool proficiencies, flute, horn, and dulcimer.
I think it has to be a dulcimer.
It has to be something that you don't need, you can still have your mouth for.
Right?
I got three of them.
I'm going to make my favorite enemy giants because I'm a toy, so everybody's going to
be a giant to me. That's cool. Oh, that's a good choice. That is smart. Yeah. Ability
scores, choose. Method, choose. Yeah, I don't know why they, it's not. Choose a
background. There's only, the only background available is acolyte. Yeah, I
don't know why that is. Do you not have other ones or is it just acolyte? I
feel like it's like that if I don't buy more stuff. It's okay, I'll just be an
acolyte. Yeah, you're all, don't worry about it. You're all acolytes. You're all
in the church of... - Acolytes of toyhood.
- Of toyhood.
- Personality traits. - My language proficiencies.
- I don't wanna do this crap.
I wanna get to my stats.
- Portuguese.
- Yeah, look at this.
Maybe you're thinking about who's my character?
Portuguese, are they Brazilian?
Are they from Portugal before they possessed?
It's Brazilian.
- Yeah, and the language proficiencies
are Portuguese and goblin.
The favored enemy is a good idea, by the way,
'cause you will get bonuses on checks against them
because of that, Caleb.
- My weapon will be a rapier.
- Hold on. - And I'll have
a diplomat's pack, as well as a dulcimer.
- Yeah, that stuff is, diplomat's pack does not matter.
(laughing)
- What do you mean?
- And a prayer book. - A diplomat's pack
and a prayer book.
- Well, tell me what's in a diplomat's pack
and maybe I can-- - I have no idea.
It doesn't say.
- I never, I feel like I've only ever run one thing
where someone was like,
oh, let me get out my like,
like disguise kit and look up what could be in it.
And I was like, please--
- I'm just gonna choose a bunch of random spells here.
- He's like, please don't do that.
- Cure wounds.
What does Bane do?
Bane, identify, could be good.
- Bane is good.
Bane is sort of the inverse of bless.
So if you're playing Baldur's Gate,
you know what bless is. - Oh, I see.
- Yeah. - Hideous laughter
also will be good for my character.
- Minor illusion, vicious mockery, hideous laughter.
- Diplomats cat,
Diplomats pack has two cases for maps and scrolls,
a set of fine clothes, a bottle of ink, an ink pen,
a lamp, two flasks of oil.
- I have all this stuff as a toy?
- Yeah, a vial of perfume,
sealing wax and soap.
- How old is my character?
- I decided just recently that I'm a red car.
- You're a red car.
- I'm saying my age is one.
- Me too.
It is point five.
That was me.
Yeah, I'm going to do point seven five.
Nice.
Well, it's inches or feet.
Nine inches.
Nine inches tall.
Y'all.
Yeah, it's my weight.
As long as you guys are not like over
like a foot, a foot, really, I'll be OK with it.
These are like big dolls.
I think that mine is.
I'm an action figure.
Well, we can talk about yours.
I'll look it up.
What can you look up the size of that?
Yeah, I'm doing that.
Yeah. OK.
Um...
I, um...
It's actually for...
It's actually a steal for the price.
Yeah?
Yeah, probably. I don't know.
Specifications.
Oh, I have starting wealth.
It's in centimeters, of course.
I have to choose my personality traits?
It's required?
It doesn't have the weight, but it does.
You can roll them.
But it is about...
How many...
What is it? 2.2 centimeters per inch?
I misquote sacred text.
Wait, when do I get to do my stats?
That's Fahrenheit to Celsius.
I still have one on everything.
Oh, so it has...
It's 10 inches.
Oh, it's 10 inches?
I think I might be the tallest one here.
Would you say it is 10 inches?
I'm sorry?
I wonder I get to do my stats. I'm still at one for everything.
Oh, can you not edit it?
I just said one. I mean, I guess I'll go with one for everything.
That's fine with me.
You should know we would have you didn't ever give me the chance
to make them.
You should have you just roll them.
I'm a minus five and every step.
So yeah, just hit.
What the hell?
Did you pick a class?
Yeah.
Yeah, you picked Bard, right.
Review. Why can't I change your stats? I hate this shit.
Just do it in the...
That's okay, man. I'll stick with 1.
No, we'll edit the sheet after. It's okay.
Just hit review and edit the sheet.
What am I doing?
Just hit whatever apply changes or whatever it is to get through it.
I did, yeah.
So I'm at 1 on everything.
You're 1 on everything.
Should I put a one on everything too?
'Cause I have my strength, dexterity,
and constitution at five,
and then intelligence, wisdom, and charisma, negative five.
- How did you get that?
- 'Cause I made a custom class.
- Mm-hmm. - Custom race.
- Yeah, character manager's weird that way.
Cam, just roll 3D6 six times and apply it.
What were you saying, Caleb?
- I didn't say anything.
- Damn. (laughs)
- Caleb, what were you saying?
I made my guy I'm just waiting.
Oh he made his guy?
How did you get your stats?
My stats I have negative 5 constitution negative 4 intelligence which is fine by me.
How did you get any of anything? I don't understand.
I just don't know how it got gotten.
I don't know.
Yeah alright we'll give you that.
What's so funny man?
It's just crazy.
You're not gonna be able to do shit.
- At least from a constitution point of view.
- I said I would take all the ones.
- I'm a fucking toy, of course, yeah,
no shit I can't do anything.
- All right, I fuck with you.
- I'm playing in the lore, man.
- He is, you know what?
He's playing in the, yeah, you are.
I like that.
Cool.
All right.
Let me know when you're done.
- I'm working on it.
- Cool.
And then I wanna hear who your characters are
once we're in the story,
and I'll give a little intro to where we are.
We're at Pal-Mart.
For the folks listening, I have an image of Walmart.
I changed it to Pal-Mart
so that it's like the podcast about list, Mark.
- Okay, all right, I'm ready.
- All right, cool.
- Wait a minute.
(laughs)
- What?
- Wait, why do I have eight hit points?
Am I supposed to have that?
- My strength is negative three.
My dexterity is negative three.
My confidence is negative three.
My intelligence is zero.
My wisdom is zero.
And my charisma is zero.
- That's good.
- I have two plus ones,
but that's everything else is zero or negative one.
- That's gonna be good.
All right.
So you sit in the Palmar and let's timestamp this.
Let's wait till 12 minutes on the dot.
So folks can know, go to 12.
Just go.
You sit in the Palmart shopping mall,
the center of commerce in Duluth, Brooklyn.
The only place that rivals its size, scope,
and impact on the city is Wankoff's factory.
It makes the mall of America
look like the doll of China America,
like a little China doll.
Speaking of dolls, you guys might be dolls.
I don't know what characters you're making.
And that's not where you were a little while ago.
You were not in any kind of mall.
You weren't even planning on shopping.
Did we even exist?
You were people beforehand, before you entered these dolls.
Before you entered these characters.
And I'd like to know who you were.
And you guys, right now you sit in the Mr. Hickory Bones spooky toy shop in the mall,
by a Mr. Hickory Bones who is a creepy old toy man and he's put you guys in
different areas of the store based on exactly what you do. So I'd like to know
first who you are as a mother, a mother and her sweet little boy walk in, the
bell rings, what toys will they be buying today? Who are you guys?
Uh, okay. Here's who I am.
Mm-hmm.
My name is Davey and I'm in deep shit, man. Deep fucking shit. I owe a lot of money to
some people. See, they manufactured me for the release of the 1993 crime drama film Carlitos
Way directed by Brian De Palma. They modeled me after Sean Penn's corrupt lawyer character
David Kleinfeld. They expected to make a whole bucket of money with my toy line. Every kid
in America was supposed to be playing with a fully articulated hairline Acura Davey Kleinfeld
with included prop tape recorder.
I was going to be a fucking hit man,
but the box office result for the movie
was lukewarm at best.
So now I'm in deep fucking shit.
I was supposed to be the best-selling toy in the world
and now I got to find a way to make back that cash
and I can't even do it by being a lawyer like in the movie
because I'm a toy.
I'm so fucked.
I'm so fucking fucked and as for how I became a toy.
Well, I guess it's either that I'm Sean Penn
and I got trapped in this toy body,
which also got me stuck in character as David Klinefeld,
or maybe I'm just method acting, or I guess I could just have been a toy all along
and just never had it was a person, or maybe I'm the real David Klinefeld
from the movie who escaped from the TV and then became a toy in the process.
Or I guess also I could be the guy who came up with the idea for the toy
and they trapped me into the toy as a punishment for the toy selling bad.
Or maybe I'm just a random guy who happened to accidentally become a toy
and also happens to have the exact same personality
and values as David Kleinfeld from the movie Carlitos Way,
I honestly can't remember.
The point is I need $1 million and fast.
And also it's Halloween,
so I'm a psychotic serial killer as well.
Okay, cool.
- That's scary.
- That's so, yeah.
I'm a little spooked out, man.
Wow.
So this guy is, yeah, he's like,
it seems like you maybe have either multiple personality
or which is, which is by the way normal.
I'm David Klinefeld from the film called "Did You Not Listen?"
I don't think any of you guys have seen that movie.
No, I still haven't seen it.
You keep telling me I haven't seen it.
No, me neither.
Basically, he's a lawyer.
He's played by Sean Penn.
Okay, and that I got.
So you're sitting in the movie's action figure.
From the movie.
I'm in between Batman and Optimus Prime.
Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, and below you is a Lego set for Sallow.
So. (laughing)
And cool.
And speaking of more toys,
nah, it would have been a good subway,
but I gotta save it.
Speaking of other toys, further down the way we have,
speaking of Transformers,
I believe we have a car also in the midst.
- Not a Transformer at all.
- I know, but we have a car.
labeled as a transformer, but there was a manufacturing disaster.
You have like, like, like, like, like,
a fingerprints on you of kids trying to break.
Yeah. Yeah. Most of my all the wheels have been ripped off.
One of the doors is gone because kids have been trying to turn me into a bug
every single time they see me.
Cool. I am a red car.
I am the most classic toy,
the most classic toy you could have.
I don't remember much about my life before,
but I remember that I had a red car.
So I became a red car.
The last thing I remember was I was driving down the Pacific
Highway in a red car.
And I think maybe I crashed and then I woke up.
Okay.
It's coming back to me.
I crashed my red car.
I, my head got chopped off by, because it was a,
It was a classic car, had very little safety features,
no airbag, red car.
My head flew out into the Pacific Ocean
all the way back around the entire world
and then landed in basically, well, maybe not my head,
my soul flew all the way around the world
and landed in Brooklyn in a red car toy
because basically I thought it was cool.
And now that I'm a car, I don't really even care
about becoming a human again.
I want, what are cars like?
Gasoline.
So I want to get one gallon of gasoline.
(laughing)
- I think it's all number-based goals so far.
- Yeah, I'm gonna be keeping a running tally
of how much money I get.
- Yeah, good.
Okay, and so speaking of hot rods,
we got quite the last toy,
way in the back of Mr. Hickory Bones' toy shop.
And who is this? And who were they?
Well, I'm the ideal top...
Who's this?
Hey, we're doing the D&D right now.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
(laughing)
- It's Pierce.
Hey Pierce.
(laughing)
Wave hi to everyone.
I'm the ideal top and the perfect bottom.
This dirty cock interactive fuck my cock masturbator delivers an incredible pleasure combination.
This stroker features life like fanta flesh skin combined with a super hot male voice
and powerful vibrations for an unforgettable sensory experience.
The handheld design offers up a tight asshole and stimulating tunnel.
The interior is soft and snug with a firm exterior shaft.
Featuring a built in rechargeable hi-fi speaker that delivers his irresistible voice.
This stud will tell you how good it feels and what he wants you to do with him with
every thrust.
He screams, moans, and begs you to yank his stiff shaft.
The powerful micro-bullet near the base provides extra stimulating vibration and concentrated
pleasure.
I became this item after a shootout with the police.
I was shot 16 times in the chest and then I fell into a vat of the phantom flesh mixer
almost exactly like Child's Play 3, where Chucky's blood coagulates into the dolls that
create the latex in Chucky's skin.
I was the...
I mean, based on the other two guys, I think I'm the only actual serial killer in the group.
And now my goal is to fuck somebody's bones out of their body.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- All right.
- So yeah.
- Bones.
- Good, great, great toy for child's play.
- Out of their body.
- I am doing this because you and Julio said that I should.
- You said don't do it man, it's a kid,
we're gonna be belonging to a kid.
- We're all sitting next to each other on the shelf.
- 18 year old, no me and Patches talked it out
and I have a different storyline than you guys.
- Well, you'll be a part of the same group.
- Yeah, be a part of the same group of toys
that belongs to a child.
- It'll make sense in a second.
- Yeah, it'll make sense who's buying me.
- The mom is gonna buy you for herself,
but she's gonna mix it up
and she's gonna give it to the kid.
- Let's make it make sense.
So, here you guys are in the toy shop,
well, in the mall, in the toy shop section,
over there in the top right.
Let me drop in Mr. Hickory.
I thought I had him in there.
Get him.
Let me go lock the door real quick.
You're going to lock the door in case somebody comes in?
In case Pierce tries to come back in, dude.
Perfect.
Mr. Hickory himself.
What was his full name?
Mr. Hickory Bones, actually.
Scary.
- Here a woman and a young boy walk in.
Do not pay attention to the boy looking like a soldier
in a fantasy setting.
- He's dressed up, it's Halloween.
- I know. - Yes.
- And that's why.
- Mom, I wanna be a fantasy soldier.
- Mm-hmm, that's what he said.
- Can you make me a fantasy soldier costume this year?
- The name of it, I think.
- Which one is Mr. Hickory?
- Can I be a top-down Roll20 character tile, Mom?
- Fantasy Soldier does kinda seem like a
Spirit Halloween-linked outfit.
- Yeah, yeah.
And so the boy and his mom walk in.
This boy is Gary.
He's a sweet young boy who,
(garbled speech)
who doesn't know it yet,
but he's got an enterprising future ahead of him.
And his mother is a neglectful bitch named Jossica.
- What else is new?
Yep, and she drags in Gary and she says,
"Come on, Gary!
"Come on, let's get you a toy!
"And let's get me a toy, too."
And she wanders on over to the section you think she would,
while Gary looks over at the toys that are there,
sees a Transformer, he sees a Batman, he sees a Pokemon,
and then he hears from behind him a Mr. Hickory Bones.
"Oh, young lad, is there a toy
that has caught your eye.
And Gary says, Oh, geez, I don't know.
I really like some of these toys, but
I want something a little different than just a Batman.
Well, I'm giving a thumbs up inside my box.
I'm giving a thumbs up.
OK, and I'm also holding the little toy size tape recorder
that's included with my box and I'm pointing to it.
I'm actually going to roll to see if he notices that
His insight is pretty good for for a child.
I'm chilling with the prospector from Toy Story two.
OK, cool.
He he looks up and he sees
he sees a movie goes, well, it's like doesn't he isn't quite
registered his movement yet?
You know, it's a little too not real to him, but he does.
Something's different about this one.
It's like, what's this one?
And Mr.
Hickory Bones comes over and with a almost skeletal hand,
he puts it on the young boy's shoulder and says,
This is a very special toy.
From a long ago, back when movies were movies.
- I do like movies.
- Yes, you do like movies.
And what about this one?
And he goes over to the red car.
Oh yeah, this is about to get good.
- Red car?
Does it transform?
- No, it doesn't.
- Doesn't transform.
- What about a classic toy?
Something that one doesn't just go out and get anymore.
One finds in say, an attic or under a bed.
An old classic toy, as perennial as the grass.
- Hmm, okay.
- And he takes the red car.
- What?
- And he takes the car and the lawyer.
That's right. He takes the car first. He took the car first.
He wants the client. He doubled back.
He doubled back. He was like, "Well, I already got the car."
Right. How could this be the perfect day?
He realized he wasn't satisfied with the car. The car wasn't enough for him.
No, it's not. No, he actually thought the car was more than enough.
Right. Jossica waltzes over.
She's knocking down shit as she's walking by.
She has her hand down. She's just knocking shit over with the...
Does she have a bra on? No.
And she has the-
Awesome, what do you think's knocking everything over?
Mm-hmm.
And she holds up the Pipe Dream Extreme Dirty Talk Interactive Fuck My Cock Masturbator.
And she goes, "Can I try it out?"
[Laughter]
And, uh, he goes, "Yeah."
"Why, of course you can."
Um, I'll- I suppose I'll just-
"Yeah, well you can watch 'em."
And she goes off to a back room.
- The back rooms?
- Wait, wait, this is actually scary.
- No.
- Okay.
- But maybe.
And she goes off to a back room off screen.
And you know what?
I don't wanna do this.
Pat, why don't you describe what she does to you?
- Well, you can guess.
- Well, okay. - No I can't.
- So she takes me out of the package, right?
And then as soon as she moves it,
the
- She said she has to pull a ripcord to start.
(laughing)
- But, she also has to do that.
- It's like a chain ripcord too.
It's like a metal chain.
(imitates chain)
- He had both extra phlegms going on here.
- And over that with the hi-fi speaker,
you can hear the voice go, "Hey baby."
- Yeah, all right.
Shut up.
- You shut up.
She just shoves it up there.
And it's like there's like nothing.
There's like no friction for like it feels like a mile.
And then finally, there's some there's something to go up against.
And it's not what you were used to when they tested you in the factory.
I did not even test me in the factory.
They just put me in a box.
They test each and every single one of them.
They don't tell you that. Yeah.
Well, yeah, they test them.
That's why they got they have realistic
Weighted balls.
That's what it says on the package.
So do I.
And uh, I don't believe you.
She does this for like, "Ahh, ahh!"
She does this for like a minute.
And then, um,
you don't feel like any
contractions, but you do hear
like a "grrrr"
and not from her mouth.
And she goes, "Ahh." Her stomach?
Yeah, and she goes, "Alright, yeah." And she takes it out.
And she uh,
put you back in the box. Is there a baby in there? And she goes over to... Is that a baby?
Is that a baby noise? Is that a baby? What noise is that? She goes over to the to Mr. Hickory
Bunch and says, "Yeah, I'll take it. Do you have eight others?" He's like, "That's the only one."
Okay. She picked the one that has a butt hole. But there is eight David Kleinfeld's on the shelf.
Mm-hmm. No, there's not bro. There's yeah, they can't move them in. Nobody has bought one since 1993
It's fully shocked do you want to try to get them to buy it you want to find a way to do that? Yeah
What are you gonna try to do door? Yeah door? I'll have the one at the back
We'll push them all off the shelf and have them all land in like cool pose each and a different cool pose like
They all alive
holding a clipboard.
Yeah, they're all alive.
They're all alive.
Okay.
Yup, I'm all of them, actually.
You're all of them? You're an army of David Kleinfelds?
Yeah, but each of the different possibilities
for how my soul got into a toy,
each one of them is a different one of those.
One of them is actually Sean Penn,
one of them is the character that escaped from the movie.
Yeah, the Sean Penn immediately tries to tie up
the nearest woman he could find and threaten her
with a baseball bat.
are figuring out their thing.
Yeah, okay.
Roll a, good God, performance check.
And based on that, we'll then see what happens
and maybe additional rolls.
- All right, let's see here.
Performance, well, performance, I have a plus one, so.
What did I get? - 10?
- 10. - Cool.
You managed to push over two other dolls.
Both of them do the worm simultaneously.
- Damn, badass. - Which is pretty good.
And Gary goes, "Hmm, I bet I could sell those maybe."
He's already thinking about being a C Enterprise.
And he says, "I'll take those as well.
"Mom, can I get them?"
And she goes, "Mmm, okay, that's yes."
And then they go up to the counter, they pay.
And before they leave, Hickory Bones says, "Do be warned."
What you have just bought may not be what it seems.
And they are already out the door,
they're in the car, they're gone.
- He's talking to nobody.
- Yeah, yep.
- He's talking to a wall.
- He's slowly losing his mind.
And now--
- Yeah, a guy who's in the pharmacy
across the mall hallway is buying a box of tissues.
And he's like, "What?"
- He doesn't, he doesn't hear it,
he hears it, he doesn't say anything,
he just puts the tissue box back.
(laughing)
Wipes his nose with his sleeve and just leaves.
And we are now in the home of Gary C. Enterprises
and his piece of shit mom, Jossica.
So you might be wondering, how did they get such a nice home?
- Is there a father in the picture?
- It's beautiful, man.
- This is an incredible home.
- They have a bunch of fried eggs.
- I'm seeing a white square.
I'm seeing a white square.
It's because Jossica, and good news for the three Kleinfelds, which I want to know what
the goal for each of those are.
We're all collectively trying to get a million dollars.
You only got three?
I thought it was eight.
They only bought three of them.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Probably wise.
We're all trying to collectively get a million dollars.
Jessica's great-grandfather died due to a misspelling on the will instead of
Jessica getting the money she did. And so now she has gotten all this money and
hired a designer to help design a nice home. Lord knows she has no
taste. And Gary C. Enterprises, in case it's not clear, lives there now as sort of a
new kid in town, he's, you know, wasn't rich beforehand,
doesn't really know what to do with all this money
and all this, his mom is still awful,
but he just wants to be happy.
And he's excited to get these new toys.
And he walks in and he's like,
"Oh boy, I'm gonna play with each of you."
And not that one, he points to his mom's toy that she got.
And he heads off to his room with the two toys.
- Just let him play with it.
- Yeah, why can't he play with it?
- He can't play with it?
I mean, he doesn't have to--
original song about how I wish I was a normal toy.
It's up to you.
You could do a ballad.
Mm-hmm.
I okay.
So I'm yours.
You wish that the kid would play with you?
Is that what you're going to do?
I wish, I wish that I wasn't, um, no, that's a good idea.
I wish that I died in a regular toy factory.
He's playing with us and you're getting all jealous.
Why won't he play with me?
Yeah.
Why won't he?
Well, I know why he won't play with me.
But, but sing it in your song.
Sing a song about it.
sing a song about why you're so upset that he won't play with you.
I wish I died in a normal toy factory.
Why did I try to rob the pipe dream factory?
And then you keep singing.
Is she doing this in the living room?
- No way.
(laughing)
- Seemed really fast.
- It's the master bedroom.
She's like sprinted in.
- Okay, now the bedroom where you have your couch,
and your two tables, and armchair.
- So some child's play,
and I thought that we were all supposed to be evil murderers.
- You thought that, you heard child's play,
and you thought to be a sexual, sex toy.
- I thought of the most evil thing.
- He didn't even know there was a movie.
- You heard child's play.
- This is so mean.
- No, 'cause child's play is a movie about an evil man,
and I thought that it was going to be a grown man.
I thought that this was going to be about grown stuff.
- What are you talking about?
It's literally about a doll killing a kid.
There's no grown men in it at all
besides the police officer.
- Well, I thought that the dad was going to buy it.
- There's no dad in the movie.
- Why would it make that better?
- Yeah, it's a single mom.
- I think that I fucked up my character so bad.
- No, I think you did a good job.
- It's good, it's good.
You just need to take more risks.
You need to think about--
- Yeah, just lean into it.
- Yeah, just lean into it, man.
- No, 'cause now I have a whole different subplot,
and I think I ruined the whole episode.
- No, you could be a--
- She's gonna get tired of you eventually.
- And you could be a father figure to this kid.
- Right now, you have an object,
we're just sitting here getting played
by some dumb loser kid.
- You have a chance to fuck her bones out of her body.
- First of all, you have to fuck her,
and you get to have sex with a woman,
which none of us will ever have the opportunity to do.
- Your goal is to fuck my pep talk.
I give up.
- Can I drive while she is sewing?
While she's doing that, can I drive in the gap
under the door and then in the box
so maybe she thinks that I go in her too?
- Roll a, yeah, roll stealth.
- Okay, I'm rolling stealth.
Oh my God, my stats are so bad.
Oh, I rolled it accidentally with advantage,
but the first one was an 18.
- That's great, yeah.
- Since you're in heavy armor, so you have disadvantage.
(laughing)
That's not advantage.
- God damn it.
- No, yeah, you-- - First one was still 18.
- Why are you wearing heavy armor?
- I don't know. - It still counts.
- It's a car. - You get the first one.
I don't know why you're wearing heavy,
but you still count the first one.
You make it through, yeah, you slide under the door,
and now you're in the room.
She, as you can see, is just on top of the machine
that is singing.
Who you can understand. - I wanna sit right next
to the open box of him,
so she does maybe get confused and thinks she bought two.
- Okay, cool.
I'll keep that stealth role and you can go in there.
Anything you're doing, Kleinfelds.
Yeah, so basically me, the three Kleinfelds are under the bed.
We're standing in a circle and we're talking to each other and
the three of us the main one.
I'm Davey and then there's Dave and David and we're like, all
right, Dave.
We got to make a lot of fucking money really fucking fast.
I don't know how we're going to fucking do this.
We got it.
Maybe we can rip someone off.
No, I don't and we're going around a circle and what's going
to happen is that Davey is going to send out Dave and David.
They're going to go out and they're going to get day jobs
and try to climb the corporate ladder.
And just since they're toys,
they don't really need to eat or have a place to live.
So they don't have, they have no expenses.
So they're just gonna go out
and go do some job interviews,
try to get into a law firm,
maybe start out as like a, you know.
- So we will head to a job.
- Davey will stay in the house.
Those two guys can go and be kind of offscreen,
passively earning money.
- Okay, I'm gonna put them.
- Those are my cookie clickers.
- All right, cool.
I'm gonna move them into the cookie clicker zone.
We might, maybe we'll see them later.
In the meantime, so yeah, she now,
Josska gets tired and she immediately falls asleep.
And, eh, eh.
- I've room one time to wake her up.
- And she goes over to the box where she put
the fuck toy in there, where she put Pat.
And--
- My new goal is to kill myself.
(laughing)
And she goes in there and she sees the car in there
and she goes, "Hmm."
And she goes to put it in her mouth first.
- I know she's holding me, but I still,
wheels going reverse, beep, beep, beep, beep, ah!
- And she drops you, scared.
- Okay, let's hurry off into a mouse hole.
- Yeah, okay.
- Oh my god, we should move into the mouse hole network
and befriend the mice.
- It's a very good idea.
- Yeah, you go in there and you do see a little mouse
with a newspaper and some glasses on.
And he's sort of startled by a car
crashing into his living room.
It's like, ah!
- I headlight flash SOS.
- It's her again, isn't it?
And he tries to use, he tries to pull you in.
He calls over his family.
And they're all starting to pull you in to the mouse hole.
Even the little kid is trying to help out, you know,
and they yank you in and yank you through the hole.
And they're all sort of looking at you now.
They're trying to understand, like, is he alive?
Like, what is this thing like?
Like to try to get a sense of you.
One of the kids goes in the in the car driver's seat and starts to honk the horn.
Oh, and he jumps out and his mother grabs him.
And the man who, the man mouse who helped pull you in says,
"I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were alive.
I saw SOS flashing, I assumed there was a driver."
- No, man, it's okay.
I'm just a mouse like you guys.
I just wanted to come.
I just, that big old lady tried to eat me,
but man, I just want cheese and shit.
Let's just chill.
- Roll deception with disadvantage.
- How, why?
- 'Cause you are not, they are mice,
so they know what a mouse is.
They have bad eyesight, famously, man.
Look at the smell and shit.
They have to fuck each other.
Can I walk into the mouse hole?
You can walk.
You, yeah, you just roll stealth.
It's gonna be a lower DC because she's asleep.
Me?
I got a four.
Okay.
Roll an interception roll.
Okay, cool.
And what'd you get?
Let me roll.
Sorry, it's, my thing goes so damn slow.
No, that's life, bro.
It's crazy.
Stealth.
It's fucking life.
10.
That's fine, that's perfect.
Okay.
walk in. Yeah. I'm like, "Oh, did I hear you say, did somebody say that somebody tried to
eat you? Did you say somebody tried to eat you?" That's... Yeah, she tried to eat me,
man. You know, that's assault with intent to digest. We could press charges. We could
really make something of this. Really? I think we could really, I think we could really get
a good result out of this lawsuit here. If you want to move forward, I'm your guy. I
don't know. Yeah, okay, well, here. Let's write the papers up and you can serve her.
I mean, she's right there.
All right, all I need is a $1 million retainer.
I've been walking--
That's a million, it's $1 million a year.
I've been walking into the kitchen
and I'm trying to jump into the blender.
(laughing)
He says--
Big dick, it's just waddling towards--
Waddling around in a Vitamix, just popping up.
It won't kill you.
No.
It won't kill you, it makes you more
- You're so durable, man. - Ribs for her pleasure.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah. - 'Cause you ribs.
- It was a rib for her pleasure. - It was a durable thing on her.
- Yeah. - Yeah, maybe just,
my goal is to just die.
At first I had all these big dreams,
but now I realize nothing's ever gonna,
nothing good will come from this.
So my goal is to just die.
- Your dream was to fuck someone's bones out of their body.
You were the closest to your dream of anybody else here.
- You had an opportunity. - Yeah, and then I,
I realized that I don't even,
what's the point of it all?
- You don't even like sex?
- I don't even, I tried it for the first time,
I don't even like it.
And now I just wanna die.
- It's listen, Mr. Talk?
Mr. Talk?
- My real last name was Renfro before this.
- Yeah, Mr. Renfro.
He waddles into the mouse home with the Vitamix
just spinning around his head.
- Really? - Yeah.
- I think I may have an opportunity for you.
If you're feeling your life is forfeit,
maybe we could work something out.
You know what I mean?
Maybe you could do a little something for me.
(groaning)
- Toys! - We could help each other out.
Maybe I'll help you.
You maybe fuck me.
- Oh, toys!
- I'm too big to even do that.
The only way that we could even do that
is if you crawled into the butt on my balls.
Gary Santerprise is looking for his toys now.
So he heads over to his mother's room.
You guys are not there though, as far as you can see.
Oh, I don't know where they are.
Toys!
Here, I push out the family of mice.
Ah, mice!
Here we are!
Oh, here are all your toys!
The father turns, he goes,
after we saved you, how could you?
And I block the door with my body.
I parallel park in front of the door.
Gary screams, mother wakes up, Jossica, she goes,
"What, oh, mice, those mice again!"
And she goes over and she takes out a bat
that says, "Mice killer."
And she just starts going crazy trying to kill these mice.
And she says, "That's it, this is not gonna work.
We're going, let's, come on, we're,
we're going to the office.
We're gonna go see your grandfather."
office. He'll help us with this. I'm tired of having to do everything myself.
Grand. Are we going in a car? Yes we're going in a car! And she's like, "Why did I
say that?" Guys, I think we have to go to the office. I think we have to go to the
office. I think that's the place to be. Mm-hmm. And what'd you say your
name was? Roofer? The sex toy?
My name was...
Renfair?
My name was Cody Renfro.
Renfro. It's also probably, I mean it's an office buddy, it's probably on a pretty high
floor you might be able to jump out of a window or something. Or you could just close yourself
in the corner. I knew a guy who killed himself that way. Alright, let's go.
Okay.
So, yeah, you guys present yourself. Gary's all happy to see his toys. Well, most of them.
Did the mice family get obliterated?
Yeah, they're dead and the mom
also just grabs
The pipe dream extreme just from the head takes it with the Vitamix doesn't remove it
Rags hidden throws it in the car
Katamari sex toy
Anything that is attached to it. She's gonna put in her body
Sticky after being up in her that anything it touches is permanently. Yeah
I've got M&M's and McDonald's fries on stuff
to me because of the car, because it's in a minivan.
Yeah, you're rolling.
I would like to under the under the front seat, just collecting every coin,
every coin and every.
Wait, no, not the coins, not the coins.
I'm in the couch cushions.
I'm rooting around.
I'm looking for I need I need to make a million dollars.
Well, you can put all the coins in my butthole.
No, I'm going to put them in my.
It's attached to the thing.
I'm gonna deposit them in my bank account.
That I have.
Would have given me some kind of purpose. I'm trying to find where they keep the gas in the car.
Where oh, yeah, I mean it's in the gas. Okay. I don't know that. You don't know where it is?
Okay. Yeah, I don't I'm just looking. We're just toys. I know that there's gas in a car.
But I don't know. Isn't it kind of interesting that there's parts of a car that are in the car,
but not in the car, you know, this is the kind of thing that I'm thinking.
A two different ends almost. Yeah.
Mm hmm. So then you then what do you get?
What are you trying to do then?
Like because so you're in the backseat right now with Gary
and he's like going like moving you around, going, I'm playing in a car, in a car.
Like he's like attempting to you.
So how do you what do you do to to get him off of your case in this case?
My fart.
(laughing)
You make the plastic that makes up the car
kind of burn slightly.
- Uh-huh.
- And like, he like puts you down for a second
and he picks up the Kleinfelds,
or the one Kleinfeld he has.
- Felt good so I keep doing it.
- Okay, you keep farting.
Sex toy with all the shit,
you're just on the ground now doing this?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm just trying to like,
I don't know. I'm collecting so much stuff that it's weighing me down and it's making me feel even worse.
If you want to kill yourself, you could try to get in the way of the gas pedal or brake or something.
I am. I'm putting the... I flopped the tip of my head right underneath the brakes so you can't hit the brakes.
Roll an athletics check.
Negative one.
I got a negative one.
You just shoot right up inside her.
And you got
meanwhile, red car.
You have this opportunity now to sort of try to explore
the inner workings of the car.
You find like a little hole.
It's not a well-maintained car.
Oh, my God.
Start to explore inside of it.
Now, I don't know enough about the inside of a car, to be honest.
I can't drive because I have no gas.
I can't drive anywhere.
So I walk.
So what do you do?
You walk with my four wheels.
Yeah. Like as if they're like, like putt putt.
Like putt putt. Yeah, I was going to say. Yeah. OK.
So you're putting into it.
You see after putting roll it actually a roll investigation check.
I think you have like minus five intelligence.
Hold the phone.
I'm holding it.
That's a two. That's a two.
You find the freon
for the air. Oh my God, gas! Yeah. And I start sucking it up. Yeah. Yeah, I don't know, I've
never drank in Freon. Do you know what happens after you drink it? You turn into cold. You
get cold. I think you turn into Mr. Freeze from Spat. You get ice powers. Oh! Blue car.
with ice powers you're blue now - now your blue car okay yeah and she slams on the
brake she's at the office she runs in there's like I'm gonna go see your
grandfather he needs to give us more money and money I need a million dollars
and you're in the office building floor first floor of the office and you see
now. I see the two David Kleinfelts are working here. Yep, they're already
working here. So they go over to confer with you and they say they've been doing
well. You can get tell you could say how they say that but they've been doing
well and that they're almost they're they're almost at about 500k right now.
They've been crushing it. Like an hour? Oh my god. They've been doing amazing. They're amazing
lawyers and there's two of them. They're really really good lawyers. I mean David
Klinefeld is a good lawyer. He's a nasty crook but and he betrays everybody in his
life but he's a good lawyer. Listen he acquitted Carlito Brigante. He got him
out of a 30-year stint. Yeah so they've been making money doing criminal
criminal representation litigation. They somehow made the office. They work for
the DA they made $500,000 a day. Oh Bluecar is here and he says room. I had to see if the
picture updated. It did I think. Yeah I got it. Yeah yeah nice. Yeah and so she's
marching you through the office and you get to the the top floor you get to the
office of the grandfather and he, Mr. Peter Griffin.
And he says, "Eh, what are you doing here?
"I thought I told you to eh, eh, meh."
- Okay, so what I'm seeing here is that not only
does he sound like a car beeping,
but he also is a character from a TV slash movie.
So I feel like me and Caleb's characters both have
some type of kinship with him.
- And he also has a cock. - And it's almost as if
he's our-- - True.
- He also has realistic balls.
- Yeah.
- So I feel like maybe-- - All three of you.
- I want to be best friends with this guy.
- Does he have a stapler?
- Yes.
- I try to staple my balls to the floor.
- Does it have pullable skin?
- Hey Doris, what are you doing here?
(imitates cat meowing)
Why do you got this thing?
What is this thing?
and he was holding you up, Pat, and waving you around.
He's got a Vitamix on it.
Ah, Grandpa, or my father.
- Wait, let's talk to his hand now.
He's part of me now.
'Cause I'm like a Katamari, so he touched me.
- Yeah.
- Wah, wah.
He's trying to shake you off.
- Wait, now Patrick controls him.
Now Patrick controls him.
- So here's the thing.
Yeah, this is maybe a good target for you guys
for possession.
Maybe even a three-way possession.
- Whoa.
- I try to possess him first.
- Okay.
- Well, I'm already stuck to him.
- No, but that's only an animate object
so you can Katamari.
You can't Katamari guys.
- To possess somebody, you have to knock them out cold.
So you have to beat them up, knock them out.
- I'm swinging the Vitamix.
- I just start driving kind of over and over into his foot,
kind of just doing nothing.
Okay, all you guys roll initiative.
Yes.
I'm swinging the Vitamix to try and hit him in the head.
I'm rolling initiative.
Okay.
Oh, I got a nat 20.
Me and Caleb both got nat 20s.
And I got a two.
All right, let me get the--
The one roll where the nat 20 doesn't matter at all,
we wasted it.
It does matter on Patch's system.
It does.
It doesn't if we both get it.
It's true, it's just whoever has the higher dex.
We both have the same decks.
It's whoever...
is blue.
I actually don't...
I guess re-roll.
It's whoever's better at the game Suica.
Re-roll.
Whoever has a higher win rate in the game,
the web game Suica.
I got a negative two somehow. Re-roll, bitch.
I re-rolled
and I got a negative two. Not you.
And I won the roll off.
I won the roll off with a five.
Ha ha ha ha bitch you got owned.
- All right, cool.
- Oh well.
- You got a five.
We got a, so we got, well really it's two 20s.
- Fuck, fuck, fuck.
- That's my guy, my, David Kleinfeld,
he knows that he rolled badly and he's like fuck, fuck.
- Blue car with his freeze powers.
Then we got David Kleinfeld with his lawyer powers.
Then it's Peter, Grandpa Peter Griffin.
And then it's Pat,
aka-- - Pipe Dream Extreme
Dirty Talk Interactive Fuck My Cock Masturbator.
- Just calling you Pipe Dream.
Cool, hi.
It's just easier for me, that's all.
I'm sorry, it's not like a big deal.
All right, here, okay, we're in the corner office over here.
- Whoa, this is a big ass office.
- Yeah.
Oh, I got a ton of-- - Oh, there's toilets in it?
- Going forward, yeah, there's toilets right in the center.
So if you want to use the center console for toilets.
All right, cool.
So first of all, you have also the mom
and Gary to contend with.
So I don't know how you guys want to handle them.
'Cause they are also here.
- I don't care about them.
I'll, I'm, I'm, I'll fuck it mask off.
- Okay, cool.
So you're up. - This is the part
of the movie when the mom finds out that Chucky is alive.
- You're up, blue car.
It's up to you.
- I am going to use my freeze ability.
- Cool.
So I can tell you what that'll do,
'cause we don't have it written down,
but it will shoot a 30 foot cone of frost damage.
- 30 feet?
(laughing)
- I'm one half of it.
- What?
- From a toy car, it comes out of the headlights.
- Can you imagine a bug breathing fire?
(laughing)
- Do you think a dragon amount of fire?
- Okay, and I would like to, does it have a,
Is there a possibility to freeze them?
- Yes, there is.
They're gonna have to roll a con saving throw
to see if they get frozen.
- Okay, I'd like to put all three in my cone
and then freeze them, my snow cone.
- All three of your what?
- All three of them, the women, children, men.
- Okay.
- In my snow cone and freeze them.
- You're gonna have to step out of the place.
- Okay.
- You'll sort of zoom back here.
And you'll just.
- Just walk in the office.
is seeing a small car zoom out of an office room.
And it just...
(laughter)
It's a giant cone of ice.
Okay, I...
Cool, yeah.
I coned them.
Alright, cool.
I'm gonna roll for them.
It's a deck saving throw and then a con saving throw.
So let's see how they do.
Okay, he saves.
She saves.
He does not save.
Better be Peter.
And he...
Okay, yeah.
So they both take half damage, so roll 4d8.
Okay.
16.
Okay, so they both take eight damage.
So they are still alive, the two who got hit.
Which is the boy and the-- Yeah, and the mom.
But barely, they are holding on by a thread.
What about the third?
The third?
Oh yeah, him? He failed both in his deck saving throw and he failed in his ability to not be frozen.
So he is-
So he's frozen?
He's frozen. He is virtually incapacitated.
So this would be- you like have a chance here on your next turn to possess him.
Amazing.
Right.
Um, uh, yeah the boy right now and the mom are just like shivering cold.
The mom doesn't understand what's going-
"Why? Why? Why?" Like she somehow gets it more than anyone that there's something going on.
You like it, bitch.
Beep, beep, beep, beep.
Cameron's getting Mio out of the front door. I'm going to get a glass of water while he does that.
For sure. Yeah. The boy is Gary C. Enterprise is in shambles on the floor,
or vowing to never buy a toy again
and to only make sound investments in hot soda
and cold dog startup type enterprises
and to never have fun.
- It's ruining his whole life.
- It's ruining his whole everything.
One toy.
- One toy has ruined his life.
- This is what Chucky's about.
It's about how toys can do that.
- Well, it's two toys.
Okay, I am returned.
- Cool.
So what happened was, was he froze the, he froze Peter Griffin.
He, um, nearly killed the two, the two other characters, but Peter Griffin's
frozen and incapacitated, so he can be, um, possessed now by you guys.
All right.
Is it my turn?
Is your turn.
Okay.
Uh, I, um, I'm going to go up to blue car.
And I'm going to start hitting him with a paper clip like it's a
crowbar a bunch of times. And I'm going like, "Fuck you, you
fuck you and your goddamn wheels." The world of toys, it's
every toy for himself. And you got to fucking learn that you
self-righteous car, you and your coat of the streets. You think
you're so great because you and I'm just beat. I'm trying to
kill out beat man what a beat roll an attack roll because that's right I'm a
betrayer well I'm honking the lawyer and everything I do is for myself I'm
honking as you and not the polite honk from curb your enthusiasm buddy a mean
honk mmm a defensive honk what is your a 1114 you miss bitch
- Yeah, with that heavy armor.
- It's just a paperclip.
(laughing)
- He has heavy armor.
- I am hitting you, but it's just going, ding.
- Yeah.
- And not really gonna--
- You're smart, you tried to use the paperclip
to reset me, man.
- And now it's Peter Griffin's turn.
- I'm blinded.
- He is frozen, he's not gonna get out of that
for a little bit, so he is just frozen there.
The two other characters are just in shock as well.
So it is your turn, Fucktoy, Pipe Dream.
You are right next to him.
He dropped you and you fell behind the desk
as the cone of ice flew over.
So you did not end up getting frozen with Peter Griffin.
- But you can-- - He's Vains?
- You can possess him.
- I don't know what Vains is, but it says racial fucking.
- You're a guy, you had a backstory.
- Racial fucking.
Why does that say racial fucking?
- I don't know. - It says fuckling.
- That's my race.
My race is a fuckling.
- Vains, racial fuckling. - This is the class I made.
I don't think I have a bro you made racial fuckling with veins what has
happened what happens with you use veins what is racial I think it really does
like a Christopher Hitchens insult no I don't like saying that I think veins is
an attribute sir sure what are you trying to do me I'm trying to kill Peter
Peter Griffin and then my, well, if I get into his body,
will I not want to kill myself anymore or?
- You can only answer that.
- I guess the possession would make me
not want to kill myself.
I realized all too soon, I realize,
okay, so in this moment I realize
that if I become human again,
then I will have a part, like I can, you know,
use my thumbs, I can go and walk around and stuff.
(laughing)
I can go on a, like if I possess him,
everything in my life is gonna change.
- Could use my thumbs.
- Yes, dude. - So, I'm gonna try,
I'm still in the room, right?
- Oh, yeah.
- I'm next to Peter Griffin.
- Yeah, they are having like an inter-toy conflict.
- Yeah, okay, then I'm gonna try and possess,
I'm going to try to do the, what's it, the ritual of Dabella.
I'm going to try and do that.
- What do you chant?
- Hey Dabella.
Not really, I fucked up.
I fucked up.
I had a shootout with the cops
and it kind of made me realize,
this is less like child's play
it's more like the movie Fluke.
Uh...
- Debella says, I don't know Fluke.
What's Fluke?
- Fluke is a movie about Eric Stoltz
uh... being reincarnated
as his family dog
and watching his friend from work
steal his wife and he can't do anything
about it because he's a dog. - Oh, I know about this movie.
Yeah. - Um...
I guess it's more like Fluke that uh...
uh... losing my form
my...
My human form has made me realize that life is precious, and I shouldn't end the lives of others
I'm actually turning a new leaf. I shouldn't end the lives of others and wait you're gonna
I can take this this guy. I'm just gonna lead a normal life after this
The worst possible result
What do you mean
I'm gonna get away with all my crimes, and then I'm just gonna walk away scot-free
'Cause I died in the toy factory.
- Do you think that's a good result
for a murderer to walk away free?
Reveals a lot about your internally held beliefs.
- So, Democrat, here's how this works.
You can possess him uncontested right now.
He is frozen solid.
- Well, I'm just gonna do that then.
- So you can do that.
You will be frozen solid now.
You two have a chance.
The second, like you guys each have a chance
to like be able to possess Peter Griffin.
If you do it like,
(laughing)
stupid sentence.
- So dumb.
- You guys each have a chance to do it.
You can either do it and it'll be like a contest.
But right now, Pat is gonna have a like plus three
on the rolls in those contests because he got there first.
- Okay.
- Each of you have a chance, or you can work together.
Those are your options.
- Davey Klinefeld is not interested at all.
Like he probably is.
He probably would be interested in possessing, but he's way too.
He wants to drag everybody down.
He can. That's what he cares about a lot more.
So I don't even I won't roll to try to possess.
I'll just try to stop them and try and kill them before they can do it.
OK, so you're up, Blue Car. What do you want to do?
I want to possess Peter Griffin, man. OK.
So you roll up to him and now it's going to be just a straight D20 contest.
OK, here I go.
And you roll as well.
Fuck Vibrator.
Oh, fuck me.
I got a 8.
I'm also doing a contest?
If you want to possess.
Well, how can I not?
Holy shit.
I'm trying to get them to stop.
I'm trying to kill them.
I guess while they do that.
I don't know how they're going to handle it for me.
On your turn, you can just attack in that case.
Okay.
All right.
I'm sorry.
Well, sorry, Blue Car.
I just want one fucking gallon of gas.
There are other people you could try to possess.
You can finish knocking out the mom or the boy.
The kid is too young, nobody's gonna sell gas to a kid.
The mom?
It's Gary C. Enterprise.
The mom probably doesn't even know how to pump gas.
Wait, I wanna possess Gary C. Enterprise.
Okay, he has two HP left.
If you knock him out right now.
I'm gonna knock him out right now.
Okay, roll with advantage.
Okay.
Nice. With that dagger, you knocked him out cold.
And you can now--
- I used my dagger that I come with.
I come with a two-inch recorder, a clipboard, and a dagger.
(laughing)
- And the boy is knocked out.
You take over his body.
- Okay, I'm in it, I'm in it?
- You're in it.
And you're not frozen solid.
- I would just, I'm just gonna leave
and exit the adventure.
- You're leaving?
- Yeah, I just wanted to make it canon
that Gary's the Enterprise and the other campaigns we did
that all along he was secretly the character
David Kleinfeld from "Frozen."
(laughing)
- Which makes sense, he's scheming, you know?
Maybe he gets a little bit softer as he gets older.
- So maybe this will change,
maybe some of this will come into play.
So I just wanted to make a permanent change to the lore.
So yeah, I'm just gonna walk out,
walk off the screen and never be seen again.
- Yeah. - Me?
- You just run away into the woods, blue car.
- I just go out of the door like Pokemon style.
I just hear, "Shoo, shoo, shoo, shoo, shoo,"
and I'm gone into the blackness.
- Yeah, you see your two other Kleinfelds
are just hard at work.
Like, "Wait, what about the billion dollars?"
And they see you walk out.
- They're at each other's throat.
They're both backstabbing each other.
- Yeah, yeah, love it.
- He doesn't want any part of it.
- I am going to knock out the mom and take over her body.
- Okay, roll an attack, roll with advantage.
with it. Wait, so I am Peter, frozen Peter Griffin right now. You're frozen Peter Griffin.
So I'm just waiting to defrost. Once we're ahead of initiative, it'll happen much quicker.
I use my spear and I hit her. Yeah. Roll for damage. And it's a 20. Yeah, she's knocked
out cold. 6. Nice. You take over her. You feel the worst anyone can ever feel. Yeah,
I feel really bad.
Just bodily, it's not all right.
I feel like there's a hole in my...
Will I have a hole?
Yeah, you hear that noise now.
(growling)
Like loud and clear.
Like holding a seashell up to your ear.
I'm just hearing ocean.
She hears it all the time.
Okay.
Not just when she comes.
Well, I wanna get out of this body fast,
but I have a mission to accomplish.
Wait, so now she's in the toy?
'Cause it's a switch-a-roo, right?
No.
No, I knocked her out.
The toy is now empty.
I'm going to pick up the blue car and I'm going to go out to the parking lot of the office
and siphon some gas.
Okay, cool.
You go do that.
While you're doing that now, Peter Griffin is now unfrozen.
He still has some HP.
You're still him.
Holy crap.
What do you want to do?
Holy crap!
I'm free!
I'm free from being a sex toy!
A poorly thought out character!
And then I pick up the sex toy.
I pick up the sex toy on the ground, the Pipe Dream Extreme Dirty Talk Fuck My Cock Masturbator.
And I shove it up my butt.
Yeah, cool.
Basically you're shoving your dead body up your own butt.
Yeah, shoving my own dead body up my own butt.
And guess what happens?
What happens?
- What happened?
- You die?
- All of my bones shoot out of my mouth.
- Fuck yes, yeah.
(laughing)
You did it.
- I didn't want to do it.
I thought that it's a Tales from the Crypt style ending.
- Amazing.
- Where I accidentally got what I wanted.
- Oh wow, that's amazing.
- I got what I wanted, but at what cost?
- You did an amazing job.
You did it.
I love that.
- Wow.
That was great.
And you siphon gas, mom?
- Okay, yeah, so I pick up the blue car.
- That's so good, Package.
- I bring it outside.
I see a Ford Fiesta.
I take a piece of,
a piece of,
like a water hose that's attached to the building,
attached to the hookup.
Put one side in the tank,
the other side in my mouth.
And this lady's got some suction action going on.
- Of course she does.
So I do a deep pull and oh my God,
I can already hear the gas, here comes the gas.
I put the blue car on the ground
and I just kind of dump a bunch of gas
on a blue Hot Wheels car that's sitting on the ground.
And then I leave this body and I go back into the car.
I don't wanna be this disgusting body.
- Oh, I love it.
- I finally have gas and I pull out onto the road
and this is what happens.
I'm in the bike lane.
I'm going about four miles an hour.
It's fast for a toy.
Call it's all an ass.
Yeah, fuck.
It's really fast.
You run out of gas really fast.
And only it's only it didn't really last.
It was one gallon, but it barely any of it got in me.
She was just kind of spraying it on me.
So I go about 30 feet.
I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm
like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm
I go about 30 feet.
- Yeah.
- And then the song ends.
- I like the idea of like,
the horror movie character.
You're the only one who's like,
has like a consistent potential horror background
where you just possess people for like 30 seconds at a time
to get them to siphon gas for you.
(laughing)
- I'm trying to make it all the way through
Life is a Highway by Rascal Flatts.
20 seconds at a time.
And now also I'm so far away from the office at this point.
It's gonna take me hours to just crawl back.
- Yeah, the trailer would just be like,
yeah, something weird happened.
I just started sucking on gas.
And it's like, that's what everyone says.
And then there's no horror.
- You drive by me, I'm the kid,
and I have like another, I've cornered another kid
in the schoolyard, and I'm like,
I don't know what to tell you.
I got you out of detention.
You owe me, you owe me.
You owe me a dessert, you owe me pudding.
and I'm just, I'm really getting up.
- Yeah, you're finessing.
- And yeah, I'm completely--
- I love it.
- Does it work? - Destroying him.
- Do you get the pudding?
- No.
He starts, he gets his friends to beat me up.
- And so it goes.
And that's, and happy Halloween.
- The bag of Peter Griffin flesh
is sitting on the office floor.
- It's more than a bag, it's blown everywhere.
- Yeah.
I must have missed something crazy when I went to get that Amazon packet.
You really did.
Patrick exploded Peter Garnett.
He did a good job, we'll tell you about it.
Happy Halloween everyone.
Happy Halloween.
A blue car.
And also missed the poop.