(sipping)
(burping)
- You're listening to Beers We Drink,
America's number one beer podcast.
(record scratching)
(upbeat music)
- What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
(burping)
- This is a journey into--
- Into the middle of--
- Plain and clean--
- Bud Light.
♪ Food Rippin' ♪
♪ Beers we drank, motherfucker ♪
♪ With Juvio, Caleb, and Rex ♪
- Beer. - Uh-oh, uh-oh.
- Here it comes, here it comes.
- It's beer time, here it comes.
- Oh, God.
- Here, I'll do my answer. - It's a cool cap of.
- That does not look like a beer, man.
I'm gonna be real, that looks to me like a liquid death.
- Guys.
- Show me.
- You, I think, you know, I have never been
to the U.S. in my entire life.
and walking around here I was like,
I wonder what the beer situation's like
in this beautiful country,
this beautiful big, big ass country.
And I found the most badass beer in the entire world.
It is a tall boy. - You are a cringe man.
- It is completely black,
it has an insane skull on it,
and it literally has death on it.
Like that'll even kill people who die drinking this.
Check it out.
- Okay, but it says sparkling water on it.
- Bro, here, okay, I don't wanna interrupt the flow.
- Oh, you're right.
- Go ahead and give it a taste test and a review.
- Oh, it's so light, I can't even taste the alcohol.
(laughing)
- You are over, you are done for.
This is the last straw for me, man.
- Yeah, you can't do that.
- I was joking.
- Oh, thank God.
- It was my joke.
- I actually know what a sparkling water is.
Thank you very much.
- I don't know why you opened this.
- Give it a sparkling water rating.
- I think you're stupid, I don't like sparkling water at all.
I should just give this to my girlfriend.
- This dude bought a $2 joke.
That's $400 Mexican dollars.
- Yeah, that's pretty penny.
- I don't wanna talk about money right now.
I wanna cry, I wanna start crying.
- Stop, do not talk about money, stop.
- So I saw this big ass Shiner Rock beer can.
- Shiner Bock, you said rock.
- Shiner Bock.
said Shiner Rock. It looks like it said rock on my end. Yeah what's that Jade? Anyways,
Shiner Rock. I saw an awesome ad for it and I was like whoa. It said something about luxury
or some shit. I forgot what it said. It does look luxurious. It's in a golden can. It's
a golden can. That's not cheap. And I saw it and I was like wow I gotta have it and
now I'm gonna drink it. Alright what's the rating? It tastes just like any other light
beer and have never tasted in my entire life.
Okay, numerical and basketball play.
Shiny Rock, the same, what's there's like a...
It's like lighter than a Bud Light.
Which is not great I guess.
Well maybe it is if you don't drink like a thousand of these.
I'll say it's like a 6.5.
Okay, that's pretty good actually.
That's not bad.
I mean I don't hate it, I just think it's like super light.
It's like barely any alcohol over this one, basically.
Yeah, it is more though.
Okay, you guys.
I have a long-standing feud with this brand.
It is called, referred to as its name, Montauk.
So here's the thing with Montauk, man.
They make a watermelon beer.
And the first, and I think only time I've had this beer, I thought that it was going
to be a watermelon seltzer because it just says watermelon in big letters.
Turns out it was a fucking beer. So I hated it. Zero. And also zero inches. I know that, I mean,
you tell me if that's good or bad. That's bad.
But I'm giving him another chance. Montauk, I'm a nice guy. I'm a courteous, sweet guy.
I'm going to give you one more try. So I got the summer ale. And what sounds better
than a summer ale from a brand called Montauk.
Guys, this is a vacation spot that people come
from all over the universe to go to.
This is going to be good.
- Where's Montauk at? - Here I go.
- I think it's like a Shandy.
- I don't remember where Montauk is.
- It's a Shandy?
What's a Shandy?
- Montauk is somewhere in New York.
It's like Long Island or some shit.
- I love New York. - Okay, here I go guys.
Hmm.
- Yeah, I did it again.
- Is it a beer or is it a--
- Maybe take a third sip.
- This is, you know what,
Rex, that's not a half bad idea, my friend.
Okay, all right.
To all of my reverse sober gophers out there
who love drinking and enjoy ales of all kinds,
run, don't walk to your nearest beer store
and get a Montauk Summer Ale.
Guys, this is an 8'1" and a 6'9".
- Wow.
That's an unprecedented score.
- What's the taste of the summer?
- Guys, this has notes of different fruits.
- Such as?
- Such as a medley.
- Okay.
Which comprise of?
- Hold on, let me take one more sip.
It has a, it's on the hoppy end.
- Okay.
- I wouldn't quite call it a pale ale.
It doesn't have that kind of classic IPA bitterness to it,
but it has the refreshingness.
It's very hoppy.
But, and it's not a lager.
There's nothing deep about it.
There's nothing dark about it.
This is a great beer if you're on a boat or a kayak
and you don't wanna go home.
You never want it to end.
This would be a good beer for you.
- Okay.
- Guys, there it is.
That's my review.
I think before Rex goes, I want to say a couple of things.
Number one, the Shining Rock is actually
going down really smooth.
But I actually do feel that it does have alcohol in it.
So I would like to revise my rating and give it a 6.8.
Because I really hate harsh beers that I can't drink
and I make faces.
That's a good man.
I think that might be one of your highest ratings ever.
I think-- I don't know-- a single height in feet.
Also, I want to say Rex's beard looks so strange from where
I can see.
It looks like a painting that's been wrapped into a can.
- It does look like that Machine Girl album.
- Yes.
So I guess I'll introduce my beer.
I asked my roommates when they went to the grocery store,
I said, "Find me a weird beer."
(laughing)
- I've made this mistake before.
- So they got me a Thin Man Brewery, Trial by Wombat.
- Wow.
Wow, that is an actually repulsive can.
That is so fucking repulsive.
What kind of beer is this?
Because this is giving me no information.
This is obviously an India Pale Ale.
Okay.
It was either that or a sour.
Yeah.
Hopped with galaxy.
I don't know what that means.
That's the world.
I have a strong feeling you're about to find out.
I think he's been sipping it and he still doesn't know what it tastes like.
If I had to say what it tastes like,
it's like if someone put a Bud Light
and an IPA down in front of you,
and then blindfolded you,
and you picked up the Bud Light,
but you thought it was the IPA,
that's what it tastes like.
So it tastes like a light beer
where you're imagining there's more hops in it.
- That's kind of what this tastes like, I guess,
this Montauk.
Maybe they might be a little bit similar.
- It seems as though--
- It tastes like someone's feeding you an IPA
from like four feet away.
- Maybe you're drinking a Bud Light.
(laughing)
Okay, that made no sense.
Feeding you a drink from feet away.
- Four feet away.
(laughing)
- Like it's just, like the IPA is just a little far away
from the rest of the beer.
- So here's a good way to describe it.
It's like drinking a Bud Light, but smelling an IPA.
- Yes.
- Oh, that's perfect.
- Maybe that might be a little better of a description
than just drinking it from a long way away.
(laughing)
Maybe a big straw with a bunch of loops in it.
Guys, are you catching up on the trend
that we're kind of setting ourselves up to?
I think everyone loves Bud Light.
I think the cancellation of Bud Light has to end.
It's over.
And Bud Light has to get three new spokesmen
for the brand new marketing campaign.
Well.
Kid Rock drank Bud Light.
He did?
He squashed the beef?
He got caught drinking Bud Light.
He got caught.
- Well, he didn't want to waste it.
Was he shotgunning it?
- No, he was drinking it in a normal way.
- Yeah, he was like at a stadium
and someone took a photo of him
from down at the peasant seats.
- In a box.
- Yeah.
- And you know those boxes don't just have Bud Light.
They have Blue Moon.
- Yeah.
Which the only beer gayer than Bud Light is a Blue Moon.
So, they've got, what's the, they got a Fat Tire?
Fat Tire is one of my dad's favorite beers.
- Yeah, those are beers men in their 40s drink.
- Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
And they're like, "Oh, I'm gonna get into beer.
"Let me get the slightly more expensive one
"at the grocery store."
They don't know what the fuck's going on.
- They don't have a clue.
- They've never rated a beer based on the height
of the person that might drink it.
- Yeah.
- These people are fucking stupid.
- I feel like I'm a beer expert at this point.
- We are beer experts.
We drink more beer than almost anybody,
like in terms of variety.
- That's true, actually.
I've never had a more varied consumption of beer
in my entire life than I have this past couple of months.
- Yeah, true.
How susceptible do you guys think you are
to falling into those sort of rabbit holes
where you just get into a thing?
- 100%.
- 100%, I think all men are susceptible
to hobbies, they call them.
- I think I could, well, not just like a hobby,
but just something stupid, like getting into gay beers
or something that I caught myself before I came into this trip
is I bought a safety razor
because I saw one TikTok of a guy being like,
they're good for you.
I was like, okay, I'm gonna buy one.
And I bought one and I didn't know how to open it.
So I didn't use it for like some weeks.
And then right before my trip,
I finally figured out how to use it.
And the tutorial that I watched of a guy
like shaving himself, he had like a brush,
he had a whole thing.
And I was like, maybe I should buy all these
fucking stupid shit. - Wow.
- And I was like, you know what?
I'll just buy some aftershave and I'm gonna be done with it.
I don't wanna get into this, this is too stupid.
- I get made fun of by my wife,
who is out of town by the way,
when the wife is away at the mice show play.
The bed is not made behind me, you'll notice.
'Cause I didn't ask her. - That's the mice playing.
- Looks the same as always.
- 'Cause nobody made me do it this morning.
- And there's a backpack on it.
- And there's a backpack, which is supposed to go
in the cubby, but I don't give a fuck.
- And the drawer behind you is slightly ajar.
- Good.
I'm gonna take out the drawers and put food in 'em.
(laughing)
Yep, I'm crazy.
What was I saying?
- Something about getting made fun of.
- She makes fun of me because I get into things
pretty often for about two months.
That's the interval for me.
Two months.
Last thing I was into was watches,
and I keep buying single watches.
- That's crazy.
- I watch a bunch of videos about the way watches work
and the movement of watches.
- This bro's watching watches.
- I was watching watches.
I was watch it, I was watch it watching.
- Yeah.
- And it was, I mean, it's, I like shit like that.
I've always said if I had the money and a garage,
I would be a model train guy.
- Why do you need a garage for that?
I could have sworn you were going
in a different direction with that.
Why not like a basement?
- That's fine too.
Yeah, that's fine.
Any extra space, if I had an extra room,
maybe I would even be a model train guy.
I have all this shit, I don't need--
- Do you have lofted ceilings?
High ceilings in your apartment?
- Decently high ceilings.
You're thinking I could put it around the top,
like a Christmas decoration? - Yeah, like a vertical,
yeah, use the vertical space. - That's a pretty good idea.
- That would be insane.
What you could just do when your wife is away,
she's going to be like-- (laughing)
- Hands over her eyes, like a home makeover video.
- Yeah, I know, I--
- Maybe, I got a surprise.
- Right at the top of her hand range.
- Her corner vision?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, she's like, try to make it as long as you can
before she notices.
Because what is she gonna do?
Is she gonna clean the ceiling?
- Yeah, you've got a little remote that like turns it on.
- Maybe that's how I could sell it,
is I maybe put some kind, you know those Swiffer dusters?
Put one of those on the front.
And I say like, I was just thinking with my brain,
using my noodle, and this is how we're gonna dust
the corners of the apartment.
No more cobwebs in this apartment.
Mm-hmm.
It'd be cool if there was really strong magnets,
and you could say you were cleaning the window
by getting those, like, magnet cleaners.
But on the inside, it's just a big TV,
and you just kind of move it. Yes.
Oh, I'm tired.
I've been cleaning the window all day long.
By the way, that -- that --
I don't even know why you said "window cleaner."
That is just the most crazy stretch invention
I've ever heard in my life.
A magnet window cleaner that is a TV?
Yeah, well, they've got those, the window cleaners that are magnets
from like the outside, right?
I haven't seen these.
I know what you mean.
Yeah.
There's like a brush part, like a, like a soft cloth.
Oh, so it brushes the outside?
Right.
And then you've got it on the inside.
So you can sit in there and just do like this.
These are also like very common to like, just like clean, like the inside of a,
like fish tanks when you don't want to like check all this shit out.
- Yeah. - That would really help me out
'cause I'm paying upwards of two or $3,000 a year
to have these guys come clean my windows.
- Yeah, you could get down there with a big hose
and kind of put your thumb over it really tight
and shoot straight up.
- Yeah, these guys, they hate me, man.
I insist on walking around with a towel
right above my nipples all the time
and just dropping it at the perfect time.
My penis is covered by their helmet
if there were to be a camera behind them.
They do not like me.
- And just think, you could spend $400
on really expensive magnets.
- Yeah.
- $1,600 on a new flat screen TV.
- I did get the A-OK to get a new TV the other day.
- Yo!
- Wait, how big we talking?
- How big?
- Guys, my wife--
- It's gonna be so small.
- My wife is prepared to go--
My wife is prepared to go as large as 42 inches.
(laughing)
Guys, this is huge.
- Damn.
- This is fucking huge.
- Dang.
- That's a five inch difference.
- You're gonna put the big game on there?
- Oh, I'm gonna put the big everything on there.
Everything's gonna look big on there,
'cause it's a big TV.
- Yeah, I will say I did just get a 42 inch TV
and I do feel that it's pretty big.
- It's a decent size, I have a small apartment,
I feel like it's not too small.
And also, I do think it's a little corny
to have a TV so big that it is like too big.
You know what I mean?
- You say that, but it is fun.
- I'm putting it somewhere right now.
I don't know, I'm putting it somewhere right now.
- Yeah, well, but that's different being,
I mean like, if you go to like a couple's house
and they have just a giant TV that dominates the room.
- That means the man wears the pants.
- The TV should, well, I wear pants.
- That means the man--
- No, you don't, you don't wear pants.
You just told us you don't wear pants.
You walk around with your--
- I wear the pants, my wife is out of town
and guess what, you guys?
When I came back from the park with the dog today,
which is one of my chores,
I didn't wipe his paws off when he came inside.
- Come on.
- So he got dirt everywhere.
- You're so naughty.
- And I'm not gonna clean it until right before she gets home
so she never notices.
- I can already tell how this is gonna go.
- They should make a tape measure
that measures 60 inches is 42 inches.
- That would be useful for a lot of shit.
- Yeah.
- I can only think of--
- Yeah, look at my 200 inch penis.
- Yeah, women don't know how long an inch is.
You just get a tape measure, see?
- 10. - Yeah.
- Told you.
- Biggest in the world.
Jonah Falcon can blow me.
- Rex is on some handyman shit.
- Yeah, I've been hanging stuff lately.
So I hung my big TV, I hung my smaller TV,
bought some shelves, built some shelves, hung them.
- Amazing.
- He's been so, so productive and so handy.
Rex, why don't you give us a little tour
of your desk right now?
- Oh, sure, yeah, so.
The desk door, the favorite segment of many fans.
The trial by walnut.
- Let's take a look at what's right here.
Oh, what could that be?
- Oh my God.
- Just all in a week's worth since I set up my desk.
- Until you set up your, what do you mean
until you set up your desk, take it to the kitchen,
throw that away.
- After I set up my desk, you know,
just like it's been like a week, you know.
- That is lunacy.
all those in the last week.
Have you thought about investing on a little trash bin,
as they call it in the UK?
Yeah, a bin.
A bin?
Bin service.
There's just little tiny bits of...
That's why you put a bag in it.
You're saving them for later.
No, I got to take them to the sink
and then empty them into the sink
and then put them into the recycle bin.
But what a lot of people don't realize
is that from your bedroom to your kitchen
is probably about two or 300 miles.
Right.
This is not, this is going to, you're going to be, I mean, you're going to be
crawling on your hands and knees begging for water by the time you get there.
It's probably 10 feet.
In terms of routing, I need to go all the way, maybe like three feet.
As soon as you say all the way, I'm out.
Yeah.
I hate going all the way.
I don't need to know the rest of it, guys.
Yeah.
I probably need to walk another 10 feet.
So it's probably like 20 feet.
Guys, there is some big news for all the men in the world.
What is it? Sam Sulek is starting his fall cut. I don't know who Sam Sulek is. He is a
21 year old bodybuilder who is on more steroids than probably any human being in
the world. Look up a picture of him right now. The guy that was like having
trouble breathing? Yeah he's always... Get the fuck out of here you fucking dog!
- Dog.
- That guy is like his dog.
- Yeah, he's always--
- Is that him not cutting?
Is that him bulking?
- He's cutting now.
- But I'm saying when he like,
that video that went around where he couldn't breathe.
- Yeah.
- Is that him bulking?
- Yes, yeah.
- Oh my God.
- So he eats like 7,000 calories a day.
- Yeah.
- Oh my God, dude.
- And every morning he drinks a gallon of chocolate milk
for breakfast.
And this guy is a hero to me and many, many others.
You guys should see the comments.
I watch every one of his videos.
They're 40 minutes long.
It's just him working out
and talking about the workouts he does.
You should see the comments on these videos, man.
People are like, "Sam, you changed my life.
I used to think you should eat vegetables and fruits.
I just recently realized that that is gay.
And now I drink chocolate milk for every meal.
And I wake up, I cook a steak the night before,
put it on my nightstand, wake up and eat it.
Yep, this guy's massive.
This guy's, yeah, that's him.
I mean, this is the ideal male physique, guys.
But I just thought you guys might want a little update.
He started the cut, he's on day two.
- That's so crazy.
Do you think that guy's gonna make it?
- Make it to what? - I mean, to what?
- 400 pounds? - To another year?
- Probably another year. - I think he's got at least
three good years left in him.
- Yeah, well he's 21, let's see, Ziz,
Ziz, Ziz, never learned how to say his name.
He died at what, 26, 27?
- Yeah.
- And I would, oh, wait, hold on.
- No!
- I never knew that guy used to,
I know he's like a meme.
- Yes, he's just an old bodybuilding forum guy.
- Right.
I don't get that shit.
I'm more like a books and chess type of guy.
He's like an Indian guy that looked like a lanky nerd.
Yeah.
Guys, tragedy is striking. Hold on.
Tragedy is striking in a major way.
The beer has been spilled.
The beer has been spilled on my mouse pad, guys.
No!
Guys, this is going to stick it up.
Alright. Mental reset.
Mental reset.
Guys, I'm on tour.
You are on tour. How's that?
Yeah, I'm on tour and I got plenty of stories on the tour.
I think Texas is completely based, especially the San Antonio area.
I think anyone who chooses to leave, to live in either in LA or New York is an idiot.
This is true.
This is the best place to live in.
You can just drive your car, your awesome car everywhere.
I want to buy a truck so bad.
But also I've run into some issues on my way here.
- No.
What has happened?
- Which is really sad.
- What the fuck did they do to you?
- On my first day up here,
it wasn't even the good people of Texas, I don't think.
On my way here, before I hit the border,
I got stopped, I like the border town, by a cop.
And I was like, "Yo, you were going so incredibly fast
"on your awesome car."
I was like, "Thank you, man."
And I dabbed him up.
(laughing)
And he was like, "No, actually you have to pay me for that."
I was like, "Ah, shit."
So he starts talking about how I owe the state,
like I think it's like around 300 bucks or some shit.
He's like, "Yeah, you gotta pay this fine for 300 bucks."
- Who gives a fuck?
You're in a different fucking country.
- I'm gonna take, no, that's just in Mexico.
It's in a different city, but still Mexico.
- Wait, so by 300 bucks, you mean like $7?
- 300 American?
- 300 American, yeah.
- Oh God, that's a bad speaking.
- What?
- Yeah, it's like 6,000 pesos.
I'm just trying to make the conversion on my head.
And I was like, "Oh, okay."
And he's like, "Yeah, well, you gotta pay this.
I'm gonna take your license and your registration.
It's gonna stay here.
You can leave the note with a phone number
if you have anyone here."
I was like, "No, I don't got family.
I don't have any cash on me, whatever."
And he's like, "Okay, well, I can give you a discount
and you can pay 60 bucks for this."
I was like, "Uh."
- Negotiator.
- Yeah. - Look at you.
- Well, I didn't say anything.
I was like, "I don't have any money on me."
It's like, all right, I'll give you a discount for 60 bucks.
You don't have to pay 60 bucks.
- All right, $15 for the ticket and a dollar for my Coke.
- That is actually kind of what happened.
He told me like, you can pay this like immediately now,
cash only at the gas station store.
I was like, okay, I'll do that.
- What kind of fucking system do you guys have?
You pay your tickets at the gas station?
- Chill.
- Did you get scammed?
- Hang on, hang on, hang on.
I was like, okay, yeah, I'll do that.
I'll pay the money then.
And I was like, he kept on like,
do you have your cash on you now?
I was like, no, no, no, I gotta go there
and I gotta take some cash out and then I'll pay it.
He's like, all right, I'll help you out.
I'll take half of it off.
You can pay only like 20,
like essentially like just like 20 bucks on this fine.
I was like, okay.
So we just drive to like the nearest gas station.
I take out like 10 bucks that I needed
to like make these two bucks.
And I just pay this like code that he gave me.
And I was like, "Okay, I got my ticket."
And I gave it to him.
I was like, "All right, all right, here you go."
I was like, "All right, just don't do it again, all right?"
I was like, "All right, sorry."
So I got a ticket, I guess, and I just paid 20 bucks
and I got out of it, which is completely fine with me.
- Did he follow you to the gas station?
- This is a cartel shakedown.
This is not a police officer, man.
- That is completely fake.
- He gave me a thing, like a coded,
like an actual barcode thing that I had to pay at the gas station.
- Cash app. - Yeah.
- Okay, but did you have to go-- - Not a cash app.
Did you have to go to like an official like mexico.mx.org?
Nope.
Yeah, you got scammed.
You got scammed.
For $20.
I don't care.
You still got-- just admit you got scammed, though.
Yeah, I don't care.
I've been scammed worse by the actual government before.
When I got a--
I think-- I don't know if I told this on the podcast,
but this one time I got a ticket for speeding,
like some speed camera got my license plate,
but it was so dark it was actually someone else's license
plate.
and I try my best at just like going around town
and getting reverted.
And at the end of the year, I go to pay my fee
for owning a car and the ticket's still there.
And I email the person, I was like,
well, I thought I did this.
He's just like, no, well, you gotta go
tell the other people that you did it.
I was like, you know what, it's $20.
I'll just eat, I just get scammed, I guess.
So if I get scammed for $20, you're free to go by me.
I don't care, I don't care what's $20.
- I don't really disagree with that.
- Yeah, you're getting off, I'm fine with that.
You know, if it's not gonna lead
to any kind of escalation, then sure.
- Yeah, I'd rather pay 20 bucks.
- He probably would have killed you if you didn't pay.
- Yeah, and I didn't give him any money.
I just gave him like the receipt.
I was like, here you go, I paid $20.
He's like, all right.
And he gave me my shit and I just watched it all my way.
- So he has some kind of thing worked out
with this gas station.
How, what did his car and outfit look like?
- He looked like a transit officer.
- Interesting.
- So he had a--
- Did he have like a siren at all?
- A conductor's cap.
- He had a complete siren and a very official car
and everything.
I think it's in some way a complete scam
that I scared so little about
that I kind of stopped thinking about it because--
- Is it possible that he was an actual police officer
doing a scam?
- Yes. - A corrupt cop?
- 100% because he kept telling me if I had any cash on me
at his truck and I was like, no I don't,
I'm gonna go take some cash out.
Just so nakedly corrupt.
I like that.
That is kind of awesome.
Yeah.
Anyways, that's how I was here.
Yeah, I know.
That was not the least of my woes.
After that, I went on my merry way.
I got to the bridge.
Luckily, I decided to cross on a Tuesday morning.
So there was no one waiting.
There was no line to the bridge.
There was no one on the bridge.
Nice.
And coming out, there was completely no traffic.
So I was sitting out of there in like five minutes tops.
Nada.
I got a little lost in Laredo because it's such a shit town.
But I got my permit and I was on my way.
But before I left Laredo, I saw a little bump on my front tire.
I was like, hmm, that doesn't look big, but I think that's always a problem.
So I was a little worried, but I just kept going.
That happened, that was like, what, Tuesday?
Wednesday, I went to hang out with a friend.
And we go have lunch, and we come out of lunch,
and what do I see on my tire?
On the same exact tire, but this.
No.
This gnarly slash on my tire.
A slasher.
A slasher attacked me.
This is horrible.
This is the worst news.
This is one of the worst things I've ever heard.
I have been a victim of a racist crime,
and I don't know when it happened,
but I'm so thankful that he decided to do it
on the one tire that was already damaged.
So it didn't cost me more than a single tire to get replaced.
- That is amazing.
- So that's why I remain steadfast on my thinking
that Texas is based and we should all completely move here.
- I would love to move.
I would love to get a compound, man.
Oh, I want a compound so badly.
- You can actually do a full fantasy factory in Texas.
- We could actually do the, what's it called,
the gemstones, like down here.
- You wanna do a church.
- Yeah, we could do a church.
- The pod church.
- The podcast church.
- Where we all live on the same area.
- Can you imagine Caleb with like a Kenneth Copeland face?
- Who dat is?
- Like the guy who looks insane.
You know who Caleb Copeland is?
- The boyfriend?
- No, that is crazy that they don't know him.
- Who is Kenneth Copeland?
- But it would be cool if we had a huge property
and we all had houses in each corner of it
and we had to drive quads to go do the podcast.
- We need quads.
(laughing)
We need quads.
- I think we would die if we were on a quad.
- We had to drive 15 minutes on a quad
to get to a shared meeting spot.
- You don't know this guy?
- Oh, that guy.
- Yeah, the pastor. - I don't know who that is.
I don't know why I said, "Oh, that guy."
- The pastor with the insane face.
Oh shit.
Whoa.
He looks cool.
He looks grumpy.
He looks like a, sorry, mini pants.
Yeah, he does.
He looks exactly like the, uh, Walter.
Yeah.
He's speaking of Walter.
I have a New York complaint.
Oh, go ahead.
Let it fly.
No, I knew it was coming.
I knew one day the rose tinted glasses were going to fade.
The sheen of this amazing city was going to wear off.
So three days ago.
I'm fully stink maxed.
I'm ready for my shower.
Yes, sir.
And I go and I turn my shower on.
And what do I have?
No hot water.
Oh, so I call my super.
And he doesn't answer.
What's a strong word?
Oh, oh, you don't know about supers.
What's a super?
They're guys who live in the building who never answer the phone.
Yes.
Oh, that's cool.
I called the maintenance guy.
He says, I'll take a look at it.
Nothing happens.
Second day.
Call again.
No answer.
Third day today.
Call three times in a row.
Turns out he's on vacation.
Oh my feet up on the beach right now.
Bro.
He's probably drinking one of these Montauk summer.
Else they point summer.
-Meanwhile, I-- -The taste of the summer.
--am fully stinky.
My hair is greasy.
The worst thing is, yesterday, I ate Popeyes.
-No.
-I had extremely nasty, gross diarrhea.
I wanted to take a shower to rinse it out of my butthole.
-Yes, after he found out that he didn't have to eat hot water.
-After you already knew that the hot water was gone,
you decided, "I will eat Popeyes."
-Yes.
and I took a cold shower and I backed up slowly
like into the shower to get the water into my asshole.
- I bet that was hot.
(laughs)
I bet that was fucking hot.
- And then what would you know,
30 minutes after I get out of the shower,
I have to have diarrhea again.
- It's a vicious cycle.
- And I thought, I can't do it again.
I can't live like this.
I can't take a second cold shower.
- You don't like cold showers?
- No, it's horrible.
- They're amazing.
- I think your opinion of a cold shower
is directly related to how much hair you have.
- I think that I probably experience cold showers
maybe worse 'cause it's pure scalp.
- Yeah, but it, here's the thing, right?
- Yeah, but it doesn't stick around.
- It doesn't hold the cold in for me.
- The coldness doesn't stick around.
- Well, but I know you're wrapping your hair in a towel
and doing a Marge Simpson with it.
You don't have to lie to me.
- I mean, not in the shower.
- Well, in the shower, you're already cold.
There's already cold water being sprayed
- All on your beautiful body.
- That's not how that works,
'cause it feels even colder,
and it becomes like being whipped by a cold wind, you know?
Like your hair turns into a whip of ice.
- Have you ever worn a shower cap?
- Well, that's what I did,
is I wore my hair up so I didn't get it wet.
- I find cold showers pretty refreshing.
I end every shower with a little cold area.
- I do the same thing.
- It's nice.
you need a little heat.
- That is true.
- You don't wanna wash your body in cold.
- It is, yeah.
- You wanna refresh yourself in cold.
- The hotel I stayed at in DC this past weekend,
my hotel room, the shower had no hot water.
But I didn't even complain.
- That sucks.
- I'm such a baby.
'Cause like, I was just thinking,
what are they gonna do,
send me to another room
and I gotta move my one bag over there?
That sounds like a nightmare.
- Yeah.
- I'm not doing that shit.
So I just took three cold showers while I was there.
- Dude, I love hotels.
Hotels are so sick.
- Me too, man.
- They're so awesome.
- I love hotel, it's the best sleep,
it's the only good sleep I ever get is in a hotel.
- Maybe that's just because your wife isn't there.
- That's true, but also I think it's the blackout curtains,
the blackout shades.
- There is nothing that a hotel should have--
- Wait, your bedroom is in a different room
than your windows.
- But the window, the door has windows to the bedroom.
- So you need a blackout curtain for the bed,
for the bed door.
I sleep with a sleeping mask on these days.
Really?
Yeah.
If I'm trying to get a good night's sleep,
which is not that often, but if I am, I wear my sleeping mask.
Do you find that the mask creates blemishes
or sits on your face, do you think?
No, I wash it pretty often.
I wash it pretty often.
And it's pretty breathable.
I got a nice one.
It was $25 if you have to know everything
about my personal finances.
I do.
I was very interested.
- You know what I want to do though?
I want to go to a hotel that has a pool, man.
Let me swim, man.
- Dude, that's--
- In a hotel pool?
- Yes, are you crazy?
- Are you crazy?
You're gonna get HIV, the virus, the parasites.
- I got-- - Don't give a fuck
about getting HIV.
- I got something to put into this conversation.
- Put that.
- Just 30 minutes ago, I was in the pool at this hotel.
And it was so relaxing.
- You people are crazy. - Rex, this is the most
sanitary pool you can get in.
These are chlorinated to the point where you walk into the room
and you're having some kind of aging orange attack.
Who fucking cares even if it's completely dark shit in there?
You just take a shower anyways afterwards.
Yeah. Well, not me.
When I'm ... If there's a hotel with a pool,
my shower is the pool.
Okay, that is crazy.
How's that crazy?
There are used condoms and plastic bags and diapers.
Okay, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You're hanging out in an odd motel, man.
You're not in a motel. That is a motel.
That is a motel.
Do not, do not, you know, don't come down here.
- Do not besmirch the good name of hotels.
- The sanctity of hotels.
This hotel has graced me with hot water,
fast enough internet so I could do my job.
- It only took them eight minutes
to download Google Chrome, y'all.
- I did, let's not talk about that.
I have a kitchen in my room,
even though the fare is so cheap.
I get this beautiful breakfast
every single day of my mornings.
Look at that.
- Look at that Texas waffle.
- Where am I gonna get that anywhere in this world?
- Hotel pools are nice.
- Yeah.
- I will say, I grew up going to a resort pool.
So I am like, you know.
- Are you anti-water park as well?
Any public pool?
- I haven't been to a water park in a long time.
- I'm not gonna lie, I don't like water parks.
- I love them.
- I think they're stinky.
- I'm not opposed to it, but as I got older,
it became like grosser to me.
- Is it an ache of yours?
- It's not, well, let's not go too far.
- It sounds like an ache of yours.
- I just would prefer not to be touched by that water.
- We should all do a getaway at some Mexican beach.
- We should go to Atlantis.
(laughing)
That's an actual resort.
You're laughing.
I'm laughing.
Because you think I'm talking about
The lost city.
The lost city from far history.
But no guys.
Atlantis Resort.
This is a resort.
And I, a kid that was,
that I knew from.
We should go to Sandals and share a room together.
I'm down.
My brother knew this kid who was like
the son of the owner of Atlantis or something
when we were growing up.
And they were like close friends
and kept being like,
man I'll take you guys to Atlantis.
I wanna take you guys to Atlantis so bad.
So we went to go to Atlantis and see the mermaids and he never did man.
He got addicted to drugs.
Oh, well, many of the relatives fall into this fate.
I've never been to a rich guy's son thing to do.
Yeah.
I've never been to an actual Island.
This looks scary, man.
I went to the Bahamas.
That's the only place I've ever been.
That was not technically in America.
When my parents got divorced the first week, my dad was like, we're going on a
cruise y'all and we went to the Bahamas for one day.
-Did you share a room with your dad or did he have his own?
-No, we had two sets of bunk bed for me, my dad, and my two brothers.
-Tom was not having any sex.
-Oh, fuck no, man. We all got so sick.
-Yes, that seems to be the only reason to go on a cruise.
-That's funny how as soon as--
Yeah, it's like a place for adults to be college students.
I think they're just like cheap vacations.
They're cheaper than any hotels.
Yeah, and they have an all-cruises,
well, maybe not all-cruises, but this cruise had an all-in,
all-you-can-drink-booze option that was like...
What the fuck else are you going to do?
That is sick.
You paid double the ticket for unlimited all-you-can-drink-booze.
they give you a wristband and you just say,
"Give me a gin and tonic."
And they have to give it to you.
- Most of the time you guys have been to like a place
that's just like an all-inclusive,
where they take care of all of your needs.
- When I went to Cancun when I was 12 years old
and I drank so many strawberry daiquiris
that I threw up in the pool.
(laughing)
- Oh, that's why you don't like pools.
You think kids are throwing up in that shit.
(laughing)
- I love all-inclusive.
I love not thinking about my life.
I love just going to get fat and drinking.
- They handle everything, man.
- I love that.
- I had a bunch of steak.
- That's how I really need,
that's how I've been probably since I cruised.
- Life should be every single day.
- Life should be all inclusive.
- I need servants to cook me awesome food.
- I feel like-- - That sounds so amazing.
- It doesn't feel wrong to go to Mexico and have servants,
but I feel like it's wrong for you to go to Cancun
and have servants or something like that.
- Me?
- Yeah, you.
- What's that?
- These are your brothers.
- I don't give a shit.
- Yeah, you should have solidarity with them.
Me?
They would kill me in a heartbeat.
You know, in Cancun, they basically have the same living conditions as they do in Dubai,
where they just make all the staff sleep in this one big stinky room.
Really? I don't believe that. In Mexico?
Yeah.
Wow.
It's pretty cool. And every single morning, they have to come up and serve you all your treats,
all your drinks.
Whoa.
And you give them one peso as a tip.
No, I give them a dollar for their cooking.
- I know a couple of comedians who did like,
like cruise ship gigs,
where they live on a cruise ship for like six months,
and they do like improv in some ship.
And that seems like,
they always talk about it like it was hell,
but it seems amazing.
- Yeah. - I think for 30 days,
it would be cool.
- You have to do one hour of work every day.
- Yeah, but you can't leave.
- You can leave, you just lose all your money.
Okay, so this was like recommended to me a couple of times
like when I was in school.
One of my teacher was like,
yeah, if you just like go work at a cruise
for like a couple of months,
you basically make so much money
because even if they don't like pay you like that much more
than you would make like at a normal hotel,
you pretty much, you like don't leave.
So you don't spend it anywhere.
Yeah, it is all inclusive.
You just put yourself in like a prison
basically for a couple of months.
Then you come out with a bunch of money.
There's nothing wrong with prison. Many people leave prison enriched.
They have master's degrees and a new religion.
So basically that's, that's what life was.
And I think I could have done it if I was desperate enough.
But, uh, I think that's the chip sailed.
I don't want to be in prison anymore.
Very, very funny.
That ship sailed.
Very funny.
That is very, very funny.
I think I would like doing something like that though.
I would love to have some, some job that just like deletes a year of your life.
You know,
like ice fishing or something?
When I was a kid, I really wanted to be an
Alaskan crab fisherman.
Yeah.
Because of that show.
And I was obsessed with that show.
And my mom is so kind of neurotic that she was like,
I was 10 years old saying I wanted to do the
reality TV show job.
And she was like, no, it's too dangerous.
You're going to die.
She was like, really?
She talked me out of it.
When I was 10 years old, she thought that that dream was
going to persist for another decade.
Yeah.
But it did not. I really, I don't care about the deadliest catch anymore.
I've been watching these videos, you guys watch these videos of this guy who's a lobster fisherman?
You're gonna have to be more specific.
Yeah, because there's so many of those guys. Well, I do have like a, I have come across
some TikToks of like guys who just like go out on the water
and what they post the most I guess is just like them like getting
like crabs and just like taking all the barnacles off them. Oh yeah, that's
That's what this guy does too.
He takes, he gets lobsters and he says,
"We're gonna fix this guy up."
He takes like pliers, he takes all the barnacles off him,
gives him a little piece of fish
and throws him back into the ocean.
That sounds like it would be fun to do.
But he does not, strangely enough,
does not make that many videos about the thousands
of lobsters he catches a day that get turned into food.
Crazy.
Well, listen, well, I thought they were just like doing like,
they're dropping like the big cage
And then sometimes they get like crabs and lobsters
and I'm like, no, we're not here for these.
- No, this guy, he only throws back lobsters
that are too big, 'cause if they're past a certain size,
then you have to throw them back legally in Maine.
- Have you seen like the praying crabs
with like the big bellies
and like the millions of eggs that they have on them?
- They're beautiful.
- Have you seen a blue lobster?
- I have never seen a blue lobster in person.
I've seen photos.
- Photos. - Photos.
- I've seen photos of these.
- I like fishing, I would like to go fishing again.
I haven't gone in many years.
- I've never been fishing.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- That's crazy.
- We need to, Brian's been talking about
chartering a boat.
- Ooh, that'd be fun.
- On the sound or something.
- Off where, like New York?
- Yeah, you can like charter a fishing boat.
I think it's like 500 bucks and you go out
and you fish for a day.
- Yeah, and you get beer.
- And you get beer and pizza.
- Yummy.
- Wait, do you get pizza in the boat?
- Um, I would hope so.
- You could just order the pizza ahead of time.
They have a little cabin cruiser.
- Well, it's not gonna come to you in the water.
- Well, I don't know what these pizza guys are doing.
- There's a microwave.
- Okay, I'm sold.
I'm gonna go fishing on the microwave boat.
- Have you guys ever stayed on a houseboat?
- No.
- No. - He's thinking.
but wow, that was a long time to think about that question.
What could have possibly been the weird house that you stated
that you thought it was maybe a houseboat?
There was some friends of my grandma that had a huge mega yacht.
Wow.
I think they sold it before I was able to be on a boat.
They are completely broke now, which is also funny.
You can be on a boat whenever.
And they lived, and here's the thing too,
they lived in a house that was shaped like a boat.
- Wow, that's dedication.
- It was, it was a beautiful house.
- When I got moved into college in Boston,
my mom came up and it was like the week
that everybody was moving into college.
So Boston has like 50 colleges,
so there was no like cheap hotels or Airbnbs,
except she found a listing on VRBO
that was, it was like houseboat, sleeps four.
And she drove up with like all my shit.
And we get there and it was not a houseboat, it was a boat.
- Just a regular boat?
- It was just a regular fucking boat, man.
It was a boat that had cushions on it,
on like a couch, and that was the bed.
And it was one of the worst nights of sleep
of my entire life.
I kept thinking that somebody was,
there was no lock on the door.
So I was like, and I'd never been to Boston before.
I was like some crazy guy's going to come in here and start fishing or something.
Yeah. In your butthole.
Yeah. I mean fishing for something.
Whoa.
My dad had a boat with like a little cabin in it and uh,
when Arizona, yeah, he, it was about two hours away that he would go to,
that's the dream about this.
Yeah. But he, whenever he would get so mad at his girlfriend,
he would just go there and sleep for two days.
(laughing)
- Wow.
- And it had like, you know, if you were at the dock,
you could get like a DirecTV and like,
you had like a little 20 inch TV.
So he'd watch like football and take phone calls on it.
- That's sick.
- Just completely ignore everyone.
- I used to want to live on a boat so bad.
Like there was this documentary about this girl
who was like 16 or 17 that came out when I was in high school
and it was about her,
like she went all the way across the world by herself
on a sailboat.
And I was like, I'm gonna do that shit.
And then I watched two YouTube videos about sailing
and it seemed so hard, man.
- Yeah, absolutely not.
- I think that's the same case with like the people
who like talk about living in a,
like a van.
- Yeah, van life, man.
- Like they set up like all these videos
about them like making this van like beautiful,
but they're like, where do you go pee and poop?
- Out the war.
- I have a bucket that I keep around
and then I throw it out every once in a while.
- Yeah, the stink bucket.
- The stink bucket.
- I've been known to admire the nomads in my time.
- Really?
- Yeah, the transient souls
who travel across this great nation.
But at this time in my life, man,
I'm getting too old for that shit.
- You are.
- I don't wanna ever sleep in a car again.
- The moment you taste a bit of comfort,
it's impossible to go back.
Me and my buddy John, we used to, both of our parents,
we had two parents between the two of us,
he would, they hated marijuana.
They hated it so, so much and we could not,
and they knew that we liked smoking it
and they would not let us go to their house
to smoke this stuff.
But they also hated each other,
they never talked to each other.
So we would say, I would say, I'm going to John's house,
John would say, I'm going to Caleb's house,
and then we would go and sleep in his Passat and smoke weed.
Wow.
And I slept in that car probably 40 times.
- That is fucking awesome.
- It was so awesome, man.
We would listen to WTF with Mark Maron and smoke weed.
Guys, this has gotta be the ultimate vibe.
- You had a gay boyfriend.
You were in a gay boyfriend relationship.
- No, he was Christian.
- Okay.
You guys never kissed?
- We kissed, but not like that.
- Okay.
- Just indirectly, but--
- Kissed in a funny way, like guys like to do.
Do you guys want to become digital nomads with me?
No.
You know, I just said I don't want to, but yeah, I do.
Yeah, I'd like to completely retract my previous statements
on being a digital nomad.
I think you are the one who has the most easiest life
to just be on the road,
because you live in such a small space.
I have a dog. No offense.
No, this is you, man.
I have a dog, I have a wife.
I got issues, man.
- Yeah. - There's stuff I can't,
people depend on me.
I'm sending checks back to Africa, man.
I can't do this shit.
- And you have to show up in person to do the podcast.
- That's true.
- Well, that's true.
- You gotta go back to prison every single Tuesday.
- It would be funny to have two vans
and then you just have someone else
drive a different van to go podcast in.
- That's my office.
That's actually a good idea.
See, I could do two vans.
A two van lifestyle, two van life.
That's a great idea.
- Double wide.
- Yeah, we're like, yeah, 'cause if I am getting bad sleep
or my wife's mad 'cause I'm farting or something
'cause I drink beer, I'm gonna go to the boys van.
- Go to the fart van.
- Bye bye.
See you in Idaho.
We're driving.
- That's a horrible idea.
- It would be cool to do like a John Madden-style
touring podcast, but you never get out
and like do anything in front of anyone.
- We should ride bikes all across the country
and do podcasts while we're on the bikes.
Like a regular bicycle?
When I was young, many, many years ago,
everything like that was so interesting to me.
I wanted to do the Appalachian Trail so, so badly
until I found out there was bears on the trail.
And then I didn't want to do it so much, man.
I do not want to-
You can scare them off.
Maybe you can.
I'm four feet tall.
What am I going to do?
You're also the youngest of everyone here.
I'm four feet tall and I look exactly like a fish.
- I would not do well with a bear.
I have a salmon colored skin.
- Are you a good swimmer?
- I'm one of the best swimmers in the world.
- You can just swim upstream and get away from him.
- Well he's very aerodynamic.
- Bears are lightning fast.
People don't know about bears.
- Can you put your headphones the way you had them
before we talked? - Way back here?
- Yeah, just for a treat.
Just a visual treat for the video watchers.
Caleb somehow gave himself a receding hairline
while already being bald.
- I have a receding hair, my hairline is fully receded.
If it goes any further than this,
it's God is almost not real.
(laughing)
Almost.
- Still believe.
- Still believe, 'cause he's given me
so many amazing blessings.
Like this second Montauk Summer Ale
that I'm about to crack open.
- Wow. - Let's go.
- This is how good this beer is, guys.
I gotta like a beer a lot to drink two on this show.
- That is true.
- Or it needs to be in a 12 ounce can
instead of a tall boy.
- 'Cause it's 50 minutes in, you didn't really drink it
that fast. - Yeah.
- The shenanigan is not even done,
and I do feel it in my head.
- You are wasted. - This is okay.
- You are wasted as fuck, man.
- That's not true, but I'm also,
I wanted dinner, and I feel like I don't wanna drive
to the Whataburger anymore.
- You acting like a slut, 'cause you're so wasted.
- I'm not acting like a slut, stop.
- You're going wild. - Stop.
- You are being a hunk. - No, I'm not.
Stop, I'm so shy. - Did you guys have
Girls Gone Wild in Mexico?
- Yeah.
- That's awesome.
Was it different?
Or was it like a port?
Was it like, "Girls Gone Wild Mexico"?
- It was dubbed badly.
- Well, that is really sad for the big fans.
- Los señoritos es gone wild.
- Tetas oculos.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, that's what they were saying basically.
And they would just go like, "Woo!"
And I'd be like, "That's awesome."
- That little jingle, I can almost hear it now
from all the times I stayed up till 2 or 3 a.m.
watching Adult Swim as a 12-year-old.
- I remember one time waking up to,
like I fell asleep to Comedy Central,
waking up to one of those commercials,
and I had a boner already when I woke up.
(laughing)
- That's so crazy.
No one ever wakes up with a boner.
- But it was like I had been watching,
I remember thinking, this is how dumb I was as a kid,
it was probably one of my first wake-up boners,
I was like, oh my God, just the sound of Girls Gone Wild
made me get a boner in my sleep and woke up with one.
- Yeah.
(humming)
- I don't remember anything.
- Uh, have we talked about
Wardell on here?
- Oh, about how he kicked us out of his house
to jack off to Girls Gone Wild?
- Yeah.
- That was so funny.
I don't know if we talked about it.
- No.
- Yeah, we were at Wardell's house and he was like,
(laughing)
Probably not a story he wants out there,
but you know what?
He doesn't know.
Actually, I think he does subscribe to the Patreon.
- No, he doesn't listen to this one.
- He definitely doesn't listen to this one.
- Brandon, if you're listening, may God speed.
But one time we were at his house and he was like,
"Dude, do you guys remember Girls Gone Wild?"
And we were like, "Yeah, we remember Girls Gone Wild."
And he was like, "Bro, let's watch one of the commercials."
And he pulled it up.
He watched, we watched probably 15 of these commercials.
And then he was like, man, that is some funny ass shit.
You guys need to leave my apartment right now for no reason.
And we're like, okay.
- Yeah, he was so excited,
ran to his room, grabbed his laptop,
and started looking at r/girlsconfile.
(laughing)
And then he was like, oh, I'm so tired.
- As we left his apartment, he like,
Literally like we heard the padlock snap and we saw the shades get drawn
Been doing cocaine like
So late does anyone notice how late it got it was like 11 o'clock
Yeah, it was so fucking awesome. I respected him so much for that. It really was a legendary moment, dude
But I mean who can blame a man these commercials were hot yeah, I
Mean is there even something to
Jack off to the girls gone wild like it's just what they're showing their breasts. Yeah. Yeah, this guy's
So are you so desensitized a female nudity at this point that you even?
Have to assume someone's looking up here on reddit. He is like
I
I would believe that.
It's not true.
I think there's more than monster in those cans.
Yep.
I think that's where you shoot.
In the cans?
Yeah.
Like what are those?
Like a...
Like a spittoon.
Ding.
I don't think...
I've never had that much aim with where it goes.
Me neither, man.
It just has a mind of its own.
It just goes where it's going.
This shit is disgusting.
360 degree cone of danger.
I hate it.
You hate jizz?
- Me too.
- I hate jizz.
- If I get jizz on my hands,
I mean, my day's ruined, I think.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause every single person,
and I meet a lot of people, you know.
I'm out on the campaign trail.
Every single person I meet, I'm shaking their hand,
and I am saying to myself, like,
"This is disgusting, this guy doesn't know
"that I jizzed on these 14 minutes ago."
(laughing)
It's really nasty.
- Yeah, that is nasty.
- Not a good habit.
- You wash the hands before you hit the trail?
- Just rub them together.
- Yeah, with really warm water.
And then they're like,
hey, did you like break your remote control,
use some super glue or something?
I guess something like that.
- Yeah.
- I've never understood that.
Is cum sticky?
Is that how it like dries or something?
- Have you never,
you've never gotten cum on yourself
and then used warm water
and it turns into a second skin?
- It's never come with its entire life.
(laughing)
- I don't get it.
Is cum white?
Or is it bright, bright red?
I really never got a clear answer on this in sexual education.
I usually just--
I usually just do it like yellow into the toilet.
Into the toilet?
Yeah, long yellow jizz.
No, I mean, I just--
I've never left it around long enough for it to be like--
Hear no evil, see no evil.
I like that.
It's gone as soon as it's out.
We're not examining it.
This means you go in your mouth.
This is what this means.
- How would that mean that?
- 'Cause you're like, yeah, I've never even seen this stuff.
It goes in your mouth.
- I've seen it for like less than a minute.
- Yeah, of course, listen, I'm not sitting there
watching it, seeing if it's gonna do something.
- Well, that's what I'm saying.
I've never seen it get sticky.
I feel like that's one of those things
that's just like a joke.
- No, it is sticky.
You are--
- This is crazy.
- You are infertile.
- You have, you're shooting blinks.
- No.
- Yes.
- You're a complete alien from hell.
- What does it look like?
Describe to me Jizz.
- Just right now.
- It's white, it's gross.
- This is like the--
- Fills up your belly button.
- This is making it so,
he's never seen it his entire life.
- You've never seen Jizz?
- It's like an egg yolk.
- Yeah, okay.
That might be a little thick.
That might be a little bit thick and clear.
- Yeah.
I like that I said egg yolk
and you and I both knew what I meant by that.
- Yeah, it's mucus.
- Yeah.
- Oh yeah, you did say yolk and you meant white.
(laughing)
Egg yolk.
That's bad.
If it looks like egg yolk,
that is exactly,
that's exactly a chart of like good, good, good,
really fucking bad.
Go to the ER right now.
You have egg yolk jizz.
Well I used to worry because you know I drink like two monsters a day forever
that my cum would be like you know like if you left a lightsaber face down on
the ground. You know how they say this? What are your descriptions to that?
Nothing makes any fucking sense. Like if you just had like acid and just like ate through the
ground. Oh like it's bubbling. Yeah like it's like in Breaking Bad when it eats
through the the bathtub and the body parts fall through. Do you think you have a thing where you know what
I hope people will say that if you drink pineapple juice,
it'll taste good,
but yours is just gonna give someone a lot of energy
for like an hour or so,
and they'll just crash it down.
- Oh, that's a pretty good idea.
Yeah, 'cause your body is,
you're getting rid of the different toxins in your body.
Caffeine has gotta be among some of the worst ones
in your body.
You have so much excess caffeine
that it probably does go straight to your loads.
- I do think it would be cool
if I could somehow figure out the perfect cocktail
where if someone interacted with my cum,
they just had like a heart attack from all this.
Oh wow. Yeah, that's really smart.
You know, it'd be cool to get your jizz.
You guys know like Pharaoh fluid?
Yeah.
They're like magnetic. It'd be cool to do that.
Yes.
Maybe load up on iron.
Right. Oh, dude.
And then you start, you know, or I mean, you could get the same results, I guess,
putting it on like a subwoofer.
I think that should be cool.
I think that would be a very cool video.
Somebody has some spare jizz sitting around.
Yeah, just go ahead and try that out.
That'd be terrible. Don't try that.
I'd like to see it at least once before I pass away.
Yeah, it'd be cool if you just came quicksilvered.
That would be fucking cool.
Mercury, just fucking.
Yeah.
Shoulda snot like this conversation.
Yeah, I'm sorry. He's...
Dude, he's so mad, bro.
He's saying, "Please, no more."
Shut the fuck up!
Why is this so pissed? This isn't supposed to be a sleep.
Give me one minute, Phil.
Give me one minute and I will take you wherever you want.
[dog whining]
Okay.
No!
Bastard dog, man.
Isn't it his bedtime?
Uh, he was in the crate for like two hours while I went to the show, so...
I'm gonna leave him out until I probably go to bed.
Okay.
But he probably does need to pee, so I do need to go.
Motherfucking dog, man.
I hate dogs.
episode we're gonna open up Rex to see what's inside of him.
Alright I'm down. Alright bye. Bye.