E.G. Hymen.
Can't hynd it.
*slurp*
The song's playing. Shut up.
Shut the fuck up.
Unless you know the lyrics, you could carry a few of this.
*burp*
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's number one beer podcast.
*record scratch*
*music*
Hey.
What's up all my chuggers?
Trying to get that burp out.
*burp*
This is a Johnny.
the
are
no
they'll not only a bag
specials special sunday edition
uh...
special late addition guys
welcome back
to the number one beer podcast probably in the fucking world and in the land
this is the best podcast in the world we do it sometimes
live and we're learning this recently that this is a live podcast we have
found out the last couple weeks
uh...
grab a
grab a uh...
that a coolie
who
sit back
act a fool e this podcast is for jack and julie guys and it's that's right
and it's
for me
it's and it's fully
need for nearly you need me to do it
and you might be surprised msic howie the hell you guys to a beer podcast
to have a don't you want to do a rogan
pod experience a podcast this is something called sober october guys you
should not be here drinking this
you should be on the treadmill
you should be on the assault bike you should be a kettlebell exercises where
the kettlebell looks like a gorilla's head
yeah okay
but not us man
this year we're taking sober october off as much as i would like to be
celebrating with my comrades
tom segura joe rogan
and the other couple of guys
here we are having a great month
drinking beer tom segura this is one of those
nicest most charitable guys you know a lot of people don't know he gave me my
start
today
i am having
a bit of a repeat but i had a different edition last time last time i had
Sapporo black i believe this is Sapporo premium beer guys
and this comes in a premium
can
this is having and we've talked about this before i'm gonna take my first step to
give you a bus score
didn't also group to be out just recently that he wanted to kill a woman
yes it's a report that he's still
guys support
this is an amazing beer
my hat goes off to the japanese
big waste about everybody in that country
is amazing
i believe is a japanese
uh... let me just double check
you going
i'm not belling
guys it's for vietnam
this is
a tragedy
i respect the vietnamese
just as much as i respect the japanese
thank you vietnam thank you vietnam
this is a six
six foot eleven six but i i think six but eleven to us this is seven feet
I'm not gonna play like a bitch and be coy about this.
This is a 7 foot beer.
This is an 8'6".
This is a great beer, man.
You love the Sapporo.
I do.
Alright, I'm gonna open mine.
I have a seasonal favorite, Feast Beer.
Victory.
It looks like Fest Beer to me.
Victory Royale.
It's Fortnite beer.
It's a Fest Beer.
You're right, it is a Fest Beer.
I was very hungry and I got the feast beer.
Now I guess it's just an October festival.
So let me guess, this is the same people who make sour monkey.
Victory, right?
That's the name?
This has got to be some kind of pumpkin-esque ale.
Well, it's a Madison style lager.
Let's take a sip.
That is a regular beer.
That is a solid 7.0.
Oh, okay.
A league average 5.6.
Okay.
This is an above average.
5.6 is league average to you?
5.6?
I think so.
6.5.
In what league, man?
I think that's what it is.
I think the TV makes you look taller.
I don't think it makes you look longer.
In the Israeli league.
Yeah.
Yeah, I gained new respect. I gained new respect for a
Man named Iman Shumpert an NBA player this week because he dropped one of the craziest bars. I've ever heard in my entire life
He's talking somebody DJ Vlad. I think asked him. He was like if Kevin if they put Kevin Durant in the NBA right now
Do you think he could score a hundred points and he said
First of all, he said you want a man which was funny enough
But then he said if you gave him that little rock he could shoot all the way from Arkansas and that
Good he came up with that on the spot in front of DJ Vlad which he was probably nervous
Yeah, cuz who wouldn't be in front of DJ Vlad DJ Vlad very little rock. He'll shoot it from Arkansas. That is fire
That is insane. No way
It's amazing. I was like I have to hear more of this guy turns out he has a big penis. Okay, Juvio
So
Think many of you know this
But there's an insane
alcohol curfew in my my city
Where on Sundays you're not allowed to buy any sorts of alcohol at the at the corner store
Past like 6 p.m
So I am I just scrub whatever we had in the fridge. It's one of my
My go-to hangout beers
The classic. Oh, you can't even see it white beer. Nicolau Baltra a
You were right white beer. Come on
boom
Fucking white dude little rewriting. Let's see. Let's see how this holds up to the last time you rated
It's just the best beer of all time
I mean, it's the best one to hang out in and drink 20 of them.
- You wanna hang out in that?
You fucking little, little man.
- This is how I hang out with my friends.
I just drink this like once.
- And that's it.
I just eat some chips and I leave.
- You do kind of do that.
You do love chips.
When you came to my house,
you ate a bag of chips every single day.
- Yep, and then I left.
- I would like to say something.
Before we get into the nitty gritty,
kind of the down to dirty, the mud of this podcast,
which is, for those of you who've never been here,
stick around if you like stories
stick around if you like
uh... friendly friendly jabs between friends about their ethnicities or maybe
their hair
yes stick around if you like any that kind of shit
for those who do not who do not like beer
okay because we do be it's mostly beer around here. I propose that next week
on our one hundredth episode
or one hundred and first episode this is the one hundredth on our one hundred and first
episode
i propose
that we do
liquor
we've enjoyed
okay
liquor which is
eat now we know and now that's kind of it now because i'm thinking maybe we do a
little bit
of a
kinda more higher class highbrow style thing maybe we dress up
okay where the same suit i wear to my wedding
because it's the only suit
that i have in the only button down shirt that i own
and maybe we sit back with foreign meat
but two fingers worth of something delicious like screwball something
really classy
we sit back and we sit on this week is that
jumped out on them
now i like that and it's settled next week
liquor we've enjoyed
yeah okay
rex
tell us the story that you wanted to tell us earlier
so i uh...
i was at a time i flew back in today
uh... part of the reason why this that was it was late
and i was
color like rushing to get off the plane is kinda like a fucked up thing where
the plane landed too early
and then you're like waiting at the gate
and then i was like way at the back of the reform southwest by the way
affluent all over
but have you found southwest airline airline uh...
no doubt
so you know they fuckin
like just don't have assigned seats it's just a free-for-all
no i have not flown southwest airlines i'm realizing yeah
that can't be [ __ ] true it's completely true
first class is first come there's no first class
it's just all class whoa you can see there's no dividing
communism airlines i hate that [ __ ] i was just way at the back of the plane
because i had like the last boarding pass but whatever so i
So I finally get off, I'm rushing through LaGuardia, I'm like, I haven't sent any texts since I
landed, I'm like ready to go, get in my cab, have a nice relaxing cab ride, send all the
texts I need to, over the 30-40 minutes it's going to take.
You love texting.
I do love the text.
So I get in the cab, and I'm like, he's like, "Where are you going?"
And I'm like, I tell him my address, and he just starts driving, and I'm like, "Don't you
need to you know put that into your GPS?" He's like "no no you direct me." I was like "what?"
Okay, so you got a voice. All right. So uh well I didn't mean to do the voice. Anyway. You already
did it so you have to continue. Yep do it again. So I'm like "okay uh go right here" and so he just
- Okay, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- This is not an Uber, this is a taxi.
- This is a taxi, this is a taxi.
- And tell me why you would choose a taxi
over a Rideshare app.
- It was closer, and I was lazy.
'Cause at LaGuardia-- - 'Cause it was.
- Button on your phone, man. - The exit?
- No, no, no, no, no, to the exit.
- 'Cause you have to go to the,
you have to walk over to the parking deck at LaGuardia
to get into an Uber, yeah. - Yeah, yeah.
You go down the escalators,
and then your just taxis are right there on the left.
- Yeah.
- Or you can walk to the thing and do your Uber.
And I was like, I don't feel like fucking with that.
The taxis are fine.
I've never had a problem with the taxis.
So I get into this taxi and you know how like
every app gives you like little mini directions
to optimize your route.
So I'm like telling this guy like, okay, take a left.
Okay, now take a right.
- And you're looking at your phone.
- I'm looking at my phone the whole time
trying to direct this guy.
He little does he know you are his GPS.
- Yes.
And like maybe like five minutes in, I'm like,
"Hey, this would probably be easier
"if I just input it into your GPS for you.
"Is there any way I can do that?
"Would you do that?
"Maybe that would be a better..."
So she goes, "Same thing, no difference."
- Wow.
- I was like, "Okay, all right."
So I thought-- - I think that this
was either his first shift
or his very last shift as a taxi driver.
- Yeah, I was like, what?
It was the most confusing thing of all time.
And I just couldn't believe it.
Like what kind of person drives without using the app now?
- Especially picking up people
from the airport all the time.
- Right.
And it wasn't like he didn't have the GPS built
into his car directly in arm's length of him.
He just didn't want to do it.
So did you push after this?
Since he said it's the same difference.
Like, do you just go with it?
Yeah, I had to!
He said no difference.
Might as well just put it in if it's no difference.
If it's the same thing.
No, he said no difference as in like, it makes no difference
if you just tell me the direction so I'm not going to do it.
He's saying it's too much of a hassle to put it into the GPS.
Yeah.
You know what I would have done?
a
and taking the train back because it was pissing me off so much. Yeah that would
have made me pretty mad. I mean if you know if you brought this up to go in on
taxi drivers let's fucking do it man. First of all. Also they have a new app now what
the fuck is that? A new app? Yeah they have arrow instead of curb. Oh what
really? Yeah. So you do use an app to call it? No no no no I got it cuz cuz curb has
the screens right? Uh-huh. Well this had the screen but it was for something called
Arrow. Had Sandy Kenyon and fucking Jeopardy. It just did the same loop every
five minutes. Okay so this is what I was about to fucking say man. If you are
going to make a trivia game and put it on an iPad that sits on the back of a not
even iPad an Amazon Kindle Fire. Right. Or Kindle Fire tablet. Kindle tablet. And put
it on the back of a fucking headrest and I'm gonna get in and say "oh trivia hmm
I'm learned it I'd like to play this" I've learned. And the first question you
ask me is you show me four colors and you say which one of these is blue I am
going to fucking kill myself if I ever go through that again if I ever go
through that a fucking gin that drives me out of my fucking mind man I'm sorry I
just had to get that out that trivia is such bullshit hey which one of these is
a photo of a giraffe what the hell is wrong with you who designed this shit
I'm sorry wait what is this you were hoping it was gonna be cash cab yes at
least or or ask me something about oh I don't know the Archduke of Franz
and
Hey, what shape is this?
Which one of these is a square? I don't know
First grade was a long time ago for me. How many are just where I learned my I learned my shapes when I was
in first grade
Sorry man, just really pissed me off gotta get gotta get through that you have a really good drivers
With drivers coming back from the airport. He's coughing
Yeah, I am coughing. Oh, you have a cough button. That's nice
But yeah, I I had a I had a lady I took an uber in
North Carolina waited about half an hour for it. We go downtown. Oh, this is what guy it by the way guys
This is why I want to class stuff up a little bit while I was in North Carolina
me Chad and Adam went to a
Cocktail bar at bespoke cocktail bar mind you with a bartender who had a twirly mustache
Uh huh.
And instead of a menu he'd say, "What kind of spirit do you like?"
Oh, a spirit.
And I'd say, "I'm not too kind to those of the other world, those who have passed on."
He said, "No, it's a name that we gave alcohol."
Uh huh.
I said, "Okay, well I like that."
And he said, "Do you like gin, vodka, whiskey, or tequila?"
I said, "I like tequila."
He said, "Do you like savory flavors or fruity flavors?"
And I said, "I like savory flavors!"
I like fruity flavors, actually.
I really like fruity flavors.
And he made me one of the most delicious things I've ever had, guys.
And this was an amazing drink.
So now I'm into this kind of thing.
Anyway, on the Uber over there, I get a woman named Paulina.
She says, "Where are you going tonight?
What's Ernest Money and Sons?"
Name of the bar, by the way.
Ernest Money and Sons.
is
a
want to meet Ernest Money I'd like to shake the hand of every single one of his sons.
Bring them all out right now. But if you're in Wilmington, North Carolina this is a good
place to go guys. It is a private club which means you have to pay $5 to be a lifetime
member so if you don't have your money straight, if you don't have your cash correct, don't
even try. Anyway, Uber over there, a woman named Paulina picks me up, she's about 80 years
old and she says, "What is Ernest Money and Sons?" I've dropped people off there before.
listening to positive encouraging K love radio which is a southeastern Christian
radio station and I say it is a bespoke cocktail bar basically say exactly what
I just said to you guys bespoke cocktail bar and I thought she was gonna say well
what is that what's bespoke mean she says what is a cocktail she's 80 years old
old man and she had never heard of this concept and I said a cocktail is when you mix two
things together.
That's true.
She said well that sounds great and then full silence as we drive all the way, about 25
minutes there, just blasting Newsboys on the radio.
That's awesome.
Yeah, it was great man.
Someone linked the Earliest Money and Sons webpage and I'm looking at their Instagram.
Guys, they need more traction in their Instagram.
We should do a shout out on our stories
for Ernest Money and Sons on Instagram.
- See, people who own bars don't realize
that nobody sees a picture of a drink like this.
It's not like food.
There's no like, nobody's doing like a cheese bomb
type of thing on this where it's like,
oh, I need to eat those fries so badly.
This is like, this could be a fucking...
Uh, uh, this could be piss.
This doesn't look like anything.
Yeah, none of these look like anything.
This is the same problem I have when I watch, uh...
Badlands.
Badlands Chugs.
Is he'll just like-
I miss my people.
-Earn this money. -He'll just-
He'll just have like a bucket and just like
put a bunch of like different sodas in it and just make a black concoction.
And drink it and go like,
"Aww, that's so yummy."
And I watch that every single day, basically.
and i go like i don't know what how what my how much support to feel but after
watching that they are my supposed to a great soda
my supposed to be a c_e_o_ me
you think he he has big soda
propping him up
i think completely a
one hundred percent
he might be big soda
uses so they would call him if you played basketball
you know b is gonna name on the court
but before we get off of uh... rex's trip
i wanted to tell
to quickly mention, when we wanted to record like in the middle of the week, I checked
Discord and at like around 11am I see a message from Rex where he sent us a picture of a Rick
and Morty cart and a Squid Games cart.
Oh yeah, I have it right here.
I'm hitting that shit.
Wait, you have them?
We're like, oh that's so funny.
No, no, it's the same thing.
So it's an R&M brand.
Which stands for Rick and Morty.
Squidbox.
Oh, okay.
Okay, so I'd like for you to give us a vape review, live on air.
First ever.
And I'd like for you to talk into your microphone as well.
It's not very good.
Somehow it got quieter when you got closer.
It's not a very good microphone.
There we go.
But it does have a wind strap.
Detachable even.
That's what I thought was so crazy.
Why would you ever keep a vape on your wrist?
Well, it's even, it's a neck strap so you can, you know, work at your gas station job
and you don't lose your vape.
That's just fuck.
Anyways, he sends this at 11am and then around like 2 or 3 my time I text the group chat,
"Yo guys, you guys want to record tomorrow night?"
And what do you know, Rex tells us.
Oh, I am so sick. I can't even say like more than two words before I start hacking
So I was like this motherfucker
Gave himself cancer and it's like no I can't I just can't record the podcast anymore
You think he got got by the squid box?
No, I was already sick when I bought this guy's what it looked like and it was really funny to me
That he got completely gone by the squid box
Yeah, that was not a wise purchasing decision I was in the middle of
Southeast Missouri, I went to a gas station to buy a vape.
I bought, uh, like a diamond air bar.
And I bought a favorites and I bought a squid box because it made me laugh.
And I tried it once and I thought I posted it.
Someone said, relax.
He's not, he's not well.
He's actually not well. He hit it one time. He didn't cough the first 20 minutes.
And now he's having to... He turned off his microphone to cough.
Oh.
Whew. Anyway.
I posted it on Twitter and someone replied that the people who got
tracheotomies from vaping got them from hitting the R&M vapes.
Is that true?
I didn't know.
I don't think it is, but the little part of me that thinks it could be true made sure I never hit it again.
And here you are hitting it.
It was not, it's in the chat. He's making fun of you.
Yeah, I am fucked up dude.
I hate being sick, but I haven't been sick in some time and I'd like to get it sick again.
No, it's not pleasant. You think it's not that bad and then you get it and it is bad.
So what got you?
See the only kind of sick that's good is when you're kind of making it up a little bit like you don't feel great
But you could definitely still live a normal life, but you're taking the excuse. Yeah
Yeah, okay. I'm sick. I get to be sick for two days. Whatever
watch TV
So what's the thing that got you actually Rex?
It's probably
the coronavirus
It is most certainly the corona. Yes. I definitely got it from a from like a they're saying it's back
They're saying COVID is back, sleeping bugs are...
*Squeak*
Bed bugs, sleeping bed bugs...
Sleeping bugs?
Are crawling all over every single major town in the world.
The fuck is sleeping bed bugs? I wouldn't be worried about a sleeping bug.
They are completely immune to any weapon now, is what I've heard.
Alright, have you guys ever had bed bugs?
No, and I really hope to keep it that way.
I had them one time when I was in high school.
And it was the same week that our washer and dryer broke
Oh, I had to haul I had to haul all this shit
Till that cuz you're supposed to like put it in the dryer for like three hours or something
Because it kills them or some shit and I had to I had to like dry
Everything that we owned at a laundromat down the street and I definitely I didn't know what I was doing
I definitely gave bed bugs to like 4,000 people
For sure. Yeah, that's awesome. Anybody else who went in that launcher Matt definitely got bedbugs
My yeah
Apparently like started in Paris and it's been like spreading fucking all over
It's a Mexican destructible bedbugs. Yeah. Yeah, it's a Mexico City right now and I just picked up
My girlfriend who just came back from Mexico City
So I will be spending the next part of it and not sleeping on our bed. I'll be sleeping on the floor
If it started in Paris, it's definitely in my bed
What is that? Why is that?
What's that people I have over
Parisians
Beautiful Parisian women stinkies lay in my bed and I paint them. They're completely stinky. Yeah, I
Paint beautiful women I do amazing
What do you think?
Huh, what do you think has the stinkiest apartment out of all of me? I have a fucking dog. I have a dog
Yeah, it's true. Yeah, it's got to be me if you have a dog
Please say my mom's house smells like so much fucking shit, dude
I walked into my mom. They have two dogs and it smells so it smells double bad and
They're what both of the dogs are so fat. They're the fattest dogs of every single time
There's a video my mom took like two years ago
Where I hadn't been home in like a year and I got home and my my mom's dog got fat in that one year
Went from like just a normal dog to the fattest dog. You will ever see in your entire life and
There's a video she took of me hysterically laughing and like like getting back in my car
Because I like can't even I can't even look at him. It was like the funniest thing I've ever seen in my life
anyway, that is the fattest ugliest dog of all time and
Yeah, dogs smell like shit cats. I don't know which one was worse though a cat apartment or a dog apartment
I think
Usually it's got a bunch of hair in it all over the place
But a dog apartment has just a bunch of piss and shit all over the floor
Yeah, a dog apartment has piss and shit. You literally keep the cat shit in the house
Yeah, but they shit in the little
that's what it dot my dog doesn't she but i guess it's shit inside at the end
since he was like
two months old
he just smells bad because he plays in shit
vote the previous tenants
at my place
the like downstairs they just locked the dogs in there all the time
and let them just piss and shit on the ground
and the entire like a_c_ is like straight-up yellow
from michael it's uh...
the
that
You and Brian going to get kidnapped for an entire Saturday.
- That sucked.
- I didn't also talk about my little thing about my haircut,
which I thought was really funny.
- Uh-huh.
- And I think that's the four things that happened this week.
- Okay, well let's go through them in order.
What was the first one you said?
- I mean, I guess the first one that happened
was my haircut.
I just thought it was funny.
So I finally went to get my haircut
after like a couple months,
and I didn't really know where to go,
So I just went to a place that my girlfriend has gone to before and I went with her.
So I was like, "Oh, I'll just go with you and I'll just get a haircut or whatever."
So we go to this place and a little callback when we're talking about glasses, I have got
both the things.
I can't see far or near.
So whenever I'm getting a haircut and I take my glasses off, I can't see myself in the
mirror.
So I just sit down, she's cutting my hair, I'm like, "Oh, you know, I just want..."
I didn't really have the strength to be like, "I'll just get like a mullet or whatever."
So I just want to get like, you know, two on the sides and just a little bit off of
the top.
You know, normal guy haircut.
Normal Hitler haircut.
Yeah.
So basically, she starts cutting and I have to hold back for like the entire time because
I'm like I just came to the HGW hair place where the guy next to me is getting his hair
like painted like pink and yellow and I'm just like sitting here asking for the Hitler Youth
cut.
And I was trying so hard not to laugh and then she's like okay I'm done, put my glasses back
on and is like oh it doesn't look like Hitler that much.
And like.
You look like a complete Hitler.
I immediately, the fan service was like this is so funny.
I just got the Hitler at this like, S&W.
You went to sports clubs with two S's man.
You need to stop going there.
No, I went to the, it's like complete, it's you know, it's where girls, annoying girls get their hair painted in crazy ways.
It's where, you know, it's in a rich part of town.
It's completely not where a guy is supposed to just go and get like, oh let me just get a two and live off the top.
And I still went there and I was like, yep, let me get that, let me get that Hitler, please.
But they did a good job, I feel great.
You need to get a funny haircut.
You need to get a normally...
I wanted to get a mullet, but I was too meek and quiet and shy.
Don't be so shy and quiet then.
You're such a bombastic piece of shit.
This guy, for people who don't know, Jubio is like Chris Farley style.
He shows up, he opens your fridge, he starts rummaging through perfume pills and shit,
Russian
to
the
one woman that's bold. Who's that? Will Smith's wife. True. I thought you were talking about
Doja Cat. She is the Hitler cut, you know what I'm saying? She is in the Hitler cut. She's
making Hitler cuts. Yeah. That's the kind of music she makes, y'all. Thank you. Thank
you Doja Cat. Let's go! This is a racist Nazi. Get the fuck away from me, you skinhead. Yep.
I thought you were pointing at me.
And she completely dates white guys.
And also, stop dating honkies.
Thank you so much.
Stop showing me your feet in our racial chat rooms that we hang out in.
And get your feet out of my mouth.
Maybe the all time funniest tweet.
Forever.
Who is she?
Noreatka.
Noreatka, dude, he's the man.
She in racial chat room, showing feet.
Alright, now.
Next thing in order.
Caleb and Brian got kidnapped for half a day.
So like I was saying last time on Pears We Drink.
Previously.
Me and Brian had to go to a...
Party.
Nevermind.
I was gonna say it.
I have to say it.
I have to say it now.
I won't say it.
We get there, it looks exactly like a plantation.
and they immediately make us clean up.
That's all I'm saying.
- That's awesome.
- That's all I'm gonna say.
They made us clean up.
That's all I wanna say.
Anyway, we get there and this is the most
demonic shit ever, guys.
There is so many, like this is an evil piece of property.
There's scary demon, they had a demon
that had a big cock, like statue.
And I was like, what the fuck is up with that?
That's some crazy shit.
and they were like yeah uh... it's just the the the previous owner was a
collective
the clack they collected the the fuck you tell me about cock guys yes here's a
cock
they had a scavenger hunt for that
alcohol for the car
and me and brian all those all two of those scavenger hunt places they're like
a map that's getting from the map that had all the alcohol
the place you get out the whole lake
marked on the map and people were only going to the two closest ones.
So me and him are there for 12 hours.
So at the end of the day, the last three hours were me and him walking to the last three
places and just taking all of the wine and stuff.
It was really awful.
Everybody was taking mushrooms.
Really?
God.
Except for me and Brian.
People are taking, they're micro dosing mushrooms.
They're sitting there.
I gotta be quiet because you might hear me.
They're sitting there, everybody there was dressed like a fucking pirate.
sitting around eating the worst food imaginable.
They were like, "Oh, dinner will be served soon."
Dinner was some fucked up eggplant salad that was like, it was disgusting.
It was so disgusting.
And then also Brian got in a fight with a woman because he thought that she didn't like
him.
He was just all fucked up.
a girl who's like not that nice to him and at the end of the night he walked up to her
and he's like "so you fucking hate me"
"you fucking hate me, what's that about?
why do you hate me so much?"
she was like "what are you talking about?"
and she was like "yeah, i can tell you fucking hate me"
"what, is it how i look?"
and i just went to the bathroom and i was like "i can't be around this dude"
drunk brian is so crazy
I get scared when I'm around drunk Brian.
I'm like, he might get in a fight.
He might punch someone right now because--
- He was so ready to go.
- He tried to fight, one time we were playing pool
and he wanted to fight this guy
and then I had to explain to Brian that the guy was gay.
And I was like, you can't fight this guy, man.
This is not a good look for you to fight this gay guy
at this bar right now.
Because he thought that he was being mean
but he was just saying kind of gay stuff.
he was like yeah like it was a brian would like miss a shot and the guy would be
like nice shot and brian was took that as like fuck this guy but really he was
just being kind of catty or whatever right but it was so fucking funny and
anyway that day sucked okay next one oh you were you became a slave to your mom
on your trip.
Okay guys, so I went to North Carolina this past week.
I went to North Carolina because my mom called me about a month and a half ago and she was
like "Hey, the car that you sold your stepdad is still in your name because you didn't get
the bill of sale notarized."
Wow, he's opening the Sour Monkey triple IPA, or triple Sour Monkey already?
You finished the beast sphere?
The beast spheres?
if you see yourself
peace there's a sense of ever seen you drink a beer maybe
and i feel horrible
alliance i'm coughing like every minute that's why you need to be here
you'll be back
uh... my mom
called me but they have a good says
bill sealed in get notarized for this car
we need you to come down
go to the d_n_c_
you get this all figured out
and i say okay when you want to come
probably like through the from like the thirtieth through the second would
probably be easiest for our schedule
and i say okay cool
into the phone call i say okay
bye mom
she said oh wait i forgot to tell you
we're moving into a new house
so while you're here you can help us move
and i kinda see what's going on at this point i'm like okay i think i'm seeing
what is really happening
So, I look at flights, the flights that leave on the 30th and come back on the 2nd are like,
they're like $500.
They're like so expensive.
And I was like, I'm not paying more than $100 to come help you move.
This isn't happening.
I'm going to come on the 3rd and leave on the 6th.
And she was like, "Okay, whatever."
She was all mad about it.
I get there on the 3rd.
She picks me up from the airport, immediately takes me to her old house.
They waited to move until I got into town.
Oh my god.
So I spent the next two days, all I did on my trip home, except for go to Ernest Money
and Sons and have an amazing tequila cocktail, is move boxes of fucking books and bullshit.
And also she didn't pack in normal boxes, she just put everything in the Tupperware she
has in her house because she didn't want to spend money on boxes.
So I'm moving a box this big with pins in it, and I'm stuffing it into the back of her car.
It made me, I was fuming dude.
Oh god. I would be pissed.
And then we get to the, and it gets worse guys, we get to the DMV.
Uh huh.
Hand them my ID. I like to handle the thing that I like to do.
She says, "Oh well you, yeah, exactly."
She says, "Oh well you could have just gotten it notarized in New York. They send you a fax and then you could have just sent it."
Oh no.
This bitch makes me come down.
And also so she was like she was like I'll pay for your flight and I said, okay cool
She says I'll reimburse you $50. So I'm losing I lost like a hundred and thirty bucks
Yeah on just the flights to go home and help my mom move
To help my mom. I had to help my mom. How awful is this story?
This is the worst story of all time. She needs to go to jail. Yeah, I'm sorry
That's horrible.
I'm popping off on everybody.
Taxi driver's my mom.
Whatever.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, man.
I'm s-
Yeah, that is horrible.
That's okay.
That- It's okay.
It makes me fuckin'-
It makes me sick to my stomach.
Well, at least I don't have cancer like Rex.
What was the fourth one?
Uhhhh...
I forgot.
I think Rex-
I- Rex-
You went out of town.
You didn't even tell us.
You- I- I found out-
Like, a day or two ago when I-
I said something to you and you were like,
"Oh, I'm out of town."
Yeah.
it
wins too
so i small town
into me to my girlfriend's parents
and stay with them for a week
uh... and i immediately got sick
and then like
the first by the way now that i think about it was probably what they were
expecting from uh... it was a guy dating their daughter coming from new york city
Yes.
Do you just get off here immediately?
Like, do you have a handkerchief?
And my nose is running.
My allergies.
So anyway.
I finally start to like feel a little better on like Thursday.
And uh...
They're like, "We want to have family game night.
Please join us."
And the dad gets Heineken.
Like a 12 pack of Heineken.
Okay.
So I'm like, "I'll have one beer.
I'm gonna like be as non-competitive as possible. Yeah, I'm gonna be like we're playing uno. It's going great
the dad comes in and
He's carrying the big bowl of assorted poker chips and decks of playing cards, and I'm like, oh my god
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, you're already locking in. I'm like no don't do this to me
so they start playing blackjack and
And like, they're playing it like PvP, like they're like playing against the dad.
Or like playing against, they're like, but not as the dealer, he's just another guy.
I didn't ask this when you told me this last, were you guys, was anybody putting any money up?
No money, just the chips.
So it's already making you mad just that there's no stakes?
Yeah, it's already zero stakes, there's absolutely nothing to be gained.
Just a waste of fucking time.
But I'm like, oh, that's not actually...
The rules aren't actually that...
You know, there's like a dealer, everyone plays against a dealer.
It's not like...
It's not PvP like this.
You're playing it like poker.
And so I'm like, why don't I just deal for you guys?
And I'll just show you guys the rules.
And so I'm doing...
I kind of like get into like the character of like an online poker dealer.
And I'm like, "17, would you like to hit? 13, would you like to hit?
Alright, Parajax, would you like to split?"
Yeah, Sexmonster, I don't know who Kanye West is.
He's immediately such a pro.
Yeah, I'm like, saying the numbers immediately, I'm like,
taking bets, I'm like, "You win, you lose, congratulations, sir.
21, blackjack, you know?"
I can't do it to you.
Yeah, so...
Reading the chat.
I can't, Ryan I'm reading the chat, we're doing crazy time.
*cough*
Oh fuck.
Oh jeez.
Anyway.
He's doing this whole thing the entire time, he's just coughing into the damn cards.
Yeah.
So anyway, they're having a blast, they're having a good time.
I feel like I'm like hiding my gambling level appropriately.
Like clearly I know, but I'm not an addict.
Uh huh.
And then they're like, "Okay, let's play poker."
And so they started exploiting the rules of like Texas Hold'em, because like only the mom knows.
And we get into this hand where it's like myself versus her brother, and I have a pair of- I have a pocket aces,
he has pocket kings.
Nothing happens on the first four cards, river comes, it's a king.
He flips over his cards, and I look at him, and there's like a violent twinkle in my eye.
*laughter*
I am just like, holy-
There's no stakes. I am just pissed. I am like you, like in my head I'm like you
river bitch, you fucking piece of shit, I'll fucking kill you. Like you know, it's
over nothing. There's no stakes. But in my head I'm like, oh I can't, I'm like, oh
that's a great, good luck man, that was awesome, great win. Just like violently
the
and you're like, "Oh, sweet bananas, what's that?"
- What is that?
- Okay, wait, so eight grapes pays 40x?
Oh, okay, very interesting.
- Oh, that's so interesting.
- You should've taken the casino.
- You should've said, "You wanna know about gambling?
"I'll show you gambling."
- Yeah, well, I was trying not to be like,
you know, I have a $300 a week gambling habit.
Thank you for not saying addiction. We don't use the "A" word in this podcast.
It's not an addiction. It's a habit.
I've made it a habit by being addicted to it for three years.
I think, um...
Yeah, I think that gambling addiction might be...
could be worse than, like, opioid addiction
when it comes to, like, in-laws finding out.
Right. Exactly. I'm like, this is the one thing they can't...
they can know I'm Jewish.
If you're addicted to fucking kills, at least you're skinny, you know?
Yeah.
Kind of non-threatening.
If you're a gambling addict, you're painfully sober,
you've been up for three days,
Yes.
and you are asking them for money.
So that might be the worst case scenario.
It is truly, like, the one thing that, like, every father-in-law would hate to find out.
Yeah.
I was like, "I cannot let them know."
that was like the first time
first time I ever played pool with Jana's family was at my brother-in-law's
wedding
like four years ago or something
and they're just white guys they just play pool they just hit the ball as hard
as they can
and
I'm a good pool player and I
had a eight ball break and run I broke
the rack and then I hit every single ball without my opponent coming to
the table
a single time
and I was so locked in and they were like
uh it was like a magic trick to them you would swear that I was like David
Blaine they couldn't believe it and they were like that was crazy and I
was like dude it is so crazy and then but I felt a demon come over me
and I was like maybe we do like 20 bucks on the next game
no no it's actually a bachelor party let's put 20 bucks actually here
I'll put 20 bucks, you put 5. I'll give you 4-1 odds on the game.
No, dude.
And yeah, I took like... doing that I took like $35 off him on his bachelor party.
Just because I was so addicted to playing pool.
It is so funny when you just accidentally show your real evil personality to...
Like the one people you're not allowed to.
Yeah, the one people you need to put on your pool.
Also, every time I hang out with my in-laws, they're always like,
"You guys want to get crazy tonight and have two beers each?"
Exactly.
And I go like, "I don't know how I'm going to handle two beers, guys.
That might be a little much for me."
So I was only going to have like one beer with her family, and the dad kept bringing
me more beer.
That was a test.
I hate to tell you.
That shit was a test.
Well, he brought me three beers, which is a completely normal amount of beers to drink.
I feel like. But then the next morning, he goes, "Oh, my head. Those three beers really
beat me up." So I think fast, think fast. I'm like, "Oh, me too. So hungover. I can
never drink that much beer." Oh, those three beers got me coughing.
What even happened last night guys?
Oh fuck me I had, I had three beers.
Oh my god, three beers?
I don't even know how I did that.
Yeah, I was talking to somebody today about, I think my mom probably thinks that I'm like
a massive alcoholic because every single time I go to her house I just drink wine the entire
time like from noon to midnight I'm just drinking wine and I don't have the heart to just be
the
on
just
right now
I talk to my mom maybe once every month and a half on the phone.
I want to give her some kind of jitterbug style or firefly, whatever that like kids phone was.
Something where I can, there should be a program on your iPhone where if you want to you can
set a time limit on a phone call and then after 15 minutes or whatever it just makes
it look like the call dropped.
It says call failed.
That would be, if they came out with a new iPhone that had that feature, I would be sitting
in, I would be camping outside of the Apple Store to get this new phone.
I know.
Just certain contacts in your phone.
Imagine being able to stop your mom from talking to you for longer than something.
Dude, it would actually be my mom and the landlord of the office.
Yeah.
Because he's talking to me about how lazy people who pick up trash for a living, how
lazy garbage men are. Does he call you often? That's so fucking sick.
Your hand plugged is mic'd. I had a crazy thing with my landlord recently.
She let us know like I think last month or three months ago. She was like, "You know
what? I don't think I'm going to be able to keep renting to you guys past our winter
contract was up which is in January. She just let us know like with
enough time so we can like look for another place. She's like yeah I just
can't do it anymore and you know I got whatever. She's like some excuse I
forgot what she said not something not that crazy. But then like last week she
texted like the previous people like they were staying here and she's like
yeah there's like all these issues and I've got like all this all like these
health problems and I just I feel so ashamed with the new guys you
know what and I just completely run out of money and now I was like dude what?
run out of money? I just completely ran out of money when she has done nothing to this
apartment in nearly a year and we pay our rent on time every single time
with that deposit she just completely run out of money I don't she is so insane I
I don't know what she does.
I wish I had the patience to ask her what is wrong with her,
but I just--
- You just wanna have to have a conversation with her.
I get it.
- Yeah, every time I see her, it's just so stressful.
I'm like, you know what, it sucks that I do have to go
in January, but I'd rather not deal with you anymore.
I'll take that hit.
I'll take a move to not deal with you.
- I went to buy a house so badly,
but guys, here's a problem.
i have no money
if i had met but uh... thousands of dollars i would buy a house i would have
one of the most fucked up mortgages of all time
i would be paying if the house cost a hundred thousand dollars to buy
in the long run i probably play paying one point eight million dollars that's
the kind of thing i would qualify for
i would still do it
just because
the idea of having to rent for another like ten years
drives me out of my mind and
that's just a little
there's no hope
somebody does this after forty minutes every single time
this might be a big deal
uh... this is the there's there's no hope for us guys
in new york city
we need to be living in west texas
i remember driving through west texas and i was looking at zillow
and it was like a hundred acre lots for like
for
like
The mortgage was about what I pay for like here.
Yeah.
Dude.
Yeah, that's my mom.
My mom told me her rent at her old place and it's like huge.
It was huge.
It was like the, it was the biggest house she's lived in, in my lifetime.
It was giant.
And she paid $1,400 a month for it.
Yeah.
for
one of those like old drug dealer mansions
yes i think so corny
but i don't think it would be like no no lawn work at all
yeah nothing green at all but fountains
fountains and uh... and uh... uh... semi-circle driveway
where were parking like like for runners and like really old
like shitty cars yes steve and qualms yes all my god
what we need is we need the a_n_p_ high pass
that's kai san at ok
we need to establish
i need you to be able to become a kai san at
level streamer
and we know
do a full
pipe house
uh... we have strippers
and we check for a little delivered
person this is what every single every meal is check for labor getting on
sundays we know people who know people
yeah this is a constant outlook on new york
He lives somewhere in New York.
Really?
Your mic is not working again.
Yeah.
Why are you- I'm switching mics.
He lives in New York with like other like- I actually saw a tweet about this today.
I think he lives with like three or four other streamers.
Uh huh.
Yeah, dude.
And it's a- it looks weird.
No, he lives in New York.
Yeah, I don't know about the Amp House.
Why?
I don't think I want to become a Kaisenet.
I want to become low-key and mysterious.
You...
You're the least mysterious person I've ever met.
Yes I am.
Tell me one thing about me.
So that's what I mean. It's not that you're mysterious.
It's that there's just not a lot going on.
Yeah, there's no mystique.
Tell me one thing about me.
You don't have any secrets.
There's nothing worth discovering.
Yeah, you have kind of just nothing.
I mean, you need to establish, if you want to be mysterious, you have to have something,
you need to have like people peeking, you know what it is dude?
Have people peeking in while you're streaming.
The hood is actually doing a lot for me.
I'm going to be completely honest with you.
That is mystique.
I think the big thing, Kaisenat's big break was that there was a mouse in his room.
That's true.
Yeah, that was like, the thing that skyrocketed him to stardom was that there was a mouse
in his room and he went like *high pitched scream* or something.
I think it's also the thing where he's just yelling all the time.
Yeah, I think that you can do that. You need to up your volume
in a major way. That's what you have to do nowadays to be like the
biggest streamer in the world. There's a guy... You have to be a scream man. Yeah, there's a guy
who's like a league streamer who was just like
meddling, like okay streamer, who wasn't really doing like crazy numbers
But then he just like switched his whole personality to be like a screaming SQC type beat.
And right now he's like the biggest European League streamer of all time.
Really?
Just because of his personality.
Why is that guy who's always at Brookland screaming at League?
No, he's European. He's completely in Europe.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
But as you can see, it's just children, dude.
It's Kesha.
They need to hear screaming.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
Yeah, I don't know. I don't like streaming that much.
My little brother who's like 12 years old was just like...
I would just be... like the night after we went to Earnest Money & Sons, I was like...
Hungover. Legendary.
Guys, this is one for the books. We went to Earnest Money & Sons, ate cookout, and we were home by 11 o'clock.
Oh, dude. I wish I had cookout. We talked about Escape from Tarkov the entire time we were at the bar.
Game that you played once.
a game i played one time but i just was
very interested
yeah and we were talking about the uh... has had a few people talking about
missing from park on the entire time
and the bartender was like
uh... sorry i can't help but but uh... for a little bit
it sounds like you guys have compared to our usual clientele so pretty
interesting lives
(laughter)
We were talking about a fucking video game for two hours.
What the hell is wrong with you?
But, he was cool.
Um, what was I saying?
Oh, yeah, so the night after that, I'm so hungover,
and, uh, we are, I'm sitting at my, at my mom's, like, table, her dinner table,
dinner table and I'm like eating like a like cereal like dry cereal cuz she only
had oat milk and I don't fuck with that shit and my little brother comes down
the stairs like this like tinted fingers right because he thinks that this is kind
of a cool thing that you do he's 12 years old he's 12 years old by the way six
feet tall so he towers over me he walks down the stairs like this sits down and
goes "Caleb, have you seen Skibbity Toilet?"
"Yes! Yes!"
And I said, "Buddy, don't even fucking get me started on Skibbity Toilet right now."
And then I spent about 20 minutes saying, "Dude, who do you think is going to win? The
Skibbity men or the cameraman, man? The Skibbities are basically invading the entire city. This
This is getting really scary if you're a cameraman.
It was awesome.
That was like probably the most I've ever bonded with any family member.
That's so sick.
Was him telling me about Skibbity Toilet.
Was he team toilet or team cameraman?
You know he team toilet.
They got that song.
That's true.
The one song.
They got that song.
Every single one video.
Yeah, how could you be team cameraman when Skibbity got that song?
I thought the skivvies were the evil ones and the cameraman were the good ones.
I got an evil brother man.
That's true.
Is he the tallest in your family?
By far.
Oh yeah.
He's 12 years old, he's 6 feet tall.
It makes me so mad dude.
It makes me so fucking mad.
And he also has, he can't, he can't play sports.
He like is interested in the knives on CSGO, but he doesn't play CSGO.
He gets on and he looks at every knife skin and then tries to find real life versions of
them.
That's his version of a sport.
Oh dude, you're making me depressed.
It's, no, no, it's very cool.
It's very cool and he will grow up to be one of the most normal adults who ever lived.
He needs to be playing sports, he needs to come home and be training on aim trainer.
Your ass went to a small town for one week and you're like, this boy better be on a football event.
We need eugenics.
This boy needs to drop that damn Xbox and a phone. It's making him fruity.
He loves the phone and it is making him fruity.
Yeah, I think having a brother that much younger than me has definitely made me...
I think whenever I want to have kids, we're going Amish, dude.
Okay.
There's no...
TV and video games and looking at a phone is so bad for a kid.
Well, okay.
You were on the computer when you were like 11.
Not, but I didn't have this one.
I didn't have this tapping one.
I think there's a balance that you'll find when you get to that point that you are not
thinking of right now.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
I think...
I like to believe that I would pass down the genetics able to be on the computer all the
time and turn out at least moderately normal.
You are going to tell your kid to play Mario 64 and be like "you're going to enjoy this."
I would not do that to them.
You're going to do that.
I was thinking today whether or not I would let my kid play the Persona games and what
it would teach them.
I think probably 13 years old.
Well it's Pokemon but then there's all this weird stuff with boobs.
Then I skip over.
Skip all the stuff with the boobs.
What happens with the boobs?
They jiggle.
And it's just odd.
supposed to be in high school and the whole game is like now we're gonna go to
the I'm trying to discover the mystery of the serial killer and they're like
before we find the serial killer let's all go to the bathhouse and all the guys
are gonna try to sneak up on the girls that look at them in the in the shower
yeah and I fucking watch it just so I know how to avoid it my next playthrough
so that I know exactly what parts to skip.
But it really is odd, man.
I'll say that much.
And it's not like it's a game from the 1800s.
Guys, this is only a 10-year-old video game.
Mm-hmm.
The thing is, it's just fine for Japanese to be slight pedophiles.
Uh...
Yes, we'll probably end on that.
That's probably a good--
Don't make my plan that's the end!
That's probably a good place as any.
- Rex thinks that, and I think that's enough for this week.
- In the episode.
- That's two weeks in a row, you can't do this to me.
- You had something wrong with you.
See Lex, something about being a pedophile.
- Last week.
- I think last week you said something
about being a pedophile as well.
- I had Carl Malone.
- Well man, I would say that reflects on you more so
than it reflects on me and Julio.
- All right, well next week we're gonna do
liquor we enjoyed.
- We're team Yelp, and I'm spot limo.
- Liquor we enjoyed next week.
We'll see you guys, thank you for joining us.
And that's it, goodbye.
- Bye.