And we're recording and it's the theme song.
[SOUND]
You're listening to beers we drank, America's number one beer broadcast.
[MUSIC]
What's up all my chuggers?
*BURP*
This is a journey into...
*Gibberish*
...Pinekint!
...Bud Light!
...Half-Fu Ribbon!
...Beers We Drank, Motherfucker!
With Juvio, Caleb, and Rex!
*Beer*
Welcome back, ladies and gentlemen, to...
...Beers We...
...Drank!
Guys, and as your host, I would like to, at the top,
Caleb is gonna regale us with an awesome apology
to his friend Rex.
For what?
Why?
Why would I apologize to Rex?
You tortured him by telling him the wrong time and he ran and he's so tired.
Look, he's still wearing his jacket.
He just-
I did literally run directly from outside.
I didn't torture anybody.
You told him to run.
You told me 6 o'clock on the dot.
I think I said right around 6 o'clock I said.
I think those are the exact words.
Rux ran-
Which is 2 or 3 minutes on either end.
You didn't have to run.
You did not have to run. Let's see, let's pull up the record because we actually have these.
Okay, I did say right at six. So yes, I would like to issue an apology.
I would like to issue a full apology to my friend Rex. Rex, tell me before you get into your mirror,
tell me what is this huge man looming in the background of your life?
Take a look here. It's Chinese Patrick.
Is a friend of yours?
This is a, it's a TikTok screenshot I found when I was looking for a new background.
Cause my room is messy and I didn't like the background.
It really kinda does look like Patrick, man.
That is Patrick's face.
Pat owns that beanie?
Yeah.
Wow.
That's Chinese Patrick.
Well, that's pretty impressive.
Chinese Patrick.
Is that his username on TikTok?
I don't think so.
Let's go beer.
Let's get into beer.
I um, I have a really bad beer this week.
I honestly guys I did not I did not want any alcohol
I had alcohol last couple nights, and I've been eating my against zero time. Oh another Heineken zero guys
As well he can't drink any beer guys come on I'm running out of laundry
I'm having a bad day. Okay, I already told
Rex my dog is vomiting up yellow
Yellow disgusting the same time a almost to the minute two days in a row like 4 55 p.m
He has vomited up two yellow puddles and the first time dogs vomit a lot
So or not a lot, but every once in a while, there's vomit randomly
And so I didn't worry about it too much and then this time same exact time
So now I gotta take him to the vet tomorrow. Do are you feeding him poop?
That was also my question.
That's exactly what Rex asked.
Again, no.
He's not eating poop.
He's not eating anything yellow even.
He did, two days ago, get about a teaspoon of bolognese off the ground, which really
pissed me off because I spent a long time working on that for people, human people,
not a dog.
No, it was on the ground.
I don't think you can serve bolognese to people from the ground
Here's the thing Rex you would never know I
Would if you come over to my house and I make bolognese and I put in one
Teaspoon falls on the ground and I and your portion is one teaspoon short
You're giving me first of all
You are a fucking ground bolognese. I spent the whole time making the food. I'm at your house. How is that my fault?
You're serving me literal ground food. It's not your fault. You're not paying for anything
I paid for all the ingredients. I will if there's a dog hair on one of the bowls, you are getting the dog hair
I'm picking up a bottle of wine on the way
This is ridiculous. I already got bottles of wine.
You're treating me like shit. You're treating me like your fucking dog.
You want to come over next week? Sure, I'd love to.
Okay, I have a follow-up question. Maybe he hasn't been eating poop or anything yellow. Has he been been eating anything
red and green combination type shit two different things
things.
Oh yes, he's been eating cherries and uh...
Lettuce.
Right.
And, so I guess that would make yellow.
No bitch, he eats fucking brown pebbles.
That's all he eats is pebbles that are this big.
Rachel Ray makes these pebbles.
Well when brown is in a dog's stomach it turns yellow.
This is true.
Wait, what's that?
What's that? Can you explain this for me please?
When brown is in a dog's stomach...
I want to learn about this process.
When a chestnut of a dog burns brown into yellow...
Can we get to your beers?
I don't want...
This is all I've had to think about all day is if my dog is dying and what colors he ate
and what colors are coming back out of him.
So I need to hear from you two what colors you are drinking right now.
Well I have elected as the best beer in the world
Beer?
Beer.
I have a-
Woah!
You scared me man.
Turn that background off.
I don't care.
I feel like there's going to be a bad reveal once we take this head away.
Some sort of insane mess.
I saw his mess.
Oh, it's just a pile of clothes.
Okay.
Yeah.
I have a-
White elephant.
The Belgian Tremends.
Okay.
And it says it's...
Can you see this? Elected as the best beer in the world.
Whoa!
Democratically elected? I don't remember being involved.
I didn't vote.
So we're gonna see.
We're gonna see if this is the best beer in the world.
Yep, that's beer.
It's okay.
a 5 out of 10 beer. Is it the best in the world? I have a new idea, okay? Okay. So give it a
number rating first of all. Go ahead. Yeah, that's like a 5, 5 and a half out of 10. Okay,
so now we are going to skip over basketball. Because this beer was supposedly elected, give
me an elected official that this beer most resembles in flavor.
It's Joe Biden because I can barely remember what it tastes like after I drink it.
Damn. So that's a turd sandwich I would call that.
Yeah. It's a completely average, just, you know it's beer, it tastes like beer, you can't
remember a single thing that's happened about the beer or any features about it.
the
I can't vote for a sober man. Well, you're sober so you wouldn't vote for yourself. Do not sober
That's a sober beer. That's sober because I want to have something for the show. So you are sober here
I'm sober at the moment
Okay, I won't be in
eight hours
So
hours I don't know but I can feel it I probably wake up and go get a beer okay
at 2 in the morning all right well I'm gonna go next and I'm gonna I actually
brought a beer that I've been talking about for a while on the stream and I
think on the show which is a a carta blanca a carp blanch this is it has a
bit of a red stripe look to it it's a it's a regional beer it's one of the
oldest most popular beers in the region here. This is a Acaiwamita which Acaiwam is like
a like a like a 40 ounce 40 but this is the the small version of that so this is a
less than that. 12 ounce? Maybe I don't know I'm not sure. Anyways this is a cute little beer it's
beer that all the poor people drank until it got gentrified so now you can get it at expensive
the
and
right
means
now
I have a reason. I was just at the supermarket. I did the buy on your phone and pick it up at the parking lot thing.
I was on my phone and I was looking at Twitter. Apparently he can't remember anything. He can't remember his name anymore.
That is not a problem to me.
Okay.
He is like the prevent defense of presidents.
I mean, yeah, what is a president goes...
The president, the only reason the president exists is for us to have the battle every couple
years and so the kind of the crazier somebody is, the funnier the battle is.
So I'm looking forward to the battle of 2024 very much so.
Yeah, but what I'm saying as a person on the outside is, why not, why just being two old,
the oldest white guys in the world, why not the two youngest babies in the world?
to bring race into this, huh? Yeah. The two youngest babies in the world. Okay, and do
you care if they're white or not? You seem obsessed with the fact that it's white, old
white guys? It's more the age thing. Okay, reverse racism. We should see whose balls are
saggier. That's who should get to be the president. With the babies? That is really strange. You
think they should take the babies? Why are you saying that? Because it's very odd, man.
the old white man on the dot.
Well you said that after he said the baby thing.
I said the baby thing.
We should see who has balls that are staggered.
We were discussing the baby thing and you were like I want to look at them.
The balls.
Alright.
And oh I should be the judge.
Yeah I'm right.
I should be the judge.
I should see which ones look better and taste better.
No no no no no.
Why?
You're nasty man.
Ok so what's going on this week guys?
Let's get into it.
What's happened since, first of all I miss you guys.
I miss you too. I feel like you know, it'll explain thing in rope on having you
Can we talk about that?
Damn we just broke up the news like that. Yep
And I'm playing a I it was originally for persona now I'm playing a much much worse game
Which actually okay
so I played the first one right and I was like this is really like stupid and clearly is made for like
14 year olds, but it's kind of funny. So I like it and I like the mystery stuff
Even though it's all really predictable I get to the second one now all of a sudden this is a game for pedophiles. I'm completely
Like I am not going to listen I got to solve the mystery though, so I
All the whole mystery and then I am out of there after the third one
And then I will really be out and I'm not playing any of the spin-offs. Okay, maybe I'll watch some
Let's plays on YouTube just this make sure the mysteries get solved. So it seems
It seems we were in the chat are in the know it seems that Rex is really in the know
I have never heard anything past the name for this game. So you really have to explain what you mean with those two statements
okay, the first one is just kind of
very the kind of convoluted writing that you expect from like
a lot of like Japanese stuff like like TV shows and shit where if you get past
like the first season or second season or whatever it just kind of gets really
crazy and has a million twists and all this shit and it's kind of fun
I kind of like that aspect of that shit but then the second one is like
every single it's divided into chapters and there's one character they're all
high schoolers there's one character that every single chapter like falls on the
ground it has her and it has her full ass exposed and that is it always factors
into the mystery somehow wait is that true yeah in the first in the first
thing there's a there's a there's a part where like the lights go out and then
this this fucking one character like falls over and her ass and her ass and pussy is
like out and then they're like where were you during the during the murder and one guy's
like oh I was in the room and they're like okay so what happened he's like well nothing
happened and they say you have to have been the murderer because you would have said that
you liked seeing her asshole and that's like how the murder gets solved. Wait, wait. It's
Bizarre man
Yeah, so I don't really know how I'm feeling about this one, right?
And again, this is Rex's recommendation and he said specifically he gets to be a text. I played the first one
He said do the first one's good, but the second and third one are the best
Yeah
so
Yeah, I don't know. I'm just gonna
All right, I'm gonna finish it out I guess I have a follow-up question which Japanese shows have you swatched
Naruto okay, I guess that makes sense. That is a Japanese show avatar
That's not different rats
What else King of the Hill?
Okay
They're all kind of the my favorite shows. So I'm into Japan. All right, but yeah, I think
I don't know. I do I think I'm going to probably quit playing these games after this one for real and play ace
Attorney because it was free on game pass and it looks like the same kind of thing without
sex
Yeah, but you need it. It needs to be more Japanese. It needs to be funny. Ace Attorney isn't funny enough
What?
How have we like skirted around Rex just fully recommending you to play yakuza for so long?
uh... that's another one of those that those there's too many of those games
so
and i was a little bit more than a does the one with the zero next to it
that's a a a a a a small
yet but
they also don't look all that fun to me they look too much like grant that dot
o
the
it like rent that's not a that is
i'd i don't dislike rent that's not a bad tried playing
replaying g_t_a_ five
and uh... it was a really really boring me
you know what i had a little over the budget you can afford those are really
good one
i've never played any of the city to five and i really like you should have
played it
i think you can force like maybe the political
you know that's a lot where your cousin is calling you all the time
but you have another country yet what does that sound awesome as fuck
you know you're in new york
running around.
"Rico my cousin."
Yeah.
Uh, that's the type of things he says.
You would like Yakuza, especially because you like the...
I think if you get into Japanese stuff, there's like a part of your brain that enjoys how
retarded Japanese storytelling is.
Sorry, one Heineken zeroed down.
Done and dusted.
Thank you.
On to the next.
Oh, what's the second beer?
Heineken one.
Heineken zero.
Um, fuck you.
Why are you even asking?
you
why even ask that
because you're setting
sorry
so you like japanese people because you think that they have a disability
is that what you say?
well they just like love to ham fist like a twist
every 30 seconds
towards the end of a story
that's like japanese storytelling style
that is what i've experienced
yeah playing the persona games
and then
playing uh
this other game
I thought that that was just like a quirk of the Persona series, but it is so awesome for there to be
so many twists, no real like, and then always a pretty disappointing ending.
Yes, that is literally it. Amazing twists in like the middle towards the late part of a story,
and then just an impossibility to wrap it up well.
Yeah, kind of lost type of thing.
That is 100% every good Japanese story is like that.
Even the best ones, they always fail at the end.
Yakuza, on the other hand, blows it.
Actually finishes strong.
- Sticks the landing. - Sticks the landing.
- Okay, so maybe I will check out this game.
- Yeah, because it actually...
It's like, emotional and good
in a way that like contrasts with how stupid the actual game is.
Do you know what I mean? I think the feeling that I, listen I like Japan fine. Yeah. And I,
but I keep playing these games and wishing that there was one that took place in America
at like Hollywood high. Yeah. And I could, there was some kind of awesome murder going on there
and then I realized that that's kind of just LA noir. Yeah. Yeah, Sidney Sweeney's in it. It's a
full uh what do they call that FMV yeah yeah FMV Sydney Sweeney is just a picture or a video
and she's talking to you and uh you can see under her skirt Japanese style yeah again why are you
making no no no no no no this is American style okay she gets hit by a car and then you get to see
The blasts explode. You see them for one second and the car explodes.
Yeah.
Awesome.
How long until I can try to push you into playing the MGS games do you think?
I don't like doing emulation because I feel...
I don't like being involved in black hat hacking.
Which I consider emulation to be black hat hacking.
I only participate in white hat stuff.
Well the fifth one is on the computer.
Well then I might be able to play that.
I might be able to play that one.
I do think that MGS5 is probably one of the best games ever made.
Yeah it's really good.
You know I've been playing Danganronpa, which again bad name, doesn't feel like a Japanese
word to me.
What does it mean?
I don't think it means anything.
No, it means something. It means like bullet theft or some shit.
I looked it up because I was like, "This doesn't make any sense."
Okay.
Or bullet identity or something. I don't know. Some shit like that.
I'm sure we're about to learn right now from Rex.
I couldn't tell you because I don't know what's in there.
Can I do a little aside? Doesn't Rex look like he's wearing a suit right now?
Yeah, I thought he was.
I thought you were going full Green Day.
No.
I'm just wearing a hoodie and a jacket.
It's a suit-esque kind of jacket.
Yeah.
Well, all jackets are suit-esque.
I found an amazing video today because the other game I've been playing is Vampire Survivors.
I play this game a lot when I'm just like, when the wife goes to sleep and I have to
stay up with the dog because he's like really energetic.
I sit there and I throw a ball and I play Vampire Survivors because I can just play it
with one thumb stick on the Xbox.
and I have been like listening to uh audio books while I play it so I started listening
to Killers of the Flower Moon but I don't want to watch the movie but I the story I don't
want to watch it yet but the story I didn't know it was a real story when I found out it
was I got this audio book and then um I got a little bored with that one after I listened
to
that it was some kind of new translation of of meditations where he says like uh
he's like it's first couple minutes feels normal and then he's like and then i met uh epidaeus
and i thought he was the real mvp and i loved his vibe and it's some kind of like
fucking it's some kind of like zoomer translated
that like is i'll have to send it to you it's fucking crazy it's um but it's still i think
it still has like an old british guy narrating it right and i've just been imagining all day
just that guy getting the job to be a narrator for a marcus aurelius audiobook and then he gets
into the booth and starts reading it and it's also mark that's a that's a not a long book but it's
it's not a super short book and the the whole thing is like an hour long which means they took
out everything and just made it about like not talking to girls or something.
So I'm gonna listen to the whole thing and I'm gonna report back.
What's funny about Marcus Aurelius, and this has been going around on Twitter and Reddit,
is that his wife cheated on him with like a gladiator.
So it like, recontextualized, he's like, you know, don't talk to girls, don't enjoy anything.
Meanwhile, he's married and his wife is cheating on him with like a retarded jock.
That's the funniest shit in the world!
it is like
such a book for losers
yeah but
yeah i mean once you get past a lot of the basic stuff it is a lot of like
fine detail advice
that really can only apply to your life if you're the biggest nerd in the world
yeah which is what it is
like he's writing that meanwhile his wife is just
and here's the thing you could kill your wife back then for doing that
but he probably wasn't strong enough
yeah
she was risking death to get dick
now cheating means nothing now
you know
you can't kill your wife for cheating
but back then you could fuckin
you could ground up like five guys and just go kill her
that's true
i think it's very admirable
of him to write that stuff
and then not pretend not to care
yeah i
i don't know anybody who's ever recommended me that book who i thought
was really cool. Right. For sure. But that's kind of true of any philosophy book I think.
Anybody who is like, "read this book, it'll change your life" means, "read this book, this
is how I got to be like this." Yeah, well I think if your life is changed by a philosophy
book, you have like a mental deficiency. Yeah, if you have one, if anybody has one book where
they're like, "this is the book, man," you need to, they got something wrong with them
man except for the infallible word of God. Right. Well right, obviously. If you read a
book like that and you and you don't you actually think just a guy wrote it like
the Bible makes sense you think God wrote it if that changes your life that's fine
if you read a book that just a guy wrote a guy like 2000 years ago or even even
worse if you read fucking some Mark Fisher book and you're like this changed
my entire life. He killed himself. He killed himself with his car man. Or something. That's
not who gives a fuck about. I just you can like the book but it can't be like oh this
changed my life so much. That's just whack. It's not admirable to think so much you kill
yourself. Which is exactly. That's the biggest loser thing you can do. That's fucking gay.
thinking what are you retarded he thought oh the key to life was to kill yourself
shit i'm not reading your damn book i'm gonna catch this oh god don't you write a book about
a sword fucking idiot yeah right book about movies a behind if marcus aurelius had written a behind
the scenes about all the plays that were happening and who was having sex with who like an oral
history of Saturday Night Live. God dang it. That would have been fucking... I would have
loved that book. I would love that book, man. But instead he wrote this dumbass book. This
dumbass book that says, "Hey, don't wear the same clothes outside as you wear in your house."
Suck my dick, man. Fuck you. Fuck you, Marcus Aurelius. Fucking dumbass. Go get Cheeto on
your wife some more. Yeah, I'm done with all this kind of shit. I'm only reading
historical nonfiction from now on. Nah, you can't do that. That's a
dark road. No man, I want to read about... I want to get into... I've never been in one
of these men who is very so obsessed with war, so I want to read war books from
now on because they will make me... they'll prepare me for what is to come in
this
possible version of this when I was a kid when I was a kid I read basically every
thing at my reading level of like 10 or 11 years old that had ever been written
about the Holocaust I read pretty much all of it yeah I read pretty much all of it I
read the big one I read was that book milkweed and all that kind of stuff I
I read Maus and all this shit, and then I, uh...
I don't know, I never got interested in any of like Civil War stuff or anything like that.
What inspired this?
What inspired my desire to read about war?
Yeah.
Because I think that I'm going to be thrown on the front line of some war very, very soon.
I can feel it.
I can feel that I have...
His head is so reflective of the behind the enemy.
I think I have about a 28 month, 28 more months as a civilian I would say.
Do you think the US Army would use Caleb as a Rudolph?
And now I never...
Yes or no question, it's really simple.
You know, maybe.
They maybe would.
That really stunned me.
That really is funny.
I would be open to that.
I'd serve my country, but I'm not even sure that I will be fighting for the United States.
But I know that I will be drafted into some kind of war.
It could be a gang war.
It could be another...
It's gang war right on the side of...
I'm fully a Hoover Street Crip.
I see.
See I do I think we're going up in a in a Brooklyn I
think I've had a for too long the hipsters and the
Yeah, see that's a tough one for me I've seen that one act out it happens
Yeah, this is the most common war
In the entirety of the world
The gangsters will be like you should go back where you came from
And it'll be like a Chinese girl in big glasses and they'll be like I moved here three years ago. I live
This is the hipster verse gangsta
Okay, so you're clearly on the side of the hipsters just based off of the impressions you're doing
I do think we have a perfect-
I'm pulling on the side of the gangstas!
No, we have a perfect hipsta vs gangsta thing going on right here.
I would say.
What, is I'm gangsta?
Yeah.
See, that's what I was gonna say.
Yeah, look at me.
Wait, hold on.
There he goes.
He's gonna button the top button and then unbutton the rest of them?
He's not sure.
to do that, yep.
I'm fine.
But I'll do it anyway.
Hipstas vs gangstas is tough for me because I lived the life of a hipsta, but I was born
and bred a gangsta.
Right.
I'm a G straight from the 9-1-0.
I'm from Drillmington, Kilmington, North Carolina, about an hour north of Myrta Beach.
So this is a tough one for me.
And also I like the gangsta outfits more, clearly.
they look better on me than any kind of hipster BS
you know
uh...
what are you laughing at?
you need a skull tattoo
this is going to take you to the next level
no i'm saying on your skull
i have gang tattoos tons of gang tattoos from all the games i've been in
you know i don't play yakuza because i live that shit
it's a bit of a
this is my back
the doctor said this is where my back started it's a condition i have
long-term leader raters tattoo on your forehead
is what i'm saying
i would get that
you know brooklyn that's that i think i'm for i think i'm pretty much talking
to my wife about this the other night
i think i'm pretty much done with tattoos i'd think that not that i fully regret
getting tattoos
but they hurt very badly they're expensive
And I just don't, I think I got enough of these fucking things.
I don't need any more of them.
They're a little bit disgusting, you know, if you get a bunch of them.
Yeah.
I do think in general they're usually pretty embarrassing.
So I think I'm dumb.
When I was growing up it was like everybody had tattoos and, you know, I just wanted to
be like my brother.
And then now I'm more into kind of Japanese video games.
So I don't really care that much about this kind of thing.
So you don't think that if you play too much Yakuza you'll be like, "Oh, I'll just get a
dragon tattoo on my back."
It would be cool to get a dragon tattoo on your back.
Well, yeah, because also you have no worry about somebody taking it the wrong way if
you live in America.
You can get all sorts of...
Hasn't that always kind of also been kind of a just a not...
I mean, Pat got a tattoo and people took it the wrong way.
I feel like you can get a tattoo the wrong way.
But maybe not a Yakuza tattoo.
Yeah, he would look like a...
There might not be that many people who know what that is.
Also, my brother has a dragon tattoo on his back.
Hey, that goddamn girl from that movie had a dragon tattoo.
Rooney Mara had got that. Nobody thought she was Yakuza.
Well, maybe I didn't see the movie.
Yeah, I didn't see the movie. I can't prove you wrong on that.
It was a really long movie about a lady detective who was really special because she's got tattoos
all over and the mystery is she got kidnapped by a rapist.
Yeah, typically a woman detective creating more crime.
Creating it by being victimized?
Yeah. Get out of there! I'll let you
investigate dinner.
It's not even funny. It's like the worst joke
ever.
You look like Ben Franklin right now.
He looks like a mariachi bro.
I'm laughing too much man.
Oh god.
Whatever.
I'm trying to move this show.
Guys we gotta break this show out into the mainstream.
We can't be saying shit like this.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I don't know how to reach across the aisle to the new audiences.
Dude, I, uh, oh someone said Rick's talking about Vosch right now.
I saw that picture!
What happened?
I did see the clip.
It was very funny.
Vosch, one of the fattest people who's ever lived.
Drama alert.
Vosch, wait, people are reminding me in the chat of so many things we have to talk about.
number one
vosh uh...
saw or had a bunch of pictures disgusting drawn pornography on
and actually that was
that was uh...
another thing that made me think i don't want to play this danganronpa game
because i was like i think that this
is why this guy's probably like this he probably played this game when he was
like fifteen
yeah
uh...
so that was a disgusting thing but in other sort of perverted news
drake
had his schmeat
flopping in the wind on a bed.
- What? - His shit is like
- Oh yeah, I saw that. - A wiggling.
- He had a wiggling worm that he showed a woman
through the web.
- Okay, so first things first,
he did not show that to a woman.
He posted that himself.
- He leaked that post?
No, he did not.
- He leaked that himself.
- Why would he choose now?
Do you think maybe he just got the like
dick lengthening surgery and got home
and just started wiggling his new wiener on the bed
and recorded it and sent it to his publicist
and was like, "Send this to somebody over 18
"and let's get this online."
- I can't fathom the mind of Drake,
but I know for a fact that he wants that attention.
'Cause there's no attention on Drake right now.
No one gave a fuck about Drake before this happened.
- I don't think that's true.
- Everything was about Taylor Swift.
Everything was about fucking Megan Thee Stallion
and Ice Spice and whatever other women.
It's time for the men to come back.
And he brought it back by showing
his huge dangly floppy penis.
- So he did this for us, is what you're saying.
- Okay.
- He took attention off this was for the guys.
- So I have a counterpoint.
You know how everyone before this was like,
oh, why is Drake doing all this corny shit?
Why is he acting so gay and talking like a girl on stream?
I think and then people then this comes out and people are like oh we got to respect Drake because he's got a penis
And I'm I'm thinking why is he got that and why is he acting like this?
X norm on what you mean player
He's so embarrassing
He's so I would yeah, cuz he has a huge penis. Was he gonna feel embarrassed? He gets to just open his pants and see I
Would like to say one thing. Okay. Hmm cuz you brought a good thing up. He's been acting gay
I spent probably 45 minutes looking at this video
Frame by frame play by play. I'm not kidding. I was in the bathroom
It was taking a little longer than normal and I thought I'd dedicate some time put in some hours, right?
Did you happen to have any stitching?
Didn't see any stitching but I will say this man. I've seen a lot of cocks in my life
That is very clearly a gay man's penis. I love right now
know. It's too big. It's too big. First of all, yeah. No woman needs. They don't want
that is genetically affirmed to me.
It's too gay for a woman that only could go in a guy.
Only a big guy could use that.
Okay.
So that's it.
Number two, it was, it's too wiggly.
It's way too wiggly.
Okay.
It doesn't, and the number three, it did not have a lightning bolt Harry Potter vein that
all straight men's penises have.
If you don't have that vein, then the guy you're having sex with and you are the same.
That's my rhyme.
The vein, if you don't have the vein, the sex is the same.
And if you do, the girl you screw.
A girl you screw.
But the biggest thing is, it's way too big.
The biggest thing is penis.
And the smaller your dick is, the straighter you are.
And, uh...
Yeah, that's all I have to say on that.
The micropenis guys are also gay.
No, that's the straightest thing ever.
I think there's a range.
It's 50/50.
Okay.
There's 50/50? What?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. There's like...
'Cause there's straight guys with really tiny, like, micropenises.
like to be like humiliated for it and there's gay guys with micro penises that
are just like I need my ass to be destroyed and it's kind of the same
impulse but yeah okay I think you're saying there's a sweet spot in the
middle if it's too small or too big right then you're your odds of being gay
are and you're heterosexual if it's in the middle right so you might be right
chance that your sweet penis is making you gay. My sweet penis? My sweet penis. Is that
what you just said? My sweet penis is making me gay? That's what you just said. Nuh uh.
You said there's a 50% chance my sweet penis is making me gay? What are you saying? Odd
choice of words, Jubio. My sweet penis. But, wait, what was the thing that we came out with?
Well, we didn't come out with it. We invented it. Well, we didn't invent it. We thought of
of
people listen to this podcast they talk to us all the time we can't tell you they
are obviously don't wanna compromise their identities and a lot of them would
probably get flamed in public for this project also to be honest we don't want
the heat
ok you know we don't want to be we're doing fine without it
so uh... maybe that is going around and this is the first week off of the
celebrity only p real that has now just dribbled down into our open mouths
Here's what I'll say.
The sheer joy that Drake's penis brought to every man in the world that day proves that
peen real is a public good.
The world is enriched by peen real.
I think I agree.
I think that this could be... and also, this is giving an amazing lesson to men all around
the world.
As Drake often has.
does take care he does Marvin's room what's the lesson off of that oh you it's
good to cry you can cry and still be an awesome badass boss who wears sweaters
yeah right and then the newer albums come out what's the lesson from these you can
have much younger friends yeah you can have much much younger friends who were
in elementary school when you were in college that's the lesson of all these
is
Yeah.
Okay.
Because you're Drake and you're fucking gay.
It's delightful to see a man's penis for the first time.
God, oh, that feeling?
When you unzip it and you see it for the first time?
That is the best feeling ever.
I don't need to see it again.
You can put it away right after.
Let me see it.
I want to see that shit.
I need to know.
I do have-
Put it added to the Rolodex.
I have a-
Small but ever-growing desire to see all of my friends penises the more I get to know them the longer that I go
Being friends with a man without ever seeing their penis
The weirder it is to me the more I feel like they have something to hide if I've been friends with somebody for 10 years
And I've never once seen their penis not even a trunk. Yeah, that's
Something is wrong there a man's penis is like 30% of his person
It's 30% of his body. Yeah, well, it's 30% of his mind
You know, this is some Marcus Aurelius shit. I'm sure that I will get to this very soon in the book
Absolutely, I mean a man bases his entire identity off of his penis
The penis is a smaller medium. There's a reason why you look down and and and you see it
It's because it's the same as it's a reflection pond you look down and you yourself
You see all your hopes and all your dreams your future your potential is all what he acts good that
Disgusting pink piece of meat, right?
Or in some cases brown like poop. Oh
I want to talk about the color of it - it looked purple. I
Don't know
It looked like he may have a plump purple penis
He's a purple penis eater.
Just wanna say that.
Yeah.
I think he may have just seen an eggplant emoji.
Covering it.
Maybe. Well it also could have been, you know what it is?
Maybe he was jelking it so hard to get it like so full of blood.
That it was like, it looked like a suffocated person.
Yeah, he was laying there for like 10 hours that day.
Just like, "I gotta get this right."
Just adding rubber bands on the bottom.
Yeah, so long getting ready to
Wiggly it's no wiggling that and what girl is watching that video that he sent this to what?
Scene so many penises that he's trying to fuck. Oh
Is I can do the one thing it's supposed to get hard
By the way, it wasn't enough that it was a big dick
I need to see that shit wiggle something that I don't know
I don't know if you notice kill but someone in my chat noticed immediately after the video came out
They came into the chat and they're like Drake has no balls
Let me let me say something okay. Mm-hmm. I
Have a similar affliction
Okay, my Pete gets
Wiggle we gets
And I won't say it gets as large as Drake's that would be completely crazy for me to say that when it gets purple
when it gets
When my dick gets purple
My balls shoot up to protect themselves for my razor-sharp dick
Okay, and if you put your hand at the base of your penis
It's possible that it looks like you have no balls and instead you have a hand there. Yeah
so
That I don't I don't fault him for having
It should basically look like a spoon.
It should be just a shaft and then a small teardrop where your ball skin is.
Exactly, yes.
If your balls hang- oh here's another thing.
If your balls hang low, you're gay.
Yeah.
What's the rhyme?
If your balls hang low, you're on the down low- no.
You're um.
You like bunghole.
If your balls hang, men you do bang.
the
So it's really that simple.
So that's pretty much any conclusions on Drake's thing?
I liked looking at it, I think I'll look at it again right now.
I just want to get one other...
Let me see if I can look at this video.
Drake penis video.
It's kind of hard to find, right?
Is Kyle Penis Problems still a public subredditor?
There's probably one, there's probably a post top of the market where it's like "I can't
fucking believe this Drake shit."
Yeah, that's what I'm looking for.
Where can I find a video of Drake's meat?
Drake 11 inch penis reveal.
Oh, I got, alright.
Wait, I'd like for you guys to hear this.
This is, uh, I just pulled up this.
It's not coming through on Discord.
Can you hear this?
No.
*Drake singing*
You got Rickrolled?
I got fuckin' Rickrolled, guys.
You thought I- you thought I-
*Drake laughing*
You thought Drake's penis was gonna be on YouTube?
I did some kind of black hat hacking and changed the link to say
xhamster.com/drake11inchpenisreveal
Um, so that has happened to me...
Uh, fuck, man. Alright, oh, I found it.
He meant to troll the world?
Wait, ok I'm looking at this video.
Looks like he's in a tour bus I would guess.
Or a plane.
Someone said he was in his mansion.
Yeah I think he's in bed.
Cause he's filming in a mirror and it's a pretty decent sized way.
Yeah but there's a lot of wiggling.
Maybe that's why it's wiggling is cause he's in a plane or a bumpy...
Oh there's altitude.
Yes.
all
Wiggly your penis gets on an airplane
and I feel like that would be talked about on this porn website the
Most recent comment is like I'm not gay and I got turned on
So everybody kind of has
The same reaction to this as we do I think they like it. I
See you made any public appearances since this happened. I
Don't think so. I try I am a immediately went to go to his Instagram story to see what he was posting on there
But he was just posting pictures of his friends and that's again. I like that. It's nonchalant. This is not a big deal
Okay to have your wiggling worm broadcast to the entire world. It shouldn't be something where you go into hiding
Oh, I'm not gonna really say like imagine he did like a full Kendrick Lamar
He's gone out of the public eye for like five years and then he makes a an album about how much this hurt him
right? I don't want to see that out of Drake. Maybe one, one fucking single where he addresses
this, right? Money longer than my dick, kind of, some kind of question, answer kind of
thing there where he explains why he took this, this video. Right. And then I want him
to move on, okay? It's that fucking simple. Okay. Uh, and next up to bat I would say, you
And next up to bat, I would say Julio needs a drop of it similar to this.
Yep.
I think I'm good.
Let me see it wiggle.
I think I'm good at that.
We are getting, I've known you for years at this point, never even been close to seeing
your penis.
How long have we been friends?
Never even seen you in underwear.
That is true.
What do you mean that is true?
I'm starting to think that you have a giant fucking long one.
Do you want me to strip in front of you?
Not strip, but, oh, oh, spur of the moment.
We're walking through Central Park, let's skinny dip in the fountain.
Something like that.
Or, oh, Caleb, let's go get changed together at the JCPenney.
Let's try on different jeans, husky jeans.
Stuff like that.
Okay?
I think the first ever time I went to New York, I was staying at your apartment, and
I think the second or third night, you were fully, in your other words, just jumping around.
Because I knew that this was the first time that we had hung out in person and we had
something we had to get over.
You know?
So here's what you do.
When I walk around in my underwear and it's your first time ever seeing me, you head straight
to the bathroom, you come out in your underwear, and you and me, we sit in the kitchen, we
smoke some weed and we talk about movies for a little bit.
And if we, you know, we try not to break eye contact because who knows about these wandering
eyes.
Yeah.
Um, I don't think I'm ever going back to New York City.
Why?
Whatever man.
I think I'm banned.
You're afraid of penises?
I'm afraid of the government trying to kill me.
Oh, because they don't like you anymore?
Yeah, they don't fuck with me no more.
So you miss your chance.
I think that I will have another chance.
You have to come get it.
i think i will come get it
that's when i think i'm going to have a i'm going to have a jason board
to come see you
you all know anything about it i'll be very
very stuffed with his own money what way
jason brown that the other military different language in the a fake
passport
and i'm gonna cross the border with uh... where they call them
a wolf
you can just cross the border it's fine
now it's so hard to do that kind of thing it's not so because i have to get a real
passport easier you to fake one
right and all i've talked to somebody recently
who's uh...
whose dad was like a missionary and he's telling me he came back from a one of
his like missionary trips
and he he noticed that his dad had a fake passport with a fake name
uh... well
like he may be as a spy
or he was kidnapped by the cartel and they were making
smuggled shit in
or maybe he was a
a clone
or a doppelganger
okay maybe that happened yeah
what would you guys do if you saw
if you saw what happen? I saw a clone at the airport when I was
when i was detained by the officers
where they only keep the clone
uh... just someone from china
What do you mean you saw a clone? You can't explain this.
Okay, so...
You saw a clone of somebody from China.
I will tell the story once again.
I was at the...
Uh...
At the airport. I got there.
They didn't fuck with my...
How many trips I took to the U.S.
And they sent me to the room where they sent all the Chinese people that come to the airport.
LGA... No, not LGA.
JFK, if you're from China or anywhere around there, don't go to JFK.
They will arrest you.
Uh...
But one of them, one of them, they were reprimanding him.
It was like, this is not your name or your face or you.
You are the clone.
And he was like, oh, yeah, yeah.
And you saw a real life clone accusation by TSA JFK Airport.
Yep. And he went, yeah, OK, I'm sorry.
And then he just got.
He said, I'm sorry for being a clone.
And he left.
Yeah, basically.
Dude, I fully fucking believe this.
What the fuck?
You're joking right now.
you're making up a fib.
This is like less than half of a joke.
The clone is completely true. All the details. It was a different airport.
All that kind of thing. Yeah. I'm scared of clones, man.
Have you ever seen anybody on the street and been like, that looks just like me?
No.
I'm sure this happens every single day to you. Nope. No,
I'm kidding.
Do you have that because of your, like, head?
Yes man.
I go to a gym that has a lot of bald guys, and there are times when I think I'm looking
at the mirror.
You see yourself?
No, when I'm literally looking at the mirror.
That's me!
And, like, it's those, you know how rooms in gyms are like all mirror, all mirror all
the time?
It's all mirrors on the walls?
For some gym, my gym is like this.
And so sometimes I'll be in one of those corners where there's like two mirrors that are right
next to each other.
So they cast a reflection that where I can't, I can't see the front of my head if I'm like
sitting there, but I can see the back of my head or something.
And so I'm used to this angle.
And a couple of times now I've seen myself get up off of something and walk away and realize
it wasn't me.
It was just another bald white guy in a t-shirt, white t-shirt.
you start freaking out that maybe you lost consciousness?
Well it does...
Maybe, ooh, maybe I'm astral projecting or something.
Haven't gotten to that yet, but every single time it does give me a little bit of a startle.
Alright.
Well.
Yeah.
Yeah, I've never had that happen.
I've seen...
No?
The thing that happens to me though is I'll just see any other Jewish guy and I'm like,
"Yeah, that guy probably looks exactly like me."
And it could be like a fat old guy or it could be Timothee Chalamet.
I've never met...
Okay.
Is Timothee Chalamet Jewish?
Is he chosen?
He...
No.
Is he?
Dude, that's awesome.
I thought he was just small and skinny.
Basically anyone that's ever been in a movie is...
No, I think he's just French, bro.
His last name is Chalamet.
That doesn't strike me as that much of a Jewish name.
Timothee Chalamet, Jewish.
He's half Russian, Jewish, and Austrian Jewish descent.
Wait, Nicole, well, Nicole Flander.
He's a Flander?
I knew I liked something about him.
Yeah, something like that.
Yeah, I don't know.
He's Flanders.
People love to be surprised when people are Jewish.
I'm not surprised.
I don't love it.
Like, why would I fucking lie about Timothy's childhood?
I don't think you're lying, I just didn't know.
I didn't know.
Yeah, I thought you were just a little French kid.
You can't spot it.
I just don't have that kind of detector, I guess.
But I can tell when people are bald.
Even if they have a hat on.
That is true, you can't do that.
It's a kind of demure, kind of shyness.
It's a way you carry yourself.
Yeah, if you walk around and you're scared,
you're a little easily startled,
and you're like grabbing your hat,
your hat as you like that that guy's bald right now I don't think I agree with
you no being bald is like having a small penis in the sense that it
Half of them are gay.
Oh, that's an interesting...
Oh, interesting.
Like having a small penis.
Okay!
Fuck you.
I think it changes the way you carry yourself.
I think it's just...
Well, oh, actually that is a good point because some people,
like me, you go bald and you
start becoming even more powerful.
Right. And I think some people realize
a small penis and then you become Hitler like you become Jeffrey Epstein or right
now I can't think of any good Harvey Weinstein yeah has it ever been a single
evil bald person?
yes
yeah man
are you stupid?
lex luther
Jeff Bezos
lets see
Kingpin
social issue
plankton is bald no hair on plankton
kingpin is mostly fat
and bald
you would leave it fat though
big fat guy
a
like
a six-pack even though he's fat.
That is not true.
He has a six-pack.
Look up kingpin six-pack right now, man.
He has abs.
He has one of those iron bellies that football coaches have when you're growing up.
Yeah.
No, he has a fully fat belly.
Nope.
You looked up something different.
Not in the drawings I have.
These are all different drawings of him naked and he's all fat and belly-some.
the
I really respect that about you, that you don't see it that way.
Because that would be a real problem.
I don't see hair.
You don't?
I simply don't.
You don't think my hair?
No.
I just look at your pink face and I go, "Oh, that's my friend right there."
I am getting so pink.
Off two Heineken zeros.
You got the Asian glow up to Heineken zeros.
I mean, this is crazy.
Okay, we have to I have to go because we have to play the two premier games. Okay
Guys, you can go after your house. I thank you if you're ever in the northern part of Mexico. Oh, he's gone. I
I recommend you you drink this. It's alright
It's alright. It's really light. It's no big deal
Yeah, I don't think I saw you take a single sip past the first one. Okay, okay, he drank it. All right. See you guys
next
Day meaning tomorrow. Bye. Bye