[Sipping]
[Burping]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer broadcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[Burp]
This is a journey into
[Muffled]
Bud Light.
Ha!
Foo!
Ribbit!
I know it's a--
Beers we drank, motherfucker, with Juvio, Caleb, and Rex.
Beer.
Listen.
And--
And listen to the show.
--and we're on the show.
Listen to this, guys.
I have a new--
I have a brand new sound.
I have a new thing.
I can do this up here.
Damn.
Oh, yeah, I forgot that Caleb can drink beer.
Well, but I made an exception because I am--
I'm just completely fine with having diarrhea tonight
because I have been wimping on the beer thing.
So I have a Gulsch premium, a Grosch?
A Gulsch premium Pilsner that comes with,
it has its own little bottle.
- That is premium looking.
- It has its own little bottle topper,
like a fancy restaurant water bottle.
- That's just gonna kill you.
- Let's see.
Yeah, that's not very good.
Yeah, that's not very good at all.
- How about you, Rex, what do you have?
I have a really cool beer.
It's called Coke Zero.
Mind you, everybody, Rex just woke up from his eight hour nap.
No, from an eight hour nap.
You have a, your house kind of has a Breaking Bad vibe to it right now.
I've asked Julio to like kind of figure out how to crop the room out of it.
I'm going to be doing the square crop,
but people can see kind of a little bit on the floor there.
It's getting worse.
My life has a complete shambles.
It has that same kind of vibe as Jesse's house in Breaking Bad,
where you bought a bunch of stuff,
but nothing that goes on any wall.
You just have big white open walls
where nobody like you would ever put anything.
I kind of have that right now.
You have that?
You know what I bought for this room to actually combat that?
Some of these boys.
Oh my god, soundproofing.
That's what we call that.
I'm turning this shit into a studio.
That's amazing.
I'm pretty much becoming a complete professional.
I got a boom arm, I got a soundproofing, and I got a modello negra.
I hate ordering those, man.
Why?
A what?
I just don't feel that...
I also feel like the only places I've ever seen that beer be served at like a normal
dive bar or whatever is in Portland and in Bushwick.
Nobody sells that beer in North Carolina because they know that it'd be a problem.
Like guys would just be ordering it in the craziest fucking way.
It's not even a problem.
I'm in Mexico.
I have a bunch of these in my fridge because...
And it don't sit right with me.
Like two weeks ago, I had some friends over and they did that thing where it's like 2
AM and they would still just went out to buy some beers.
And I just got left with a bunch of beers in my fridge, which I'm not super enthused
about especially because I've never drank a Modelo Negro in my entire life.
They're good.
And now I'm gonna try them out.
All right.
Live taste test.
Tell us what you think.
Yep, that shit yummers.
It's okay.
I think it's yummers.
I think that shit is yummers.
Yep, that shit is yummers.
All right, Rex, what do you have?
I already said I have a Coke Zero.
You have a Coke Zed?
Yep, there's a mango cart in my fridge, but I don't know who it belongs to.
Hmm.
and then grab a mango cart.
- He's gotten in trouble before for stealing stuff
from the fridge. - Really?
- That's not his.
- That's not true, I've never been talked about.
- That's true, he told me about,
he got put into a predatory contract,
no, in a contract.
- Oh.
- To repay a salad that he took illegally.
- The salad contract, the 5,200% APR salad contract.
- Excuse me, what salad was this?
- Like a Trader Joe's pre-made Caesar salad.
And you had to pay how much?
$52,000 for it.
For a salad?
If I didn't replace it within two days,
I owed one more salad
and then it added another salad every week.
Oh, okay.
You know, so a 50, you know,
like a 5,000% APR salad, short-term salad loan.
Gotcha.
Basically a payday loan for salads.
Yeah, that's pretty predatory.
How many salads did you end up paying back?
One.
- You made it back in full pretty quickly, huh?
- I did.
- Pretty responsible guy.
- You'll never believe it, about 47 hours in,
I got my ass in the store.
- Just the--
- 47 hours.
- Right there.
(laughs)
Right under the wire.
- Right under the wire. - I like that.
- Came back with some salads.
- I used to steal so much food when I had roommates.
I would steal food all the time, dude.
- Well, I'm a nice guy. - It was so easy.
No, I'm a bad, bad guy.
You steal food from Neil.
I used to take so much food from Neil,
'cause Neil, he just thought that he was stupid, I guess,
and he would just be like,
"Huh, I coulda swore I bought some Campbell's chunky soup."
- Just gaslighting yourself on purpose.
- Yeah, I musta just not.
And I go, "Oh yeah, I don't know."
And I just look in the opposite direction.
I'm a really bad liar.
- Yeah.
- I used to take that,
I used to take his Easy Cheese all the time.
- I don't know what's Easy Cheese.
- What is that?
- Sprite cheese, spray cheese out of the can.
The key with taking anything like that,
Like you can take all, if somebody has milk
and is your roommate, if somebody has easy cheese,
if they have salsa, anything that's in some kind of--
- Big container.
- Container where they can't see exactly how much is in it,
you can take as much as you want
except for the last serving.
People will only notice if it's unopened,
if they left it unopened,
or if you took the last serving and threw it away.
- I feel like the weight of it is also a big tell.
Like if--
How often, nobody has a mental,
like, oh yeah, I know exactly how much my gallon
of Fair Life chocolate milk is.
- I think if it's like, if you left it
like right after you opened it,
and it's like really full, and then you go back to it,
and it's like, I don't know,
like a quarter of the way full at that point,
I think you would be like, all right, this was not me.
- See, what I do-- - But if it's like
somewhere in the middle there,
I think you could get away.
- That's fine. - When I used to steal
like food from Neil.
I just did like the vodka trick
that you did with your parents' vodka.
I just filled it back up with water.
You filled the chocolate milk with water?
Well, chocolate milk, salsa.
If he had Lunchables, I'd open up the Lunchable,
I'd eat just the crackers and then replace it with water.
And he basically had no idea.
He just would--
I felt like I didn't buy the water Lunchables.
Yeah, he's like, "You gotta stop making
these water and cheese Lunchables.
It doesn't even make sense."
I fucking hate these water bowls.
And I said, "God, dude, you know what?
That probably has something to do with fucking Michelle Obama.
And then he would get so angry thinking about Michelle Obama,
they completely forget about his water Lunchable. Yeah.
Water and cheese Lunchable. That's for a dog. Yeah, exactly. Yeah.
That's a pretty good idea for a dog actually. Yeah. No. Speaking of dogs,
Phil has yesterday, Phil peed not once,
but twice inside the house.
Inside the house. Unfortunately he's been put down now. I don't,
I thought about it. I thought about it heavily yesterday. Very heavily.
I thought about completely killing my own dog.
I think we need to look at the circumstances.
Well, what was the context here?
Did he get really scared?
OK. Yeah, I wanted to see if he could pee.
I was giving him a bunch of green tea to see what would happen.
Yeah, I was feeding him five hour energies
that we wrote over and over again and then big bottles of Gatorade.
And then it turns out he peed.
Hmm. No, he was just being a bitch, man.
He's just being a bitch ass dog.
And I just, it just, he was on my last nerve, I'll say that.
And I don't want to go any further than that because he might hear me.
He's in the other room.
Well, his time is coming to grow up soon, right?
His time is coming to grow up.
Yeah.
Like a year in, a year in or two years in, maybe they stop becoming,
they stop being puppies and they get a job.
Yeah.
He, I'm hoping, I'm hoping that I'm going to be an empty nester pretty soon here.
And he'll finally start fucking leaving at least during the day.
Yeah.
That's the nice thing about a cat is that cats mature.
Cats have a curve to them.
Dogs start off as babies and you have to take care of them
and watch every single thing that they do.
And then they get a little bit less.
But then when they're old, they get even worse than they were at the beginning.
Now and then, like, you know, you ever do that thing
where you go over to somebody's house?
I hate this. You go to somebody's house.
And they have an old dog and you go, Oh, what's up?
Hey there, old timer. Nice to meet you.
You bend over to pet him and they say, Oh, no, don't pet him.
He has cancer in his entire body.
If anything he does hurts him, don't even look at him actually.
Don't breathe.
If he moves himself, he's going to start internally bleeding.
That is not, I don't know.
I've never experienced that.
You know what's the worst part about seeing an old dog at someone's house?
Well, the worst part is like when they're just like pissing and shitting everywhere
and they just have like piss and shit in their ass all the time.
And it just stinks.
Yeah. Everywhere.
And you're supposed to be like, oh, hello, puppy.
Yeah, I actually like it.
Guys, thanks for having me over.
Oh, take couch is that I had this
miniature pincher who was blind.
He had diabetes.
They always go blind.
They went. He's completely blind.
And he had he was incontinent, so I had him in a diaper.
But he was like daredevil
because I had to give him like insulin.
And but he like had like a sixth sense to know
and I was going to stab him in the neck with a needle.
So he would like dodge it like in midair.
He was like literally just like he looked like the resident evil
dog.
Like he was just like bones just bones straight up.
So you'd like stab him into like his neck, which is like this
thick.
It's just like he would just jump like move back at the last
possible second.
He would feel the force of the needle coming towards him and
then he would bite at his diaper and he would like bite his
penis from outside the diaper.
Like he was like trying to get the last bit of taco and let
(laughter)
and he gave himself like
diaper rash
(laughter)
it just
it was crazy
and he would piss himself like 9 times a day
(laughter)
oh my god man
he was awesome
and he lived 20 years after that
he lived like 2 years
only died when I moved and then just like I missed you so much I moved I put him
in the fucking bathroom and then I came home I was like hey why aren't you
moving and it just you know I was like all right well he completely had died he
had completely died yeah completely just his body finally shut down
R.I.P.
What's his name?
Cash.
I adopted him.
That's so money.
He had a dog named Cash.
It wasn't my dog.
Like I didn't, I only had him for like a year, right?
Like I adopted him.
He was already fucked.
So you didn't even love him?
I liked him a lot actually.
I thought he was great.
He was a good dog?
He was a good dog.
Right, he was yours or he was like a family dog?
No, he was just some random dog.
- Okay. - Lived in my ex's apartment complex
and they were just like trying to throw him out
with the trash basically.
They were like trying to get him to run away
but he was too blind to leave the porch.
- And you said, dog named Cash.
I know the perfect place for you.
- Give me that, yeah.
- My house, my family's house for some reason.
- I had an apartment at the time.
- That's very sweet.
Did you guys ever have any smaller pets?
You ever have any lizards or?
- I still have turtles.
You have turtles?
I had turtles.
Oh, what happened to them?
Um, I know.
I don't want to know.
They probably flew away into soup.
They went away.
Probably.
I had a turtle.
I ran into a pot.
I had a box turtle.
That I got from the ground
outside of my house.
Yeah.
And it just and I was like,
I'm going to save this turtle.
And it just pretty much instantly died.
Me and my brother used to
we used to go, we should go
like look for snakes.
Me and my older brother,
we go look for snakes cause I live near a swamp and uh,
but we didn't know which ones were poisonous and which ones weren't.
So we would hunt,
we would catch the snake first and then we would walk over from the swamp over to
my mom's house and we would hold up the snake in the front yard and have it like
right next to our heads and be like, is this one?
And a couple of times they were really badly poisonous ones.
So we just had to throw them as far as we could.
Yeah, you ever get a bit tight spiral?
I never got bit by a snake.
They're pretty easy to catch.
Yeah, they don't really have a stick.
That's the whole thing.
You just catch them with a stick.
Oh, and then you just grab them.
You slot you kind of like grab with one hand.
You slide your other hand like you're straightening them out.
And then if you just hold them behind their head,
then they basically can't do anything.
Yeah, like they can't, you know.
Yeah. Turn their head around.
All they can do is try and get you to eat an apple.
Yeah, exactly.
Which they would pretty often.
They could try to trick you.
They'd be walking back to my house and I'd say, "I'm going to show you to my mom."
They'd say, "Hmm, you know what else you should show your mom is this beautiful red,
shiny apple.
This waxy, waxy, delicious apple."
And I'd say...
Nothing bad will happen.
I've never even had that.
I don't even know what that is.
Where'd that come from?
Yeah, yeah.
These don't even grow here.
How did you even get that?
Yeah.
For small pets, I also used to have like a hamster, or maybe two hamsters, I think.
The funny thing is that they say that hamsters never just like quietly pass away.
They will die like from a horrific way.
And I'm pretty sure both of them died a crazy way, which is one of them,
I think, just got lost and just showed up dead one day.
And the other one, I think he got it's like like legs stuck in like something.
And he just got so hurt that he died of a heart attack, I assume.
Yeah.
That's pretty awful.
My roommate had a hamster and I'm pretty sure it died of like a heartbreak
because people just forgot it existed.
That's pretty sad.
My buddy used to have a fish named Booger that only ate boogers.
That he would just come in and he'd feed him his boogers.
And then I used to have two, I had two rabbits, two bunny rabbits when I was a kid
and we had them for a couple of months, but my dad thought they were so disgusting
that they weren't allowed inside the houses.
So they're outdoor bunny rabbits.
And they lived in a cage that like hung off of our like back porch.
And then one day, one day we like went out of town for a week.
And my dad hired the kid next door to like watch the rabbits and come feed him.
And he just didn't feed them.
And they just starved to death.
Jesus. Oh, I.
Yeah, it was pretty bad.
And we came back and there clearly had been like
coyotes or not
I foxes that like jumped up and like ate the meat out of the fucking crates of the
It was pretty terrible
Yeah
That's horrifying. Yeah, and we fed those boogers - we basically always fed we fed every animal boogers
Bill tries to drink my bath water every time I have a bath he like comes in
Oh, yeah, and he just like looks at me really crazy and just starts like
Slowly going down to like drink the to take a sip of the bath water
Here's another gross dog thing spill over lick the bed
Look the bed, what are you saying? What are you implying after you know after what do you after what sleeping? What?
The vigorous activity I know for you. Maybe it's not that vigorous, but you know like two three minutes of
Mild exercise on the bed. I don't know what you're talking about looks sweat
Like jumping on the bed no, but when I shit my pants I let him lick the inside of my boxers even better. Yeah
He likes it when I have real bad swamp ass and I run a half marathon and then I come inside
This is for you or you know
Or the girl yeah
He prefer he likes me more. He's gay. You're a gay dog. Oh
It does have a gay dog watch your mouth
This is well, this is widely known maybe goes both ways
We're hoping you're hoping
He has a boyfriend named Luke. It's my buddy Eric's dog and
They always meet up and and Phil tries to fuck his face
Yeah, yeah, it's pretty
Hopping at least he's the top. That's right. That's why my son ever told me he was gay
I'd say you better be that straight up are you pitching or catching what's going on? Yeah
If you're catching, you're out.
It's over.
We're done.
I'm having a new son.
I'm proud of you.
I'm buying you all sorts of new stuff to upgrade your butt.
We're going to get you in tip-top shape.
We're getting you a shiny new asshole.
We're putting wax lips on your butthole and we're getting you back on that street.
We're getting you the new self-lubricated asshole.
Is there any other surgery to the ass that's not just making it huge, huge too big?
You can use surgery to make your ass hole huge.
Not your ass hole, but there is Brazilian butt lift.
Oh, I see.
Which is becoming more and more popular as the days go on in this world.
One of her friends just told us about she had to get Botox injected into her shoulders.
And I'm just thinking about what else you could get Botox injected to make you feel
so good.
The most relaxed ass of all time.
- Isn't Botox, don't you get Botox for like a bunch of shit?
Like you get Botox for like if you go to like surgery
for a specific thing?
- I think it was like a, oh, new thing.
Hello, what's that?
- Yeah, I gave up on that beer
because I know it's gonna make me shit.
So I just got a normal white clart.
- White clart. - White clart.
- That's probably one of the biggest white clarts
I've ever seen in my entire life.
- Wait. - It's probably normal size.
- It's normal size.
(laughing)
- Don't hold it that way. - It's happening again.
- It's just a normal size. - Stop holding shit
like a baby.
I was remembering that clip from the Twitch
where Caleb held up a flower to show how normal size he was.
- I'm a normal size.
I don't, I'm not little in any way.
- Do you think that you're still--
- By the way, this is not a dollhouse furniture bed.
- No, I'm sure it's not.
Do you think you're still gonna grow some
in the coming years?
- Man, it's so funny you say that.
I say probably every nine months I get a pain in my legs
and I go, it's happening.
It's fucking happening.
- See that's such like-- - The growth horror is coming.
It's happening.
- Yeah. - Well I'm hitting six too.
- I had that until I was like,
until like two months ago.
I would be like, yep.
- Yeah, so I got a couple years, I'm fine.
- Yeah. - Bryce, have we ever talked
publicly about your scenario?
Your, would you, would you rather
- You came up in New York.
- Yeah.
- I think this is a perfect space for it.
- I don't even remember.
I kind of remember.
I don't remember the details though.
(laughing)
Explain.
- Okay, so here's the scenario.
No matter what, you shrink five inches.
Would you rather know that you shrunk or not know?
Would you rather remember
that you used to be five inches taller
Or that you were always a little tiny.
- I don't really recall how this thought was born,
but I do recall that it was,
we took like a 40 minute just walk back to our Airbnb.
- Yeah, we were just walking.
- And the entire time Rex was trying to explain
this scenario to, I think, Caleb.
And I don't think you guys ever came to a consensus,
we just got to our destination and you guys stopped talking.
- No, the consensus was absolutely
that you don't wanna know.
- Yeah, but you would know.
Well, that was the fatal flaw of the hypothetical,
is that you don't want to know, but you will know.
No, you wouldn't know.
Because, what do you mean you wouldn't know?
Your shoes are smaller.
You're close, okay, so you're hiding behind
this coward's veil of it being a hypothetical.
How about you have some dignity
and be better at building out your logical situations?
Oh, I'm sorry, it's logical to shrink five inches overnight?
No, I mean a logical, it's a logic problem.
I think at the heart, this is a logic problem.
This can be expressed as an equation.
Yeah, what's the equation?
Five minus five plus.
Yep.
Plus what?
Yep, plus what?
That's the whole question, isn't it?
That's the entire fucking question.
I think it's a stupid scenario.
It is really stupid.
And it's also just a thing that people under six feet
would just talk about.
And I don't concern myself with these type of scenarios.
So I just don't.
Okay, well, here's one for you.
Would you rather be more mentally disabled than you are
or way more mentally disabled than you are?
And by the way, you won't know either way
because of how stupid you are.
You won't notice anything that ever happens to you.
You're basically a picture.
That's about what you are, is a picture of a person.
I am not a picture of a person.
I'm actually quite smart.
Okay.
And I know two languages.
Solve something right now.
- I don't have like a puzzle.
- He looked around for a puzzle and he doesn't have one.
Guess what I have?
- That's a puzzle.
- You guys keep like trinkets and puzzles?
- Yeah, look what else I have.
I have an alien head.
See, you've melted your brain with video games.
You don't have a simple brain, man.
- This is a book.
- I got tons of books.
So many that I can't even reach for one right now.
Does this count?
A knife?
Yeah.
I mean that's smart in a different way.
You have street smarts, I can say that much.
I was thinking about that today.
About what?
About being street smart or being...
Would you say you're more street smart or more book intelligence?
I think I'm more book intelligence, yeah.
I think you are book intelligence, Rex.
I think Caleb is street smart.
I'm 100% book intelligence.
That's not true.
It is true.
I'm street smart.
Yeah, you got me and Rex flipped.
Yeah.
I do a street smart job and he does a book smart job,
but in our real lives, the people we really are,
it's flipped.
I'm a dork and he's a pussy getting animal.
I take it back.
You're both street smart.
Well, you don't even get to switch me to book smarts,
the one I want to be and you switch him to what he wants to be?
- Well, that's just the way he is.
- Yeah.
- I think you just have to accept where you are.
- Guess what I'm reading?
- What?
- Shel Silverstein, "Where the Sidewalk Ends,"
a book of collected children's poems.
So is that not a book to you?
- Why are you reading children's poems?
- Well, I'm not reading it, it's an audio book,
so technically I'm listening.
- Oh.
- Just do it, that was like a bunch of kids books.
- I'm reading a Good Night Moon,
well, technically I'm listening to Good Night Moon.
(laughing)
There's a lot of amazing stuff in it.
- Yeah, do you consider that reading?
Listening to a book? - No, I don't like
audio books. - No.
- I like reading.
I have a Kindle, but I don't even like it.
- I saw, do you know who John Carmack is?
- Yeah.
- He made like some posts today that was like,
I used to only be able to, okay.
He's the guy who made like Doom.
Oh, he was he do.
He did Rogan recently or so.
Yeah. OK.
And he's talking about how he used to listen to audio books
on like one point five speed.
And then he's like slowly trained his brain to listen to it
at one point nine speed.
He just yeah, it's great.
Helping the speed.
And that's not reading.
You're not you're not like remember anything at that point.
No, no, no.
I agree with you.
Yeah, I like I like reading really, really slow.
Yeah, that's how I prefer to read.
I read nice and slow.
I I'm really good at reading exactly.
This much of a book, can you see that?
Just this much, this much is that like, are you holding the front or the back?
This is the front.
Yeah, so this is yeah, yeah, yeah, 56, 50 pages into a lot of books.
I understand.
What's this book?
This is a thing.
Numena by Nick Land.
Don't worry about it.
- Mm-hmm, it's a gay book.
- It is a gay book.
It's a very gay book. - We gotcha.
We gotcha.
- I don't read books. - The thing is,
I really only do one, you don't read books?
- No, I think that's for nerds.
- And how would you say that you're book smart
if you don't read books?
- I've read books in the past. - See, you're not book smart.
You are not even street smart.
- Yeah. - Well, there's only two
different-- - You think you're book smart
just because you're not street smart,
but in reality, you're neither.
- Yeah. - I have to be one then.
- No, you don't. - I can't just be none.
- You're a brain nun, you're the first one who's none.
- That's not true, I'm looking this up.
I'm completely looking this up.
- Yeah, you're a full brain eunuch,
you've been lobotomized.
- What's the dichotomy between book smart and street smart?
- Is there a third option?
- The third option is neither.
- A third one.
- Yeah.
- The third option is you're just not anything.
- Yeah, some people are not book smart,
and therefore they like to think they're street smart.
- One, two, three, four,
there's actually like seven of them.
- Okay, I remember. - So someone asked,
what other kinds of smarts are there?
Street smart, for example.
So someone says, word smart
or verbal linguistic intelligence.
- Well, because you just said verbal,
I think that you're out on that one.
- Next. - That's book smart.
- Picture smart or visual spatial intelligence.
- Okay, that's just creative.
- I could be that one. - You could be that.
You could be that, maybe. - I think I'm that one.
Logic smart or logical mathematical intelligence.
- That's obviously me. - Probably not.
Body smart or body kinesthetic intelligence.
- So that's just being athletic.
- Yeah, music smart or musical rhythmic intelligence.
- I'm probably that.
- Self smart or interpersonal intelligence.
- Okay, so emotional intelligence.
- Right, yeah, I guess I'm emotionally intelligent.
- That's, all of that is cope.
That is bullshit.
- Yeah, I would agree.
- There's only two types for it.
- People smart, nature smart.
- Nature smart, that's the most.
- Or life smart, or existential intelligence.
- Yeah.
- Wow.
- Actually, I think I'm life smart.
- You think you have existential intelligence?
- I'm smart about the entire life.
- That's, no, that's book smart.
All of those fall under the categories of either--
- Yeah, there's books about every single one of those.
- Yeah, you're either book smart or you're--
- Well, books, there's a lot of bullshit books anyways.
- That's like--
- Now he's anti-book.
Are you hearing this?
are like you're autistic and you're high intelligence or you're
retarded and you're high interpersonal intelligence.
The reality is things.
The fact that we're doing this right now proves that none of us are anything
but just low value.
Oh, yeah.
People that like 400 years ago, there's no chance we would be living past 14.
We would be like as soon as we hit puberty and they realize that we were going to be
ugly, they were going to throw us all in a pit and nobody wants to fuck us.
We're bad, bad people.
We're like mistakes.
All three of us.
I'm not a pet person.
Yeah.
I would not be a pet person.
You would be used as a human ladder.
They would put you in carbonite and climb up you.
You would be a playground installation.
Yeah.
They would, they would not.
They would hang a little candy bar above your head and you put your arms up and
then they just flash freeze you.
Exactly.
Yeah.
That's what you would be.
You'd be used to clean out gutters.
I would be an alpha male back in the day.
You think so?
Yeah.
Is this modern world, this modern age, is destroying you?
The modern age has pretty much destroyed all my avenues, my opportunities to get any money
or love or friendship or kinship.
And I just have to resort to being on Discord calls with other men talking about how to
make money on the latest crypto NFT shit.
That is what we talk about all the time.
That's just me.
I'm always talking about that.
- I'm sick of us talking about the way to make money
on the latest crypto NFT, but--
- I just have so much money now on the crypto space
and women are not into that and I don't care.
- Fuck 'em.
- Yeah.
- They need to--
- They're not gonna make it.
- I was thinking today, you know--
- They're gonna turn around.
- Have you guys seen that--
- They're gonna have fun staying poor.
- TikTok guy, and God bless him,
that guy who's, he's in a wheelchair and he has a big head,
but he has like a very pretty wife.
- Mm.
- You know, have you seen this guy?
- Oh yeah.
Yeah. And he's like got a really good job or something.
He's like got a whole his whole his life is like amazing. Right.
I was singing yesterday about like it used to be.
We thought it would be dead.
No. Well, when you were at your lowest point in your life
where just everything was going wrong for you, you get fired
or somebody breaks up with you or whatever.
You could always be like, man, at least I'm not horribly disabled.
But these guys are fucking winning, dude.
Yeah, you're like this.
Worse than a guy who can't even use his legs.
I know, dude. It's like, fuck, that would be awesome now.
I'm like, that'd be fucking incredible, man.
I'd be out there giving motivational speeches and shit.
Yeah. My mom would be sending videos of me to people like, look at this
inspirational genius guy whose head is the size of a peanut.
And like that's that is the life, man.
Well, that's like that Iceland guy.
So I hope that's not offensive to say.
What I saw in the guy that's like the best.
We talked about that last week.
We talked about it last week.
Yeah, we talked about it last week.
Yeah, he's just like a multi-millionaire.
He's got a wife and kids.
He has a perfect life.
He's voted the best guy.
It's not like I want to fucking go run.
It's not like I want to use my legs.
I hate that I have legs.
My legs hurt from how much I haven't walked in the past three weeks.
Exactly, yeah.
I walked down the stairs and I almost fell.
If I could go to the gym three days a week and skip legs and just never use them and they're
gone and I'm just like, I just have the most insane upper body ever and I still, I weigh
I weigh 90 pounds and I'm ripped because I don't have any legs.
That's ideal.
Do you think you can make it as like that type of like motivational speaker just
traveling the world, just speaking about?
I think I can motivate people.
I can do that with being bald.
Yeah, you could do that with being bald.
Yeah.
So now that I think about it, I'm a fool.
Can we get a sample of your speech?
That is legitimately being bald at your young age.
Hang on, let's see if I can get this bald speech.
Guys, guys,
Uh, well, it's more of a, I'm sharing an anecdote about my bald life.
So that's powerful.
You may, everybody looks at me and they say, man, his life is perfect.
His life is amazing.
He's the ball.
The, this bald guy's figured it all out.
He knows how to do it better than anybody.
Right.
But I want you to know, I want you to know this shit right now, all you people
holding onto your hair and maybe you just shave for the first time you're
getting nicks and cuts every single time.
Buddy, I'm three years in, and look what I did to my head.
(laughing)
Look at that.
Right in the center.
Right in the center of my head.
- It's like a horn.
- I put a horn in my head.
- You look like a dive bar.
- Pool cue, pool ball, cue call.
- Cue ball. - Pool call.
That's right.
Look at me, guys.
I look like a giant pimple.
I look incredible, despite.
You look like someone put a cigarette out on your head.
And let me tell you what,
if you think that I wasn't walking around my house
with a giant piece of toilet paper
hanging from the top of my head for about two hours,
you got another thing coming.
Yes, sir.
So that's what I would do,
is I would kind of just use my bald experience
to relate to other bald men.
You should just put like a,
what's the word they call it?
The fucking, oh.
A what?
A bandaid?
Yeah, you should put a bandaid on that.
I thought about it.
I was like, "You know what that is?
That's cowardice."
That's cowardice, right?
Because I walk around and go, "Oh, Pulp Fiction."
And I go, "Yeah," and not admitting to them the truth.
I'm trying to be more...
I'm trying to only tell the truth and give my 100% authentic self all the time.
And if I'm walking around with a bandaid on top of my head, what kind of message am I
I sending to these bald teenagers and preteens that listen to this show?
Very true. Yeah. I think if you go bald, you know,
your young age,
it's fine for you to get a wig or maybe like a horn or
just some sort of thing.
Like a realistic wig.
Um, no, it was like expensive wigs. Yeah.
It looks so good in that, uh, uh, final fantasy.
Or the orange one.
- The orange one, yeah.
- Yeah, a lot of people masturbated to that.
- Yeah, I think you should have like a year
where you just wear wigs for like a year or something.
- I legitimately think in your wedding photos
you should wear that wig.
- Guys, I've looked into everything, okay?
I'm not gonna, again, I'm not gonna lie to you
and say I've always been proud to be bald.
I've looked into everything.
When I first started losing my hair,
there's something called, they call it, it's a wig,
they call it a hair system
because men are so afraid of wearing a wig
that they call it a hair system.
And they're like, they make videos like, I just spent $1,200 on a brand new hair system.
And it's like, this is RuPaul, you're doing RuPaul.
But for like, I've got like a guy who works at like a sweet green, like that kind of look.
Who's giving a disgusting feedback noise?
It's really scaring me.
It's like kicking.
Yeah, there it goes.
I came back for a second.
But yeah, I looked into that shit.
It's too hard, though.
Yeah, it's like a stereo. It makes it feel like you're like pimping out your car.
Exactly. Yeah, yeah. All of a sudden, it's basically like that, a hair system is to like
guys who are balding and want to change it, what like a tube amp is to guys who get into
like record players.
Yeah.
You know what I mean? Like it's that level of like, you're spending too much money on
this. Yeah, you're like, you're in too deep. You need to stop.
Yeah.
- Your wife is disgusted by you.
- Yeah, I don't want my bald-ass head to be my hobby.
I want it to be my shining strongest feature
where I walk down the street and people say,
"Fuck, I don't wanna ever meet that guy."
That's what I like.
- Yeah.
- I like that, when I had hair, dude,
people thought I was too friendly
and they liked me too much.
Now that I'm bald, people always assume
that I'm a really mean gay guy
and it makes me really happy.
- Yeah.
- I get way different goodwill.
- And you are a really mean gay guy.
- In more ways than you would really even imagine, yeah.
But-- - Yeah.
- You're gay smart.
- Yeah. - Guy smart.
- Guy smart.
I think we should just all get into wigs.
- Yeah.
- What kind of wig are you wearing?
- So, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so,
- So, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so,
- What, I could wear a wig.
- Luchador masks.
- Yes sir.
- And I could start wearing a luchador mask
because then people, nobody knows
if I'm cut or uncut under that thing.
- Is that what they call that when you go bald?
- Yeah, I'm cut.
- Right.
- That's what they say.
- No, the problem with luchador masks
is that they get very hot immediately
so you can't really wear them after like 20 minutes.
- I feel like--
- It's funny that you know that.
- Yeah.
- This guy, you definitely are like,
yeah, your size, you should have been a luchador.
For sure.
I had luchador masks when I was a kid.
Whoa, do you like, did you like grow up liking luchadors?
Like it was like a, like how kids like wrestling?
Like it was my Marvel?
No, I like, I liked like wrestling.
I liked like WWE, I guess when I was a kid, but I don't, I never really cared that much.
Do you like it enough as an adult to make it a podcast?
No, nope, I don't.
We're not doing that.
We're not getting into wrestling.
Can't do it.
Yeah, I can't do it either.
I have it on good authority that we have an invitation to all go to Mexico
City to watch Lucha Libre whenever you guys come down here.
Is Lucha Libre a cartoon?
It's a thing.
No, you're thinking of Nacho Libre.
No, that's not.
Will he be there?
Someone who looks like him.
A lot of people who look like him will be there.
Really? That is the craziest movie, man.
Yeah, that is the funniest movie ever that they made that movie.
A movie where Jack Black fully is like, man, I got to be a lucha door.
I want to be a lucha door.
He got it right at the cusp that last year.
2007, 2008.
That was the same year as like Tropic Thunder.
Yep. Tropic Thunder.
And he but he went in, but they actually cover their ass in the movie, though,
where he was like an adopted kid.
Yeah, yeah.
Where they don't pretend.
They also do that on Tropic Thunder.
Yeah, but.
It's a white guy who thinks he's black for some reason.
You're right. Yeah, no, they do it on both.
But if you don't watch the first 15 minutes of the movie, it just reads
completely differently on both movies.
Yeah.
But on Nacho Libre, he's literally talking to the guy at the monastery and
he's like, I'm going to have diarrhea.
He says that shit.
Yeah.
God bless Jack Black. He does, dude.
I need to watch that movie.
Natural Ego?
Underrated performance in Tropic Thunder
is Tom Cruise as a Jewish guy.
I don't know why,
but every time I watch
Tropic Thunder or I see Tom Cruise
in that Jewish guy costume,
I always think of
Andy S. from Twitter.
A little bit, yeah.
I think liking that Tom Cruise scene
at the end of Tropic Thunder, that's Reddit
to like that scene.
Really?
Which scene are you talking about?
The dancing thing.
Oh yeah, I agree with that.
You think it's Reddit that he's dancing?
It's Reddit to like that scene.
Yeah.
Why is it Reddit to like that scene?
Because that's where I saw that the first time before I watched the movie, was on Reddit.
Reddit?
You didn't watch that?
A lot of news also ends up being pretty Reddit.
Yeah.
So like the election of Barack Obama, I saw that on Reddit.
And that was pretty Reddit.
And it ended up being, yeah.
So it's a pretty much perfect system that I have.
Yeah.
Yeah, for you an avid Reddit user.
Oh, my God. Yes.
I can't believe you of all people didn't see Tropic Thunder organically.
I didn't see any movies until I was like 15.
I didn't see Superbad until I was 18.
I didn't see Borat till I was 21.
Wow. Isn't that wild?
That is wild.
You're like a one of those tribes that exist
like untouched by modern society.
I know, that's kind of how I felt.
All I knew was--
And he's still like that.
He never watches any movies at all or any entertainment.
Yeah, you fucking wish.
You don't watch anything.
You wish I didn't watch movies.
Guess what I watched two days ago?
What did you watch two days ago?
A little movie called
"I Hired an Assassin to Kill Me"
by an auteur filmmaker named Mr. Beast.
Have you seen this film?
No.
This guy--
Please give us a detailed review.
Oh my God.
Letterboxdstyle, letterboxdstyle, five stars.
I've seen it twice, I've seen it twice now.
Okay.
Alright, letterboxdstyle.
There are some pieces of art in this world that grab you by the lapel and dare you to
feel something.
This is one of these.
We open on the top of a moving train.
Our hero, Mr. Beast, aka Jimmy.
Yeah. Which in parentheses, it also turns out this is the filmmaker himself. Addresses
the camera and explains the situation, which once he gets into the details, you might realize
is quite horrific. An assassin, a trained assassin is hunting him currently. He has
exactly 12 hours or has Jimmy says till the end of the day to stab him not with
a real knife not a sharp knife but with a simulacrum of a knife a rubber knife
okay that which he must bend against Jimmy's body okay the assassin is tied
up with his two friends, with Jimmy's two friends on two carts behind Jimmy.
They let him go, the count begins.
First stop, a warehouse.
Jimmy's hiding behind a mirror, the assassin finds him almost instantly.
Jimmy gets away by breaking open a brick wall and barrels fly everywhere and crack the windshield
of a sprinter van.
What the hell?
the assassin is in the building.
Jimmy's friend Carl runs over his car with a tank.
The assassin says, "It's as flat as a pancake."
That's a direct quote.
I honestly can't tell if you're being sincere or not.
You could be completely lying about this.
I think he's completely sincere.
All of this is true.
Next stop, a hotel.
And you may be saying, "Hmm, what, a Best Western?
15 rooms?"
- Buddy, no, 25 floors with at least 10 rooms on each floor.
And guess who's in one of the rooms?
- Mr. Beast? - Mr. Beast.
- Well, there's no way they could find him in there.
That's too many rooms.
- Well, that's what Jimmy was thinking
when he set up this whole thing.
But he rented out every single room.
The assassin walks in, he starts opening every single door.
But right before the assassin gets to Jimmy's room,
Jimmy escapes in a hidden elevator
that he hid behind a fake wall.
Next stop is a bank.
They go into the bank, he locks the assassin into a vault,
he pulls the vault out of the brick wall,
and then at the end, for absolutely no reason,
they blow up the bank with actual bombs
and the whole thing explodes.
- What the fuck?
- The climax of the movie, coming up right now.
Jimmy sets up an entire carnival.
There's rides, there's booths, there's roller coasters,
but he gets there before the assassin.
Because of his time advantage, he stages an entire scene.
Oh no, Jimmy was climbing up onto one of the rides,
he fell off, he broke his ankle.
The production is halted.
All of the actual production cameras are hidden.
And the only cameras left on set are like little spy cameras.
So they tell the assassin, sorry, the video's over.
Jimmy broke his ankle, rather,
and he's on that stretcher over there.
and they have him in a splint.
And the assassin walks over and as he walks over,
he twists the tip of the knife, the rubber knife,
against his index finger like this, right?
And he says, "What happened?"
And Jimmy goes, "Broke my ankle."
The assassin cold as ice.
"All this for a broken ankle, huh?
I'm not buying it."
Stabs him in cold blood right there.
- Yeah, dude.
And the assassin makes $100,000.
- Wait, what?
They paid an actual killer money?
- He was like a guy who used to work for the CIA.
- Yeah, okay.
- He used to be like a guy who would kill
like a random mercenary contract killer dude.
And like a real, this guy's actually a monster.
You can tell in the video that he's a monster
because he does certain things where you're like,
this is not your first time doing this.
where when he's in the hotel, he kicks open all the doors,
but he kicks them open in this weird way
that I've never seen anybody kick open a door in anything,
where he like looks away from the door
and he like donkey kicks it
like two feet underneath the handle.
Every single time he opens like 10 doors like this.
And it's like, dude, that's,
this guy has done this way too many times before.
And also he's wicked smart
because he knew that Jimmy was actually fine
and did not have a broken ankle,
but it really blew my mind.
It really was one of their better videos they've made.
I don't actually want to watch that now.
It's really, really good.
X killers and shit like that are always so insane to me.
Like that one video that was going viral on Twitter
like a couple of months ago,
where it's like an ex assassin for like the actual mob
just watching someone do like killing like kill clips on Hitman.
Oh, yeah. And it's for Vanity Fair.
Yeah. No, it's not.
It's like some like some like YouTube channel, like a random YouTube channel.
And they're just like having me react like,
"Yeah, so basically, I wouldn't...
Me, myself, I wouldn't have done that.
I wouldn't have thrown an axe across the room
at a direction that someone said,
because you could miss."
I was like, "Okay, man, that's crazy."
But then he just goes like,
"Yeah, I've done that before,
where I push someone off a building and they die."
I was like, "Whoa, that's weird."
- And all the comments are like,
"Why do I find this guy strangely charming?"
- He's kind of funny.
- They should have him more.
You ever seen the Iceman tapes?
No.
Dude, it's one of the best video
or one of the best documentary series of all time.
It's like four or five part HBO documentary series
where they interview this guy, Robert,
suddenly find his name, the Iceman.
Anyway, he was this guy,
it's called the Iceman Tapes Conversations with a Killer,
Richard Kuklinski, former hitman.
serves two life sentences for murder after admitting he killed over 200 people.
So this guy got booked.
He was like a mafia guy who got booked for like maybe two murders or three
murders or something as a hit man. And then as soon as he got in jail,
he said that he killed like, he actually killed like 10 people.
And then HBO did this documentary with him.
And then he admits to killing like 200 people, but they're clear.
Most of them are clearly lies where he just will like tell these stories.
He was like, "So the guy was as small as an ant."
And I caught him, I picked him up by his little shirt and I swallowed him whole with one bite
like the giant from Jack and the Beanstalk.
And they're shooting it all dramatic and they have a dun-dun.
And he's like, "The next guy."
His blood was as red as an apple.
Yeah.
"The next guy."
I stabbed him in cold blood.
before me, he turned into an alien and vaporized away and was clearly abducted by...
Like he just has these crazy stories where everything ends with, "I was this close to
die."
There's movie stories.
He literally, he tells stories that are just straight up taken from James Bond movies.
And he just makes himself sound like the coolest, most badass guy of all time.
And he calls himself the Iceman.
I think even a couple of mafia people like openly were like, yeah, I don't think like
he didn't do a lot of stuff.
He's just like like he worked for the mafia.
He killed some people, but he wasn't like this crazy.
He wasn't a demon, but he basically like portrays himself as a demon.
It's the same thing that happened with the the guy, the Irishman, the Irishman is based
off of where he he didn't actually kill Jimmy Hoffa.
just like made it up at the like right before he died.
Pretty smart.
Yeah, I'm kind of sick of like that medium, honestly.
Mafia movies?
The Netflix movie.
No, like the documentary like a mini show.
I think it's like so overdone and it's so annoying.
I hate reality.
It's so no, it's always like they build it up like this is going to be
the craziest thing of all time.
And it's just like, oh, it's just like this guy who just killed a bunch of women.
Did you ever watch the videos of those?
A guy that like he's like a he's like the capo of like the
Colombo family name like got out and then he gets into like YouTube
like podcast beefs with like really old like mob guys different
crime families.
Awesome.
He's very funny.
He like he was like really big in the 80s and 90s.
He ran like a gas scheme like a gas siphoning scheme all along the
East Coast.
And then he like went to prison for 10 years and then like got
out and then he just goes on like lad Bible and shit like
that.
And he's like, Yeah, I thought they were gonna fucking kill me.
He's dope dude. He's awesome, man. My favorite one of those
like documentary like stories is like the the Tinder Schindler
Oh, that dude was awesome.
That guy is the GOAT.
Basically, I don't know if you've seen this, Kilo, but basically some guy in Europe, he
would just like swindle this women all across Europe.
He would just be on Tinder.
He portrayed himself as being some sort of millionaire.
He got money from I think some jewelry shop or whatever from his family.
Just some lie like that.
And he would just go out with women.
He would show them this insane, lavish lifestyle.
He would just keep texting them and like only seeing them like once every,
every so, so many weeks. Uh, and at some point he would just like, be like, Oh my God,
my enemies are after me and I need some fucking money. Uh,
and then we'll just give him money. Yeah. He was like,
my office pulled up and they fucking show my bodyguard and it was just like show
him like the same pictures every time. And he'd think that this is like,
I don't know if it was like under hundreds of women.
So he got a bunch of money. Uh, and the, my, I love that,
that documentary because at some point,
like there's a little bit of retribution
because at the end, like one of the women
are like figures out who he is.
Like he, she sells like some of his stuff
and she gets some money back.
But he just like flees to Israel
and like all the women that like lost all that money,
they're just like, yeah, we're still owe that money.
And it's like, okay, sick story, man.
Like he just gets away.
- Why does Israel harbor this guy?
- Because he's Israeli.
- Oh, okay.
Just an Israeli guy.
I didn't know he was just an Israeli guy.
Yeah, I thought you said he was European.
Well, it happened in Europe,
but he was like an Israeli guy.
He was also like apparently convicted in Israel.
So that's why he just was like staying in Europe, I guess.
I see.
But he just like goes back
and he like didn't serve like any time, I think.
And he's just like still like posting pictures on Instagram
of like dating a model
and like being like just riding a Lamborghini.
This guy's a beast.
Talking to Netflix like,
That is so cool.
I owe American Express $100,000 and no one's helping me.
And I'm like, oh, well, that's the end.
So, yeah, that's my favorite guy of all time.
And we're going to have a monsoon.
Do you think that you could be a scammer for a social engineer?
Yes. I could not.
I don't think I have that in me.
I'm too honest and friendly.
I think friendly is actually I think that's something that those people are.
Yeah, they're very friendly.
I do love that movie with Tom Hanks and Leo.
Yeah, you got to not have a conscience to do it.
Well, I don't know because I feel like for the most part, you're ripping off like, at
least in that movie, you're ripping off like a bank or whatever.
Like who cares?
If I could press a button and steal from a bank, I would.
Yeah, of course, who wouldn't?
But it's just the whole thing, you know, you have to kill the teller, you have to kill
the security guard, you have to kill two or three hostages.
that's kind of where I draw the line as the third hostage.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, if you could still just strictly steal from like rich people who
won't really miss it or like the bank, but you don't get to those leagues without scamming like,
you know, the small guy first, you got to practice.
You got to steal money from homeless people to get a taste of practice. What you can actually
do is you can create a complete recreation of the bank with cardboard and you can hire
or homeless people to occupy all the different places.
And then, you know, if one of the you know, if you accidentally have
bad trigger discipline and one of the fucking rounds goes off
into this guy's abdomen or whatever, it's not that big of a deal.
Yeah. Yeah. That's season two of the rehearsal.
Yeah, yeah.
Nathan Fielder planning to he's planning out a mass shooting.
These like central casting Tim and Eric extras.
(laughing)
They just like sit around in a high school.
Yeah.
(laughing)
I don't know if I could scam a homeless person.
Like, I don't even know how,
but I would tell them to give me their $5
that they just got from someone else.
Like, what would you even tell them?
I'd say, I'll double that.
I'd say, I'd pretend it was, I was investing for them.
Yeah. Yeah.
I'm about to invest. I'd say it's penny stocks.
You just had a farmer walk around.
Who the fuck is that?
(laughing)
An actual yokel.
- That's the guy we saw at SASS
from on the second episode, I believe.
- It is. - Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- He's looking terrible these days.
- Yeah, he's a farmer now.
- Wow, good for him.
Well, that completely distracted me.
I didn't see a farmer that often.
- I was really worried about that happening.
- Yeah. - Yeah, no.
I don't know, I forgot what we were talking about.
We were talking about being farmers.
I don't think I could be a farmer.
- Farmer with a full Sasquatch walk.
I could be a farmer.
People say that they could be farmers,
but I feel like it's way more work than you think it is.
I've done it before.
It's not that hard.
No, you have never done it before.
I have to imagine you lying to the bathroom.
I've literally had this exact argument
with Cam and Pat on the podcast before.
Okay, new argument.
I worked at a farm over the summer.
I worked at a soybean farm.
I plugged the irrigation holes.
I did everything.
You were a soy boy?
No, I farmed soybeans in Louisiana.
You were a soy boy in Louisiana for a summer.
That's what they call those.
That's what they call them.
If you want to call it that dude, it was bad, bro. I was with my,
my mom's like friends for a friend from high or from somewhere from high school
or college.
I was like staying with her family and like working on their farm for a summer.
And uh, they were like literally in word every,
every hour racist. They were like,
yeah, it was crazy.
It's like a Twitter bot and word every
Yeah, some guy, like this is also like,
they would sit around and they would watch Obama
give like speeches on TV,
just so they could just say the N-word to their TV.
And I was like, and I was not,
and I didn't know this when I signed up to do this.
And I was only, I was like 14.
So I didn't have a lot of agency in my life.
So day one, I text my mom and I'm like,
hey, your friend's husband is racist.
My mom's like, "Oh, they just don't know what,
you know, they're just from a different time."
I'm like, "They're the same age as you.
What are you talking about?"
- They're from a different place.
- And then I showed their kid Team Fortress 2,
and you do not wanna hear what he called the Demo Man.
- Demo Man, yeah.
- It was bad when he started playing the Demo Man
and started doing just all sorts of terrible stuff.
And I was like, "God, what have I unlocked in this kid?"
But it was bad, man.
It was not a good time.
- No. - Yeah.
that's the hard part of farming is the intolerance. Do you think you could be a farmer Rex? No,
I'm too delicate. I think that nowadays like if you want to run like a successful farm you need
to like acres of you know land and like the big ass machines. That is genius. So I don't think
it's that hard anymore I think it's it's incredibly easy. Pretty hard. You have to
- You need to know how to drive stuff.
- I know how to drive stuff.
- It's mostly about the business part.
It's just like having to run
like the hardest, least successful business you can have.
You don't make any money farming anymore.
- I know business and how to drive.
I think I could do it.
- That's not true.
- Yeah, farming is just a losing business
that gets propped up by taxes and shit.
- Yeah, you have to pay royalties on your--
- I could pay your seeds.
- You have to pay royalties on the seeds that you use
because they're owned by,
like companies have the patent on the specific genetic modification of the seed.
So it's like you're using a sample in a fucking hip hop song and you're paying
the Nina Simone's estate for the rest of your life.
Like that's that kind of situation.
Just use my own seeds from the store.
So that's the thing is they've literally eliminated every other seed in the
world. Yeah. It's pretty genius.
It is except for Antarctica.
Yeah.
Not a lot of stuff grows in Antarctica, though.
You don't know about the secret Antarctica seed repository?
No.
It might not be Antarctica.
It's definitely in somewhere really cold.
There's like an underground bunker
that has like a copy of every seed.
Really?
To like repopulate the earth with plants after.
Yeah, I think that--
Svalbard Global Seed Vault?
That YouTube video kept popping up on my recommended
and I never watched it.
I never heard of those.
It's so boring.
It's on the Norwegian island of Spitsbergen
in the Arctic archipelago.
- Yeah.
- Man, that's pretty dope looking.
- Yeah, it's like the seed repository of last resort.
- I mean, do vegetables go extinct?
- If a nuclear winter happens.
- Yeah.
- When would that ever happen?
- That's a good point.
- Yeah, you're right.
- We're all friends here.
Yeah, it's definitely not about to happen.
We're just going to happen.
Shut up there,
because they were talking about the like depleted uranium rounds
that Britain has given to the UK.
Yeah, I saw a bunch of pictures of like babies that were born after being.
It's fucked up what the human body can produce,
which is a little bit of radiation. It's fucked up.
Yeah, the radiation is not so good, man. Yeah. Yeah.
I don't I, uh, I think it's such a clear choice between living in the middle of New York City,
where you get exactly bullseye hit and destroyed versus living like everybody's like, oh, I just
want to live 50 miles outside of a city. Oh, OK. So when the fucking nuke hits, you want all your
skin to slowly just fall off like a lizard.
You want to die with no skin doing that,
the help me thing from Hellraiser.
That's what you want to do?
- Yeah, just vaporize me instantly.
- I want to be a shadow.
- You guys ever saw that, I don't know what it was from.
Maybe you can help me with this, Rex.
But I remember watching this a bunch of times
when I was a kid or somewhere,
but I don't know where it's from.
It was just like some anime or it's like the bombs
like hitting Japan.
Oh, that anime is awful.
I saw that as a kid and it made me leftist.
Yeah.
I don't, I remember it's just, I've only seen like clips of that.
I don't know.
I don't know what, where that's from, but I, and I don't know how I watched that so
many times.
I don't even know what you're talking about.
So that's all.
You know what it is?
No.
It's some anime where like the guy, he must've been, he must've like been
sexually attracted to like pictures of people.
He must've been hit by the nuke.
- That's true, for his brain to come up with something
so sick, but he basically did just like an anime slow motion
of like little kids eyeballs melting and like old grannies
having their skin burned off.
It's really-- - Have you ever seen that?
- It's pretty gnarly.
- It's pretty much like the precursor of like
that HBO show, "Chernobyl," I guess.
- Yes.
- Yeah, I do know that if you are in the blast range
of like the nuclear bomb, it happens so fast
that you like die before you understand what's happening.
- Oh yeah, yeah.
- That's good.
- It's like quicker than the neurons
can actually reach your brain.
- Yeah, your body just vaporizes.
It's fine.
- It's pretty cool. - It's pretty good.
- You know that they put the,
this is an amazing place to be kind of rave slowly,
kind of winding down the podcast is great.
But you know that they put the big loads
of nuclear armaments they put at like
in these very desolate parts of the United States
because they know that they'll be the first targets
in any kind of like nuclear engagement.
So if Russia sends four nuclear bombs,
they're all gonna be headed towards
where all of our nuclear bombs are.
And they did that so that all the farmers die
and all the amazing smart city people live.
- Yeah.
- But the thing is, man, bro, if they send nukes,
they're sending 50,000 of them.
And there's gonna be like everywhere you walk,
you're getting hit by one.
If they were water balloons, we'd be in trouble.
You know, the fact that they are nuclear warheads just makes it
that much worse.
Yeah.
I just hope I loved reading.
I was reading about Einstein a bunch and what I forget who the
president was at the time and but there's like this anecdote
or Wilson.
Yeah, like Einstein met with the president.
He was like, yo, you know, like fucking Dukes are real bad.
This is like, we gotta be good about this.
And then he left the office and the president turned
and he's like, that guy's a fucking pussy.
(laughing)
That guy's a bitch.
- That is so dope, dude.
Yeah, Einstein was a bitch.
That's why Oppenheimer was cool.
- Yeah.
- I can't wait to see that movie.
- I can't wait to watch the movie now.
- I'm so excited.
- That's like a hack bit to talk about
how he planned out, I am become death destroyer worlds,
like he was like at home looking up shit to say.
- But it is cool.
- It is fucking hard.
That is a hard line.
- Oh dude, he, when I was a kid.
- He killed that.
- Tell you where that was in my life,
my desktop background.
- Yeah.
- And yeah, guess what was behind it?
The word.
- Nuclear.
- No, space.
It has nothing to do with space.
He was not involved in space at all.
But you look at those words and you say,
Holy fuck dude, that is existentialism, motherfucker.
You know what, I've changed my mind. You are book smart.
You are completely book smart.
Obviously.
The Baghdad Gita.
Okay, bye guys.
Bye.