Whatever man
That is
Key I got him with the tiny voice man, you can't hear it. Yeah. Yeah. No, I can't hear the tiny voice
I'm probably on the tiny voice right now
No, I actually don't know that shit. Can they see you man? Try to move down more?
Yeah, I mean grifter our Matthew Matthew, baby
Hey!
Holy shit, dude.
Are we ready to go?
Ready to crack some beers?
Ready to drink some beers?
Hey, buddy.
Hey.
Yeah?
Come up and-
Mine's already cracked, holy shit.
Oh, wow.
Wait, let's do the theme song.
Hold on.
Wait, you and me do it.
It's, um, "Damp and damp, man.
What's up to all my chuggers?"
Yo, what's up?
It's the Israel's Number One Podcast.
Wrong one, man.
It's like-
Let me let that burp out.
How does it go?
Oh, let me let that- let me get that burp out.
wrong one man, wrong one man, it's like, how does this go?
oh let me let that, let me get that burp out
ummm
beers we drank mothafucka
with Juvio, Caleb and Rex
wow
and also Brian and Mike and Noah and Alex
yeah
wait where's Rex?
what is Rex doing? what the fuck is he doing?
so Rex, he uh
he's still so busy with work
he uh, he's currently
Addied out and it's really funny science talk to him because I
So I went oh, I'm staying with him. So I went over to his place. He's really been really helpful really nice
He set me up on an air mattress
And he's just like I'm just like trying to take a nap because I'm so tired
And he just walks up to me and just has me some chips and doesn't just and goes away and just come tracking
and he handed me some candy.
I'm like, "Alright man, thank you."
You handed candy? He's momming you?
Is he locked in?
Is he locked in right now?
He's locked in.
He's so dialed in, but also he's also still so distracted.
So he keeps like going back to work
and he's like so dialed in and he walks outside
and he's just talking to me like,
"Yeah, this actually, I hooked my entire room to like Alexa.
Check this out. Alexa, play some Family Guy."
And he's like, "Oh yeah."
And he's like, "Alright man, thanks."
You saw that when we went to his house
where the pride and joy of his life is that
can
about it for 30 minutes and I was like, Oh, what are you working on right now?
And he was like, well, I'm in a TFT game, but playing TFT for like four hours,
like I'm playing TFT.
Yeah.
He said he was going to like do it.
He was going to try to be here, uh, but he couldn't make it and that's his loss.
So we're doing a little special episode with all the people that we know in New York.
Yep.
And a guy from Canada, a guy from DC.
Yeah.
Oh, I'm American.
That's right.
Yeah, you're looking good, man.
Thank you, man.
You're sticky. You're sticking to...
Oh, shit.
You're sticking to stuff. What do you have on your head?
A long...
Is this a bandana?
That is not a bandana, mate.
I'm learning right now.
It says "folding camping chair."
It's a camping chair bag.
I just got back.
Oh, from your tour.
Yeah, I need a tour.
What's your MOS, bro?
What?
Blown up in the plane.
Whoa.
can't tell you that you can't tell me that man no no no no he's a it's a he
can't tell us my under exactly you know like steel team six oh yeah special
forces he's operate that shit that's why I have this disguise on this is a
disguise so I'll kind of can't figure out who he is oh if they did you'd be
dead man I'm a bad man I believe that I could see you being some kind of
a
and he said, "Thank God you're not tall."
Which, first of all, were my feelings, man.
Those are--
Right, the same size.
Yeah, you wish, man.
No, no.
I'm like 6'2".
I'm an operator.
You may.
Maybe mentally you are much bigger than me,
but in terms of stature, bro,
I basically got a centimeter on you.
Which I don't think is that much, right?
Nope.
No, not a centimeter's not much.
So how's America, man?
You liking it here?
I love it.
Well, I guess--
First time in America.
First time in America is you've been on a tour.
You're born overseas already.
You served your entire life and now you're finally here for the first time.
Yeah.
It's crazy.
And it was worth fighting for, right?
Yeah.
I lost a lot of guys.
This is what...
Lost a lot of guys.
I lost all my guys.
We know he loves guys too.
I love guys.
He really loves my guys.
Who's the number one guy that you lost, Matt?
Jamie.
Oh not Jamie, no.
He was my guy.
No, not Jamie Foxx.
The one from Monster Garage.
This is not a funny matter, not Jamie Foxx.
No, don't laugh about Jamie Foxx.
He got some bad news today.
Jamie Monday. Who's the one that was married to Sandra Bullock?
Jamie Foxx.
Wait, was it the motorcycle guy?
Yeah, yeah, Jamie Motorcycle.
No, what the fuck was his name?
Yeah, he was West Coast Customs or something.
West Coast Customs or something?
Yeah, it was chop or Orange County chopper.
No, he did Monster Garage.
Oh, whatever. He had one of those shops.
Monster Garage.
And he looked, he had like a fucked up-
Someone look it up and tell me the-
Yeah, someone said it in cat.
He looked like he was 60 and he was like 35.
That guy was cool as fuck, man.
Jamie Savage, they're saying.
I watched the-
No, that's a different-
That's the Mythbusters guy.
That's not his name.
That's basically the Mythbusters guy.
Jamie Savage.
What is that?
No, that's a combination.
Oh, Jamie.
Jesse James.
It was not Jamie, okay.
Wait, that's really it?
Yeah, Jesse James is actually Jesse James.
Yeah, his parents named him after the cowboy.
That's badass, dude.
You named him after a cowboy?
Yeah, I'm gonna name my kid Charlie Chaplin or some shit like that.
Yeah, you might heal their mustache.
Just ruin your life just off the bat, dude.
I mean, that might be the best possible...
That guy's had a hard life. I think he's addicted to drugs.
But that might be the best...
Charlie Chaplin?
No, Jesse James.
That might be the best possible outcome for somebody named Jesse James.
What's hard about being addicted to drugs? They're fun as hell, man.
Well, because eventually, dude, you gotta get off 'em, man.
No, you don't.
Straight up, dude.
No, he's rich.
That's some real shit.
He's rich, so he clearly is functioning pretty well.
You think he's still rich? I'd be pretty surprised, honestly.
I would bet Jesse James is somebody who lost it all.
I bet he lost it all.
I kinda wanna try methadone.
[laughter]
Just jump straight to methadone?
Sorry, I found out that you drink it.
Yeah, it's like a little comes in a little cup.
It comes a little.
Let me try that one time.
Cameron mean camera Olive Garden and he they handed us a pink
lemonade sample and when we walked in really.
Oh, thanks and I chugged mine and he like kept his and brought
it to the table and then we sat down and he had the pink lemonade
the tiny cup and the waitress came up.
She was like, hi, can I say what the fuck is that?
You can't have that this fucking restaurant and he was like,
you know, lemonade.
She's at all.
I
the
Not everyone's drinking this we gotta we gotta do the ratings man. You know how the rules
I'm gonna give this a
I'm gonna give this a five. No, I'm gonna give this a six two and this is a
This is a also a six to basketball player on the basketball player scale
I'll say six seven you get this at six seven six seven just cuz it's a pilsner you gotta give it contact
OK, give me the basketball player, though.
Basketball player?
It's like Chris Paul.
Shut up.
Oh, Chris Paul, though.
Oh, Chris Paul right now.
Chris Paul right now.
OK.
Six man Chris Paul.
Yeah, yeah.
It's like a guy you want to plug and play any time.
You can put him on any team.
He's going to make a difference.
A Smirnoff Ice.
He got Ice.
This is not my choice.
Gale just walked up to me, and he did the stupidest thing
of all time.
He handed me a hat.
I was like, check this out.
Put this on.
And he just pulls this out.
I'm like, okay, I'm fucking nice to tell you.
So I'm, I'm iced and I'm icing and it's, it's all right.
That's actually not bad.
You don't hate it. I don't hate it. It kind of tastes like, just like candy, man.
Okay. Mr. Veteran, what do you give this?
I think I give this like a nine.
Yeah. Never had beer before.
Middle East. I've been kicking bad in the Middle East, man.
Damn.
And having this, is this American?
I don't know.
It better be.
It better be American. I fought for this.
Damn, thank you, dude.
A lot of boys died for this.
Alright, I might have to bump my score up.
I'll give it a 7 then.
If I know people died for this shit.
You've been a little disrespectful.
It was like a blood diamond.
Dude, I would never disrespect troops in front of you.
You already know that shit.
Thank you.
Mike, what are you giving? Oh wait, you have something else.
I have a White Claw Surge Blackberry.
Barry and I would give this a five out of ten. I think this is this is a six foot
guy who is you see him on the court this is a guy you went to school with you
come back during the summer you're playing pickup ball with him and he's
fine. I didn't fight for that. This is disrespect. This is maybe the first ever
rating that wasn't even in the league dude. Wow that's really bad.
All right, what do you have?
All right, we got a Sapporo Reserve.
It's delicious.
One of the best beers ever, I'd say.
10 out of 10?
No, not a 10 out of 10.
No.
That's reserved for the best.
This is probably a 7.5 out of 10.
We do the Portnoy scale here.
There is no 10.
This is a Jimmer Ferdet.
This is better.
It's from a foreign land or at least performs better in a foreign land.
I actually agree that Sapporo is a Jimmer Ferdet and here's why.
Before you buy it, it sounds like the best beer ever.
And then you buy that shit, and you're like, "Oh, I'm going to have to go back and buy
another one."
in a foreign land.
- It actually, I actually agree
that Sapporo is in jibber for that and here's why.
Before you buy it, it sounds like the best beer ever.
And then you buy that shit and it's just okay.
Especially for the price.
- But you get this somewhere overseas,
it's fucking amazing.
- Yeah, yeah, it would blow your mind.
- It's like, wow, this is the best.
- Because it's the only way you can read the label.
- Also, I haven't had Sapporo been sitting in this office
for like two days.
- No, actually I brought that.
- Yeah, but thank you.
- Oh, yeah.
You brought it last night and you left it there.
No, I brought it last night.
I put it in my backpack.
Then I brought it back home, put it back in the fridge.
Then I put it back here.
So it's seen the world is what you're saying.
It's yes.
It's traveled just like Jim or for death.
You did a flat Stanley with the, with the beer, man.
That's a good idea.
We should do a beer that we, everybody lives in different places.
We should hand a, we should do a Bud Light that everybody takes a
photo with in a different car.
And you can do one driving directly into the white house.
That's a great idea.
I'm
had something funny to report.
My younger, one of my cousins was bragging to everyone else
that his younger brother was being tested for autism.
- Bragging?
- Yeah, he was like, I'm smart and my younger brother--
- Just go and get them out the hood.
- The autistic ones are really smart.
- This, I don't think he was saying
he was like a smart autistic.
I think he was saying he's like a--
- He was not-- - He's weird and that's why--
- So it was not gonna,
this wasn't a get them out the hood situation
where like he's gonna invent the next Facebook.
I don't think so.
No, I don't think so.
I also, I don't think, I think he's a normal kid.
I hate to say it, I think it was kind of a swap.
The younger brother, normal, like a normal kid runs around and screams.
You think they switched the results?
Yeah, yeah.
Younger brother runs around, screams, like pulls dog's tails.
Yeah.
Normal, seven year old boy.
That's what boys should do.
Yeah.
The older brother, in his teens, like high achieving student, gets really mad when the
younger brother is getting attention paid to him, like gets into fights with everyone at
the table over how they're resolving disputes.
I think the results were switched.
That'd be kind of a classic little Maury situation.
That'd be a funny way to destroy a family if you're a doctor I guess.
To be clear, I don't think anyone, nobody was diagnosed with autism.
One of the older kids was lying and he was like, "My younger brother might have autism."
Well what happened to me today?
Well I put super glue in my mouth.
Tried to open a bottle of super glue.
You don't lick your mouth?
I don't know how to open- people open stuff with their hands.
I don't know how to do that man, it hurts my hand.
Use it over your elbow.
That's real.
I don't open shit with my- I'm sure this is how they do it over in the other countries.
I use my teeth dude. God gave me teeth.
I'm just throwing them on coke bottles one fucking-
They're not just for eating.
They're not for eating at all. I barely use them to eat.
I used them to open super glue.
The entire thing exploded in my mouth.
And I was like,
"Well, this is like getting any other thing in your mouth.
Let me go and put cold water on it instantly."
And all of it just hardened.
And I've just had something,
I've had glue stuck between my teeth for four hours.
- It's an L day for Caleb today.
Yes, you're doing L.
- I've taken all Ls.
Guys, here's what happened to me today, man.
I woke up and I woke up at 6.30.
I had to go pick him up.
- Do it, Jubio.
I woke up at 630, I had to drive to Newark to pick him up, direct flight from Abu Dhabi.
Abu Dhabi, the war torch machine of Abu Dhabi.
Dude, it's crazy.
It's insane in Abu Dhabi. I think he's in spec ops.
We had to make a lot of signs saying welcome back our hero troops.
Yeah, man, he had to go to that.
They have a golf tour over there now, right?
right? Yeah. What's it called?
The L-I-V-E.
Yeah, LIV.
And they took the PGA.
They're racking.
They did, but they also still paid everyone like $8 billion.
They paid people. Wait, it got dissolved?
Yeah, they were shamed from buying it.
Oh, they had to. They had to.
So now they're going to start sending the regular PGA guys out into the fucking...
To Dubai?
That is so awesome.
Fucking Bubba Watson.
And it literally cost... I mean, it's expensive to have a golf course here. It's probably $40
40 times more expensive to have a golf course than to have grass.
Yeah. That's insane. But they, they got their own thing going on.
What was I saying? God. Oh, huh. Oh, my L report.
I woke up. This is, yeah. Had to go to Newark. This is already a huge L.
I drank a cold brew coffee, right? Second L. I pick him up.
We go to where you work. You give me too many drinks, guys.
way too many drinks. And then he starts driving.
And then I'm really too tired. And then I start driving.
And then I hop behind the wheel. We drive over to Micro Center.
It's Black Friday. Where's the deals?
Let me get a deal on a brand new gaming mouse, guys.
100% MSRP, G Pro Super Light.
I get forced to purchase by three guys who are with me.
I get completely forced. My hand is forced.
I had no option. It's all right.
Well, is it a good mouse?
I don't even...
Guys, here's the worst part.
I haven't even opened it. It's been sitting in my car. I might use it after this, but who fucking knows?
Third L. I have to... what was my third L?
I think that's the glue.
Third L? Glue my mouth. Glued my mouth. I got it all over my tongue, both my lips and my teeth.
Fourth L.
Everybody takes a nap except for me, apparently.
Game fuel.
Oh, and I take... I had a game fuel that I got at Micro Center, and I thought, "Guys, that's probably a hundred and sixty milligrams of caffeine.
That's a normal drink."
300 milligrams of caffeine. I've had six between the and you gave me cold brew drinks at your
cold brew rum drink. Give me a cold brew rum drink. So now I've had I'm at like 700 milligrams
of caffeine today. And then I went to the gym and I started working out and thought fully
thought I had a stroke while I was doing reverse curls. I was like, this has got to be the
worst way to die ever. I'm not even like doing a deadlift. I'm not even doing something hard.
I'm doing reverse curls and I got your neck up again. No, man, I mean, I lived. Well, because
I didn't do upright roads.
That's how I chose life.
I chose life.
I chose life today.
I chose life today as I do every day.
Well, we'll see about tomorrow.
But then I didn't get to have dinner before this.
So now I'm a little bit splitting hairs.
Yeah, I'll be honest.
It doesn't seem that hard.
Julio L report.
You can't give us 100 L's because then you're just complaining.
So Julio L report.
I literally thought this was like some of my closest friends in the world in one room.
Complaining, complaining, whining, whining.
Okay, I'm taking my shot without anybody.
All right.
Whoa.
Alright, whoa!
Oh no!
Go, cheers!
Then cheers, man.
Cheers.
To Drinksgiving.
Wow.
Drinksgiving.
This is awful.
That is worse than I remember it being.
It was actually incredibly smooth and delicious.
Wow, George Dickel White Dog, incredible.
This is, for people who saw it, this is the whiskey that we poured in beef stew a week
ago and ate the beef stew.
It's worse straight than it is in the beef stew.
I miss the beef stew.
I know it described it as a corn
forward before, and I wish it
tasted more like corn.
I honestly really would have preferred
that. You like that?
They should sell this bottle for
two hundred and fifty dollars.
Battle hardens.
It reminds me of the Middle East.
That is true.
That that that that that that
throw burn. Uh-huh.
Mustard gas.
Search a chemical.
Oh, that tastes good, man.
Mustard gas has been there since
What, 1989? You've been stationed over there?
Yep.
It's been a long time.
First time home in, what, 31 years?
Well, I've never been home. I was born there.
I was born on the base.
He was born by way of expats, and they immediately enlisted him.
Actually, he enlisted himself.
Himself, at the age of 13, 14?
They put, like, two different things down, like when they teach a dog how to speak English with buttons.
And he chose to enlist.
It's just a bunch of guns.
He just picked one.
And he just grabbed one, man.
I was grabbing one, and I started shooting.
sure
I think Brigadier General is actually like the second highest thing you can be next to the President, I want to say.
Yeah, that's not real.
Well, besides the five-star.
But second...
Five-star general, but there hasn't been a five-star general since I've been around.
The second thing next to the President is the First Lady, mister. I went to school.
Oh, sorry. Well, there's President, First Lady, Brigadier General.
These days.
And then the guy who services the Brigadier General.
I'll say it. The First Lady.
Damn, man. We have the gun.
Yeah, he should have the gun.
He brought his service.
How many people how many people would have to die in the line of
succession for Mike to be elected president?
One.
I mean, you live in Washington.
I think that you might it might only be like 50,000 people.
It might be that many. Yeah, it might be actually fewer than that.
Fewer than 50. Yeah.
You think before they just start going down a staff list and all the papers
and they go be. Yeah. They'd be looking at responsible young men who own
property in Washington, D.C.
Oh, property.
My girlfriend owns the property.
That's actually even cooler.
I'm actually her complete tenant.
That's amazing.
You pay rent to your girlfriend?
I pay rent on Venmo every month to my girlfriend.
Yeah.
I am such an alpha.
That's amazing.
I fought for that.
Who's that report?
Mike's. That's an alpha.
That's a fucking dub, bro.
None of the liability of owning property.
I didn't take any else today.
I just had a long walk.
You just took an, that was an L.
You took a 30 minute walk.
40, 40.
People are saying my 40 minute walk from the other end of town to the office was an L.
The other end of town?
I don't think it was an L because I ate a lot yesterday.
It was Thanksgiving.
My first Thanksgiving.
You worked it off, man.
I had nothing but heavy plates and then this morning I got poisoned by a secret worker
at a restaurant.
You did, dude.
I took a nap and I just walked for minutes over here. It was really cold. So took the cousin walk
I took the cousin
Yeah
It was alright. It was a little cold in my face. So I'm gonna go get a yeet shy see after this
I think we think he would look exact he has the same facial hair
Construction as well. Yes. This is a big problem yesterday. We played secret Hitler
And he literally look at him and tell me that with a face
Well, first of all the face the the hair the mustache the beliefs. This is a ringer for Adolf
It's some Hitler lineage that he literally has to be he went to Mexico. I fled Germany. He did
That's what they always say
The first game the first game of the night I was actually Hitler
He actually was and Brian just ruined it for the rest of your life. So the rest of the night
I was just feeling like for you. I did my job something got taken away from me
my
thought he was Hitler every time. I mean, and he would just be every single game he'd be
like, Oh, I hope the liberals win this time. Like, so kind of weird and coy. It was odd.
And of course he didn't win that much. Yeah. I lost all games. Yeah. Anyways, no else to
report. You know, report. I think I only had one L today, which was, I was pooping in the
airport and then they're, they're almost here to pick me up and they told me it cut it short
I haven't finished it yet.
It's so...
Okay.
Let's don't...
You left the crust.
We did say specifically, "Leave the crust."
I...
Yeah.
You left the...
Still got the crust.
I did leave the crust.
That's battle-hardened, dude.
That's crazy.
That has nothing to me.
That's the norm.
Dude, I love that.
I'm pooping, gunshots, I stop it.
Yes, I fight.
You guys sometimes...
Yeah.
I mean, I guess that might be...
That's the only thing that could interrupt a man taking a shit in the middle of the desert
is a gunshot whizzing by your head.
You know that?
I got a fight right now.
That's how W's.
All it takes is a friend.
All you need is a friend to pick you up.
And then you go, "I'm leaving this crust right now."
And I bet that was a deep dish.
I bet for real, that was Chicago style.
Popping out of the airport, got the donut.
It took a lot out of me to cut that, to cut it short.
Damn, dude.
I had to hold the rails and cut that thing short.
You were sitting in the disabled spot?
I'm a veteran.
Why would I not?
You're right.
That's a good point.
Yeah, that's a good point.
Like, there's a couple guys in there.
I can go in there.
A couple guys in the disabled stall?
No, no, no.
There's a couple guys in the other stalls.
I knew somebody in college, I won't say who it is, but he refused to shit in anything
but disabled stalls the entire time we were in college.
And I explained to him at some point that there has to have been at some point somebody in
a wheelchair sitting outside my house.
And I was like, "I'm not going to do that."
And he was like, "I'm not going to do that."
I won't say who it is, but he refused to shit in anything but disabled stalls the entire time we were in college.
And I explained to him at some point that there has to have been at some point somebody in a wheelchair sitting outside of the stall.
And then the guy walks out, well it's Joe Gleason, Joe walks out.
Joe walks out, and they're like, "What's this guy?"
There's a guy in a wheelchair?
Yeah, this guy has to be...
Joe is tall though.
Well, that is some kind of disability, I think. At least on an airplane.
and
of
I was once on a flight to Russia.
I was upgraded to something called Imperial Class.
Whoa!
Which was those things-
That sounds better than First Class.
Where they have-
It was way better.
It was where they have those pods for you.
The stuff you only see in promotional videos
for like Air Emirates.
Oh my God.
Where it's you each-
Like five people in the front get their own pods.
And they have like a meal.
And it was just completely empty and they gave it to us.
Did you get a steak or some home treats?
I remember getting-
They served food on like really fancy china.
None of the fake like recycled cardboard shit.
like they gave us plates, real plates.
It was fire.
And I ate the plate.
I want to, did you ransack the mini bar?
Oh, you know, I did.
Yeah, I was, I was what, 13 and you know, I was fucking on the stewardess.
Way.
Mike, can you stand up real quick?
Can you raise your hand real quick?
Just so people can tell, can tell how tall you are.
Stand up.
Oh yeah.
And then Alex.
I know it looks.
Alex, no one and Mike stand up.
No, sit back down.
So you're.
Should I stand up?
Yeah.
Stand up.
Whoa.
*laughing*
*more laughing*
That's crazy man.
He's like a little boy.
You guys should do Robin Big, remember that show?
I am not a little boy.
We were talking about the movie Brothers before,
but the one about
Arnold Schwarzenegger and Danny DeVito,
we gotta do that. I'll be Arnold Schwarzenegger.
Wait, don't! Stop sticking with DeVito, man!
That's crazy man.
That's racist!
You wouldn't last a second in the war.
the
drunk guy that fell asleep at my bar today.
(laughs)
And then--
- I was close.
- Yeah, you were close.
- And then he wouldn't leave with his girlfriend
and she was like begging him, like,
"Please, let's go home, let's go home."
And he was like, "No, fuck you."
And then he went to sleep.
Not that type of bar, by the way.
It's kind of fancy.
- You have an insane rate of crazy people
coming to that restaurant for a place
that really shouldn't have that.
- I took Big W, Big W, fake keys with the low cut.
That's your momma.
Alright, on to the next one.
I will say, double your report, every time I burp into the mic, it kills Brian.
The stink of it?
He loves it. Just the sound.
He really goes crazy.
He can't, look at him.
That's funny dude.
That's a dub.
Huge L, technically today.
Usually I know when I'm at home with my dad, to like not engage in argument.
says something to just be like, yeah, I do believe like Israel's controlled by lizard,
etc, etc.
For some reason, I got into an argument with him last night.
And that was a profound I couldn't tell you what the argument was about.
He kept changing stuff.
I think he's been watching like Ben Shapiro videos because he keeps trying to own me in
conversations.
I'm so amazed when old people know about like Ben Shapiro or Steven Crowder.
He sent me a text the other day and he was like, "Look at this Candace Owens video.
I think she makes some seriously good points.
Have you heard of her?"
I was like, "Not responding."
I really did.
I accidentally killed my dad.
But there was one thing that really stuck with me, which cannot possibly be true, but
But it's like rattling around in my head.
He was like, I actually told Vladimir Putin how to keep the Belarusian president in charge
of the country.
And they followed my plan point by point.
He's still there.
I was like, no, not at all.
I think that maybe he's in a meeting.
And he brought it up and he was bragging about it to me.
And I was like, I could not, there was no, there's no way to engage with him.
Yeah.
There's like no response.
We have a panel of really knowledgeable guys right here.
Why don't you go step by step what the plan is.
He didn't tell me the plan. He was just like, yeah, I emailed them and yeah, they followed my plan point by point.
Wow.
I was like, dad, there's no way.
I didn't impress him on it though. I mean, it's probably true.
Last time I saw my grandpa, I went to Jersey because he wouldn't come to New York because he said it's a sanctuary city.
And literally before I even hugged him, hello, I went to go get lunch with him in Jersey at a diner.
I like walked in and from across the diner he was like, "Do you have any Muslims in your
neighborhood?"
I was like, "Yeah."
And he's like, "Oh, we made a good choice coming to Jersey."
I was like, "Jesus Christ, man."
He's just so loud.
Then he tip $5, $100 bill.
The thing that started the argument was my dad was like, "I bet the newspaper doesn't
put in why Hamas attacked Israel."
I was like, "Yeah, we do.
Yeah, we did."
And he just did not believe me.
Yeah.
Did not believe me.
that
raw eggs. Like every morning he eats raw eggs. No, not every morning, just most mornings.
Most mornings he eats raw eggs, man. Rocky vibes, man. It is fully rocky vibes. It is
rocky vibes. I'm basically training to beat up any guy that looks like Apollo Green that
I see. I'm just gonna, you know, go full force and they'll understand. You should enlist.
You need to enlist. You do feel like a guy who lost out on enlisting a little bit. I've
definitely thought about it.
Mostly like the Coast Guard.
Wait, you look like the kid who says he's a future Marine.
No, I don't.
You do.
No.
Wait, that is a child.
I am a grown man.
You have a grown up version of him.
No.
Wait, look at the camera.
That's a black guy.
Vans?
That guy has a--
No, it's a little white boy.
It's a little white boy, yeah.
Chat is saying he does.
People are saying he does.
No, no, actually not.
They're not saying that.
No one's ever said that.
God.
Yeah. And then I, um, I got up at 5 30, uh, took my two raw eggs,
uh, which are delicious.
I took them.
Uh, and then, uh, I had to get, um, driven to the airport to go pick up our,
our glorious veteran, which I mean, also is miserable.
Uh, Julio made me sit in the backseat, even though I called shotgun,
clearly not, you know, the same with the American rules are about you should
the
We'll just drop it on my stuff wait and oh you're keeping yourself in my place
Last point
We we took we took turns going shotgun. We did not take turns. I had to run and
Yeah, no then he called me a bitch
And then yeah, I had to hang out with these fucking guys all day which you know
Yeah, obvious W, but only half the the W
We know it was awesome
Thank you. I need to see the picture of him
In front of the skyline
Yeah, we just took a bunch of him first time in the city maybe back or not back
It was yeah, it was awesome Caleb took me to a children's park that was cool I took it
I
last time right?
He did.
Yeah, yeah.
He did that by blurting.
Unlike the Brian incident where he just showed his address a couple times on stream.
And he doesn't like to be heard.
And besides that, didn't you show them your card info too?
No, I didn't show them my card info.
Just the last four digits in the security code.
Not the security code.
Not that important.
Don't, if you look this up, I swear to God, I'm going to get my special forces SEAL team
nine guy.
He's going to come and kill you.
kill anybody for no reason. He's out of his mind. So now that you're here man, are you
going to get like a security job, a bouncer? You'd make a great bouncer I think. If I pulled
up at the club and I saw you dressed like this, I might just leave man. I'm gonna be
straight up. I might not even hand you an ID. I don't know what I want to be. I might be
the
out and go crazy taxi. Yeah. I think, um, I think we might send you back pretty soon.
We got a new mission for you, boss. They might recall me back. Yeah. Did you get discharged
or did you just, you served your, your years? I served my years. I said I needed some, a
little bit of time. Were you guys ever close to joining the military? I was pretty close.
You were definitely close, man.
He did, wait, he did, you know what he did, man?
He did a child Air Force training.
I did more than that, though, dude.
Tony Cowden, are you kidding me?
Oh, yeah, he also did CrossFit.
No, no, I mean, I did CrossFit for like six months
and then I moved on 'cause I,
'cause she's gay?
There's this guy in our hometown,
this guy Tony Cowden.
Well, there's a couple guys in our hometown
because we're-- Tony Cowden is the beast.
We're like an hour from Fort Bragg and Camp Lejeune,
so
Every story I've heard about this guy is definitely a lie.
That I've told you?
No, it's all true.
You said that he was a guy, he dealt drugs in high school and then tell the story.
Confirmed by his sister.
Yeah, confirmed by his sister man.
Yeah, he was selling coke in high school and then got caught and because his dad was like friends with the sheriff's department
He got off and then he went to like the State University and then was selling more coke
DEA agent came up to him in the grocery store and told him like yeah, we're gonna pop you were on a
Task force do that. I don't know. I don't know but it dude Tony is not a liar. He is a
Country, man
He's a complete liar. He's on the first team to hunt bin Laden, bro. I will fight him CIA operative actually someone puts money
Tony's a huge liar actually
lying a
Drug he got fucking this other story. I heard about him is that he was in like some like
What do they call that when a bunch of cars are in a line? Oh come no, that's real
No, that's a parade and got blown up by a
The only person
No, that's real that's real that's real
It's confirmed within the special forces community it's confirmed I'm serious
No, this is real this is real this is real real real I've seen pictures of the Mercedes I've met
I've met multiple guys who have said
It was armored Mercedes and he's the only one that survived
That you would be like and oh, it's real. I swear. I swear. It's real. It's real. It's so real
Tony lies about like almost everything that's real. That's real. It was a pimped-out
Mercedes and it had a PlayStation and I mean so you look no this shit is real. No, that shit is that's
Well, how wild city could you start from the CIA?
Because he's crazy
Or because he heard his foot. He was the most decorated
Like a ranger at the time before he joined the CIA
Where's Chad at? Where's Chad at? I need Chad to back me up.
It's confirmed.
I need Chad to back me up here.
Dude, he literally was... Iron Man was on the TV behind you as he told you this story.
I was like, "Yeah, dude, I came up with something called an arc reactor."
And then Jeff Bridges came up with one too, and we had a complete battle on top of a building.
Nah, nah. I will always... The thing is, Tony is such a scary guy that when he tells you a story,
you have to believe it because he can smell when you think you're lying.
and he...
Tony Stark?
Yeah, Tony Stark.
Yeah.
[laughter]
And my name was Tony, it's not his name.
His name's Daryl.
Yeah.
But yeah, he ran for, uh...
Yeah, he ran for...
No, he ran for, like, actual...
Oh, for Congress.
Congress.
For a House of Representatives.
He ran for the House of Representatives.
Uh, he has, uh, an insane TBI from the, um, the blast that blew up that Mercedes.
Insane TBI, he's nuts.
Yeah, I completely believe it.
He's completely insane.
And, uh, he didn't come...
He didn't come from a softball tournament.
He didn't come anywhere close to winning at all.
No, but he had a fire website where you could win an AR-15.
Actually?
Yeah.
Why didn't we enter?
Chad did enter.
He donated $5.
And he entered.
So we could give away?
Yeah, it was like if you donate $5 to the campaign, you could win an AR-15.
Being around Tony and his like, I don't know, there's like probably 20 or 30 Special Forces guys
that are like, you should join up.
So you never even, how close did you get?
Um, I was like, oh I'm strong enough and if they train me I could probably make it.
But then I realized like you gotta, yeah dude I was built.
He says you're not strong enough.
Yeah dude I was strong enough and they were like, yeah you could do it.
And as soon as I thought about like, oh I'll have to like kill people if I do this.
That's the best part of the job.
I didn't want to do it anymore.
Yeah, ask him man.
Yeah, it's not me.
It's like 80% of the boys.
Not for me dude, I'm a baby.
Yeah, yeah, shoot some guns.
No, no.
You don't want to kill?
You don't wanna kill?
Kill some bad guys?
Osama?
I'll put that bullet in.
I wanna nurture life.
That was you, man?
He was the one who went through his hard drive and found all that answer.
I love beauty, man.
Do you love beauty?
Excuse me.
He's beautiful?
He is beautiful, man.
I would lay with him.
You would lay with him?
Yeah.
He's still alive today.
That's pause.
Is there a bra button?
Yeah, wait, hold on.
It's probably one of the top ones.
Yeah.
I would be his concubine.
I'll put this wig on and I would dance
Say you'd lay with him again. I would lay with Osama bin Laden
Would you have sex with the crickets man?
I'm just trying to clarify for the yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. I'm I might kill you too
Have you seen everyone saying he's fire recently everyone's like
Yeah, people were saying that people were saying Osama bin Laden is they're like fire people take the word like wait
He actually kind of had a point. That's what I'm saying
Everyone I think they're always suck. They're stupid as fuck. They don't they don't realize he ran two planes into the Twin Towers
He did first. I'm here. Boom this
Wait, what he did this when did he do it?
Years back. I really want to make one of those videos. It's like, you know, they always do like like
This true crime videos, it's like when to high school kids shot up the high school
They're high school in Columbine. I do I want to make one that's like like that that crazy time when two planes
I
Think that'd be good. I've been watching a lot of those videos watch a video yesterday. I was making an unsolved mystery. Yeah
Nobody knows who did it. This is the craziest thing ever. I made a video or no. I watched a video
Yesterday that was a kid who killed his own mom guys
Killed a this video. I made this video
No
It's one of these like ripoffs of the JCS criminal psychology videos the ones that you fall asleep to and he made
That's normal. I think that's normal that didn't weird
I am I feel like I'm free to fold to blow your spot up. Yeah. No, you're not free to do anything
Nice last night we're hanging out a branch apartment
It was me cam and Pat and Brian because he lives there and we were honest
You - honest TV
It was logged into his account
So, you know how you like watching YouTube videos and like scroll down what you're like playing at something
I just give you like you regularly recommended
So we do that like once and there's this like one video. It's like top
10 most scariest stories of all time and it's like a two-hour video watch and it's like although it watch through is like
Oh, that's kind of funny. Did he watch that?
I don't know
It might be a glitch then we keep scrolling down then at the the grid of like four five videos
All fits the fills up with like creepy stories from I don't know where like 40
Scariest stories of all of all time. Yeah, you're on. Yeah, it's all like three hours four hour five hour videos
They're like so many of them and they're all completely watch the completion and it was just so funny to us that they're just like
Watching that all day it makes it explains a lot about you
You fall asleep to scary stories every single night. Yeah, I like you wake up terrified. I wear my eggs
It's a normal thing.
It's actually cool.
And you should kill yourself.
I watched a FNAF video about the entire Laura FNAF.
Any of you follow up to that one?
What?
The entire Laura FNAF.
Have you ever watched that one?
Five Nights at Freddy's.
Oh, FNAF.
Yeah.
Five Nights at Freddy's.
Me and Noah know.
No, that's not.
I'd be harmonized on that shit.
I'd be very happy.
nights at freddy's.
No, actually I wouldn't because that's not scary and that is my dream.
You're not scared of Five Nights at Freddy's?
Actually...
What the hell's wrong with you?
It's a lot like the...
I really want to watch that movie.
I'm not gonna lie.
I went to the theater to watch the movie and it was an L.
You saw it?
It's an L.
It's an L?
I was trying to get me, Pat, and Cam to go to the premiere and take a bunch of...
Just like jump over the rope and take a bunch of pictures of us on the red carpet at their Five Nights at Freddy's premiere.
the
all over their bodies? Hair? Hair. Yeah, so it wouldn't be maybe the least person to be a doll.
And by the way, it's not a doll, it's an animatronic. So you're wrong on two counts.
Hannah's dad was in town and I dropped her off to see a movie with him. And there was like a
billion people at the theater. Don't watch my dad. And she was like, there's nothing in the theater,
but Five Nights at Freddy's and this Meg Ryan comedy. And when we, and she was like, there's
is
it was
I
in his movies when people die so like if they could just do a super cut of
yeah I would watch that yeah I would watch that but that's it
Mike shooting you in the head man. This is the craziest game of Russian roulette I've ever seen.
Did you like the flower moon movie? Yeah I thought it was really great like I was very
touched by the ending. That's amazing. Have you seen it? I've not seen it. The end for whoever
seen it the ending is very touching it's very moving. Genuinely the last like minute of the
movie is very moving. I'm not gonna lie I think you're the only person that's
watched this movie here. I will say that's the way I feel about Heat and Heat is the
longest movie of all time and the last minute makes me cry every time. I did I
saw, he's a liar, I did see Heat with Noah maybe two weeks ago. He did not cry.
Well I didn't cry because people were being rude in the theater. The next day I
I cried in the walk-in at work thinking about
I'm so serious. No my my co-worker put the ending Moby song on and I had to go into the walk-in
No, I didn't I did not ask him
Damn good guess
Nice
That was well done Mike. How did you know where that was?
Way he's going again. Wait, hold on
Hitler was back
Thank God he really that was a serious roulette you just played man in a major way
Yeah, I'm trying to think of lies a good movie. I seen that I haven't seen any good movies in a couple you're honored
Good they don't exist anymore man damn. That's a really
In the theater or just in general in general brother and watch a good movie. You have mascara on your nose. It was killing me
Mascara yeah, let's see what is it gone. Yep. No, it's gone. Okay, my hate your vape. Yeah, it might be volcanic
So here you go. Just trust it on that
Part salt. Yeah, no, it told us that he has a salt that smells and tastes exactly like a fart
No, it doesn't taste like a fart, but it's when you open the bag up. It makes the whole room smell like fart
I don't understand how you can smell like a fart black salt black salt. No, can you explain the racist?
Can you explain the porno drink that you made us? Oh, yeah
At a at 9 a.m. I made Alex and Julio drink a porn star martini
But you don't know what that is. It's the most like consumed cocktail in the entire world
It's a British then it's a very British
We walk into this restaurant, you know, they they order a bloody mary. They're twinning
So me and I were like, oh we should twin some mimosas and I gave them a tiki cold brew rum drink and I go
Oh, yeah, can we get some of Moses? You're like, I'm gonna make you a porn drink. I was like, all right
No, you guys asked for passion fruit. We said can we get action on the menu man? Oh
You guys just said passion fruit
Passion fruit. Oh, we're the were the martinis good. Yeah, they were fine. Yeah
I will I will say the passion fruit mimosa is made the porn star martini is much better
Yeah, so and I don't know who kind of looks like a porn star over there
I can see you having a big one and being
Jeremy but can I raise you?
Way Juvia, what's your opener?
Let me see your thing and that works that works what in church or where are you?
At church and
And then you say let me see your thing in your normal voice. Yeah, and then what do you say?
You have to go one lower because you started high
please
that's
What are you gonna do the rest of the time you guys are here man, dude everything
Everything fellas come meet us at we're doing a beers. We drink meetup at Brooklyn, New York
Yeah, and Bushwick in 30 minutes. All right, y'all
Troutman on Chapman's on Troutman Street. Yeah
Yeah, buys a drink you can hear there. We don't we won't care. We will kill you with the gun though
I'm thinking bring that we had we had a we had like a
Airsoft Glock that I can't believe they sold in a store. That was like it looked exactly like a glass
Oh, yeah, they sold it. They had to go to Connecticut to buy it. Oh
I thought you meant like this it's gone. No, no, no, we threw it away because it got my best friend
Growing up got a charge for for having a fake in his is like full metal airsoft
Putting it in boiling water and taking the orange tip off. That's I think exactly what they did on someone in traffic
That's crazy
Probably deserved it. He wouldn't have gotten the ticket though. If you got all I got was a ticket
He got arrested he wouldn't have gotten arrested though if he hadn't immediately
After pulling the gun on somebody pulled into the parking lot of a discount tire because he couldn't find the extendo clip
*laughter*
He was like, "what?"
He's like searching around the back of his car, pulling through a discount tire,
and then immediately like, cops all over him like,
"Put your fucking gun on the ground! Put the fucking gun on the ground!"
Jesus Christ dude, I couldn't believe that they sold this shit.
They did nine months in uh...
What, eight months for an airsoft gun?
Yeah, well the judge was even like,
"This is fucking weird."
Well, I don't know.
Uh...
Yeah, that's what the judge...
*arguing*
Damn, that might be the craziest possible state to be waving a fake Glock at somebody in traffic.
Which you could easily die for that.
Well also he could have just bought a real gun.
Yeah, exactly.
They're probably the same price almost.
Or you're doing a fake one, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, it was a nice hair show.
Yeah, get a...
Yeah, he did like nine months in like a county jail for that.
Jesus Christ.
Get a high tech, bro.
150 bucks.
Yeah.
And well, it'll break the first time that you pull it out at anything.
Yeah, but if you're just showing it off...
Wait, wait, wait.
That's shade man high techs high tech
$150 gun are you kidding me? No, it doesn't shoot bullets man
Fine with me man
Enough to kill myself
They make a gun called a yeet can and on the side. It says a yeet cannon. That's we're gonna get it
I need to have some kind of gun. I wanted to get it since we have an office
I wanted to get a gun and you can leave you have a guy who can conceal
But you have to transport $5,000 in cash every single month.
So I would have to take out $5,000 from our business account,
bring it here and then bring it back to the bank once a month.
That's worth it.
Is it worth it?
Yeah.
I mean, you only have to do it like once.
What the hell am I doing?
Of course I'm going to do it.
And then you get the license.
We're getting so much mileage out of this prop.
Imagine if you had like an AR-15 or a real gun.
Wait, how does that work?
Yeah, and we all just do it.
I mean, sorry, the real gun.
You have to have a reason, I guess, to transport money.
I guess they're not going to send somebody to escort you.
You have to be a handgun licensee, you have to be like ex-law enforcement.
Or exactly, you have to transport large amounts of cash.
Yeah.
Which is bullshit.
Spin the bottle.
I don't know what podcast about this.
Don't worry, it's in the Supreme Court right now.
It's going to get struck down and we're all going to be carrying this time next year.
I guess I'm going to stick with my Supreme Court.
New York City's like unconstitutional...
Facts.
...can still carry laws.
Really?
Yeah, it's in the Supreme Court right now.
They're reviewing it the New York Supreme Court is a big one the big one way and the Californian ones
The LA County ones and
The New York City ones
That's right
We're gonna be open carrying 1911s. I am wait man in the bodega, bro
Yes, sir miss
people walking around with guns all the time a really I saw some I saw a security guard at Walgreens who had a gun and
a
who would come in and he would steal COVID tests every single day.
And then they started having security guard with a gun.
Those are, they give those out for free.
That's what I was like, what the hell is he?
But he would like come in and he was just like a homeless guy.
And he sits inside of the bank all the time.
Was he selling them?
I have no idea.
I mean, maybe I would, I would think so.
It'd be crazy to take that many.
And then yeah, not sell them.
Yeah.
He's doing one a day.
He would just.
He's never seen a gun before.
He's.
No, he's never seen a fake gun before.
is
of
technically ambiguous for show.
You're from Kashmir. I mean, we literally say you're mixed and I believe you Hitler and anything is what you are. I mean, the swastika was an Indian symbol.
Exactly.
Let me have a gun.
And the DMV. Come on, just let me
it's crazy that Julio actually works for the cartel. That's not true.
He works for the cartel and any CBP officers are watching he works for
all of their videos.
I forgot, CBP don't fuck with me no more.
They stopped fucking with you.
Dude, two years ago, I got into the airport so early in the morning that they were like,
"You know what? You seem chill. Just go through. We won't even look at your passport. You're that chill."
I'm like, "Oh, thank you, man."
And I dapped him up and I just went on my way. I don't remember where I was going.
I test him around. I land at 5am, a little early.
So I'm a little worried.
But I think like, "Oh, you know what? It's so early. It's so early. They're gonna be like,
'Oh my god, it's you from the other day. I'm gonna... I fucked with you.'"
I fuck with you, just get in, I won't even look at you.
But I just get the most inquisitive, sleepy officer of all time.
She looks at my passport once and she's like, wait a minute, you're not from this country.
I'm like, yep.
You're the guy at Beer's Wee Dre.
She, yeah, they're not fans anymore, I don't think.
I think they unsubscribed from the Patreon.
They used to rock with us.
Yeah, they used to rock with us.
They no longer.
What happened?
What changed?
I think too much wokeism by the other hosts.
So they, she's looking at my passport, she sees that I have 1,000 trillion million dollars, and also I have two, what are they called, the seals, whatever, the stamps, right?
I forgot the word. And she's like, "What do you do for a job?" And I go like, "Twitch streaming?" And she's like, "Nah, L, that's an L response, dog."
And then she goes like oh, then she's like asking me about like all these questions. I like my life and everything
She gets really interesting about this one really weird trip that I took in 2018 where I spent just to one day in the country
It's like what do you spend just a one day in the country? I was like what yeah this in 2018
It says you were in the country for four hours. I was like oh for a layover. I need a one day in the country
For a layover is like oh, that's weird
Where were you going? I was like somewhere else. All right
so
Sir, uh, they they're like, you know what we set up not far. We go into the little room
They sent me to a little room where I just sit there for like half an hour cavity search
They asked me this the same thing. I thought I was gonna get there. He didn't get there
Oh a cop just like just asking like what do you do for work? Where do you live? What do you live with?
What do they do for work? Do they have like any fly benefits? I'm like, no
I pay for this with my drug money.
I mean, so I just they just made me wait and in the time I waited
there for like half an hour.
I think it was the first person that got sent there for the next
30 minutes.
They only send Chinese people.
So I think they thought I was from Hong Kong.
Straight up.
Chubio is a member of the Sinaloa cartel.
He is trafficking precursor chemicals into the United States
for
He was talking about the Sinaloa Cartel, Jubio is smuggling precursor chemicals, Twitch, Plagas
Terrorism.
It's all, that is so funny to pull a "Does your mom know you're gay?"
Yeah.
As a TSA agent.
And I was like, "Who's they?"
And she's just like, acting like she didn't ask me that.
She's like, "What are you doing in the city?
Oh, are you friends with someone?
Oh, that's cool.
Are you doing anything for Thanksgiving?"
I was like, "Yeah, I guess."
She looks at my back, she says that I'm just a nerd.
And she's like, "You know what?
Just get out of here."
Some use you didn't you fuck up your address?
They're like, oh, why are you staying and I gave him Rex's address?
I mean I gave him I had given them breakfast address beforehand like on the contact contact form
but then she asked me at the border of the
Customs and I was like, oh, yeah, I'm going to like a different address like
Wait a minute
This is this is just fucked up the story
Let's kill him you know maybe get in yeah, Oh could be this you want a slice of the pie anyways
I think slide through it next time I show up at customs. They're they will kill me, so I'm never coming back I
Need you to come back
No, I'm just gonna marry you bro straight up. I'm just gonna green card. Yeah, I'm gonna marry you you're never leaving
You're never going back to Mexico all right. Let's see what's one more sound effect. We could do hold on wait
Somebody's gonna get something amazing right now
Somebody talk everybody talk
What do you have to say to all these beautiful people you've been protecting all these years man
Home to Venmo you at all
All right, well you should all subscribe to this
This is a robot sound effect wait hold on wait, I'll find you a sound of a hold on we'll hit him with
That was damn well hit him with the record scratch with him with all the clapping yeah, we take that all day
Thank you, man. Good night everybody
Wait somebody actually subscribe
Yo, more subs!
I didn't realize that.
Oh my god.
Holy shit.