and i'm gonna play
it's better
don't forget man
this better be six months
pocketed
please students are no one of our lives
but i think it's a good thing to know that since this man i don't know what
about it
the
is
and he loves me
the
it's
are you
thing
let's not worry about it guys will be another episode of
is we drank this is the year's we're a hundred at this point
we are and
also i'm just a little bit of a studio and i'm joined by this lovely lady
uh... the bottom of the screen
you know what the the because you know i have a really good
all i'm so sorry ma'am i didn't mean to say anything out of the ordinary or rude
that is a really a lot of pocket
that is clearly that is that is my bad
and i will let you be a go first and then i will let rex the man go first
Okay, but what number episode is this?
You said?
This is two or three hundred I believe.
Ah yeah.
So, in the spirit of Sitsmas everybody, today I have gone ahead and brought on a classic
Christmas beer in Mexico.
It's called Noche Buena.
Which
See that could be not true.
We can't check you on this.
Yeah, this could be a complete lie.
- Okay, well you can Google the name of the beer.
- You probably just got a red beer.
- This is a seasonal beer.
It only comes out around the holidays
and Nacho Buena, when you translate it,
it stands for Christmas Eve.
These are really famous, people really like these.
So much so that I think for some time
they made them available year round.
But I don't know if that's still a thing
or which is like a one time deal.
Anyways, I got, I saw one, I got one, and I'm gonna drink it now.
It looks amazing, I'm not gonna lie. I like the foil top.
Yeah, I like it.
Wow, I like it!
What does it taste like?
It tastes completely like a beer.
Though it's made in Mexico.
You're kidding!
No.
And it's got 5.9% alcohol.
What's your problem, man?
Okay, that's pretty decent.
and it's I feel like it's filling me up with the Christmas spirit.
I want to give gifts to my friends.
Uh hey I'll take a gift I've never said no to one.
Guys uh my wife picked my beer again my lovely wife shout out to her for doing this this is amazing
to have this uh done for me and she picked out speaking of Christmas beers fugly sweater.
Oh that's awesome.
A dark lager brewed with ginger, cloves, nutmeg and cinnamon.
That's a Christmas beer.
I would fucking hope so. I'm gonna take a sip and report back.
Yeah, something I don't tell you about reviewing beers is that it's really hard to tell what's in them when there's no labels with the ingredients.
Just the title of the beer.
Okay, I'm gonna say this tastes like a bit of a flat Guinness.
This is like a non-nitro Guinness.
It has a lot of darkly deep flavor to it.
Not really getting any of the ginger, nutmeg or cinnamon,
maybe a little bit of the cloves.
Overall, it really just tastes like a dark beer to me.
And it's okay, I'm gonna give this a five, two,
5.2 out of 10.
- All right, now that I've taken a couple sips of this,
this is definitely a dark beer, but I actually like it.
I think you guys would also--
- That's surprising, you usually hate the--
- Yeah, I think you guys would really like these, yeah.
I want to give you a Christmas beer.
- I don't love dark beer usually.
I actually kinda, I like Guinness,
but that's mostly 'cause it kinda tastes like whipped cream.
Then you can give yourself a milk mustache.
- It is very milky and thick.
- Yeah.
I have a... hold on, hold on.
I do have a blue beard.
This is a sea quench ale.
A dogfish head sea quench ale.
And it is a lime beer.
What is this?
Oh, a lime beer!
Blissfully brewed with lime juice, lime peel, black limes, and sea salt.
Did you know that this bastard up here, between you and me, is...
Well, for me, he's right over here to stage right.
Yeah.
No, it's you.
Do you know that he thinks that a lemon and a lime are the same thing in his country?
Well, he's talking about limon.
Yeah.
That's the same thing there. Isn't that wild?
It is crazy.
It's just one word. It's limon.
No, that's not true.
It's true.
I think it's its own thing.
There's limon and then there's lima.
Lima is what you guys call lemon and lime is what we call the limon.
And why is that?
Thank you guys!
Look at how amazing my life is. Amazing life, amazing wife.
I just was hand-delivered miso soup.
So this is the kind of beer that I might be indulging in pretty soon.
Wow.
I don't think that's a beer.
Shut up!
Would you say miso hungry?
I would say me so hungry if I was a fucking racist shitbag
Which I'm not so I won't say it. We already said it. You know, I didn't
What other kind of things will you say if you were a racist shitbag
Probably the thing I just said about the lines
Yeah, anyways, what's up with this line yeah, it's yummy just tastes like
beer with lime
That's very good. That's like a solid eight
You can't make any beer worse with lime. I don't think I think even this dark beer would be a little better with some
Yeah
It's my favorite beer maybe ever is Bud Light lime. Yeah
Yeah, I wasn't I went to a new grocery store to buy beer cuz I've kind of
hit every beer they have at the
Bodega near me. Yeah, and I was like, oh so many choices
And none of them really sounded appealing.
Yeah.
It's always like this with stuff.
I was afraid that that was going to happen to me as well when I was living in my apartment,
which I've moved out of.
We'll talk about that later.
There was like this 7-Eleven near me that I used to just hit up.
And I ran so dry on options that I was considering getting the soju last time.
It was between that and I didn't find it again.
I'm running out of interesting beers in my area.
I will have to start making treks to different parts of this city, which is a bummer for
me because I hate moving my body.
Yeah, I'm the same way.
Yeah.
So, I have a thing with like, you know, theoretically, logically, it would make sense to buy a bunch
a different beer at a store once and keep them in the fridge for weeks at a time.
But that is impossible because a beer in the fridge might as well have already been drank.
That's right.
There's no way that a beer will not drink these beers that are sitting in the fridge.
Yeah.
If it's sitting there for a week between fucking recording sessions, sometimes more, you're
not going to just sit there and be like, "Oh my God, this freaking Morty beer is staring
I mean, the taste, every time I eat an egg out of the fridge,
that thing is not going to live.
You cannot have beer at your house.
I try-- the only-- I never keep alcohol in my house.
I buy alcohol, I drink it, and then I drive around my house.
Yeah.
Listen--
I do have a lot of gin right now.
I bought a big thing of gin.
New Amsterdam or what?
it's uh...
whatever noah told me to get it's like the
the botanist
can you turn down your gain a little bit?
turn down my gain?
you fucking wish you bitch ass motherfucker
you can't just drink gin on its own
you need like...
L that to my dad man
well that is true
i mean you absolutely can just drink it
but why would you do that?
well...
Well why not? Mix it with something tasty.
I'm not sure what you mean.
Well fuck you then.
I guess I'm a fucking idiot.
I'm in your camp. I think you're winning this debate.
Gin is definitely the weirdest of all of the major spirits to drink neat for sure.
Right.
It's mostly enjoyed with a tonic.
And you run out of it.
I think that's a diet tonic by the way guys.
Yeah, I should just get a big thing of tonic.
I was making gimlets for myself with bodega lime juice.
Oh wow.
And I ran out of that.
How were those?
They were delicious, obviously.
What's that, gin, lime juice, simple syrup, that's it?
Sugar, simple syrup, is that what you want to do?
That sounds pretty good to me.
Yeah, I actually think I'd like one instead of this brown beer I have.
I have yeah, I'm considering taking it as like, you know, if I'm too lazy to get beer
I'll just make them make a cocktail. Yeah, we did we did liquor that one time, but we have not cocktails
We haven't that would be interesting during season two beers. We drink season two. We might
We might actually be making some kind of smoked
infused
bourbon drink
You know what we should do also?
We should make these cocktails while we're recording.
We should record them in the kitchen.
Yeah, we would have to. We would have to do it.
That's the only way that it would make sense because I think that each of us would individually fail in unique ways at putting together a real cocktail.
This is actually really funny. When I was studying my real major, we had some sort of mixology class.
So I learned how to make...
Yeah, of course a Mexican college would have like a class about getting drunk.
Anyways...
That was math.
Yeah.
I, uh, I, I...
The one part tequila, the one part limon...
I learned how to make a bunch of drinks, uh, and then our final exam, uh, the teacher had a list...
Oh, I have to study! I'm getting to the final exam!
Our final exam was, the teacher had a list of like drinks
Wait, I'm just thinking about the fact that you had a mixology class in college
It's not fucking crazy
Dude, I went to Arizona State
It's not that crazy
I went to TV school and I didn't have a fucking class, that's stupid
Mixology, was it 101? Was there a whole program?
It makes sense with the context of the major, which I won't go into detail right now.
It's too boring.
Just working at the Rio Cancun, that's the major.
Our final attempt was, the teacher had a list of drinks, and you had to just assign a random drink, and you had to just make it in front of everybody.
And I got an 8 because I forgot to just add some ice cubes at the end.
So I just kind of fucked it up.
8 out of 100?
8 out of 10.
Oh, that's good.
Yeah, they don't have letters in Mexico.
They can't afford that.
Yeah, it was fine.
But I think I did keep the PDF, so I do have like a whole book worth of like mixed drinks
and how to make them and shit.
Oh, thank God you have that.
I don't think there's any resources online about how to make mixed drinks.
I don't know why you're coming after me for my interesting life.
I don't know why you care so much.
That is interesting.
You do have an interesting life.
Whatever, I'll just kill myself.
And if you, I mean if you want to get mad at Rex, you can ask him why he is fully Native
American today.
Why are you there?
You are the second person to say that to me.
I'm surprised I'm the second.
I would have thought it would have been 100 or 200 people.
Who was the first person?
I did walk very fast.
That must be the second person you've talked to today.
Wait, who was the first person?
My roommate who looked at me and said
"You look hella Native American today."
Yeah.
What's up with that man?
I finally brushed my hair.
So I'm trying to keep it from getting tangled again.
I think something else also changed.
Aside from that.
It's the shaving.
Right, I forgot that I did that.
mixed with the braided hair mixed with that cardigan
I just brushed my hair and it just came out like this
That's the only thing that changed
My hair has been brushed
It's also the slit
I was thinking the braids, that's why my hair is in braids
It's your whole look, basically
Right
Is this the new cardigan that you were looking for?
Yeah
This motherfucker bought a cardigan on grailed, I never heard of that
I did, I did, look at it
You ever heard of bright clothes on grailed?
is
I do see mistletoe as well.
There is mistletoe in there!
Wait, yeah, I think this is it.
There's stars.
It is! I got it and I did not expect it to be so Christmas vibes.
But as a Jewish person, I looked at it and I was like,
this is like an outdoorsy type thing.
And then I was like, wait, this is actually completely Christmas.
Are you going home for Christmas?
I am.
See? So why?
If you're so Jewish.
Uh, because...
If you're so Jewish, why have you come home?
Here's the Jewish answer. Here's the Jewish answer.
Uh, my mom has been yelling at me for the past month and a half because I have not come home all year.
Mmm.
Which...
So it's mom's fault.
Well, Jewish mothers, notoriously annoying.
Mmm, okay.
So comment, don't have me.
Right. My mom annoyed me until I agreed to come home, and flying home at Christmas kind of makes sense anyway.
Because everyone leaves during Christmas. No one's home in New York during Christmas.
Well, except for me. Little old me. In New York City, all alone.
Yeah, my wife's family's coming into town, we decided to do Christmas here this year.
It's ruining my life, that's why we're remodeling the entire house so quickly, fast.
Oh, that's fucked. I'm sorry, man.
yeah and then also i realized today though i talked to my mom about i was
like you have not got a come over christmas
that's my grandma
look a month ago knows that you have not come home a minute i'll come in january
just to see everybody but will be there for christmas
and then today ten days out from christmas
t-minus ten
i forgot to that i had not talked my dad about it yet
so tomorrow i have to call my dad one week before christmas and be like
and just so you know i forgot about you and i'm not going to
so that's going to be a really good phone call. I think what i'm going to do is
i'm going to couch it in, I was talking to cam about this
tomorrow i need to go rotate the tires on my car
which is going to take a while and i'm not going to pay some scumbag mechanic to do it
i'll just go rotate the tires on my car, i'll have to jack it up a million times, i have a spare
that i can pop between all of them
And it's gonna take a long time
But I'm gonna call my dad when I'm doing that and be like, yeah
I'm rotating my the tires on my car and he's gonna be so just
Impressed by that that I think I can kind of say anything I need to say after that
Okay, you kind of won't even hear it. I do have a story about this
So one time I was driving my car and I was going to see my dad
and
And I got a flat tire. Maybe like, on the highway.
And so I, you know, realized I had a flat tire, got off the highway, pulled into like the closest like parking lot I could find.
And I called my dad, because he was like two miles away. I was like, "Hey, you know what? I got a flat tire."
He's like, "Alright, I'll come get you. We'll get this taken care of."
And then he watched me struggle to change the tire on my car while laughing.
No, dude. This is a position...
You are a pussy.
And I'm like, I don't even know what I'm saying.
You know, it's fucking 110 degrees out.
I'm fucking dying.
I'm like, my abs hurt from like, leaning over so much.
It hurts from giggling so much.
Yeah, exactly.
My father-in-law, when I was in high school,
well before we were married,
he taught me how to
change the tire on a car.
car and it has been probably in my top 10 life skills that I've had taught to me
like no question. It was the best thing he's ever done for me because that is
such an embarrassing thing to not be able to do because especially once you
learn how to do it it's the simplest thing ever. Yeah it's not that I didn't
know how to do it it was just that I thought we would like you know go get a
tire, put it on here, yeah and no he just watched. He just kind of leaned against
this car and watched. He owned it. Yeah that stuff. Yeah. It was very funny looking back
on it but. Okay. Jubio you look fucking lovely man. Let's address that elephant in the room.
You look beautiful, the light is shining on you, and not only that, you look to be in a
new space. Guys, I have to come clean. I fully failed. I, Caleb texted us earlier today and
and he was like, "Should we do eight for a beer to drink?"
And I was like, "Sounds lovely."
And then he texted me a little before eight,
it was like streaming live. - 10.55 or so.
- And I was like, "Sorry, I'm at HEV,
"I'm getting a Christmas tree and some Christmas lights."
And guys, they had Christmas trees,
they had no Christmas lights.
And there were so many people at HEV,
we just dipped and we didn't get the tree.
you should
I'm so sorry to everybody.
Oh, and also I moved into a house.
I live in a house.
He moved into a new house, you guys.
Yeah!
I fully ditched my apartment with my crazy landlord who I still haven't heard from yet.
Still haven't heard from her.
She is probably locked herself in there, starving to death.
No food, no water.
She is dying.
Yeah!
(claps)
- Yeah!
- It's really funny, we went,
so we moved on Saturday, which was the ninth,
which is the day after rent's due,
and I don't know why I thought that my crazy landlord,
well, I thought it would make sense for her to show up
immediately the next day at my apartment and be like,
"Where's my fucking money?"
But she didn't, and we did a whole ass move
that took the entire day.
We moved all our things, we still left some things
back at the apartment.
Sunday, next day, we go back in,
we take some stuff out that we left,
and we saw our old neighbors, and we're like,
yeah, we're moving out, our landlord fucking stinks,
and the apartment kinda sucks.
But we haven't really seen her yet.
And they both, like the first floor neighbors,
were like, yeah, she is really strange,
She would just knock on your door.
She would just walk up to my neighbor's window
and just knock on it for her to let her into the building.
- She seems haunted.
- It's really funny.
It's a really crazy lady.
I was like, "Oh, that's crazy.
"Well, if she shows up, we'll just leave the key somewhere
"and she can just take 'em, I guess."
And then, we're like, "All right," so we leave.
And then we still left some stuff at the apartment
and we kind of didn't feel like going back in on Monday.
So we just left shit there until like yesterday
where I was like, you know what?
- That's the move.
- I might as well just go get the last thing,
the last stuff that we left.
So I go back in, there's no one pretty much at the building.
I grab all the things that I left.
There's nothing else at the apartment
that's not just garbage.
And I just leave the keys in like the mailbox
that's in front of the apartment.
And I was like, just text the neighbor that if she shows up,
their keys are there.
And I'm pretty much, I'm fully done with that apartment.
- You're free.
- I did steal a key to the building
because my girlfriend sent some packages there
that she needs to be retrieved.
So I do have that still.
But other than that, I'm fully free.
I'm in a new house.
You can see--
- What's the new landlord situation like?
She appears to be a teacher at the state university.
- Okay.
- She is not--
- She appears to be, but she could be some kind of sicario.
- Well, she's not 80 years old and crazy.
- Okay, well that's good.
- And I've texted her about some problems with the house
and she's been really receptive, which is really nice.
And as long as she doesn't show up knocking on my door,
yelling at me, I don't care.
As long as-- - It's a win.
- I really don't want to see any numbers anymore.
I just, I'm really enjoying how big this house is.
It's fully two floors.
It's in a fenced in neighborhood,
so if you wanna look up my address
by looking at that window, you can show up.
You can't come inside.
There's a, I'm gonna, you know,
there's a fence around this whole thing.
I would be very shocked and surprised if we had even a single person in Mexico listen
to this show.
Probably not.
Probably nobody.
I think if someone from Mexico listened to this show they would hate you.
Why?
Yeah, you sell out your people on a daily basis.
I do not.
What do you mean?
Yeah you do, by taking it from me and this fucking guy.
Yeah.
I guess so.
We roast you all day.
Why would you be drinking a modelo?
Yeah, defend your proud people? This guy hates beer?
What the hell is wrong with you?
I just don't like beer or spicy food much.
Yeah, that is literally...
Oh, what is that like, dude?
What is that? No, I know that's not fucking true.
Yeah.
I know that's not true. Yeah, this guy loves burritos and tacos.
He actually does. Listen, I like burritos and tacos.
And I like beer and I like spicy foods.
Yeah.
and I like big bottles of tequila.
I think that if I could do it all over again,
and I was given the choice that everybody's given by God,
I would choose to be born in the richest family
in all of Mexico.
- Right. - Yeah, that'd be--
- But I would choose to be born in Mexico.
- Well, it's, so something I noticed on this last trip
that I took to a really small town in Mexico,
is that I'm, you know, I wasn't really born
and like that rich of a family or anything.
But I was lucky to be born in like a nice big city
because we went down to this like small,
like middle of Mexico town.
It just sucked.
The hotel that we stayed at had to be like in a,
you know, surrounded by a fence also
because they were like,
"You shouldn't really walk out of here at night
"or whatever.
"Don't really mingle with the locals."
And we ended up--
- What's wrong with the locals?
- They were violent.
- Vampires? - In a killing way, yeah.
- Oh, killing violent people, that's good.
- And I, so we, at some point of one of the nights,
we ended up at someone's house,
and they live in this huge house,
it's just a, they had a sort of a mansion.
It was the biggest house I had seen in years,
and I was like, this house is crazy and awesome,
you still live in poop city, basically.
- Yeah, you can live in Poop City.
- I don't think I would take that trade, honestly.
- That's like the biggest house in North Carolina
that isn't this one house, it's like a historical thing
owned by somebody, some rich guy.
But the biggest private piece of property
is this giant 15-bedroom mansion,
has an 18-hole golf course, has like six pools,
all this crazy shit, and it's like $6 million.
which in new york is like one brownstone cost six billion dollars
yeah
when he was just funny because
it you try and buy property here and the biggest house anywhere else
is the same
yeah it's gonna it's it's it truly is absurd
it's not worth it
i did see i was looking like if you try to live on my fifty-seventh have
like in life
central park area
Millionaire's Row.
Yeah.
Just the like,
homeowners association fee
is like a mortgage on a two million dollar house.
Alone.
Yeah.
Not including the property, but like,
There was like one I saw for sale, it was like four hundred thousand.
I was like, "Oh, that's like a good deal."
And then it was like, "Yeah, but the homeowners is an extra five thousand a month."
And it's probably a studio.
No, it was like, decently sized. It was like a two bedroom.
Really?
I was like, "Oh, that's a good deal," but then it's like, "No, that's still $7,000 a month."
One of those big skyscrapers on the south end of Central Park has this thing where
if you become a member of it, or if you buy a unit, you have to become a member of their community thing.
And it's like a country club where you have to spend X amount of money at the restaurant,
but that amount they have to spend the restaurant every year is like fifteen
thousand dollars
that's a lot of like a half of his spend at the restaurant
that's crazy
that's so awesome dude
you go in and you just get uh...
here's what i would do medical such a nice guy
uh... i go in
i would say can i have one it cannot have seven apple
justin apple or ron apple don't even cut it
and the apple
Apple costs what? How much does an apple cost? 15, 20 bucks?
I think it's like $30.
Okay, so I pay $30 and then I tip my waiter $14,970.
I don't think that counts.
And then, the next month, I get kicked out for two reasons.
Number one, I thought that that worked and that I could stay there.
But number two, I spent all my money on this apple.
Well, I want to know what happens if you don't pay that.
'Cause like...
Surely they're just like...
What's happening?
You need $25 million for the unit.
They're not gonna kick you out.
Well, that's what I'm saying.
They'll probably just fine you or some shit.
Like, what can a homeowners association do to you?
If you don't pay them?
Dude...
In the...
In the southeast of the United States...
They can do a lot.
Like what?
What can they do?
They...
Can basically not mow your lawn.
Well, that's what I'm saying.
It's a New York City apartment.
You have--
You can get lawn.
And they can put-- sometimes as a prank,
they'll put a bunch of forks in your lawn.
It happened to my old pastor.
That's funny.
Yeah, they forked his lawn.
I think I would take--
Genev Capusta, that was his--
--a nasty forked lawn over $5,000 a month.
Literally $60,000 a year.
I think I would take--
probably most pranks.
I think I agree.
Maybe they don't wash your window.
I would let someone scare me in the elevator every time.
With like a mask.
I think a more like real scenario is that they just like fine you or like say that you're
in debt to them so like when your next payment rolls around they're like well you can pay
this but you have to like pay whatever you owe beforehand.
What I would say is I'm not even gonna pay my fucking rent if you're gonna charge me
this extra stuff.
Yeah that's ridiculous.
What can a homeowner's association actually do?
I don't know.
Yeah, well, it is a contract that you sign when you get in, so I guess they could have,
but they're not, maybe they will at a giant skyscraper, but.
Yeah, they pull up my contract and I've signed it as like Poop Williams.
Exactly, because you already paid the deposit.
They're like, I don't care what he fucking signs.
Mr. Poop, you can't.
Mr. Poop Williams, we are suing you.
Well, that's unfortunate because my name is actually Poop Johnson.
You got the wrong guy, sister.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think...
You go, you go.
I think one day I will make an excellent addition to the neighborhood watch in a very, very
medium neighborhood.
I think you pull out the...
What's their thing?
The yard?
That video you did for the yard where you were wearing the cop outfit?
You just pull that out and start walking.
Walking Phil.
He's, you know, like running at small children.
Yep.
and you're like, "Freeze!"
and
not
be like baring your teeth the hackles are up it's none of that he walks by people
sometimes and he looks at them it goes whoo and I all they always say what the
fuck and I say sorry but we're Walgreens and he did his little noise he hummed
we'll say he hummed he's saying it this woman right and the Walgreens lady says
DON'T GROWL AT PEOPLE! BEHAVE!
and I said
YO!
what the fuck did you just say to my dog you fucking bitch?
and then yeah yeah I did
and then I yeah dude and then I started throwing shit at her cans of beans
exploding on her head made her look like she had diarrhea in her hair
no I did nothing I bought a Red Bull from her
yeah I completed my transaction
I completed my transaction I didn't use the three dollars in credit that I have
of
that
dog growl at you? Exactly! It's worse because dogs don't have kind of souls
and human brains Rex but... I think people just think that a dog grumbling at someone is
just a precursor to a to a deathly attack. He's never attacked he's gotten he's
He's gotten up to people's necks but he can barely reach because he's very small.
I don't think he would bite anybody.
I am kind of waiting.
For him to attack someone?
I'm waiting until, I feel like once, he just turned two, and I feel like once he's like
three or four, either the rate or the likelihood of an attack either goes way down or way, way
up.
Right.
is
That is like it's really
The most like if you have to be a dog shit owner of a dog to have your dog attack
You have to be an actual retard
Yeah, like have a dog that attacks, you know, he has started doing though as he started we go to the park
Take him off leash. This is prime attack time, by the way, and then he starts
The train that goes right by the park. He just chases the train
I think I talked about this last week and then tonight
There were some people having maybe a first date style picnic
And these poor bastards are right in the line of where the train where he would chase the train
And so the train starts coming
He's got the ball in his mouth and I'm saying Phil Phil drop the ball
Anytime he looks at the transact leave it leave it leave it Phil Phil come here and
that he starts just
Beelining straight for these people and they jumped up and grabbed all their shit and they were like really scared that he was gonna eat them
But then he ran right past him and I had to say and I was
I was also a little bit convinced that he would eat them. So I had to be like
It's just a train. It just likes a train, which is a crazy thing to yell 45 feet away
Being a dog owner is such an embarrassing thing
public
Yeah
the
stockilling
dot killing now
uh... respect me
uh... that's exactly right now but i thought i'd be a cd skid this dude who
has
a very scary
rottweiler
mhm
and this is a dog
that is known as a killer
yet animal
this is a
orca style animal that targets humans and kills them
and i like rottweilers they have big heads
but this guy's dog
is going
*roar* slobbering his eyes when dogs get really angry their eyes turn like
completely black
and this dog is freaking the fuck out
getting so mad
baring his teeth
growling right in this guy's face like snapping at him
and this fucking guy
instead of doing what i would do
this dog this guy
jumps on the dogs back and like
holtz is paused down
and starts talking shit to it
gets like literally right up in its ears like
you're not the boss bitch
on the fucking boss you don't have a job
i have a job i make all the money and he talks like he talks like the dog
understands what he's saying
right and he and uh... all the captions are always like
uh...
these get a little crazy over here in the thomas household
but as long as everyone knows who's really in charge
we have a great time
it's like this this is not a good situation
that's uh... that's like the circus guide that got eaten by a tiger is like
one of the one of these days that those in turn around just by his head off
this sigfried and roy
yeah
i think that you got maimed
and her adly
but i do not believe he was digested
That also happened like that that uh, like the dog whisperer guy on TV
Caesar Milan. Yeah where he was like people
He just kind of got bit by a dog a million times
No, you do get just bit by a dog when you have dogs bite you
They don't as long as they don't
Bite your arm off then. I don't really care like that's the thing that kind of sucks
If a kid, if I'm walking by some fucking snot-nosed kid, and the kid decides to, literally what
every little kid does when they see Phil, if they're like under three, they immediately
try to touch his dong or his asshole.
Every single time.
The two places where you should not be touching on the dog.
And a couple of times they've touched his dick or touched his asshole, and he just goes
like, he like turns around and growls at them.
the thing is if my dog fucking bites this stupid little kid
i have to kill him
i have to electric chair kill my dog legally
or not even if they don't press charges that's the polite thing to do
unfortunately
to get them tested yeah
all of my fucking uh... all of that my dog's entire life
depends on whether or not uh... uh... two-year-old kid walking on the street
is gonna try to kick his ass
that's what it depends a gamble every single day
and if you're having a dog in new york is especially
volatile because
this is a word
well i don't
especially volatile especially volatile
the dog might blow up
the dog could have a max win
of violence of violent outbursts max win guys i'm sorry to interrupt but i do have
one more beer
which is the zero gravity
IPA and I'm guessing that I will make it probably an eighth through this because I just read that it is 9% you guys
This is bordering on wine territory, which was making me sleepy Christmas does not happen in on space
What the fuck did you just say what the fuck are you guys is not this guy's so fucked up off the Christmas beer
He can barely even think you say
Christmas is not happening on space?
Let's move on.
What the fuck? Who are you talking to?
Are you good, man?
I don't know why I said that.
*laughter*
What conversation are you having inside of your head?
I didn't want you to say those words!
Christmas is not happening on space.
*laughter*
I kinda- I think I see what you mean.
You know what? I'm turning this around.
Christmas is a fully Earth thing. It doesn't happen in space.
I agree with myself. I've just thought about it for a second.
I mean, I think, I can't say if you're true or not, or if you're right or not, because
um, what you said the first time really made no sense.
You are so fucking...
What happened?
What happened in your brain?
He moved, man. Just let him, let him live, man.
You said, you say stupid things every fucking episode like that.
I do not say...
Not out of context.
What did you say like a month ago?
That was making us laugh so fucking hard.
*laughter*
I don't remember!
Uh, uh, Julio? You seem to remember.
The poutine is a fry-based meal or something like that.
Poutine... it was some... oh fuck, what was it?
It was poutine is a something meal. God damn it, it was funny.
But, that's okay.
I think maybe potato-based? Fry-based?
I think either one of those, yeah.
Yeah.
But that makes sense. It's dumb but it makes sense in context.
This is the Christmas episode. This is coming out on Christmas.
Is it?
Santa delivered a sentence into your mouth.
Oh wait no, it comes out today. I'm stupid.
I just tricked you.
You did trick me, you fucking piece of shit.
I'm sorry.
I forgot we were completely live and it goes out right after this.
Do you think if there was like settlements on Mars, they would still have Santa?
the
well obviously if you're on mars is no god
you can't get that would be a good set and you can be very few christians so
it
because there's almost zero mention of mars in the bible
yeah i think that anyway dot create mars on the pocket of those lakes well day
theoretical expressive amounts i think
There's no way where people just don't go crazy after like a couple years
After a year. Yeah, I mean of course i'm meant to be on mars man
And also that they would fuck up the fucking oxygen levels ever so slightly where it would give people awful brain damage
Listen that I know i'm being scouted by tons of different companies. Listen to me and listen to me now
I'm not going to mars. I will not repopulate mars or populate it for the first time
Yeah, I'm being reached out to by thousands of fucking companies that want to send me to be the atom
Uh of the new mars settlement. I'm not gonna do it. Yeah. Well, they don't know how hair would react to living on mars
so they need to know that
Everyone is going to be perfectly spheroid bald. It's actually not true, man
It's you know, you know what the truth is
What's the truth?
They picked aubrey plaza to be the eve and I was the only person that she would go with
That's right. Aubrey Plaza.
Aubrey Plaza. 41 year old Aubrey Plaza and me.
Populating Mars all by ourselves.
100 year old Aubrey Plaza.
Having sex together.
Then we have kids. The kids have sex.
We're going old school.
Those kids have sex with each other.
On and on and on and on and on.
That is the beautiful miracle of life.
As told in the Bible.
I feel like the Bible doesn't get enough shit for that.
I think it just isn't a big deal.
the
you
It's not a big deal.
It's not a big deal until you do like nine times that.
And then-
What about those fucking guys that that guy made that video about?
Where the guy just goes, "Duh!"
You seen that?
No.
You haven't seen that?
The most inbred family in America?
Oh, no.
You have to watch this video.
This is the best video ever because I really like these people.
I think that I- not even making fun of them, I think that they are good people.
And the guy says-
content that you like to watch on YouTube but I don't really watch that.
Let's take a step back for a minute. The first guy to engage in that like
incestuous you know the most inbred family incest family, was he a very smart
guy? Yes he knew that his spawn would one day be YouTube stars. Right. Well then I
I don't really see a problem with it.
I wonder how that works.
Which one of them gets to get the welfare?
I think probably I
That is the honestly I would if they had a patreon where they had a podcast and they just went
Each other I would I would subscribe to that they could make a lot of money off me. I
Would pay 10 bucks a month
I'd be the one tier above the base tier to listen to that so that I can get video of it
So you get the D&D episodes?
I get the-
*laughter*
Get the D&D episodes!
The D&D episodes, they roll a one-sided die.
I would listen to that.
They're doing coin flips on everything.
But yeah, I'm gonna have to disagree with you there, Rex.
I do think that inbreeding and incest is pretty bad.
It's not bad until you do it like four times.
I think it's just a thing that the Bible just makes you assume that happened a long time ago,
but at some point it got phased out of the...
I think my wife found out a couple years ago that her great-great-grandparents were first cousins.
It's just that it's not that big of a deal, man.
People do that shit.
I just wouldn't want to fuck my fucking cousin, man.
Yeah, of course. That's nasty.
She's ugly.
Yeah, but she's hot.
But you have to do it.
Maybe if I had to do it I probably if I had to do anything. I would I've said that before
If I had to do anything I would do it if I absolutely had to have to walk two blocks to buy a beer
Would you do that?
You know I did last night man
I knew because he was rolling around 11 p.m. I knew that time was ticking down man
We're trying to get one more game of Valoran in okay, and I
I saw my opportunity.
Mike had to go piss or something for a minute.
So I did my duty and I walked out.
I told my wife I'm going to go grab a beer real quick.
She said, "Okay, don't play another game.
I'm trying to go to bed soon."
I said, "Don't even worry about it.
I got you."
I opened my front door.
I basically fall down the stairs, sprint two blocks.
I get a beer, a two block away beer, I got this beer in under three minutes.
Which was an amazing feat.
That's really impressive.
I, uh, during a TFT game, I suddenly had the urge to poop.
And I waited at, basically, I took a poop, wiped, washed my hands, came back to my desk
in one round.
Wow!
I'm gonna say this is this is impressive, but I don't think it's it's that comparable to kill thing because
Tfd is a game that you can just if you're playing on the computer
You can just get your phone and you can just play it could have played it on your phone
Yeah, you could have played it on your phone
It that seems like a big oversight for you one second it will take less than around to do to install it and login
Well, I didn't I realized that while I was on the toilet, but I was thinking more about
pooping as fast as possible and
Playing my ass with water wiping washing my hands and running back
Do you have a bidet on every single toilet in your apartment at this point?
There is two toilets and I only use one of them. There's no toilet in the whole apartment
Well, there's three but there's two that are really usable. There's one in the basement. That's just a
I feel like two two if it for a three-bedroom two toilets is completely normal. Yeah
apartment what yeah how we never know how insane Rex's apartment is I know that
nobody lives on the bottom floor which is very odd to me
no someone does live on the bottom floor oh I thought all of you were upstairs
mm-hmm why do you have six bedrooms that's a really really tiny oh wait
this is an office right right yeah okay now I remember and every room is the
same size as this basically. Yeah it's like I mean you can't see the whole room
in my webcam. It's really funny how. There's one wall, there's one wall,
there's the other, there's the back wall, my desk is up against the wall, it's
literally a cube. Yeah. It's not very comfortable. It's really funny to me how
Rex leveled up from living and sleeping in a hallway for a year and
And now he just lives in an apartment that's entirely a hallway.
[laughter]
That is a level up. You did live in a hallway.
You lived in a hallway of a castle, which was a very odd combination.
It was. The place was awesome.
I kind of miss it, but not really.
Fond memories of the doorbell, for sure.
The doorbell, the view of the water, nothing else.
You always oversell this view.
I thought it was a great view.
I would say that the view was nice.
It was a window where you could see between two buildings this much water.
That is enough water. I'm sorry, how much water can you see from your window?
Zero! But I don't claim to have a view, piece of shit asshole!
Wait, well you've been stuck in this prison for what, like five years now?
I've been in this apartment for three and a half years, yeah.
years. Yeah. So at this point you're like the sensitize of what people like to look at
out of their windows because you look out your window, you see a naked guy.
I like looking at my parking lot. I like the parking lot. If you want to look at water,
buddy, nobody's going to stop you from going to the bathtub and putting your head underwater
until you can't fucking think anymore. Go ahead. If you need to relax so bad.
Do you have a bathtub? You have a bathtub, right? I kind of forgot. I just remembered
that I- I do have a bathtub.
No, I was talking Rex I guess I took I remember taking a shower there and almost flipping like every single time
Yeah, I almost slip every time I take a shower
I am a bat. I take a bath almost every single day you guys
This is how I decompress at the end of my very long days
You have a really, you know long schedule with a lot of things on it
Recently, it's true. I
Go in the bathtub at the end of the day and I watch my balls float up to the surface of the water and this is
Literally the most meditative thing imaginable
You have not lived until you've seen the buoyancy of your own balls. That is true. And they are buoyant
There's air in there man. Yeah, somebody's got to get to the bottom of this. Why are my balls floating up?
You should just inflate them. Yeah, I do inflate them with helium
and
We keep drowning us!
No, I don't drown them. I suffocate them in a shirt.
In a shirt?
Completely normal.
Yeah. Yeah, I suffocate my jizz in a shirt.
Ah, I see.
Well, it's already dirty, I would hope.
Yeah, of course it's dirty. I already used it to jizz into like 45 times.
Hey, this is a shirt you wear every day?
I wore it to the gym one time on accident.
*laughs*
Oh, dude, come on.
What?
You're lying right now. You did not wear the cum shirt to the gym.
Not THE cum shirt. A cum shirt.
Well, why aren't you only using one shirt?
I'm not, dude. I have a whole rotation.
Why? Use one shirt.
Use- oh, that'd be disgusting. It'd get so covered in jizz.
*laughs*
What man?
Are you guys being so fucking weird at this?
You've had an entire cum class in?
Yeah, I fucking, I open my door, I shoot one into the pocket, I'm still a guy who wears
t-shirts with pockets on the front, I shoot one into the pocket and then I fucking go
to the bathroom and take a shit.
Do that every morning.
Morning shit, a little coffee, jizz in the shirt, go take a shit.
Is it like a shoot or is it like a kind of like an empty into type deal?
Are you saying does it have enough, I would say that my cum is very low PSI.
I would say that it almost comes out kind of like lava flow.
Right.
It just yeah, just kind of dribbling pieces of debris flying.
Yeah.
So the third is like, you know, like an inch away, you would say.
are you cutting a wedding of celery?
I probably couldn't make it an inch.
I'm just holding it over it.
At sort of an angle.
So that it kind of fills in.
Kind of like you're tapping sap from a maple tree.
I don't want to get too personal here, but how long is the rotation?
Of Jizz shirts?
Yeah.
I mean, let's see how many shirts do I have.
You don't jizz on every shirt do you have?
Guys, I was lying.
the
Does he use any paper?
Like, yeah, use a paper product. That's what it's for.
No, it's not! They're abrasive!
My shirts are amazing! Millions of cotton count thread counts.
Those are very comfortable on the skin.
Get some wipe...Jizz Wipes? They sell those?
A border wet wipe will do the trick.
The fragrance inflames my hand!
The what? What, the cum doesn't?
No, my cum is amazingly unfragrant. It's completely clear.
I have refused to believe that your cum isn't radioactive.
What do you mean?
I think if you left it on your skin it would fucking burn you alive.
You think I have corrosive caustic cum?
Yeah, I think most people do.
Yeah, yeah I think that's not too far off.
Because it's so fully saturated with sperm.
Well you don't drink any water.
I drink, I would say I drink more water than anybody I know and it's not even close.
How much water do you drink?
I probably drink at least a gallon and a half of water every single day.
That is a straight up lie.
You have no idea, you have no fucking idea.
I probably pee 20 times a day.
I mean I do that too, but that's not.
But you drink energy drinks.
I drink a crazy amount of water.
And I drink, you know, one of these.
A hydroflask.
one
the
and I drank about 16 ounces of water,
just chugged it two separate times.
- That's why you need a hydro,
so you don't have to get up.
- But I still have to, I still wake up though,
'cause I'm so thirsty.
- Yeah, but waking up's not a problem,
getting up is a problem.
(laughing)
- Waking up is a problem.
- I still wake up though, is the situation.
- I still wake up, I don't wanna wake up.
You can just, in the middle of the night,
go drink water.
- Yeah, but waking up in the middle of the night,
turning over, drinking a little bit,
going back to sleep, that's easy.
But I also, I cannot drink a little bit of water.
I cannot drink a sip of water.
I can only ever chug a glass of water.
So if I had a Hydro Flask, I would be drinking,
I'd be drinking 32 ounces of water
every single time I drink water, instantly.
I only ever chug water, I'm not kidding.
When I go to a, every waiter hates me
because I go to restaurants, they fill up my water glass
and then before they've left the table,
they fill up the last person's glass
and I already need a refill
because I just chug the entire thing in one sip.
Okay, get up and go get a glass of water and chug it in front of us right now.
Okay.
The gauntlet has been thrown down.
I hate him so much, he's just lying about everything in his life right now.
I come in a t-shirt, I drink a gallon and a half of water.
I can't see every single t-shirt.
I'm sorry, first of all, if you drank that much water, your cum would be shooting because it is so light.
I know he can hear us right now, but I was thinking just now over the past like five minutes or
so that I would love to gift him a hydro flask as a Christmas present.
Okay, of course I was lying about the cum shirt.
I already said that you retard.
The water thing is completely true.
I'm sorry I'm doing a comedy podcast, not a fucking Native American research podcast.
I can't even drink this water.
No, this is void.
I can't tell how much water there is in the fucking rec...
This is so stupid.
This is so dumb.
It's literally falling down his throat.
I can't see how much water there is in there, man.
Okay, this is probably 24 ounces of water.
We did not drink that entire thing.
Literally filled it to the top and drank it right now.
Why didn't you show that before you did that?
You don't believe me?
No!
Why would you not believe me?
That's like no water.
Because you literally...
*gurgling*
Like you're a fucking-
I'm fucking chugged it, are you fucking brain dead?
*laughing*
Have you never seen any-
This is the biggest glass of water I own.
I go to the sink everyday and I drink this probably ten times.
You drank that like you're a Fortnite character drinking a chug jug.
Yeah, that's what I'm telling you Rex, is that I drink fast!
*laughing*
I swear on my mother's life, I filled this all the way to the top.
right to where the thread starts we can't do you have to run it back
because that's a crazy thing to not believe as soon as I watch the replay
watch the replay as soon as I tipped it over here water started coming out you
can see it dribble down the side of my mouth I'm full
it's alright you drink a lot I got a water anyway you know what I actually
don't need to because I don't need to prove anything to you - if you don't want
to believe me that's on you but I want you to know of course I lied about the
cum shirt thing I was being funny the water thing is completely true a hundred
percent true realize realize realize that's very good again you know comedy
Podcast you got to be funny. That was very very funny Rex. You have the water hoodie as well. Wait, but he's
Ready, I have a water
It's the truth man, I've changed my
It's the fucking truth. I drink an absurd amount of water. That's why I have that's why I don't like
drinking beer at
restaurants because it's cheap
Right, and I will have and I never drink soda at restaurants because if I get a soda at a restaurant
I will have five sodas by the time I leave because I just chug every single thing that comes in front of my face
You know what? I do I don't take that in an odd manner. I do lemonade
lemonade
Places lemonade is a thousand calories of lemonade if I was drinking lemonade at a restaurant
I'll just look down asses and I'm I'm good
Can't do rather have a thousand glasses of beer thousand calories of beer
Exactly. I'm gonna do a thousand calories. I'll do it on beer every time and now I'm gonna have this miso soup
Thank you guys for joining us yeah for another episode water we drink I'm your host I'm your host I'm your water man
Caleb pits I
Drink 150 of these every single day swear to God
Please join us next week
dude
We may come back for a gamma session because we need to change something
Really change
We've been in a bad sorts. We have lost
$750 in the last two days. I wouldn't even say loss. I'd say we reversed one them
Yes, wait, we're you know hot streak like yes
$850 there is now a hundred dollars left
No doubt and the only thing that paid with the last $20 was
You know what that means you have to do one one thing just one bite and you back up big one
All right, goodbye beer drink