[Sipping]
[Burp]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer broadcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[Burp]
This is a journey into sea,
into the land,
planet,
♪ I'm a fool ribbon ♪
- Beers we drank, motherfucker,
with Jubio, Caleb, and Rex.
- Beer.
- And we're back.
- Good things come to those who wait.
I'll say that much.
- Oh, it's a spinner.
I just fucked this up so bad.
- This is good.
- Today, I'm rocking with a June Shine hard kombucha, guys.
This is the Grapefruit Paloma.
I've had many of the other flavors on this.
This is a go-to for me.
And here's why, guys.
I get, when I drink beer, even just one beer,
I get some of the most heinous, cartoonishly bad diarrhea
that anybody has ever had.
Like, literally go into the bathroom,
I mean, maybe 10 seconds on the toilet
and my entire house smells like diarrhea
because of the strength of the,
like the potency of what's coming out of my body
just from drinking like one Bud Light.
So every week is a struggle for me.
And this week, this episode, man, I just, I couldn't do it.
So I did something that's good, good for the gut,
good for the microbiome, a lot of bacteria in here.
So cheers, man.
This is a, this is like a seven, two out of 10
and maybe a six foot six basketball player.
like a healthy beer.
You know, a beer that's good for you.
We need a beer that is medicine.
- This is kind of medicine.
Yeah, oh, that's a good,
a beer that has maybe like Tylenol in it.
- Yeah. - You can't get hung over.
- That'd be a good idea.
- That's a great idea. - That's a great idea.
You wanna go next, Rex?
- Sure.
I have a delicious Margarita Gose
from Cigar City Brewing.
- Oh, nice. - So this is an ale
brewed with orange, lime and salt.
Oh, okay.
And it is very tart and salty
and honestly quite good.
Low on alcohol content though, it's like 4%.
Yeah, that's good.
But I would say, what's that?
No, keep going, keep going.
I'll hold my question.
This is like a 7.5 out of 10.
I really like this, I could drink this any day of the week.
And this is maybe like a 6.8 on the basketball scale.
- Something I hadn't really,
I guess I kind of had brought this up
I think last week or two weeks ago.
But do you feel like the beer scene
at your new residence has changed radically
from your last residence?
Because if we can all recall,
every time you were just like,
I'm just gonna run out for a beer.
When I think of what I'm going to run out for a beer,
I think I'm going to hit the 7-Eleven or the OXO,
which is a Mexican 7-Eleven.
And I'll get, and there's only like,
there's like, Amstel, there's Michelob,
there's like, you know, really regular beers.
But he would just come back
with like the most cartoonish SpongeBob, Patrick.
- You always came back with like-
- Santa Chicks.
- And they had that kind of like cheap can.
It's clear that it was like a small amount of cans.
wasn't mass-produced. Yeah, but it was also like the most insane beards I've ever
seen in my entire life. And now you're living in New York, Brooklyn,
and now you're getting, you know, India Paleo, gay butt, grapefruit,
actually grapefruit is mine. Do you think that the scene has radically changed with
your move? So I was fortunate living where I did before where like you know 200
feet away was a liquor store that had a weird beer section. They had like a
craft beer kind of like freezer you know you could walk into. Yeah there's not as
many of that of those here you kind of have to like go to a like a brewery and
and buy the beers there to get that kind of thing.
- Yeah, so it's like, that's not as easy
to find where I am at.
- Right.
- Like it's like, you're limited by what's
in a grocery store.
- Or I was gonna say, that one time
that we did the live action Boots We Drink,
we went to that one grocery store by Caleb's
and it was just, he had really crazy beers.
They had like a really big selection.
so much so that it was a little overwhelming.
But none SpongeBob themed.
No, you don't get the funny beers that are called like stink bomb and shit.
Stink bomb, triple IPA, fart bomb, poop beer.
There is gay beer. Have you guys ever had gay beer?
No.
It's a good beer.
What do they make gay beer?
Yeah, probably in your butt.
*laughter*
It's called gay beer man.
Gay beer golden lager.
Right now, before you go straight for gay beer,
before you go straight for gay beer,
verify you are over 21.
Yes I'm 21 bro.
He's not, he's lying.
Yeah, it's a good thing they don't verify you being straight.
These guys don't seem that gay in the promotional photos.
Just two best buds chillin' with ascots on.
How's this?
I'm not gay.
on. How's this gay at all?
Morning Brooklyn. Okay, it is a Brooklyn.
I want to go ahead and take a look at my beer. This week, I
didn't really notice, I didn't really read what any of this
said until just now. But it is it is a Stiegel Rattler. It's a
grapefruit beer. And it completely looks like a like a
soda. It looks like a Sprite.
- Wait, all of us have gone with a fruity note this week.
- It is really good.
It does taste like a soda. - Kind of shaved-y vibes.
This is, you might, have you ever had a June Shine, Julio?
- No, I have never.
- You might like these.
They're like-- - I've never had a kombucha.
- Never had a kombucha? - Nope.
- Man, I drink a lot of kombucha.
It's probably one of my favorite.
- I'm very straightforward with what I drink.
I don't even like mineral water.
- Mineral water?
- Yeah, I don't like it much.
I can't tell the difference between any waters.
How do you tell? What's the difference?
It tastes weird for me.
Mm. So you don't like minerals, then?
Yeah, I kind of water.
I kind of hate mineral water. Yeah.
Minerals. Do you drink soda?
Don't drink soda.
What's your best?
What's your number one beverage?
Like if we if we looked at the after water
or maybe before water, if we looked at
If I'm at a restaurant that I've never been to or I go to often, most likely I would probably
just ask for like a lemonade.
Lemonade, hmm.
And at home I would just do like a sweet tea or just like anything with water.
Anything with water?
Yeah.
Maybe like some minerals with water.
No, no minerals.
streets and tasties no disgusting rocks in my shit. Do you put chamoy in your water?
You ever done that? That is so so disgusting to my ears. I can't even parse I can't I can't
even look at you right now. You should put chamoy on your beer. Guys we're so weird.
Yeah chamoy is good on like I would imagine something more normal not so much like a like
a tasty taster. Well I like even more than chamoy on the rim I like those that really really
thick kind of chamoy that they put sometimes on like beers.
If you get like a like I had like a mango cart.
I think they're called chamoy at us.
A chamoy at a oh my God, it was so good.
You guys just stuff on it to my girlfriend.
Just loves telling me over and over.
She loves beating my head with with the fact that she keeps telling me
that you guys will just absolutely love Mexico City.
I would love that.
We're going to take him to the Pee and Poo Mart,
where you can just walk the street and you'll get the most insane drinks of all time.
It's called the Pee and Poo Mart?
Something like that.
Some Mexican-Spanish shit.
Yeah, it's like a lost in translation type of thing.
I see.
Anyways, speaking of Mexico.
That is why we are late this week.
We were celebrating Hispanic Heritage Month,
And Caleb and Rex have both prepared a poem to read to me for my heritage.
Yes I have, hold on.
Yep, here we go man.
We're almost just loading up my award winning poem.
Rex has a brand new look.
I accidentally completely shaved off all my facial hair three days ago.
It was a complete accident. How did you do that by accident?
I was in a rush and I accidentally gave myself a complete uneven Hitler stache
and just said I need to just fully get rid of it all.
Well, here's what I have to say about the beautiful nation of Mexico, the eagle and the snake.
This is a little poem by me called "The Woman from Mexico".
Okay.
There was a woman from Mexico who ate too much hot salsa in her burrito.
It colored her tresses flaming red and gave her too much energy, she said.
Now all she wants to do is the Fandango.
Whoa.
Yeah.
So Fandango...
I don't know what Fandango is.
It's a movie. You buy movie tickets on it.
So she's probably going to go see...
That was like a game, no?
That was like a game, a really boring game.
Fandango is a movie ticket website.
So this lady...
She drank too much sauce and she wanted to go to the movies.
And a burrito and it made her so hot that she had to go see a movie.
Because, oh, you know why?
Because a movie theater is always cold.
That's true.
Even in the middle of the summer, I'm bringing a hoodie to the movie theater, y'all.
True.
I like sitting in there.
Cozyed up.
That is a...
It was so crazy going to Texas.
I don't know if I talked about this.
But it was so awesomely cold
anywhere that was indoors.
And as soon as you stepped outside
you were like, "Oh, I am in hell."
But heaven is just...
You know, I just gotta park my car
in this awesome huge parking lot
and then just step right into heaven.
That's why everybody loves malls in the south.
in the south.
Because in the south it gets so hot in the summers.
They're more like forums rather than malls.
Yeah.
The little things where it's like the strip mall thing where it's just like different
stores and every one of them just look the same, every single one.
I have to go back to North Carolina this month because my brother got a speeding ticket in
a car that I thought I transferred the title to my stepdad but I guess I didn't.
So I have a court appearance at the end of the month in North Carolina.
So I have to like fly down to North Carolina and be like, I have to like transfer the title
and go to the DMV and say, "That ain't my car, dawg.
That's my bro's car."
But it's okay, I'm just gonna...
That's scary.
Well, it's not that scary.
It's just like annoying.
I'm typing a poem.
Let him write it.
Something similar happened to me recently.
My sister, she's just using a car that's sold to my name.
Because I sold it to my dad.
And she got in an accident and all the insurance stuff is still technically under my name.
So I got an email like, "Oh, you rented this car."
And I was like, I thought I was getting my identity stolen.
But then I was like, "Oh, no. It's just a car thing."
Oh, yeah.
That shit just scares me. I don't want to be known by the government.
Yeah, my mom is really pushing me to come down there.
But I guess technically I could just get it notarized
Of like oh, yeah, I don't own this car anymore. But here's why my here's how women and mom specifically are so tricky
She's saying oh you got to go to you have to come home and you need to
You need to switch this car title out and shit and specifically like the the court dates at like on the 5th of October
So you just should come like probably between September 30th and like October 7th like that'd be right
And I'm yeah. Yeah, sure and she's like, oh and now that I'm thinking about it
While you're in town, you could help me move into the new house. I'm moving into no
And so now I'm thinking
Doesn't even exist maybe there is no court date
Maybe my lying bitch mom is just trying to get me trying to not hire a mover
And she's trying to get me down there because she knows that I'm as strong as an ox
But that I screamed at her when she said that I was like you have to be fucking kidding me
This is so fucked up to make you do three of the worst things that a human has to do
DV
Yeah fly and hang out with your mom and also moving the for
Everything about it is terrible. Everything about it is actually like, this is one of the worst things.
That's like, that's literally the devil's whisper.
It's terrible.
You should take care of this task at the DMV and then spend the rest of the time with your mom.
Helping your, not just with your mom, helping her move.
And you know that I'm gonna get all the heavy stuff.
And you're gonna be pissed and then you're not gonna be able to yell at her.
gonna be like I'll pay you in pizza. Bitch I can buy my own pizza. Shut the fuck up.
I'm a rich and successful podcaster. I'm from New York City bitch. We're gonna pizza up
the ass. What do I need North Carolina ass pizza for? Here's the worst part dude. She
was like, she was like and I'll cover your flight. Up to $100. Up to $100? Bitch you
You got me on JetBlue!
That's what I'm saying, dude.
You got me on Spirit!
Hell no!
You have to make something up.
I'm about to have to pay to go help my fucking mom move.
Oh my god.
She thought that she was like...
You have to make something up.
She thought she was so slick.
You cannot go through with this.
This is so fucked up.
She was like, "Yeah, my flight up to $100..."
I check all the flights, $300, $400.
I'm paying to go...
I paid $300 because my brother got in an accident so that I can go help my mom move and eat
some batty Chick-fil-A that she orders at six in the morning
and then I wake up at noon
and it's been sitting on the counter for six hours.
- She doesn't even put it in the fridge.
- She doesn't.
- She doesn't even have an air fryer.
They don't have that technology.
- She does have actually an air fryer.
She has the same model as me.
'Cause she got it for me.
She bought five of them at Costco
in a five for two deal or something.
- That should not be a package they sell at Costco.
- That is a crazy package.
It was like a, it's like a Christmas.
It's like, if you just need one gift for a bunch of people.
- Yeah.
- Rex has like told us like pretty evil stuff,
pretty much evil stories about him and his parents,
his mom being the devil or whatever.
This is legitimately the worst thing
I've heard someone's parents do to them.
- Yeah, that is really bad.
- They threw Rex in a dungeon for a year
and it made him stronger and now here he is.
- This is the kind of shit that my mom does all the time.
I remember when I was like--
- Can you pull up the mic to like close to your face?
- When I was like 14 and my brother,
my younger brother was like 12,
I remember I got in huge trouble
because I had to write a paper
and I basically copied and pasted it
from like an article I found.
And my mom found out.
So she confronted me and I admitted to it.
I was like, yep, I stole it all.
She said, you're grounded for three months.
She said three months.
And then my brother walked down the stairs
and he had greasy hair.
And my mom said, when's the last time you took a shower?
And he said, I don't remember.
And she said, you are also grounded for three months.
She grounded both of us for three months,
me because I plagiarized an entire paper
and him because he could not remember the last time he showered.
(laughter)
Dude, I got into the stupidest fucking Jewish argument with my mom
and it pissed me off so bad.
What are we going to make the weather today?
Yeah, exactly.
So, like, when the movers were here moving my stuff in,
there was like a cool guy from like Brooklyn that was like moving my stuff.
and we were talking and like sometimes when I talk to someone with like a
really heavy Brooklyn accent, I'll like kind of slip into like having that
accent. Yeah. I've seen you do this. Mm-hmm. It's a code switch. He was like, "Oh, like are you like from
here?" Because my accent was so accurate and good and I was like, "No." When I was
growing up, when my mom would get angry at me, she would yell at me and when she
yells at me she loses the ability to talk with her normal accent from Brooklyn
yeah she just yells at me in a Brooklyn accent and she yelled at me all the time
because I was a naughty boy growing up and so I you know after taught like I
called her for a reason and then she talked about herself for an hour and
then for whatever whatever came over me in that moment I decided to tell that
story to her. She was like, "I didn't yell at you when you were growing up."
I was like, "Of course you did." "They just do that when they fly."
I was like, "Yeah, you did. And it's fine. I probably deserved it." She's like, "No, when you were
like four or six years old, I never yelled at you." And I was like, "It's so
obvious what I meant by when I was growing up." "When you were a single day old, I wasn't
I'm yelling at you.
- And she was like, "Well, that's not what you said."
And I'm like, "To anyone I've ever said that to,
they completely understand what I mean by that."
- Yeah.
- But she was like, she argued with me
for 30 minutes about that.
(laughing)
- Dude, I've had this argument with my mom
probably every single Christmas.
Me and my brothers gang up on her
and then she starts crying and runs away.
(laughing)
- I wish I could make my mom cry.
I would feel bad, she's so stupid and pitiful.
- Yeah, my mom's gonna have my mom's.
It's pretty easy to punch that ticket with my mom though.
- The problem here is that Caleb has a gang.
He's a gang of brothers.
- That is true.
- It's just me versus the world.
- You're just a lone soldier, yeah.
You need us to come with you.
We'll just go over there.
- Yeah, you yelled at us too.
I remember you yelled at me, mom.
- Yeah, mom.
- Fucking bitch.
- No, but it will always be like me and my brothers
just sitting around laughing about something
from our childhood and then we'll be like,
oh yeah, and then mom got mad and my, or, or, or even like,
yeah, I remember mom cried and then my mom will walk in.
(laughing)
I didn't cry.
And then run away crying and lock herself in her room.
(laughing)
It's really awesome.
- That is fucking sick as fuck.
- You know, she's going through a lot.
She's, she's in her seventies or eighties or nineties
by now.
- She's moving.
- Yeah, who knows how fucking old that bitch is.
- She's trying to, she's trying to scam me.
So there's a lot going on.
Yeah, the eye.
Can I say my poem?
I would love to.
Okay, why do you lose clues?
Steve towel?
That is a that's a that's a robe dude.
It's just oh my God.
It's a full Steve.
It is a full Steve.
All right, don't I wrote this in three minutes.
So you can't get mad about it.
I would never get mad at it.
So this is this is about Mexican heritage.
Mm-hmm.
There sat a man eating a mango and he saw a woman doing the tango.
That's Spanish.
He would have been hot.
Unfortunately, she was not.
Wow.
Oh.
She just had her quinceanera and her face was covered in red sauce
like marinara and also she was fat.
And she's 15.
(laughing)
- She's the fat 15 year old,
and she's being ogled by this Mexican man in a mango.
- Get mad at me, I told you I wrote it.
(laughing)
- Well, I have one about,
I have actually a Mexican poem as well.
- What the fuck is that?
- Here's my newer poem.
- Okay.
It's called "Trumpty Dumpty Built a Great Wall"
In my once great country, borderless criminals roam
Welcome to America, now go the fuck home
Two Bushes and Obama did nothing at all
Let's use our Trump card to build a great wall
Who will build this great wall?
Oh that's a no brainer
Thousands fill our jails with INS detainers
Heroin pot and cocaine arrive in bricks
Instead, let's have them throw mud in the mix.
Shady leftover cops from the failed war on drugs
reassigned to the border to supervise
these wall-building thugs.
America's being invaded.
Oh, wait.
America being invaded, we're under attack.
Illegal immigrants, a monkey on Statue of Liberty's back.
The Mexican side will be one big easel
for illegal gang members spray painting weasels.
to
the
Wait, what?
By making illegal immigrants enemies of the state.
Right.
So, that was my other poem that I wrote.
Is the "learn to masturbate because Mexicans have a hundred kids" is that the bit there?
Wait, I'm looking through this guy's poems.
This is Joe in the Box.
I don't know if we did this guy when we did our Poetry episode, but almost all of his things
Is there the cartel on the boat disabling
m'lady colorblindness?
What?
Malady.
Poets lives-- oh, you're right.
Poets lives matter.
Oh my god.
That kind of sounds awesome.
Podcasters lives matter.
Coronavirus, parentheses scary.
I guess I've never given the thought,
but I guess they were completely exist racist poets
in these times.
- Even in these perfectly woke times?
- Yeah.
I would think that poem was like,
just like such an inherently female coded,
woke coded type of thing.
- And you don't think that women can be racist.
- Yup.
- The students never met a fricking white woman.
- Yeah, a Karen.
- Yeah, I met a Karen.
- Name one Karen you met.
Name a name.
- Wait, hang on, I got something to say about Karens.
- Pop off.
- Listen up Karens.
Actually, listen up the world.
- Okay.
- I think we are over labeling people as Karens.
I think not every person having a meltdown is a Karen
and not every meltdown must be recorded.
- I think almost no meltdowns should be recorded
in all honesty.
It's usually recording somebody having a really awful moment.
that you're saying that because that is the now consensus take on that.
What?
That like, oh, they're just having a bad day.
Well, I'm not sitting down on a.
I mean, no, I'm not.
You are a mean Internet guy, though.
No, I don't.
You have a different brain than me and Juvia.
Yeah, I don't.
I don't think.
I don't have a lot of misery in a way that I don't find myself capable of.
OK, I don't enjoy their misery.
I never have.
You have.
There was a moment where people were anti-Karen and then there was a Karen revamption arc.
It all is from the video of the lady where she's just recording her and she like crouches down and
tries to like hide and like disappear. That is like this lady seriously has something very very
wrong with her. Yeah it has come around. But hey man. No one is is like oh yeah. The first Karen
and
was having it some kind of BPD powered break.
- Yup.
- Some synapse in his brain was not firing
in the right order and he just flipped through
the dictionary in his brain and just put his finger
on a random word and it was unlucky.
But it was a Karen video essentially
and therefore I'm against that video.
- Well I think that the Karen videos like
kinda came and went with COVID,
like all the COVID trends as well.
Because people pretended to care about the well-being of their employees.
Now I feel like search Karen videos from this week,
a lot of them are just people being insane at Walmart
and then the Chinese AI cotton farm generated voice,
like, this male racist Karen at Walmart
wouldn't let this man buy his items.
And then the video plays and it's just the guy being like,
I want to buy essentially like a thousand of this one item at the at the fucking at the fucking checkout of the self checkout when it's you can't do that.
And the guy's like, no, I can't leave.
You can buy a thousand paper plates at the self checkout.
It's not a problem.
It is a thousand bigger things that you are.
OK, you are being a Karen now.
You are being a Karen.
You're being an actual Karen.
I'm going to do a 360 degree turn and you're Karen now.
First of all, I have never complained about anything, ever.
Because I'm overly self-conscious about stereotypes.
And you bow to any sushi place that you've ever come across.
Overly self-conscious about stereotypes.
Full waist bow at the bowling alley because the guy's Filipino.
That's very funny you guys. I'm talking about one specific set of stereotypes.
Is that why you like gambling? Because you're the one Jewish guy who enjoys throwing his money away?
You don't even like it. It pains you so much, but you get this amazing rush of feeling like
you're not Jewish for one second. Have you ever seen how excited I get when I get the little
the rake back and it's like three pennies.
And I'm like, "Ooh!"
(laughing)
- That's when you get the cut of that,
the promotional cut of the house edge.
That is when it slips through for one second.
The veil is just lifted.
- Oh, $2.
What am I supposed to do with $4?
- Go ahead and transfer this one to the bank.
- That bonus is, those cuts that you get
from like the online banks have got to be like way worse
than you get at like real casinos, rather.
Online casinos.
You don't get like a break back at the casino.
I know that you don't, but when you're a person that goes there.
Yeah, you get drinks.
I feel like any of that is way more tangible than the 20 bucks that we have gotten.
If you go to Atlantic City or Las Vegas for like a full weekend and you like talk to one of the pit bosses
And like introduce yourself to like somebody and like make some friends. They will comp a hotel room. They'll comp your meals
They will comp at anything that you need to keep you gambling even if you're not gambling that much
Yeah, I think it's like maybe it's more like a social thing like yeah, I'm the only thing
It's just like a just a machine me like yeah, you get just gamble this much and we'll give you like five bucks
And it's like really not something that you can even like look look towards
They have to make it up, but real casinos suck
Real casinos are under attack as we speak by Vegas
I just was reading about this the MGM has been completely hacked
They're signing people in on a clipboard like it's Hurricane Katrina, and they're sitting in a giant football stadium guys
We need to go to MGM and we need to save them you need to get down there and save them
to
- Your black hat hacker brain probably would think to do that.
- I think that's your affiliates.
- And then you see a little kid pointing at it and crying because they've never seen a
human's asshole before, and you go, "Look at this Karen, I'm gonna record this."
- That is the Karen moment.
- It should be like, if you're inside that dome right now, it should be like you're in
the Matrix, and it should be all of the BME Pain Olympics videos.
With a thousand screens surrounding you.
- Big white room.
- What is the youngest age that a person could be labeled as a Karen?
Probably one years old.
Probably one second old.
You know, you cannot.
As long as it takes to grow your hair to your shoulder length
from the day that you're born.
Probably two years.
I think at least
around 30.
No. 30?
No. Yeah.
You cannot be a teenage or
infant aged Karen.
Karen is a mindset.
It has nothing to do with age.
I
Know if you're if you're a fucking 20 years old and annoying at like a restaurant that is Karen behavior
That is true. I knew kids growing up who were very rude at restaurants. Yeah
Her and my grandpa have a similar
That's why I'm very I'm like out of my way nice to a point that
Is annoying to my wife to like waiters and stuff. Yeah, and I feel guilty. I'll like I
Don't know. I I try to like clean the tables before I leave and
She's like, can we leave?
You actually left a problem. I'm mad at her because she dropped a crumb on the table at the restaurant
Well, I still have to do the dishes.
Oh, yeah, exactly.
But so the reason where this comes from is apparently my mom,
like a couple of months ago, she was at dinner with my brother
and he said that she actually ordered a piece of salmon medium rare.
Mm hmm. Oh, they were like,
you say medium rare.
So, yeah, medium rare.
They're like, we can't.
It's not like sushi grade salmon.
It's like a grilled salmon.
We can't just undercook the salmon.
It's illegal.
And my mom freaked out.
- That's so funny.
- I make the salmon medium rare at home all the time.
It's fine.
Please, I'll give you an extra $10
if you just undercook it.
- Actual Karen moment.
She got mad at this waiter
because he wouldn't put in an illegal order
for an undercooked fish.
So awesome.
Alright, show me the crushing.
For those listening on audio, Rex has a can crusher that he's-
For those listening on audio, just, just listen up.
Just listen.
[loud, high-pitched screeching]
Oh my god! That is so loud!
[high-pitched screeching]
Fuck me, the levels on this fucking episode are gonna be so fucked.
Wow.
Look at that. Oh!
Oh, and he still made a mess.
Wow.
So as soon as, okay, so this is how this went down.
As soon as last week's episode ended and we did, we did for a second week in a row,
we did a, what, let's see, Freck's disgusting can addled desk.
He immediately messages me a minute after we're done recording.
Oh my God, I am going to order a, a can crusher on Amazon.
And I'm going to, you said while you were speaking and I was like, that is so stupid,
but that would be so funny.
And now he's actually done it, and it's so funny,
but it is so loud and annoying that I hope he uses--
- That is one of the last things I've ever heard.
- I'm gonna show this.
(boxes clattering)
- Oh, nice, you've been-- - Whoa.
- The desk is clear, huh?
- I did it like two days ago. - Show me, show me.
- So-- - For the third week in a row.
Oh, eh. - Still four.
- It's manageable. - But you, oh, okay, six.
- Yeah, there's a few. - All right, come on, bitch.
And he has a mousepad!
I do have a mousepad.
Wait, you bust up.
You completely bust up.
Everyone was bullying me for not having a mousepad.
That's because it was crazy, man.
Everyone was like, "The cans are fine.
That's normal.
The mousepad is not."
Who told you the cans were normal?
There was a comment on the beers we drank.
There was a single one comment.
Everybody said the cans are normal.
Everyone was saying--
Okay, so this is the problem.
Everyone was saying it, no one was disagreeing.
I know, I love and thank everyone who comments on the episodes, but if you're just, you know,
"Oh, I like Rex, I like when he does this."
Don't, if you're even just the only person, don't do that.
Don't support him.
Don't support him because he'll just do shit like this.
I'm seeing, I'm seeing a return.
So Chib says, "Cans normal, no mousepad, friggin psycho."
but then Smiler responds, "Two or three cans is fine.
27 is fucking crazy."
(laughing)
- So it was really-- - Clearly they don't drink
enough cans of liquid on a daily basis.
- Dude, I gotta tell you,
and I mean, I have my own little can collection right now,
I hate to say it, but it's not on my desk.
- Where is it?
- It's right here.
- Yup. - Oh.
I got a couple of cans right there.
- Well, I think that's different.
You have a can ledge.
You have a ledge.
- I have a can ledge.
It's not on my desk.
- Ledge made for cans.
- Okay, that's because Caleb has a desk
that is maybe a third the size of me.
- No, I could fit cans in the back.
- I don't know if you have a can ledge.
- I will say, after we record this,
two of these were from last night,
and then two of these,
or three of these are from last night,
one of these is from tonight.
After I record this, these are all going away.
There is no way that it will get worse.
This is the worst it's ever been, I think.
- Whoa.
- Yeah.
- Fine.
Fine, let's fix it.
- No, he's gonna, how do I mute you?
- Why did I do that?
- How do I mute you?
- No, the cancel the desk.
No.
- Go ahead, let's fix it.
Come on, no, no, no.
- I'm gonna-- - This is what
you're talking about.
- I'm gonna put your volume at like minus 17.
- You're being difficult.
You're being difficult right now.
Oh my God.
(laughing)
This is so awful.
- Okay, okay, you have to stop.
- That's the last one.
- You actually have to stop.
- And you love it too.
You love it so much.
- Why can you buy this?
Why can someone just buy this?
What do you buy this at?
- Yeah, I bought this on Amazon.
- So. - He's ashamed.
He's ashamed.
- How much? - The soul of shame.
- It was $80.
- Oh my God.
- It was completely worth it.
It was $80.
- Yeah, it was worth it.
- I get a lot of enjoyment out of it.
It's fun.
Are you gonna bring it with you as a party trick now to every single party?
It needs to be plugged into a wall, but yes, I will do that.
That is actually a fucking great idea.
They make it over to people's houses.
They make a pneumatic one that's air-powered, that's a little less expensive, but you need a compressor.
Oh man, you don't wanna get... that's way worse.
I think that would be so dangerous now.
A compressor?
Yeah, I don't know.
it's going to be a lot louder.
That would have been a much, much worse experience.
There's three tiers of can crusher.
There's mounted on the wall, lever activated.
I love those.
$20.
I really like those though.
Those are great.
If you have a porch, there's like $60, but you need an air compressor pneumatic.
And there is one single electric can crusher.
And you got it.
And I got a premium tier.
- We could also, I mean, you could get a hydraulic press.
- I mean, that's basically what it is.
- But like a really,
- Those are literally a thousand dollars.
- I think they're way more than a thousand dollars.
I think you have to have room for it basically to.
- What kind of pressures or like forces is it rated for?
- That one?
- Yeah, just.
- I have no clue.
- What's the strongest thing?
- Can we get the world's strongest can?
- No, can you go, do you have any food in your house?
- No. - Oh.
He's not right now.
Actually, no, I believe that he doesn't have fruit in his house.
Yeah, there's no fruit.
It's been eaten.
Oh, yeah.
There's no fresh fruit.
Next time you go to the grocery store,
can you grab like an apple and put it in it
and just see what it has?
No, we do grapes and then like an apple.
It doesn't go low enough to do grapes.
Apple, though.
I really like those hydraulic press videos,
but I always do think that I would be--
If I owned one of those, I'd be fucking terrified of it.
- To put your hand in there?
- No, 'cause they put like anything in there
and then it just shatters into a million pieces
and shoots at the speed of light in every direction.
- I think by the point where you--
- Yeah, that's why you just do the cans.
- I think by the point where you own
a whole ass hydraulic press,
you're like kind of way past like worrying about anything.
- You're over the baby fear of it?
Yeah, I guess maybe.
- Yeah.
- I do think that this is a really awesome party trick.
Now, I'm thinking about it more and more.
I think this will be the complete legend of the party.
- It is very fun when you've got people over
and you're hanging out, you're drinking beer,
and you go, "Hey, watch this."
And you pull it out from behind the couch.
- And you crush a bottle.
- Everyone gathers around and you crush a can.
- Speaking of glass bottle, glass goes everywhere.
- Why has there been no invite to your house yet?
- 'Cause it's nasty right now.
Also, there's two people staying over.
I mean, yeah, I'll have you over.
- I wanna see your kitchen.
I just set up a pots and pans rack yesterday. Oh
And where did you choose to place this?
on the wall
Nice, you guys have an island? No. Well, we we built
Like it Brian's place like one of those. Oh, yeah
What's it like a little table on road?
Yeah wheels just went crazy
It's not on wheels it is just a regular table is it on the heart
It's a what
Do you have a bar cart we do have a bar stocked with every kind of alcohol that a guy like you could ever imagine
No, it just has cables in it and it smells like curry
I just smell like curry. That is a great question spill the uber eats on it or something. Oh
No, I want curry so bad. There's a Nepal place near me. That's really good
Yeah, it's like no no Indian food near me really
Which sucks. Yeah, the Nepalese place is good. Yeah, I'll have you over have some some jerk food some Nepalese food
Gamble on my base and we got into
Jamaican food and I'm thinking it's one of my new favorites. It's a the place sells like freshly made like in-house
Jamaican beef patties with like
every different type of
Filling what kind of footage Jamaican?
It's like jerk chicken, oxtail, which is basically like a slow cooked beef thing.
Rice and peas.
Everything has like kind of a, yeah, plantains.
Everything has kind of a like citrusy flavor to it.
It's like a, I don't know, it's really good.
I think like every Central American country's cuisine has like plantains in it.
Do you guys have plantains in Mexico or not really?
Yeah, like in the south.
You do?
Yeah, like Veracruz.
Mmm, I love plantains.
I don't like them at all.
You don't like sweet ones?
No, I don't like plantains.
What about green ones?
Nope, I like regular-ass bananas.
But green plantains are basically potatoes, man.
I don't like them.
Well, I think, was it you that gave me some plantain chips?
I think I like that.
Yeah, those are like the good.
That's like the most I've ever liked any plantain based stuff.
They're basically just like potato chips.
And but they have like just a little they're a little more like starchy.
Like you need like a glass of water to actually eat them.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
Not for me.
I'm still there's a
like Jamaican pizza shop that's
Instagram famous.
I have never been because there is literally a 40 person line at all times.
Really? To go there.
And you cannot order ahead.
You have to stand in line.
Oh, that's good.
That means it's really good. They sell a jerk chicken pizza.
They sell a chicken and French toast pizza.
They sell a chicken and waffle pizza.
They sell a jerk chicken black truffle Alfredo pizza.
Wait, I want to.
Can you send me a picture of this chicken and waffle pizza?
I want to I want to see this.
I it's just listed on their menu.
Let me see.
This is one of those things where someone just says like a way I want to go here.
I'm looking at a picture it.
I'm looking at the menu. I want to go here.
Yeah, I need to.
I need to get a crew together to stand in line for an hour with me.
Let's fucking go, man.
Oh, my God. The prices are actually insanely reasonable, too.
No, that's for one slice.
How much is my slice? What?
It's like $12 for a slice of pizza.
For the jerk chicken black truffle Alfredo, it's $11.96 for a slice.
That shit has got to be so good.
12 for a pizza? For a slice of pizza?
I bet it's good, man. Wait, I'm gonna look up the reviews.
It's gonna be so good and the slices have to be so big that it's almost like half a pizza.
There's no way.
Let's look at the reviews here.
Guys, four and a half stars on Google.
1,200 Google reviews.
Yeah.
Wait.
This is gonna be amazing.
We're going here.
To support black owned was great.
They are indeed black owned.
You're kidding.
I know.
Imagine a white guy selling an oxtail pizza.
That'd be way, that'd be so bad.
I don't think that would go over very well at all.
If there's a white guy who made a pizza restaurant that's all Jamaican food.
I don't think a 4.5, like impresses me.
- 4.5 with 1,200 reviews is really good.
- Maybe the 1,200 reviews would like sway me over,
but I was thinking about this yesterday.
I think for me to think that the product is good,
it has to be like 4.6, 4.7.
4.8 is probably perfect.
If it has five, like a five or a 4.9,
it probably has like two or three reviews.
It's on New York Times Cooking from this year, and here's the title of their video.
There are over 8,000 pizzerias in NYC.
So how did a Brooklyn pizza shop with no deliveries become a celebrity destination?
They took notes from the sneaker world.
Watch to find out why Lil Yachty, Odell McIntyre, Sean Kingston, and Rich Hoving Kwan are lining
up for Oxtail Pizza.
I did see that little Yachty was there. I did just see that photo or that video of him.
That is pretty awesome.
They can say that.
Brilliant idea. Drop pizza like sneakers.
Jesus Christ.
I will say, there's just a little preview of what you'll see next week. I bought glasses
finally. Uh-huh. And I was at this glasses store in Soho and this woman like runs in
from there's like a bunch of people like down the street when I went in and I was
like huh I wonder what that's about and like the street was closed off like the
cops were there so I figured it was just like you know some shit and it was like
this woman like runs in like halfway through and it's like a takeoff is down
the street throwing 100s on the sidewalk.
Whoa!
Did you grab one?
Did you get one?
No.
Fuck!
It was literally, it was like a Kaisenat like, like street riot.
Oh, well he's, he, he was on Kaisenat's stream actually.
Yeah.
So...
So you look foolish now.
For not knowing your culture.
Why do I look foolish?
Why do I look foolish for saying that?
What did I say that was weird?
Tell me what I did wrong.
So many things.
You're fine.
Do I sound like a robot?
You sound like a normal.
Am I frozen?
No, you are normal.
You guys can see me moving left to right right now?
Can you hear us?
No, I can hear you.
Yeah, but you sound like a jiggly robot.
No, but that's fine.
A jiggly robot?
Yeah, see, you both sound auto-tuned to me.
But that's okay.
This is a really good website that we use.
that's fine. A jiggly robot.
Yeah, I see you both sound auto-tuned to me, but that's okay.
This is a really good website that we use.
Yeah. I'm using it for another a hundred episodes.
Rex, do you want to go on an Atlantic city trip soon?
I would love to.
I thought you hated Atlantic city. I caught you.
Here's the thing. Do I want to go to a,
do I find a real life casino worse than online gambling?
Without a doubt.
Would I give up the opportunity to go to a casino with my
friends?
Of course not.
Why would I do that?
Would be foolish.
I think as enjoyable as it was to go hang out with over their
friends to another destination.
Let's do like a little road trip thing.
I do think that we somehow like just cooked the perfectly
worse vacation day of all time.
when we went to Titanic City.
- We were all sick and hungover.
- We were all so sick, hungover.
We went out so early.
- I don't remember that.
- We went out so early.
The vibes were so crazy the entire way there.
You called me a child for my McDonald's order.
- That is true.
- Wow, that's tough.
(laughing)
What did you order?
- I think just like a thing.
I think you made fun of me because I had the OJ.
- Yeah, you got orange juice.
Oh, you got orange juice. Yeah. Yeah.
You're hung over, you get a coffee.
It was it was also like so
cold and just so I don't know.
It was just like really bad vibes.
And we ate me.
We ended up making Rex eat like a like a poop patty at the end of the.
Oh, yeah.
But I will not have to do that anymore because I eat now.
Now you will eat a birria taco at Johnny also at Johnny Rockets.
Yay.
Actually, there's a really good sandwich place in Atlantic City
that called like White House subs.
I think we'll go back there.
That sounds dope.
Can you take a train to Atlantic City?
I don't believe so.
I think you they have like buses, but really we should just drive.
Yeah, but we should not do a day trip.
We should go for like a weekend.
We're like two days or something because the hotels are pretty cheap.
And Harris is like nice.
And we get swimming a pool.
And into a pool.
Yeah, that's I love hotel pool.
I love hotels.
I mean, I am 100% convinced I love hotels.
I never want to stay in a disgusting Airbnb ever again.
Not that I could anymore in New York City.
Yeah, I just found we find that out from Brian that
I told I got I found that out through a thing of video like somewhere I found out that they had that I told brain that New York is is deleting all airbnb's or some shit.
They just made like some really strict rules yes like you need to be living in there with them you need to like.
You can only have like two people in airbnb at a time.
It's kind of funny because Airbnb didn't update a month or two ago.
We're bringing back the, we know that everyone hates Airbnb now, so we're bringing back the classic old field of Airbnb a couple years ago, where it's actually someone's house.
You have to go into this mode and you'll actually just stay at someone's room and they'll be there and you can talk to them and share their house.
And then like a month later, New York's like,
yeah, you can't be like a slumlord anymore.
Like we have suffered a couple times.
Now you actually have to live there.
- There is, it sucks 'cause I'm in like the one neighborhood
in New York where there's actually no hotels.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- There's no fucking hotels.
Oh wait, there's a red carpet in here?
Nevermind guys, there's a red carpet in a two-star hotel.
Guys, this is the place to be.
$150 a night for what looks like the worst hotel room you could imagine.
This is like a sex hotel. This is like one that you go to to have sex.
Yeah, it's gonna be your only option guys.
I will simply stay at one of my friends' apartments.
Just go stay in Manhattan at the Trump Tower.
I'm not gonna do that. I almost did that.
I almost did that, when I came back from New York last time, I saw a...
Okay.
So, Rex has linked us a YouTube video of Jadakiss enjoys ordering pizza with just the crust.
Just the crust?
It's a TMC video from four years ago.
Oh my god!
Wait, I have to show this on video.
What the fuck?
I'm not doing this in post. I'm doing this on right now
That's one of the craziest things I've ever seen in my life maybe
I
Forgot what I was saying this is do you know what I think I
Think New York pizza is the best piece in the world
Chicago in the Libby Dam those are the only
like
and
under construction right now so I have not been able to eat there in months
really so sad I'm almost going to cry it really is making me so fucked up man I
don't want to show it's just the into the video so people can actually see this
this horrible pizza it's a pizza with just the crust yeah it is well not just
There's that little bit of edge around that constitutes some middle
It looks like the stay from logo
Three slices of the middle as well. I think that's sauce
Three sorry not three slices three things of
Sauce I thought it was pepperonis when I first saw it though. Okay, so completely drunk
So funny.
I actually have had one and a half and I'm
looking at some interesting work stuff that just came across my
my your desk desk here.
Yeah. Says.
Yeah, I mean, this is a tundra's fortune puts a lot of its eggs in one basket,
which can be a good or bad thing, depending on the outcome.
Six point five fair from big wind boards on a pragmatic play.
So this is this is the kind of work that it's
I mean, hot off the presses right in front of me.
Cash chips got a seven.
Infected wild got a seven.
I mean, we know what we're doing after this.
I got to make myself a steak sandwich and a salad.
And then all bets.
Talk about how big wind boards was in hot water.
Big wind boards is being targeted in a lawsuit.
I think we did talk about this.
They're trying to shut down the only honest journalistic.
I don't think it's honest.
I don't think I completely think it's not honest.
You don't know what you're talking about.
Dude, Big Ben will be like, oh yeah, this one is like it's 9.8 rated.
You'll get your money back guaranteed, my friend.
And you will play the demo.
That's not what they would say.
You'll play the demo.
You'll play the demo and in five spins.
Oh, my God.
You got the you got the bonus.
They would never be so.
That's not the case.
What are you even talking about?
So crazily.
Have you ever, do you even know
The first thing about big wind board.
The first thing big wind board says is, yeah, I never win.
I never win when I gamble.
And you know what?
I believe him.
Is it because he's real guy?
I think there's a team, but there is one guy that runs the YouTube
and he responds to people being like, this is fake.
No one has ever won this.
And he goes, Yeah, you're right. Yeah.
Or he'll bitch about streamers.
We should have him on.
Speaking of journalists.
What is streamers?
Yeah, he hates gambling streamers.
How come?
Yeah, because he does all these exposés about how it's fake money
and how they're getting paid by the casino, which one of the best things
is that a lot of these guys have like these on their websites
have like this tab called like verify or something.
And they're like, look, you can see
all of my Bitcoin deposits coming from my wallet.
on this wallet.
And like you see all my transaction history.
But all of them have like the exact amount of money
that they put into the casino
coming from the casino in the previous transaction.
- Yeah.
- And then when they're like, well, why is it?
And they're like, well,
they pay me a stipend to promote their website,
but it's the exact amount that they put back in.
- Yeah.
- It's so awesome, dude.
- Yeah, Big Win Board rules.
Shout out Big Win Board.
- Shout out.
- I don't know if any of these guys remember.
- Probably my most visited website.
- It's not even close for me.
- Yeah.
- It is overtaken.
My screen time on Big Win Board is just above anything else.
- I just always have a tab, either a Big Win,
I check the YouTube channel every day.
I have a tab of it open at all times.
- Rex will have people over at his room
and just make him watch him spin demo reels.
- That is true, I did do that to Julio.
- He did that to me and he poisoned me with his room.
(laughs)
- What does that mean?
- Yeah, we talked about this before,
but yeah, he, in his disgusting, humid room
that would just poison him every single day of his life.
I went to hang out in there and he was like,
"Look, I'm doing a penguin boards demo reels."
And I sat on his bed for a single second
and I felt like I was, I just fell asleep.
I just passed out.
I couldn't stay awake.
I didn't find out that he had mold and yeah,
but then like that.
Oh, speaking of you getting so sick,
the your old Airbnb still has that.
I walk by it every day on the way to the office.
It still has that fucking sign in front of it
that says that this is not fit for human life.
That is awesome.
It's so dope.
Yeah, she can't contact with that guy.
We should we should be like,
yo, what's up, man?
Just ask him to rent it to you guys under the table
because you guys like that place.
We don't.
I don't.
- Oh, that place is horrible.
The smell is horrible.
- The smell was always bad.
- The smell is bad.
There's rats in the walls.
The cops will come in every single day,
be like, "Yo, I'm gonna kill you if you keep staying here."
- Yeah, I guess that's not so good.
- Yeah, it's horrible.
- But it was close and it was cheap.
- Yeah. - It was close.
- I wouldn't call it cheap.
- Or maybe not even cheap.
- Yeah. - It was around though.
- Yeah. - It was around.
But what I will say is that when I made Julio watch me play Big Win Board, I hit a nice 5000x
on atero echo spins.
I would not be able to recall because I was passed out due to being chloroformed by Rex.
That's amazing guys.
My only slot max win, you guessed it, on Big Win Board.
Is it atero?
No, it's true blood or whatever it is.
True blood.
the
- That is true.
- That is a completely sucks.
- That's what I'm saying.
That's what I'm saying you have max win on that thing.
- Oh, he thinks they're using a fake demo.
Well, that's provided by the slot provider.
That's no fault of Big Win Board, I would say.
- Okay, okay, we're done here.
We're done.
- We're done, I'm so hungry.
I have to go make this steak.
- All right, goodbye.
- Goodbye, my friends. - Goodbye.