Go!
Record and listen to this.
[Burps]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer podcast.
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
This is a journey into fears we drank
Fears we drank motherfuckers with Juvio Caleb and Rex Merry Cipsmas bitch
Yes, what brand new fucking intro with Eminem dog, yeah, wait
That's crazy as fuck actually funny enough that intro was written by OJ the alien and it was performed by Eminem the real one
That's amazing news man guys welcome to 150th episode of beers we drank we're back again after a short
It's amazing it really it doesn't even feel real this is the greatest
Podcast greatest pot 9 beer party greatest podcast on planet Earth today
We have a very special we have we hit today. We have a correspondent guys guys
Snap it up for that. We have a correspondent who's on location in some part of Mexico doing I'm
Guessing some kind of investigative reporting because there's so many things going on. I'm coming live from beer, Mexico
well, that's like tequila does the place where all the beer comes from and
You wouldn't believe the kind of fear they got in here. They got this weird beer. I don't know how to pronounce
Oh, I'm already about to be disappointed. Oh wait. No, it actually is a beer
Oh, I thought you were supposed to take out a diet coke
Yeah, but they make it here Stella are twa. Yeah some sort of Alex
Citra I don't know. It's not such weird. Let me taste it from 1366 man put some respect on that
How do you fuck up a drink it was doing it was bubbling
That is just so late in the rifle and I love a stellar twang. All right, give me a rating man
That's a perfect seven out of ten
Okay, finally a normal rating from you. Yeah, I like that guys
This I had I made a mistake
Made this mistake many times before and today's no different
I had my wife pick up my beer for me and she always gets me some she hates it. I do this podcast
is
tattooed pumpkin Bronx Brewing Co. Guys, this is a pumpkin ale. This is one of my least
favorite things on earth. I'm already halfway through it because Jubia took a long time
and I got thirsty. I'm going to take a sip.
Yeah.
Okay. Honestly, I'm getting zero pumpkin off of this.
Okay.
The can is very annoying to me, it's some kind of evil gourd with tattoos all over it.
It just tastes like an IPA.
I'm going to give this a 5.9 out of 10.
And basketball?
This is like the third string shooting guard.
This is like a bench presence.
This is a vet, you know.
So actually, you know what, I changed my mind.
This is a development player.
This is somebody from overseas who played in EuroLeague basketball or something.
And they played a long time and they were just middle of the road.
Maybe a white guy.
This is a white guy.
So whatever height comes along with that.
And I think there's a possibility that this guy could get better with some time in the
league.
But right now he's very middle of the road.
Okay.
All right.
Well, now we go to our nun.
So I have...
Oh, first roast of the podcast!
Wait!
You do look like a beautiful nun.
At first I thought you had a blouse on like a pirate.
Well, this is...
Okay, hold on.
This is my...
Your Team Liquid jersey.
This is my team liquid jersey
Hoodie that I bought right, uh that makes you look like you're a gun
How does it make you look at gundam
It makes you look like you're a gundam pilot. It looks like a bad power rangers
Uh hoodie. All right. I think it makes you look like you shop at uniclo man
I don't think it's doing much other than that
Okay. Well
You're the penguin of 2023. I honestly don't want to say how much I spent on this. Anyway,
now you have to now you have to you should have said this $40. Oh, God, man. Oh, my God,
that is hurting me. I bought I brought from my fridge a another Bel Air sour. Okay.
A repeat beer. It is a repeat beer. I was going to go to the store. It's fine. That's I'm going
I'm gonna hold this up, but this is an L, but that's okay.
- So this is like an eight to me.
This is basically a perfect beer.
I could drink this all day.
It's delicious.
- A Bel Air sour.
So tell me how this differs from a normal sour.
- It doesn't make you feel bloated.
It doesn't make you feel like you're drinking
800 calories of beer.
- Okay.
- It makes you feel like you're drinking
a normal amount of calories,
Because it's only 5.8%, so it's not like a sour monkey.
You could just sit and sip this on a warm day, on a cold day, for a job well done, to get
a job done, whatever you need.
It's a very versatile beer.
If you have no job.
If you have no job, you probably would be spending...
How much do these cost for a six pack, do you know?
I think it was like 12 bucks for a six.
Oh, that's not too bad.
That's not outrageous.
- Well, I would like to have an addendum
to the beer reviewing, now that we have a,
since we're having a repeat beer,
I would like to come in with something fresh,
something I don't have with me right now,
but I've just come back from New York
and I immediately left town, I'll get into that later,
and I tried my first Guinness, and my first St. Sal,
- But you have your first Guinness.
- And my first, the Schieweck as well.
I had all those, and I can review them all
right here, right now, because I'm probably--
- Okay, yeah, no, these are three important beers to me.
I love Guinness on Giraffe.
I had never had a Tsing Tsao before,
but that was an amazing beer.
And then what was the other one you said?
- The Zivek.
- A Zivek, yeah, that's a legendary beer in these parts.
- I will leave with the Zivek,
because I had it while we were doing
that You'll Have to Drink thing with Pat and Cam.
- Okay.
- That is fully demonetized and censored on YouTube,
so I don't think that Vod's gonna ever see the light of day.
- That's all right, man.
- I thought that was all right.
I really like the Zivek.
That's another like six, seven out of 10.
I really enjoyed my time with the Shivek.
I would gladly go back to it.
It was a great, it was really big.
It was a really big bottle.
And it was just great to drink it with friends.
- Yeah.
- I like it a lot.
Second, we went to Chinatown with some friends.
We had some Chinese buns that were so delicious.
And I had my first Xing Cao.
And I thought maybe it was a little too much.
Because maybe we're not--
- Too much in what way?
- I don't know, I think the buns were just maybe so full.
- Yeah, that's not the kind of meal you need a beer after.
- Yeah, so I think in other circumstances
I would like this thing to sell more.
But in crushing it with a Chinese bun with it
was really not, it's time to shine,
so it's gonna go with a five for now.
- Okay.
- It may, I may change my rating
once I go back to Chinatown,
But it'll be that for now.
And lastly, my Guinness review.
I had some Guinness the last day in New York.
I was hanging out with everyone at the bar.
- At Cozy, yeah.
That's where they have Guinness on draft.
- You left.
So it was me, Noah, Cam, Brian and Alex.
- And I was there too.
- And also Rex.
- Whoa.
I was on I've been you forget about your co-host. It's fine. No, it's fine
So Alex orders to get this for some reason and
He goes like oh no, I know how I get this. I was like, oh, that's funny me neither
So it's like oh, here you go. Take a sip and I took a sip and it was mid
Yeah
Okay
Okay, buddy, well you're gonna as somebody who lived in Boston for 26 months you're gonna have to explain yourself to me
It's been it's been said of the show before I don't fuck with dark beers
Light beers are where my heart's at and I thought you're a light supremacist. Yeah, I'm not gonna say that
He said yeah, you already said. Yeah, it's already confirmed. All right, I
Had a sip of Guinness. I didn't much like it or enjoyed it or find it interesting
So I was like, you know what that's enough for me. So in my eyes, that's a two
Wow, that is a strong anti-Irish sentiment.
Coming out of Jubio.
Coming out of the luchador himself.
That is, Guinness is an interesting beer because the first time I had it I also thought it was
disgusting.
The second time I thought it was even worse because I had it in a can and it just does
not translate well to a can.
And then I moved to New York after I had already long left Boston, I moved to New York and now
I enjoy Guinness.
And I think the reason I enjoy it is because I found out that it may seem like a heavy
beer because of the color and the texture, but it's actually, guys, it's one of the lightest
beers you can buy.
This is a beer that is like 4.2% and like 100 calories for a 12-ounce pour.
It just has this kind of malty taste that is, it kind of tricks you into thinking it's heavy,
but man, it's really not.
I don't know.
I didn't really, I'm going to fool through the parentheses.
It was just a sip, I didn't have a full beer.
- Okay, yeah.
- But even that, I was like, you know what?
I'm good, I tried it, I don't really think
I'm gonna like it.
So maybe I'll give another shot later on.
- What was the best drink you had while you were
in New York?
Not even, it doesn't have to be beer,
best alcoholic drink you had while you were in New York?
We had a lot.
- Okay, I think I'm gonna say the margaritaville.
- The margaritaville?
(laughing)
Margaritaville? Dude, the five o'clock somewhere at Margaritaville? We have to go through the
entire trip day by day. Okay. We're not gonna do that. We'll just talk about the legendary night.
What a legendary night. When we went to get sushi? Well, we started off with the most legendary night
start off at the M&M store. We went to the M&M store. We went to the M&M store. We had big plans.
Alex is not here, but you saw him last week. He bought a
Stupid amount of M&Ms. I don't think he finished him and he spent $35 USD on M&Ms
And I think he ate almost every single one. Okay, and while he in his five-day trip, which is crazy
Yeah, that's crazy
It was like a pound and a half of M&Ms little aside. It called them an M is real
No, it's a witness and he said it's true
moving on
We went to the M&M store
It was just a magical time where I think I was walking downstairs
Because we're always obviously we went all the way up and we're walking back down and I think I just like
Just need the fuck out of like someone's like bag or something and maybe like someone's child
And I just kept walking and the guy who was my victim. He just turns around and he goes
You say excuse me, buddy, and I just kept walking. That's racially motivated. Yeah
He could tell that you're from a place where they don't say excuse me. I didn't fuck with that
I just kept walking sour experience at the M&M store. Yeah, great
Thankfully after that we went we had we headed for that
Just the iconic New York slice at Times Square
Yeah, the worst one. I think I've ever had it was not great and it was also so expensive. Yeah
But and I burnt the fuck out of my mouth
So guys don't get a slice at Times Square also a sour experience next we turn it around
360 degrees walking walking and working away from it. Yeah fucking Margaritaville sixth floor
Guys when I tell you this is the best bar in New York City. I don't play about this shit. I'm up this this is my life
Okay, my life is fucking drinking. So this is the best bar in New York City, and it's not even close
This bar, you get on an escalator, it brings you up, who even knows how many floors this is.
Then you have to go to another, to an elevator to go up to the sixth floor.
And then you come out, perfectly dead bar.
They have thousands of drinks, all of them amazingly delicious.
They come out of a bottle, the guy doesn't make them at all.
They're insanely sweet, they're all blue.
And guess what happened to us guys?
we're sitting there and we look like also at the family
we look like a fucking family sitting there right over the picture for people
and if you want more proof that we look like a family to be proof
a guy walked up to us and said
do you guys want
a postcard a free christmas postcard
uh... free christmas card
done for you right now at margaritaville new york city
and we said by god i we do we really really do
So they got us together, brought out a DSLR, this is an expensive type of camera, and took
this photo.
Look at us guys.
Look at us.
Look how happy we all are.
Look at me, man.
That's the happiest I've ever fucking been in my life.
Oh my god.
Look at these drinks.
Look at the colors of these drinks.
Have you ever seen colors like this in a drink?
That was just, I mean, it was amazing.
There's no two ways about it.
That was the best bar experience ever.
i was great was so beautiful
it was fucking beautiful
and then
we will go ahead you you're telling the entire night uh... yeah
uh... after that
and i was before after that but we we have we'll head to the uh... to the tree
and was completely off because was november
yet we went to the thirty rocker to the rockefeller center tree
and it had not been turned on and people are still out taking photos of him i
think it was a very big
And there was a light show, there was a light show across the way done by some fashion house,
Dolce and Gabbana or something.
I thought it was Dior, I forget.
Maybe it was Dior, whatever, it was one of these fancy brands.
It was really strange.
It was highly strange.
And guys, here's an example of how we've lost Christ in this country.
I remember seeing that the first time I went to New York City when I was 14.
I remember seeing that same light show and it was Christ, Mother Mary, Christmas trees,
snowflakes all sorts of wintery wonderland type uh... thanks this time
we go we sit in front of it
the light show begins
sagittarius
torus
aries
every kind of pagan symbol that one could imagine
a shamrock
blasted all over the downtown streets of new york city this is a disgusting
display
of atheism
in a way that i don't think should be allowed or legal
uh... in the state really didn't understand that like show that we look
at it for like a second or like a writer's kind of quick
was very boring is very loud
i really wish it seemed like they were taking advantage of people may be
checking to see if the tree was on
and remains they instead had their light show they said come look at this way
yet look look behind you
look at the so it
and that is the soft that puts in a sour mood but then
What happened next, Juvia?
- Dan, we had it, I don't know what the area's called,
but we went-- - The West Village.
- We went to the West Village,
and we went to this crazy cocktail bar
where you order a plant,
and they bring you a drink, basically.
- Guys, you order a plant,
and I know it seems like there may be
some kind of language barrier here
because of how he's describing it,
but I swear on my mother's future grave
that this is a bar where you walk in and you say,
"Give me the rosemary."
And they make a thing that tastes,
or that has something to do with rosemary.
And me, you know me, I'm a chocolate lover.
We had already gone to the M&M store,
but I didn't have my fill yet.
I got the cocoa nibs.
- Well, it was really funny because you ordered that,
and you didn't know, there was like a brown smear
on Caleb's glass.
- And I thought it was a leaf, y'all.
- And he thought it was, first he thought it was a leaf,
like some decoration stuff.
But then, approximately like 10 or 15 minutes
into us drinking our cocktails,
he just licks it and he goes like, "Oh, it's chocolate."
- It was chocolate and then I started using my teeth
in the fancy cocktail bar to scrape the chocolate
off of my $20 drink because I'm gonna get my money's worth,
man, it's that simple.
- Was it supposed to have chocolate in it or was it--
- Yeah, dude, it was Cocoa Nibs.
It was Cocoa Nibs, man, of course it's supposed
to have chocolate in it.
Was that my plant?
Yeah, that was the plant I ordered.
I ordered cocoa nibs.
Alex ordered pandan.
Noah ordered vanilla.
The vanilla was a complete milkshake for Christmas.
The vanilla was a milkshake.
But yeah, that was an amazing experience.
Avocado leaf because it was very delicious to me.
Yup.
It was basically a margarita.
It was the worst drink on the table,
I'm gonna be honest with you.
I liked it low key,
but I kind of liked the milkshake more.
It was a complete Christmas mood night type of thing.
It was, it was.
We were right next to the fire.
And then after that we leave, oh before that, I guess we can tell this, the Brian thing.
He goes to order like one oyster for each of us at the table and he goes like, "Oh, I'll
have this and I'll have five oysters."
And the waiter just like takes a beat and just like freezes up and she goes, "35?"
35?
I think I was like, "What?
35?"
She thought he ordered 35 oysters for the table.
He does his order again.
Five oysters and whatever drink.
And she goes like, "Oh, oh man."
She was like, "They were about to bring us 35 oysters.
They loved us so much that they were going to give us seven oysters ahead."
35 oysters would have been a crazy...
And this was before dinner too.
And had you ever had an oyster before?
Nope.
What did you think of an oyster, man?
I liked it.
It's not bad.
I don't know when I would go back and order another oyster, but I liked it.
Well, when you're hungry.
But we'll get to that.
Okay.
Where did we go after we went to Mace, the cocktail bar?
I think after we should let Rex take it over because this is when he joined the party.
That is true.
So I had been on an Adderall-fueled work binge leading up to a deadline, and I met them at
nine o'clock in ... Where was that?
part of the West Village still yeah West Village yeah to go to sushi Nakazawa
which is the zero dreams of sushi his son it's not his son it's his apprentice man
those are the princess well that is the same thing true because a master is a
father for life
Holy shit.
So it's a omakase restaurant.
So omakase is like a tasting menu for sushi.
They bring you like all these different types.
And it's $150 a person.
And did I pay?
No!
Fuck no.
I didn't pay a dime, man.
Holy crap, I love my friends so much.
Yes.
And so we get there and they take us back to our table.
We are six young, disgusting men.
Everyone in this restaurant is like old money style New York.
Everyone's wearing a suit.
All the waiters were wearing suits.
All the people in there were wearing like comfortable, expensive clothes.
We got there and sat down and immediately a woman behind Alex started bawling, crying.
That's when you know you're in a fancy restaurant.
when somebody feels like they're when somebody's crying and they don't even
feel like they're making a scene yeah it's transcended the point of politeness
right yeah it's you know very small room maybe enough room for like 20 people
enough for them to notice that I was wearing a Nike hoodie to the yes he did
have they did pull Alex was wearing a paper jersey yeah most of us looked out
of place. Not me man. I had a nice cashmere sweater on. I looked amazing. So we, you know,
we get there and we're like, okay, so let's get some drinks. We open up the wine menu,
the drink menu, which is huge, like 30 pages long. And we just started scrolling through
it and being like, Ooh, this, this, this sake is $30,000.
Yeah, they had a $17,000 sake.
Wait, can we get the $17,000 sake?
I asked Brian if we could get it and I kind of, I 10% expected him to say, "Yeah man, let's do it."
But then we were like, "Okay, we'll get a cheaper Apollo sake," which is, you know, still expensive,
And then we'll get some beers.
And uh...
We all were like, "Can we have the Orion please?"
And the Japanese man in his suit was like, "Oh, the Orion."
- "Orion." - He said, "O-O-Rion."
- "Orion." Yeah, sorry. - Yeah, and I was like, "God damn it, man."
We've already-- we've been there five minutes, we've already been made into complete fools.
They gave us a rag that you're supposed to wash your-- supposed to wipe your hands with.
Right? And I immediately put it on my face.
Like I was it like at a spa. I think you can write it. I think that was that'll mind if you do that
There's nothing wrong with that. I think they respect you do that
They put down like the the pickled ginger and then like a little wet map for your fingers
Yeah, and Caleb tried to pick it up with his chopsticks and be like is this food is this food?
Yeah, that was funny as fuck
So anyway, we finally start to get our sushi and it is amazing.
I don't even like sushi and that was-
It was divine, man.
Yeah, but it's also one of those meals where it's like,
you don't get- I was still kind of hungry after.
Really? I was stuffed, man.
20 pieces of like sushi is not that much.
Like that's that's like a full meal, but that's not like enough to last you for a day. Do you know what I mean?
No, you can't do Oh mad. You're not doing the oh, here's everything I hate doing one meal a day at sushi. Nakazawa man
Yeah, you can't do that shit
I I'm just saying so for me I was like, you know, this is amazing
So they bring out, you know, it starts from
What did it start with was it was the salmon first? I think I don't know man. Yeah. Anyway, they bring multiple
Yeah, they went salmon they went tuna they went
Eel they went all sorts of places
We went to every single part of the ocean
Yeah in a way that I was we went to parts of the ocean that I didn't think I was comfortable with I'm gonna be
Real they pulled out something called umi or ubi or doogie and this shit looked this shit looked like dookie
This actually looked like orange baby diarrhea sitting on top of a bed of rice and I thought that I was being pranked
I thought it was it was a what would you do kind of thing where it's like if a sushi restaurant served you a baby
Shit on a piece of rice. Would you eat it?
And then it turns out I would eat anything one funny thing was Brian ordered caviar and then you
Joined it like let me get the caviar
I had a little tiny bowl covered in gold flakes and I shared it man. He did share it cuz I'm a real one
And I the only other time I'd ever had caviar is some guy brought it to a birthday party and it was piping hot
And I told him I got a lot of satisfaction and telling him that I thought it was really disgusting
and
This time though. It was undeniable caviar rich people. You have amazing taste keep eating this. Yeah
It was it was kind of cool because they had multiple waiters because they have to like bring each individual course out
Yeah, it was like a Japanese man wearing like a grand Seiko
Middle-aged Japanese woman and then like a black nerd
Like a guy that is very clearly just into anime. Yeah
He's into sushi, man
Go sushi. Yeah, but yeah, so she and anime
So my man, yeah, I just watch episode 2 of the persona for animation. Yeah, but then a month
Right. It's big. I'm on my second. It's been a month and a half and I've watched two episodes of anime
It was done and I'm starting to like this shit, man
It was it was very good anime is dope, you know
Sushi, so it's fun to watch but uh eating sushi is more fun. I would say eating sushi is amazing guys
Today I went to the gym with
Patrick Doran no way. I went to the gym with Patrick Doran. It was amazing
Not that much to tell just teach him how to work out
But Noah also went to the gym today and he texted me about an hour ago and said that he was in the locker room
After, um, after working out, he did a back day and he was like, kind of checking out
his pump, right?
Nothing wrong with this.
This is what men are supposed to do in the gym.
Arnold said this, you're supposed to always be posing between sets.
But he's sitting there checking out his back and a guy walks in and says, looking good
man.
And Noah says, thank you, bro.
And then the guy says this, we all start somewhere.
*laughter*
How fucked up is that man?
Me and Hillbill texted about this for 30 minutes.
What the who the fuck says that?
That's crazy!
That guy better have been the most ripped gentleman alive.
Why was he ripped?
I didn't even ask dude.
I was so pissed off.
I was at the dog park.
I was seeing fucking red for my friend.
Can you FaceTime him and ask him if he was ripped?
I'll text him right now.
I'll text him right now if he was ripped.
is ripped that's fine it's still rude but it's fine but if he if he was like a big
fat guy but like you know functional strength construction worker fat guy
it's so funny to be like to like don't do not lead with the rude thing to be like
really nice and just be like oh yeah yeah kill yourself yeah dude I mean it's
not that bad what about a criticism sandwich whatever happened to that you
You look good, we all start somewhere, but I started even before that.
Say something like that.
Right.
Or, "I wanna fuck you, man."
That maybe as a sandwich would have worked.
Honestly, I thought that was going to be a gay sex story.
I think if you say thank you to a compliment, you have to accept that the person that you're
saying thank you to is going to...
They get to make a rude comment about it.
They have full, they're fully in control.
The second that you, that you, um,
Thank, thank you to a compliment comes from a position of power. Right. Right.
If I say, Hey man, that's a great hat. You don't look bald today.
Thank you, man. Yeah. See, but now you up to say whatever you want.
Exactly. You have the goodwill of the compliment.
You have a plus 30 buff to getting away with anything that you say now.
Yeah.
Like, imagine if the guy had just walked in and said, as Noah's posing, "We all start somewhere."
That would have been next-level rude.
Right?
That's just straight-up rude.
But that would have been the kind of rude where it's like, "Okay, we can just fight about this."
But the fact that the guy said, "Looking good, man. We all start somewhere."
That is like, "How am I gonna fight this guy? He just said I look good."
Yeah.
He may have wanted to take Noah under his wing to make him a big buff guy.
I think he wants to.
Thank you, but
Something Noah says slightly but like guy who just worked out on cable machines only with gloves for 20 years kind of jacked
He sounds mad to me. I'm gonna be honest. Oh, that is so he sounds pretty sounds mad
It sounds like this guy was fucking yoked this guy
Yeah
So that's a leech a guy being like I remember when I cuz I okay when I was in college. I had a friend who
he was like a
Special Forces guy and we would hang out on my porch and smoke cigarettes because he couldn't smoke in his apartment
and I remember like he was obviously just you know, fucking jacked like six four like massive and then I remember one day
I was wearing like a long-sleeve shirt. He's like, hey, man, that's like a nice shirt
You know, like I remember when I used to have your exact body
It's like okay man sure, you know that gave you some hope no it did
But that's the thing rip guys love to be like I remember when I look like that and then it took me another two years
To get where I'm at now
So as you read I don't think he also guys who were at the gym were retarded so you have to accept that
He probably didn't mean it to be rude. I'm rocking with guys
like wants to be like a
Like a bodybuilder like when he's still like 17
What do you mean me?
No, you were you like that?
When I was 17, I wanted to be a powerlifter. I wanted to be like an Olympic. I wanted to be like a
350 pound guy who could deadlift 1200 pounds. That's what I wanted
I did not care about I used to work here's this is a very funny thing about if anybody does weightlifting
They'll understand how funny this is when I was in college
my
My weightlifting maxes were I could squat 405 I could deadlift 505 and I could bench
Because I did not give a fuck about like trying to look good at all
I just wanted to and I would eat like 4,500 calories a day
That's so awesome, what did you what kind of music was in the headphone
With roughly I remember yeah
*laughing*
That might be the worst song ever and I was like damn there's some real shit right now
I really got to tackle my shit right now
Yeah, he says to the worst music ever or I would listen to to WTF with Mark Maron
while lifting
While lifting. Yeah, that's
When the Obama podcast came out and stuff like probably before that or maybe around then
Yeah, it was like I'd be like, oh shit man. TJ Miller just went on WTF. I gotta hit the gym
Oh man, that's awesome.
It was amazing. Yeah. And now I'm getting everybody into the gym.
Everybody started going to my exact gym now. And it's basically the biggest blessing ever.
Hold on, my dog's barking. I need to put him away. Give me a sec.
He's going to put him down. Julio, have you ever lifted weights? Have you ever been to a gym?
I went to a gym recently, but no,
I've never really lifted anything, no.
I
Try like my thing is I'll have like a moment where I'm like getting fat. I'm out of shape
I should get fit and then I'm like
All right time to just go as hard as possible and then keep going from there. Don't warm up
Don't do anything hurt myself immediately
Just like the worst thing you could possibly do people say that but I was you know, I was teaching
Patrick how to do weightlifting today and I think that I was taking it way too slow
I had him do a deadlift with a five-pound dumbbell like
And I was doing it I was like, I think I'm being a little too cautious about injury
But it is a little bit like if somebody first comes to the gym for the first time and they hurt themselves instantly
They're never gonna go again. Yeah, so you have to really ease them in and nobody knows how to do anything at first
So it's like, you know
What do you think?
Did he like it? I think he basically fell in love with it. I
Think I will say we got we got on the treadmill and we were doing like an incline walk
And I the heart rate monitor thing had to be broken because we were doing the incline walk in my heart
We were doing the same speed or he was doing a little less than me and my heart rate was like
151 on average and his heart rate I looked over it was a hundred and ninety-five
Like for his age like the absolute maximum that your heart can go
So there's no way that that's that it has to be a faulty thing. Yeah, I don't think that's
That might be real it might that's a thing. I really was questioning
I didn't bring it up because I didn't want him to be freaked out
I'm sure he has no idea like the max heart rate is but
Yeah, man, it was fun, dude. We got to get you to in the gym going crazy. Yeah, I remember
Do you wear like like the fitness bands of anything like that like like a fit Apple watch?
Yeah, I have an Apple watch that Cameron's fiance sold me for like 25 bucks, but it's the first version
So it doesn't do anything except basically track your heart rate
So I do that I and I remember to charge it maybe every tenth time I go to the gym
Yeah, one of my favorite things about those is they'll like try and tell you how many calories you burned like exercising
Yeah, and it's always so funny how wrong it is. Yeah, it will say that you burned like
4,000 calories doing a run for 20 minutes. Yeah, I remember I had to come off of DDR and it'd be like you burned
700 calories in the last hour and I'm like that is
Really can't be true
It's like
the Apple stuff like really like
Lenient with the how many steps it counts for you. Like I think it's
Fuckin hope not dude, cuz I'm getting like 15k steps a day and I feel this is a huge point of pride in my life
Right. So if that is wrong, then I have to rethink a lot of things that I tell people
I think it might be wrong. I think you should look into like getting in
Just like if you walk like two miles, that's like 10,000
No, I think five miles is 10,000
Depends on how big your step is. Well, I take little tiny. Yeah, I do like a Dexter's
laboratory style
Mr. Mr. Krabs, did you think that's how I walk? I think huge steps
Yeah, yeah, so if you're striding that's like you're not gonna get your steps in
Let's see. I will yo coat because he takes big steps. Yeah, that's why he gets 300 steps a day
Right is cuz the big steps his steps are so big
I probably I'd say I walk probably a mile and a half round trip to the dog park a day
Two miles round trip to the office every day and a mile round trip to the gym every day
So it's like five miles or something booth if I go do it one extra thing I get to about 15,000 steps, right?
Yes, I feel fine about
But I don't believe anybody who says that I don't understand how people like lose weight by like
Walking for an hour a day that makes no you must be eating nothing if you're doing that
Yeah, like my grandpa lost like 50 pounds walking for an hour a day
If you go from doing nothing to something you will like lose a little bit of weight. I
Guess you're right like walking. It's like yeah, you just maintain because you burn calories, you know, I
Really I need to stop recently. I've started getting back into I got a stop it man
I've started getting back into candy
Which is bad, I've never bought candy I know
Okay, I bought here's what happened man
Halloween came around right and a month ago
Yeah, so I did it's been a month-long love affair with candy
Here's what I had to do the other day man all those M&Ms that I bought from from the M&M store
Which was the first time buying adult candy was buying M&Ms at the M&M store
Adult candy as an adult. I bought the M&Ms. I came home. I would eat six M&Ms every day
This is how fucking psycho I am about this kind of thing
I wouldn't let myself have more than six M&Ms, but I would always have six M&Ms
I did this for like one week and then I was like
I like ate six M&Ms and walked away from the pantry and did this I went and
then walked back to the pantry and threw away all of the M&Ms there's probably a
hundred fifty M&Ms left. You could have just given them the jam. No dude no I
can't have them dude I had to throw them away that's how much because I can't
control myself in more than I have one moment of self-control and with that one
I threw it away!
6 M&Ms is 100 calories when it's the brownie fudge M&Ms!
I can't be affording an extra 100 calories for no reason? I should eat 3 apples!
Those are really fire.
That's so funny.
So now I'm trying to change it around, now I'm switching out my candy for pineapple.
And today I've had 1 and a half pineapples.
Just addicted to peanut butter.
I'm drinking these little naked juices. That's my sweet.
There we go, see that's fruit.
This is good man.
Yeah, 140 calories.
That's good to have.
And then maybe probably 900 calories of like goldfish.
The snacks will kill you man.
The snacks are the worst.
The snacks will destroy you bro.
I also had to throw away my plantain chips.
Damn.
Because there were both of them?
No dude.
Because I love them so much.
I fucking love plantain chips. Salt and vinegar plantain chips are my favorite thing on earth.
You love them too hard.
And I love them too hard.
There's potassium in them, it's good for you.
Dude, it's fucking fried potatoes basically.
A plantain is a fucking potato.
No, it's a banana, isn't it?
No, it's a different thing.
It's basically, in terms of carbs, it's the same nutritional profile as a potato basically.
So it's just a potato chip.
You ever seen a fat Irish person?
Yes!
Yeah, a podcast with one. Never mind.
What are you talking about?
What the fuck are you talking about?
I've never seen a fat Irish person.
Cam went to Ireland and came back and said that he was the fattest people he's ever seen in his life.
These people are, these people have the worst diet.
He said they eat Thanksgiving every meal.
This is not...
Of course fat Irish people are fucking fat.
Oh wait, my Thanksgiving review.
Oh yeah, first Thanksgiving.
Thanksgiving is so magical.
magical I never knew we loved it so good in a with their friends with their
friends yeah and have the whole friends over to have an awesome meal wow it was
amazing yep I'll give it a loved it guys a nine out of ten Wow that's amazing
you guys don't have anything like Thanksgiving over there in Mexico pretty
much just Christmas we do like the just a big dinner on Christmas usually yeah
That is sad as fuck because Thanksgiving is the best holiday.
The green spaghetti.
You should just come to New York every Thanksgiving.
I want to eat the green spaghetti, I still haven't had this shit.
I'll try it.
We'll see how it goes.
I really, I'm kind of shaken up by my experience with CVP.
They don't really fuck with me so much.
Oh yeah, yeah, you got kind of yelled at by Border Patrol.
I'm trying not to take three trips to the US every single year maybe.
Maybe we'll just lay back to two and one road trip
Maybe we'll do
Thanksgiving in Mexico next year
That's right, and you can cook us all sorts of Mexican food
Okay
Chili reeno. That's my dad's favorite thing. I
I'm gonna be honest with you. I don't really fuck with that, but yeah, we can do that
But you're gonna make it for my dad man. He's coming. It's coming. Yeah, bitch. Okay. I'm bringing Dave
Everyone can bring a family speaking of family and festivities. Can I ask you about Phil's birthday?
Yes, I had a birthday party for my dog and yes Rex didn't come you didn't invite me
You I thought I invited you that's on me I was I literally was planning to get mad at you for not coming on this
I forgot
Low key. Well, hang on from what I saw from the Instagram stories
I thought it was some sort of like you can only come if you have a dog or deal. Nope. Nope
It was just feeling clancy Rex definitely could have come. I thought he was in the group chat that I texted about it
I guess not. Oh, yeah. No, I'm not
Well, all right. Well, you can come to his birthday next year, you know by God's grace that he lives that long
You're gonna eat guys
50 M&Ms Phil turned two years old y'all
He'll turn two years old man. This is a big milestone for a dog. That's 14, dude
Feelings are starting to bubble up in his stomach for different girl dogs
And he can't act on them because his balls have been obliterated
His penis is about a quarter of the size that it once was he's not gay anymore
Nope, he's really he's lost his gay impulses. Damn. I
Can't believe I didn't you weren't invited Rex
I think I brought it up last night. I was like, yeah and Rex couldn't even fucking respond to the
Yep, that's just the kind of guy I am yeah not very conscientious, but that's okay
Well, I forgot you lived in New York cuz I haven't seen you in so long damn I
Don't have a chance of that. I'm busy. Yeah. Oh, yeah, he's too busy
He moves to New York and he doesn't and where all of his friends live and instead of seeing his friends
He doesn't see his friends guys. You know what the hell is wrong with him?
The thing is you have you have SNL hours, you know, they always say I
Think your microphone cut off. Yeah, what's the no it didn't bitch. It's 10. No, it didn't you fucking bitch
And it's back right? Yeah, that's amazing
Listen, you have SNL hours, which means you work until 4 in the morning, right?
You work like 6 p.m. To 4 in the morning if you woke up at 7 and you worked until 5
You'd live a normal life. I would I'm trying I uh, I
actually set myself back worse because I was working like 11 to 8 and
Now I'm waking up at like 2 30 in the afternoon. Yeah, that's terrible man. It's horrible. It's horrible because it gets like
Dark out at 430. Yeah, you need to wait you need one night or one day
You just need to wake up at 7 a.m
And then you'll keep doing that as long as you don't stay up too late after that
You just need to make yourself wake up at 7 1 day
730 on
It is fun Wednesday, and then I took a nap and just completely fucked it
Yeah, I've been having really scary napping dreams recently
I've been napping a lot and it's been putting me into a dream world where I had to explain
a fluffernutter sandwich to somebody in my dream last night.
A fluffernutter sandwich, it's marshmallow fluff and nutter, which is peanut butter.
And it is an amazing sandwich.
Well, you don't need to put the banana on, I don't really do the banana.
Did you talk about my crazy dream that I had while I was sleeping on Kim's couch?
Please tell me, man.
- Well, it's not very much to tell,
but it was both Patrick and Cameron were in my dream,
and they were both speaking perfect English,
perfect Spanish.
- Okay.
- It was just so crazy to me,
and then I don't think anything happened.
They were just talking to me in Spanish.
- Oh wait, that's interesting.
Do you ever have dreams in English?
- I don't think so.
I don't really--
- Wow.
- All your dreams are in Spanish?
- I don't remember dreams often,
So I wouldn't really tell you I just remember that because I woke up and in campus couch
And I was like that is so crazy. This couch is giving me powers. I think
Dream about your friends. Yeah guys
Honestly Cameron and Patrick have been in at least three of my dreams every week for probably four years at this point. Yeah. Yeah
That's how much I'm thinking about these two and it's always us at a water park
It's never like how dreams are sometimes or something scary is happening
It's always us at a restaurant or us doing a roller coaster or something. It's never a bad dream with these two
highly recommend
You two on the other hand every night is a nightmare with you two in it
The complete evil versions of my other two friends. It is true. We are the evil versions of came and Pat
Yep, you look kind of bizarre world versions of them
Yes, you are fully yeah, so you have the size where Patrick is the big one
That's you Juvio and Rex is the small Cameron. Yes
It really is scary that I keep finding myself surrounded by two guys that look exactly like
Them do you think you're Mario?
Do I think you know, this is a question I've thought about a lot
(laughing)
- No, no, I couldn't be Mario.
- Yeah, I think so.
- Why couldn't be Mario?
'Cause Mario's too, I'm too stoic to be Mario, man.
Mario wears his heart on his sleeve.
When he gets lava on his bum,
he runs around and goes, "Ai, ai, ai."
Me? - You do something like that.
- I wouldn't even tell anybody if I had lava on my bum.
- You're kind of Bowser to me.
- Thank you, man, thank you.
You have the statue of a football.
is
You're a fucking Goomba, man.
I think you are a Goomba.
Racial slurs, I mean.
I think it, the more I'm thinking about it, you are a full Goomba from the ground.
From the ground?
That's where they're from, man, they pop out of that shit.
Yep.
And Jubio is completely-
Then why, when they go back into the ground, do they die?
Well they get squished, but nice try, man.
Well if they come from the ground, they should be able to go back into it.
Okay, I'm not gonna argue with a Goomba, man.
Shut up.
(laughs)
- Juvio is Petey Piranha.
Silent, but big.
- And his breath is low-key fire.
- Yep, yep, straight up.
I mean, everybody has a full Mario crew
if they look around hard enough.
- Yeah, yeah, everyone's got the Mario.
- When are they gonna make another WarioWare game?
- They just did.
- Oh, well, that's amazing news.
I don't know, they just did one like last, I think two weeks ago.
Where are they gonna go with these?
You already, in the old ones you could already pick a man's booger.
I think it's time to kill off the Switch.
That's my idea.
That's my take.
Okay.
Can I also do what with it?
Let's enter the gaming corner for a minute.
I think I agree.
The Switch has been out for what, 10 years?
Yep, basically.
Almost?
Since 2015 or something?
Mario Kart 8 is 10 years old, basically.
Yeah, that's crazy. I
I bought a switch in like
2018 maybe and it was I'd already felt it felt so old then yeah, I like I couldn't believe I was like fuck
They're about to come out with another one as soon as I get this shit
Didn't happen man. It will never
Didn't fucking happen. They should make a new switch. There's this is
Switch to work consoles. And by the way, this is this is the new wave. This is a new way
You're addicted you're addicted to your big phone with joysticks
I
Can't believe that I funded this habit. Yes
Like two full days just like
Just a setting up emulators
I'm just I I have a I have a switch with Mario Kart 8 and like all the DLC and
I just like got it all from and I've been playing it on the plane and on the bus
Like you wait you been you've been playing us a hacked switch. Yeah, basically, that's bloody illegal
I mean this man is admitting to crimes. There's no wonder Border Patrol doesn't want to fuck with you
man, fuck what a patrol
Don't say that shit. Don't say that
Yeah
Just say I respect
Authority, I police. Yeah Cartman style. I thought I thought that maybe I would end up buying a steam deck
But then I realized that there's nothing that I would ever want to play on it that I wouldn't just want to play
I don't travel. I mean, I guess I travel a lot. But when I travel I just look at my phone
Well, you just want to play Valorant is the problem
Exactly or one indie game a year
But I don't need a steam deck to play that if I want to play the outer wilds
I'm not gonna play that on which by the way amazing game if anybody hasn't played it
Run don't walk you haven't played the outer wilds man. Maybe I'll play it on this dude. Do you like fucking?
Existential bullshit
Wait, you love the thing instead of game. Yes
I'm gonna get into the video
With Kim, dude, I I don't I'm not fucking with the I the only games
I like are competitive shooters and like walking simulators that you make your girlfriend play to get into video games. That's it
I only like Valorant and dear Esther CS go and what remains of Edith Finch. I
like I like
fucking
overwatch -
And gone I'm just about to say and gone home
I couldn't think of another competitive shooter, but I do like gone home man
That's the only kind of thing I like but I also recently I'm starting to get into games that are scary in a way
That it's different from other games
I've started to get into games where you open it up. You start playing it and you're like, this is interesting
This is a bit weird and then it turns out that it's a haunted game. Are you familiar with this kind of game? No
and
games. How do I find it?
YouTube videos, man.
Yeah, I watch YouTube videos.
It called the scariest game ever, and it's two and a half hours long.
That's what I watch when I do the dishes.
There should be a game that says, boo, what's
what's more baby behavior?
Just watching how a video essays and get influenced by them
or just playing the same racing games they used to play on the PS2.
Probably the YouTube video when racing games are fun.
I used to play I just played dirt three or dirt four. I just played dirt before I
Used to play it way back in my WTF with mark Barrett era what was happening in dirt for I
used to play dirt three and
Listen to WTF with mark Baron. I'd probably play that for six and a half hours a day
That's not like what tribes ascend was out. I would only ever play tribes ascend and dirt three, you know
I'm almost tribes ascend and fucking she played rocket League. I
Played a little bit of rocket League never got that into it because I always played with mouse and keyboard
So we should get into that we should we should make a team which makes this you can't turn the rocket League. I'm down. Yeah, I
Feel like it's something I'd be good at I'm good at sports good at every single sport. I've ever played
It is hard the way that they they do when they do flips and they like meet the ball in there
Yeah, a lot you lost me man
The amount of times I've done that and just like kind of slap the ball down with no speed whatsoever
Yeah, just kill it. Yeah
It's pretty depressing when the thing is man
I've
competitive games have kind of been ruined for me by playing one that I'm good at because the idea of somebody like me entering a
Competitive lobby who's like really bad at a game like Rocket League. I just know that I'm pissing people off and actually ruining their nights
Well, you can do 1v1s. There is competitive 1v1. Yeah
Which is really yeah, oh, that's smart. Yeah, so that's what we're making a team
So we just piss each other off and we're like you are really bad at this game and we stopped playing it after one night
Yeah, cuz the most you can play is with up to three people
But I played the the hoops version. I probably put 200 hours. I hate that's such a stupid game mode
I love just basketball version. Yeah. Yeah, it sounds fun. Yeah, it was awesome. It's not fun
There's a tip-off
Yeah, that makes more sense to me because I don't fuck with soccer much man. Yeah soccer is gay I am from America
You guys need to open your hearts to new experiences. I wish I could hit a ball to the goal. That was far away
Oh, I wish I could kick a ball. That's so far. Okay. Wait, is that way are you being sorry in this impression?
Are you being a guy playing soccer is like I wish I could kick a ball
Yeah, I think he just does it man. I think that's the whole game
I wish I could
It's not boring using fucking a third of your body to play a game stupid
You should either use 1% of your body
I agree hands or all of your body you guys need to get into the rugby down there in the south. Yeah, I
think
people like like
Like school like American football
Like University like college American football rather
Do they play it in at Mexican universities? Yeah
Really?
That's just like two teams
In my town have any of those guys ever gone to the NFL. I think one of them
Over like one case, but I don't I don't remember his name. I can look it up later
But yeah, it has that been before but it's really it's not like big enough for it to like be an actual professional league
But it's a college like sports that some people follow
Wow college football really has grabbed the attention of fathers all over the entire world. That's an amazing. Yeah
Revelation that I'm having right now. Well, cuz it's a regional, you know, yeah, I guess you're right
It's specifically my town versus this other town, right? That's about football man growing up
We had the we I mean college football is pretty big in North Carolina
I would say big college basketball is way bigger, but our football team is the Carolina Panthers. So it's both right
It's both care. We didn't even get one just for North Carolina and and we fucking hate South Carolina from they put mustard and barbecue, man
Mustard in their barbecue sauce, isn't that crazy?
I'm not crazy
sense did. But go down to Myrtle Beach and tell them that, and they'll probably fall
over because they're so addicted to drugs. That's right. Yeah, see, even now I can't
help but barbing my neighbors down south. Yeah. And also, they were the, this isn't
probably true, but they were the last people to leave the Confederacy. I believe it, and
so do you. Yeah. Okay. And North Carolina didn't even want to be in it, man. North Carolina
hated being in the fucking confederate oh god we hated the confederacy more than
anything dude but but yeah but we wanted friends you guys have you ever wanted
friends so bad that you join a racist militia yeah yeah exactly it's happened
and
to get a kid a pair of pads and a stick.
- Yeah.
There's no like booster support for hockey.
You gotta be like into hockey to play.
- Yeah, you have to have, yeah.
There's not like, there's no rich man
who's giving out scholarships to buy hockey clothes.
- Yeah, whereas football, they'll put any man in pads.
Any boy. - Exactly.
They put me in pads, man.
I was huge when I was a kid.
I was bigger as a kid than I am now.
- Yeah.
I was like 11 years old. I was a complete machine with football. I had no idea what I was doing
They called me butterfingers because I couldn't catch a pass
but I was the biggest kid and I played center and
I
Could block anybody man
there was a there was a couple of seasons where I I was 11 and
I they had to move me up into the next age range. So I was the youngest kid in my entire division because I
couldn't make the weight for the 11 year olds and so I had to play with the 12 and 13 year olds and
There was two different games where I didn't even make weight for that division because I was so fat
Yeah, so I just had to sit there on the sidelines fatly
Cheering on my team because I did I was I was under 115 pounds. That's sick
Yeah, it was awesome in this one time
I played so much Mario Tennis on the GameCube that I went and took tennis lessons for like a year.
That's awesome. This one time you did something for a year? Yeah. Wow, that's a big, that's a very big commitment.
Were you good at tennis? I don't think so. Was it the Mario Tennis for the Game Boy where you don't even play as fucking Mario?
No, the GameCube. Oh.
I played the one on Game Boy and it's like you're playing like infinite jest.
You're not even, you're just like a random kid at a tennis school.
Okay, yeah, it really it didn't make any sense to me there's an almost no Mario
It's really sad he's on the fucking front of the cartridge let me be Mario man
Yeah, I don't want to make my own guy. I don't play Caleb at the at the tennis school
All right, man Mario baseball
Almost baseball fun. That is true. Mario baseball was really fun
I wish that's how it worked in I wish that that's exactly how baseball worked in real life
Where if you got three Dominican guys you put them in an outfield together because they will jump on each other's heads to kiss
the ball
That really is how baseball should work that would be so amazing chemistry
What do you think it's legal to jump on someone's head yeah, of course it is anything goes
Yeah
It's more legal than jumping on your opponent's head for sure
All right, and make sense to me
There's only one thing that's illegal to do in sports
And that's be Josh Giddey. That's right
That's right free Rex's boy
All right
guys another amazing episode of beer cast about
Drink about drink. This is your host Caleb signing off. I
Love yo, bitch ass. This is your host next week. It's gonna be a normal time that it comes out
It was weird this week because of me. Goodbye. I'm the host. Bye. Should I do my camera down here from now on?
Yeah
That's intimate
Yeah, I should do it down here. Nope, okay
Nope and it's over. Goodbye problem with this man