[Sipping]
[Burping]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer broadcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my
chuggers? I'm trying to get that
[Gagging]
This is a journey
into sea, into the middle of the planet,
Bud Light.
Ha!
Foo Rippin'!
Beers we drank, motherfucker, with Juvio, Caleb, and Rex.
Yo.
I'm surprised you fucking stupid bastard from Mexico.
Hold on.
Oh my god, look at that.
OK, would we like to go one by one?
Yeah, Rex, why don't you go first?
We could pick on this how you can.
You're completely muted.
I'm completely muted?
(laughing)
- Participant Rex is having a problem.
- He's just muted, he can't hear a single word you're saying.
- Yeah, cannot read properties of ordified readings.
- All right. - Okay.
- Can you hear me again?
- Yeah, you're very loud though.
- Oh my God, sorry.
- What about now?
- What's wrong with you?
- My microphone wasn't working.
- Oh no, it's so loud.
- You're so loud.
All right, what about now?
Really hot.
A little more.
Let me make sure, I can't even touch my settings.
Okay.
What about now, is this fine?
Maybe that's fine.
Just talk there.
Okay.
Now, what beer have you brought today?
I have a delicious Bud Light.
I got a tall Bud Light.
A tall boy Bud Light?
Yeah.
What did you get?
Well, go ahead, take a sip and give us a review.
- Hmm.
That's Bud Light, yum.
Four out of 10.
- Four out of 10, okay.
What'd you bring, Jibya?
- I brought a tall can, tall blue can of Bud Light.
- Hold the phone, what's going on here today?
- It's producing the choicest chops.
- The choicest chops. - Choicest chops.
- And barley malt.
- And rice. - And rice.
Wait, how did you know that?
- Well guys, let me show you why.
Because I too have a tall boy butt.
(laughing)
- Oh my God. - That's right.
Always brewed using the choicest hops,
best barley malt, and rice.
It doesn't say any, no kind of qualifier
for how good the rice is though.
- I don't think mine has any rice.
- The best hops, the best barley malt, and some rice.
- I'm gonna take some rice.
- Well, hold on.
- I'm gonna take a sip.
- Hold on, what do you call a choice thing, the best thing?
- Oh, oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, that is near orgasmic how amazing that beer is.
I'm gonna give that, hold on, one more sip.
- My dick could still come, I would definitely
give that a 10 out of 10.
- What?
- I'm gonna give that a six three.
And the only reason it's not higher
is because a Bud Light tastes like a worse Coors Light,
if you ask me.
It tastes like a watered down Coors Light.
But it is a great beer.
- Coors Light's a six five.
- A Coors Light is a seven on my scale.
I love a Coors Light.
- Oh, I thought we were doing it on basketball heights.
So it's like a five to--
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Hang on, hang on.
- Okay, okay, no, this is good.
This is the new scale for beers we drank.
This is how, so who's the shortest basketball player ever?
I think Muggsy Bogues, I think he was five foot three maybe?
- Sure, yeah.
- The tallest ever was maybe Bol, no sorry.
Maybe Manute Bol, he was seven foot seven.
- Yeah.
- Something like that.
So let's say five three to seven foot seven.
So everybody let's go around
and redo our ratings for these beers.
- All the beers so far?
- I mean no, this beer.
Just this beer.
Oh, OK.
This isn't Eric Bledsoe.
This is 6'2".
I have to-- guys, I have to break the news to you guys.
Yep.
I never once--
You only know centimeters.
I never once in my life have ever watched
a single second of NBA basketball.
Well, you don't-- do you know what a height is?
You can just say height.
Michael Jordan.
Michael Jordan is 6'6".
Michael Jordan of beers, right here.
OK.
Well, don't say that.
This is a Steve Nash, six foot three,
cucked by his wife.
He got cucked by his wife?
Yeah.
Oh, poor Nash, dude.
He had a hard life, man.
He did.
He lost out on an NBA championship,
and I guess he got cucked by his wife, I just found out.
Isn't that a coach?
Steve Nash?
Yeah, he's a coach now.
I think he's an assistant coach now.
Yeah, he got fired from being a head coach.
Yeah, he used to be basically one of the best white boys
to ever do it in the NBA.
I would say probably the best.
No, Larry Bird, the second best
American white boy to ever play
in the NBA, probably.
OK.
And he's Canadian too.
And how about this?
God damn it!
Fuck!
Non-European.
Yeah, I knew what you meant.
Yeah.
So what is that your favorite
NBA player?
Yeah.
No, my favorite NBA player is Mike
Bibby.
Look up a picture if you want to
know why. Look up Mike Bibby. Kevin Love. Yeah, I like players like Mike Bibby, Kevin Love.
Wait, hold on. Paul Wall. Paul Wall is a great player. No, John Wall, I'm sorry. John Wall
is not white. I see. Yeah, Paul Wall is an American rapper. 100%. John Wall is a black
guy who played for the Wizards. You are thinking of Paul Wall, the rapper.
I just assume all walls are white.
So where should one start if someone has never watched NBA basketball sport?
Actually I have a good recommendation. The way I got into the NBA was by playing it but
also by playing NBA 2K. Because if you play 2K, I'm sure this is similar with like FIFA
or something.
You play 2K, you learn all the players
and all the rules and stuff.
And also you make a guy whose name is like
Mr. Krabs and you go 82 and O
and average 150 points a game.
It's like basically the most fun video game you can do.
- And you wish that there was a real life Mr. Krabs
out there in the league.
- I literally, this is embarrassing to admit,
I pretty much every single time I've played,
I've made a My Character, My Player on NBA 2K.
I make a version of me, a guy who kinda looks like me,
but he's like six foot 11 and he's mixed.
(laughing)
- Well I love that 2K has like an app
that you can upload your face into.
- Yeah, I've never done that.
- Yeah, it doesn't work.
- Could you use it for like recreational use
and not to create a guy for 2K?
- Like can you scan your face with it for no reason?
Yeah, just like save the picture for no reason.
- Just take, you're saying you're inventing a photo app?
Where you take a photo of your face?
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
- Save the picture?
- A face scanning app.
- Oh, okay.
- That saves your face as a scan into a 2K player.
- I'm sure you could export it in some way.
Yeah, and then you could use a connect,
and then you could do some like,
a Planet of the Apes mo-cap kind of stuff.
- I've been thinking a lot about apps recently.
- Why?
I think I'm gonna become an app sky. I told Rex about one of my ideas like a month ago
What was your idea?
I think I told you
like in the dead of night
in the middle of night
In the dead of night I told him about my app idea
Sorry I have a brain full of my own app ideas
Yeah
Which are better than yours
No I wanna hear yours
Okay do you wanna tell them what my idea was
No I don't remember
You tell it
I, in the middle of the night, I sent him,
Rex, we should make an app.
We should make a fax app.
And he was like, what is that?
And I was like, like a fax.
- F-A-C-T-S or F-A-X?
- F-A-X. - F-A-X, okay.
- Yeah, and he wasn't too, he didn't love it,
for, I could tell.
- For one, there is already an app
that you can use your phone to scan documents
and then send it as a PDF,
which I think is quite literally what you're talking about.
- Well, but I guess the only thing would be
that you could send it to a fax number.
- Yeah, you could always send it to a username
that you know on the community app, fax app.
- No, it wouldn't be a fax, no.
You're already ruining your app.
- How am I ruining it?
- 'Cause you're making it not make any sense.
It's not a fax if it's just a thing
where you send people scans of documents
who also have the app.
It's not a fax at all.
I mean, that's true.
- This is awful.
I could use the fucking Notes app to scan a document.
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna be completely honest.
I thought at the time that the idea,
I had a good idea for an app,
but I don't really recall it correctly.
But I mean, I don't even really care
about the facts app that much, honestly.
I've just been brainstorming.
- Okay, what ideas do you have, Rex?
- My app that I truly want to make
is one that just applies to jobs for you.
Just use--
- Oh, you've told me that before.
That is a genius idea.
- Yeah, yeah, just like a chat GPT thing
that fills out like a job application for you.
- Why not make that?
You know how to program.
It's easy.
- I told someone this and they said it already exists
and I tried to find it and I didn't find it.
But I do think it's a good idea.
I think I would pay like $5 a month.
- Like if Indeed offered that?
- Yeah, I feel like that's a no-brainer for,
if you could build it and then sell it to Indeed,
that'd be easy.
I have an idea for an app where you,
basically you can go on the app
and you can see all of your friends.
You can add friends, you can minus friends,
you can have a wall, a profile photo,
and you can put your relationship status on it,
but the catch is that you have to have
a harvard.edu email address.
- That's really smart.
- Do you think this is good?
- I think you will have to be learning Chinese, buddy.
- Oh shit!
That already exists, doesn't it?
- Yeah.
- Oh shit.
- I think you're gonna be excluding a lot of people
with that idea.
- I think they should make that,
but they should only allow Chinese people.
It's all harvard.edu email addresses, but and then my email address. So when
they're talking about I'm studying for this bio Kim final, I can comment on
whatever I want and say sup
because wouldn't that be wouldn't that is that like the dream to be the face
or the myspace tom to just be able to just do whatever you know, everyone
hates you. Everyone hates the everyone loves tom. He was my first friend.
- You were not on MySpace.
You were not on MySpace.
- I was on MySpace, are you crazy?
- You were 17 years old right now.
- I was on MySpace, I was 11 years old.
I put my height as five foot three, it was a one inch lie.
And I put my body type as more to love.
And my top eight--
- That's a one inch lie you've done.
(laughing)
- My top eight was my brother,
Little John and my brother's friends.
- Nice. - Top three.
- Well, his friends were multiple.
- A bunch of, all of his friends.
- Oh, okay.
- Whatever, I think I only had 16 friends or something.
But I was really, I think I deactivated it
'cause I was scared of being molested
because my dad said that that could happen online.
- Which I don't think you would have had to worry about.
- No, it was more to love.
- Would either Rex or me make it
into your top eight these days?
- Top eight, oh, for sure.
- Thank you.
- You know what, just because I know how you two are,
I would make you battle for the eighth spot.
- Yeah, I was gonna say.
There could only be one of us.
- Yeah, 'cause it'd be kind of embarrassing
if my top eight was like Cam, Pat, you two, Patches,
Tom.
- Yeah, Tom.
Just round it out.
- I think it'd be funny if it was still just your brother
and seven of his friends.
They're not even your friends.
- I think it would be funny to have that
and have it be all of us.
And then like Tom is the eighth
and then your wife just out.
- Yeah, she's, "Oh baby, you were nine, I'm sorry."
Didn't Justin Timberlake buy MySpace at some point?
- No, he bought the music window.
- I think he bought MySpace.
- Well, I think MySpace turned into a music thing.
- Yeah.
- I remember I had this history teacher
that would upload face-melting guitar solos.
- I bet they were.
We were friends with your teacher on Myspace?
No, but we all looked at it.
*burp*
Oh, you would go and find him?
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
He had one of those extremely Nazi-ass German names.
He was dope.
Yeah?
He got stabbed in the head and his eye twitched.
What?
And he spent all of his money on custom guitars.
And drank nothing but Mountain Dew. He was dope.
This guy is a beast.
Yeah.
Wait, what?
- At the front desk lady fired 'cause he fucked her
and they found out.
- Whoa!
- And he kept his job? - Wait, they fired her
for fucking her?
- Yeah, for fucking her.
- For fucking him?
- Yeah, yeah.
And he and her drove the same car, BMW Z3.
- That's why they had sex. - Fire, yep.
- You can have sex with almost anybody
that drives the same car as you.
- Yes.
- You have everything to talk about.
- Of course.
- Don't you wish the air conditioner,
don't you wish it got a little colder, a little faster?
- Don't you wish people would stop breaking into your car?
(laughter)
- Licking your steering wheel?
Don't you hate when your steering wheel
smells like my breath?
I mean, some guy's breath.
(laughter)
- I saw a picture on Twitter that was like,
it was like a note on someone's car that was like,
"I'm tired of breaking into cars.
"Here's my cash app.
"Just like, give me so I won't break into your car."
I was like, that's smart.
I should start doing that.
- We should fix the San Francisco situation.
What's going on with all the damn crime up there?
- Oh yeah, I saw the Mark Rober video
where he puts, where he puts his,
have you seen those videos
where he makes a little prank box?
- Yeah, I think it's funny how he keeps trying
to make it seem like it's like a thing for charity
or like he's doing good in the world,
but it's just like a proto jail
to destroy like every single poor person
in the world thing.
- Yeah, poor people, their lives aren't hard enough.
Let's cover them in glitter
and make them smell like farts.
(laughing)
This is good, Mark Grover.
Yeah, that's the funny thing about those.
- Every comment's like, "Yeah, that kid thought
"he was gonna get a PS5 for free.
"Fuck you, kid, you fucking, you're a criminal."
- Every comment is, "Justice has officially been served."
And then you watch the video and it's four kids
in a storage unit that they live in,
and none of them can't speak any English,
they have no eyes, they don't even know
what's happening to them.
They open the thing, they're just kidding.
They honestly, some of them, I've seen this,
I've watched all the videos,
some of them literally think that that's what a PS5 does
'cause they don't know any better.
They open the box, it sprays fart spray in their mouths.
- Yeah, they just-- - It calls the cops.
- Sit there and look at it for like half a minute
and they're like, "Let's just throw this out.
"I don't think this is what it's supposed to be doing."
- I think I don't like PlayStations.
I think I'm an Xbox kind of kid.
- Yeah, he should just make one,
he should just start making those machines explode.
- He also, if he really wants to catch villains,
he needs to make it appeal more to a villain.
What does a villain want to do with a PlayStation?
You know, he's busy plotting.
He should make it-- - He wants to shoot
in online video games.
- He should tie up one of them on,
well no, that doesn't make any sense.
- He wants to use a bot.
he should put one near a train track
and make it look like,
do a ballistics dummy that looks like a woman,
or just use a real woman, I don't care.
And then put it,
and then maybe a big bundle of rope right next to her.
- Yeah.
- And say villains, villains of San Francisco have at it.
- Well, one of them, one year was,
I thought it was really funny
because it was like the Oculus VR headset box.
- Yeah.
- And I was like, no one knows what this is.
(laughs)
Like just go back to like putting like headphone boxes or like an iPhone box.
Yeah. That was the video,
the most recent one where people are just like cracking the windows on the,
the like the cars. Yeah. It's pretty cool, man.
It kind of seems like a cool job.
Yeah. Window breaker into?
Yeah. Window break.
Well, they got it down to a science. It's so, it's so, they do it so quick.
They break into the back window and they open up your back seat
to see if you've got anything in the trunk.
And then if they don't see anything, they just leave.
- Yeah, they say it a lot.
- Have you guys ever been thieved from?
- Yes.
- Have I talked about the time my house got broken into
and none of my stuff got stolen?
- I don't think you've talked about this on the podcast.
I know you've told me before.
What happened?
- So, where I lived, there was a group of,
Let's call it low-income housing, like in the alley behind us.
Yeah, let's call it low-income housing.
I mean, that's what it was. It was like section 8 stuff.
You wanted to call it the ghetto.
It was not. But it just happened to be where it was.
The hood!
Anyway, the way our house was set up was there was like a porch
to like go out and smoke cigarettes on.
And there was a sliding glass.
Is that what it was for?
That's what they built it!
That's what they built it?
[laughter]
So you had a smoking section in the house.
Yeah, big sliding glass door.
So you could see in and then there was like my one roommate and I both had like
desktop computers, like gaming computer setups and shit.
And, um, you know, I have my three monitors and shit.
He had his set up across from mine.
And then like in the room just next to it, there is like a TV and like a PS4
and Beats headphones and a laptop.
and they like broken through the sliding glass door.
They ripped this like blanket that I was using like off of my
desk took a look at myself and was like not for me.
Thanks tried to steal by other roommates desktop.
It got caught on the wires.
They just dropped it and it like shattered on my girl and
then they stole my other roommate his TV his ps4 his beats
headphones both of the laptops.
It's just like all this stuff.
It just did me, just like looked at mine and was like,
"Yeah, I'm good on that." And then, just like...
Yeah, I mean honestly you wish they stole it. That is so insulting.
I was honestly, I was so happy. I was like,
"Oh my God, I'm so sorry this happened to you."
This is so horrible. You're playing cookie clicker
on all three monitors as you talk to it.
Just nothing happened to my stuff.
Completely just untouched. They looked at it and said,
No thank you.
- Did your room perhaps look like
the way your current room looks like?
- No, 'cause they came in through an office,
and so it was just like a desk with computer equipment on it.
- Right, no. - And they thought
my computer was worse than my roommate's,
so they tried to steal his.
- Okay.
- Did his have more lights?
- Yes.
- Mm. (laughs)
That's why you don't put RGB in your fucking computer, man.
- Yeah, I had just a shitty case that looked bad.
- You want it to look very humble.
- Yeah.
Put it in like an old, some old HP case.
That's the move, honestly.
- It was a sleeper build?
- It was a sleeper build.
I mean, it was just--
- Sleepy build?
- It just looked like shit.
'Cause it was the first computer I built.
But like, it was very funny.
And just having to pretend to be like sad about it,
like nothing, you know, nothing happened to me.
I'm not too beat up in any way.
- Yeah.
- Uh, you know.
And then he's like, "Can we get my PS4?"
Like he's talking to the police and being like,
"Can we, you know, track my PS4?"
(laughing)
Meanwhile, I'm just still just playing video games.
And I remember that was during my Adderall snorting days
and the cop was like kind of taking like notes down
on everything that was like missing.
And like, I was sitting at my desk and didn't think about it
and there's just a rolled up $1 bill
dyed completely blue from all that Adderall.
(laughing)
Just like making eye contact with him about it
as he's staring at the record.
- It's not illegal to snort your own Adderall
that you have a prescription for?
- Exactly. - Yeah.
You can do, it's your medicine,
you can do whatever you want with it.
- Exactly.
That's 100% true.
- Fuck that cop.
- So, it's very funny. - Yeah, fuck him.
Did he even find anything from your roommates?
- Fuck no. - Stolen goods?
- What do, cops never retrieve anything.
- No, pretty much never.
It's always, I mean, unless it's a car,
they don't really try at all either.
- No, no.
- We should switch to like a no cops situation,
but we have like a Batman in every city.
- I've been saying this.
- I think that would solve every single crime in the world.
- I think that's why Rex wants to move to New York City, man.
- Yeah, to be Batman.
- Do you think I could be Batman?
I think you could be Batman for a couple of reasons.
- I think I could beat up like a poor person.
- Yeah.
- And get into like a internecine fight
with like some guy who likes to tell riddles.
- Yeah, that is the kind of folks
that you tend to attract, I would say.
- Yeah, yeah, I think I could get into a long fight
that destroys the city, accomplishes nothing
with a guy who dresses up in spandex.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, what's with all this heat for Batman?
You need to chill.
- Sorry. - Pointless fight.
He's trying to protect the city, you motherfucker.
What are you doing for Gotham?
- Yeah, but they destroy it in the end.
- Every superhero destroys every city.
Have you seen Man of Steel?
Literally 50 million people die in that movie
because Superman is punching Zob or Zod or Zog,
whatever his name is, through--
- Zog, he's punching the Zog.
(laughing)
- Superman versus Zog.
He's punching him through the Empire State Building.
- See, blonde hair, blue eyes Superman is really crazy.
(laughing)
- My dad got thieved from when I was a kid.
Somebody, he used to have these ferns,
they were the only things he loved in his life.
He had two ferns that sat out on his front porch.
- Would you sit between them?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
That was...
- What is that, is that even a joke?
Would you sit between, yes, okay.
Actually we would.
It was on the porch between,
it was literally the setup of the show.
It was a fern on either side.
Scott Aukerman must have walked by my dad's porch one day
and been like, this is the show.
- Was this a smoking porch or no smoking porch?
- My dad would smoke cigars out there.
So there was two rocking chairs,
a little table and a fern on either end of the porch.
- Yeah, they have a mama over there.
- Yeah, and my dad cared about these ferns so much.
He would take them inside when it was cold.
All he cared about were these ferns.
And one day somebody stole them and I've never seen him.
His voice went up two octaves and he was like,
"I just don't understand why you would take a fern.
"It doesn't make sense.
"And then he said, the funniest thing to me was he was like,
"and the thing is now they have to take care of them."
(laughing)
- He's right though.
- He's worried about the ferns.
- It's like stealing a dog.
It's like now you just have a responsibility.
- Yeah, now you have to take care of the ferns.
- I think that actually happened to my dad.
I remember one day, they used to have these donation boxes
outside of this Burger King we would go to,
where you could put clothing or whatever to donate.
And sitting right beside it, clearly meant for donation,
were these two porcelain dragons,
like Chinese dragons with tassels.
- Whoa.
- He whipped the car around, parked.
- Like father, like son, man.
Yeah, and just brought them into his home for years.
Uh, and he fucking dude, he was fucking, he loved those.
And then I think someone like broken and they like broke.
Oh, it was like, yeah.
And he was devastated.
Wow.
I've never seen the man.
So sad.
These criminals, man, we need to put it into all crime in this.
We need a Batman.
Batman barely stops any crime though, you know,
to be honest.
It's funny how one of the things on the new movie
you're like, yeah, the criminals are just scared of the night
because maybe I'm there, maybe I'm not.
And then they're like showing like--
There's one guy in a city of eight million people
who's running around, only at night by the way.
They're showing like four crimes happening at the same time
and he's not in a single one of them.
Yeah.
He's like on the train.
Motherfucker.
That's the thing, we need,
If you want to do a Batman thing, you really need 100 Batmans,
or 1,000 Batmans.
And maybe they should be wearing blue outfits and have guns.
[LAUGHTER]
And tasers, and they should be really fat.
They should not really do all that much.
They should be very, very-- just the minimum amount of training,
and just let them loose and see what happens.
That's my idea.
They should make sure they couldn't graduate from college.
Yeah, exactly.
They had to go to a college where
you shoot a gun in the air.
That's most of their assignment.
Yeah.
- When were you stolen from, Julio?
- I got mugged when I was a kid once.
- You were a kid?
- What kind of sick fucker--
- Was it another kid that mugged you?
- Who mugs a child?
- I don't know.
Some 17 year old, I don't know,
was in the street at night.
- How old were you?
- I don't remember.
I think I was like 15, 16 maybe.
- Did they take, what'd they take?
I think they took a bracelet that I had
and I didn't have anything else.
Maybe like a cell phone.
- I feel like this, it's, wait, sorry, what else?
- Well, we were walking back from the store,
it was me and my cousin.
We're walking back from the store
because we bought some sodas to drink to eat dinner.
- Don't tell me he took the soda.
- He took, he literally took one of the sodas.
- No, God. - One of them?
- Whose was it?
Yours or your friend's? - It's degenerate.
- I think mine.
- Oh no!
No! - I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry. - Yeah.
It was long ago, I don't really care about it anymore.
- I feel like getting a weapon--
- Did he have a weapon? - Is not a big deal anymore.
- What's up? - Did he have a weapon?
- No, it was three guys.
It was like a gang of criminals.
- Oh God, MS-13.
I hate that for you.
You know, this is funny, I always hear,
it's always the most giant people I know
who have been mugged?
- I was a kid.
- But you were probably the same height as you are now.
- I was completely not.
- When you were 17 or 16,
you weren't the same height as you are now?
- I don't remember.
- This guy has the worst memory, I can't remember.
He's acting like he was four years old.
- I do actually have really bad memory.
- I know, I work with you.
Yeah, so.
But yeah, a buddy of mine was mugged
and he's like six foot seven.
And he was just mugged by a lone guy.
And I just can't imagine why you would pick...
Pick a girl! What are you doing?
Right.
Here's the thing, right?
No one carries cash anymore.
Yeah.
So mugging is like...
And cell phones are...
It's so hard to steal a cell phone and have it be worth anything.
Right, because iPhones, they just get iCloud locked.
Yeah.
And it costs like $300 to get the tools to...
You literally have to kill somebody
and then take over their identity to steal a phone.
Yeah. I did... No, hold on.
I did look this up because I was thinking about it.
I wanted to-- - About doing it?
- Well, just converting all the ones
that are clearly stolen on eBay
into something that's sellable.
And it costs like $300 for the tool to do it.
And you have to know how to like solder.
And it's like, that's not worth it
to someone who's willing to rob someone for an iPhone.
- Yeah, I honestly don't know
what people get robbed for anymore.
Like they'll take, I mean,
even if they take a credit card or a debit card,
You can lock it. - Right, I'm just gonna call.
- Yeah, exactly, and they need your phone.
The only thing I've heard is if you're at an ATM,
they'll make you take the money out.
And that scares me so, so badly.
- But there's cameras on the ATM.
- Because I have an embarrassing pin code.
- What is it? - What is your pin code?
- 1111.
- That is embarrassing.
- It's 11, yeah, it's 1111.
So fuck me, right?
- Yeah, mine's 6969.
- It's my mom's birthday, okay?
- Yep.
- She was born-- - One, one, one, one.
- Yep, 11, 11. - The first of January
in 2011. - 2011, yes, yes.
How'd you know?
(laughing)
- Ah, she's quite young.
- She's a spring chicken.
- Yep. (burps)
- Oh my God, he's almost done with his Bud Light.
- Guys. (coughs)
- That was not a, how big, how many ounces are in that can?
- Yeah, this is--
- That does not look the same size as this can.
- I have a-- - They're all the same size.
- No, yours is definitely smaller.
- How many ounces is your can? - You have a medium boy.
- You're a small, you're a small--
How many ounces is your can?
Say it right now.
It says in milliliters, it doesn't say ounces.
Okay, so what is it?
It's 473 milliliters.
Oh, that's definitely not as big as this one.
This one's got to be 750.
Yeah, this is 740.
I'll check.
I'll check how much it is.
Yeah, that's a 16 ounce can.
This is a 24 ounce can.
You are a baby.
You're not rolling with the big dogs today.
Yeah, this is 16 ounces.
Yeah, these are 24, dude.
No wonder you're dumb.
Wait.
Whoa!
Oh!
Oh, my God.
He has three more. You're an alcoholic and you have a problem.
You think so? Yes!
Open one of those bad boys right now. Don't say that.
Open it. No, come on. Don't make me drink another beer.
Drink that beer you motherfucker.
Oh shit.
What?
Did it pop on you?
Wait, that's not fair anymore. Now I'm going to drink 32 ounces.
You're bigger than us.
24 ounces.
You're bigger than us. We're 5 foot 9. You're 6 foot 7.
Yeah, but I gotta drive home after this
Don't worry I have another beer after this as well
Whoa, okay. What was the first time you guys ever drunk-drived?
I don't really think I've ever drunk drove really
High drove plenty of time. Never mind me neither
Yeah, I've never been like to like I mean like drinks or whatever the drunkest ever been
And it was with you guys when you guys tried to poison me at that bar.
Oh yeah, I remember that.
But I distinctly remember once I went to my buddy's house because it was his birthday
and it was like on a Monday night.
So it was kind of an awkward day to be like drinking, but I was drinking anyways.
I was like, "Alright, well I got to go home now."
So I was drinking and then I drove home and then I showed up to work the next day.
but I wasn't always drunk.
We were drinking probably like some gay light beer.
The first time I was always very careful about drug driving when I was like
really young because I just was like cops in Wilmington.
There's like a checkpoint every single night going anywhere.
And every night. Yeah, pretty much. Yeah.
And if you're especially when I lived on the I lived on Pleasure Island,
this was the name of the island I lived on.
There's a bridge there that would always have a check.
Pleasure Island.
I live in the sexual island.
Locals only, man.
It wasn't.
It was locals only, especially in the winter.
But they always had a checkpoint there.
So, and if you're underage, man,
this is the most fucked up law in the world.
If you're underage, if you blow anything over a zero zero,
you get a DUI.
If you're under 21.
That is fucked up.
Isn't that one of the most awful things ever?
I do remember sorry but to cut you up but that was remind me one time I was drinking in the park with someone and I they spilled beer on my lap and then this was like after work so it was like midnight.
We go back to my car or i go to like drop them off and there's a cop like parked behind their car.
So they get out and the cop, I'm like, "Hey,"
you know, we're like talking to the cop to get him to move out of the way of the car.
And the cop is like, "You smell like beer."
And I was like, "No, I don't."
That's my smell!
That's just my natural smell.
And I was just like shooting the shit with him, he's this Asian dude, and I...
That's gonna come in later, folks.
He's like, "You don't seem very afraid of me."
And I was like, "Buddy, why does they come?"
I got no fear.
You said, "I'm white" to an Asian cop?
Yes, dude.
That's crazy.
I was a little drunk.
Oh my god.
That's the only time I can think of that I have drunk drugs.
Didn't he kill you?
Why didn't you just say, "Yeah, he spilled beer on me"?
Because I'm 17.
Oh god.
Well, you could have said, "I'm using this new deodorant.
It's a prank deodorant, but it's the only deodorant I can afford. I'm very poor.
It's my prank beer deodorant.
It's a prank beer deodorant. It's literally just for...
They bought it for moments like this.
When I talk to cops.
Yeah.
That's a good idea. A beer deodorant.
Wait, that's a wrap.
Well, not a wrap, but that's an invention.
Have you anything to drink tonight? Have I?
And then it's the beer drink.
You tell me.
No, it's worse than the deodorant.
- He's like, "Do you have deodorant?"
He's like, "Applying it."
(laughing)
- Smell my armpit, smell it.
You have to be really close.
- No, you smell like alcohol, you just spray him with it.
- That is actually an amazing idea.
That is an amazing fucking idea.
A pepper spray that smells like beer,
that doesn't hurt them.
It's like a skunk.
- And it's invisible.
- Yeah, it's like a skunk spray.
So like if you're in an argument with your girlfriend
She's like, I'm leaving.
You just spray her.
[LAUGHTER]
Spray her with a beer spray.
Fucking bitch.
Go ahead.
I know you're going to speed home.
I see what kind of man wants you fucking now, bitch.
Yeah, exactly.
You smell like beer, you bitch.
Get out of my house.
You're drunk.
Yeah, you're drunk.
Go home.
Oh, you're drunk.
Yeah, FaceTiming somebody.
She's drunk.
I can smell it on her.
Walking up to your roommate, she's fucked up.
You can smell it on her, bro.
She smells like fucking beer.
She doesn't mean it.
But it's still pepper spray, so she's on the floor.
She's so drunk she's crying and she has a red face.
No, that's wrong guys.
We can't do that.
Why?
That's a bad app.
I watched last night.
I watched the social network.
Is that where you got your app idea from earlier?
I didn't realize until right now, but yeah.
It was subconscious.
I got it on the intake.
- People forget Facebook was for Harvard students only.
- I will never forget, 'cause that movie is a 10 out of 10.
- You think so?
- That's like a six foot seven movie.
- That movie is pushing seven feet for me.
I love that movie, man.
That score, oh.
- Trent Reznor.
- You know what, Trent?
- I revisited it recently that I thought was,
I forgot that I really liked.
It's Men in Black.
- Men in Black?
That's a six foot nine.
- It is so good.
- That's an amazing movie.
- And it's so funny.
- Why did they not do a spin-off movie
about the cockroach guy?
- I agree.
- That is the funniest character of all time.
- And they should have done a spin-off movie
about the guy in the wheelchair from Wild Wild West.
- Yes, and also, if they do redo the,
if they make a reboot with the cockroach guy,
it should be Will Sasso.
- Yes. - That's my thoughts.
- He loved Will Sasso. - I think he would,
I think he would, I love Will Sasso.
Are you kidding me?
Those funny ass vines where he spits out a lemon?
(laughing)
That is the funniest shit ever.
- He ran Vine for one year.
- He was running that shit in a major way.
- Until he got took over by black people
doing racist jokes to themselves.
- He put water under the lemon.
People had spit out lemons for hundreds of years.
(laughing)
But nobody thought to put water behind the lemon.
This guy's a fucking genius.
- What does he do nowadays?
- Will Sasso, he does stand up.
He's always been a stand up.
- He does stand up comedy, his comedy podcast.
- Yeah, he does.
He's on Theo Vaughn's podcast and all that kind of shit.
- Do you think he's still spitting out lemons to this day?
- Probably.
- I would hope so.
- Yeah.
- I mean, yeah, I mean, I can't believe
hasn't made one of those videos in so long. He would dominate TikTok. These
kids don't remember, man. He needs to have his own podcast. Bobby Lee has a
podcast. He should have a podcast. I agree. Him with a lemon in his mouth.
Wait, no. It's an it's okay. So it's always one hour. Okay. It is always starts
with the lemon in his mouth. Yes. But the time where he spits it out is always
random so you know a lot of point he's gonna start talking normal again that's
the app yeah and that's also an app where you can send someone a picture or an idea
you're watching the little sauce a podcast and then you know what happens
right after he spits the lemon out mm-hmm
he should just go until he can't have a lemon in his mouth anymore till he can't
stand it and then he spits it out.
And by the way, there is water behind that lemon.
- Yep.
- And oh, this is actually a great idea.
- And just like Squarespace is behind our podcast.
(laughing)
- Use code beers for $1 off.
- What if he did something where it was like
you could do prop bets, like it was a live stream.
- Yeah.
- And it's like the bet for what color
the Gatorade is gonna be.
It's like what liquid does he have behind the lemon today?
'Cause maybe they just do water the first episode,
but by the fourth episode,
he's spitting out KSI and Logan Paul's "Prime."
- Yeah.
- This is no longer like a podcast idea,
but it's more like a TikTok live idea.
- I don't know the difference.
TikTok this, Instagram that.
We're using all trails to find out the best hiking spots.
I can't keep these apps separate in my brain anymore.
- You've never seen like a TikTok live type thing?
- These are all the same to me, okay?
Let me pull up the apps I have on my phone.
I can't even, I couldn't even tell you what these are.
- God, this Bud Light is awful.
- Dunkin'.
- I'm drinking two of 'em.
You have the Dunkin' app?
- Sheets.
Domino's.
- No. - Well, it's not good
that two of the three have been food so far.
- I think all three have been food.
The Sheets app is also food.
- Well, Sheet.
(both laughing)
Well, it's actually Google Sheets.
Wait, he's taking a phone call in the middle of the show?
Home Depot.
Who, God only knows.
Balls, B-A-L-L-Z, that's a video game, I do know that one.
Zelle, Zillow, what is Zille, is that another restaurant?
My Instant Soundboard.
But yeah, so that's just a little look into my phone.
If you've ever wanted to get into my phone,
which by the way you can't,
because my pin code is very secure
and it's nothing like the pin code for--
- 111. - Ah, fuck you,
how'd you know?
No, it's actually a six digit pin code,
I said it is a six digit.
The only thing I like about my phone is the fact that I put the
pictures widget on the top.
Yeah.
So I always get like a funny picture on there.
Right now it's a picture of me.
I do like funny pictures, man.
I'm not going to lie.
It's a picture of my friends.
It's now it's doing.
Oh, here's an idea for an app.
If you needed another idea for an app.
What if there was an app where you could instantly sue somebody?
Like it filed instantly to like a small claims court
or something.
It just did all that paperwork for you and sent it in.
'Cause they have the AI traffic lawyers.
- Yes.
- But not for small claims court.
So if you get the wrong order.
- It actually does exist.
- It does exist?
This exists?
- It's an app?
- Oh God dammit.
- There's a lawyer app.
- What?
- That does every like lawyer action for you.
- The McDonald's lawyer app?
- For slip and fall?
I mean, maybe not for a slip and fall, but it'll write you a lawyerly email.
You can probably send an email.
I would be sending them a cease and desist.
I think like simplifying processes like the way, like the one, like the stock app did
during COVID.
I forgot what it's called.
Robinhood.
More apps like that, I think that would be perfect to get $1 million and then like completely
crash or something like that.
like the lawyer app and more complicated stuff
that people usually don't do
because it takes so much money to do.
- Yeah.
- That is honestly how you should,
what you should be trying to do now
is you should be trying to make an app
that it's never possible for it to make any money at all.
You should be getting as much VC as possible.
And then you should be filing for bankruptcy.
- Yeah, my new app gives you health insurance
for $1 a month.
- Yeah.
- Oh, I heard, I was listening to some old podcast
the other day and they were talking about Dollar Shave Club,
which Dollar Shave Club is still around as a razor brand,
but they do not do the $1 thing anymore, I don't believe.
Because that makes no sense at all.
You can't sell razors for $1.
- What's it like a refill for $1?
- Yeah, it was like you get five razors a month for $1.
But I buy the fucking razors at the Walgreens
and they're 15 bucks.
- Yeah.
- Okay, that's crazy.
- It makes no sense, how did they do that for any amount?
- You also, you don't need five razors a month.
- I do.
- Yeah, he's going through it.
He's got a head to shave.
- Oh, I go through so fast.
I go through a razor every four days probably.
- Really?
- Yeah, it sucks.
And if I use an old razor, I almost always slice off
like half of my head.
It happened the other day.
- You and I, we're shaving here.
And there's, for you, the only part you need to shave
is right this part.
- Well, I actually shaved my entire face.
Thank you very much.
- Well, not you, I'm talking to Julio.
- Oh, okay.
- I did it, I shaved you the other day.
- I know.
- A really clean guy.
- See, no, that's not a clean shave.
You do not have a clean shave.
- Well, it's been a couple days.
- That's probably three days, I'm gonna guess.
- I don't remember.
- It's three, trust me on this.
I know this kind of thing very well.
Me, I shaved yesterday, it's already coming in again,
and my head is--
- Do you walk around the city,
inspecting people's faces and their facial hair
and being like-- - No!
- Seven days, five days,
this morning, two days. - No, I just do it
when somebody claims that they're clean shaven
and they're not.
- I don't think that's true.
I think you're hiding something.
You're hiding a secret.
- I will say, I look very far down
from a very high place at men who are bald
but they're half-stepping it
and they don't have a clean shaven head.
That is disgusting to me.
- That is fucking disgusting.
- Looking at a lot of pictures of Stavros recently.
- Yeah, well he has long hair though.
Like if you have a, just say like a six day grow out
on your head, like kind of a shadow,
get rid of that thing, man.
You know what I get asked sometimes?
I get asked sometimes, because my head is so clean shaven,
people will ask me if I was going bald
or I decided just to shave my head,
'cause they can't even tell, 'cause it's such a close shave.
- Right, they can't even see where it grows in.
- Exactly, they don't see the awful horseshoe,
the Larry David horseshoe that I have growing
on the top of my head.
- I think-- - But the thing is,
Larry David would look horrible fully shaved bald.
And you could do that.
- No, I couldn't do that.
I've tried growing my hair out, it's bad.
- At this point, Larry David has claimed
that haircut for his people.
I think if we see someone walking around
with that type of haircut, I'm assuming they are--
- You're saying Larry David.
- I'm assuming they're a certain type of guy.
- Larry David, I mean, that's fair,
but Larry David-- - Of a certain type of faith.
- Is a handsome fellow, he just happens to be bald.
- Larry David is not handsome.
Are you crazy?
- He's an old man.
He's eight years old. - He's an old ugly fart.
- He's fucking fat too.
- And it says the end of it on the show,
which I find disgusting.
- He's an appalling, abhorrent piece of shit.
And also, by the way, he's rude.
Near constantly.
- On his show even.
He doesn't care about showing how horrible--
- If I was him--
- A president's wife.
- If I was him, you know what I'd be doing?
Editing out my rudeness from my show.
What is this guy thinking?
The whole world knows he's rude, buddy.
- Yeah, does he know he said the N-word like 11 times?
- It's okay to blow up behind the scenes.
Every actor does it.
I do it on almost every Home Planet video that we shoot.
But you're supposed to cut it out, okay?
Don't add that.
I mean, whoever's editing that show needs to be fired.
I'll say that much.
- Do you think you could do, like I said,
come about your life, Caleb, as a comedian?
My life is that I sit at home and I play video games
and then I clean the house right before my wife gets home.
That'd be the worst.
- Like a show girl.
- Did you ever watch the, what's that comedian
that got canceled for being too rude to his wife?
The girl he loves so much, fuck.
- Oh, are you talking about the nerd?
- Yeah.
- Who are you talking about?
- Points, At Midnight.
- No, not At Midnight.
- Chris Hardwick.
- No, not Chris Hardwick, the other guy.
The guy who--
- But he's also a nerd?
- He's also a nerd.
- Did he talk about his middle ditch?
- No, the guy who talks like really high pitch
has had a Jewish wife and he would
completely talk about it all the time.
- John Mulaney.
- Yes.
You ever watch his show, like the pilot of his show?
- Oh, it's terrible.
(burps)
- I remember watching the first episode
and he was just like, he was just like reenacting
one of his jokes that he would say on his stand up.
- Yeah, it's like the worst show ever.
- And it was really bad.
- That was in like one or two years,
he got a show and then Pete Holmes got a show.
And then they both did that.
They both just did like jokes from their standup
turned into TV episodes.
- Here's a fun one.
If you could go back in time and erase a show from history,
which would you do?
- Give me those.
- For me, it would be Netflix, The Characters.
- That is a, well. - I don't know what that is.
What is it?
- Okay, give me your reasoning why.
- I think You Should Leave would not exist.
- And you don't like I Think You Should Leave?
- I think it's horrible.
And I think every woman would agree with me.
(laughing)
- Oh, okay, I see your ploy here.
- Yeah.
- I would probably--
- Well, you know I've always found that show
to be distasteful.
- That's a good show, man.
- No.
- You think it's distasteful?
You don't like cussing, you've said this before.
- I don't like when he just repeats stuff.
- Yeah, I mean, you know, it's just a character show.
I will say the characters except for,
he has probably the funniest episode of the characters.
- Yes. - And him or John Early.
But besides those, that show is very kind of
take it or leave it for me, hit or miss.
There's a lot of bad choices on that show.
I would eliminate the news.
- Fox News, just every news. - I don't need to know all that!
- The news! - Put more cartoons on!
Yeah, what the hell? You're interrupting my shit to tell me about fucking what?
Ukraine, 9/11, I don't care.
- Pull out Bob's Burgers! - Wait, what the fuck?
What channel does this?
The news!
- They interrupt, my dad still, to this day... - NBC?
- Does cartoons have news? - My dad talks about...
My dad still talks about how...
the September 11th news report...
interrupted a rerun of Seinfeld that he hadn't seen.
- Oh, I would be pissed.
- And he was just so mad.
- I would enlist immediately.
- Yeah, yeah.
It made him so mad. - It's time for revenge.
- Anytime 9/11 is brought up, he's like,
and they fucking, I mean,
they interrupted this episode of Seinfeld.
It's like, what?
How un-American can you be?
- Wait, I have a question about this,
about your answer.
Has he gone back and watched that episode that he missed?
(laughing)
- I actually know he did.
I know when Netflix came out,
he watched all of Seinfeld
and he said he was doing it to fill in the gaps.
- That's great.
- Did you see that when they air reruns of Seinfeld,
they speed it up 7%?
- Oh, I forgot about that.
- Because, so original Seinfeld is a 25 minute episode.
- Oh.
- But modern episodes need to be 22 minutes long,
so they just speed it up a little bit
so that it's 22 minutes long.
- Do they do it with every old show?
they do that with like cheers?
- I think so.
- Is that why they don't rerun those old shows much?
They only rerun like Big Bang Theory
and How I Met Your Mother?
- I think so.
- Do you, okay, now I gotta ask you guys a question.
I don't think either of you know
what gets rerun these days.
I don't think either of you have watched cable TV in years.
- It has been years.
- Yeah, that's been a long time.
- It has, I won't lie to you.
I wanna lie so bad.
Actually, I'll lie.
I have cable, I watch it every day.
- You don't have cable.
- I do, I just told you that.
You're gonna come here?
- Dude, I love TV.
TV's so sick, but I don't have cable either.
I love prior TV. - I don't really care
about TV that much.
- I think you do.
- I mean-- - No.
- You love Pluto. - I wish there just
wasn't ads.
- Yeah.
- I hate 'em.
I hate ads.
- You love Pluto TV.
You're lying about TV.
- I don't even watch Pluto TV anymore.
That was like a two-week phase of my life
that I watched Pluto TV.
- When I was in town, we sat in Cam's apartment
for like two hours just watching all Jeopardy! episodes
on Pluto TV, and you were loving it.
- Okay, but Jeopardy! is dope.
- Well, Jeopardy! is a different thing.
Jeopardy! is dope.
- It's TV.
Jeopardy! is TV.
- Oh my God.
- This is--
- That is the dumbest argument I've ever heard.
- We were at Cam's house, we were trying to kill time.
It was either watch Jeopardy!
or watch like the worst movie ever.
I don't sit around watching TV like that.
- I, no.
- What are you talking about?
Jeopardy! airs for 30 minutes every day.
That's not TV.
That's an episode of a TV show.
- Jeopardy! also is more like a job for me.
- If it's on the television, it's TV.
What do you mean?
- I'm sitting there and I'm trying my hardest.
I have beads of sweat just running down my face,
over my nose, dripping onto my couch.
That is not, I'm just not entertaining.
I'm not being entertained.
I'm working.
- We should send it to a game show.
- I'm trying to beat my mom so, so badly.
I would be amazing on a game show.
- Yeah, which one?
- Go ahead, introduce me on a game show.
Just whatever game show.
- Okay, and from North Carolina,
he's 26 years old, 35 years old.
I forgot how old he is.
- 26.
- 26, he is a comedian from New York City.
Say hello to Caleb Pitts.
- Oh, what's up America?
- So Caleb, it says here that you have a little show,
you have a podcast.
- Yeah, yeah, shout it out now,
in a belly call me, yeah, yeah.
- Yes I do, Jubio.
- Okay.
- Mr.
- Yeah, so what do you--
- Yes I do, mister.
- Okay, so what are you here for?
What are you playing for?
- Steve, I'm playing to win it all.
- That's it, you don't wanna use the money
to like buy a house or get married?
- No, no.
(humming)
- Okay.
- Can I open my second beer at this 53 minute mark?
- Yes.
- Let that thing fly.
- I'm almost done with this one and I'm feeling--
- What's this?
Oh my God, Bud Light Seltzer Hard Soda.
- Bud Light Seltzer Hard Soda.
- I forgot about those.
- Classic Cola.
In honor of aspartame becoming a carcinogen.
- Just about to say.
Here's the thing about aspartame, man.
I mean, that came out of nowhere, that news.
- I can't believe it.
- I thought that aspartame was only in light sodas,
not in every soda.
- It is in light sodas, but it's also,
any kind of alcoholic soda is usually artificially sweetened,
so that because they, if they used full sugar,
it'd be like a 400 calorie fucking can of beer,
because it's got alcohol in it.
- And alcohol. - So you think--
- Whereas this only has 210 in this big ass can.
- Yeah, that's nothing. - Look at this thing.
- Of aspartame?
(belching)
Do you think now that it's being considered a carcinogen,
there's gonna be like aspartame like truthers?
- Yeah. - I mean, people
have hated on aspartame forever.
- Yeah, but now that it's being like officially
being told by Joe Brandon that it's bad,
do you think that's gonna be truthers?
They're like, you know what?
Actually, it was good.
- Oh, people like, what's that guy's name?
Dan something, who thinks Stevia is a miracle cure.
- Yeah, something like that.
- Stevia tastes like shit, by the way.
If you put Stevia in your coffee,
you have something, you have an absolute brain damage.
- I cannot tell the difference
between any sugar or sugar replacement.
- You have an undefined palate.
- They're all sweet.
What's the difference?
- The difference is the aftertaste.
- I don't give a fucking shit about the aftertaste.
There's coffee in it.
- No, the aftertaste matters.
- The aftertaste does matter.
- It's in my coffee and my four things of cream.
I can't even taste it anymore.
- All right, I got a new thing.
I just wanna shout out Adrifuel Labs,
which has basically Adderall in the energy drink
that they sell, which is dope as fuck.
- What are you talking about?
- Just thinking about drinks with things in them
that give you cancer.
- Are you ordering a drink right now?
- He gets what he's doing.
- Why did you look so focused for a moment?
- I had to remember what it was called.
- Adrifuel?
- Yeah, yeah, they sell,
have you ever heard of Modafinil?
- Yes, wait, Modafinil is a prescription medication.
- Uh-huh, so they sell an energy drink
that metabolizes Modafinil in your liver.
- No way, really?
- Yes.
(laughs)
- Wow, that is insane.
Modafinil is just about the most expensive one to,
Well, there's R-modafinil as well.
- Yeah.
- I heard Andrew Huberman talk about this shit.
I need to try this.
Adrofuel?
- Yes, yeah.
- Have you had it?
- No, I just got it today.
I'm so excited.
- India's first sports nutrition brand built by humans.
- Wait, no, not that one.
- Are you sure?
A-D-R-O-F-U-E-L.
- No, A-D-R-A-F-U-L.
With an umlau on the U.
- Talking to regs for more than like a couple minutes
is really dangerous because you,
At the end of their talk, you will be convinced
that you should order something from online
that's usually like a drink or some sort of like just--
- The only thing that makes me happy
is pressing the button that makes money
go out of my account.
- Oh yeah, so I'm gonna be mugging you soon.
- Adrafinil.
- Yeah.
- 100 milligrams caffeine, 150 milligrams adrafinil.
- Yeah, which turns into modafinil in your liver.
- How do you hear about this shit, man?
- I saw it on Twitter,
and I ordered it and I got it today.
- And you haven't tried it?
- Nope, 'cause I already drank a Monster this morning
by the time it arrived.
- But tomorrow you will be giving us a trip report, yes?
- I will be doing it on Monday.
- Why Monday?
- No need to work that hard on a Friday.
- True, that's true.
I think you should save this review for next week
when we--
- Adraphanil was marketed in France until September 2011
when it was voluntarily discontinued
due to an unfavorable risk-benefit ratio.
(laughing)
- That's what's up, dude.
- Oh, God.
- I'm putting that shit in my body.
- There's a case report of two patients
that Adraphidil may increase interest in sex.
- Oh, no.
- This is not Adderall, this is the opposite.
- Yeah.
- This is a disgusting, disgusting drug.
- It's different.
- Not me, it makes my penis as small as a bug.
(burping)
- Makes jacking off awesome and cumming horrible.
- Yeah, anytime I've taken Adderall,
I'm always smoking cigarettes too.
And those are two things that shrink your penis down.
And then I always go to the bathroom
and my penis gets so small that I piss on my own pants.
(laughing)
- That's fucking dope, I do that all the time.
It's awesome.
- So I piss a literal peanut on my--
- Yeah, dude, it fucking looks like a dick.
- It's nothing, it's nothing.
It's just nothing.
- It looks like a third ball.
- Yeah, and it's just hitting,
it's hitting the side of my leg
'cause it's that far in.
- That M&M bar that's like dick so small
you pee on your balls used to piss me off so much.
I'd be like, "What's your problem, man?
"I bought you a piece of--"
(laughing)
- It is something that people usually don't talk about,
how often you can pee on yourself.
- I pissed on myself a couple days ago
while I was trying to pee,
but that's because my pants, I have bad pants.
I have a bad set of pants that I've been wearing.
- Explain this, explain this.
Explain this.
- I don't know.
I think that they just have an odd fly.
And so the--
- Oh, you just flip it out through the fly.
- Yeah, you pulling your pants to the ground
like a fucking baby?
What are you talking about?
- No, I just don't use a urinal.
- I don't use a urinal either.
I still put my dick through the fly.
- Oh, you need to stand up--
- In your house?
- Yeah, what?
Sit down.
- You guys sit down to pee in your own home?
- Sometimes.
- Yeah, and I'm pulling out my phone and I'm on Twitter.
- Y'all gay ASF.
- Okay, here, I'm being a third on my spot here
in this debate, okay?
Whenever-- - Okay, we're debating now.
- Most times when I'm standing up to pee,
sometimes it's in the morning or I'm not wearing my glasses
and it just goes everywhere in the entire room,
even on the roof, due to how wild the pee is.
When I sit down, when I sit down to pee,
I look, it's controlled, I can look at my phone
for longer than I should be in the toilet,
and I'm having fun.
- The only time I sit down to pee
is if I have the hardest boner of my life.
- Okay, so here's next week's homework, okay?
Rex is gonna talk to us about his weird energy drink
that he bought from India.
- Yes.
- And you are gonna sit down to pee today or this weekend,
and you're gonna talk about your experience next week.
I want you to, every time you sit down to pee tomorrow,
sit down, - Every time.
- Pull out your phone and just scroll for five minutes.
- Don't be surprised when I open this Zoom call
and I look like Jessica Rabbit, okay?
- Okay. - I would love that.
- I would actually really love that.
- Big lipstick on, blonde hair,
blonde hair down to my fucking knees.
- I would not complain about that whatsoever.
- All just from sitting down to pee.
- Okay, I'm sure that'll happen.
- Big, busty, double D, huge-y.
- Jealous of my long hair?
- No, I'm not jealous of your hair.
- From sitting down to pee?
- Although that's just gonna make a lot more sense.
- All the extra gravity from sitting down to pee?
- All the extra grip that somebody can use
as they plow you, that's what that hair is for, I know.
- The only downside-- - Now my hole is open.
I'm giving myself hemorrhoids reading my phone so long.
(laughing)
- Yeah, the only downside to this is that you might
have a mirror in front of your toilet,
you might get a B-Reel notification
at the exact moment when you're peeing.
- I'm not kidding.
Three times a week, I get a B-Reel when I'm shitting.
- That just means you spend too much time on the toilet.
That is crazy.
The odds of that happening are just--
- I think I'm just that unlucky.
It's like, I don't even shit for days,
and I'll sit down, and I'll--
- You don't shit for days?
- What?
Yeah, do you shit every day?
- Shit at least twice a day.
I shit twice today, but yesterday I didn't shit at all.
Every morning and every night.
But sometimes I'll just sit down and I'll just
hear the B-Reel sound.
And I'm like, what am I supposed to do here?
Because of the time that I took a B-Reel while shitting,
forgetting that my mirror is directly
in front of the toilet, and almost by accident
covered up my penis.
Otherwise, it would have been fully on my B-Reel.
I mean, honestly, Rex, I hate to be
the one to break this news.
You live in the third dimension.
and you can move your phone so that you can face two different, like, you know,
I get that there's the, the,
No, it takes it on both sides.
Yeah, I know.
So turn your head to the left, take a picture of your shower and a picture of
your face.
Well, I, I, here's what I did, right.
Was I was going to take the forward, the back camera, realizing that there's a big
mirror directly in front of the toilet.
Went, well, I can't do that.
So I just turned the camera around to take a selfie,
forgetting that it also uses the other camera.
- Yeah, you need to add your fuel so, so badly.
- Wait, hang on.
I got a subsequent question.
What happened to the thinking pills?
The serene, the--
- Oh, theory or whatever they're called?
- The theory pills, yeah.
What happened to those?
- They're sitting in a stack over there.
- Did you stop taking them?
- They made me shit too much.
- More than once a week.
- I'm trying to be backed up.
I'm time maxing, dude.
- Yeah.
- I'm trying to keep my time out of the bathroom
and on the computer.
- See, shitting for me is probably,
and this is profound,
probably what pissing is for you.
- Yes, that is true.
An enjoyable experience.
- I enjoy every single shit I have.
It's my moment of solitude.
- Shitting hurts for me.
My ass hurts.
- My ass hurts all day and night, you motherfucker.
- I'm bleeding, okay?
- Your asshole's bleeding?
- Every time.
And it hurts.
- You bleed every time?
- I think that's bad.
- And then I'm blasting it with water after,
waiting for blood to stop flowing out.
- That's probably why you're probably going maximum speed
on the, you're reaching terminal velocity
with the water blasting into your ass
and it's ripping it apart like a pressure washer.
- No, it feels good.
- Oh, okay.
- Dude, you know what sucks with the bidet?
It was so hot here last week that when I--
- That you splattered it in your face.
- No, that when I was using the bidet,
the water was hot and it felt weird in my butt.
- Yeah, I like the cold, it's refreshing.
- I do like it when it's cold.
- It's like a good cutoff for taking a shit.
One quick wipe and you're out.
- You guys gotta stop with this bidet stuff.
I barely use toilet paper.
I'm not gonna use it.
- You need to get one. - I probably use
less toilet paper than you because I have a--
- You need to get one.
- I don't even want, I don't want to--
- You have a dirty butt.
You have a dirty butt.
- Oh yeah, I do.
'Cause I'm a grown man.
And if you're a grown man,
your ass should be disgusting and fucking green.
That's what your ass should be.
- No, we're done here.
- No, you should have flies flying around your ass
at all times.
- I'm shitting out undigested salad and blood
and it's wiping that shit straight off the earth.
- How is this the podcast?
(laughing)
- Oh wait, the beer.
The beer was good.
Yummy.
I like the beer.
All right, bye.
Bye.