[Sipping]
[Burp]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer podcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[Burp]
This is a journey into sea.
Into the middle of...
Planet King!
- I'm a food ribbon!
- Beers we drank, motherfucker,
with Juvio, Caleb, and Rex.
- Yo. - Cheers.
- Yo.
- Jesus Christ, man.
- Whoa, you have a bottle.
You start.
- I'm gonna start.
So this here is, this is actually a really fancy bottle,
now that I see it up close.
So this is, I was telling Rex,
this is a completely surprise mystery beer to me
because I didn't buy it this time around.
I asked my girlfriend to buy it for me.
And it looks like she got me a,
ooh, it's called Charro.
Wow.
Naked women in the bottle.
That looks like the top of a car
that somebody painted.
I will be drinking this and I'm gonna be saving the bottle
for enjoyment later on.
Amazing, what do you mean enjoyment?
What are you gonna do with the bottle?
All right, what are you going next, Caleb?
We'll take a sip and give us a rating review.
It tastes like beer.
I don't hate it.
It just tastes like beer.
You're so shit at reviewing the beers.
Well, I have a Victory Sour Monkey,
which I think I had a different version of this one time.
But I never had this one.
So I'm going to take a sip here.
It's the Sour Triple 19.2 fluid ounces, 9.5% alcohol.
He kind of looks like a Victor monkey tonight.
Oh!
Oh, it's so sour!
It really is quite sour.
But I'm going to give it, you know,
you got to grade every beer
next to beers of the same family.
As far as sours go, this is like a 5.7.
Oh my God, wait.
This is a light post-ner.
Except for on the basketball scale.
On the basketball player scale, it's probably a 6'4".
Oh, shit.
It's pretty good.
No, I can't see.
It says World Beer.
World, World, 22 World Beer Awards, Mexico Bronze.
OK.
So it's completely bronze.
You're my bronze, Mexico.
Yeah.
Yep.
All right, Rex, how about you go?
So I don't really have a beer this time.
Oh, but what I do have.
Oh my God.
Is a Bud Light Strawberita.
Wow.
OK, this is interesting because I almost buy one of these every single episode.
I get very, very close to doing it, but then I can't do it.
It looks too disgusting to me.
It's been years for me.
Yeah, this is what I drank on my 21st birthday.
Take a sip.
Yep, that's what I remember.
Is it made by Bud Light?
It is indeed.
Oh, my God.
Is it strawberry flavored?
Yeah, it is. It tastes like a strawberry margarita.
It tastes very sweet.
It's 8% alcohol.
Give it a height rating.
8%?
This is probably like a solid six foot five.
Maybe even six foot six.
Shooting guard.
Yeah. Shooting guard.
OK. And a good one at that.
It's got hops. Yeah.
OK. All right.
Debargarosen.
Yes. All right. I like it.
Well, I've had a major life change this week.
Which is?
I want you to guess.
I want you to guess what it is.
You're growing your hair out.
Wait, no.
Wait, no, look behind me.
Look behind me.
Oh, you got it.
Oh, you got an air on my chair.
Did you get that from Mr.
B?
Yes, Mr.
Bean.
Yes, we went to my friends.
A mutual friend of ours, he is leaving his company and the company is shutting down.
He wants to be on the show, so he'll be on the show at some point.
Well, he also stole so much stuff, I don't want to say his name.
Oh, never mind, never mind.
So we went to the day before the company moved and they didn't want a lot of the stuff there,
but some of the stuff they wanted. So we took probably $4,000 worth of Herman Miller chairs.
Oh my God.
Put them into a car.
I think we took seven. I think we took seven chairs.
That is more than $4,000.
Really? Oh my God.
That's a $1,500 chair, dude.
Really? It's not that.
That is crazy.
If you try to buy that brand new, that's like a $1,400 chair.
I mean, it's definitely a huge upgrade from the chair that I had previously.
But honestly, I don't care about office chairs that much.
It's funny that you say that. Oh, yeah, it's an upgrade.
when you were just sitting on like a kitchen chair.
I had a broken Ikea chair.
It was an Ikea chair,
one of the $39 ones that are just like school chairs basically.
The back of it had fallen off and so I could not recline in it.
Your back will thank you.
Yeah, I'm pretty excited. I've been chilling way more today.
Yeah. The leaning back,
like the weightlessness of the leaning back in the air on is so nice.
This is an amazing chair, guys.
Yeah.
And I also got a Billy
Billy Big Mouth Bass from the office.
So Billy Big Mouth Bass in the office.
Yeah. A little miniature USB one.
So I'm pretty excited about that.
That's come up.
What else did I steal or get gifted to me?
That's that's really the big ones that I commit.
That was the big ones.
Yeah. No other real crimes that day.
But those are my big my big moments of grand larceny.
You've been a leader of industry for the past, what, five years and you were still just sitting
on a complete wooden chair and you were gaming in a little box.
You're still kind of in a little box.
I'm still in a little box.
I still need to get a desk.
I'm having a curveball thrown my way this week.
My cousin texted me yesterday and said, "Hey, are we still good for me to come to New York
in two days?"
And I was like, "What?"
And I looked back and four months ago, I guess I had said that it was okay for him to come
to New York and visit me for one week.
But I completely forgot.
To stay with you?
Is he staying with you?
Yeah, he's staying with me.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
So the wife is not happy, guys.
She is just straight up not happy.
You should really like take like a blueprint of your apartment and show that to people
before they make plans to come and stay at your place.
I don't think you say but oh yeah virtual tours that yeah, it's like two steps
You're like we know I don't know what you said
You had to share a couch with Noah. That's why you hated it. Yeah, well, I didn't hate it
I thought you I thought it was very nice. I was very thankful for what you did for me
I'm still very thankful for what you did for me. I would probably never do that again
I would rather go to anyone else's apartment before yours because of how small it is and how tiny it is
I'm the only guy that my cousin knows in all of New York City, okay? I called him today. I
said, "What do you want to do while you're in New York City?" He said he wants to see the Statue
of Liberty. So I'm going to make his dream come completely true, okay? And he's going to stay…
A whole week to do that?
And he is going to do a lot of work for me for free, and also he is going to watch my dog a
lot. That's the plan, and I'm pretty excited for it, honestly.
That's nice.
Do you guys like when people come visit you?
No.
I do actually.
Yeah, I do.
Yeah.
But I hate feeling responsible for another person's entertainment.
For their fun.
True.
Yes.
Yeah.
I hate that responsibility.
I've been thinking about this a lot recently because I was talking to my girlfriend.
I was like, you know, we already had a guest here, stay here like in February I think.
And it went like decently nice.
We had a lot of fun.
We showed her around the city and she like enjoyed it.
Yeah, it was my girlfriend's friend.
And I was like thinking recently like what would I show someone who comes from outside the city?
And like answer the country.
I'm like, I don't I wouldn't really know.
It's like it's really hard question to just like pose yourself.
Like I think you have to like just face it when they're there.
I want to see ruins if i come to mexico i want to see giant ruins i want to see those big heads i want to see all those stones stacked on top of each other.
For ruins you're gonna be a little bit out of luck if you come to my city.
If i come to your city and there's not ruins i'm making making yeah i'm making ruins you okay your house will be obliterated lee in a demolished way.
Are you, okay.
I will be knocking it and then when I'm done I'm going to spray paint it brown so it looks very old.
And I'm going to string your skeleton up and put it in my study.
Yep.
I would have a very old looking apartment.
You know what, honestly we could probably, if we did something crazy at Julio's house when we visit him,
we could get maybe some kind of like historical plaque in like 20 years.
Can you guys not visit me at the same time?
Can you guys stagger your visits?
Why?
Do you want us to stagger our visits?
Maybe if you only see this when a share the the sofa bed.
I like sharing okay also how much is it i'll get an airbnb i'm a new airbnb in mexico.
Probably not much cheap as a as a dog shit i will we can't put like a air mattress in the empty space behind you.
No.
Oh.
I think we completely can.
There's a rug right here.
You can sleep on the rug.
I'd sleep on the rug.
I've slept on worse floors.
When we were on tour, when we stayed in Texas, I slept just on a foam roller.
That was the only thing I had.
Didn't have a blanket, just had a foam roller at this guy's house.
That's fucked.
And it was one of the worst nights of sleep I've ever gotten in my entire life.
And the guy that we were staying with was loudly having sex.
Nice.
With a man.
Yeah.
I don't know.
life and the guy that we were staying with was loudly having sex with a man.
Yeah, who knows?
I mean, I'm not I wasn't I didn't watch.
Yeah, it was you.
You didn't see who came in out of the door in and out.
It could have been a man.
I could have, but I think it was probably his girlfriend,
if I had to guess.
Mm hmm. Yeah, that's a good guess.
And she loves him.
Probably a safe assumption.
Dude, the word, I think the worst.
It would be so funny to have a girlfriend
and then ruin her life by having gay sex and have her find out.
What are you talking about?
She cheated.
Cheating on your girlfriend is funny, let alone.
No, no, no, no.
Cheating on your girlfriend.
That's horrible.
Yeah, your girlfriend with a man.
Why is that better?
It's funnier.
I didn't say it's better.
It's just funnier.
She'd be having more distraught
because, you know, when you cheat on someone, that's like, oh, you can't.
I can't give that to you.
You know, whatever. Yeah.
But you know, a woman can well, you know, don't even say it.
I'm going to forgo it.
You're about to say a woman can give you a blow job with a beard.
But no, we don't want to say that.
That's disgusting.
I've been having an emotional affair with the guy who runs
the deli down the street, I think, for a couple of years.
Does he like kind of touch your hand when you like to tap?
Does he love you?
He says, How's the dog?
Every day for a full year now he says how's the dog and i'm gonna say good he says getting big.
Yeah he's wondering when you're gonna bring it in to turn it into meat.
No he would not eat him.
I would not eat him i would not eat phil no i have no interest in.
Phil or sam.
Do you think Phil knows your name?
Phil definitely knows my name, yeah, no doubt.
Sam, Sam, you know what man?
It's honestly one of the, it's probably the longest running
stranger to stranger relationship I've ever had.
I've lived in the same place for like over three years
and I've always gone to this one deli
if I need like a sandwich or like a grocery.
And it's honestly, it's the worst deli in the entire neighborhood.
But it's just the first one I went to, so I just keep going to it.
Yeah.
And no, I would say he doesn't know me, doesn't know my name at all, but he knows that I have
a wife and he always says, "How's the dog?
The dog's getting big.
How's the wife?
What is she doing?"
The wife's getting big.
Like a bitch?
Nah, come on.
The wife's getting pretty big, man.
I go, "Yeah, actually now that you say it, yeah, I guess she is getting pretty big."
Time to get a new one.
And it's his fault, dude.
He's making me gobblers.
That's my favorite sandwich there.
The gobbler.
What's a gobbler?
And it's his fault, dude. He's making me gobblers.
That's my favorite sandwich there.
What's a gobbler?
The gobbler. It's a turkey. Okay.
It is a turkey sandwich with Swiss cheese, lettuce, tomato, Russian dressing.
It's delicious.
And it makes sense why it's called the gobbler.
Because it's turkey.
It's turkey.
And you gobble it.
Yeah.
It's a delicious sandwich.
Do you ever have an aneurysm when you talk to someone
and you just say like, yeah, can I get the yummy sandwich?
I can't say that that's happened to me, man.
I really can't.
It happened to me yesterday.
I asked, what do you do?
Someone was making brownies at the July 4th celebration.
I was at. I was like, can you add some yummy, nummy sauce to it?
This is being cute.
That's not having an aneurysm.
Wait, what the fuck is yummy, nummy sauce?
I think it's just caramelsauce in my head.
It's something yummy.
Yummy nummy sauce.
I hate you.
Did you say it really?
It was like the entire party silent
in that one moment.
Yeah, yeah, of course.
Can I have some yummy nummy sauce?
Can you put some yummy nummy sauce on it?
Did you know these people very well?
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
You if if somebody if I was doing a Fourth of July thing
and some guy brought this guy over
and he gets it, he just starts.
My wife is kind enough to make him brownies
and then she serves him one and he says,
sorry, you forgot the yummy, yummy sauce.
Can I have a beer from you?
I would duct tape him to a firework.
Send him into the stratosphere.
I did. I did drink a Sapporo Reserve.
Those are great.
I did not enjoy it.
In fact, I would liken it to a form of torture.
The Sapporo reserve.
Yeah.
What is the poor reserve go?
Uh, quite frankly, the worst beer I've ever had.
Really?
Could have just been because it was warm.
It's it sounds like it was serious.
I'm going to, yeah, I'm going to push back on that.
That's an amazing, amazing beer.
If you ever go to Gyukaku, the Japanese barbecue place, that's the
best beer you can get there, man.
I think they have it on draft too, and they do not ID.
Maybe on draft would be much better.
Everything I disagree that everything's better on draft.
Yesterday. OK, yesterday.
All right. What's the what's the trip report on all beers you had yesterday?
I drank a lot of like mixed drinks, which were great, like like tequila drinks.
Oh, amazing tequila.
Some some lavender lemonade and then some
a like margarita mix.
And I just drink just the mix with.
Right. But there is tequila that I would.
Oh, that was the some some Espolon.
There was an Espolon bottle to decent tequila.
I drank a lemonade, 40 beers yesterday.
And half of them were.
They were they were from Sonic.
They were like, you know, Sonic, like the drive in.
It was Sonic Hard Seltzers, Cherry Limed, and it was amazing.
That sounds amazing.
It was so amazing.
Oh my God.
Sonic's entered the hard seltzer game?
They've entered the hard seltzer.
We need to make a hard seltzer.
Everybody has a hard seltzer now except for us.
We're like on our own.
That's true.
Every--
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
Like a prime style hard seltzer, influencer,
beverage type deal.
We need a good name.
What do they have?
They have White Claw, Truly, Happy Dad.
- I don't even know if I've seen Happy Dad.
- That's the Nelkaboys, that's their seltzer.
We need a Happy Dad style thing.
- Yeah, we need to do something like quirky.
- Yeah.
- Something, hmm.
- I mean, we should just have a line called, "You drank."
- Oh yeah, we were talking about, yeah, beer you drank.
The seltzer you drank.
Seltzer you're drinking is good.
The hard sense where you are drinking right now.
That's an amazing.
We could do a yummy nummy sauce flavor even.
Wine you glugged.
Wine you glugged is good.
Wine you're glugging.
Tip up that wine you glugged.
I hate glugging wine though.
I hate wine.
I'm putting a stop to this right now.
I went to a girl event.
I went to a festival for lavender blooming about 2 1/2 hours outside the city.
And.
I stood in line in the drink line for like 40 minutes and just started
buying as many drinks as possible so I wouldn't have to stand back in that line.
Smart ended up buying just like a bottle of wine.
From it, just started drinking from the bottle.
I'd be like, oh, this is horrible.
Yeah, wine is not that good.
Yeah, I, I don't understand good wine.
That's that's honestly the big thing for me.
Like, I feel like with beer, I can tell if a beer is like a nice high end beer
with wine, I really can't tell at all.
It's complete BS. It's complete bullshit.
It just tastes the same, which is not that great
because you're supposed to sip it.
And when I drink alcohol, I want to grab it like this
and then bring it to my lips like this.
And then you want to can.
Wait, did you just demonstrate how to drink a beer?
Yeah, or a cup for that.
I want to do this. Yeah.
Yeah, and I think I want to do this.
Wait, you didn't even succeed at drinking.
You spit it out.
I don't really love the flavor of this.
I like the art.
Wine, you have to sip slowly.
Yeah.
You got to be a real alcoholic to glug wine.
We're drinking a beer, drinking a mixed drink.
You can just I think I think I talked about this a lot,
but did you know that in like tequila where they make tequila?
Yeah. If you go to like with the distillery there, they take you to like the tour.
And at the end, there's like a like a like a tequila tasting session.
And they like make you taste the tequila like it like a Seville's wine.
Yeah. Well, that works, too.
I mean, actual liquor you can drink like.
Yeah, you're not supposed to really shoot good liquor.
Yeah.
Good, good anything.
Good whiskey, good tequila.
You're supposed to sip it.
Yeah.
And sipping a good tequila, like a Don Julio.
What's up?
It's too spicy.
Tequila is too spicy to just sip, man.
Yeah.
I'm not going to be doing that.
It's not spicy.
It's too, too spicy for me.
I want to eat a, you know what we could do with a hard seltzer
that you drank, that you're drinking right now, is we could
do like, we could put like a mezcal worm in every single one.
And it's a gummy worm.
You know, no, it's a worm.
It's a gummy worm.
Or why are we limiting ourselves to worms?
Put any animal in it.
Put a spider, put a fly, just a single fly.
It's a cockroach.
The yummy, yummy flavor of the seltzer you're drinking right now, it's hard to
tell you you're drinking right now, it should be a gummy worm.
That I think goes without saying.
Yeah.
Hard seltzers should be like elf bars.
They should have,
they should be like mango,
banana,
peach.
Yes.
Hard seltzer.
Mint salt.
It should make you feel horrible.
Yeah.
It should,
you should feel like your insides are being churned.
Yeah.
You should be able to smoke it as well.
I agree.
You should be,
I mean,
I've been saying for years,
you should be able to smoke beer.
All beer should be smokable.
There's no reason.
We have gotten so far ahead in technology.
A.I. could get involved with this.
Let's start smoking beer.
Wasn't there like a.
Oh, no.
I was thinking about like inhalable alcohol, but I think someone made
like a powdered alcohol that you could snort.
That is for your ass, I think.
Yes.
And that's what you're going to put alcohol in your ass.
Now, I can't say I have my ass is pretty untouched.
It's pretty.
My ass is pretty.
I have...
I'm trying to think of what things I've put in my ass like medicine was.
I remember when I was a kid, I had strep throat and my mom had to put a pill in my ass.
And I was way too old.
I was like, like eight years old.
Like I can do that myself.
That's not that old.
It's too old for your mom to finger your butt.
I thought you were going to be like 14.
I was 14.
You were about to say you were 16.
Yeah, you're the same age as Cartman at eight.
Like you can't get it all the time.
Yeah. Yeah, that is true.
But yeah, I don't think I think since then I've been really put off
of putting pills and alcohol in my ass.
What do you have to put a thing in your ass?
Badly, you need hemorrhoid cream.
You have hemorrhoids.
I do. My hole is.
Is that because that's because you sit while you pee?
- Okay. - No, it's 'cause I sit while I poop
and then continue sitting for 20 minutes.
- It's 'cause you sit while you pee, man.
You sit on the toilet too long. - And then I turn the bidet
on full blast. - Caleb, did you pee,
did you pee sitting down this week?
- Twice, count 'em. - Really?
- Two times. - I could be standing up
all week. - And both times,
both times, guys, I was peeing, sitting down,
and my wife walked in, mom, you were peeing, sitting down.
- And she's like, "Oh my God, I married a girl."
Literally both times she was like,
"Oh, I'm sorry, I didn't know you were taking a shit."
And I had to be like, "No, I'm only peeing
"and sitting down because my friends told me to do it."
It was not very, it was not attractive, I don't think.
- Okay, I think if every time someone
thought you were taking a shit, you were peeing,
I think that'd be a good thing, wouldn't it?
- But I think I should have told her I was taking a shit
and just forgot to lock the door.
But instead, she knew that I was sitting down and peeing.
- I mean, do you not lock the door when you pee?
Not when my wife is the only person in the house.
Who cares? - What's the difference?
What's the difference?
What's the word?
She smells your poop?
- Yes. - She smells your poop
constantly.
- She has never ever seen me poop
and I've never seen her poop.
It's a hard line in our relationship.
It will never be crossed.
This is lifelong. - Okay.
Okay.
- I do not like poop.
I don't like to think about my wife's poop
and the poop that she makes.
and while she's pooping, I don't think about it?
- You're thinking.
(laughs)
It sounds like you're thinking about it a lot.
- This sounds like an I think you should leave joke.
- Yeah. - I don't think,
I don't want to think, I see it's scrambling me.
The idea of her pooping makes me want to divorce her
so fucking badly.
(laughs)
- Yeah.
- I won't do it.
- I think it would be cool to serve your wife a divorce
while she was pooping.
- Yeah, where are you gonna go?
You have been served. - Exactly.
Yeah, you got served.
- Okay. - For some reason,
- Your wife is taking a shit.
Hey baby, really quick, what's your name?
(laughing)
- How old are you?
- You have been served.
- You just pull your pen out.
Hey, can you sign this real quick?
- Okay, well regardless of all social norms
that you were afraid to break, how did it feel?
- It felt wrong, dude.
- How did it feel wrong?
You're just chilling, you're sitting down,
you're peeing, it's fine.
- I didn't like it, I did not like it.
- Really?
of the times my piss, my piss like came between the toilet seat and the toilet
and it dribbled down the front of the toilet? That happens to me too. I did not
like that dude. Why would you do that to yourself? Well I you know I didn't think
your shit was as small as mine. Mine's microscopic. I talked last week about pissing on my own like balls in my pants.
We did talk about that. I mean come on. You do have to take like an index finger and
just kind of point it down.
Yeah, see, I don't want to be sitting there.
My wife walks in and I'm talking to try to fucking piss.
That is like the worst possible situation I could put myself in.
Why is she walking in while you're in the bathroom?
She's trying to get moisturizer.
Well, maybe she moisturize your dick.
It would get hard when you saw her.
Well, that's a pretty good point.
Found it right now.
That's pretty funny.
Maybe if she rubbed my dick with moisturizer, it might get hard.
Yeah.
While I'm peeing, sitting down.
I can see that.
While I'm peeing, yeah.
I don't like pee.
I heard a story this week from a friend of mine who said that he was having sex with a girl
and she squirted, which I told him never tell me anything like this again.
This is disgusting.
He said that she squirted and then she just peed in his bed.
She wanted to keep it going.
She squirted and then and then just like he said that there was a gap and then it went from an explosion to a literal stream of yellow pee directly on his bed.
I will be mad he was pretty mad he said i would say get out of his.
Get out he did not like it and i can't blame him do that does not sound all that fun.
That sounds horrible i would be very offended.
I do not like all that's an insult to your intelligence.
Yeah.
Which is what i believe what was it with.
Oh yeah i think she's getting one by you by squirting and then p.m. she just has to pee and she's like well here we go i'm gonna get him with this yeah.
I don't think it was thinking at all.
I think i mean this guy has to be so good at sex to make a girl squirt and then p though.
That's what i said i was like you that's it you should take that as a compliment cuz so a lot of guys can make a girl squirt but the squirt and then she also he's all over the place.
Is true if you can get a girl to get a woman to squirt piss and shit.
At the same time you might be one of the best people at sex ever.
Are you here to ship i hate shit i hate p2 i do not like how much pornography has has a weird moments of peeing in it what.
What are you talking about sometimes sometimes you watch porn and then at the end there p.
That's true that's true.
Just random crap. What are you searching? I don't search anything. I just click on the first video that pops up.
I've never searched on porn. Have you ever seen a peeing compilation?
No, I don't watch a peeing compilation. But sometimes there is one at the end of the video for some reason.
I'm just trying to watch the part where the logo comes up and then all of a sudden there's people pissing in each other's mouths.
I don't know what's going on.
I'm trying to watch the do do do do do do do
and the Pornhub logo comes up.
That's what I do.
OK, and then all of a sudden people are pissing on each other
and eating shit.
OK, what sound is that?
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
How does it go?
I don't know.
I said, is that a sound?
The Pornhub sound?
You don't know?
I don't know.
He's a very cool version.
Yeah. Well, I'm not pretending here.
I genuinely do not know what you're talking about.
- He's like boom, ba-da-da-da-da, boom.
- That's not what it sounds like.
- Or something.
- Does it do that?
- You're doing the Seinfeld thing.
- What?
- You're doing the Seinfeld theme song.
- No I'm not.
- Yes you are.
- No, the Pornhub comes up and it goes,
burn it, burn it, burn it, burn it, burn it, burn it.
That's a true story.
- No, I think you're completely making all this up.
- All the good porn sites have basically
been taken off the internet, if you ask me.
Which ones?
All the ones where you could steal
expensive ass porn.
Like what's expensive porn?
Like luxury ass fucking
VIP exclusive porn.
Is there like Rolex porn?
Is there Rolex porn?
I mean, I'm trying to understand.
Yes, there's there's
a lot of amazing porns
that you just can't watch anymore
unless you pay for them.
But back in the day,
you used to watch them for free.
Caliber, you were a gooner
when you were 17.
You know, I've always been so afraid of masturbating more than once a week
because I thought it would make me go to hell.
So, and probably no time other than, no time more than when I was 17.
So, no, I would not say I was a gooner.
Okay.
Yeah.
And also I was really, really scared of getting caught
because I got caught with porn when I was like 11
and I think it ruined my life probably.
- Ruined your life in what way?
Do you want to elaborate on that?
- Well, I broke the computer.
I've talked about this before.
I broke my computer 'cause I looked up nakedladies.com
and then I took the VGA cable in the back
and I didn't just rip it, I ripped it
and then I spread all the pins with a butter knife
and then when I, I don't know.
- Why did you do that?
- I don't know.
- I don't think that's to do with the porn.
I think you were insane.
The internet, the search history, I didn't know how to clear it.
So I ripped out the VGA cable, spread all the pins with a butter knife,
and then I was like, "Oh, fuck, I broke the computer."
So I started spraying super glue onto the back
because I thought that would fix it.
And so I glued the cable to where all the pins were spread down,
and there was no connection at all.
And then my dad got home from work, and he was trying to play Solitaire.
And I just heard him say, "What the fuck happened to the computer?"
And then they went and they got the computer fixed, and they brought it home.
And my mom was like, "Oh my God, the computer's home.
Let's all sit as a family and go to a website."
And she typed W and it auto-filled nakedladies.com.
Yeah.
And I got in big, big, big trouble.
Yeah, I can imagine.
Wait, so I just want to understand.
What...
So you go on the website.
I just want to know the timeline.
You go on the website and then something freaks you out.
You saw a naked lady and it freaked you out.
No, no, no.
I loved it.
Oh my God.
I was...
I love it at first sight.
seen all that before.
Yeah, it was a complete boob and pussy heaven.
Yeah.
Well, not pussy.
I always would turn it off before they showed their pussies.
Okay, why?
'Cause they're disgusting.
And I still think they're a little bit disgusting,
but I used to really hate them when I was a kid.
Found it.
Yeah, straight up, I'll say it.
When I was a kid, I hated pussy,
but now I'm basically addicted.
But yeah. Now it's okay.
Now it's fine.
Yeah, it's okay.
It's like a six out of 10.
Right.
But yeah.
It's like a five foot eight out of basketball scale.
Yeah, it's kind of Isaiah Thomas kind of hype.
Mm-hmm.
But yeah, I don't know.
Something about that, dude, that will make you not like porn
all that much, I think.
Hmm.
Yeah.
OK.
I had two years of goonery.
You gooned a lot?
When I was a freshman in college,
I had a gigabit ethernet connection.
Damn.
I just downloaded so much pornography.
And I would just delete it.
I just I would watch it once and delete it.
I would like terabytes, terabytes.
I would download.
I was oh my God, hard drive and deleting it.
Just as I was doing that on a private torrent site
and my ratio got so good from it that I've just never had to worry.
Whoa, nice.
Is it IPD?
Yeah, I have like terabytes of upload credit.
What's your ratio?
I think it's getting to about one now, but it's like my up and down is like three terabytes each.
Damn!
Oh my god.
That's crazy.
Yeah, and then I started taking Adderall and that was when it kicked up a notch.
You just beaten it on Adderall?
Oh yeah.
Just oh no railing it taking hours, hours long.
What's even the point of that, man?
Feels great.
It's long.
I don't think it feels very good.
That can't feel very good.
No, you know, it doesn't feel good on that role coming.
So it just keeps going.
It doesn't.
It feels like nothing.
It's worse.
Mm. What?
Yeah.
I've never done that.
Well, I think it's kind of making me scared to think of that, though.
Yeah, you can come as many times as you want and never feel the immense pain
that comes along with it.
This sounds amazing.
I want to try this.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, you should give it a shot.
They need to make a drug.
They need to make a drug that makes your penis hole
literally like four inches wide.
I think they'll make this.
No, I don't think they do yet.
Yeah, they make it.
That's just a kidney stone.
No, kidney stones are very small.
little rods you put in there.
Mm, the sounding rods.
I see. I don't want to touch the inside.
That grosses me out.
Yeah, because I'm uncomfortable in a story about it.
I want to look inside of it, though.
We're going to hide some stuff.
Yeah, like a telescope. Yeah, exactly.
Wait, what we had in there.
What I hide in there.
Yeah.
More and more drugs probably to get through TSA.
Yeah, probably hide a big, disgusting.
- Your giant gaping hole of a penis.
- Big nugget of brown weed stuck in my dick hole.
- I don't think you can get it through TSA.
- Oh God, dude, just like a brush being just dragged
out of the inside of your penis.
- I think they have a machine that specifically
that looks at you naked and they could completely see
that your penis has a thing inside of it.
- Have you guys ever seen your naked body
on that TSA scanner?
'Cause sometimes they have the screen turned the other way.
You can literally see both your balls hanging like perfectly like at equals three.
Kind of like, you see the balls.
It looks like Squidward's eyes and nose.
Yeah.
It's not, it is not discreet at all.
They, and also it's pointed.
Do you ever think they see a really tiny penis and laugh at it?
Oh yeah.
For sure.
That probably happens literally every day.
Yeah.
Do you think they see a really big one and the woman TSA agent kind of turns
around and gives them the eye.
No, this is the probably not.
This is the gooning Rex coming to life.
Yeah, you're imagining some sexual situation.
Women hate big dicks, dude.
That is true.
They think they're gross.
Yeah, that's what they always tell me.
Yeah, they don't like them.
They hurt, apparently.
So, yeah, I might want to think it's actually really good.
I don't have one.
It is good to all the hate to have one.
Have a 14 inch penis, dude.
I would hate that so much.
You know what I hear?
I hear that guys with big dicks feel less.
Really?
Yeah.
And they're not as smart.
I heard this.
And they die first, I was just thinking.
Yes, yes.
They die way earlier.
And I also heard that they honestly don't get that many girls.
Mm hmm.
And because, like I said, girls don't like and they definitely have
an increased risk of penile cancer.
Yeah.
And they got to chop it in half.
- That'd be funny if somebody was making some point
about guys with big dicks and he was like,
and having a big dick increases your risk
of contracting a STD.
- That's true.
- 'Cause they just fuck all night long waiting for it.
(laughing)
- More surface area.
Yeah.
I don't think any of that is true, by the way.
- I think I would rather have giant balls.
Did you ever see the video when you were a kid?
Do you ever see the video when you were a kid of the, um, the,
the guy with elephant Titus of his nutsack and he's jumping around on it like a
yoga ball. What? Yeah.
He lives in some kind of village or something and he's jumping around on his
balls. He lives in a village in Colorado.
Yeah. And he jumps around on his balls and the doctor,
I guess cursed him with that.
I don't know, I've never seen this.
- It might not exist, it might be some kind of ghost memory
I have from being a child with my brother.
I make stuff up from when I was a kid,
like things that I know that I saw so hard.
One of them was, I thought for a long time
that there was a Linkin Park music video
that takes place entirely in like a bathroom sink,
where everyone's really small.
But apparently that's not true.
- That feels like a thing that would be real.
- I'm a hundred percent sure to this day,
even though I've had a lot of people tell me
it does not take place in a sink,
that there is a Linkin Park music video
that takes place in a ceramic white sink.
- Okay, how does the song go?
- Wash those hands, wash those hands.
I don't know.
I think it might be "Numb."
I think "Numb" is the one I'm thinking of.
Mmm.
Yummy num num.
No.
Nummy nummy num song.
What was it? Yummy nummy sauce?
Yummy nummy nummy song.
Can you play the nummy song?
[Laughter]
I think when you move to New York
we might have to set you up with a couple of DJ gigs.
Yeah.
That'd be fun.
You could play slot music.
Yeah.
You play No Limit City slot music.
Yeah, just No Limit City, SoundCloud, top to bottom.
I feel like that's a good idea.
I've been thinking a lot about how it probably like
really is to become a DJ. You just have to like
learn one thing.
That's true about every skill.
You have to learn one thing to be good at any one thing.
Yeah.
No, but it's like especially you see it
with DJing. You just have to buy a thing.
I think it's an incredibly common skill.
But I think, you know,
Yeah, I don't think it's easy by any means. I don't think you have to be you have to have
a borderline genius IQ to be able to find out which two songs are going to go good back
to back. Yeah, I do not have that control the floor and get people moving and shaking. Yeah,
I'm not good at that shit. Yeah, I'm doing back to back three cascade to evacuate the
dance floor and then fucking Johnny Cash hurt and it's just people don't like
that kind of thing. To your list, who do you think would be the best DJ out of
the three of us and who would be the worst? Well I look like the best DJ
but I think I'd probably be the worst. I think you'd be the best Julio. I think probably
Julio would because he has probably the most and I won't even say the best I
think you have the most taste in music. I think you have the highest emotional
quotient an EQ if you will which is whoa the DJ with the high EQ oh my god yeah
yeah I would probably do playbook cardi into my night trust because I would
break I would like to break generous generous this beer just fucked me up
He's drunk. He's so fucked up. No, I'm not drunk. First time seeing him drunk. Very,
very excited about it. I will never be drunk. This sour is pretty tough to get through, man.
Yeah. This is not my favorite. You know, but I've had, I had a beer yesterday that I thought I
really liked. I had the Grimm Brewing Company Hefeweizen. Mm-hmm. And I had one, and I had
one of them before and I really enjoyed it. And this time I had one and I thought it was good.
But then I had a second one and the second one was so disgusting to me.
Was it the one that we missed out on when we were in New York?
I think a lot of – there are just some beers in this world that you're only meant to
have one of.
Anything more and it's violating the terms of service for this beer and you should not
be –
This is why the only S-tier beers are light beers because you can just drink a billion
of them.
I kind of agree, man.
Yeah, I don't disagree with that.
Seltzer, same deal.
Yeah, same deal.
Well, the normal ones.
I remember when I went to Rex's house,
I went to Target,
and I think it was either him or his roommate,
they bought those white cloths that were supercharged.
I forget what they're called.
Yeah, those ones.
Why are they making that?
Not good.
That shit was ass.
Yeah.
[Burps]
Do you think I never got a chance to have the bang energy?
Why clause?
They make white saucers.
Yeah.
That are like a bang flavored.
I would guess they're terrible because bang has got to be the worst
tasting energy drink on the market.
I would disagree with that, but I think it is so disgusting.
Did you know?
I used to love
the root beer bang.
No.
It was amazing.
And then they stopped making it,
presumably because I was the only person on earth to drink it.
Do they still make Bang?
Or isn't Bang in big trouble?
I feel like I haven't seen it in a while.
Uh, no, they still make it, but it's definitely not as popular
popular as it used to be.
It had a moment. It really did.
Yeah, well, they got ripped off by everyone.
And now everyone's ripping off Celsius in the same way.
Oh, so Celsius is disgusting.
Like Bang had like the formula that was like the 300 milligrams caffeine,
the BCAAs, the fucking creatine and shit.
And then like Monster made rain.
Mm hmm.
Oh, rain is made by Monster? Yes.
Oh, I didn't know that.
And then they they got like sued by Bang.
And then like there's there's like a rock star version of it.
There's like a couple other versions.
There's like a bunch of ones that had like 300 milligrams caffeine,
all the BCAAs, so like that formula.
So bang kind of fell off and then Celsius comes in like a 12 ounce cans,
got 200 milligrams of caffeine. It's got the thermogenic shit in it.
And then there's like a bunch of them that have that now like a Lonnie knew
shit. Right. That's my,
you really are a, a library of information about these energy drinks.
I kind of can't believe it. Yeah. Well I drink one probably every day.
What's your last batch? What's your most recent batch ordered?
I mean, I'm kind of out.
I have I've been drinking just monsters
right in front of him.
Here's two more different ones.
This is the same one.
He's lying.
You just picked up the same two cans in three different ways.
And now you're just oh, oh, my God, it wasn't a trick of the eyes.
It was not slight of hand.
I have a question for you.
Why store them in your desk on your desk?
Store them?
No, these are ones that I've opened and drank and then either finished or didn't finish.
But are.
Yes.
So why are you storing them on your desk?
Listen, you drink one every day.
You get to walk all the way to the trash.
I'm with you.
I'm not going to walk to the trash every day of my goddamn life.
OK, why not do it?
I'm not. I'm not.
I'm not monk. OK, I'm not.
So I'm not such a clean freak that I can't have 40 or 50 cans covered in spit and
maybe a couple of boogers that I put in there after I was done drinking them
sitting on my desk.
Okay.
I have a follow up question.
Have you ever seen a trash can in your life?
Sure.
Yeah.
What kind of question is that?
Okay.
So he keep, no, wait, just stick with me here.
Why not?
Just maybe like one of those little dandy useful trash cans
and keep it near near this or you throw your damn trash.
This is actually a very good point, but I will say one thing.
It would overflow and you would not take the trash out.
This one has liquid still in it, for example.
Well, that's where you put a bag in it.
You can put a bag in it.
No, I need to take that to the sink and dump it out.
OK, like a good boy and then throw it into the recyclables.
They can they can recycle with monster energy still in the can.
They can do drink it.
Though, thank you.
The guys like that. Yeah.
I'm actually anti trash guys right now.
Why is that?
Because I hired a guy.
I hired a company to pick up the trash at the office one month ago,
and I hired him to pick it up twice a week.
And he has missed every single time.
And then I call him every Monday and every Thursday.
I say, "Hey, the trash isn't picked up."
And he says, "Give me just one more chance.
Give me just one more chance.
I promise it'll get picked up."
That's funny.
Are you serious?
Yeah, if I don't do it, if the guys don't do it this week,
you could write us off.
Well, I'll never bother you again.
And then he just misses every single time.
What the fuck?
Wait, have we ever talked about the trash pile
in the office before?
Which one?
Okay, so when I went to New York
and I went to the office for the first time, I was-
The old one or the new one?
The new one.
I was quite taken aback about how beautiful
and large the space was.
But as soon as you enter and you turn to your right,
there's a big pile of just garbage just sitting there.
Well, guess what, Julio?
That is gone.
Okay, so I felt really--
But not because this guy picked it up.
It's because I put it all in my car
and dumped it on a random street in Queens.
Oh, great.
Yeah, which I can get a ticket for,
but I didn't do it.
Yeah, someone else did it.
Brian did it.
Yes, it was Brian.
And he stole all the chairs.
What?
I can't believe he did all that by himself.
I'd like to imagine all of you wearing ski masks to go slowly wheel out.
There was a guy, one of his friends who also works at the company was there when we were there.
And I told him, I was like, man, straight up, if you were not here, I want you to know that I would be stealing
I'd be stealing MacBooks and monitors.
I'd be stealing so much shit.
And he was like, I know dude, that's why I'm here.
His boss brought it, his boss put him there
'cause they knew that me and Brian were coming.
(laughing)
- Oh, that's really funny.
So what are they gonna do?
They're just gonna sell that shit?
Or open a new company with it?
- They were saying, well, the company's moving.
And so I guess that it was more expensive
to move this entire office
than to just like basically let employees take most of whatever they wanted.
But, uh, they, there was certain things you weren't allowed to take.
I did want to take, there was like, I wanted to, I picked up like four Apple
TVs and then the guy was like, you cannot take Apple TVs.
I was like, come on, fuck you.
Just one.
I was complaining so much about getting all this free shit.
That's so funny.
What the fuck would you take?
Do you, what would you take four Apple TVs?
You don't even have, you have, you barely have one TV.
Oh man, I don't know.
To sell them?
Yeah, I hear you.
For $50 each on Facebook Marketplace?
You're not a hustler.
Oh, I'm a hustler.
No.
I've sold stuff before.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Anytime I get a new laptop, I sell my old laptop for $300,
even if it's worth way more.
That's really smart.
I need to do that.
I'm kind of in the process of doing that.
I don't know if you remember, there
used to be a little mini fridge right here.
But I once had a thing in there that I never used it,
and it got a mold in it.
It's gone.
It's sold.
I hustled.
You hustled the fridge?
Someone's uncle.
Yep. I hustled the fridge.
Wow.
Everyone is someone's uncle.
With that money.
Damn.
I got this big ass stream
deck.
That's an iPad.
That's my iPad actually.
I just lied.
Fucking idiot.
That's not a stream deck at all.
You already had that iPad.
No, I just bought that.
I can see the Apple pencil.
I just bought that. I bought both of those yesterday.
You're like that girl that peed after squirting.
Yep.
A liar.
I also just bought this as well.
You did not buy that just now.
I just bought this.
No.
I wish I could pick you up and say that I just bought you.
You wish you could do that.
I would do anything to buy your freedom.
Yeah.
I think I want to give you an h1b visa. Yeah, I think if I moved to the US I would be so incredibly
stressed every single day of my life. Oh yeah, that's what it's all about. That's because you
live in the land of siestas. You know we do here? We work. Why? Sometimes two and maybe three hours
some days. I think life would be way more expensive than my current life. Yeah, but
- And that would stress me out. - He would make more money.
No, he wouldn't make-- no, no, don't tell him that.
He would not make-- he would not make any more money.
- I mean... - I pay him the maximum amount that I can
and I'm still able to live.
- I-- he would not make any more money. - Well, you-- he would get another job.
I would.
You would definitely have to.
What do you do now?
You didn't even edit the last pod-- you didn't even listen
to the last podcast enough to see that it was de-sync.
Here's how much I love Julio.
He is routinely, at least once a month,
terrible at his job.
So, so bad.
Like next level bad.
Fucks something up so catastrophically.
People don't listen to an episode.
The episode gets 20% of the normal downloads
because the audio is unlistenable
or the video is fucked up, something like that.
That's never happened before.
But I don't care.
I don't care at all.
He's my buddy.
he has a he plays video games with me what am I gonna fire him and do the easiest
job ever by myself no no there's sometimes there's issues I will admit
sometimes said tank answer would just have an issue and we'll meet only there
is some way to maybe like audit the audio
So, well, okay, here's my defense.
We record way too late on Thursdays.
Sometimes.
Oh, I was just so busy.
Oh, I was playing Valorant with my friends.
You couldn't have it on in the background while you're playing?
No, I have one monitor, man.
What do you think I'm going to do?
He doesn't have one monitor.
That's a lie.
That is also a lie.
And you have an iPad.
What does the iPad have to do with anything?
Use it as another monitor.
Yeah, you have a laptop, an iPad, and a desktop computer and you can't listen to a fucking podcast?
I also I don't have a desk or a chair and I live in a box
You're in the chair right now!
I see the chair your video is on I know that you have a chair. I don't know about the desk
I can't see the desk. And you have headphones
You have multiple pairs of headphones
I will just say if I want you to know if anybody if you work for anybody except your close friend
You would have been fired so fast
We have people messages every single day every single day they message us and they say hey, I'm a student
Can I work for you guys for free as an intern and every single time I say no because I decided to hire
Some fucking Mexican guy to do the worst job ever
No, I got, I completely got what it takes.
I think I could make it the big leagues. I think I could edit the daily.
You could not edit the daily. I could edit the daily.
You could not straight up. You could not edit the daily.
It's so easy.
It's not easier than the podcast that you already edit.
I got, I got the skills. I know how to do it.
You have no skills.
The detail is low.
Yes, you have low conscientiousness.
You score low on the perfectionist quartile.
Yes, you do. I can tell.
You know why? Because you love chilling.
And that's why I like you.
Because you like chilling so much.
And that's why we love you.
I do love chilling.
You probably do the same.
You probably do as well as I would in your situation.
And that's why I like you.
I take, I thought, I was thinking, I've been thinking about my
my sofa bed for this entire conversation.
And I think you guys can both come together
because it has like two compartments.
You can sleep on top and the bottom.
You can pull that out.
He's changing the subject.
He is changing the subject.
We're talking about how bad he is at his job.
And he says, check out my couch.
Check out my couch that you can come sleep on.
How is that?
That's not a good deflection at all.
We saw right through that.
What's that?
I'm actually--
(laughing)
That's why he's hired.
That's why he has the job.
'Cause he's a slippery bastard.
He really is.
He's so slimy.
Yeah, you are slimy.
No.
What do you think you'll be doing in 10 years?
'Cause I know that you will not be working for me.
I'll probably be dead.
You think you'll die in 10 years?
I think I'm gonna die in 10 years, yeah.
Of what?
I can see that.
I got fired.
I got fired and I died.
Yeah, it is.
It is funny that I could just ruin just an entire, probably an
entire family if I fired you.
No, no, you don't want to do that.
No, I'm not going to do it.
Not yet, but maybe one day I will fire you unceremoniously.
You get like nine, 10 more chances.
- I'll be like, oh man, we gotta let you go.
I'm so sorry.
And then I'll still make you work for six weeks
and then you'll, and then you will officially be fired.
But I'll make you work for six weeks
and I'll give you a bunch of meetings where I'm like,
I hate doing this.
Oh my God, I really wish we could keep you.
But we have to fire you so badly and you suck so much shit.
It'd be so sad.
- You know, I'm gonna be fired from my job.
- Really?
Someone I know just got fired and he was telling me that he had like a bunch of meetings, he
just had to keep working for like six weeks and he had a bunch of meetings.
Six weeks?
Six weeks.
Yeah.
But I mean he was very checked out but he kept, he had to have like his meetings and
stuff and his boss just kept getting on the meetings and just being like, "Dude, it's
just not right what we're doing to you.
It's just not, it's just wrong."
Dude, six weeks is insane.
Yeah.
Yeah, it was really crazy.
It's too much.
Yeah, poor guy.
Yeah, I think it is wrong to be fired.
I don't think I've ever been fired.
Oh, no, I've been fired from Jersey Mike's, but that was it.
You were kind of caught and fired at one thing that you were like scamming a university
where they're paying you to do COVID.
Oh, I was not caught, but yeah, I worked for the museum at MIT, the art museum,
And the lady, my manager, very, very sweet lady,
she just kept paying me to do.
She I had to do a basically a one once a week.
I had to write a one page paper that was like,
here's how museums are handling the like covid lockdowns and do.
It was like a research position.
And then her boss found out that she was paying me to do nothing
and nobody ever read any of these things.
And then I got fired.
That's dope.
It was, it was amazing.
Cause she's an amazing lady.
And then you got unemployment.
Yes.
And then I, the Massachusetts unemployment agency found out that I was making money
from the podcast and I've owed Massachusetts like $3,000 for like four years now.
You will never ever get this.
And one day you will not get this.
You will never get this.
Yeah.
funny like meme to send the IRS.
You want to
just like a printed picture of Borat
put it in the mail?
Yeah. With my tax return, says exactly how much I owe.
You will never get this.
Yeah. Yeah, it's like one of those novelty cards that have like
it's a pop up.
Yeah, it's it's well, it's the one that has like a speaker in it
that you open it and it says it and they kind of unfurl your W two.
And yeah, but it's not even it's not even recording off the movie.
It's you saying, yeah, it's you saying
you shifty Jew.
I'm adding my own lines.
I'm adding my own anti-Semitic lines.
I've been saying you will never get this IRS.
Yeah. Have you ever been fired?
Yep. From where?
The debt collector job.
I got fired for forgiving too many people's debt.
Oh, yeah. Oh, he was too.
You were so much of an angel.
You're too kind.
I was, that's literally what it was.
Wow.
You got fired in three months.
You were so much of a sweet angel.
That's fucked up, man.
They didn't even let me finish the probation period.
They're like, "You are monumentally terrible at this job."
Wow.
That's funny.
I hate those bastards.
Another reason I hate debt collectors.
I didn't have it in me.
To be evil?
Yeah, because I lived with the guy that I worked with there, and he would just come home and
watch cop shows and say racist stuff at the TV.
He had what it took.
He had it in him.
He had that dog in him.
He had the malice.
He was born and bred for that.
Yeah.
Whereas me, I was so kind.
I was like, "I totally understand.
Capitalism's so bad."
Yeah.
You're talking about capitalism to these old ladies?
No, not really.
Were you doing pranks and the phone calls?
No, but they were, you know.
Were you doing prankses?
Prankses.
Yeah, I was doing prankses.
Nice.
It was a really dumb job.
I definitely felt bad doing it every day.
- It is funny how there's actually evil in the world.
There's evil people.
- Like rats. - Yeah, they're dope as fuck.
- There's demons roaming around the world.
- Yeah, Hunter Biden. - One attacked our friend.
- Yeah.
- But we're not allowed to talk about it apparently.
- I think he lied about that.
- He got attacked by an evil child.
- He got attacked by a demon, but he won't talk about it.
He was working at a school for kids.
- Our friend, we told him to come on the podcast
and tell the story.
Apparently he signed an NDA,
so he's not allowed to talk about it.
I think he was joking about that.
He got attacked by a child who claimed that he was evil.
So you'll hear about it later.
I won't tell the story.
I'll just tell you guys what I told them.
I told them what he told me this story.
He first texted me.
He's like, "I just got beat up at work or whatever."
I'm like, "Oh my God, are you OK? What happened?"
He's like, "Yeah, I'm all good."
And he's just like, "I'll tell you later."
And he just goes, "Fuck it! Hop on Discord right now and I'll tell you."
I was like, "Okay, whatever, man."
I hop on Discord and he tells me this huge story that we can't tell,
but it's about a demon beating him up.
And he tells me about the fact that the demon did tell him that he was evil,
way, way, way before beating him up.
And then what I told him at the end was he told me this really hard story
about the demon and its surroundings.
And then it's like yeah, I mean it's a it's a tough job or whatever. It's his job
To deal with demons, and then I I just told them well
You know what I think I think it's that you had it coming
Because he told you he was evil and you still poked the bear. That's true. That's real shit
Yep, if a child looks you in the eyes and says I'm evil
You walk the other way man
And you turn around yeah, yeah, just let him roam the world let him on YouTube and get the fuck out of
of there, dude. I don't want I don't want anything to do with this this fucking
evil kid, but our friend never learned that lesson I guess. Yeah, and he's dead now.
That's because he's Vietnamese. And he died. Don't give details. And his name is Brian?
And he stole all that shit? And he dumbed all that shit? Oh yeah, sure. It was Brian.
Yeah, maybe if Brian gave that kid an Aaron, it wouldn't have been so evil. True. Good point.
room. Okay, all right. I have to go. Okay. Bye. Bye.