*sips*
Yeah.
*burps*
You're listening to Beers We Drank, America's number one beer podcast.
*record scratch*
*music*
What's up all my channels?
I'm trying to get that burp out there.
*burps*
God, I've never heard it before.
*music*
We drank motherfucker with Juvio Caleb and Rex
Do you think that's the longest theme song in podcasting history live
From beer East I'm Sylvania hop on your barley Davidson. You're late to the hopper. Ah, you've just entered
Ever
live
Beers we drank guys first of all cheers my friends. Cheers my friends. Shall we cheers?
All right. Well, you are
Completely showing off already. So I'd like to go ahead and see what you have to drink there. I have a
Duncan's fight iced tea
It's a iced tea with lemon
From Dunkin Donuts. I'm not gonna lie to you dog. That sounds amazing
Not bad. Does it taste like?
donut
No, it tastes like iced tea with
Alcohol on it. That sounds amazing. Okay now take a sip
You know the deal give us a scale one numerical and one basketball player
Yeah, this is like a 5/8
Okay, like a like a 5.8 so like
It's doable, it's serviceable, it'll work.
It tastes like someone left an Arizona iced tea outside for two days and then you found
it and started drinking it.
It was cool out, but it was outside for sure.
So it tastes fermented.
It tastes like fermented, probably exactly what it is, fermented tea.
Yeah.
Oh no, it's spiked, sorry.
It's spiked, right.
Does it say what exactly it is spiked with?
Yeah, can you read the whole ingredient list?
Does he have red 40?
Yes or no?
So this is a premium malt beverage
and it doesn't say anything else.
Oh, it's malt.
Slightly sweet with a twist of lemon.
So you're hopping on the barley Davidson.
Guys, you gave me nothing for the taste tricks re-bloated.
Nobody gave me anything for that.
I didn't even see that.
I said, I said, you've now entered the Tasterix Rebloaded.
This is a good, this is a good pun.
Guys, I had my wife go ahead and pick me up a couple of beers.
This first one I, I am none too happy about.
Guys, this is the Pumpkin Pie Scraper.
This is not my kind of beer.
If you've been following along all these weeks, this is not my kind of beer, man.
This is just not me.
This is a Rex type beer.
So, you guys have just gone ahead and done the pumpkin spice, fall, white girl type of
Starbucks type of episode today.
Definitely.
This is a pumpkin ale with vanilla beans, spices, maple syrup, and lactose.
And I'm going to go ahead and give this one a bit of a sip.
It's a large beer.
Honestly, it's not as sweet as I was anticipating.
It's definitely, it's pumpkin-y, it tastes kind of fall-y, you know.
It's decent.
I'm going to give this a 6.4, and we'll call that a league average 6.6 player.
Guys, this is not going to be a star, but this is like a, you know, bottom of the barrel
starting small forward.
This is an alright beer.
Well, I guess...
Cubio?
Going with the fall vibes, I've gone ahead and picked up a... what appears to be a...
A sunbeard.
A family beer.
Oh, wow.
Because we serve each other...
Wait, that's you and Rex.
Wait, that's completely you and Rex!
Wait!
I don't think that's very funny.
You don't think that looks like you two?
Are you crazy?
Wait, that's you and Rex.
I'm pretty sure that's a woman, that's why I don't find that to be particularly funny.
I'd be pretty sure that you were a woman if I looked at you and didn't know your body.
It's just the blurring on the camera.
Hang on, let me fix that for you, Rex.
What do you mean you know my body?
If I didn't know that you had human male genitals, for the most part, then I would say that you
were a girl.
What do you mean for the most part?
I think that kind of looks like me.
Wow, that does look like you too.
Yeah, so it's the me and Rex beer.
Is that why you got it?
No, I got it because I can't read what it's called.
It says...
I have no idea what that means.
It's completely in German I assume.
And I just thought it was beer, but I wasn't sure at the 7-Eleven until I walked out and
I saw it right there.
Yeah, you woke up.
A full bodied beer.
So basically this is going to put me to sleep as soon as we're done recording.
Or maybe just halfway through, which would be better.
All right review that bitch
So I think over the past couple weeks had a really good track record with with beers that I liked
This one is one of those that I don't like
Oh, no, the thing is you have such a simple you have like you have like you like beer that a kid would like
Yeah, he has Homer Simpson's beer palette. Yeah, like you like the beer. I've drank you like you're on the show
I'm the only job like chicken finger chicken finger french fries kind of thing
You like pizza.
I think the skills are all fucked because we have never drank the exact same beer on this
exact same episode except for once or maybe twice.
So I don't know.
We have done that once.
Yeah, we did a Modelo episode.
Or maybe twice during the office when we were in New York.
No it was when I was in New York.
We did that three times on that episode.
Yeah, well we did it two and a half times.
Were we, did we review those or did we just drink them?
I just drank them.
Also, Bud Light episode, did that ever happen?
I think one of them didn't happen because Killa just kept drinking all the beers.
Wait!
I'm being blamed for being cool?
Oh, boohoo, I'm so good at drinking that I drank the entire six pack before we could
drink them.
Man, fuck yo bitch ass.
well anyways with this is a 5'7" person trying to try out for the
league. So they're not gonna make it. My arm looks crazy right now.
This is a very low chance of this person making it. What if he was a 6'6" person but he was very fat because he's full body.
Oh yeah that could work too. I guess we need to do BMI in combination.
- Yeah, and we also need to say whether they're
athletically gifted, genetically,
or perhaps maybe like an old free throw style shooter.
- This is a seven one person with no legs.
- We could say either a dark beer or a light beer.
- Anyway, I don't like this.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
Guys, I have big news.
- What's your big news?
- I have finally been accused of using steroids.
- Oh, well, okay.
(clapping)
Congrats, man.
- Not so much accused, but I woke up today
to a comedian I know texting me, and he said,
"Caleb, do you take any gear
"or performance enhancing drugs for lifting?"
And I had to-- - Nothing but BCAAs
and cocaine, my brother.
- I had to let him down, man.
I said, "No, man, I'm herbal supplements only, my friend."
But then I told this to Noah, and he was like,
Like you really should have given him like an insane fake steroid stack.
But I had a real kind of rubber band of a day where that was the first thing that happened
to me today and that was amazing.
That made me feel like an amazingly huge celebrity.
But then what made me feel like a non-celebrity was I told this to Noah and then he said, "If
you took steroids and you looked like this, that would be really funny."
I was like, "Whoa! What the hell? What is that about, man? That's mean!"
And then I was thinking all day about how to get him back for that meanness.
And then I made up a story about, I said a really pale woman walked by me and the dog earlier,
and the dog tried to chase her because he thought it was you.
And he believed me.
I saw a chart on Twitter that was like, taking steroids and doing nothing.
Just taking steroids will literally double the amount of muscle mass you get from doing
just regular exercise.
Pretty much, yeah.
If you take steroids, you can do, like I think I've told you guys this before, but there's
There's a guy who owns my gym.
He is huge.
He's massive.
And the other day, he had 120-pound dumbbells in each hand
going up for an incline bench press, one of these.
And he told this guy next to him,
he had headphones on, he was like,
"Hey, man, can you help me out?"
And he's like, "Yeah, sure."
He said, "Say that I'm a bitch
"and say that I can't do this."
And the guy was like, "What?"
And he's like, "Yeah, say that I'm a stupid fucking pussy and I can't do this shit."
And he was like, "Uh, okay."
So he gets down and he goes, "Hoo, hoo, hoo, hoo."
And then he says, "Say it."
And the guy goes, "You're a fucking stupid bitch and you can't do this shit."
And he's like completely pumped up to the maximum, so ready to go, and he moves the
weight about this much, like, at a time.
Does like this.
And I was like, "Oh yeah, if you're on steroids, you can just do that.
You can just go and do like, almost like you're in an improv class making fun of somebody working
out.
Just do the tiniest little range of motion.
As long as you look, as long as you kind of make yourself crazy, I think it works.
Well, this also kind of depends on-
Isn't it cool to do that and have a weighted pencil and write essays and then your arm
is just like, you know?
Did the person that asked you this, did it work out?
Did they just assume that it's-
No, I don't think so.
I don't think so.
last time I saw him I did I was wearing a shirt that was about a size and a half
too small for me and so maybe it was it maybe he got fooled by an optical
illusion which who could blame him it's happened all of us those stairs don't
know how they work yeah I'm really happy for you that's you deserve that it was
honestly hard work that was a week yep more than one less than three times a
week guys I've been grinding but that was a pretty amazing was the last time you
guys got an amazing compliment where you said wow that is good this is the
problem our men are not getting complimented enough in this shit
society here I'll give you both compliments right now Rex you don't look
anything like a woman well thank you you look nothing like the person on that
beer. Jubio, you look exactly like the person on that beer. This is a compliment to both
of you. That's a good looking guy. Look at that guy. He looks like a soccer player.
I don't know who they are. I think that's Chris Gethard.
I don't know who that is. His name is Chris Gethard. Has anyone pointed
that out? That his name is Chris Gethard? Probably multiple
children throughout his life, I would say. Yeah. I do think certain people's names lead
them to like it forces them on the narrow path of community.
Yeah, Matt Rifle.
Pitts.
Yeah.
Funny name.
Well no, you have an adorable name.
You could be like a construction worker.
All right, I'll do that.
I thought I had to be a fucking comedian.
I would so much rather be a construction worker.
You could be a plumber.
Yeah.
I want to work, I want to be...
Sanitation.
Some kind of scientist, a good scientist.
I want to be a good scientist, I want to heal people.
What's a good scientist?
Somebody who can heal people.
I'm not sure what that is.
a good scientist and want to heal people. What's a good scientist? Somebody who doesn't work
for some doofenshmirps type evil guy. I don't want to be in a layer. I want to be doing science,
not in a layer and not in an underground anything. So you want to be in a lab, not in a dungeon?
Lab not layer. This is something that we need to tell our biology 101 students. Day one,
That should be big letters on the whiteboard.
Lab not layer.
- Is it biology?
- I mean.
- We're gonna have evil biologists.
What are they gonna do?
- As an anti-American leftist,
I think that working for a supervillain.
I disgust me.
I think working for a supervillain is probably
less ontologically evil than working for the government.
- Hold the phone, wait.
the
Well, I want to do some kind of amazing giant out of this park
because my friend Rex just said ontological on a Twitch stream,
guys.
This is huge.
Ontological.
Yep.
And for those who did not go to higher education
and maybe dropped out of high school, ontological--
Yeah, and don't watch Hasan Piker.
And do not watch Hasan Piker, who's live right now.
go check them out. Guys, this is a word that means basically stuff. So this is one of the
best words to just say whenever you want. I'm serious.
You can say it whenever you want. Say ontology, say ontological, whenever, man.
This just means existing stuff. This is a great, great word.
This is ontological, you hear? Yes, it is. That's the amazing thing about
it. This is one of the best words ever. And thank you, Rex, for opening us up to this
How is it you think you would have it like infiltrating the debate streaming YouTube circles from 1 to 10?
It would probably be very
What's your idea? Let me hear your idea because i'll be honest. I don't see a path forward for that. I think it's completely so easy
I think that like who am I gonna get to argue with me? Listen, listen to me destiny
I feel like you and destiny would have one of the most amazing
Anyway for our debates and like double-digit like person who just like gets on on the touch stream and just like talks about like yeah
Fucking politics is bullshit fucking Joe Biden is gay
They eventually just get into the debate with like like anyone who does like three or four thousand four like four thousand viewers
It's I think you you could do it
this train still do his
His his podcast with 15 people where he gets 15 people in a discord call who are all different races and ideologies
and then has them just argue about like what about the weather like shit like that?
No, but it looks like someone in the chat is saying that he does but now they have sex.
What?
That's alright.
I think that's Adam22.
Yeah, you're thinking of Adam22.
True.
Adam22 does a podcast where him and his wife interview somebody and then they have sex with
the person.
Ah, gross.
Is that disgusting?
what is it called what is it called that's so gross but what guys it's
called plug talk do not look up this it really doesn't they should call it
fucking fucking fucking that makes way more sense than plug talk and it's only
- If it's only four minutes long,
this podcast stinks.
- If it was my podcast, it'd be about--
- Wait, it's only four minutes long.
- Four seconds long.
- Oh. - No, I'm kidding.
Adam22 and Lean to the Plug, if you would have me,
I would love to be the first male guest on Plug Talk.
- Shouts out.
- If I have male guests on Plug Talk,
I don't know if I'll follow it back closely.
- I don't think so, because Adam22 is not fucking gay.
- I'm gonna jog my memory real quick.
had male guests before. Who you're jogging your memory? I just jogged my memory and they've
had wait this one has like a thousand people on this one. Look how many people they have
on this one. Are you streaming pornography? All these people? No it's not porn it's just
like the the pre-porn thing. But then somebody's having sexier guys. Yeah
probably all of them probably in a dope-ass Eyes Wide Shut style orgy. Doesn't
it feel like there's so much pornography in this world that probably one in three
people has made some kind of pornographic video before? Well okay are
you like a wide like released on the internet or just in the sanctity of their
own home for private enjoyment. I don't fucking know it's fucking disgusting
either way if you ask me it's the same shit. I don't care if you watch it and I don't
care if a million people watch it you're going to hell. You said one in three? One in
three like somebody who's watching this right now is the star of a
pornographic video. So I haven't done anything like that.
Rest have you done something like that? He's done look at that face he's done it
He's done it. He's made a movie before.
I will not do that.
What is this liar's twitch that you have? This tick?
I've never... your lying tick is that you rub your vape against your can?
No, it's just condensating a lot.
So I was having fun with the condensation.
I don't understand.
Why are you trying to paint me out with some evil put on?
No, no, you're not...
Heritage you might be the only good pornographer that's ever lived. I could I do feel like I have seen
Your entire body only from like the chest down before I'll say that
Maybe you do
Oh
I bet you're one of these guys who makes these who goes on Oh Megal and has
Like the biggest dick in the world and just jacks off
A lot of people, anytime you go to Omegle, you go through like-
How often do you go to Omegle?
I mean, I gotta get the news somewhere.
So I go on Omegle and I say, "Do you know what's going on today? What's happening in Ukraine?"
And this guy's over there, some Indian guy going, "Ahhhhhh!"
[laughter]
It's like every third guy.
I really, I really didn't think that Omegle was still a thing
until I guess, it just kept getting brought back up.
I really haven't thought about that side in the years, but it appears that you're browsing
it every day.
I haven't probably been on in quite some time, but it used to be pretty fun, man.
I've said it before, but you used to go out and show your child asshole to adults.
That was funny.
That was some funny shit.
That never gets old, guys.
You shave child asshole?
Yeah.
Well, you don't shave it.
it doesn't have any hair to begin with I'm a child shaved who's shaving my
asshole you fucking pervert you are well nowadays yes but when I was a kid didn't
have to okay that was one of the biggest luxuries of being a kid summers off no
ass hair would you shave your asshole if it made shitting like maybe 5% easier I
do and it does we've talked about this have we yeah I shave my asshole everyone
to
I'm showering and I'm like, "Oh man, it's hairy down there."
And then I will shave my entire, my asshole.
How do you notice it's hairy down there?
I'm fucking, I'm in the shower.
I'm fingering my ass.
I mean, can you, how do you even see?
Like, do you get like a mirror in there?
I don't need to see.
Hair has texture.
Yeah, but how, how do you know you're getting it all?
You don't want to have like the Hitler mustache of anal hair.
I just keep feeling.
keep
I agree. Actually, apparently Manscaped makes basically a taco that you- a taco shell that
you put in your ass and it takes all the hair away. So I might buy that.
I've read- Actually, I don't know if that's true.
I've read really poor reviews. That's a really good idea for a product for
Manscaped. It's like, it's shaped exactly like a taco shell, and then you shove it in your
ass and it takes all of the hair away.
I don't think I know, like, I don't think I can imagine that,
why is it shaped like a taco?
- Well, have you ever seen your ass?
- 'Cause your ass is shaped like the shell of a taco shell.
- Yeah.
- Your ass is basically what--
- The whitespace of an asshole is a taco.
- If a taco shell was the taco meat,
your ass would be perfectly shaped
to be the holder of the meat.
- Right.
It's like a book that's opened up,
the uh...
two thousand page book
open middle
yet that's a kind of beautiful
but like a lot of seagull in the background of a pain yes
you know just kind of a faraway seagull kind of thing
this is the biggest gusty
it's not a good luck it's just a lot of
it is this group is worth way
i knew a guy who on his wedding night
uh...
he's a virgin
on his wedding night
nared his balls
penis
and his asshole
for the night before his wedding i guess
it was not me
thank you for calling me a virgin though i fucking wish
but no
it was a guy i know
i can't guide really don't go to more details but
it may be just a male tell you
how i
can you tell me
yeah who is it
my brother-in-law
but
but it doesn't matter which one i would i've got a lot of brothers-in-law
yet it's levi
that's my brother in the other world life that's my brother in life
your mind brother
while that's a major so that my friend is
Guys I'm kind of running through this pumpkin pie scraper. This is not what I was thinking
Mmm actually good man. I'm not gonna let you I had a backup beer. I had a Stella Artois
That is that I already drank some of because I was like I was like this is gonna be disgusting
I'm not gonna want to drink any of this but actually good
But now I'm gonna finish this Stella Artois off guys
- Guys, this is an amazing beer.
- I can barely get through one of the weird beers
that I buy sometimes.
I don't know how you get through two of them.
I get so-- - He's an alcoholic.
- I get so sleepy.
- Yeah, that's-- - He doesn't get giant cans.
- Well, this one's, this is like the biggest one
in a while.
- I get 16 ouncers, but I also have a high tolerance
for beer.
the other day we were at some week
we like last week i think
i came home to play our valorant league games
from a bar where i had already had like three drinks
and i had
i think i had probably ninety six ounces of beer when i got home
and then i went to bed
and it did not feel very good
but i did it
And that's really what it's about, right?
It's about kind of just ringing the bell.
- What bell?
- One of our house guests threw up last night.
And it was very funny, like laying in bed,
listening to the process of someone coming in
and like throwing up and then like hearing someone be like,
no, don't worry about the shower curtain.
No, no, no, it's fine.
- Oh, your house guest.
How many people are you housing at the moment?
- There was two last night.
- I see.
- And now it's just this one unwanted one.
Yes.
Yeah, Rex is currently housing the dead.
And there's...
...about to be another, apparently.
How are we gonna get this fool out?
I don't know.
It is so miserable.
Can you get him in here right now?
No.
Yeah, can you call him?
Can you...
Can you come grab him and say, "Hey, we're talking about how much everyone hates you."
Yeah, I'm talking about how you fucking suck and I wish you weren't here.
Is it a, uh...
Do you dislike him personally, too?
He's not just a bad house guest, he's...
See that's the worst man, because then it makes you not like the person, just because they leave the fridge open and shit.
Yeah, it's like, uh, he just plays really loud fucking music on the TV from like, till 3am.
I don't think-
What is wrong- just get headphones man, go bring him some headphones really passive aggressively.
Bring him a pair of headphones.
I don't think Rex has the ability to just dislike someone off rip. I think you are too kind of a soul.
I'm always willing to see the inherent goodness in autistic, retarded men.
It's because someone did it for you one time.
Exactly. The two men on this call.
Yeah, because we gave you about a hundred tries, and now you have to do this for every guy like you.
Yeah, that's fair.
So paying it forward, you know?
Yeah, that's sweet.
I haven't had an unwanted house guest in a very long time.
I'm trying to think, I mean my mom stayed with me, that was fucking annoying.
Yeah.
I feel like I just naturally just fall into Jerry Seinfeld-esque situations.
I wonder why.
Natural.
I wonder why, Julio.
What reason are you thinking?
I don't know, I wonder why.
What do you mean you wonder why? He's fucking, he's Jewish in New York City.
Yeah, yeah.
What kind of last name do you think Rex's...
What kind of job would Rex's last name, do you think, would get him?
That's a weird question to ask.
If Caleb's last name is...
My last name wouldn't do anything for me.
I think it's... I was thinking about it for a while, but it was really hard...
Oh, you were?
It was really hard not to just say something like...
Something really bad.
Like banking?
That's one that I was thinking.
Why would it, I mean I guess it does kind of sound like bank.
Like a check.
Mmmmm.
That's smart.
What part of, what part of Steinowitz sounds like a bankers name?
I don't understand.
That doesn't make any sense to me.
What do you think Caleb?
What do I think Rex would be?
Yeah.
A football player.
you
that's a football players last I could see that on the back of an Eagles jersey guys
you do you don't know my last name
I completely do actually know all seven of your names and your address
pretty true
yeah yours would go on a different kind of football jersey my friend
yep no yours you would be
you would be the guy that works in an auto shop that makes mufflers louder
- Oh yeah, you take the catalytic converters out of cars.
That would be your job.
Yeah, yeah.
- I wish I knew anything about cars.
It sucks so bad.
Right before I left to go to Texas,
I got my car serviced and they were like,
yo, there's like an issue with like the,
the support for your engine and for like your suspension.
I was like, oh shit.
and they were like, "But it's not like something urgent,
"you can like wait a little bit,
"we should like really, you should take care of that."
I was like, "Oh, okay."
So I just immediately the next day,
I just like drove like 500 kilometers,
like 400 miles to a different country.
And I didn't die.
So I think cars are just bullshit.
- I agree, I think all this car stuff is,
it's because there's too much gatekeeping in the car world.
Where I walk in and I say,
I say, "Hey, all the lights in the doohickeys are going off in my car."
And they say, "Oh, well this means this and this."
And I say, "You think I'm a fucking idiot?"
Okay?
I'm 90% sure that you're trying to screw me, okay?
Because I may not know what any of these symbols mean,
but I know that you only have 3.9 stars on Yelp,
and that means that you're probably screwing somebody over.
Yep.
But I'm not gonna ever learn that shit.
No.
I have a latent DIY-like issue in my brain that makes me want to do that kind of stuff
myself.
I just hate spending money.
I like one-on-one on a card.
I know.
I hate spending money.
I replaced my side-view mirror.
It took me hours.
It's supposed to be like a ten-minute fix.
It took me fucking hours.
I had to have my cousin there to hold stuff for me.
It took me forever.
It was the hottest day of the summer.
And then right after I did that, my fucking wife broke the other mirror.
So now I have to...
ago I'm gonna do that shit again.
Zip tie mirrors.
And then she was like, well it's not a big deal.
You did it once before.
I said, oh you stupid bitch.
You don't even know the half of it.
You don't even know that it took two guys.
And now you're gonna have to come out there
and sit with me.
While I yell at you.
Yeah, while I yell at you, pretend it's your fault you haven't touched it a single time.
Just hand me the fucking screwdriver!
The part's gotta be wrong.
We had to have ordered the fucking wrong part.
God.
It's so funny how pissed you get like
instantly when you're doing
anything like
with tools.
Yeah. The moment like a hammer
is in your hand, you're like, I could fucking
murder. Anything like that
I immediately get like the most
insane, anything that I don't know what I'm doing.
Like I know my way around like power tools,
I can build stuff, but if I'm
doing something with a car, as
As soon as I start doing it, I get the most insane stress headache, where I just instantly
have to lay down.
I'm like, "I can't even, I don't even want to do, I can't do any of this."
And I just give up so, so fast.
I fucking hate working on cars.
I had to replace my spark plugs a couple years ago, and I didn't have enough money to go
get it, have somebody do it for me.
I was working on my Volkswagen Rabbit.
Broke the fuck out of my engine cover.
Just destroyed it.
It had like a plastic cover.
I just obliterated it.
It was just in pieces.
I just suck at that kind of thing, man.
I'm never gonna be good.
Yeah, that's one of those things you just need to know a guy.
Because no one trusts any mechanic in the world.
Apparently every single mechanic is a thief and a scammer.
Yeah, that's again, that's a bad thing. It's a very low trust factor with these mechanics.
I completely believe that. I think I'm getting scammed by my mechanic.
You don't have like an uncle who knows how to do this stuff?
I'm legitimately running out of uncles, man. It's alarming.
What do you mean you're running out of uncles?
I'm running out of uncles.
It's alarming!
How many uncles are you losing?
Three at this point three uncles gone
They're fucking dying
Come on Rex you knew that the human who made me say it they're dying
Will they die from like gelato poisoning? No?
No, just some insane illness if you must know some insane
Familial illness it kills every single person in his family some call it a curse
Yeah, they kill all uncles you better pray to God that your your brothers and sisters never have any little kitties or else
You're probably next there. Oh, Leo. Yeah
I'm running out of uncles who can fix my car. I
Don't think I have a single uncle who knows how to fix a car and I have to let go I've anymore
No, I like go to an actual mechanic now
That sucks, which is really the saddest situation a man could be in
My brother kind of knows how to fix cars, but lives on the other side of the fucking country man
There's nothing I can I can't get all this time
Yes
Fix this shit, I don't know
It's hours and hours and hours of me sitting there unscrewing things realizing. I don't the right fucking tools
Going to Autozone. They closed my door real quick
It's getting infiltrated by the ops I'm being infiltrated by music speaking of fucking people playing music
Why is my wife never used the headphones that I gave her? What's going on with that?
You need to just kill her. You need to feed her to Phil. I never even thought of that actually
Today a kid a kid was about two seconds away from getting eaten by Phil today
I was walking home with him
With a kid?
And with this kid, and then we ran into Phil.
I was walking home with Phil from the park and he was all exhausted and a kid came up
to us and was like, "Is he sweet?"
Like a seven year old kid.
He was like, "Is he sweet?"
And I just lied.
I said, "Yeah, he's fucking, he's sweet as pumpkin pie.
Go ahead.
Is he sweet?
Touch the dog."
And the kid, instead of just petting him like I thought he was going to do, which is fine,
He did the thing that Phil hates most in this world and has made him bite me over a thousand
times, which is that he gave him a giant hug around his neck and like restrained his head.
And I literally in my head started counting, I was like, one, two, three.
And then as soon as in my brain it hit three, I said, oh, he's really hungry and we have
to go home right now.
And then this fucking this, this little kid, this annoying little kid just started walking
down the street going "Aww he was sweet! He was so sweet!" and I was like "I fooled him."
Yeah, but next time he's gonna run into you and be like "Oh my god, it's the sweet dog
that doesn't kill children." I'm gonna, I'm going for another hug. This time I think I'll
make it a little longer. Then he, I mean he gets what he gets man. You were, you were
saying how you don't want to be a villain, but you're completely a villain for your neighborhood.
i think i have a little bit of a villain for my neighborhood lady walked out at my
dog started shitting in like a pile of rocks in the day they were in like one
of those one of the things around a tree
and the lady cancer it came out i was gonna pick it up i was never left to
shit on the ground but a lady came out and started crying
like on this beautiful and she's like
i really don't like that
i was like
what i don't like when you talk shit so my rocks
as a ok i'm gonna pick it up and i picked it up
and i when i got a coffee and i was walking back home
and she walked out of her store
but left a customer come walk and she's like
i'm so sorry i thought that you're just gonna leave that shit there
but i had a bag on my hand so i don't know what the fuck she thought i was
doing
if she did and if she didn't see me to share a motion she might have honest i
mean again uh... i'd i'd do you have a very some kind of villain
reputation
I think that I ruin the vibe of almost every Mexican restaurant that I walk into.
What? Why?
Don't you guys feel- well you don't feel like this.
Rex, do you feel like this?
When you go into Mexican restaurants, doesn't it feel like they were having the best time
ever until you walked in there?
No, what?
Nobody else has felt it?
I feel like they're always like, "Yaaaah!"
Screaming at the TV, drinking margaritas, and then I walk in and it's dead fucking silence.
They turn the fucking music off.
What's going on dude? I feel like it's Toy Story. I feel like when I leave the fucking room,
everybody in the Mexican restaurant fucking is having the time of their lives, and then
as soon as I walk in, they just go, they go completely limp. And just, it's like, dude,
I want to have fun. You look like Border Patrol, man. It's your vibe. You have a cop vibe.
What would the Canadian Border Patrol, why the fuck would I be in New York City? You
You look like ice, 100%.
You look like ice right now!
100% ice right now, right there.
- You're gonna walk around with a camouflage hat on?
- Yeah, yes sir, yes sir.
- It says walker balls, man.
- Yes sir, I have papers, sir.
Yes, senor, I have papers and I'm walking
and I see my friend with long hair.
Oh my God, I can trust him in public
because he has long hair and he's probably--
- Jesus.
- He's probably the same as Jesus.
You do look Mexican, actually, now that I think about it.
me
I don't need these restaurants.
Gentrify your culture stealer.
I'm getting gentrified out of my apartment.
They raised the rent 25 bucks.
[Laughter]
I look like a maid out of fucking money?
25 bucks? Pissing me off in this bitch ass city.
I'm going to send a letter to your landlord to make sure he raises it more.
No, no, no. You need to say...
And he won't listen to me.
You need to say, "Hey there, cousin."
- Hey there, cuz.
- You are the most resilient person in New York City,
I think.
You have lived in a shoebox that pretty much
it's impossible to do any maintenance to.
You can't put any good internet into,
and it's so expensive.
Yeah, you stay there for years and years and years and years.
- Do you realize how hard it is to move?
- It's easy.
I've done it.
- It's hard as fuck.
- I think the longer you live in a place,
the more impossible it becomes to move.
- This is the longest I've ever lived anywhere.
- How long have you been in that place?
- Three years.
- Yeah, you've reached terminal moving impossibility.
- I've moved 24 times in my life up to this apartment.
I'm not gonna move, I'm not gonna make it a quarter
just to fucking go get an extra bedroom
or something where I'm paying even more.
I don't wanna do that shit, man.
- The thing about New York City
is that every apartment sucks complete ass.
- Yeah. - There's something,
there's no flawless apartment.
- Yeah, we should all just-- - Except for something
your friend has and then you don't see the flaws
and then it's like-- - Wait, Brandon Chatter
in the chat says, "I think you guys should all
"move to Mexico."
Wait, that's such a crazy idea.
Wait, Brian, do you agree?
Do you guys agree? - It's a bad idea.
- You think that's a bad idea?
- I don't wanna move to fucking Mexico.
Actually, I do.
I do kinda wanna move to Mexico.
I want to move to Mexico and learn how to code.
Would I have to code in Spanish?
No.
That's crazy.
It might be cool though.
I don't think I've ever seen non-English code, and I've seen a lot of code.
Yeah, I wonder if they do in like China, I wonder if they do...
Which I feel like it'd be easier in China because you just press one key for a word.
How do they make those keyboards?
Do they have every word on them?
No, it's like a normal keyboard. I don't know what I'm talking about
It's like a normal keyboard with auto every word and every phrase each everything has its own key
How do these guys play video games so good?
Just my thought
It's crazy how we've done like almost 30 of these and that's like the rate most racist thing as it says so far
That is given with Rex and Brian, how's that racist? That's my that is that's more of a language thing
Yeah, I'm not even sure it's true
It's one of those things you could just Google like Chinese keyboard
I'm not
Yeah
You know, I my you guys know Neil, right? Yeah
Neil was telling me we went out to Pennsylvania a couple weeks ago to do a college show and
Neil was telling me on the ride that he has a really big problem with Google which is that he's polite when he Googles things
so if he's trying to find out like
Like what cable goes to his Android thing? Uh-huh his Android phone. I would Google Android cable
He googles
May I please what yeah likes like what what cable goes to an Android phone and
Is it available nearby me? Thanks and
Types all that and then hit center
That is insane, that's not crazy he was showing me his Google history. I was just a Chinese keyboard. Mm-hmm
Yeah, I mean
That doesn't look like what I thought said straight up
That does not look anything like what I said. It was gonna look like well, this one's really small so it could be you know
It could be different thing. Yeah, that's like a 60% Yeah. Yeah, um
I
Do that with when I use like chant GPT. I'm always like may I please?
Know some information
- Do you say thanks afterwards?
- I do say thank you.
Or I'll politely correct it
if it gives me something I don't like.
- My girlfriend does that.
- I'll say thank you for the effort.
- My girlfriend told me that she does that
and I was like, that is crazy, you don't do that.
She's like, no, I recognize.
- It's called karma.
And I'm building new karma with the computers.
- It's a computer.
You know how I use AI?
I go in the Notion thing, I paste a bunch of shit on it
and I'm like, turn this into a list.
and that's it that's the one interaction i have a with the and that's it
everything i got
i stopped using chad g_p_t_ is much a really
it's like everything where you see you use it
a hundred times and it's really boring
until they come out with one that can make a movie that i say to make
didn't get stupid
i don't know
and has gotten the but it's beginning to put it
this is what you
if you do like
It's really good for programming.
'Cause you can tell it, "Do my job for me."
And it'll be like, "Okay, sir."
- It kinda does 90% of it, right?
And then you just say, you just double check.
- Yeah.
- Now all of a sudden you're a boss.
- Yes.
- Yeah, that is so good.
- I'm sitting back, I've got my feet up.
I'm talking to my computer.
- Yeah, we should just ask it
for podcast topics every week.
- It sucks at creative stuff.
It cannot do, it comes up with the worst creative things.
Well, let's see, hold on.
Open AI, chat.
Wait, I have, actually I have a way to, I have a way.
You have a way?
I have a perfect way that I can, that way I can come up with actually good funny ass
topics that will blow your mind in an alternative comedy way.
Okay.
Watch this.
Watch this shit.
Hold on.
(silence)
- Can you go sing the rap about the nice shark, please?
- Alright.
Come up with some podcast topics.
Get, okay, so that's gonna be bad, right?
But then I say this.
In the style of Tim and Eric.
Okay, certainly.
Tim and Eric are known for their sur-
(coughing)
Tim and Eric are known for their surreal and absurd humor.
Here are some podcast topics in their style.
Absurd advertising.
analyzing the weirdest commercials ever made.
Dive into the world of bizarre and nonsensical advertising
from local commercials to infomercials
that make you question reality.
Infomercles.
The unusual world of public access television.
In search... oh wait, no, this is so Tim and Eric.
In search of the most surreal internet memes.
What?
I think they did an episode on that.
Take a deep dive into the most absurd and surreal internet memes,
dissecting their origins and discussing their impact on online culture.
And then wait, let me like this, you'll like this one,
cooking with chaos, a culinary adventure in nonsensical recipes.
So this would be something like a shit taco or a piss sandwich, stuff where you go,
wait, that doesn't sound very good to eat.
You know, actually the thing about the commercials, whenever I go to the US, the most culture shock thing to me is how you guys have a person that's just like an ad.
What you mean, bitch?
Like the guy, Jake from State Farm. He just lives like a, he just, it's an ad, it's a person.
Oh, you mean like a series of commercials?
What about a mascot?
But he's got like a whole personality and he's like tweeting and posting on TikTok and Instagram.
And I see him on my Twitter when I'm in the US.
He's a man.
No, they put him...
It's just an ad that happens multiple times.
It's a series of ads.
I'm not talking about the ads.
I'm talking about these accounts.
Okay, wait.
I have another idea.
Hold on.
No, I have an idea.
So I said, "May I have some podcast topics in the style of Joe Pera?"
Oh, this is gonna be good.
So we've got the history and comfort of porch swings.
The perfect handshake.
The gentle art of rock balancing.
Finding the best bench in the park.
You know, I could see it, I guess.
Do you guys think that as white honkeys you're missing out on the cheek kiss when you say
hello to someone?
What?
Um, yeah, I honestly do feel like that.
I also feel like, just, unless you're from a very far land, you do not get to do that
to my wife.
I do that to everyone.
If you're from, like, Europe, you know?
Yeah, you know better.
Yeah, you know where the fuck you are, dog.
it's not a no it's just the cheek against the cheek
i don't want anybody touching my bitch's cheeks
that is not that is uh... the off there's a no go zone
for for men of of uh...
french backgrounds
i don't like that shit
i don't like that at all do i feel amazing when a french woman would do that
to me yes
how do you how do you do that? do french people do that?
Do they do that?
- Yeah, I think for even French people do the mwah mwah.
- I don't think so.
- I've even seen people who live in New York
but go to Europe, have been to Europe.
I've seen them do that.
- How do you say hi to a person?
First a man--
- I don't even really like shaking hands.
I don't even like saying hi.
Recently I've been doing a thing
that's been not working out at all,
but I'm gonna keep trying,
where if there's a new person that I don't know
who's in like a group of other people I know,
I'm not gonna say, "Hey, nice to meet you, I'm Caleb."
I'm just gonna sit there until they do it.
For too long, I was the one who introduced myself,
and now I'm done doing that shit.
I'm done doing that shit.
I'm gonna, and then I'm gonna,
if they never say anything, then great, we met.
- We're not talking, yeah.
- We met each, I'll even talk to them,
but I'm not gonna say my name or introduce myself.
I have no interest in doing this anymore.
- That is how you-- - Let's figure out--
That is how you get into really weird situations where you've known this person for years and you don't know their name.
And you go to their birthday party.
I'll ask somebody their name later.
What if they don't know? Because they're doing the kill 'em method.
Then I get to make them feel bad about that.
Yeah.
But you are at their party.
I'm with Caleb on this.
If you are more...
There's layers to it though.
So, you need to be either cooler or more powerful than them to have that accomplish that.
I don't think so.
I just like doing it just with...
I mean I don't like having to be the kind and gracious one anymore as I get older.
That's what I'm saying.
You don't need... if you're above them on the hierarchy, they need to come to you.
That is a thick way to think of the world, my friend.
Okay.
That is a very sick way to think of the world.
As someone who is just very friendly to anyone they ever meet.
Which is you.
You're the nicest person outside of the world.
Every time I see you-
Why are you saying he's so nice?
He's not that nice.
He is so nice.
Yeah, I'm not that nice.
He's nice to everyone.
That's why people approach you and say things to you.
And that's why Caleb, whenever he enters a room, they were like, "Oh my god, the cops are here."
Yeah.
That being said, I've been in New York for like two months.
I've completely stopped smiling outside of my apartment.
That is so sad.
As is customary.
That is so so sad.
It's called, you know, fitting in with the culture.
When you lived in Los Angeles, you walked around smiling all the time like a fucking
asshole?
See, this is what I'm saying.
This is why you can't do that here.
Nobody in Long Beach is walking around.
Hey!
Not like that.
even just like a slight smile.
A smite!
You should be like...
No, we're smiting them down.
Don't smite people, bruh!
That is bad to do!
On either coast!
No, no, no, I'm telling that.
I've realized that I have the worst all-time white guy acknowledgement face.
Let's see it.
So, you walk by me on the street.
Maybe I kinda know you or you're my neighbor or something.
And I do this.
I go like...
And then I walk away and I go, "What the fuck was that face I fucking made?
What the fuck was that, man?
That face sucked!"
And then I walk back around and say, "Hey, can I try that again?"
Like, try something- just anything new.
You know what my least favorite situation is?
When you're seeing- you see someone out on the street that you know,
and you know that you're gonna cross paths with them,
But you're far away, and you've both recognized the fact that you've seen each other.
Yeah.
What do you do in between?
Do you speed up your pace?
No, you don't.
Do you wait?
I literally, this is the only way that I've figured out how to do this.
And by the way, this is really showing how socially undeveloped the three of us are,
is that we have to have conversations and stuff like this.
But I usually just run, I walk straight up to the person.
Well, of course you walk straight up to them.
I never want the thing where you go, where like you saw somebody and then neither of
you said anything to each other and then later at some other thing you go like "Oh dude I
saw you on the street the other day" and then the worst part is when you say that shit to
them and they go "I wasn't on that street" and then you realize...
I'm saying you're going to the same place, you know?
Let's say we were meeting at a bar and we were coming from opposite ends of the street and
I see you and you see me and there's probably like a good thousand feet separating us.
Well I think, no, I'm like hey!
I do a big wave.
And then you do the wave, you do the wave, you wave for fucking a minute.
Okay, okay.
I'm gonna say this is a flawed hypothetical.
This is a really flawed hypothetical because I think this should, you have to be thinking
about this with people who are not the two of you or like anyone in our circle.
Because the two of you, we would just be like, you see each other, just go like, "Hey, hey,
hey," just for like that for like the entire way through until you're at their face.
I would do that if I saw you coming the other way.
So...
But what if I was someone you're friendly with?
Yeah.
Yeah, but that's what I'm saying.
Do you pick up the pace?
Do you just, you know, you finish waving and then you just walk normally while making direct
the
Yes!
Until you're about 15 feet away.
And then you go, "Oh, oh shit!"
"What's up?"
"Whoa, look at this crazy shit I was looking at on my phone!"
Lock screen.
Look at that!
That's insanity!
You're driving me.
Yeah, yeah, I'm looking.
Yeah.
"Whoa, look at this shit!"
Just, uh, yeah, I don't know.
This is why...
There's a lot of teenagers on the street and they would make fun of you.
See, people think there's cool people in New York.
No one in New York is cool, and no one cares.
No, these people walk around and they're just idiots, man.
Yeah.
They're giant idiots.
They don't like any good music and they hate your last movies.
New York is filled with NPCs.
Damn.
I agree, bro.
Look at stories.
Damn.
There is a serious NPC epidemic in this motherfucking city.
If I don't know you, I don't want to know you, okay?
I've been here for 36 months.
I know everybody that I'm ever going to know in this fucking city.
I certainly don't want to introduce myself to you.
Hell no!
Again, hell fucking no.
I'm not doing that shit.
What is the least NPC-addled city in the world, do you think?
Probably Atlanta.
Okay.
I was like, the last time I was in Atlanta I was talking to homeless guys and I was like,
these guys are awesome.
These guys are like, interesting.
These guys have lived?
Yeah, these guys have lived real lives.
I went to like a park in Atlanta.
Everybody at the, it was like, honestly it was like paradise.
Everybody at this park was like, like somebody threw a frisbee, not like at like too far and
it hit me, threw a frisbee at me and I catch it, all of a sudden I'm in a frisbee circle.
A frisbee.
And I'm throwing a frisbee.
And I'm saying, I love frisbee.
Nobody's correcting me.
This is how nice the people in Atlanta are.
I love Atlanta.
I would move there in an instant.
That's probably my favorite city.
Atlanta and Chicago.
I think you said that about every city.
Name one other fucking city I've ever said that about you fucking stupid bitch.
Beijing.
I've never been to Beijing, motherfucker.
Tokyo.
I've never been to Tokyo.
In my dreams I have.
I've destroyed Tokyo in my fucking dreams.
I was 15 feet tall and I broke down every single building in Tokyo in my dreams.
I think we should take over Tokyo.
My idea.
I would love to go to Tokyo, guys.
I want to try every kind of food that they have, even the crazy ones guys.
I want to try the poisonous puffer fish that if you eat it, uh, if you plug your nose and
eat it you die, however that works.
I want to try every single food.
You know what I don't like?
I had this shit recently.
Fake people.
I had this shit.
Fake people, had them in my life, cut them out.
Did not like them.
Do you guys like, have you had the sea urchin?
That yellow orange thing that sometimes they sell at sushi restaurants?
Nope.
Guys, this is one of the most disgusting foods ever made.
It is a human tongue that tastes like a garbage.
Ooni, that's what it's called.
Ooni.
That is not good man, don't eat that.
Where do you eat this?
Brian took me out to an expensive ass sushi place.
Oh, don't say that.
I wasn't thinking that you were going to say that.
Brian took me to this expensive sushi place, guys.
I don't like this expensive sushi.
I don't want to eat this weird food, man.
I want to eat avocado when I go to a sushi restaurant.
I want guacamole.
I want chips.
That's what I want.
It is really crazy when you have good sushi for the first time.
Like wait, this actually doesn't taste like fish at all.
Do you want to defend yourself?
Yes or no?
That was Brian and Chad.
He said after one piece it was bad, shut up.
But it's the only piece I'm ever going to eat in my life.
Yeah, I'm not going to lie.
Because that shit was weird.
When Brian was talking about the sushi place, he was talking and...
Everything else was great, but that thing was odd.
He was talking about the sushi place.
I was like, dude, you know what?
I know someone that loves sushi.
He joined the call.
Tell your video on if you're gonna talk
Hold on
I gotta turn off the other stream that I'm watching
Wait I'm getting called out live
I need to talk to you
He's not even ready
Bro
This is what I'm talking about
We need to befriend people who are more professional
We need to befriend people with
Hasanabi, Thestiny, TrainwrecksTV
Yes
Sobrietabby, Gideon
Speed, IShowSpeed
show speed, kaisenat, tums, what's up? Alright, defend uni. Rex is gone. I don't have to defend
it. Rex left. Rex left. Okay, you're the new Rex. Say something that Rex would say. Uh,
fuck man, I don't know, uh, small joke about, okay good, glad I don't have to do that. Uh,
no, you don't have to eat the fucking uni, the uni's not that good, that's fine. Everything
else was fucking solid. Everything else was great. I already said that. Why are you joining
the call you bitch? Because you were mad about eating nice sushi. No I was mad about eating
the uni. I said nice sushi places. You don't have to eat that. Don't give me this disgusting
orange thing man. I'm not looking for an imaginary friend. I'm looking for food. I don't need
some crazy amorphous blob. See this is what happens when someone lives in New York for
for
the advanced palate of the the japanese
i like burgers man you know what kind of guy i am
this is the way it really makes me eat species we've heard of the program
brand-news mixing people at what you want to do with the restaurant
there we go thank you
i think you really do it
i don't have a positive interaction more doesn't feel like you ruined the party
Yeah, they look at me like, "What the hell?"
Yeah, what? They don't even... I don't even look human.
I walk in and they're like disgusted.
They look just pissed off.
They just like hand me my food, kind of like looking the other way, like this.
I go, "I'm sorry, man. I really wish I was born Mexican."
Yeah, I think I've asked Jubio this before, but anytime that I've worked with Mexican chefs in particular,
they just like, meowed at me.
I don't know I don't get it but like anytime I walked into the kitchen they
would all just start meowing I'm talking like like 10 12 of them what just
meowing at me man I don't know it's happening two different restaurants I
don't get it. I don't know what that means.
I don't get it.
Whatever brought this up to me is like what are they meowing at me I was like I don't know I've never heard about this this is
This is like some brand new thing that they're doing on you.
They're terrorizing you mentally.
It's horrifying.
I don't know.
Well, that concludes the first ever live episode.
Which by the way guys, next time we do this it's going to be in Madison Square Garden.
This was the first ever, but not the last, live beers we drank.
Thank you for joining us.
Thank you so much for joining us.
Rex, let's do a can check real quick.
Before we go.
What's a can check?
What's a can chick?
You know what's a can chick.
*sigh*
Fine.
Oh wait, this means that there's a lot.
*laughter*
Trash over here.
Leave me alone.
Wait, do you have a question?
It's only 9 cans, man. It's not that much.
Alright, 1, 2, 3,
4, 5, 6,
7, 8, 9, 10, 11,
And then we let me climb up with a crushed and is the crusher ready to go
He gave up on the crusher, I know he's still got it there it is pull it out
Just crush one
It's so loud, I'm sorry, it's gonna be so loud
It's not bad
*Clapping*
That was amazing.
Happy?
Yeah I am happy.
I am so happy.
Alright, thank you for watching.
Goodbye everybody.
Bye!
Breach was like number something.