I wanna play.
*snoring*
Why's this shit so quiet for my bitch ass?
*burp*
*music*
What's up all my chuggers?
*burp*
*music*
Beer's we drank, motherfucker, with Jubio, Caleb, and Rex.
Beer.
Here.
My.
Beer.
Here it goes.
You're fingering it?
Oh!
A fail open!
We have our first ever fail open on the show, guys.
You can't fail the first open of the year.
That's a bad omen.
It's really bad.
This is so bad, dude.
Look at that.
Can you see that? Oh my god, that's completely failed. Completely failed. Can I open it? Oh,
I've opened it with my finger. I thought that the the can said beer on it. Well, I guess I'll go
first then, man. This is another episode where my wife has picked a beer out for me and I'm
gonna say it, she kind of knocked it out of the park in terms of interesting and uniquality. This
is a regular beer.
So this is a funny type of beer that has a fully white label.
It says regular beer in some very normal font.
I don't know what you call this, some sans serif font.
And it says a beer that tastes like beer, all lowercase.
And then a period.
I'm going to give this a lick.
That sounds perfect to me.
And honestly, that is a wonderful beer, you guys.
That is pretty good.
It had I mean, it looks like a card that is against humanity,
but it tastes like a beer that is for Caleb.
I'm going to give this a seven point eight out of ten guys.
And let me close my door so you don't hear the madman echoing through my house.
I wouldn't want to give you guys a taste of real entertainment
and realize that podcasts are really not that good. What?
What?
7'8" and in terms of a basketball player, I'm going to say this is OG Ananobi, recently
traded to the Knicks.
Went from my favorite team to my second favorite team.
He I believe is 6'9" or 6'8".
I feel like the NBA is so in right now.
It's trending.
The NBA is trending in a major way, guys.
Okay, let me see what you have to offer.
What does that say to you?
- That says to me a dos Equis.
That is a dos Equis.
- This is fully a dos Equis Sprite beer.
- I love a dos Equis Lager Especial.
- That is lovely.
- I'm a bigger fan.
I love the dos Equis.
I really love the dos Equis Amber.
In a big glass that has the same amount of,
it's like a bulletproof glass that they serve it in
at Mexican restaurants.
and they put about five limes in it,
that to me is a perfect beer.
That's a 10.
- That sounds like a beautiful summer snack
for an awesome winter day that I'm experiencing.
- So true.
I'm sorry that it's 68 degrees
in the frozen tundras of Mexico.
- I don't know what that means.
Is this like a special one?
This is really good.
I really like this.
I could really imagine--
- That's just a normal Dos Neques.
- You just saying that putting limes and salt in it
really put me in that.
I never really ever have that craving,
but this is like the first time I've ever had it
in my entire life.
- Go ahead, put some Limone in that.
- I don't wanna do that.
I don't wanna go downstairs and do all that shit.
- But I know you have some.
Don't lie to me, bitch.
- I do actually have some.
- Of course you do.
- Yeah, this is great.
This is actually also a seven out of 10 for me.
- Why is it 7.8?
- This is 7.8 and the exact thing
the tech NBA player that Caleb said.
- Okay, stealer vibes.
- That's what I'm thinking.
- Moving on to somebody who won't steal my shit, Rex.
I am so, for the first time I'm jealous of you guys
'cause I don't have a beer today.
Instead, I will be drinking a mixed drink,
which I will now make.
- Reveal.
Oh, a live demonstration, Bill Nye.
(laughing)
This is amazing.
- Wait, no, go all the way down, go all the way down.
Go all the way down.
- This is ingenuity.
- I wanna see the table.
- And I'm sure that this is gonna be many ingredients.
(laughing)
Okay.
- The food is on the table.
- Okay, so just guessing off this,
it's gonna be water, Mezcal, and Diet Coke.
- You wish.
- And maybe one vape.
- I have the botanist gin.
- Okay, I like that gin.
- So we get some of this,
and I think I'm gonna do like, maybe like, let's see.
One, two, three, four, five.
- Oh my God.
Oh my god, man. You are gonna be gone.
And then for my mix, I have Stuart's Fountain Classics Key Lime.
Oh, this sounds pretty good to me.
And you're gonna fill that sucker all the way up. And no ice, by the way.
There is six little ice cubes in there.
Oh my god, I didn't see them at all.
The bubble glass is really fucking with me.
The bubble glass is confusing.
Well, these are what I had.
Alright, so now the taste.
Just give it a little swirl. Use, uh...
Yeah, the spoon I was in the ice cream with a couple years...
A couple days ago.
The last year, yeah. You know.
For the year prior.
Okay. And now, the taste.
And the rating.
Oh my god.
Amazing.
That's so good.
Whoa!
That sounds really good.
That's a nice floral gin.
And I don't know what that soda is but it seems like a boutique soda right up my alley.
I want to jump in front of this.
Before this is too high, too much space.
Before you rate this, I think you have to name it.
I mean this is just what a gimlet is.
It's a gimlet that I'm too lazy to make.
This is the soda gimlet.
But a gimlet is served in a coupe.
And this is in a bubble glass.
So tell me what this is called.
You have to name it.
It's something new.
The Gremlin.
The Gremlin!
I love that.
Yeah, the Gremlin.
Because this is a true low effort, kind of disgusting version of a gimlet.
Well cheers my friend.
Give me a rating.
*snort*
*laughter*
*sigh*
Well, I made it a little strong.
I saw! I saw that with my eyes.
Uh, so...
Wow.
It's very tasty. This key lime soda is really good.
I'm gonna say this is like a solid 8 out of 10.
Wow! I'd have to get myself one of these.
I'm no longer jealous of your beer, Julio.
I wasn't jealous of your beer, really, but I did...
Cue bitch!
You love those seconds?
Regular beer?
Yeah.
Well, guys, we are back after the holiday hiatus.
I'm going to say it, man.
My life has been an absolute train wreck without this show.
Nothing has gone right.
I feel myself drifting ever further away from both of you and our friendships.
I don't like this feeling of not doing this show, and I am relieved to be back in the
saddle.
I had a good time.
Well, fuck you, man.
Yeah, man. Me and Rex have been struggling.
What is your fucking problem?
Yeah, we're trying to say that we miss each other and you're immediately saying that it was actually better than...
I didn't say it was better than ever.
I did miss talking to you guys.
Wait, do you have a problem with us?
No.
I kind of sensed that off of you, this kind of weird combative energy from you recently.
No, I...
Do you think you're too good to podcast with us?
That's how I feel at all.
Guys, it's the new year.
It's the new year.
Instant deflection.
Tell me how your new year's was, guys.
Because mine was not all that exciting.
I tried to leave the party before it was midnight.
Which I learned is some kind of faux pas.
On New Year's Eve, you're supposed to stay until midnight.
I don't think so.
Tell me your thoughts.
I think it's fine.
I was not invited to the party you were at.
You were not invited?
invited to the party you were at.
- You literally were.
You quite literally were.
(laughing)
- Wait a minute.
You were just saying that you missed our friendship.
- Should we invite everybody who's over there?
I said, yeah.
Invite everybody who's over at Cozy.
- First of all. - And he texted Noah.
- Right, first of all, he texted Noah,
which that's not an invite to me.
That's an invite to Noah. - Okay, wait, hang on.
I gotta make you
pump the brakes. - We didn't know
that you were there. - Wait, wait, wait.
- We didn't know you were there.
- You guys have to pump the brakes
and go all the way back
and tell the full context of what this is,
- What's going on?
- Me, Cam, Patrick, and our lovely girlfriends
and wives and fiancés,
went to Jack Bensinger of Joy Tactics Podcast
and I Love Comedy Video Magazine.
- Celebrity party. - And the Bear,
a famous celebrity.
We went to his celebrity party,
celebrities crawling around.
And Noah asked if people wanted to go to Cozy Corner,
which is a bar that we go to a lot.
And I had said, I wanted to go to that,
but I had said yes to this like weeks and weeks ago.
So I went to this and I thought,
we'll stay for a little bit and then we'll leave.
We get there, everybody wants to continue being there
when I wanna go to Cozy Corner.
'Cause I wanted to go to Cozy Corner,
it's right near my house, I wanted to have one drink
and then maybe stay till midnight and then go home.
And Amron asked, should we invite everybody?
And I'm like, you know what, fuck it, sure.
Let's stay here for a little bit and have a hundred dollar Uber back.
And so we invited, he invited through Noah,
everybody that was at the bar and get this guys,
zero people came. So who was actually abandoned? Who was actually abandoned?
Okay. I think that Noah,
I think he's probably like the worst conduit conduit to invite people to a
thing. Number one.
But I think at this point the three of you should have known that and should not
have gone through in order to invite everyone?
- I had jungle juice, man.
I was not legally responsible
for any single decision that I made, okay?
I felt proud that we even thought about anybody
who was not in that room.
And Rex, if it makes you, if it puts you at ease,
the party was not that fun, man.
The only fun part was that they had,
that Jack had a, and sorry, Jack,
it was, you know, no New Year's party
is gonna be that fun to me.
there was a bottle of smelling salts that we all took turns
breathing in really really hard
that was the fun part of the party
that's awesome man
and i would like to say one thing about that which is that we were doing the
smelling salts and all smelling it and going
shit like so bad like having crazy bad reactions
stanky leg
running around the room
and then thomas from pendejo time comes over
and we're like thomas you gotta do the smelling salts
and everybody's holding the maybe six inches away from their face
thomas takes them
the bottle
puts his entire knows in it
big with zero reaction pulses knows out there's smelling salts on his nose
and he said
that was not that good
and that was his only three-pack i deeply inhaling the smelling cells it
was insane dude
That sounds awesome, man.
It made me think he had something really wrong with him.
I think he's a full demon and that's why he's now cancelled and we cannot discuss him any
longer.
He is completely cancelled right now.
Why is he cancelled?
He didn't see?
Did he hurt somebody?
He hurt someone, yeah.
He made a joke and that, in 2024, might as well be illegal.
That is so fucking true.
Thomas, I don't know what you said, whatever you said, I vindicate you right now, whatever
you said, whatever you did, no man should be cancelled on this earth in this year.
He said, he said, if you get molested by Stephen Hawking, that's on you.
Okay, so in this...
Maybe you want to retract what I said, that's a horrible thing.
Thomas you should be ashamed of yourself. You should never work again in any place
But that is funny people got mad at that. Oh, yeah
People are he's been screenshotting all the replies that he's been getting all the negative. Yeah, most people telling him to kill himself
Not to be like really annoying about this, but why are they releasing the the names like a like the smash DLC in waves?
Blackout like that Stephen Hawking come on. Yeah, you can't
it
like
Pokemon just guessing every single week.
(laughing)
- Do you guys think that if that were still going on,
there would be any podcasters on there?
- On Jeffrey Epstein's island?
- Yep.
- For certain, man.
- Lex Fridman.
- Lex Fridman would be on there, no doubt.
He seemed, but not because he is the level man.
It's because he--
- What's your process?
(laughing)
- Yeah, drawing crayons.
That's really amazing.
How did you come up with putting a smiley face on the sun?
I've never thought to do something like that.
It's really impressive.
I think that he ends up in places where he shouldn't belong.
Like he doesn't necessarily have the merit
to be in a lot of the rooms that he's in.
So I think that is purely why he would be there.
He's like, he's a fucking grad student at MIT
and he's interviewing whoever, you know?
The first thing that comes to mind is Eliezer Yudkowsky.
not really that impressive
that was the blast interview i saw with them
he's like
yeah he he is not smart enough to be the podcast
died that he pretends to be
yeah cuz he thinks like he'll be talking to
somebody who's like truly evil or something
yeah and i like
have you considered that maybe love is the answer
like but now
Yeah, talking about love.
He'll talk.
He'll get into arguments with George Hotz.
He's like this, like he's the guy you hacked like the PS3
like jailbroke the PS3 like a very talented like programmer
and he will get so annoyed at him because he's just too stupid
to keep up with him.
It's very funny.
This is really mild.
What is interviewing gamers?
I should have no idea who he did.
He interviewed.
What's his name?
The guy made doom.
Yeah.
He interviews anybody that he thinks is like a groundbreaking technology guy.
He interviewed the OpenAI dude.
And the thing is, I have seen a lot of his interviews, and it's purely because a lot
of the people he interviews are not people who normally do long-form interview things.
And then you watch the interview and you say, "Oh, that's why.
They're boring people who make technology."
They're dorks.
Yeah, they're dorks.
And they get so sidetracked on like random shit and they have no personality at all.
And it's just he interviews people who are like obsessed with their work.
Mainly, I would say.
People who are really technical have this problem where they actually enjoy what they
do and they do it as a hobby as well.
And that makes you so insanely boring to be around.
And they've done it since they were 10 years old.
Right.
Just a guy who's obsessed with math worksheets.
Do you guys think you could be a good interviewee?
- A good interviewee?
No.
- No, I remember I used to say yes
to like every podcast I was asked to do.
So I did a couple of podcasts,
maybe had like 10 listeners.
- Forget about this.
- Back in the day.
- Yeah, you did do that.
- Yeah, when we met, you used to be the famous yes man.
- I thought it was rude to say no to stuff.
And then I would do these podcasts
and I would think that it would be something
where we would be sitting around doing whatever,
just talking.
And then they would always ask me,
they'd be like, how'd you get your start in comedy?
And I was like 22 years old.
Like I did not.
(laughing)
- Yeah, look at your Louis C.K. and not.
- Yeah, I had just started basically.
And I would just tell really boring stories
and then get off and be like,
fuck, I'm saying no to the next one.
And then I'd get a text from somebody.
So you wanna come do my podcast about fast food?
I said, yeah, sure.
- That sounds awesome.
- Okay, well, Pognesmelt fast food is awesome.
- Well, I wish that's what I got asked to do,
but it was actually much worse things.
- Of course.
- Yeah, we would have you hanging out.
- You could probably have infinite episodes
just debating McDonald's versus Wendy's.
- Popeye versus-- - I mean, yeah,
let's do it right now.
- I mean, you couldn't, for sure.
- I had a big blow-up argument with Chad and Brian and Noah
because they said that Zaxby's was the best fast food chicken you can get.
And I heavily disagreed.
Chick-fil-A.
Chick-fil-A?
Popeyes?
Yeah, Popeyes.
I mean, Zaxby's might be in the bottom.
I'm not saying it's the bottom, but it's certainly in the bottoms 50%.
Someone said, "Zaxby's is the GOAT," and immediately someone else said, "Zaxby's sucks so much."
That means that it's right in the middle.
Yeah, I think it's pretty mid.
I would honestly put it right there with the offerings from Whataburger.
Okay, I've not had, oh wait, I've had a chicken sandwich from Whataburger actually, and it
was pretty good, but it didn't blow my mind.
We went to, no, we went to a bad Whataburger anyways.
But yeah, it was not great.
I think Whataburger can be, like, very, I don't know, it's like, it's a really, really mixed
experience depending on which one you go to, I feel.
The supreme fast food that I've had in the last five years that blew my mind was Culver's.
Have you ever had Culver's?
Culver's is a top tier fast food.
The cheese curds, they bring your food out to your table.
It is an amazing experience front to back.
Everything about Culver's is great.
A Butter Burger, that just sounds so damn good.
Yeah, the Butter Burger, the cheese curds, and the frozen custard.
Frozen custard is wonderful.
That sounds amazing.
I would love to go there.
True Midwest chain.
Yup.
There's nothing more Wisconsin.
Ok, so here's my new, my brand new found Whataburger thing.
As a person who lives near Texas and sometimes goes to Texas, I've spoken great with Great
Live Whataburger in the past.
Last time I went, I went to Whataburger with my girlfriend and she got just like a normal
burger and I got like, I forgot what I got, I think I got like a chicken sandwich.
And I liked mine and she didn't like hers.
And then I showed a famous Texan, Brian, like, "Oh, we got a Whataburger and look what she
got."
And she said that she didn't like it.
And he just goes like the most and say like, "No!
What the fuck are you doing?
You're not supposed to order that!"
They black out, man.
You're supposed to order the...
You're supposed to fix...
To solve the puzzle of the disgusting huge menu.
And you're like, "I want this with that many patties and like with whatever bread."
I was like, you know what I see why people don't fuck with whatever I get that's always been my problem with in and out
Right in and out you go there and you get a hamburger
They have four things on the menu and then you tell somebody yeah to hang hamburger from in and out
It was pretty good and they say oh you should have gotten it dragon style
yeah, and I go I don't want to be with the the the
Disgusting fear that I would feel walking up to a cashier and trying to order off of a secret menu
That is too powerful from - that will keep me from doing any of that
Yeah, because the idea that I would say I'd be like, yeah, I want it. I want it
And they'd say what I'm talking about man. Are you fucking? Okay. Do we need to call 911?
I don't know if you can see there's four things on the menu. Do you see crazy animal style anywhere on that?
I don't think so. That would that would that loses me. This is why McDonald's is the goat fast food because it's like Legos
It's the same fucking every use to be
And let me tell you something I'm gonna stand up for this, okay McDonald's
You're on notice man
Tell you why Ronald
if I go to a McDonald's and I get a
cheeseburger that shit should be
99 cents not
379 right that
absurd that is fucking
absurd man
Which was a cheeseburger said the the kids meal which one is the cheeseburger our friend from Mexico just asked
He just asked that with his real mouth
The one the dollar menu to the one two three menu is a discu now
There's nothing on the menu. That's a dollar the fries start at three dollars
Yeah, the fries you have to use the they force you to use the app. Otherwise, they rip you off
Exactly. I honestly think
It's because they hate homeless people
It has to be
It's the only explanation they were tired of homeless people coming in getting a dollar drink a dollar delicious
Hi-c to refresh their homeless metals and bodies
Going into the bathroom and doing drugs
Comedian who would come and do my open mic in Boston and he used to do the same joke every single week about how
Disgusting it was that at McDonald's they started charging for sauces
Okay, yeah, and this joke used to bomb every week because everybody's like who gives a fuck what they church 39 cents for a sauce
but now
Antoine that was his name
You have been vindicated if I could go back in time
I would standing Oh every single fucking time you told that joke because you saw the turn coming
He did you saw what was happening to McDonald's and that is the mark of a great
I wouldn't even say comedian philosopher. This is a George Carlin level of
foresight that he had I
Truly the change that has come to fast food
Has been horrible it makes it just completely not worth it to get
99% of the city was absolutely it was three bucks for the the cheeseburger
Uh-huh. So yes
Yeah, inflation has really hit us as well because I'm looking at it on on my app. Of course. I always have it ready
and burger a shot the 39 right there which which is
We're not even safe ourselves from inflation
Oh my god over over a dollar is disgusting over $2 for what used to be a dollar menu item
Boils my fucking blood. Yeah boils my blood I'm gonna say
- Hey, a fast food restaurant that you may disagree with,
Portillo's.
- That's in Chicago, yes?
- Yes.
- Yeah, I like Portillo's.
- Yeah, a beef and cheddar croissant used to be like $4,
and now it's eight.
- The doubling, how can you justify,
I understand, what's it, inflation is up
in the last five years, even if it's 30%,
raise your prices 30%, it's not 30%,
but raise your prices 30% doubling.
Are you kidding me?
- That's what I'm saying.
This shit is ridiculous.
- What is the point?
Why would I ever go to McDonald's
when I can get tacos down the street
that have been $4 for 15 years?
- Yeah.
- Why can I get,
why would I go to McDonald's
when I can get those for the same price
or cheaper at this point?
- I think the true test right now,
and I don't know this off the top of my head,
Is a Jack in the Box taco still two for a dollar?
I would be very surprised.
Actually, Jack in the Box might be the only one with integrity.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
I feel like those somehow are still two for a dollar.
That's because their menu is so giant that they might not even know they have some items
so they wouldn't adjust them.
It's also completely like worm, beet, and oatmeal.
Well that's what every time we go to California, my dad's from California, and every time that
we went to California to visit his family.
We would, the first thing he would do when he got off the plane is we would drive to
the nearest Jack in the Box and he would eat Jack in the Box tacos and he would have a
full male orgasm in front of all of his children.
Like that was to him, it was like he waited all year to eat a Jack in the Box taco.
He thought that it was incredible.
They are really good when you drink, because they are so greasy.
Yeah, that's true.
And this is incredible.
They are somehow still two for a dollar.
Wow.
Get a look in the box.
I salute you.
You are, that is a true American fast food chain.
That is not given into this communist bullshit.
There should be something that is so disgusting that it costs 50 cents.
I agree. I fucking agree.
Every fast food restaurant should have the Disguster meal and it's 50 cents an item.
I remember having an idea for a restaurant when I was a kid. I don't think this would
work very well. But I wanted to open a restaurant that was literally just like the most dis-
not disgusting, I mean I guess disgusting, you wouldn't market it as this, but the cheapest
possible food that was like chili made with like canned vegetables and like all that kind
of stuff, but it's fully transparent and you're like, "Yeah, this is not the best food ever,
but it's very cheap."
And I used to think that's not going to work because you have these fast food places, but
now I kind of think that might work.
If you can undercut the fast food places by just doing very low quality food that is very,
very cheap, I think that you could make money off that.
I agree.
I think that idea is great, but it falls apart whenever you have so much success that you
you start trying to branch out and go to different places.
And then it's just run by a corporate office
and it's the same thing where you gotta get
all those damn profits. - That's the key.
That's the key.
That might, the old Macca's brothers,
they caved in and started franchising.
Me, never, never, never.
- You're gonna have a single Disguster restaurant?
- If you have one restaurant, two restaurants at max,
You can make millions if it pops off in a crazy way.
- Okay, so now this is my question.
- And that's all I need.
I'm a natural born millionaire, not a billionaire.
I'm not built for that.
- Where in the country would you put your disguster?
Which is what it's called.
- Probably right near my house.
It would be easy to get to work.
Any other questions?
- The disgusting restaurant in Brooklyn?
disgusting it's not disgusting. Okay what is it called? The idea it's called
Caleb's Shack. It's called Caleb's Shack and the food is not the food is not great and
it's kind of also a mix of just different foods I know how to make it
would be like fried eggs potato pancakes gochujang chicken thighs it would not be
a cohesive menu whatsoever I don't think. Yeah. And then we'd introduce the cocktail
program we'd have the gremlet there we would have let's see what else can I make
we would have a gremlet and a grogni and a margarita made with the cheapest
triple sec possible and that would be the entire cocktail. So I have a thing
about this too I think if you made a bar that only had the cheapest drinks okay
like no elaborate fancy cocktails so just a place that you could really dive in
and get your yeah this is my hometown has a bar called the opera room which used
to be here's another here's here's an example of inflation done done right
okay they used to have 75 cent PBR drafts a 10 ounce pour of PBR was 75 cents okay
Now, they've raised the price. It's 85 cents for a draft pour of PBR.
Wow.
That is inflation done right.
Yeah.
Because it was already so insanely cheap.
And they don't have any high-end, they have like only well, I think they only have tequila and whiskey.
Those are like the only liquors they have.
That's so good.
Just like plastic bottle tequila and whiskey.
But I think that that is I think they probably are some of the richest people
in the planet at this point because of how many people go to that bar.
Yeah, well any I don't want to say any but I think I most it's a it's a really it's
a meme down here that you'll go you go your entire life you'll you'll go to
university you'll get your your degree I'll get some shit job in an office you
know you just make no money but the guy who dropped out in high school and just
started a little taco truck.
It's like he owns a fucking, he owns a house,
he owns a truck.
So I think--
- Yep, see, in the US we have--
- He owns a house.
(laughing)
- That he's a taco seller.
- He's the richest guy in the world, basically.
- In the US we have trades,
and trades for you guys are you open a taco truck.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- 'Cause for us, it's like the richest people I know
are like welders.
- Yeah.
- Like that's where you make a lot of money,
The richest people you know are podcasters. Let's be real.
No, no, no, I know somebody who does roofing who makes probably more than any podcast right
now.
Makes more than Adam?
Yes, yeah.
Wow.
Easily, actually, yeah.
Damn.
Yeah, if you're like a, if you like own your own business like that, those guys, your employees
being paid so much for, he started off as just like a normal roofer and five years in
and he was making like 200 and something thousand dollars a year.
And then if you open up your own business, you're making so much money
because you have to pay these people to.
It's crazy.
That's so nice.
That's amazing.
I should have been doing something like that.
We should start our own business in the slot.
A slot business.
Well, that's true as fuck.
I do think that is the way that we become billionaires is see.
This is a hard thing for me.
Okay, because there's a clear path here
for everybody else.
Rex, obviously you're programming.
Jubio, obviously you are the mascot of the company, right?
- Right.
- We make a 2D version of you
and it's called Jubio's Jamboree,
could be like the name of the slot or something.
Where do I fit in in all this?
I don't have any kind of programming skills.
I'm not from another country.
- I think you are the CEO.
- Imagine. - No, I can't do that.
- I think like Sugar Rush, right?
Imagine Sugar Rush.
We're talking about slots, right?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
Famous bald guys, heads, top down.
Like different sweets.
And then like one guy, and then like you
with the eye heart eating shit,
it instead says free spins.
- Oh my God.
- That is amazing.
- That's actually really genius.
By the way, open up the second beer the wife brought home.
This is a Sour Me America, it says.
And this is a Bomb Pop Sour Ale, a Rocket Pop Sour Ale.
- That sounds actually incredible.
- This is my second beer. - It's actually,
this might be the best sour beer I've ever had
in terms of balancing like the sweetness
and the like kind of the over,
the richness that a lot of sour beers have
with the beeriness.
This is a perfect blend.
I'm gonna give this an eight.
- Wow.
- What's yours at?
- Oh, mine, this is just the Nutshebwena again.
It's the Christmas beer that I didn't finish.
- It was so long ago.
- Well, I bought a six pack and I drank one of them
and the other ones were drank by other people.
- Imagine having a six pack that lasted you
from before Christmas until almost a week
into the new year.
- I don't drink beer. - That is crazy.
- I don't drink beer by myself at home.
- That is crazy.
Then you're not living, man. Sorry to tell you.
I haven't drank a beer since a year ago.
Yep. Yep. So, tell me your slot idea, Rex, besides the bald one.
So, I think, like, it would be cool...
So, here's the thing about slots, right? I don't know if we've talked about this.
-Much like magicians, every slot company has like a gimmick that they like copyright and
then license.
-Yeah.
-So...
-Big time gaming, MegaWiz.
They've probably made millions on the MegaWiz.
-Yes.
Absolutely.
And I think like we could do something that's kind of like the X-Split on like No Limit
city but it's like a diagonal split on the screen. Oh, an actual X. Yes, and we could
do like a knife or sword themed slot because again. This is you playing into your favorite
things okay. Yeah it is. This is not going to work for me. It's a labor of love. But
it could have beer, swords, guns. And then Lex Fridman is interviewing you. Exactly. About
your new sword-themed slot that has now taken over the world.
Yeah, I mean I think if you made...
Like, the thing about a slot too, it should be so fun that you don't realize you're losing money.
That's true. That's why I always thought if you could make some way that it's like
basically a full rip-off of a game that people already like.
Fortnite, Minecraft, that kind of thing.
But you're losing money while you play.
That would be the most genius slot of all time.
Although, now that I say it, Fortnite is exactly that.
Yeah.
[Chuckles]
I guess that is...
That is the Fortnite model.
Imagine a Minecraft slot where you have like nine chests in front of you and you open them.
Wow.
- Wait, that is interesting,
like a first person shooter type slot.
- Yeah. - You can actually move
around a bit. - Almost like a,
like a first person scratch off.
- I like scratch offs.
I usually, I didn't go home for Christmas this year,
but normally when I go,
my dad gets me a bundle of scratch offs.
And I forgot my dad existed,
and I only told him I wasn't coming home
two days before Christmas.
So I'm sure that I have these scratch offs
sitting for me at the house.
So that is money that's on the table.
So it is possible that you guys are talking to a thousandaire
and you don't even have any idea, and I don't either.
- I really hope for your sake that it's true.
- Me too, that would be amazing.
That would be amazing if I could become a thousandaire.
- I would feel so foolish if I found out
that you had all that money
and I was tucking smack on you all these years.
- I know, yeah.
All these years and then you come running
you say, "Come on, man, buy me a gumball, buddy."
Now that I'm a thousandaire,
I could probably buy you 50 gumballs and not even notice,
but I'm not going to because of how much shiz you talked.
- Man, I'm sorry.
- You are a shiz talker.
Are you a thousandaire in Mexico, Julio?
'Cause that's like $40, right?
- It's like 50 bucks.
So yeah.
- That's kind of awesome. - That is crazy.
Do you guys have any, is there one thing in Mexico
that is so much, so much cheap, hmm.
Is there one thing in Mexico
that is so much cheaper in Mexico
that the price is almost identical
to what it would be in the US
even though you're paying,
even though the exchange rate is 20X or whatever?
- This is a really,
you phrase this really confusingly to me.
- Is there something that in the United States
would be $20 and in Mexico would be 20 pesos?
- Right.
Rent.
Basically. - Okay.
That might be the best possible option.
- Yeah, that is really nice.
- So you can pay like 2,000 pesos a month for rent?
- I used to pay 6,000 pesos in my apartment,
which I think is less than 300 bucks.
- God damn.
- And now we pay total 870 bucks per month
and we split that, me and my girlfriend.
- I need to move to Mexico, I really do.
I think it would be amazing.
I just would need to learn at least two languages.
'Cause it would be kind of embarrassing
if I only knew English and Spanish.
- What do you mean?
- I would need to, I would feel,
I don't want to be bilingual, I want to be a polyglot.
I want to know all sorts of languages.
I think that is completely a silly situation.
I have a thing to say about polyglots.
Go ahead, talk to that.
People who know two languages for, like, you know,
usefulness of it and everything, that makes sense.
I have met some really stupid people
that speak a lot of languages.
I'm convinced it is not--
Really?
--like an impressive--
I kind of think of the number of languages that you speak, and I think a lot of people do, as a bit of a marker of intelligence.
I think it's less like intelligence and more like pattern recognition.
Yeah.
Just like memorizing stuff, basically.
Yeah. It's like, and, like, I met someone who speaks like five languages, and he's not stupid by any means, but I was like,
"Oh, this is like, you would not expect that out of this guy."
And I was like, "Maybe actually it's not that hard
and you just need to just put a little bit of effort into it
and you could probably do it."
- Yeah, I think it's just mostly practice
and like putting the time in.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, but that's also a type of something.
- Yeah, but it's like a roofer could learn Spanish.
- Well, again, roofers are millionaires.
I already talked about this.
- That is true.
- And any millionaire could do pretty much anything they want
'cause they can hire a tutor.
- Not true.
I can't. - Bruce Buck.
- Well, you're not a roofer.
- That is true.
- You wish you was.
- I wish I was, dude.
- No, you don't.
- Yeah, I do.
- You love being a little gremlin
in your hallway house.
- Anti-Semitic vibes.
- Well, I live in New York, man.
I'm sorry that my house isn't a spacious Mexican villa near a mountain.
We pay so much because we don't have to live in fucking Mexico, man.
Yeah.
I live here, a Chuncheon restaurant.
Whoa.
That's right.
Yep.
And it's not very good.
And guess what, man?
A jazz bar just opened near me.
So I bet you're fucking jealous.
Have you been to it?
Yes, and it was amazing.
Really?
Is it the Ornithology Club?
No, it's called Dada.
Oh.
- Wow.
- Da, da guys.
And it says on the front, live music,
Arts Club Cocktail Bar.
- Yeah, Farts Club when you're in it.
- Well, that's what I would say if I walked in,
but I only went in one time and I hadn't seen,
they hadn't put up the decals yet that said Arts Club,
'cause I definitely would have seen them with that.
And it's one of these restaurants
where everyone who works there is French,
which is very off-putting.
- Okay.
- Very, very off-putting.
I don't like giving my order.
I order at the bar 'cause it's a little bit
of a shorter interaction.
- So what was it like?
What was in there?
- It was, honestly, I went and the food was really good
and the drinks were great,
but then they started playing fucking jazz
and I was like, oh, I think I hate music.
I think I hate live music.
- Here's the thing about jazz.
At the very, very top end, jazz is cool.
From the 1950s.
Yes.
If you are into jazz now, if you are a jazz player now, you suck.
I'll make it even a little bit more...
I don't think that white people should be playing jazz.
I've only ever seen jazz by white people.
And I really don't think, I think it's not what they should be doing.
I think that jazz, the fact that jazz clubs have the same racial makeup as a tennis tournament
when it in fact should be the same as the NBA, that's a serious problem.
Yeah.
Okay.
I really don't think that it should be white, white people are not good at this shit man.
Don't do it.
They just don't have the rhythm man.
Don't pick up that big fucking bass.
Stick to this one.
The upright, if you're a white guy,
this is not natural for you.
- Yeah. - Or this, this thing.
You should be, this is natural.
You should be doing slapping.
You should be doing primus.
You should not be doing upright,
doing all that kind of shit.
- I don't think I know anything about this.
- That is not for you, man.
You don't know anything about it?
- No.
- Well, let me educate you, man,
'cause I'm basically an expert now that I've went to Dada.
Basically what happens is you get a fat guy
Right skinny guy and a girl. Yep, and the girl plays the drums as some sort of weird gender swap
Oh, look how funny it is a girl's playing drums. Though. I assume that's what it is. It's a nice way
It's so crazy
and so they try to put the girl on the drums to distract you from the fact that they don't know what they're playing and
You basically watch three three people practice music four and a half hours. Yeah, that's the thing
it's not good. I mean I hate I don't like improv for the same exact reason. Yeah.
Which is even if you have pretty funny people doing improv it would be so much
funnier if they had written down what they were gonna do and thought of it
and they premeditated this. Right. It is so silly how people think improv is good
because it's improvised. They judge it on a different metric.
Yup.
And it shouldn't be that way for improv comedy. It shouldn't be that way for improv music.
I agree, man.
You should be busting out some crazy shit.
And Rex, by the way, also thinks any time they have somebody with Down syndrome on a
high school football team and they score a touchdown, he thinks that shouldn't count.
Well, I mean, I'll be honest.
He's like, "Well, they let him do it."
they did let him do it.
I think that's the one exception.
What, you're gonna write that down in the fucking, in the annals of high school football history
that some retarded guy got to run unimpeded for 60 yards and they had to coach him how
to keep running down the field?
You don't know if he, he may have earned it man, you don't fucking know.
Yeah he earned it by being down syndrome, being born the way that he was.
He didn't earn it by running hard, putting on his pads and-
Okay guys, I should have known what I was doing, I should have known, I should have stopped
him, this was my fault, I'm gonna take full responsibility for that.
This is the gremlin speaking bro.
He lost control.
This is a full gremlin, this is a full gremlin moment.
Okay, I have nothing to do with that, I fully disavow him and Thomas, these are the two
most disgusting people I've ever met in my entire life.
goodbyes I would never never ever imagine saying but for the also if you're
thinking talking down on Rex right now for being a disgusting ableist just know
that he did have something called a gremlin it's always been called that
yeah and it's about seven shots of gin and some soda and also he's in under
incredible stress right now for what these people are going through that's
true. My Palestinian brothers are being murdered by Israelis. That's true. And also Jeffrey Epstein's
name is being dragged through the mud. Being sullied! Being sullied! A family friend of yours
from way back in the day. Making people look down further on the Jewish people for their
predilections towards young women. It is horrible what is happening to my people. That is so true.
And by the way, you don't play into that stereotype at all.
I just want to say that off the cuff.
I got into an argument with my aunt once when the Jeffrey Epstein stuff first happened.
She's like, I just can't imagine what people are going to be saying about the Jews.
Yep, that's the right thing to be focused on.
I was like, that is 100% what the issue is.
I was like, you are insane.
You are an insane person.
That is awesome, man.
I just watched a video, a Brett Gelman interview that popped up on something where he was talking
about how he went to Israel and he was like, "This is my real home.
This is my real fucking home."
I've obviously never been to Israel, but I don't understand how people...
Not that obvious.
Okay.
Anyway.
I've never been to Israel, but I don't understand how people go there and like or like
fucking hell, yeah
Well, I mean, oh, you don't understand dude. Have you seen this bungee Bob episode where Squidward goes to the Squidward village?
*laughter*
I cannot say anything
Oh my god dude
Alright
The show is also disavowing
Caleb for his beliefs
and his thoughts on the
*laughter*
I'm not saying anything about
what ScooterBrit looks like, you made it about that
I'm saying
how cool would it be
there was a whole neighborhood of guys that were exactly like you that's awesome no he
hated it he hated it so much come on well he hated it after a little bit but when he
first got there he was like this is awesome there's no sponge bobs and you want the sponge
There's too many fucking Spongebobs and Patricks in my neighborhood!
[Laughter]
Oh...
Or maybe there used to be Spongebobs there, and you throw them into a different area.
So on and so forth.
[Laughter]
Well, that is a little too...
to
I think that's a pretty fair analogy.
- It is.
- I think that's fair, man.
- I don't know what to say, but you did
a good word to talk about the story.
- See, but I'm so, I almost said anti-Semitic.
(laughing)
I'm so--
- Anti-anti-Semitic.
- I'm so anti-anti-Semitic.
I'm so, don't even think about that kind of thing.
- Right.
- That didn't even hurt me.
and i apologize for that
now my agency will be dropping the very very soon
and that is ok there well within the right to do that
uh...
you're gonna get scooter brahms so hard
yeah
but you you know you know what i mean i feel like if you go to israel you're
like
of this is cool everybody else has the same everybody here is the same penis
like that's a good feeling i think
I guess that's true. I can see that. And I know they like basically hire...
You never even think of doing the birthright thing?
No, I was over... So obviously like you get raised Jewish, you go to Sunday school and shit.
They, from the very beginning, they're like Israel is the best place on earth.
It's basically heaven. And then you turn like 13, become a man and Jewish,
Jewish and then you realize that they're just saying that to get money from you.
Oh I see. How does Birthright work? Do you like sign up on like Delta? Like yep.
It's a free trip as far as I know right? You do it through your school or...
Yeah you do it through your Jewish community. Because like the thing about
it is I honestly I can't think of anyone I know that like went on Birthright.
Really? Yeah. It's not crazy. I feel like I know a couple people who went on birthright.
I know one person. And I didn't know about Jewish stuff until a couple years ago.
Yeah, I just, you know, it's one of those things where, especially when I was
turning like 10 years ago when I was turning like 18, Israel was already like
war zone, you know? So every Jewish mother was like, "No, you can't go to Israel
they're gonna bomb you. Oh I see. But yeah it is I don't know they try and get you
to love Israel from the very beginning. It's like here's the book and here's
Israel give them your change. But you resisted because of your amazing
steadfast morality. No I was anti-semitic. Oh that'll do it too I suppose. Yeah the
The idea of a country of Jews sounds horrible to me.
You were late episode Squidward.
Sorry to bring it back to that.
You were a Squidward that was not so much wanting to hang out with other Squidwards
because it was a bit of a reflection of yourself.
Yeah.
I was like, these people are so dour.
My thing about Jews is you think Jews are awesome like Seinfeld and Larry David.
And you're like, wow.
every Jewish person was like that how could they possibly hate us and then you
beat just a regular Jewish person and you're like oh I get it now again
nothing to say about this yeah absolutely nothing to add. You need to be arms crossed kind of shaking your head disapproving of the whole thing.
I mean I am I literally am I heard you say even go into dissing Jewish
people and not the country and this is a big no-no for me. Yeah I wish everyone
Every single Jew was like Seinfeld and did everything he did
See, I don't even think that I think every Jew is perfect exactly as they are. Yeah, Woody Allen Seinfeld
Oh, I mean, come on. You're putting me you're putting me in a corner over here man. You're trying to trick me. Okay, Dershowitz
Alan Dershowitz, I'm not he's funny. That's all I know that video was so funny that as soon as his name came out
He was like maybe I did it but what about the other ones?
Well his his thing was he was like, oh, wasn't he the one who was like a lot of these people are so focused on these
Epstein flight logs and not on the fact that Hamas is cutting off children's heads
Yeah, which is a pretty beast way to go about that. Yeah, you have to think
What would he have been doing a couple years ago before this war broke out? Well, what he what would have been his excuse then?
Probably that McDonald's raised the prices probably something like that
I would love to get Alan Dershowitz's thoughts on inflation and fast food.
He would come on beers we drank.
I think I have his phone number.
Somebody I know got his phone number and got drunk at a party and gave it out to a bunch
of people.
I think Patrick tried to play the 8-ball pool with him on the iMessage.
Did he reply?
No, I don't think he responded.
Somebody I know texted him and said something, some kind of funny message, and he just said,
"Who is this?"
Yeah, maybe it's not a big texter.
Maybe just try FaceTiming him.
Yeah, he doesn't really know about texting, I'm sure.
I remember Rudy Giuliani's number leaked on Twitter among certain types of people, and
it was, again, what people would do is they would text him or ask him to play pool.
I feel like getting a famous person's phone number...
Yeah, it's really limited in what you can do without like
prank calling them I
Don't really have anybody very famous in my phone that I would have any interest in
Well, I wish I did if you had Obama's phone number
If I had Batman's phone numbers, I was a homeless phone number. Oh Obama's phone number
From where I'm sitting. Yeah, probably the same exact thing. I
Just thank him same as I would with Batman but Batman's my number. Thank you so much man. Yeah
Well, you wouldn't think mad bad, thank you so much for being Kenyan
Thank you so much. Dot dot dot five days later for being Kenyan because he didn't respond
Right. He goes like what the fuck for smoking cigarettes fucking guy
WTF question mark. Yeah, probably what he would hit me with. I
Will rewatch the video of him drinking the Flint water the other day and that is the funniest video that I
That guy had so much goodwill as the president from so many people like remaining
Yeah, and that we're like it really really ruined it to do that stunt like give me a glass
Come on, give me he didn't have to do that at all. Yeah, he could have said this is horrible
he went to fl- I don't know if you know about this story, Flint, Michigan had
lead in their water, high amounts of lead
it led to all these birth defects and- I remember that
yeah so then Obama went to Flint and instead of being like
what a terrible situation, this was a complete failure of
this government, instead he was like you know what man
I'm thirsty, give me a glass of water and he drank a glass of tap water
and basically took the tiniest little sip
I've ever seen in my entire life
and probably spit it out as well on national television.
- That's awesome.
- They were probably like,
you can only take the world's smallest sip.
- Yeah, well, again, even if you drink the whole glass,
the problem isn't that you drank one glass
of Flint, Michigan water.
The problem is when you've been drinking it
since you were two years old.
- And your parents have been drinking it.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Yeah, and showering in it.
It's like, so, do you remember that video
that like Indian guy who's like this river is completely clean and like he
like drank a glass of the water and had to go to the hospital me and hometown
has a we have a bad water thing there was a Teflon company that dumped some
by-product into the water supply for like 20 years and they found out about it
like 2015 and uh, no, you know, me and Noah were completely normal.
Yeah.
Right.
We had all our hair and all that kind of thing.
My two most normal friends.
I go towards you, Noah, Noah's brother.
Yeah.
No kind of brain damage that makes you annoying throughout that entire group.
You know, it really is a miracle.
It's just nice that we got, you know, attacked like that and had zero side effects.
Yeah.
Well, LA too, very funny is, uh,
like the port of LA, like the bay and shit.
They used to take like nuclear waste and like, they were supposed to drop it like
50 miles outside of the coast.
Just like, like Homer style, taking a barrel of nuclear waste on like a barge.
And then the Homer style was just like, ah, fuck it.
And just like kicking it off the boat after like five minutes.
That's badass.
Like we fucking took it all the way. So does LA have nuclear water now? They were like, well, it's the ocean. It's fine
It's not true as fuck. Isn't that the water that you were living right in front of basically?
Yes, it was. That was awesome. It was really it was really fun. This is in Rex and
Like oh my god, the beach is right there. That looks so beautiful
But then the port it's like right next to the beach. So no one is ever in the water
That means asking you in the water. That is a nasty beach there
Uh, there is a video that went around of a guy fucking the beach
He like dug a hole in the ground and was was humping it and I was like I recognize that Beach
That's right in front of my house
It's probably a good beach then I
Mean, yeah, it's gonna be really good guys having sex
I've never seen anybody have sex with one of these nice beaches in Miami or anything
Kirk's in Cape Coast, nobody's having sex with the beach.
Right, they're having sex on the beach.
Exactly.
So this has got to be the best beach ever if people have to fuck it.
Right.
They have to do it.
They have to.
Yeah.
It should be...
Imagine like a metal detector guy on the beach and he just pulls...
Just starts digging and it's a pocket pussy.
He's just like, "Yes!"
[laughter]
Wonderful idea.
I don't think we've been breached yet.
I don't think we've even breached the slot idea.
I think it was just like knives.
Okay, we need to chill on it more and think about it more.
Guys, this has been a truly catastrophically good episode of "Beers We Drink."
I'm your host, Caleb Pitts.
Thank you so--although, no, I'm not actually.
This episode, Jubio is the host.
I just decided.
I'm actually not the host.
I'm a guest.
Thank you so much for listening.
I've never been on the show.
And goodbye.
Peace.
It's over guys.
Goodbye.