[Sipping]
[Burping]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer broadcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[Burp]
This is a journey into
[Muffled]
Bud Light.
Ha!
Food Ribbit!
Beers We Drink Motherfucker with Juvio, Caleb and Rex.
Welcome back to Beers We Drink and we're going and...
Hold on let me crack my thing open.
I thought you were farting.
You wish.
I wish I was farting.
Wait I don't have the...
My drink is pretty fail today I'm not gonna lie.
Okay, let's go from drinks from fail to least fail.
So, Keller, go first.
Well, I'm not saying I have the most failed drinks.
Rex is probably going to have a halo beer.
Rex already promised an epic beer,
so I'm going to put him at least fail.
Mine is kind of fail,
but it probably won't be as fail as yours.
So, go ahead.
I'm double dipping because I just was in a rush on the way home,
and I didn't have time to go to a beer store,
but there was a liquor store on the way.
So, I just got one of these again,
these on the rocks pre-made Manhattan's.
But this one's even this one's smaller.
This is actually completely fully drink already.
This kid. Well, I just poured it.
Actually, this is the
you find it open on the floor.
It just I think I think this would be this funniest alcohol to get addicted to.
Hopelessly addicted to pre-made cocktails
that cost $10, this little thing that happened to my to my dad.
He got one of those things that's like a
juice arrow for like alcoholic drinks.
It's like you literally just like get a pre-made can and then it's like a cure egg,
but it just has alcohol in it and then it puts it into, you know, what's one of those
things that I've, that I've, that I've seen like online that happens in the U S but I've never like seen in real life.
Democracy.
Yeah, that's right.
Kami.
Okay.
I was also going to say, the pre-pack, it's like mixed drinks that people get.
You open a fridge and on a Ziploc bag, it's a beer and a juice and something like that
and you mix it in a gas station.
I've never seen that either.
I don't know what the fuck that is.
I've seen TikToks of that.
I don't know what they're called, but I've seen them.
That does not feel American.
That feels South Korean.
You know how South Korea, they always introduce some, for whatever reason, there's robots
between you and just the most normal convenience store food.
Yeah.
You know?
Like you can't just get a pint of ice cream.
You have to see a robot hand make it in a vending machine.
Yeah.
And then also, here's another thing while I'm talking about Korea,
that pisses me off and a lot of the countries in that part of the world.
Don't make, don't make things cost $4,000 anything when it is actually $2.
Dude.
That makes me so mad.
I'm about to change up to your entire worldview on Korea specifically.
South Korea, they are huge on Christ and Christ-like things.
I grew up...
In Korea?
I grew up, I lived like very close to a Korean Baptist church.
I'm intimately aware of the Korean Christian...
I was surfing the radios of the world and I went to South Korea and they got a lot of
Christian songs and radio shows in English over there and it was a little wild to me.
That's because we literally used to fly over the country and push lava out of airplanes
directly onto their houses and so they started believing in the devil.
Yeah, like Minecraft.
Like literally we griefed all of Korea and they were like,
well, this is, they don't, they were like,
we don't even necessarily think there's a God,
but there's definitely a devil that is doing really bad stuff.
The Korean creeper.
My beer is a little fail because it's also kind of a repeat,
but it's a repeat of that curse beer that tastes like shit and it was really
ghost in it. The redemption arc.
So this is the last of these that I have in my fridge.
So I'm gonna try to drink this,
and when I inevitably fail,
I'm gonna drink this lemon-lime white claw that I have.
- That's sweet.
That's, you know, I will say, I wouldn't say that's a fail.
It's a repeat, but you didn't really even get to drink
that beer the first time.
But open it and show me the top of the lid.
I can't believe you didn't even just, no way.
- Oh my God, dude.
It's gross.
- What?
- It's really gross.
How is that possible?
- You think it's like past due?
How do I check that?
- Just drink your white coffee.
- Take a sip, that's how you check it.
Tell us how it tastes.
Does it taste the same?
- It looks great.
Oh my God, it's spilling all over the place.
(laughing)
Oh, what the fuck?
- I knew that was gonna happen.
- God damn it.
He did the classic, the freshman move, dude.
He went bottoms up on a bottle.
I should have gotten a less epic beer
because I wish I could have started drinking mine already.
I've been waiting for Julio to clean up.
Okay, I would like to say,
yes, I have a pre-made cocktail,
but I did already have an angry orchard,
Something is like an angry, angry orchard, murder,
murder, rape brew or the rape brew.
I don't know if it was called that, but that was kind of the that was like,
you know, how when something has a lot is really high alcohol level.
Yeah, yeah.
So what they call it, the bastard.
Yeah, the stupid fucking bitch brew.
And you do in reality drinks 75% of it.
You fall asleep watching The Simpsons.
But they're like, this is for hardcore assholes only.
That's why I like Bud Light, because they got, they call it platinum.
You like Bud Light for other reasons.
Yeah.
You like Bud Light politically.
Oh yeah.
I'm politically aligned with Bud Light.
Okay.
Are you saying?
Yeah.
You, you, Caleb Mike is strong.
Let's just pretend to talk, to say what he was going to say.
Uh, my name is Caleb.
I'd really appreciate that Bud Light has changed their
spokesperson to that Bud Light.
Okay.
The point about Bud Light is this.
I don't care that if people are mad about it, the gay can.
I think that's actually, I think that is what it is about,
is the gay can, that they have a gay can now.
- They have a gay can?
- They do have a gay can?
- That Kid Rock video is one of the best videos ever made.
- I love Kid Rock.
- Where he shoots an MP5.
- That is so fucking incredible, dude.
That, okay, Kid Rock gets shit on because of, you know,
everything about him,
but the Osmosis Jones song is easily
one of the funniest recorded lines in the music.
- I feel one way or the other.
I don't care if she's 16, she's beautiful to me.
- I just call that statue Tory.
- But I say it's mandatory.
- That's the line.
Mandatory.
That's what he says.
(laughing)
- It's mandatory.
- Yes, dude.
(laughing)
- And people are disappointed in him.
He's making videos where he's transphobic
and shoots an MP5 into Bud Light cans,
which is the funniest video ever made.
And people are like, "Really, kid?
"Seriously, Mr. Rock?"
Yeah.
- Grow up.
- Grow up, Mr. Rock.
Kid, kid.
- No longer mandatory for you.
(laughing)
- Mandatory.
How much PCP do you have to be fucking smoking
to not just write that line
but put it into a kid's movie about germs?
(laughing)
- Dude, how does that,
how do people just listen to that
and just let that shit go through as well?
- That, I would say that is,
a lot of times you see people talk about the Mickey Rooney
like thing or like stuff like that
and people say, oh, it was a different time.
when people at the time were like,
"Oh, this is not okay," right?
Like definitely there was that kind of shit going around
even back then in the '60s.
But that specific thing of Kid Rock writing the...
That actually was just a different time.
It's a different time.
That is the only way to explain it,
is like how, yeah, people didn't even know.
He must have not known what those words meant.
They must have just been like,
"Well, you know, again, it's a germ saying this."
You think it was like a young thug,
you don't have internet type of thing?
Yeah, I guess.
Yeah, it was just like,
I don't fucking know,
but something just was not...
Here's the thing, right?
If you were a musician of that kind,
up until literally that point,
you could just be with 16 year olds.
That was fine.
That is true.
I should say it's fine.
That was normal.
Nobody knew about it.
Let's record it.
Greg said he was fine and he approves of it and he agrees with it.
I think it's fine.
I do. I actually.
You guys ever think about how you live?
Tyler didn't know that Stephen Tyler was her dad
until she was like 19 or some shit.
And apparently she was a big Aerosmith fan.
So she probably was like her dad.
Listen to a lot of Aerosmith for some reason.
Well, she she probably was fucking.
She's probably like rubbing her shit
thinking about Steve and Tyler had a big poster of him in a room
and then one day found out that was her dad.
What if your daughter had a poster of you in her room?
I would just say you better say best dad ever. Yeah, right. Yeah.
What if a pedophile had a time machine and they went back in time
to molest themselves as a child?
Has anyone asked this before?
Yeah, I just know.
Read it. I just that is.
He just he just wrote that.
You wrote that and read that.
Yeah, I wrote that.
I wrote that just before the show.
Really?
That's a really good topic for today.
Wait, I actually want to talk about this.
That is such a compelling movie.
That's like, that is like Primer 2.
That is so smart.
Yeah.
I mean, what are you, yeah, I mean, okay,
so here's the thing.
On one hand,
you, what are you, it's kind of best case scenario.
Yes.
Right?
I put it off, I was doing it to myself.
But here's what I might say.
That might be what we call a vicious cycle.
- I was thinking the same thing.
'Cause that kid is gonna grow up
and know that he has to molest himself.
- Yeah, well no, he's gonna be a pedophile
'cause he was molested as a child.
- But it's still like self-contained, no?
Like let him just do it, I guess.
- Yeah, I guess, yeah.
It's like-- - He's not hurting anybody.
- Well, he's hurting himself.
I mean, he's a buddy, right?
- He's my buddy. - Not my buddy.
That's not my buddy.
Really? That's why I brought it up.
This is his future.
Yeah, he told me.
Tell you what, man, even on my worst of days,
I would never molest anybody.
Yeah, that's an awesome.
Church on that.
That is the seriousness that is just sick.
You have to be.
I'll say it.
You have to be seriously fucking sick in the head to molest a child.
I agree.
You have to be, there's got to be something wrong with you, man.
So after 17 minutes, I would like to introduce my beard.
Oh yeah, introduce your, sorry, why are you talking about your topics
if you still have a beard intro?
It felt on top, it felt, you know, logical to go to that first.
OK.
I have an honest Abe, forefather of craft, Mexican lollipop,
a watermelon and habanero cider.
That sounds pretty good actually.
Is it spicy?
Yeah.
I would hope so.
Damn.
How does it taste?
Good.
Why is the honest dave a Mexican drink?
I don't know.
What's your honest dave review?
Pretty good.
It has that flavor of like tajin and like fruit.
I mean I'm going to need a numeric value between 1 and 10.
7.
pretty good. We don't do that around here. We're not Siskel and Ebert.
Well, well, well. A Mike-tion had to occur.
Okay, so as I was saying, the elites clearly don't want us to do this episode of Beers We
Drink. They've been keeping me and Rex busy all day so that we're as tired as can be.
They made Rex wear that beanie over his beanie.
They're trying to hide his beautiful hair from the world.
I know somebody gave you that beanie today.
Somebody on the street dressed like a Jehovah's Witness gave you that.
And it was definitely some kind of CIA operative.
Yeah, it's reducing the brainwaves.
It's because we're tackling dangerous ideas.
Yeah.
Such as what if a pedophile went back in time and molested himself?
I'm kind of feeling like, I'm almost feeling like that was some kind of, maybe you didn't
write that.
I'll come clean, it's an Ayela poll.
Oh my god.
What's Ayela?
Oh, she's a girl.
She's a lady who says she's in love.
I have a pretty good one.
Would you rather fight 100 horses or 100 ducks?
I think it's supposed to be 100 duck-sized horses.
You just exposed yourself.
We got you.
You got me what?
You got me for correcting you?
Yeah, you used Reddit.
I just got you.
- You've just asked that before.
- Hook, line, and stake.
(laughing)
- I've asked it before.
It's my favorite question.
I'm giving a toast as a best man.
Toast to the happy couple,
but also, would you guys rather fight?
(laughing)
- I would take a hundred ducks, I think.
- I could easily snap the neck of a hundred ducks.
- I would kill, I'd love to kill some horses.
Horses are fucking, I'd take out all my aggression I have for dogs and just out on one horse.
The thing about the question, right, is it presumes that the hundred animals have some
sort of teamwork.
Like, you're like Neo in the Matrix fighting a hundred Mr. Smiths.
The thing is, a bunch of horses are just going to stand there and fight.
All at the same time.
Yeah, they're not going to be like, "Whoa, that guy's fighting that horse.
other horse we should help that horse.
We should do a horse genocide.
Yeah, dude, people fucking, have you ever, you know what,
people, there's guys whose entire job
is to kill one thousand cows
in a day. The other
nine hundred cows don't do shit
about when he's got a
fucking air gun to one cow's
head, they're not like, oh shit, he's
gonna kill that cow.
They just sit there and wait their turn.
Speaking of killing animals,
do you see that thing, I really
want to do that thing.
Oh, did you kill another?
Did you throw another fucking animal?
Unborn?
All right.
Preborn.
Say that preborn animal.
I'll do it.
I'll do a bird update real quick.
The birds are completely gone.
Yeah.
They they fly.
Fly sometimes.
Good.
That's what I wanted to happen.
Yeah.
They haven't laid a shit.
The bird or a twig.
Yeah.
There's a lot of gay guys walking into Jeffrey Dahmer's house.
You fucking psycho.
Yeah.
What'd you just put in your mouth?
Me?
Yeah, I tried to I pushed a piece of ice around in my drink and then I I sucked off my finger
From my drink. Did you think I ate a booger?
What did you think that I put a booger on my desk and saved it for now?
What kind of boogers do you think I have you think I've crunchy boogers my boogers are soft as silk mine are hard dude
Okay, what I said I'm shooting cement
How does that work?
The fucking it dries up and it's hard
Okay, I can have the same thing of a sinus infection. He's a dry boogers
Yeah, but right. Yes, probably I blow spider webs onto my hands whenever I sneeze and shit. I'm just purely
ooey gooey disgusting
I'm serious
Anyways, these beers are crazy.
What?
You guys think that's gross?
No, I think that's normal.
Yeah.
I think Julio and I are weird.
Julio, what's your topic for today for beers we drink?
Oh, I want to...
The number one beer podcast in the world.
Thank you.
Stay with us, please.
Okay.
Look around.
So, good thing you said that with the number one beer podcast in the world.
What about if we made our own beer?
But what would our own dream beer look like?
- This is so fucking contentious.
I've thought about this so much
because we have three different types,
we have three different tastes, honestly.
Which is that I almost never have a beer on the show.
- Okay.
- Rex always has a very funny beer.
And Julio, you always have the worst of the three, somehow.
Even though I don't even have a beer,
you always have the worst choice.
So I don't really know what,
I don't think there is a beer that can be triangulated with those three tastes.
I think a sweet one.
Chocolate beer.
Nobody wants a chocolate beer, mate.
That's disgusting.
Have you ever had a chocolate stout?
Wait, you just had one.
The one that you spit out because it had some kind of trisipeps or whatever.
No, I don't think this has any mushrooms.
I could go for a milk stout right now.
I wish I was drinking a milk stout instead. I'd go for a glass of milk
That's what if I and I'll say it a lot of people want me to say this if we were three babies
That's what the podcast would be about. Yeah milk. We drink drink
Cracking open abreast. Did I used to love?
Talk about I don't love milk
Yeah, I used to Loki not me. I love my Jewish genetics. My ass was not drinking any milk
Yeah, I could tell you were bottle or you were a formula bottle. I
Was the opposite of formula fed but after that we're what's the opposite of formula fed big-ass fucking tits
Huge tits
They smell
Just fed normally
Massive yeah, there's so you know it's so big that the shirt comes off and you're like what the fuck does that smell?
It just smells like a you know like the back of a leg that's been sitting on a car in a car seat too long
You know kind of got that just
That road trip smell that your balls get road trip smell you're at the gas station
And you take yeah, you smell your balls when you sit down on the toilet
Yeah, yeah when I go like you've been drinking so much caffeine your whole body is sweating
Yeah, exactly. Like I feel like probably some women who have Brett really large breasts. I bet when they pop them out. They're like, oh
It smells like the inside the inside of my knee, you know, yeah
So that was your entire childhood then Rex, right? Yeah, right. I was getting in my whole childhood. They're really big smelly ones
The big stinkers
My childhood man, my mom basically had no tits at all. That's so sad man. No wonder you're like flat. Yeah
so I just didn't get any of my
Nutrients and I really struggled in school. I had attitude issues
Oh, I had those you know
He's trying to sneak in I used to try to pretend that I was a younger kid because I
Just I thought that I'd be better in those classes. I
Tried to do Madison when I was four
That's really smart.
I tried to do a full Billy Madison.
If you get an A, they have to give you an A for your real class.
I was a good kid.
That's how you get a 5.1 GPA.
But that's what I did have, is heart.
I had real heart.
Right.
I had real heart. And then I got older.
At the end of my childhood.
And your heart just...
No.
Closed up?
- I would say that I have, of the three of us,
by far the most open heart.
You two are both just kind of cold, mechanical,
evil people, bad, really bad people.
- Who do you think is the most cringe-like?
- Most cringe-like is you.
- Okay, that's not what I said.
I said cringe-like.
- Also you. - Cringe-to-like.
- Yeah, definitely still you.
- That's not true at all.
- You are the cringe. - Well, what, then it's me?
- I love Christmas.
- One of us here does not love Christmas.
(laughing)
- Okay, save for the small fact that you love Christmas,
you are the most Grinch-like.
If you took Christmas completely
out of the story of the Grinch.
- That's impossible.
- What if the Grinch was about a guy
getting an Airbnb for his friends?
Who would then be the most Grinch-like?
- Yeah, who's the stingiest with money here?
It's actually Julio.
- Yeah.
I have none of it.
- Well, see, that's what a stingy person says.
Oh, I can't pay, I have none of it.
I can't pay for the bill.
You've never bought me and Rex dinner once.
- Julio has a-- - That's not true.
- A joke wallet that opens up and a fly comes out
on the spring like a cucumber.
(laughing)
- I'm not the broke friend ordering wings.
- You are the broke AF friend ordering wings
and having us memo you for one of them.
- That's not true. - We take one wing
and you go, "Hey, can you Venmo me for that?"
And I go, "Okay, what's eight divided by 12?"
(laughing)
All right, I'll send that to you, whatever.
- That is not true.
- That is true.
Back me up on this, Rex.
- Oh, I honestly, I'm thinking about it.
And my favorite Julio thing that he does
is I'll get the Airbnb,
I'll drop thousands of dollars on housing.
- Tens of thousands.
- And he will very politely get the cheapest meal
on Uber Eats for both of us.
That's not true.
He'll get us halal food. It'll be like $12 each.
Don't get me wrong, I'm very happy with it. I appreciate it.
I gotta say something, Leo. I've done that move too.
I've done that move. When I was in Raleigh with Adam, I was like,
"Hey, do you want any Taco Bell?"
[laughter]
for Ipe's or every fucking meal and I'm like, "Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm ordering."
You're ordering a fucking chalupa?
I'm ordering, "Taco Bell, you want something?"
He's like, "Bro, yes, thank you so much."
I was like, "Yeah, dude, it's not a problem."
Yeah, don't worry, I fucking got you.
And then afterwards I was like, "Damn, he really is not even going to offer to like
reimburse me for that $25 time.
That's kind of whack."
Yeah.
Listen, I just didn't know I was such a burden on my friends.
I guess I'll just go kill myself.
- We're just waiting for you to get your paper up
so that you can start shipping in.
And then it'll all fall on you.
- I'm trying to make you,
I'm trying to raise you like a son
to be a professional athlete.
- We support you.
- I really, really want you to play.
I really think that you have the perfect brain and body
to be a professional golfer.
- I would love to become a golfer.
- Now, can you imagine?
That has to be by far the easiest, not easiest sport.
It's the hardest sport, I'll say.
- Right.
fun sport to be a professional in?
Do you have to be, does my height, is my height helpful at all in golf?
Yeah.
Is height at all like a factor in golf?
I would say, if I had to guess, most pro golfers are around six feet, maybe a little over.
Okay.
Yeah, then I can do it.
As far as, there's not a lot, it's not like basketball where you need to have like long
arms and big hands or something.
Like there's pretty much good golfers at every size, you know.
- Yeah, that's what I was thinking.
- But I think that you just have a genius brain for golf
because I've seen, I've watched you play PGA Tour 2K22.
- Dude, I love that game.
- Yeah, I know.
I know you play that game.
And I've seen you play it,
and you were an ace in the hole in that game.
I've seen you hit 175 yard just dunks,
just right into the pin.
- Me and Rex was just like sitting at this court
all together like at 12 in the morning just like playing golf in silence
through each other until we're so tired we're like I just gotta go. I kind of
want to do that tonight I'm not gonna lie to you guys. After we record this we should play some PGA Tour 2k22.
Because that is a fun fucking game. I think we should do a live episode from Topgolf.
I think we should do that this May. I would love to go back to Topgolf. Topgolf is...
Is there Topgolf in New York? Oh yeah there is. There's also we could go to the Chelsea
Pier. Chelsea Pier's driving range where you like hit into the river. That's awesome.
Yeah I think about golf it's the most it's the sport that most sets itself to drinking a beer
and doing it at the same time.
Exactly.
I feel.
Oh, dude. The first time I ever played golf, I got so unbelievably fucked up and I played maybe four – I
paid for an entire 18 hours that I'd never played before on a really hard course, the municipal course
in Wilmington, which is a tough course. Good golfers play at it. And it was really expensive.
It was like $60, $65 for a car. And me and my brother just brought a bunch of Michelob
ultras and we just got so fucked up and embarrassed ourselves hitting 15 times
on every single hole and then by the fourth one we had let maybe six or seven
groups play through like play in front of like play through us yeah so we're like
okay we're just not gonna finish this like we're gonna be here all day so we
just gave up sounds fun it was honestly one of the best days so so fun I got to
The first time I ever played golf,
I really, really thought that the entire thing
was just dressing up.
So I raided my stepfather's closet,
I found every quarter zip shirt that he had.
- You're dressed for it right now.
- I remember exactly what I wore.
I wore black slacks.
I wore Skechers.
That's right, I wore Skechers.
- Wow, okay. - I wore a braided brown belt.
I wore a purple striped polo
and a gray, a heather gray quarter zip.
And then on top, I had a Boston Red Sox hat on.
And in my mouth was a $2 cigar.
- Yup.
- Yup, and let me tell you,
I looked like about a million bucks.
- You did.
You looked like about $2.
- I was using my little brother's clubs,
his children's clubs that are about eight inches too short
for me to use because he was at the time nine years old.
And I was using those in front of just a bunch of old guys.
And they were saying this guy wait, this guy is gonna be something one day
This guy could become a professional golfer and play on the tour
I think you could go
First of all, he's gonna be really good at smoking cigars by then because I was spitting all over the place
I had the thing was a different color halfway down the cigar because it was wet
And then
Yeah, man, I just want to get to the point where I get to do one of the proams with Justin Timberlake. Hmm
That's such a goal of mine. I think you could go pro
like driving f1
Definitely a crash test on me. Yeah, cuz you're you're so smooth that the wind just yes
Aerodynamics. Yeah, you're so aerodynamic out of the three of us. You're the most aerodynamic. Actually, you're a small as a pill
Speaking of I think I'm gonna I accidentally called my ball sack my pills the other day
That's gonna stick. I think that's gonna stick around
How did that happen?
Somebody
You know how your voice kind of if you if somebody punches you in the balls as you're talking your voice like changes
Yeah
I tried to say don't hit my balls and my wife hit my balls at the exact time.
So it kind of sounded like I was like, "Don't hit my pills!"
So now I think I'll call them my pills the rest of my life.
Don't hit my pills!
I think it's funny to fucking try to hit my balls all the time. How fucked up is that?
You should you should do something that is kind of on the same level for women which i don't know what it is girls don't have a simple they say like oh you don't understand.
Start punching them don't let me punch every single square inch of your body and see what hurts the most and that is what i would punch all the time i think it's funny that's what you're doing.
(laughing)
How fucked up is that?
- It is fucked up that we get a big
like Zelda style like weak point.
- We have a weak point, yeah exactly.
We have a glowing weak point, a red glowing weak point.
- Literally.
- That women think is so funny.
They think it's so, so funny.
And I've seen grown men vomit because they hit their balls.
That isn't funny.
- They're pills you mean.
- That's how funny it all is.
- They hit their pills right on the fucking,
By the way, you can also consider your penis
part of your pills, depending on--
- That's a thick pill.
- The third pill.
- Not for me.
- Yeah.
- I would say my balls and my penis
are about the same size.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, soft.
- You got triplets?
- Yeah, I have three pills that just kind of sit perfectly.
It's like, you know those magnets?
Those magnets that spin around like this?
They're all like that, you know?
- Yeah.
- Three of those just in a row.
Sometimes I think I'm jacking off
I'm just grabbing my balls and doing this for like 45 minutes.
Why is this working?
Yeah.
But I think that pills is definitely going to make its way into the lexicon very soon.
I'm going to use that.
I think that's how most stuff that we say is born.
You just said something stupid.
Exactly.
Like fud.
Or pills.
This is like somebody doing, or you know I invented cap.
You did not invent that.
Prove me right.
What was the context of you inventing cap?
What were you calling cap?
Someone capped right at me and I said that's cap.
Capping about what?
They were capping about, I don't even remember, it's been so long.
I invented that probably 2004.
Right.
Yeah?
Well I invented the gritty.
You invented gritting your teeth.
No, I did not invent that.
You did not invent that.
You did invent that.
That's stupid.
Yeah, you invented the shitty, you invented shitting your pants.
You invented that.
That's not true, I did not invent that.
Okay, how did you invent the gritty then?
I saw someone do it and I was like, "That's the gritty."
Wait, that's not, that's not, wait.
You can't say you just saw someone do it.
That's naming the gritty.
Yeah.
Yeah, I invented it.
I invented it.
I saw someone do it.
I guess that's the same thing with Cap.
Like I didn't invent lying.
Yeah.
Although I wish I did.
I don't know what Ricky Gervais is.
See if they rebooted that movie
it'd be called The Invention of Capping.
Right.
And isn't that...
If that doesn't make Kid Rock shoot up a fucking school
then I don't know what will
because that is some serious shit.
Kid Rock shouldn't shoot up a school.
How funny would that be?
I mean...
Would you even be mad if your kid got shot by Kid Rock?
Oh yeah. Yeah, I'd definitely... yeah.
And then what?
I'd probably be mad if anybody killed my child.
Wait, who was he threatening by shooting all that beer?
He's threatening me.
He's threatening us. Wait, he was threatening this podcast.
Wait, what? We need to stand our ground.
He was saying, "Beers we drink, beers I shoot."
He should shoot Kid Rock.
Yeah, exactly.
That's what we need to do is we need to get a beer that shoots kid rock.
Yeah.
Tie it all together.
That's a dream beer.
Our dream beer.
Yeah.
This beer bites back.
It's sweet.
It's chocolate.
And it shoots kid rock.
Wait, that's the label.
It's like it looks like this machine kills fascists, but it says this beer kills kid rock.
This is so smart.
Yeah, like, we could, it could be like a, like a death type thing.
It'll be just like, just like an edgy name.
Yeah.
That's, we'll be like, "Whoa, that's awesome."
We should do a line of different "This Machine Kills Fascists" laptop stickers
that are just not even recognizable as parodies.
Yeah.
"This machine drinks beer."
"I drank a beer."
Just in that same font and kind of width.
"This guy drank a beer."
Yeah, "This guy drank a beer."
Tattoo on your back
Whatever
This machine kills fascist stick you're like this is the inspiration but I don't want to say any of these words
That's a good idea. We need to get you guys a bunch of tattoos like me
hundreds and hundreds of tattoos
You're a virgin like me yeah, I wouldn't be able to be buried in a cemetery
Yeah, that's true. You don't want to be buried in a Jewish cemetery. I don't
Oh, yeah, is your family do not right
the
Honestly, I think you should get a tattoo wearing your forehead that says the devil
That's the devil. Yeah
That's good
Like the Drake one, yeah
Yeah
To meet Drake no
What about some knuckle tattoos that say "Dunceville"?
I saw knuckle tattoos the other day that literally were nonsense.
I swear to God, I saw this guy, I was at a diner, and a guy...
Dirt Evil?
That's cool.
Dirt Evil.
I saw a guy at a diner, a guy who was working at a diner in the kitchen the other day, and
I couldn't even remember, I can't remember exactly what they said, but they might as well have said like "mobile bedoodle".
Like they said just nothing. It was just like random consonants and letters and like vowels in like just alternating order to make it look like it was a word, but none of them were words.
Oh that's cool. It could be like just like the initials to something and it just, no one gets it but you.
It was like trying to do it was like he was you know when you start a word all but you don't put a word you just do like words letters you think might be in just yeah yeah.
Yeah it's like that and i.
Yeah i kinda wanted to ask him like is that is that like grandma's name is that like.
Is that some kind of thing that you like is a food that you like or something left left hand word second hand.
I would do.
How do.
Oh this is actually really smart.
I would be left on this one on my on my palm it would be the number four.
Uh-huh, okay dead and then on the other promise to say left for dead -
And people be like what's that it's a game
Yeah, did you really like that game? See?
Yeah, oh PS
That's good
Yeah, I
I think getting I I know somebody who has a dishonored hand tattoo that's dope
dishonored like the video game yeah they have there's some symbol in it or some
shit and she that's the side of someone on her hand whose whose impulse control
is so bad they don't like have the time to think about the fact that this
honored will be forgotten in like six months because they had to have gotten
that like right away, right?
- Yeah.
- You know, that's why--
- I used to be such a,
I used to be kind of such a snob about tattoos.
And I was like, yeah, you should always get something
that's like always gonna look good
for the rest of your life.
- Yeah. - And like be time,
no, you should get--
- No, you should get a return--
- If you wanna get tattoos,
first of all, you shouldn't get tattoos.
But if you're going to,
you should get every,
the first thing that pops into your mind
every single time and never think about it.
- No, 100%.
- You should just get them.
There's like, there's no such thing as a good tattoo.
They're all stupid.
If you wanna be, if you wanna have them, just get them.
- I think the thing that-
- Getting a beer mug tattooed
and someone asking me what it means.
- That's it, I've had people do that with this.
It's a fucking eagle.
It's a bird.
- What does that mean? - Or this one.
This one, a skull with flames in it.
They're like, what does that mean?
I don't know, I'd probably-
- It's a skull with flames in it.
- Yeah, it's like a dead guy's head, bones,
and then it's on fire.
- Yeah.
I think people love getting like Givley tattoos
and like cartoon tattoos.
I think that's what people get these days.
- Yeah. - Yeah, I would never
do that shit.
I think that's for the devil.
- Yeah.
- I think it's an evil endeavor
and I would never sell my body like that.
- I would get a beer re-drink tattoo like yesterday.
- What would it look like?
- I'm gonna get like an old English tummy rocker
like Tupac had West Coast.
I'll just have beer like around my my belly.
Yeah, I think it'd be cool.
I want to get one of those like Yakuza style tattoos,
but instead of like a cool animal, it's like a beer splashing with water.
Like like the Japanese wave.
Mm. That's a good.
Yeah. Great wave of beer on your right.
Giant back. Just huge.
And people and just like in like for one person, one month.
It looks exactly like this.
Yeah. Like it looks like a piss.
Yeah. The color just goes awful.
Yeah, yeah, it just gets so so bad.
I'm going I'm I'm hiking up the mountain to get the Thailand like,
you know, tick tick tick tattoo.
Tabori.
Yeah, I'm going I'm walking a mile uphill every day to get that done.
I finally show it and it's just a huge bug.
Yeah, you get a Tabori fucking like
18000 dollar beer mug tattoo done by a 90 year old man in Korea.
He's just hitting you're hitting a needle with a mallet for days at a time.
He's going to get that by the biceps into cans of Sapporo.
Like the guy turned to the professor,
you know, turn himself into a snake or whatever.
Yeah, but it's just different beer cans.
And then your face, a big smiley face.
Yeah, that is the happiest man of all time.
It is the the serpent guy.
know the beer man that we just invented.
Yeah.
He could be like, uh, uh, did somebody check in on Mr. Cool Ice?
I don't even know who that is.
I think he's dead.
You don't know Mr. Cool Ice? Look up Mr. Cool Ice right now.
I know Mr. Cool Ice.
Mr. Cool Ice is this guy who has, um, all these great tattoos.
That say, uh, that say Mr. Cool Ice.
Yeah, that guy.
Oh wait, he's, he's, he's doing alright.
it improved. Dude these are cool. This is on shitty the shitty tattoos subreddit. These
are cool tattoos. Yeah. These are awesome. These are cool dude. I would have that on
my body tomorrow. Wait did he get it on his head though? Oh yeah he has the uh he has the
sunglasses on the back of his head. That is so cool. Sunglasses on the back of the head
is fucking dope. Rex I think you should do like Mr. Cool Eyes but with that outfit that
69 or like years ago.
What's that like, pussy?
Oh yeah, pussy.
The N word.
Oh yeah.
I think you can do that one.
That is the funniest thing of like,
there's only like four guys in the world.
Is that like that image was so funny 10 years ago.
Yeah.
Nobody can like a rapper.
Who's another person like that?
Every single rapper of all time.
You know who I think is going to be like that is the backpack song kid.
I feel like he's trying to get that.
I think that in like I think I honestly think in 10 years
he's going to be like an A24 director or something.
Yeah, we're like he's going to make a movie or he'll be the lead in a Saftey Brothers movie.
And you know who's going to be in a Saftey Brothers movie?
Oh, genius. Who?
Matan Evans.
Probably.
It's probably already in the next one.
What we were talking about, I think with we're talking about with Alex,
where like, it's so stupid, that whole thing of like,
oh yeah, he's everywhere.
But literally, what the, how the fuck is he doing that shit?
That's so scary. - I know, dude.
Literally, he shows up once a day, right?
- Yeah, I could all day be like,
ah yeah, this kid's trying too hard,
but then like, does he have like a whole team
working on this?
Like, this is unreal.
- Are we just going to like LA-based events now?
- No, dude, he's all over the place.
I don't think it's a little bit of background of every video.
I don't it's it is crazy.
It's a it's like a Nathan Fielder thing.
Like we'll find out that it's like, yeah, it does feel like a setup.
Yeah. Yeah.
And also, there's the like that kid definitely one day
is going to be some kind of world leader or something that I think he's 15 or 14.
A very powerful voice for a 15 year old.
Yeah, definitely.
He sounds like me when I was like the same age and I had a high voice
And I would try I made runescape videos and I would make I would do a deeper voice
because, yeah, I didn't want people to think I was a girl.
Well, being like the most famous guy now just means that you make
like the worst videos of all time.
So like he could easily be like an Aiden Ross type figure.
Like, yeah, yeah, with these kids, man, they're all having a rough go of it.
I think they need a potential figure.
- They need books, they need three different
personal figures that do make a single podcast
about drinking a beer.
- Should we step in?
- Yeah.
- Should we do something about this?
Should we take over Twitch?
- Yeah, you see that tweet about like,
oh, Rogan is bad, Peterson is bad, Tate is bad.
All right, but who's gonna be a good male role model?
That's us, that's us right there.
Yes.
Rex is gonna teach him about money.
Caleb is going to teach him about life and I'll teach him about gaming using the computer.
I'll gracefully go bald at 25.
Okay, so you insulted me.
Yeah.
And also, actually, there's a big compliment that you're saying I went bald this year.
As I said gracefully.
I would say that I went bald at...
Two years old.
17. I would say I'm a bald at 17. Yeah, but you didn't shave your head until...
You didn't give up. No, no, no, no, but that's not when you go bald. You go bald the second you
start balding. That is when you go bald. You look fine. Why? Because that's the only
place that you can place a line. Because otherwise the line is when you have no
hair on your entire head. Yeah. If you go bald not by your own volition, it's
It's the second that you start balding.
- Okay.
I feel like the moment you go past here, right?
When you're at the crest of your head.
- This is coming from somebody who's already started balding.
You've already gone bald.
That's what I'm saying.
You're bald.
You have a full head of hair, but you're bald.
Yeah, see the widow's peak, it's over.
It's over for me.
It's completely over.
I guess no one's ever gotten like hair plugs?
No.
I know somebody who might get them.
You?
He keeps talking about it.
No, not me.
I don't think, I think, uh, I, the thing is if you get the hair plugs you have to do stuff
for the rest of your life.
And I hate that.
Isn't that just for like six months?
And then...
No.
No no no no no.
an oxidil for the rest of your life,
if you wanna keep them.
- And right. - The hair.
- The hairs. - Okay.
The hairs.
- Yeah, what I'm really hoping is that AI technology.
- It's gonna put hair on every single picture
that's taken of you?
(laughing)
- I mean, you know, we will get to the point
where you have a, it's funny if that is like
just a problem we can never solve.
- Like hair loss?
Like we cure every kind of cancer, there's no poverty in the world, but if you're bald,
that's just how it works, man.
Sorry.
You know what it is, it's big pharma.
I have been thinking about that, which is like, probably as much scientific research
goes into curing cancer as does not being bald.
No, I actually think it's severely underfunded, because that's a pretty hard thing.
You know, the only people who give money...
People with cancer fucking die.
People with no hair live.
And they're suffering every day.
I can't argue with that.
You're right.
There has to be more money going into baldness because those people are alive.
The fatality rate for baldness, it's not zero.
It's not zero, but it's not as high as cancer.
I'll say that.
How many rich people have cancer?
How many rich people are bald?
On purpose, almost zero.
Basically what I've learned using YouTube is that basically every Hollywood leading man
has had hair surgery.
The most successful ones, Joel McHale had a really good one.
McHale's hair surgery, his hair comeback is great.
Matthew McConaughey is a legendary hair comeback.
Yeah
This is breaking my heart. You're ruining the Hollywood magic for me right now. Look up Matthew McConaughey bald
There's he had a fucked up
hairline, well, you knew you know who are like really good like images like before and after for like
Like Harold and come back so like soccer players
Because they could like taking pictures of them like every single day like you've been doing shaved his hair. He looks fine
No, he had there's there's a couple photos
He did shave his head, but that's Regenix
Yeah, he was on his way out, what would you
Yeah, that's like a point I think that's like really popular like the football world and
You know since they get like take take taking the pictures like every like every single day
Yeah
you can see like people who are like like they're just like all the way back here and then then they're like the next year
They look like the hairline is completely back
Yeah, dude, the only and here's here's a proof that no matter how much money LeBron James is proof that if it's bad enough
No amount of money will ever fix it because LeBron's hairline always goes back and forth every single year
Where the beginning of the year it's perfect and then but when the time the playoffs come he has to go get new plugs again
Yeah
It's it's fucking crazy. It's a plus like finite
Yeah, it's I mean if your body doesn't want them. I mean if you're if you are already balding
It's just gonna shoot that hair back out, right? So I think Rogan's got plugs like three times
Okay
Cuz you just have to keep getting them fucking installed. That's so sad, dude
We kind of hey looks great now
Yeah, shit with no hair, you know who looks insane that I think looks insane. It's Chris Pine
Did he get a hair thing? I
Think he got a face thing. He looks like the most beautiful girl. I think he's so good-looking
He always looks like it's so pissed off his silver Fox. Can I look I?
Don't know about the
City is something to us
The weekly Rex
Guess yeah
I was talking about this the other day.
He looks, no, his face looks so crazy.
He looks like he's always mad and he's doing like a kissy face.
I like it because I would want to...
You want to kiss his face?
No, I don't.
You know who I found out had plastic surgery?
Who?
And this is going to break your heart because she's one of the baddest bitches in the world right now.
Mm-hmm.
Wait, let me look up her name real quick. Hold on.
- Wait, hold on.
That's right guys, Brie Larson.
Yeah, Brie Larson used to have a fucked up nose,
but she got something called rhinoplasty
and they turned her nose into a Doritos.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
But she used to have a big fucked up,
she used to have a normal nose
and now she has some kind of odd GI Joe nose.
- Who do you think is the baddest bitch right now?
Let's talk, you know what, this is a guys podcast.
I don't think we've ever gotten into the weeds on women.
Right?
- True.
- So here's the baddest bitches.
Wait, hold on, I need to look up another game.
- Several?
Yeah, top 10 women.
- Well, I think it's a title that gets passed down.
- Okay, all right.
Baddest bitches in the game right now.
Number one, Mary Elizabeth Winstead.
- Yep.
- Okay.
Number two, Zoe Deschanel.
- All right.
- Damn, she is so, so hot.
Number three.
No, no, number three.
That one girl who did the rap,
or the like sing-along version of "Look At Me Now"
by Chris Brown.
You remember her?
- Yeah.
- Carmen, Carmen.
Carmen is fine.
- I don't know who Carmen is.
I'm gonna go with the
the
She dumb bad.
Yeah.
If I was a Roddy rich man, that would be my box.
If I was a Roddy rich man.
Harriet Tubman.
OK, yes.
Emmeline Pankhurst.
Who's that?
I don't know. Rosa Parks.
I don't know if she's bad.
Rita Calo.
Kamala Harris.
Yeah.
Actually no.
Maya Angelou.
Yep.
Don't know who that is.
I'm gonna go ahead and get
the- additional resources wait-
you're so silly. Yeah I will say
did Kamala Harris back in the day
she was pretty fun. She's right
now yes she's fine. With the
the
that
a picture and I'll see if I change my mind. Montel Williams. Montel Williams, that's who
it was. Yeah. I think you guys are, I think you guys are severely wrong. No. No what? I
think there's only one bad bitch in the game right now. I do think she's a bad bitch. And
her name is Kate Upton. Kate Upton is so fire. I can't lie, Kate Upton is so fucking fire.
Yeah, what's she now like?
100 years old
Dead
Kate up to now
I
Don't know
Probably selling her body probably selling her body for for money
Yeah, he up to now
She looks to be married to a guy who knows just leave her lander. That's right
From Rick and Morty. Yeah. Yeah
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- That's good.
- Anyways.
- We have to talk about how we need,
we haven't gotten any updates on whether or not
Justin Rolland is gonna be in the next Rick and Morty season.
- He's not, unfortunately.
He should be though.
- You think he should be?
You think they should let him back in?
- He's vindicated.
I don't see why not.
- According to law, there's nothing we can say.
- I think they should launch a competing project.
- I can't argue with the judge.
Oh, okay, wait.
What was his?
- Called,
uh,
Make an Rorty.
Okay, and this would maybe be about like a guy and maybe it's like a 60 second or
we'll say it's a nice because it's different, right?
We're having 16 year old sexual situations because she's well,
she gets she gets stuck in something on every single planet.
Yeah, he's got to help her out of it.
It'd be funny if it was a woman and she had to park the spaceship and
she like hit something every time that'd be a good recurring gag.
That's too much.
That would be, what do you mean, how would that be a sexist?
I don't understand.
Like, guys.
Ever since you put up this beanie.
Yeah, what if there was a Jewish alien, Rex?
Huh?
You're gonna laugh at this?
What if there was a fucking Jewish alien?
And what does he do?
What does he do?
Does he probably...
He's fucking, he's greedy.
You think that's funny?
- Yeah, it's a bit funny. - What if there was a Jewish elf
who was running the banks in the Harry Potter world?
- Yeah, I bet you'd think that was really, really funny
if they had a bunch of Jewish elves.
- I thought that was great representation.
- That's not true. - It is crazy how,
I mean, it's been harped on enough,
but a couple of those goblins
look exactly like Alan Dershowitz.
Like one to one, it's unreal.
Like definitely they were like--
- Yeah, he does. - Yeah.
- Just Googling Jewish guys.
the guy at a Universal Studios or whatever that has to like.
That's like modeling those, because, you know, they have them like super life
like, yeah, and like what kind of references for those got to be bad.
That they would have got that trumpet guy, the little Jewish guy.
Oh, yeah. What's his name?
Yeah, that is legitimately a he's a green guy.
Escape from Green Card. Yeah.
Do you guys love Harry Potter as much as I do?
I used to. I literally watched all the Harry Potter movies at the same like only one day because I had never watched them.
I have this concept in my head.
I used to not make a big deal out of it. When I was growing up, I was the biggest Harry Potter fan.
I loved it. And now and still to this day. You pop one of those movies in, I'll watch it front to back no problem.
It doesn't matter which one. I love them.
What's the best one you think?
The best one man. A lot of people would say it's the third one because Alfonso Caran made it
It's the fourth one. It's gobbled of fire. It's definitely gobbled of fire
Yes, any person who says that the third one is the best one is such a fucking herb who is like yeah
No, it's Alfonso Carani made it eat - mama tambien. It's like dude. Shut the fuck up. Okay, the fourth one has a
Underwater mermaid first of all and actually I'm gonna leave it at that cuz I don't want to spoil anything because it's such an amazing movie
Okay, I think it's been out for
20 years. Okay, then I'll spoil it. They're gonna make a grimdark HBO
Harry Potter remake and here's what I'm gonna do. I'm gonna wait four years and then I'm gonna skip that fourth season
Yep, I'm not even gonna watch the first three. I'm gonna skip to that fourth season. They should what I'm serious
- They could do so good. - And by the way, guys,
guess who's getting maybe cast as Dobby?
(laughing)
- You look very pink today.
- They should make a Harry Potter with rape and murder.
- They're going to, that's what the HBO one will be.
Dude, they're gonna show tits.
They're gonna show Professor McGonagall's flappy grannies.
They're gonna show that on like episode one.
'Cause they have to, the HBO thing.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Well, that's what I'll be saying when I watch it.
Wait, you know what?
I don't think Succession has any breasts in it.
- I think.
- But they say stuff like, they say fuck stick.
- Yeah.
There's plenty of HBO shows that don't have breasts.
- I wanna say that.
- Yeah, I guess you're right.
- Maybe not.
- I think there's like a scale
and it's like you can either put money on tits
or you could put money on like language
are
their head should pop off.
- Their shirts open up and their breasts show.
- Yeah, well that's the two options they have.
Yeah, they should do like Leisure Suit Larry,
but it's Harry Potter is going around
and he's doing x-ray on all the girls' clothes and stuff.
- That's kind of what the game is like, right?
Just like, the wand is just like a gun, pretty much.
- Yeah, and that's sick.
- Yeah, no, the game is, that's the thing,
the game, I think at the end of the game,
you learn how to do the kill the avada kedavra, the killing one.
And so, but it doesn't like prevent you from using it anywhere.
So you just walk up to like the head of the entire school, just kill him.
Yeah. But it's not like GTA. There's no star system.
So you just kill him and people just go, nobody does anything.
People just walk right over his body. They go, Oh, what's that?
- Nope.
- Did Harry Potter just give us the sequel to Bully
that we always wanted these years, but we never got?
- Kind of, dude.
I love Bully.
I was talking to somebody today
that that is probably my second favorite Rockstar game.
I love that game.
- I've never played it.
- Yeah, I've never played it either.
- I think it's worth going back and playing it.
- Yes, it is worth going back and playing.
I only played it maybe five years ago.
I never played it when it came out,
'cause I thought it was gonna be too scary,
'cause I was so scared of bullies.
I think I'm going to get into emulation in a bad way this year.
I don't think there's a good way to get into emulation.
The thing is a lot of those games don't hold up.
With N64 it's like Starforce Gemini, is that what it's called? Something Gemini, the rare game.
And Mario 64, that's pretty much it.
I think I would still love Star Fox to this day.
a
And it has like the weird zombies.
And guys, I'll admit it, when Peppy gets infected by the zombie, I cried.
I really cried. - What? I didn't know that happened.
- Okay, I'm not gonna... - Spoilers.
- Never mind. Peppy fans, I hate to break the news to you,
but he gets assimilated. It's very, very sad.
- I thought Peppy was a girl.
When I was playing Star Fox 64. - What kind of girls do you hang out with?
- Peppy one? - Hey, there, Julio!
- Oh, wait, not Peppy. Slippy. I thought Slippy was a girl.
- Slippy might be a girl, it's a frog,
it's that there's no difference.
But Peppy is the old rabbit.
- Yeah, Peppy's a guy, Falco is a guy,
Fox is a guy, Slippy is a girl.
- Slippy definitely has a girlish attitude.
I don't know that I would necessarily call him a girl.
Crystal, on the other hand, from Star Fox Adventures,
is foin.
- Yeah, well she had boobs, I think.
- She seriously had some boobs on her, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, and when I was a kid.
- Yeah, they also, like, they tried to discourage you
from having sex with her in two ways,
which is one, she's a fox,
but then number two, they made her blue.
- Right.
- And I still was just, I was beating it raw to Crystal.
- I think you might've been a furry when you were a kid.
- Man, these Kamala Harris pictures are just fucking insane.
She just looked so different.
- All right, Rex, tell them about your new project.
Link to your new project.
This camera, that camera, go ahead.
- What new project?
I don't know what you're talking about.
- Go ahead.
- I don't have any new projects.
There's no new projects.
- Admit it.
- There's no new projects.
- I'll admit to your new project.
- I don't have any new projects.
- Admit to your new project.
Okay, so what were you bragging about?
- Rex is gonna start in the new,
the reboot to Pranked with,
it's gonna be Pranked with Rex.
That's what it's gonna be called.
- Are you thinking about Punked?
- Fuck.
(laughs)
Thinking about something, really?
[laughter]
Yeah, we'll end it there.