[Sipping]
[Burp]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer broadcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[Burp]
This is a journey into sea,
into the land,
Bud Light.
Ha!
Food ribbon!
Beers We Drank, Motherfucker, with Juvio, Caleb, and Rex.
Hey, what's up?
Hold on.
And good morning.
Wait, this is Beers We Drank 21, which means--
Oh!
Oh, shit.
21.
Like the vine.
Like Drake.
21.
Yeah, like Drake.
Oh, we're like Drake.
We are like Drake.
This is me looking at you.
This is how you're looking.
You know, I got a text from...
I can hear myself through Rex's headphones,
which is bad news.
No, it's fine.
No, it's not good.
What about now?
People don't like that.
People love that.
People love the quirks of the show.
Yeah, the guy is...
It's good that you said that.
I'm a brave, kind of, I'm a stepper.
Okay.
Yeah.
So I got a text from Julio, not that long ago,
and he said we should do, I can still hear it.
he said that we should do a modelo episode
and i said i don't know that i will but then i went into the grocery store and
i saw something that seems so amazing to me
so i got it and that is
a modelo
auto ok auto
you just completely fucked up the entire show
why? the whole show is fucked
i didn't know we were doing a modelo episode we're not doing a modelo episode i have
another beard another chango beard tyro beard oh i'm sorry am i the only one
who followed the homework?
Suck it off, suck it off.
Suck me off, suck it completely off my body.
- Okay.
- 'Cause I'm drinking a Modelo, a Modelo auto.
- And this has different flavors than the normal Modelo.
- So now, you know how we've been talking about
how fucked our weeks are this entire week?
- Yeah.
- You are being part of the fucker now.
Because I just said in the afternoon,
before lunch I was like,
maybe we should do a Modelo episode.
We did the boat light episode.
I think that was fun.
Like that we all had the same beer.
I thought that was an interesting thing, but then he went, no, I'm getting
secret, I'm getting secret surprise beers.
So I was like, okay, I'll just do something else.
You said that.
And now you're coming in here and you just blew everything to pieces basically.
And now you're just gesticulating like a cartoon.
You're mad that I got you.
I reversed you.
How did you get me?
You just lied to me.
That's what you did.
- I got you.
- You just completely lied to me.
- That's what getting is.
That's what a prank is, is lying.
- How was it a prank?
You just lied to me.
- I don't know.
- You were in a close friend's house
and you lied to me.
You just stabbed me in the back.
- I just wanted, when I got into the grocery store,
I realized that a Modelo actually sounded quite fine to me.
- Well.
- So I got one.
And guess what guys?
It's not as good as a normal Modelo.
I should have gotten a normal Modelo instead of the auto!
And this one has...
3 grams of carbs and 90 calories per serving.
Looks like it's 24 ounce, 4% alcohol, pretty, it's on the low end.
Okay, so now, despite Caleb's lying, I'm putting it into paper right now that next week we
do have homework and we're going to have the real Modellos.
That's going to be the Modello episode.
and there's no line.
- Yeah, exactly, this isn't even a normal Modelo.
- I hedged it, I have a Modelo light beer in the fridge,
but I didn't grab it
'cause I thought we were gonna do Modelo next week.
- So you just spoiled your selection next week.
You're not even doing a Modelo next week.
You're doing a Modelo light beer.
- Well, no, I'll just do it.
We're doing Modelo.
No, this is stupid.
- No, we'll do straight Modelo.
- You have ruined the entire show for the rest of time.
- This is foolish.
- You're a fool.
- Whatever.
- For our ceremonial 21st episode.
- The beer we drank of getting beers.
- I don't even want to drink anymore.
- Okay guys, what is more 21, right?
Than drinking beer and acting like a mess, okay?
And that's what, this is in the spirit of turning 21.
I bought the wrong drink.
I feel-- - Don't like it?
- I don't like it at all.
I bought the wrong drink.
I'm brand new to drinking.
I don't know what's going on.
Guys, tell me about your 21st birthday
or actually your 18th birthday, Julio.
- Okay, I'm gonna open this for you first.
- Because you live in a degenerate mud hole?
- It was normal.
- What did you do?
Did you go out and have a celebratory cerveza
or maybe a margarita?
- No.
- You didn't go drinking on your 18th birthday?
- I think like 16, 17, towards like literally 20s
is one of those times where I was like,
I don't care about my birthday.
And all I did was just go to my family and just have a lunch.
- Wow.
celebration that means that you are a loser I didn't know that about you I
didn't realize you were such a massive loser yeah yeah you just got knocked out
what'd you do for your 21st Rex I walked to the gas station I got to Bud Light
lime maritas and they didn't card me and it pissed me off.
They didn't card me and I was like I just this is the one day I want to be carded.
I told you about the time I got carded right in the US?
No.
I got carded two years ago when I was 26 years old.
Wow.
I was in Chicago with some friends and I went into this uh just like gas station.
Okay, it was in Chicago. I don't know where it was. Maybe Chicago, maybe Houston.
I do know that I was in my mid-20s and I walk in and I'm like, "Oh, I'm gonna buy a thing of beers."
So I walk in, I grab a case of beers and I'm walking out to pay with my money.
And the guy who seems like he barely spoke English, but I'm not gonna get into that.
You don't like those.
He's like, "Oh, yeah, what's your... I need your ID."
I was like, okay, so I show him my ID, which is always a problem because my ID doesn't say when I was born for some reason
And he looks at it is like yeah, this doesn't I would announce a that at the machine. I don't know what this is say
So he's like I need one that goes into the machine. They need to like scan it
Instead of like looking with his eyes
So I couldn't buy beers
That's a saddest fuck it is said
Can you be fair you beer I want to open mine you do look like a middle schooler to be completely I'm hoping it may be
Fair you look like a Mandela effect
Nets to classified he looks like a modella effect guys
That's racist
Again, I have a chatter again and I'm gonna be I know you are gonna say rule number one of the podcast
Don't repeat a beer the the next week
But I do I want to remind you guys that there is an addendum if you had a shit week
You got to just repeat if you want you get to break every single rule
Which I think I did so I think I'm gonna repeat and drink this thing whatever
Excuses I have a hearty snacks, which I like I have a
Succulent sipper. Oh my god. It's a cactus cooler
It might be it's a orange pineapple hard seltzer
My ex
Okay, wait is this
It has the same logo as cactus cooler. Have you ever had cactus cooler? It's my favorite. Yeah. Yeah
It's I think it's a knockoff of cactus cooler. Tell me if it tastes like cactus cooler
Which is would make sense why it's called the succulent sipper
What the fuck is a cactus cooler? It's a West Coast soda
High season that orange juice. No, it's like I would say it's closer to a Fanta
That's really good. It's like a combo pineapple orange Fanta. Well, you like it. Yeah. What's the flavor?
What he's saying it's a cactus cooler, but it's with alcohol in it. That is amazing
For my 21st birthday my older brother visited me in Boston, but it was a it was a school day
And so like we went out drinking that the that night and at like midnight
But all the bars closed in Boston at like 1 so we were only out for like an hour and then the next day we just
Heard drinking before my 930 a.m. Class at this bar. That was just open
So I was it was like we're just one of the worst days of my entire life
I was just like fucked up trying to do like an art history class for three hours
Not that fun. No, it sounds horrible. Yeah, wait, so what did you miss you?
just like he visited me for my 21st birthday so that we could drink that's
how big of a deal a 21st birthday should should be to you right and you seem to
be kind of disrespecting that tradition well I basically don't care about
anything because I am hold the phone that's cool that's actually fucking cool
as shit I'm sorry I said that I said that to like one of those what are those
like the guys who campaign, you see something, I forgot what they are.
Canvassers.
Canvassers, yeah, there's a canvasser once that came up to me in Austin, he was like,
"Yo, you seem like you care about something."
And I just walked right straight past him and I said, "I don't care about anything."
I just went in my way.
Wow.
That guy's probably still thinking about that and how cool you are.
He probably quit volunteering for probably a pretty damn good cause because you were
were so cool that it ruined this entire--
- Well, I can't do anything, even if I did care.
I'm from a different country.
What the fuck am I gonna do?
- All they just need signature is
you can just fucking write a name on there.
- No, they're gonna--
- No, you need their address.
- They're gonna kill me.
- It'd be funny to write an address that's just in Mexico.
- Yeah, see what they do.
- I don't think they would like that.
- One of your fucked up 14 line addresses.
Bro, I need to send you a Christmas gift.
- It's not 14, no, it's completely--
- And your phone number is 50 digits long.
It's really not.
When I type your phone number into my phone,
it literally, like the format is like two digits,
two digits, one digit, three digit, five digit.
That's yeah.
Put spaces between all of them.
Well, the only thing is you just have to add +52,
which is the country code.
That's it.
If you live somewhere with a country code,
you need to move because you don't have those here.
Yeah, they do.
You know what ours is?
One.
Number one.
Yep.
One.
Easy to remember.
No, it's you and Canada and something else.
I think the Virgin Islands is plus one.
I think the Virgin Islands, isn't that a US territory or a Canadian territory or something?
Sounds like that, yeah.
So we still got that, buddy.
That's still us.
I do think that that's stupid.
I think area cards are stupid.
I think everyone should just move to using WhatsApp for phone-related purposes.
I think everyone should use email to communicate.
I love checking my email. I love seeing the number go up.
How many unread emails do you have on your phone right now?
Probably 20,000.
I bet you guys can't beat me.
Okay. Whoa. Okay.
I have 35,229.
Okay. So I have two figures, but I think one of them is up.
It's a, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a,
it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a,
It's being inflated because I also have the podcast account on my email apps.
So my Gmail app says 3,400 but my mail app says 29,000 which is insane.
I don't know what the discrepancy is.
My Gmail app, hold your breath guys, 49,834 unread emails.
Big fucking winner.
Yep.
Wait, okay, my mail app on Apple is 142,285.
- What the fuck are you guys signing up to
to get emailed?
- I don't even know how that's possible.
- New egg, I signed up for new egg when I was 15,
it probably ruined my life.
Like they send me 50 emails every day, at least.
- One of my old email addresses, I think I get,
I think eBay, it's a big email there,
they will email you every single day
about something that you cared about 15 years ago.
And I just, when I log into that email account,
just look at it, it's like, I don't want that anymore,
but I don't know how to turn this off.
- Yeah.
- So I just closed the window.
- I think I also, I think every once in a while
I get an eBay email that's like,
do you still wanna know about Nintendo 64s?
(laughing)
Do you still wanna know what Nintendo 64s are for sale?
And I go, I don't think so.
I don't think I need a Nintendo 64.
- You're trying to buy a Nintendo 64?
I bought one for $30 when I was like 11.
- Yeah.
- And then I still get the emails about it.
- Dude, what was your first gaming console you bought?
- I bought?
- Yeah, that you bought.
- Like I bought with my own money?
- Yeah.
- Probably an N64.
First one I ever had was an N64.
I had an N64, then I had a PS2,
then we sold the PS2, I got a GameCube,
and then we got an Xbox.
- I loved GameCube, you were so good at it.
And then I had the Xbox for a long time.
Then I had the Xbox 360.
And then I didn't have I haven't had one since then, except for a switch.
Yeah, I got a I bought a PS2
from a tennis instructor down the street from me
for $60.
It was all my birthday money, and it came.
He gave me Need for Speed Underground.
Man, I. Wow.
Yeah, and that's the only way you're getting manhunt by the way.
Well, this is what really pisses me off.
My mom forced me, forced me to go to GameStop and sell manhunt.
No! For $3. Oh, I was just about to say $3!
And that is why I will never visit her in the nursing home.
I remember when Halo 3 came out, I think I turned in
every game that I owned so that I could buy Halo 3.
And I think I literally turned in like 15 games to buy Halo 3.
And how much did you get?
I think I probably got 40 bucks for it.
Yeah.
Okay.
I think my first console was the N64.
But I talked about this all the time on stream.
I have like certain games that I used to play a lot.
Like I think I played Mario Kart a lot.
I played some like movie title games.
I played a lot as well, but I was I think I was too stupid to figure out how to save a game
So I just whatever I would just turn to get the game on I would play the first
Couple levels and I was like, okay, I'm done and then I would do the same thing every single day of my childhood
Well, that's what was so fucked about the n64 is you had to have the expansion slot first for like a Zelda game
Yeah, whenever I talk about that people in my channel, which I never ever had that
Yeah, people in Chad were like no you didn't need that there's you could save them to the cart
And I was like, uh, no, I never I couldn't do that
I don't think which I don't know if I if I if I knew I didn't know how to do that
The first console I bought though. I think it was a ps4
Was a spoiled child then I got all my consoles bought for me
Growing. All right. Well, what's your top five games you played as like a kid?
Like until you know, you got into shooters and shit
Well, I mean lover
Glover, yeah Glover was an amazing game
I only played really fucked up games on the n64 because I also did not have the save thing
So I tried to play like Majora's Mask and it I just couldn't save it. So I just gave it to my friend
Glover
Star Force Gemini, I think it was called
That game was amazing. That game was sick. I
Love the first level of that game
Conqueror's Bad Fur Day
You're an amazing childhood. I conquered bad for a day was my brother's friend
But I only had it I only had it for like a week because he left it at our house
But I played it all the time and I learned how to cuss
number three
The demo that was on the Xbox the original Xbox game that was called like something frenzy
Party frenzy or whatever. Do you know what I'm talking about?
I have to find this game
And then another game that I loved growing up that was not like a real game
hmm
That is - oh oh Kelly Slater pro surfing
Okay, cuz I oh so I won. I had an Xbox and then I won a raffle at
public pool and I won an Xbox and another Xbox and a
Copy of Kelly Slater pro surfing and instead of selling the brand-new Xbox. I thought it was cooler to have two Xbox
So I just we already had one and I just had the other one and if my brother was using the one then I would just
Plug the other one in downstairs, right? That's sick. That's dope. All right, Julio. I think my top five I think
Maybe two spots are gonna be occupied by movie games because I usually love Z. Sorry. That's the name of the game
I love the the Toy Story 2 game on the N64 and I also love the Bugs Life game as well
on the N64 but I never really got to finish them. I love Mario Kart both on N64 and on
the GameCube. I also really like Mario Tennis on the GameCube. I think my last one is gonna
be like one of the games I played the most that I can remember. It's on my PSP. I had
I had Burnout something, it's one of the Burnout games that was like ported from PS2 to PSP
and that shit was so good.
Oh my god, that was so good.
The PSP was amazing.
It was.
I also had Sarge's Heroes, did you ever play that?
No.
It was like about being an army man, like a green army man, a toy.
Nope.
And then a game that I loved on the Xbox was called Conflict Desert Storm.
And that was like a third person shooter. It was really really fire.
It was just about being in the Middle East in the 90's. It was beast.
That makes a lot of sense.
Alright, ready?
Mario Party 4.
Yep. Okay.
Super Mario Baseball.
Oh yes! For Gamecube?
Yep.
Yeah, I'm so jealous.
I used to hit straight dingers on that game with PD Piranha.
Yes, dude. Yes, and I used to just
choose all the power characters. Oh yeah.
You get a power character, you get PD Piranha to play pitcher,
and you get one other pitcher, and then you take the Koopas
so that they all have synergy in the field.
Yes. I could hit dingers with Goomba.
That's how good I was with that game.
With that thin bat.
Brother, the bat don't got to be so thin.
Why you got that thin bat?
Hey, Monty Mole, why are you pulling up with the noodle?
Get a normal Louisville Slugger and hit that shit.
Yeah.
Real quick aside, isn't baseball like the best ever like arcade sport game of all
time?
Um, it's pretty fun.
I would say, for like years, and I just want to put it out there.
The 2005 to 2015 Madden games are pretty unbeatable.
And also NFL Blitz.
Y'all ever played NFL Blitz? That was another amazing sports game.
But speaking strictly like arcade,
like arcade-y type conversions of sports, I think baseball is the king of them.
I would say Mario Superstar Baseball is the best sports game ever.
Yeah. Yeah. It's unbeatable. I think I've talked about this. So for number three was Madden '06
where I spent three hours one day creating 53 players named like my name.
They were all 6'8", 300 pounds, perfect stats in every way, dark as night.
You had a 6'8" wide receiver?
Yeah.
Well, here's the thing.
Two real players on the team.
Tom Brady, Randy Moss.
Nice.
Everyone else, fuck it.
I would go, I would take the ball, I'd do a QB sneak, play one.
I'd run. Did you say they were dark as night? Sorry.
Did I miss that? You said they were dark.
It was 50 black guys with Jewish names
running around.
Yup. Uh huh.
What team was it?
It was like randomly created. Oh, okay.
I think I hit the random button.
And same thing for the logo.
I would do a QB sneak, play one,
run all the way back to my one yard line,
Throw a seam route down the sidelines
99-yard touchdown to Randy Moss
Every play it was amazing. I had so Brady could throw 99
You can throw about 70 and Randy Moss
You would just a little spin move when he caught the ball press B and just Wow take off down the sideline
Amazing I think NFL blitz is probably why I never got into the NFL because I played NFL blitz before I really had
ever watched football and I was like, "Oh, this is cool.
You get to hear the crunching of their bones when they hit each other.
There's blood everywhere. People's arms fly off.
This is how football should be."
And then I watched it and it was all just people sitting around,
waiting on guys talking to each other.
It's a very boring sport to watch.
- I think I also had Madden 06 for the GameCube.
Riggs, wasn't there a section,
if you wanted to express on that game,
You could just watch like a trailer for Madden Blitz,
NFL Blitz.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I think I remember watching that a couple of times
and being like, wow, that game looks so sick.
- It was a sick game.
- You could import your character from NCAA 05.
Amazing game.
- I remember playing the NCAA games
more than the Madden games,
and they were just not as fun, man.
- No, no.
It's so fun to just put up 90 points
in a five minute quarter.
Yeah, just going just no defense.
Just all throwing the ball as far as possible.
There's no play.
You go for it every fourth down.
Never punt.
Never, never.
No.
And the only time you play is to do a fake punt.
And yeah, and I would always I didn't know what any of the plays meant
when I looked at them, so I would always just do Hail Mary every single play.
No, dude, picking a defensive play, it's like fucking whatever.
Yeah, I don't care.
The one, just a wall.
Yeah, I would just pick the one with the biggest,
like the most amount of circles on the graphic.
Yeah.
Do they still make Madden games?
They do.
Yeah, 100%.
But they've definitely been usurped
in popularity by 2K, right?
Yes, 2K24, Kobe Bryant on the cover.
24.
That's a different sport.
Yeah.
Did he play this season?
Kobe Bryant, that's what you just asked?
No, he didn't play, he retired in 2016, you moron.
- Oh, okay.
- And then he blew up horrifically in a helicopter.
- Oh yeah, I forgot about that.
- So what's the rest of your list?
- Original Harry Potter game for the PC.
- Okay.
- I'm getting girl vibes from your selections.
- You're getting girl vibes after Madden '06?
- It seems like you were kind of hedging your Harry Potter
selection with the Madden pick. I will say I do have a girl game for my sixth
spot which is Little Big Planet. Oh Little Big Planet was good. But you could
also develop a level that looked like boobs. Yeah but that's a
completely game for girls. That is true. Alright last game for me
Matrix Reloaded. Oh my of course that's the best game ever. Yeah that game is so
fucking fun when you go running on security level you go to the security
scene is the most fun I've ever had in a game dude I never amazing can you can
you just go through it in detail for the next half an hour it's basically the
mate you it's the it's one of the those first like gen 3 console movie games
that were all exactly how you wanted the movie game to be with like Matrix
Reloaded and Spider-Man where you were like doing just everything
that you wanted to do when you watch the movie.
Yeah, right and nothing extra.
They understood the assignment.
They'd completely wanted to fight you wanted to press buttons.
So it was like Devil May Cry combat.
Yeah, you ran on the walls.
You did Matrix like bullet time shit did all that stuff.
It had cursing in it.
There's a scene at the end where the Wachowskis cursed.
There's a scene where you, yep.
Mm-hmm.
They're in it.
Yeah.
Uh, they, uh, you just, just fighting Morpheus in the clouds.
There's just so many twins.
Yep.
The twins.
Oh my God.
The twins, the twins, beautiful twins.
It's, it's truly one of the best games ever made.
It is an amazing, amazing.
And it does not hold up at all.
I'm sure.
But when, I mean, you can't, I don't, I don't, I don't get, I feel like every
once in a while, I'll see a YouTube video.
That's like super Mario.
Sunshine is not as good as you remember it being.
And I'm like, I'm sure it's not.
They've everything has gotten the worst game that comes out.
Now would have been the greatest game of all time in 2003.
That's a lie by the way, it holds up except for the intro.
The intro is so slow.
The intro, the unskippable intro is really, really annoying.
where they send you to fucking jail every single time.
- Yeah, yeah.
I also, that game needs to have a courtroom scene
where I can plead my case.
- Yeah. - That's my feeling.
- I think it should have that,
but it should still do the cut scene
where you still get sent to jail no matter what you do.
- Do you remember watching like old Flash videos
and they would be like, "Oh, Super Mario accounting?"
You know, like that kind of like.
And I didn't understand that
there's not that many Mario games.
He just plays all the sports.
and they're all good.
I would play Super Mario Accounting.
- They probably have not made a bad Mario game once,
I don't think.
Did you guys ever play Paper Mario?
- Nope.
- Fans of 2D rejoice.
This game is for you.
Super Mario, Paper Super Mario and the secret door, right?
Wait, why is that door so secret?
Well, buddy, it's two dimensional
and you're looking at it from the wrong direction.
And what you have to do is you have to switch
into the three-dimensional world to see this door.
By IGN's review, nine out of 10.
- I think I played Super Mario for the N64,
that was like my first ever RPG,
but I didn't know what an RPG game was.
So I think it was in a hotel.
- Wait, you played Super Mario--
- Paper Mario, sorry.
- Oh, Paper Mario, okay.
- I think I played Paper Mario on like a N64,
one of those like hotel rooms.
I was like, "Please, can I play this game?
"I wanna play this game."
So they let me play the game.
- You played it in a hotel room?
My parents never let me play the N64 at the hotel room.
- It was so expensive, man.
- It was so expensive, but I would just do it.
- Yep, fuck it.
- Because I didn't know about money.
- Don't ask for permission, ask for forgiveness.
- I did ask for permission.
And then I played it, and I was like,
I don't get this game at all.
I don't know what's going on.
Why can't I just jump and kill the enemies?
- Yeah.
- So I stopped playing shortly after.
- The best Mario RPG is Super Mario RPG for the,
I think either the N64 or the Super Nintendo,
but it had, it was the Super Mario RPG
and the Legend of the Seven Stars.
It was basically like an old Final Fantasy game.
It was so much fun.
- Yeah, that's beautiful.
- Yeah.
- It never occurred for RPG games as a kid.
I didn't care.
- Yeah, they were a little too slow for me.
- It also just occurred to me that when you were talking
about my HX reloaded, I was thinking to myself,
like I did really enjoy like movie games but I guess I just didn't under like it
didn't come to my mind that there would be movie games for movies are not like
picture game picture movies so we're only play like monster saying like the
Incredibles games was a picture movie even like animated movies yeah like an
animated movie oh I like your turn better yeah I thought you said picture
movie I said Pixar I said picture movie I said you motherfucker that damn picture
movie okay okay whatever man my week has been complete shit and are you making
fun of me yeah does that make you feel feels better now that I know that it's
working that's getting to you no it's not going to me but yeah I I do I miss
that kind of like like I feel like I've not in a while played a game without
watching probably five hours of reviews for the game mm-hmm and then I play it
for 20 minutes and I decide I don't really like it well here's the thing
video games are not fun anymore that's actually true what do you say about that
oh they're hard work you have to work like do you mean you feel when you play
any video game that it is work or you feel like the games they make now are work?
The games they make now are work but also it just feels like work.
Have you gone back and played Skyrim because I would say that there's no game that holds
up worse than Skyrim.
I never played it, knew I would not like it, and have no interest in playing it now.
It's been released like nine times.
It has been released nine times.
Speaking of Rees, we were doing crosswords the other day.
There was a fucking Rebus in the crossword.
Oh no no no.
I don't want to have anything to do with a Rebus man.
So this is why...
It pissed me off so much.
Uh huh, go ahead.
And then I got up...
What day was it?
It was Thursday.
Oh yeah, you got anything Thursday through Sunday, you got to expect once a month they're
going to put a Rebus in there.
they were they were two Rebus's next to each other and I didn't really I didn't
really understand the actual clues that had both Rebus's but I got it you know
like vertically and understood that there was like two Rebus's next to each
other and I got off with Julio because we did it on stream and I was telling my
girlfriend about it and then realizing the puns of the Rebus's as I was telling
her about it and getting like progressively more mad about the rebuses.
Yeah.
There was like a game.
There was like a question about Coolio song gangsters paradise.
Answer was gangsters.
Die, die paradise.
Parade die.
Oh God.
And I was like, Oh you pieces of shit.
I hate that.
Where do you get off?
So this is why in the middle of like nowhere, I texted you.
Caleb, how long did it take you to do the Thursday's crossword?
Because it took Rex with my minutes and that's almost like an hour.
OK, if you were if you were on your own doing that,
that would be not that bad of a time, I would say for a Thursday.
Julio doesn't really help me with the crosswords.
I know that's not a bad time at all.
I would say under an hour for a Thursday, for a hard Thursday with Revis's
is a decent time.
Yeah, if it wasn't for the chat,
I wouldn't have known what a rebus is,
which is an invaluable contribution on their part.
Yeah, I remember the first time I came up against what it just it just
I just never I didn't know what it was, and I just quit the crossword completely.
I think it's complete bullshit.
I think that shouldn't be allowed.
I agree.
There's a lot of things I don't think should be allowed in a crossword
referencing a Broadway production
should not be allowed in a crossword.
Well, New York Times.
That's what I mean.
Broadway's in New York.
Here's what we need, boys.
Broadway's everywhere.
We need a crossword that is done by the Daily Wire.
That's what we need.
We need the Daily Wire and the Blaze to do a crossword
because I can get that shit.
OK.
Probably five minutes.
OK, how about this?
New opportunity.
Me and Cam have been talking about this brand new
kind of like news agency type of deal.
We don't have to really get into it too much.
How about we produce our own crosswords?
I'm fine with that.
Yeah.
They're pretty weird to make though.
There's a guy who does the mini crossword.
You know what his name is?
Yes, I do.
He has a very...
Let's just call it... Here, wait, let's spell it.
Hold on.
I think it's John or Gus.
For people who are not
in my team games subscribers. First of all you should be.
Yeah. Okay here's the guy's name. Joel.
That's his first name. Nothing wrong with that. Here's the guy's last name.
F A G
L I A N O. That's a fucking fake name dude.
How? And this guy does almost every single mini.
Yeah. He's done the last eight minis.
I mean come on. Get it together New York Times. I don't understand how that guy
didn't kill himself. Yeah, going through middle school. Well because he probably went to the
kind of schools that groom you to be a crossword editor at the New York Times.
That's true. He probably was never bullied once in his life and it was all pretty easy for him.
Well, he was never bullied by by people at his schools. What about
You don't think Yale graduation or wherever the fuck he went. He's going up on stage
He's getting his diploma and they're like a fag Leono
Fag Leono report fag Leono. I mean that's his name, you know, yeah born 1992. It's an American puzzle creator
Okay, born 1992. He has to know he'll he went to Drexel guys
Yeah, he lives in
So we could go visit him yeah
His hobbies include playing chess and
Basketball watching sports and jogging. I do like I mean, he's cool
Making the minute. I like him. He's easily the best friend. I
Would love to be friends with Joe Joel F my idea
He would be that in my phone by the way, he would be Joel F
He would be I I cannot risk the the the name getting cut off because it's too long
No idea we come and visit him at his party where he plays basketball and we invite him to the show
And we say we know your story. We know what you went through. We want to give you an outlet to express yourself
Okay
Would be here yeah, yeah, he has to drink a beer
Also, I if I had to guess I would say that the fact that he's still on the minis and not doing the maxis is
Do well though no, but it probably has something to do with some kind of prejudice against his name
Because he is Jewish there is anti Jewish
Sentiment I'm gonna say in the New York Times
Joel Fagliano is not Jewish. I just saw it on his Wikipedia. It says he is a Jewish writer
Okay, so you this is one of your boys and you need you have his back. It doesn't say that anyway
Oh my god, it's true. It's true. It's true
Imagine coming through Ellis Island and choosing Fagliano
Because you think that that sounds Italian. Yeah, right
Yeah, you're like trying to hide. I will say he did
Fool me. I thought it was Italian
The fact that you guys would think that we that anybody from Italy would have that as a last name and their bloodline would survive
Really says more about you
Then I'm assuming he like they're like his family just escaped the country
That I could believe if it was like they were the first
Italians to come to America because they were like, "We have to get out of Italy. We are
getting destroyed in Italy," then I could believe that.
I believe that.
He interned with Will Shorts, classic Maxi maker.
That guy is basically the crossword goat, so I might say.
Yeah. Three summers under Will Shorts.
I'm so sorry that you came up against a rebus. That's sad. I have not done a crossword in
a while I've been dabbling in new kinds of hobbies.
Such as?
Such as taking my cousin around New York City.
I've decided this is one of my favorite hobbies and I can't get enough of it.
How's that going?
Well, he just left yesterday so I need another new hobby.
But I do want new hobbies, man.
I did just pick up basketball again.
I've been playing a lot of basketball.
You should pick up reading.
I already read before bed.
What do you read?
Whoa, what's a book you've read?
What's the last book?
I'm not sure, sorry.
Tone was wrong.
Caleb, my fellow intellectual,
what's the last book that you read?
The last book that I read
was
The Haunted by Chuck Palahniuk
and before that
The History of Sexuality
by Michelle Foucault
And before that, the Norm Macdonald book,
and I'm gonna read the Norm Macdonald book again
right now, I think.
(laughing)
Actually, it's either between the Norm,
I'm gonna reread the Norm book,
or I'm gonna reread the Big Book of Basketball
by Bill Simmons, 'cause I love Bill Simmons.
- Yeah, yeah, that's like me, you know,
it's like Finnegan's Wake, Portnoy's Complaint,
Green Eggs and Ham.
(laughing)
I really, I like Bill Simmons a lot.
- You're coming in so hot right now.
- I'm sorry.
- Pull it a little bit.
- I saw a lady today on the, speaking of reading,
I saw a lady today on the subway
who was reading Outliers by Malcolm Gladwell.
And I really, it really, I could not believe
that somebody still read that book.
Like was reading that book publicly for,
you have to assume the first time.
But it really made me feel very embarrassed for this lady
that she was reading Outliers by Malcolm Gladwell.
- It's kind of, I can't wait to performatively read
on the subway.
- Don't, there's, nobody is actually getting
any reading done on the subway.
It's impossible.
Everybody smells like diarrhea.
People are poking you, asking you to buy lemonade.
There's no reason to,
I've never brought a book on the subway.
I never will.
That is the time where you get to look at your phone.
This is built into your life.
You can look at your fucking phone.
I think I understand now why you don't sit down in the bathroom
because you're sitting down to travel.
That's true.
This is insane.
What?
So it's just interesting, Rex.
So you're telling me that when you get in your car, you usually
stand up all the way?
Well, I'm not looking at my phone.
That's for sure.
You don't look at your phone when you drive?
What the fuck?
No, I have GPS up.
I don't know where I'm going.
Oh, I always look at my phone when I drive.
The entire time I'm looking at my phone.
- Hang on, can you explain your theory for me, Rex?
I just want to understand what you were, what you meant.
- He's saying I've developed a distaste for sitting
because I have to do it on the, although I very,
I almost never do it on the subway.
- It's not a distaste, but like, you know,
that's a built-in phone time to his day.
If he's going somewhere, he's sitting on the subway,
he's on his phone.
Whereas me, I'm not going anywhere on the subway.
- He's getting a screen time, okay, yeah.
- He gets a screen time during a sit down.
So on the train, honestly, screen time on the toilet.
Honestly, guys, I never, ever take the train.
I only take the train if I'm going to Manhattan, which is maybe once a month.
And I drive every other place.
I hate the train.
I love the train.
I hate it, man.
I hate that shit.
The other day I was with my cousin.
We were at the World Trade Center and there's a bus that goes
all the way from the World Trade Center directly in front of my house.
And it's like 20 minutes slower than taking the train.
And I just told him that it was faster and we got on it
and rode for an hour and 10 minutes so that we didn't have to get on the train.
That's crazy to me that you would rather take the bus than the train.
It's like a big it's like a Greyhound.
It's like a coach bus.
Whoa.
Yeah, it's got like comfy seats and iPhone chargers and stuff.
It's nice.
You got AC.
Oh yeah.
It's as cold as a fucking ice.
How expensive is that?
Four bucks.
Really? Mm hmm.
Yeah, it's anytime I'm at there's one at Central Park and there's one at the World Trade Center.
Anytime I'm near either of those, I'm not going taking the train and even at rush hour.
There's like nobody on it.
I love those fucking buses.
The QM buses.
Hmm.
Shout out.
Shout out to the QM 25 man.
You trying to find my house?
Look along the route.
All the way from right in front of one of the stops.
Yeah, that's kind of beast.
Yeah.
I just don't like any kind of public transportation.
I just don't.
I also just don't like going anywhere.
I don't like the the fact that the train like today I had to go to Manhattan.
Well, I didn't have to, but I thought I had to.
And I waited for the train for I waited for the M for like 25 minutes.
And the app kept saying it was coming in like two minutes.
And then it just wasn't.
And then I had to walk 15 minutes to another train.
That is bullshit, man.
If this was anywhere but Manhattan, I would have just hopped in the whip and I would have been gone.
Yeah.
Interesting.
I think it's funny that Rex has the idea of like a white girl of what it's like to live in New York.
So I'm like, yeah, I'm going to get on the train.
I'm going to read my little book.
I'm going to go have breakfast with my best friends.
Yeah.
Buddy, your first day in New York City, I am literally making sure you get robbed.
I will do anything to make sure you get robbed.
You're going to be walking around with a messenger bag,
and that shit is going to get swiped off you by a 12 year old.
I will literally be putting a hit on you.
I probably wouldn't even be mad if I got robbed.
I have insurance on my phone.
I don't care. Robbers insurance.
Yes. Robbers insurance. Yeah.
I get it. Why are we not robbing you?
This is the easiest fraud.
- There's no benefit to being robbed.
- There's no benefit to robbing a phone anymore.
- Yeah, they just lock the phone.
- But then you could have two phones.
- Yeah, but it doesn't work anymore.
- It's completely locked.
You can't use it at all in any sorts of way.
- You could use it as a prop in a movie.
- That is true.
- So go ahead and, I don't know, I'm just saying,
if you move to New York and we maybe wanna make a movie,
then we will be robbing you in a fake robbery so that we can use your phone as a prop.
I mean you could just use my normal phone as a prop.
It's too dangerous.
It puts off radiation.
It's the same type of insurance.
That's true.
It puts off a high radiation when you put it near your head or your testicles.
Did you know that?
I didn't know that.
Yeah.
Is that true?
Yeah, your phone puts off radiation.
It's basically why everybody in this fucking world has become such blue haired SJWs because
they've been keeping their phone near their damn nuts.
Yeah, and near their head and it's shrinking their brain and making them
incapable of thinking logically. Yeah, it's taking away critical thinking which is why
the people like, like what happened to Gary Johnson? Nobody talks about him
anymore maybe because people's brains are too small to accept his ideas. I put my
phone next to my butt and I think that's why I get so uncomfortable sitting for
too long. I think that's probably why your butt is
I make sure my wife used to do that and then I have made it a strict rule that
we're not allowed to have a phone in the bed. Why? Because I don't want to
have a developmentally disabled child. It's that simple. I think that's up to
chance no matter what. Wait what's going on? I don't want to have a kid with who has
like an eye on their forehead you know what I mean? So I make sure that the phone...
- Is she pregnant?
- I don't fucking know, you ask her.
- It's none of my business.
- Can you go ask her if she's pregnant right now?
- She's at the park with the dog.
- Can you call her?
- What's getting a little big lately, are you pregnant?
(laughing)
- Asking your wife, saying,
I think we really need to get a pregnancy test
because you are looking straight up like an orca.
You look huge.
- I don't think anything she does pre having a baby matters.
- That is not true.
- Things never leave your body.
- That is true.
- Something will never,
hey, and if you want an example,
hey Julio, you ever heard of something called bubble gum?
It doesn't leave your body for over seven years.
- Okay, wait, so it leaves the body then?
You just said never, and then you just gave me a time frame.
- Say she eats a bubble gum now,
and then in six years and three months,
I conceive into her,
and then we have a bubble gum baby.
- Okay, can I ask you a question?
- No!
- Can you Google what, can you right now
go on Google and type poop?
- Okay, I'm not sure how this is relevant,
but yes, I can type poop.
Okay, now what?
- And search it.
- I searched it, it says dictionary poop,
the after most and highest deck of a ship,
especially if it's a sailing ship,
where it typically forms a roof of a cabin in the stern.
- All right, all right, all right, hang on.
Next step here, click images.
OK, I'm not sure what your point is.
Oh, it's a bunch of pictures of brown ice cream.
Why'd you make me look at this now? I'm hungry.
So I think stuff does leave your body. Hmm.
It's just, oh, wow.
Some of these are completely the worst things I've ever seen.
There's I clicked on one that was in a diaper,
and now I'm getting just pictures of black sludge in diapers.
People asking, is this healthy?
And it's literally like it's like slime from an alien movie
on a diaper.
And they're just like posting that. Yeah.
That's awesome.
He's a close that right now.
On if you search poop on Google, the tabs at the top, you know,
like images, news, videos, you have images, news, videos.
Color is the next one.
I hate that. I hate I hate the the moving buttons on Google.
The thing is so stupid.
We, I don't, luckily I don't use Google.
That's the first time I've used it in over six years.
I'm a duck, duck, go man.
(sighs)
- You can't escape, dude.
Do you have an iPhone? - I don't care about any of that.
- Oh, I can't escape?
Okay, name one thing about my fucking life.
- You are bald.
- But Google doesn't know that.
(laughing)
- Have you never gone to the ad place?
- You know what we should do?
We should look at our Google AdSense profiles.
How do you know how you can see what Google thinks you are?
No.
AdSense profile,
you can you can look at like what Google thinks that you're
you are based on what you kind of stuff that you do.
How do you like for this?
People like for this on the tenure.
Let me see if I can find it.
Rex, what is this hat?
It's from the Lavender Festival.
Oh I see. You completely came in here with a whole new vibe and we've barely even talked about it.
I mean, is the vibe that the camera is off-center?
The camera's off-center, you have a stoner type weed smoker vibe.
You're wearing a hat. You've never worn a hat in your entire life.
My hair...
What is even on the hat?
It's a bear.
Can you get really close to the camera so we can see it?
Okay, go to your Google thing, then go to account, then go to...
That work?
Yeah.
I'm going to my Google thing.
Then go to data and privacy.
Okay.
And then go to...
Hmm.
My ad center?
Let me see.
Make a plan for your digital legacy.
What kind of, what shit is this, man?
This site is insane.
Go to
ad personalization.
Where do you see that?
Yeah, where do you see that?
You know, I don't know.
This is probably a pretty old thing.
Personalize ad, go to my ad center.
OK, so that's where we have a problem because I have my turned off.
All right. Wait. Oh, you have your turned off?
OK, here's what it says about me.
Gender.
male. Interesting. That's a green circle for you Google. Age, don't like this, 25 to 34,
which I was really expecting based on what the kinds of things that I look at that it
was going to say that I was like 14, but no. Languages, two languages. That's right. People
say I have a bi vibe. It's wrong. People always say I have a bi vibe. There it is. Wait, which
I'm
Whoa.
I act like a single motherfucker online.
Household income, moderately high.
Whoa. Okay.
All right, I'll take that. So you should get wrong.
Education, not enough info.
They're saying I'm uneducated.
Industry I work in, technology.
Okay.
Employer size, large employer.
Home ownership, not enough info, and I'm not a parent.
So I would say they got, let's see,
they really only got my age, my gender and my relationship, or no,
I'm not single. Whoa. My gender. And that's it actually.
You're a moderately high income.
No, I'm not.
You live in New York City.
Average or lower income.
Let's see. What is the, what is the median?
The medium income is like $48,000.
Then I'm right there or under.
Let's see. Median American income.
Is your, do you have your Google ads thing?
Oh my God. I'm way less $70,000.
Meet in the national median household income.
Not household household.
Oh yeah. I guess you're right.
That's one earner is in Alabama is $52,000.
$31,000 is the median income.
Okay. Then I'm, I'm above that.
So you're moderately to highly paid.
I mean, this thing is fucking, I mean,
This is getting scary guys.
It's not scary.
Do you have one Rex or no?
I do.
Male 25 to 34 language, English, single, high income, bachelor's
degree, technology, large employer, renter, not a parent.
So that one's almost completely correct.
Yeah.
Everything with the large employer.
I think your employers can, your employer can be considered as large.
A large employer is 250 to 10,000 employees.
Yeah. You ain't that. Yeah.
No, I term, I term right now because I am actually off of the,
I didn't even know I could turn. Actually, I think I was, I have just,
I think it's funny to do this once every couple of years, but you know what?
I'm going to turn it off.
That one's not as fun as having your,
the one that I do like is having Google track everywhere I go. So
Every, at the end of the month,
it'll just send me like a notification like,
oh, this is where you did this month.
It's like, oh, you walked this much.
Oh, you drove this much.
This whole places you went to.
And I think that's a little cool.
- There's so much shit on fucking Google,
the applications.
What the hell is Jamboard?
- I think that's like a music.
- You don't have a jam yet?
Well, let me create one.
What the hell, I can make a jam?
I've always wanted to make a jam.
- I love jamming.
- We've given him too many toys.
the
This sucks.
Sorry, man.
I thought I discovered a new app,
but it basically just sucks like the rest of them.
Yeah.
Google Fi Wireless, that could be interesting.
You know, I actually sucks to--
I still have Google Fi.
Is that when they,
is that the like Google Fiber, is that that?
What is Google Fi?
It's a--
Network.
It's a network.
Oh, it's like a cellular service?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's cheap,
And it uses T-Mobile and Sprint at the same time.
How do they manage this, Rex?
Through some sort of carrier switching mechanism.
I don't believe you.
I think I want to switch to Mint because they have those funny commercials.
With Ryan Reynolds?
Yeah, with Free Guy.
That's what I call him.
Yeah.
And he made like a hundred million dollars from that.
Yeah, they didn't even sell out.
He sold out his entire company.
I think he...
No, he started it.
Yeah, he started it and he sold out.
His thing is to start companies or buy companies then do all the ads for free so that they can like
They have his name open value. Yeah, he did the same thing with aviation and
Then he just sells them and makes him a hundred mil. They did that with George Clooney did that with
Casamigos, I think they made like he made like a half a billion dollars selling Casamigos. Mm-hmm
You know who also is like a billionaire
Ashton Kutcher. Oh, yeah, he's like a like a tech. He's like an angel investor, right? Yeah
What's the best
Bullshit yeah computer. Yeah shark tank stuff, you know, yeah, he's
He's got one, let's see
See if there's anything good one password
Well that seems like a bad idea one password I have one password for
everything and I get hacked all the time. I shouldn't say that. Whatever I don't
care. He invested in that company that made all the celebrities by bored apes
Moonpay. He's a genius. That's funny. Did you guys know that Andy Milonakis is
getting shit on because he he scammed like a million dollars off his NFT thing? I don't
care about any of them to like look up what it was but what happened?
He was basically taking pictures of stuff in his house and making them NFTs.
That's dope, why did he scam them?
Well because he said that there was basically gonna be metaverse incorporation and they were
going to have virtual worlds and none of that happened.
After the initial six months of people buying and selling and being like "oh these NFTs are
gonna do something at some point and then nothing ever happening. I think if you
get scammed on crypto on metaverse or NFT stuff current year and anyway in the
future I think you're a sucker. I think these people were suckers from the
beginning. Yeah you have that kind of money and you spend it on that you are
you either have enough money that it doesn't matter or you're actually a
a fucking idiot. Yeah. All right.
I'll say the people who bought NFTs were seriously fucking morons.
That's very not afraid to say that.
So Spotify, Uber, Shazam, SoundCloud, Airbnb.
Sounds like my damn phone.
Yeah. Yeah.
He bought my phone.
So, yeah, those are just apps on his phone.
What are you saying, Rex?
Everybody has his ass.
That's Ashley Kutcher investments.
Yeah, I'm invested in a lot of stuff.
Me and Rex had a funny Shazam adventure this week.
What did you guys do?
[laughter]
I had one specific line that I knew was a Drake verse,
but I didn't know what song it was from.
And I tried to tell it to Hugo.
It did have a certain word in it, so I'm not going to repeat it.
Uh-huh.
And he didn't know it and then he kept playing me Drake songs and then it turned out to be a legend
You were just thinking I'm a legend
Yeah, but he just thought about he was misremembering like the lyrics in a really funny way
And he was like, I can't find this song. I don't know what the song is. I was trying to help him
I was like, oh, do you should just sing it to Shazam?
And he said it and she was like no, I don't know what that
to me. Well, Shazam did and then it kept going and I was like, that's enough. That's all I have.
Yeah. So basically Shazam is bullshit. Shazam is not bullshit. Shazam is awesome sauce.
What are you looking at? Nothing important.
Okay. Okay. I was looking at big wind board because all this talk about NFTs made me want to gamble.
Oh, let's do it.
Yeah, I'm so down to do it.
Oh, my God.
That's what we need after this long week, guys.
We do need a game session, one for the epic one.
Yeah, we need an epic one.
Maybe we'll even record it.
Who knows?
Probably not.
I was up to Juvia.
I was asked whether GWA was dead last night.
I don't know, would you consider a Phoenix dead?
If it was sitting in a bunch of ash that it had just exploded into?
I guess so.
Don't answer that question because the answer is no.
The Phoenix will rise again and that's exactly what we're about to do by gambling probably
$45.
Okay, let's go.
Alright, let's go.
Let's go.