[Sipping]
[Burping]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer broadcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[Burp]
This is a journey into
[Muffled]
Bud Light.
Ha!
Foo Rippin'!
I know it's hot.
Beers we drank, motherfucker.
With Jubio, Caleb, and Rex.
Beer.
Oh.
Hold on.
Man, whenever I drink a bottle, it never really does a sound.
Oh, it's pink.
I'm trying to choose between--
all right, I'm going to use this one.
OK, I'll go first.
Today--
Okay, well I guess Kayla was going first because he showed the entire beer.
I didn't do that on purpose. I, I, uh,
I have a Heineken. This is brewed in Holland.
It's a Heineken original. It says Diplom
Deannour Amsterdam in 1883.
It's pretty interesting stuff. Not one of my favorite beers, but, um, yeah,
I was pretty last minute.
What do you have?
I got a Prey beer.
That looks like it says "Ray."
It actually is Ray.
But I like to say it says "Prey."
But look, it's my hometown.
It's like one of the stables of the city, the mountains.
It's a locally brewed--
it says that it's a artisanal beer from the North.
Mexican IPA Cerveza.
- Sounds amazing and delicious. - Let's check it out.
- I have... - It tastes weird.
Yeah.
I have meteoroids.
Cheers, my friends.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
It's a slushy beer
that's supposed to taste like watermelon rock candy,
Blue raspberry, black cherry, blueberry, cherry, and pink vanilla cotton candy.
And what does it taste like, actually?
Shit.
Awful.
Yeah, it tastes bad.
It does not taste bad.
It tastes not so good.
Nah, no bueno.
It is crazy to me how these insane beers are supposed to convey all these flavors.
Like, I cannot parse the fact that you're supposed to be drinking like a milkshake beer.
year. I mean it does taste sweet it just it has like a nastiness to it that's overwhelming.
Yeah but it's good. It tastes like someone took like a Jolly Rancher and put it in a
stale like Miller Lite. Here's what we need we are far enough into this I don't know why
the
fifth
ball if you can tell the sweat dripping down my forehead the clear stench of
winning wafting off of my sweaty body yeah but here's what we need we're 17
episodes into this show it is about time that a brewery somewhere in this great
nation decides to sponsor us and send us a bunch of free beers we will positively
We'll probably review any free beer we get.
It's publicity to thousands of people.
Just do it.
I think Bud Light should sponsor us.
They need a comeback.
Except Bud Light!
[Laughter]
No, I like Bud Light.
Do you guys see that Modelo is now the number one beer in the world because of the Bud Light boycott?
You have to really make conservatives pretty pissed for them to choose a Mexican guy's stuff.
Yeah, that is funny how it's like, oh, we hate the trans beer. We're gonna drink a beer from the country that we hate.
Well, I'll tell Gibbs.
The secret is that Mexicans drink a lot of beer.
So they're just a stable customer base.
So it's not that it went up, it's just the bud light went down.
That's a great point, actually.
Yeah.
They spread the market share.
Right.
Now Modelo is on top.
It's not like that market share all went to Modelo.
Probably very little of it did.
Right, it went to Coors Light, it went to Miller Light.
Coors Light and Miller Light both also canceled.
Actually Coors Light, I don't think it is.
Why?
I think Miller Light did a--
Is Miller also Anheuser-Busch?
I mean, Modelo's Anheuser-Busch.
True.
Well, I think like all every beer
pretty much is Anheuser-Busch, honestly.
everything is either Coca-Cola or Pepsi, and even then that's sold by Disney.
They should've... did you see there was that thing that was like, there were like some
people doing a neo-nazi rally outside of Disneyland? They should have done that
outside of Busch Gardens. What were they doing there? 100%. Why? Yeah, why were they doing that outside of...
I don't know. Probably just for fun. Free tickets I guess? You think they got free tickets for doing that?
sure man. Why would they give him free tickets? Well, Walt Disney was not a fan. Oh my god,
I forgot about the problematic history of the Disney Corporation and that's all my ass.
And that's why if you show up to Disney World with a Nazi flag they'll be like, "Come on
right, come right on in." Listen, we don't like it, but it was Walt's last wishes. That
and
like this child actor but I don't remember who it was.
Old Disney cartoons are so funny because it's just blackface.
Yeah ten minutes of somebody riding a car in blackface or something.
Just doing ragtime piano in blackface.
I would say those animators man they had style back then.
Was that Disney?
Wasn't that like mostly Hanna-Barbera like doing crazy racist stuff?
They all do crazy racist stuff.
the
I don't know what the fuck you're talking about so and I'm not gonna learn about it
So I've never been to a picnic so I everything I know about Hannah Barbera's from watching Harvey Birdman
And then just like piecing together the backstory yeah, and also yeah, you tell me there's two men named Hannah and Barbara
No, no no no no
So - that's what it was one guy
You think it was one guy named Hannah Barbera?
Yeah, no, it's two guys that make sense red Hannah and and
Barbara
But I'm pretty sure it's two guys it's like a law firm kind of
Completely one guy named Hannah
the
fact check in before the end of the episode.
yep and you got fucking destroyed and it didn't say anything about racism when I
googled that so. That is true. You also got destroyed on that count. They erased all of those. They have been pretty
spared of the racism accusations I would say. Well that's because they they went
back and they they attach it like a like a screen at the start of those episodes
like it's like hey this is from another time but we're still gonna show it to you
you can you can watch this is when cats and mouse used to fight all the time
warning that's quite a bonus fuck do you guys remember that yeah Tom and Jerry
remember Tom and Jerry yeah it was so bad I do and then that was pretty violent
runner was wanted to the the coyote wanted to kill the Roadrunner so badly
with TNT. That's fucked up.
I mean, that's what kids do nowadays.
Between animals, you know, like there's not, it really wasn't that crazy.
Yeah. But there's 1 billion kids trying to blow up their friends with TNT.
That is true. These days, the road runner would be making
a YouTube short.
Houses out of bricks. Yeah.
And he'd be...
Houses out of bricks.
Wait, what?
The same thing.
Yeah, these days a roadrunner would be painting a road onto a wall.
So these days he'd be ordering gadgets on Amazon.com.
Yep, ordering TNT on Amazon.com.
Amazon Basics TNT.
If they made that show today. Amazon basically is Acme.
Amazon Basics is the Acme of real life.
That's so true.
Yeah, that's one of my more astute points.
I think that these days, they would probably do the Roadrunner killing the coyote.
What?
It's closed because everything's gone.
Everything's fucking topsy-turvy upside down. We live in a reverse world.
It's every day is opposite day in this bullshit country.
The Roadrunner...
That's the original plot anyway.
Well no, the roadrunner would be trying to eat the coyote!
Is what they would do. They'd be usurping the natural order.
I see.
Yeah, the roadrunner would be trying to shatter the glass ceiling and get a job above the coyote.
Exactly. And then he would fire the coyote for Instagram videos he made 8 years ago.
It's really not that big of a deal. This fuck is a different time, 2015.
He would've taken a picture of the coyote after a TNT exploded in his face,
Charring his skull black. Yep. Uncovered it and gotten him fired from human resources.
It would have been over. It's just no question. That'd be funny if the coyote, they never show what the coyote does with the rest of his time.
Also, is this the only motherfucking roadrunner in the entire fucking desert?
There's gotta be other roadrunners. Is there other coyotes? That's a pack animal.
the
I
I think that's the first Riz sighting on national television.
That was the first time we had Riz on national TV?
Yeah.
Speaking of, they should put that show on Nat Geo.
That show should be on the Discovery Channel, Nat Geo.
Tom and Jerry?
Yes, it's an animal kingdom.
Animal planet? What's that, the Hanna-Barbera extended universe?
Yeah, wasn't that the planet all the cartoons take place on?
Animal planet, where animals walk around, they talk to each other, they can buy things?
I mean, this is how crazy things are these days.
That they think there should be an animal planet. These days, that wouldn't even be a TV channel.
That would be a planet.
They would make that into a real planet. They would turn the moon into an animal planet.
And probably, you know who would live there?
Who?
Vegans. Probably.
the
in space because there's no air.
Exactly, there would be no mylar reaction.
Exactly.
You couldn't even crack an egg because it would float off the surface of the moon and
fly into space.
It would be complete bullshit trying to eat any kind of meat in space.
Did you guys ever have astronaut ice cream?
No.
Well, that's just Dippin' Dots, right?
I've had Dippin' Dots. Dippin' Dots are so good. They're so yummy.
I love Dippin' Dots. The Banana Split Dippin' Dots for me is the best dessert you can have.
You know, it's really funny. During the 90s, like early 2000s, a lot of US businesses came down to Mexico.
And they were like, "Hey, we're going to make a dessert. We're going to make a dessert."
And they were like, "Oh, we're going to make a dessert."
A lot of like US businesses like came down to Mexico,
like Whataburger, I think we had Taco Bell at some point.
- Did you say Whataburger?
- Whataburger.
- Oh, I got excited.
- A burger made of water?
- That is a Whataburger.
- I just wanted to know what it was.
I didn't even have an idea.
- There is a Whataburger.
- That's how they get Americans to say hi to you.
- I'll get to that.
And we used to have like all that cool shit,
but everything like went away.
So we don't have Whataburger, we don't have Taco Bell,
we don't have Dippin' Dots anymore.
and I miss it so much.
We don't have Mountain Dew.
It completely got kicked out of the country.
- That's some bullshit.
Why did they leave?
Did you chase them out?
- I think it's a health thing.
- Really?
- You just cannot buy Mountain Dew in Mexico at all.
- You can buy fucking Takis.
- And Coke.
- Takis are the most disgustingly--
- Not the OXO.
- Excess of sodio, the snack that you can fucking buy.
- Yeah, but it's from the little,
the little, uh, you know, well this one doesn't have it.
The little labels, you know, that says excess of sodium. Yeah.
So you know that you're doing a bad thing. That is true.
I wouldn't say it's bad.
There's no evidence that sodium is bad for you. Yeah.
Except for that one song on 808s and a heartbreak where
Jeezy says he's going to watch his sodium.
That's the only time I've ever heard of it.
Please show the scientific evidence that sodium is bad for your heart.
Excesso sodio.
Yeah, I don't know where they got that from.
I will say that a couple weeks ago I had a giant hoagie.
And then I went to the gym and I had about a three minute heart palpitation and I had
to be talked out of calling 911.
So I think that, and I think sodium was, I think I had excesso sodio that day.
I think I feel like you get yourself into a lot of situate a lot of times you go to the gym and you have like some sort of
Like I think something is wrong
It is so when you're working out and you just feel like you actually might die
Yeah, that's what I mean. It was it was doing bent over rows. I think I it wasn't actually a heart palpitation
I think I'm 100% sure it was a
esophageal spasm, but they're very hard to tell the difference because they're,
God placed them right next to each other because it was perfect image. Yeah.
I love having a like heartburn and stuff like that. Or just,
just any of the thing,
well just any of the things that make you feel like you're having a heart attack
but aren't, I'm so good at ignoring those now.
They don't even faze me anymore.
Anything with the esophagus feels like you're like dying and like exploding.
Yeah. It feels like you don't. There's like lava inside of you.
It's fucking crazy.
There's so many terrible things about our bodies.
Are you familiar with the vagus nerve?
No.
The vagus nerve is a nerve that goes down the back of your head, past your heart, and into
your leg, I think.
And if it gets pinched or poked at any point along that route, you just get a massive heart
palpitation and heart pain.
or you think it feels like you're having a heart attack, like an actual heart attack,
because it goes like right next to your heart.
And that's like the thickest point of the nerve or some shit.
So it's just concentrated there.
It's a very bad.
Our bodies were poorly designed.
Yeah, it's funny when that stuff like that happens,
like when you lock your knees too long and you just like faint.
Yeah, I've never fainted.
You've never fainted?
Have you ever known anybody who just I mean,
I know plenty of people who have this, who just have had a seizure for no apparent medical
reason.
Have you had one?
Yes.
You had a seizure?
You both had one?
No, I didn't have one.
I know someone who has seizures.
Rex, have you had a seizure?
Oh yeah, it wasn't for no reason though.
What happened?
What did it feel like?
Terrible.
And then I woke up on the ground.
It happened twice, really.
I just woke up on the ground both times.
But it wasn't for no reason?
What happened?
Well, the second time I woke up, I was in the bathroom, and I was like, "Oh, I'm going to
have a seizure."
And then I woke up and I was like, "Oh, I'm going to have a seizure."
But it wasn't for no reason? What happened?
Uh, well the second time was because I was on a bunch of shit.
Uh huh.
But the first time I was just like 12.
Just something came over me and I went to the bathroom to like throw up.
And then I woke up and my... I was like leaned over like the toilet like praying position.
And uh, I hit my face on the toilet and my...
EWWWW!
My teeth went through my lip.
Ew, you put your face on the toilet?
Look at me! Look at that!
You can see it, you can still hear it. That's disgusting.
Yeah, so it's fine. Did it feel
cool, like, not cool, did it feel
intriguing? So the one when I was 12, because I woke up on the ground
It was intriguing because I thought I was like on a train because like
everything was like shaking like my whole body was like yeah shaking and
weird so I was like oh I've been transported to the 1840s and I am on a
train now. That is crazy that that's your first thought when you're 12 years old.
I read a lot of books. Very imaginative kid yeah a lot of a lot of magic treehouse.
So when I was in my 20s, I was just like, oh, I died.
Yeah, I died and came back to life.
Yeah, but whenever somebody I feel like I see every once in a while, somebody
posts on Instagram like, hey, y'all like doing this in a hospital bed.
Yeah.
Hey, y'all, just so you know, I had a seizure last night at 9.
32 p.m.
Doctors say it was nothing.
It's like what what are these doctors talking about if they're somebody's coming in they're like I had a seizure
Somebody had to put a sponge in my mouth, so I wouldn't bite my tongue off. I was drooling white foam and
They're like it's probably nothing. Yeah, it is just nothing
That is just kind of like a like a spur-of-the-moment kind of thing yeah, but why would your body do that?
That's fine. I have a spasm that I've given myself from vaping too much. I'm pretty sure what's a spasm like like
I just have like a twitch that happens sometimes when I'm like my like leg will just kick can we see it?
Well, it doesn't it's involuntary
Going right now. Let's see it. No, I know I have it's when I'm tired
Make yourself tired. I don't care
Just kick your loader, just fake it, I don't care.
- Run it around.
(laughing)
- Run it around for a couple minutes to get really tired.
And then do it.
- I'll think about it.
- I've never had a serious medical thing.
Well, I guess when I was a kid, I had my tonsils out
and then the sutures split open.
And I started like, I was just sitting
on my grandma's bed watching TV.
And I was like, oh, I have like a,
like a loogie in my throat.
And I like spit into my hand.
- It was all blood.
- And it was just a giant chunk of blood.
And then I went, ah!
And I ran into the bathroom.
And my grandpa thought that I was going to die,
but he didn't have like an ice pack.
He was like thinking that if he put ice on it,
it would for some reason like stop the bleeding.
So he grabbed like a, he had like a ribeye.
You got hit by a baseball.
Yeah, that's what he's thinking.
So he had it, but he grabbed a ribeye, a frozen, like a ribeye that he had
in the freezer, and he just put like cold meat on my neck.
And I, yeah, I put a gallon of blood.
And then he told me later, he was like, I was fully convinced
you were going to die, which makes it way worse.
That when we we called an ambulance, an ambulance got there
and he was like and they were like, all right, we'll take him to hospital.
he needs emergency surgery. And my grandpa was like, all right,
but how much does the ambulance cost? And they were like $600. Like, nah,
it's okay.
They didn't even have a car at the time. My grandparents didn't have a car.
So he had to call my mom who was an hour away to drive into town and pick me up
and take me to the hospital.
So it took like basically two hours to get me there.
How do you see the thing?
How do I split it?
I don't know.
Both of them split though and I just had like a hemorrhage.
Just yawn really hard?
Yeah, and then I, it was a nightmare dude.
I went, I had my surgery and then I woke up and it was so painful, so much more painful
than the actual tonsil surgery for some reason.
I woke up in like the worst pain, I was completely delirious.
I passed out from the time that the EMTs got there and I was just asleep until the next
day, basically, when my surgery was done.
And I woke up and my friend's mom was a nurse and she was my nurse.
And so I fully thought that I was dead.
Like because I was like, this is like someone I know.
This doesn't make any sense.
Yeah.
Bright white lights, white room.
My friend Jordan's mom being like, it's going to be okay.
I was like, oh yeah, I'm dead.
I've gone to the other world.
Did you not know she was a nurse beforehand?
Honestly, my first thought was like wow me and Jordan's mom died at the same time. That is so crazy
I mean, I guess I I
Never really thought of the fact that she was a nurse
What do you think happened to her how did she die?
Car I thought that she died in it. I mean I was pretty you know, this was like
Bush years, so I thought that she died an Islamic terrorist attack
And I wouldn't say it, you know, I wouldn't think that now but at the time I was a bit conservative for a ten-year-old
Yeah, I thought I mean it's unfortunate. Yeah nowadays I would have thought that she got lynched by a mega
And you know racist that's what I would have thought. I really would have because she had red hair
You know, so I would have done it was some kind of racial motivation for the death
But you're not a very good ten-year-old because obviously she would never have gone to heaven and she does not have a soul
Copper cab be damned. I really I
She was a nice lady
We thought that over in there's not having a soul part. Yeah
Well, I think it was actually a fake redhead. She had that she had that box box hair. Mm-hmm
She had boxed hair.
She had that boxed dye hair.
Yeah, she was kind of a thought now that I think about it.
But she married a guy who could do that thing with his chest where it goes like boop boop
boop boop boop boop boop boop boop boop.
You know that thing?
No.
That's a thought behavior.
Yeah, you know that thing that old white guys do?
Well, you wouldn't know an old white guy.
But old white guys, they have big boobs on their bodies.
And when you say like, man, you have giant tits when you're a kid because you're a very
the
fifth
short. That's about it. And he could do that thing with his boobs. I remember just shit
that you do things that I would say to my friend's parents. I mean, I just like, I think I, I
think I settled down when I got a little older, but when I was like parents from the time
my parents got divorced until like the end of eighth grade, when I would go to somebody's
parents house, I would just, I was so rude, dude. Yeah. It is fun being like a rude kid.
I think that's a prerequisite to be a podcaster.
No, I've always been deathly afraid of being rude to people, especially my friends' parents.
You're the rudest guy I know.
How am I rude?
I've never once been rude to anyone in the world.
For starters, you just raised your voice at me.
That's not even true.
You literally did, and I'm afraid of you.
You have an insensitive mustache.
Please don't do it again.
No.
That's not true.
You have an insensitive right wing Nazi mustache.
I'm very cordial.
Things about you.
I'm cordial. I'm nice.
You drink a lot of cordial and then you hit everyone around here.
Like I'm spitting.
Admit it. Admit it right now on the podcast.
You abuse your girlfriend.
Say it. Say you hit her.
I hit her every day.
Oh, well, whatever I tried.
I love learning lore about more Rex I think because I've heard a lot about you.
You're always just around, I've known you since you were a child saying rude things to your friends' parents.
But I never knew about Rex just falling into a toilet and dying and then waking up.
Oh don't even remind me.
Yeah falling into a toilet and being like, "This is a portal to a fucking train!"
A steam locomotive!
the
It's funny. It's a funny thing.
It is funny.
I bet you liked the toilet. I bet you woke up and then you licked it for a couple minutes.
And then you said, "Mom, Mom."
I think I did like moan a little bit.
He had his toilet in the bowl.
Or his head in the bowl.
He had his head in the bowl.
And he said, "Ugh."
And his head in the bowl.
(laughing)
- You're nasty.
- Shit happens.
In the toilet bowl. - Speaking of nasty,
this beer, I hate this beer.
- You know, I'm not the biggest fan
of this Heineken, neither.
- This is giving me heartburn.
- We should all get the same beer next week.
- Bud Light.
We need to have a Bud Light episode.
- Speaking of Bud Light, I had a,
well, you know, I'm just gonna,
I'm gonna give up on this Heineken.
I'm only like halfway through.
But I'm gonna give up on it.
and I'm gonna grab this other one.
I think I've had this on the show before.
There's a Bud Light lime.
- Ooh.
- This is one of my favorite beers on planet Earth.
- These are huge cans. - But I got it.
Yeah, that's why I'm only drinking half of it.
I got it because I got a six,
I was out of town the past couple of days,
and I got a six pack of Bud Light Orange
while I was upstate.
That is an amazing, amazing beer.
And I recommend anybody who listens to this
to try Bud Light Orange.
Very good stuff.
It's almost as good as Bud Light Lime,
but it's a little too sweet for me.
So I'm gonna have a sip of this.
- Is it orange flavored?
- It's brewed with orange peel.
- Oh. - Like a blue moon.
You know what's a really good Bud Light drink?
- What? - A Lime-A-Rita.
You know, I keep seeing these in the, uh,
in the grocery store when I buy beers for this show,
but I think I'm just not ready to buy like a drink,
like a 600 calorie, eight ABV drink like that.
Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, it's like a, it's just a very, it's like a very,
very sugary sweet thing.
I used to drink a bunch of them when I turned like 21,
I would go to the gas station and get two for $5.
Yeah, it's like a Mike's Hard kind of thing where you're like, you only drink it if you're
like young.
Yeah.
Do you guys have any recollection of like any Mexican beers in like way in the past?
Like there's...
Mexican beers in the past.
I was talking about this with my girlfriend the other day.
There's this like beer called Sol, the Sun Beer, I guess.
That always like all their marketing was like, it's like the world's, you know, it's world
famous Mexican beer it's fucking everywhere and I was like thinking
about it the other day and I was like oh that's if I feel like I haven't seen
that there'd be like anywhere like at all but the only way the only way to like
get it now like obviously I think it's just getting like like like a mixed
drink like a Clamato type deal.
Oh, yeah.
Why do you guys like those so much?
The Chiladas.
They do love the Chiladas.
My godfather growing up, he would always, we would always go
through this like drive-thru convenience, like beer liquor
store thing and would always get like Clamato stuff and I just
I never understood what like why only he liked it, but it's
like so popular now.
And I don't like it at all.
They're insanely popular.
You know what it is?
Mixing it into the big cup is fun.
When I was in,
when I lived in LA I did that a couple of times.
But the, uh, it's not a good,
it's not a good drink, man.
It really is not good.
Tomato juice is nasty. It's horrible.
And I love tomatoes.
I'm a huge fan of a tomato.
I'll eat a tomato sandwich even.
But a tomato juice...
I eat tomato sandwiches all the time. Are you crazy?
That's not true.
Are you crazy?
Big slice-
This is a southern thing, you guys must not understand this.
Two big slices of tomato, salt and pepper, mayonnaise and lettuce on white bread.
It's an ama- It's like the best sandwich you can have.
That's half a sandwich. You're missing the meat.
They're good. It's just a BLT without the-
What about a cucumber?
The best part of a BLT is the tomatoes.
It's a B.
No, the bee is an afterthought.
No, that is not true.
You put the word "bee" in a bee.
The bee gets a taste.
It's the one that comes first.
It's basically just salt. That's what I'm saying.
You salt the tomatoes,
and you put mayo on it. It's a tomato and mayo sandwich.
So this is a
household who didn't have money for
a bee as a speed.
No, everybody in the South eats a tomato sandwich.
Yeah, everyone in the South cannot afford
a bee as speed.
the
Like which one live oak bank PNC Bank. Are you guys even listening? I
Think I don't think PNC is southern
Well, we had it in the South Rex
Don't got chase down there. Let's open an account. We actually basically don't have chase. I
Don't believe you that's there's no way that's true
Bank of America
the
into bank mergers. I think of Chase as a person. I don't think I even knew what Chase was until
I moved up to Boston. But that's probably more on me. I'm a Bank of America man through and
through. I love them. I think it's funny what Chase is doing to Rex. I love hearing about
it every year. Oh yeah. It just won't change. They think you make five bucks. It's like
worst credit curse than me, which is really funny. Explain what is the problem. Cause
I spend a lot of money. It's specifically only a problem when I go to New York because
I pay for everything.
- Okay, okay.
You need to explain the problem on the podcast
for people to listen to the stories.
- Sure.
So, this started like the first time we went to New York
because I had a child's credit limit
and like within like three days.
- What was the limit, do you know?
- I think it might have been like $3,000.
- Oh, that's actually, that's not low.
I don't think of that as a low credit limit.
- I thought it was lower than that.
It was like 2500.
It could have been 2500 actually.
2500 sounds right.
So it's 2500 and then you know,
I put like a week-long Airbnb on it.
I put like, you know, meals for everyone on it.
Just, you know, just instantly filled it up, paid it off and like filled it up again.
So I called them.
I was like, hey, can you do like a, you know, like an inquiry, give my credit up?
And you're like, Oh, Mr. Blank, we're going to help you.
Yes.
And he called the Tokyo offices.
Yeah.
They were bowing to me over the phone.
And anyway, they were like, yeah, no, you know, he can't do anything.
I was like, come on.
They dropped the accent for that part.
Yeah.
I dropped the accent for it because I realized I was being racist on the podcast.
Yeah, yeah, that's okay.
He does it so often.
When we were talking to Annie, he was like
I don't know what we were talking about, he was just like doing the accent
and he realizes that Annie's there
in the call and he's like, "Oh, sorry, I'm sorry, Annie."
And he's like,
goes back to the story and says the accent again.
He's like, "Dude, what are you doing?"
You know what I'm realizing is that
you think of me as
basically also Asian because
I've never heard you do that voice before
and I guess you do it so much.
I only do it in a specific context.
He does it every night.
Which is to be racist.
I don't even...
In my heart, in my true heart of hearts...
It's totally different to him.
It just sounds like English.
Well it is English.
The lady was speaking English.
Yeah.
And then I try to do the same thing the next time I was in New York.
time I was in New York and you're like still just now I call them like three
times a month or like three times a year to be like, Hey, can you increase my
credit limits since I'm like maxing on my credit card every month?
You're like, no, can't do anything.
And then you have to like reach out to them and they don't, because I get, I
guess it's like a having no money type of thing, but I always get like emails
on the calls of people like wanting to like give me credit cards and like get
all my money. Yeah yeah I'm basically pre-approved for four or five cards
right now so watch out. Yeah but uh I did call them like a couple months ago got a
very nice Indian man I was super polite to him. And what did he sound like? Okay he goes
hello mr. blank yes so anyway he just was very we were very nice to each other
he's like let me take care of that for you I call myself it was Mario
Mario
Excuse me guys
he's like so anyway I just lied about how much money I'm making he up my card
wait Wow that's every time I know I make a million bucks a year that's basically
what I said I'm six feet tall I brush my teeth
very well mr. Pitts you're a pre-approved for a house like that the other day
never brushing my teeth but that I'm a pre-approved for a loan for a house
I think I'm gonna buy a house tomorrow.
You should definitely buy a house, that'd be so sick.
Everybody in my hometown is doing so well and they're all buying houses.
Everybody I know in New York is a fucking loser renting at like 40 years old.
Yeah.
Well I don't think it's affordable to buy a house in New York.
Whereas it's probably like-
You can buy a house in like Queens for you know, $350,000.
Can you?
Oh yeah.
I think I'm gonna...
I'm gonna buy it.
Oh, really?
Yeah, I did...
I did...
I did look at like
houses in Queens, and there was one that
just literally was just like a picture
of like a disaster.
It literally...
Like it was like...
Yeah.
Yeah, it was just like waving literally. Yes. I was like does someone even live here?
No, I
Have looked in Ridgewood at like some houses and stuff. Just when I I mean I look all the time
Just when I'm like curious and they're always
There the thing is they're very big. They're like five bedrooms, but they're always like 1.3 million dollars
Yeah, it's like I live like far out
Looking like silo and look random towns like for like their houses like it kills me
But that's a really ugly one, yeah
I'm gonna get a really nice house, but you got to live far out
Yeah, if you live it if you're willing to live which I am also I looked at a house
Like a year and a half ago. That was like I really don't want to
like if I if I could buy like a lot for
$10,000 and put like a trailer on it. Then I would I would spend four months of the year and
I looked at North Carolina and it was like a house in the mountains and like you look at the it has like a view
It's like on a mountain
View into the valley, most beautiful thing you've ever seen in your life, three bedroom
house, $89,000.
Wow.
It's just, it's, I live in the worst place in the world.
I think I'm gonna, if I do buy a house, I think I would like to buy a house like in
somewhere in the Mexican beach, like somewhere in the south.
Puerto Escondido.
Uh, maybe not there, I think that's expensive.
But maybe somewhere else.
It's the only place I know of.
I mean, there's hella beaches all over.
Probably not very good though.
I don't know, I saw one the other day that's like 200,000...
No, like houses, houses like a really nice vacation house.
Like in some random beach and it's like beautiful.
So I think there'll be my retirement plan.
I'll buy a house on the beach.
You'd be so good at being retired.
No, I think so. No, I wouldn't.
That means we need to juice your streaming career. You need to start streaming in Spanish.
You would be the biggest Spanish streamer in the world.
No, I don't want that. I don't like that. I don't like being on-camera talent.
What are you doing?
What?
You're a mogul.
I'm not a mogul.
You have your hands in many different on-camera...
No, no, no, no.
- See, he's waving away, oh, cover the kid.
- No, that's not true.
That's not true. - Don't even look at me.
- I think you're one of the 10 greatest streamers alive.
- I would agree with that.
- You cannot name more than five streamers.
- That's not true, I'll name 10 right now.
- Okay.
- Taric.
- Yep.
- Okay.
- Mm-hmm.
- Shroud.
- Yep. - Okay.
- Sinatra.
- Who's that, Sinatra?
(laughing)
Who's that among us fella?
Disguised Toast.
Okay.
Mizkif.
Oh, now you're getting scared. You're shaking your boots.
Ludwig.
Uh-huh.
His girlfriend.
What's her name?
Pokimane.
Crazy, awesome chick.
[Laughter]
No, I don't know. Cutie Cinderella.
Okay.
Aiden Ross.
Yup.
Kai Sinat.
Oh my god.
TrainwrecksTV.
There's 10 for you.
Top 10.
There's, that's my top 10 dead or alive.
I think we could have Aiden Ross on this show.
I think he would like it.
No shot.
He would love it so much.
We would have a better chance of getting Donald Trump on this show than Aiden Ross.
Definitely.
I honestly feel like watching that kid and watching a lot of those people that we need
to return to like 1920s fatty arm buckle Hollywood.
Like these people should not be famous.
These are some of the least talented people in the world I think.
We need like, I don't know, we need people who can swallow their own hands and shit.
I think there is something charming about someone that's just that like dumb and just
confident about it because I saw someone describe like what they look for in a
streamer and it was just like, you know,
cause they were talking about XQC who's like really,
like 11. Yeah.
And it was like, you know, like I love like,
it's like watching like videos with my brother.
And so everyone just has a retarded brother that they want to hang out with,
but can't. And that's what's true.
I cannot make it big because I'm just not like that intellectual.
I'm too intellectual. I always talk about the current events in the news and like
Donald Trump Donald like politics and economics
There is simply no way anyone can make it in twitch talking about the news and politics
I think that you could be a massive, I think that you, I think that we need to wait until
a game comes out that is, that you, that you are going to make popular.
I think that that would be big for you.
That is going to be the long drive and that's going to go down tomorrow.
I'm going to become the biggest streamer of all time.
a
the
chips are sweet and hot jacks, Jack links, beef jerky.
Sure.
And I like a protein shake.
OK, and I like a.
That's some kind of trail mix, I'll go with the trail mix every time.
I love trail mix.
Well, one of the like healthy ones with sunflower seeds.
I don't like them in.
Because I got enough of them in the car already.
turn that out
That's beautiful man, that's usually that's my road trip load out
I like what is your road trip loaded goldfish? I like goldfish. I like gatorade
I like I love gatorade
I like uh, yep beef jerky excellent road trip snack
I'll take a cheese it in a pinch
I like those cheese and peanut butter sandwiches, the cracker sandwiches.
Yeah, those are good.
I've survived off of the peanut butter sandwich.
Me too.
When I was vegan, that was...
That's a meal.
And you can eat the...
And they're like 25 cents.
Yeah, and they're dense too.
I just realized you are both ex-vegans.
Well, he's ex-vegetarian. He was a half-slaver.
You guys both leveled up.
I think it's a serious level down for me.
Yeah, for sure.
You think so?
Yeah, I think that my moral core has rotted black ever since I stopped or started eating meat.
Yeah.
Now you're enjoying too many chicken sandwiches and it's bad for you.
Well, sometimes I will eat chicken thighs, specifically.
I will be like, I just ate three chickens worth of like three chickens have died for this.
This is just not right.
Well, they were born for this.
They were born to serve.
I were all born to serve in this fucked up world, man, but they do not need to be executed.
This is a really, really yummy.
What if they were so yummy?
Here's my solution.
to the meat problem?
and
the
Around they're gonna peck old ladies. They're gonna
Probably rob somebody they're gonna do some bad bad thing. Okay, once they make that mistake
Yeah, so you you like
Yeah
chicken system
I'm down with killing chickens because I'm pro-death
But I think that they should have a chance to fuck up and listen
I'm gonna be doing fucking 1980s CIA shit, handing out drugs and all that shit.
Like I'm gonna try to make these chickens commit the crime.
But unless you commit the crime, you should not do the time on my dinner plate.
Well, how do you know that the chickens that are already dead have not been already prescribed to be, you know...
That they thought about doing evil deeds such as those?
I mean, they already thought about it.
Yeah, but they gotta have the chance to actually commit some of these horrible atrocities.
Yeah, but what I'm saying is, what if that were already happened in the past and that's why we have the system that we have today?
Well, I think that would have probably heard about that.
If chickens somehow grew facial hair and somehow had his particular facial hair, then we sentence it to death for having sensitive mustache.
sensitive chicken hitler but if we had to it would be one of the most expensive
possible meals that Dave's hot chicken yeah
well you know the Hitler's biggest crime was opening a chicken restaurant himself
yeah yeah bastard going down to McDonald's to get the the Hitler shake
with the Hitler meal? I don't want the Hitler meal. I don't need Hitler meal.
Can I get a McHitler for McHitler's birthday?
No, I don't want any... His name isn't McHitler.
You would say Hitler's birthday, not McHitler's birthday.
He would be offended by that because you're calling him Irish.
Yeah. Did you get the grimace shake?
No.
Dude, the funniest thing I got this past week was
I was just mining with business and I just get a random text from Rex
Thanks from Rex that says give me a shake on me farting and it just
Grimace shake me farting. What was it like?
Tasted I think it's like birthday. I think it made you completely purple. You look like grimace right now
You got completely grimaced grimaced on
It was a good shake the issue was they make you buy like a Big Mac to get it
Oh, and I hate a DMV a big Mac
Whatever
You're crazy for that
Now, in comparison to a McDouble,
- The McMac is one of my 10 sacred sandwiches.
- In comparison to a McDouble?
- 10 sacred sandwiches?
- In comparison to a hot and spicy McChicken?
It's not even a top 10 sandwich at McDonald's.
- That's, no, okay, I dare you.
Okay, speaking of naming 10 things,
I dare you to name 10 McDonald's items
better than the McMac.
- Okay.
- I might give you the McDouble,
but the Mac sauce is just, it's too good.
- Hot and spicy McChicken.
- I do like that.
Yup. And the McDouble. So that's two.
Start at three.
Junior Bacon Cheeseburger.
I think you've already lost one.
I think I would already rather have a Big Mac.
A McWrap.
*Screams*
The breakfast wrap?
You're not telling me a McSalad is better than a Big Mac. This is bullshit.
This is not real.
Okay, the particular Big Mac that I got was awful.
I'll accept that. That's fine by me.
But I will say that McDonald's has better breakfast than their lunch or their supper.
Oh for sure. McRiddles is the best meal ever invented.
and
Dave's Double at Wendy's.
The In-N-Out 2x2.
The Five Guys Normal Burger, no cheese.
The Subway Tuna Sandwich.
The Subway BMT.
The Popeye's chicken sandwich, the Chick-fil-A chicken sandwich, Supreme, the Chick-fil-A
breakfast sandwich, the spicy filet, and to wrap it all up...
My grandma, when I was a kid, she used to make that sandwich and it was just sugar and
butter, so I'm gonna put that as number 10.
So funny enough, no mention of the famed southern tomato sandwich on this list.
Oh, you want me to go 20 do you?
No I don't want you to go 20.
Oh that's a top 20 sandwich.
No don't go 20.
It's number 12.
It has been for 8 years.
Don't go 20.
You cannot have 10 other sandwiches that are not the tomato sandwich.
Oh I can't go 21 but I can do the tomato sandwich.
Have you ever been to a Whataburger?
the
ourselves enough to pay rent and then we'll just like pay for shit on the tour.
I went to Whataburger and I tried to pay with the company card and then I had to
spend 30 minutes on the phone with a lady explaining them to them that we were
traveling and that's why it wasn't like some Bonnie and Clyde stole our card and
was driving across the country conveniently stopping at every venue.
buying enough Whataburger for about three to four people yeah yeah yeah also a
a white castle is amazing I love white castle but that's a slider that's not a
sandwich and I think a Culver's is insanely good that's an amazing amazing
hamburger I think a lot of burger chicken strip sandwich I think of all
I've had Chick-fil-A a couple times. I don't think you were there for the first time I had Chick-fil-A.
Yeah, it was this big thing. We went to the Chick-fil-A in Manhattan.
Was it? Yeah.
Okay, maybe you're right. And you loved it.
I do like Chick-fil-A. And we hated standing up because there was nowhere to sit.
Yeah, it was during COVID.
I think it was the first time I had Chick-fil-A.
Yeah, it was during COVID, I guess.
Yeah, I don't know.
I think I've only been to like Chick-fil-A, Five Guys, In-N-Out, Whataburger, and like Popeyes.
And like every time someone else like talks about...
Yeah, Subway, of course.
But like every time like someone talks about like their local, like, "Oh, this sandwich is so good."
I just don't have that experience.
Also, I have to give a shout out to PT's Burgers and Fries in North Carolina.
PT's, keep doing your thing. The 8-ounce is amazing.
You know what's a good sandwich?
What?
The Crypto Monkey NFT sandwich.
I can't believe I've never been.
You've never been? It's so good.
I know. Both of you have said it's amazing.
Did you say Bun B is an investor or something?
Yeah, yeah. No, that's real.
That's so awesome.
Trillburgers. Or Bun B, do they supply the meat or some shit?
Yeah, so it's like, Bun B does the food for it.
Oh, okay.
Or it's like the partner company.
And I remember I went there one time before going to the airport,
and they were filming a Bun B video there.
I was just awkwardly waiting for a burger to the side while like
20 people...
You saw Bun B?
Yeah.
That's cool.
He's playing a song. He's a rapper.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
And his brother basically died, so...
Oh, rest in peace, Joe B.
His name is actually Pimp C, but nice try.
Sorry.
Yeah, so I bet you can't now I don't because I don't have any concept of what any of this is because I'm from a
different country
You were both love Mexico so much and I will convince you to move here the first time you go if you come here
the
that's
just
the
touching the ball.
That's right.
Arms crossed, top of the key.
You go over there, you sit in the corner, set a screen for him, somebody dive.
I've got a whiteboard that I'm pulling out of my...
It's 4v5, some guys are just sitting there kind of guarding you, just hands up like a
mime.
Yeah, I'm like, don't even waste your time.
I control the flow, dude.
It's not coming here.