I hit play.
Wait, I'm into the next level.
Nope. I'm floating dragon. Yeah, stop that man. Yes, we gotta record now.
Trying to make art here man. You're fucking it up.
[record scratch]
[music]
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[burp]
[music]
I'm a Heineken, Bud Light, Ha!
Foo Riven!
I don't die.
Beers we drank, motherfucker.
With Juvio, Caleb, and Rex.
Beer.
Welcome back!
Welcome back, y'all.
And hello to all of my beautiful Gophers, guys.
It's Gopher October.
In November.
Gopher remember-member.
Gopher remember.
And what do we have today, guys?
Well, I'll start because I'm the Gopher.
We have...
We have Gopher remember.
I like that write that down. We have a Heineken 0.0 actually let me try that again.
Oh guys yeah sober, sober gopher November is over man. Yeah that's right I got a Heineken.
Yeah Heineken 0.0 I fooled you.
But if it's like 0.09 how pissed would you be?
Don't be insane if they're just lying about there not being any alcohol in it.
I think that it's...
Oh, this says alcohol free. I don't know how that's...
Every other non-alcoholic beer I've gotten says that it's .5% or lower.
I don't know how this one, they got it to actually be zero.
But, listen, even one drop of alcohol is horrific poison for your body that will destroy you slowly.
Mentally and spiritually.
That is true.
I'm gonna give this a sip.
Well, rather, I just did.
And, guys, this is one of the best non-alcoholic beers.
beers i'm going crazy today i think this is one of the best non-alcoholic beers in the world let
me tell you why i'm going crazy guys oh real quick before you get to your beers last night
last night i was fully a gopher gofering around we went to a new jazz bar that came up right down
the street for right in my neighborhood brand new and uh it was so delightful it's called da da
And what are the crossroads? 60th and Myrtle Avenue. Okay. Da-da. They have live jazz. I went with my
wife, Noah, and his girlfriend. My wife. We got a charcuterie board and I was thinking, "Man,
I'm gonna eat the charcuterie board." Little did I know Noah wanted to give me a cocktail and he
ordered me a black Manhattan and I lost my gopher status for one hour and it made me feel so sick
and so drunk to drink one drink because I've ridded my alcohol, my body of alcohol so much.
And then I got home and I felt sick and I took Dayquil and then I woke up and I had one of
the worst hangovers of my entire life from one drink and Dayquil.
Are you still fully sick?
Yeah.
Yeah, no insurance in my life so I can't go get antibiotics for what is clearly a sinus
infection all my snot is Nickelodeon slime green.
Ew.
Yeah, so it's really, it's not been that good for me.
But guys, Heineken Zero is nursing me back to health.
I was wondering when--
Delicious malt beverage.
When this day was gonna come
where you had the Heineken Zero,
since it's known to be one of the best alcohol-free beers.
I love it, Heineken Zero is amazing.
I'm gonna give this five out of five peanuts
on the Gopher scale.
And the Gopher's--
What's the seed?
The Gopher, I don't know.
The Gopher's popping out of his hole today
to drink this Heineken.
I am drinking a Brooklyn Brewing Bel Air Sour.
A tropical sour.
new. Delightful. That sounds delightful. Give me the notes. You have sour, obviously. A
little sour, but unlike a sour monkey, it has half the alcohol in it, so it's just pleasurable
to drink. Oh, that's nice. We have a normal 5% beer. 5.8. Okay, so give me a numerical
rating
nice
yeah
I got a...
We all have poppers today!
Popper bottles!
I popped my bottle.
We're popping our bottles.
And I got a...
It's actually kind of weird.
It's got a weird label on it.
It says 1906.
But it's a...
It's a Estrella Galicia, I think.
It's like a Spanish beer from Spain.
This is like a special reserve type of thing.
It came in like a little fancy box.
this is actually a beer that my girlfriend got for her birthday and I stole one
so this is a legal contraband beer
what does that say about your girlfriend that she gets beer for her birthday?
she likes it
oh I don't like it though
what the hell
maybe you're the woman in the relationship
guys this is foolish
actually you're in a relationship with a man and you're the girl
Yeah, this is she gets a beer for her boy for her birthday and you
Sneak a little sip. Oh look only because you're the girlfriend and girlfriend's like stealing stuff. Yeah, i'm gonna keep going with my
Walk around the house so rudely interrupted I do like wearing my big hoodie and walking out with my pennies
uh guys
I
I liked
We had a little streak going of drinking nice light beers that I love drinking because they don't taste much like beer.
But this is full on. This is a full on beer. I would like to call it a...
Yeah, that's what I would call it. Full power beer.
A full power beer. Fully loaded.
Fully loaded, fully flavored and I don't like it.
It's a little... I think it's a 6.5%
I just got off the notes of a disgusting beer that I wouldn't like to drink.
It doesn't, I guess- This is not a 10 million.
No, this is not a 10 million.
I think I would go with a one.
Out of 10.
It's so frustrating.
It really is.
This pisses me off more than it should that you refuse to adhere to a very simple set
of rating rules that we have come...
Like a rubric.
There's no one foot tall person.
There's no one...
It's a streak.
It's a baby that ran into the court.
That's not a player.
They don't count.
They don't say...
And now a baby is on the court and they don't pass to the...
The baby's not playing, man.
And the baby runs on the...
would
a
Do you pass to him?
Doing like a Steve Nash no look pass and just exploding the baby.
I'm not gonna lie, I would pass it to the baby.
That would be so funny.
If you pass it, if you, if a baby ran onto the court in an NBA game and you passed it to the baby,
you would be, you would be completely kicked out of the league.
You'd be playing in China in one week too.
You can't pass it to the baby.
Follow me.
Even if the baby scores, they're not.
Here's a, here's an old Chinese joke.
You pass it to the baby and then the baby passes it into the river because it's a girl. How about that?
I don't understand.
Baby passes the ball?
It passes away in the river. It's drowned. The baby drowned.
Wait, how's that Chinese?
Is that the kind of joke that we're doing on this show now? Is jokes about infanticide?
I'm sorry.
That's what we think.
I'm having a hard time, okay?
Why are you having a hard time?
I'm just...
What's going on?
The work is so busy, dude.
Tell us all about it.
I do not want to.
But I just, you know.
But do it anyway.
Honestly, man, I don't want to hear it.
My brain is completely mush.
You have a fully nerd job.
I don't want to have anything to do with that.
Yeah.
My brain is mush because in addition to being a gopher this October.
Why do I keep thinking it's October, man?
It's November.
That's how much...
Our brains are completely mush.
In addition to being a gopher this November.
Well, yours was always mush.
True.
I have been waking up at 7 in the morning.
Oh my.
Clap.
Thank you.
I've been waking up at 7 in the morning and I've been going to the gym and I've been,
before I go to do my weight lifting, I go, and I do that at 11 o'clock, I go at 7 in
the morning and I go and I run for an hour.
And this has been one of the worst decisions I think I've ever made in my entire life.
It's so cold.
It's very, very cold.
It's very hard to do.
What are you doing at 8am, at 7am?
Why don't you just wake up like an hour or two earlier?
Because it feels like that's a good time to wake up, especially now that the sun goes away
at 445, I wanted to have a little bit more sunlight in my life, so I've been waking up
early.
And I thought that I was going to get used to it in like a week, and I have not gotten
used to it.
Every day, waking up is so fucking hard, man.
I think a...
Oh, let's get in here.
I think 8am is the GOAT.
You think 8am is the GOAT?
8am might be the GOAT.
I like 7 because you feel a little better than everybody else.
Listen, I don't want to obscure you, but I woke up today fully at 4am.
There's no reason for that.
Why'd you do that?
Dog.
I drove hot tonight to the airport.
That is not...
That doesn't count, man.
Yeah, that's bullshit.
Everybody's had to do that.
You're not, uh, you said upscaling me. You're not upscaling me.
I'm special and I'm upscaling you and I'm not camping and I
I tried to go back to sleep but I just couldn't. So I was just like you know
what fuck it I'll just go I'll just feed the dog and I'll go on my little walk.
I am, guys, I know I'm usually your host but I know when you think of
lead man, think of front man, you think of me but
today I just simply cannot carry that burden.
Today I have a dog that I have to take care of that I fully lost already.
She left the room and I don't know where she is.
I saw her walk out. She's on to a better, newer life, man. Just let her go.
She doesn't like hanging out with me, is what I've noticed.
If you love her, let her go.
No, she hates me fully. I've told her teacher to not bite me.
I'm trying to teach her that right now.
But there's several issues with that.
Number one, she's a puppy and she's one day old and she likes to bite.
Not so smart.
She has...
Can you see that?
I don't know if you can see that.
No.
It's just a little white.
Oh, I actually see a scratch, I do.
She has long-ass puppy nails and she just likes to, you know, get on top of you and she scratched
the fucking shit out of me and I feel really hurt and I want to explain to her in English
why she shouldn't do that.
That's probably your first mistake is speaking to a dog in English.
in
zero. I just have to say I love these things.
What does it, wait, what does it taste like?
It tastes exactly like a Heineken.
I have never had a Heineken. So this is not,
it's one to one. It tastes like a, like a light beer. It's a nice,
maybe it's a, you would like it. I think it would be a tumbler.
If I was a gopher.
I almost bought like a big Heineken today for the show.
I should have, we should have coordinated.
The last alcoholic drink I had, uh,
for october it was on halloween i was feeling so sick and i was like but you know what man
if i'm gonna be a gopher for a whole month i gotta have one last beer and so i got a tall
boy heineken and that's cheating that's like i gotta have one last meal and then you get like
you know a bucket of chicken from kfc what that's a good meal how's that cheating good meal
Well, that's too big. That's too big for one meal.
That's too big for one beer.
You can have one big meal.
If it was your last meal though, one last meal, of course you'd do a big meal.
Okay, wait, hang on. Before we keep going with this,
Rex, you are dying tomorrow.
You have one last meal you can eat tonight.
What are you eating?
Probably the Forever Feast.
Okay.
That is not a thing, by the way.
Okay, what's the Forever Feast?
It's a Mr. Beast.
Mr. Beast?
Mr. Beast Feast?
You would eat a Mr. Beast Feast?
Mr. Beast Forever Feast.
Okay, what is the...
What are you talking... What is a Forever Feast?
It's a...
It's like a... It's a plate that never gets empty.
You keep eating and it just refills itself.
Well, but you...
Okay, but you...
What's on... What is in the...
You have to stop eating at midnight.
food
uh... whereas the u_s_ very simple question
what if you could eat if you had been you have to do not need after midnight
because it's not that day anymore to last day you can eat
for a week will say that i don't want to catch my food
what is the problem with that you can't be a good i know that it's a forever
Feast. Things keep popping up but what's in the Forever Feast man you're pissing me off so much.
I have a new question don't answer the food one. How much is the drink also forever or
does do you only have like a one glass of water? You just get one small glass of water.
That's fucked up. That's a fucked up thing to do someone. Mr. Beast is torturing you.
He is. That's what he is. He's the torturer. He is fully a torturer. Did you see the people
the
so crazy racist man i'm trying to be in the office reboot i can't be next to you guys in a recorded
video man i'm not racist you're right you're not at all but i think that once i once they
i talked to a homeless woman the other day really and i followed her around to buy her things whoa
oh okay you took a homeless lady on a shopping spree well she uh she tried because at first
she came up to me and she was like, "Can I get some milk for my baby?" and I was like,
"There's no way that's real." But in the off chance it is, I would, you know, be remiss
if I missed the opportunity to help a starving black baby. But then she was like, they didn't
have anything and she's like, "Can I get some headphones so I can listen to my baby?"
I was like, I mean...
What?
What the hell?
And then they didn't have...
A TV to watch my baby and a massage chair to massage my baby?
And then they didn't have headphones, so she was like, "Can I just get, like, the thing to file your nails?"
Okay.
*laughter*
This is so strange.
Number one, why do you think that...
I think if someone were to ask me for milk instead of money, I would be like, "Oh yeah, you probably have a baby."
You should have squirted some just out of your nipples right at her.
There you go.
That's right.
Open your hands up.
That's my last meal. It's my own milk.
That's not your last meal.
I'm thinking about breast milk a lot.
you already picked one of those
Yeah, I think that if one day my wife gets pregnant and we have a baby, I think I have
to try it.
I mean, yeah, you have to.
I don't think it's that weird to do that.
I think it's completely weird.
I think it's completely weird and wrong, but I'm just too, I watch too much Nitro Circus
and the Dudesons and Jackass growing up.
Would you store it in bottles?
That's the kind of thing I think I'd have to do.
Would I store it in bottles?
Yeah.
- Yes, but I would get like Grand Marnier,
like nice bottles and keep the breast milk in there.
- Yeah, like a Don Julio 1942 bottle.
- Yeah, 1942, exactly.
Like nice, I'd get, and I'd have a top shelf
where I keep all of it, unrefrigerated.
- Okay, so you'd be--
- And then I'd pop it open, pour it on the rocks
for my child, because that's the kind of thing
that I'm gonna be training him to do.
- I thought you were gonna say that you were gonna be
showing out like proud that yeah we got this shit right here and i'm drinking it
instead of like just oh i it's a private stash it's in the fridge and i just oh i just grabbed
the bat by accident i watched i re-watched that la beast video the other day where he
leaves a gallon of milk outside for a month and then he drinks it and uh that's got to be one of
the greatest videos of all time he throws up inside of his washing machine because he did not have the
for the foresight
think about the fact that
completely separated thirty day old milk might make him vomit
so he did not have a bag next to him
so instead he has to reason is garage in his to run to his washing machine and
throw up into the side of it
i think he's the smartest guy alive
i think he's a g_m_ is definitely uh... genius
filmmaker
there's no doubt to me about that
It is crazy that he-
He is a- a- a complete auteur.
Do you think he's got like the most insane, um...
Like insurance of all time?
Because he's- he's done some insane stuff, like he's seen like
Whole cacti, he's- he's drank like poison basically.
I think that there's basically no way that any insurance company would possibly cover him.
I think he's gotta be like a cyborg or some shit.
That keeps like-
That has to be- when you fill out an insurance form for Blue Cross Blue Shield
and you fill out occupation and your occupation is eating cactus and expired cereal from 50
years ago, I think your premiums go way the fuck up.
Yeah, I'd be pissed. I'd be like, I'm paying for this guy to get better.
I think you have a better chance writing down Alaskan crab fisherman than I'm the LA beast.
I feel like there's no way that, I mean, he's got to be, his insurance premium is probably
$70,000 a month because there's no way that anybody would would cover that.
You're losing money. Yeah there should be like the guy that gets hurt for work. I
think more people should just be tortured for money. Remove the work element.
Remove like like people shouldn't be filling out spreadsheets anymore. We've
got computers that do that for us. They should just be like electrocuted. Yeah but
for
blood almost. Like you go and you get electrocuted for just as long as you can and then you get
paid for it. I agree. Because I don't think that we need, I think that we should not be
living in communism socialism, this destroys Christianity, it shouldn't exist. But I do
think that people shouldn't have to work because working is really really hard. But if you
can take, if you can withstand thousands of volts of electricity pulsing through your body
and making your skeleton blue and pop out and flash,
then yeah, dude, you should be making money.
- My first thought on this is I would completely do it.
My second thought is, would you guys come with me
to do this job with me?
- And like, come with you and also do it?
Probably not.
I don't like getting hurt very much.
- How much do you think they should get paid
to be 40 hours in the torture chamber?
- 40 straight hours of torture,
or like eight hour shifts?
- Eight hour shifts.
- Well, it depends on the country.
9 to 5, you know, break for lunch.
Did you know that the work week in Mexico is 48 hours?
Really?
It's a big debate right now going on. They're trying to make it 40.
You guys do a 6 hour work or 10 hour work days?
I think we just work the entire week plus Saturday.
Oh, okay.
I think that's what it's supposed to be like.
It was a whole thing with my old job, like office job.
that I technically worked like half a day on Saturdays,
but I never actually worked any Saturday.
But when it comes to the vacation days,
they take one day, one extra day off of your days
if you are asking for a Saturday vacation day as well.
- That's wrong, man.
- That is wrong.
But anyways, I wouldn't do the electrocution job in Mexico
if that was the case.
- Well, it doesn't necessarily have to be--
the
water
on
ever
if that if that was what i was getting paid for dude
i'd work i'd work a hundred hours a week i'd be catching doubles i'd be picking
up shifts from other guys who didn't have a white forehead to have a date
and i think it was just
i'd be telling i mean
i'd pride bore a hole in my head with the water that because i don't care
my forehead
i'll sit there in any even if it's like
as okay as long as i could sit there and listen to
you to videos
about uh... drama between different
uh... three years
no phones man
well that's it's own kind of torture
that's what that's a course in a similar house rules
you have to be a little bit you bring your phone and record
the the
bad working conditions and amazon
uh... but
record the piss bottles and shit
now this is a little bit of this week and be on your phone
i did think earlier i walked by one of those people who is uh... doing that
amazon prime deliveries with and have that blue box that bag box thing
yes
and
i think there's almost no world where if i work that job for a year i wouldn't at
some point
during my route have to take a shit in that box
i think that that box would get
a shit in it
so fast if i was a m_l_ for better breaks when you're in the road
what do you do it if you if you're a delivery man yeah and i'm trying to
position just ask
people if you can shit
and their house
uh... you never had a m_ is on gas giving take a shit no i have not
really
pretty much every time they deliver something as you think take a shit my
apartment
are you serious what do you say yet did
so yeah man i'm a nice guy
that
Notice that they leave their boxes.
They're like blue.
Yeah, they're everywhere.
Yeah.
So, clearly you can just take a shit in it.
Yeah, just leave it.
What's this blue box that you guys are talking about?
I don't...
I think in cities, because they'll park on a block and then they have a bunch of packages
to deliver on the block.
So instead of drive up every...
Oh, it's like a crate.
...to every address.
Yeah, they have like a crate that they put on their back.
what you like death stranding and they have to walk down the block and try to get there.
That's messed up. I think New York is the best city in the world because you can just drive
around and you can just watch a movie on your car. That is true. My brother-in-law,
maybe I shouldn't say this, he just had a child. My brother-in-law, he went to school in Georgia
and he would drive up to North Carolina a lot for like family events and stuff
and every single time I'd be like "Hey, how was the drive?"
It's like an 8 hour drive, he'd be like "It was good, I watched two movies."
So he was driving on the highway with his phone on the steering wheel
and he would just watch Guardians of the Galaxy, the entire thing.
That's badass, dude.
I've done that.
I used to do that with my old car that didn't have like Apple CarPlay
But it was so I just had like maps on my phone.
I would just like drive like this basically just holding the like totally like this.
So I get that I could I could do that.
I could do that today.
I was sorry.
Go ahead.
One time I dropped Julio off at the airport and I watched like some video for like 40 minutes while I was in traffic in LA.
on the way home
to people who get that anymore?
uh...
wow
but i feel like you'd be safe
the it's the most obvious defense ever
I was on Google Maps, man.
Right.
I'm sorry, officer.
I was on Google Maps trying to figure out where to go.
Trying to figure out which side of the street I was going to drive.
Did it, like, check?
All right, let me see your last three apps.
I can't go through your phone, man.
Let me look at your last three apps.
No, they can go through your phone.
No, they can't.
Yeah, they can.
You have to have a warrant to go through a telephone.
I don't think that's true.
That is 100% true.
OK, I will believe you because I don't actually know.
You have to have a warrant to go through a telephone,
any kind of digital thingy.
So if you have a digital thing on you,
then, and they say, I wanna touch your digital stuff,
you have to say, where's your warrant, fool?
Where's your warrant, pig?
- Okay, so you're just out of shadow of the law,
then he'll just assume that you're not on NAPL maps.
- Don't try me on the police knowledge, dude.
I watch videos all day and night that are--
- And you've got your car towed.
- Auditing, dude, have you seen these videos
were
share
Amazing dude. Yeah, I think it's amazing. These type of videos like one that I heard about like also like years ago
We're just a guy to just recording like while he's walking and she's like go set a business
It's just recording a lady and then she gets he gets like pissed and then those are the clips
I usually end up on like current fucking Karen 2033 company compilation. Yeah, I guess man guess where these videos never take place
Your house, Los Angeles, California
California.
That's true.
Because in that city, it's full of actors who are actually grateful for any screen time
that they could possibly get.
Don't play it, Karen.
Don't play anybody, dude.
So these guys, if they really want, if they want to not get beat up or called awful names,
like White, which happens in a lot of the videos, "Hey, you're White," then they should
be going to Los Angeles and walking around East LA.
Yeah, well they don't go cameras, but they got all those like
High speed chase videos they come out every that is true every two weeks. There's a lot of car chases in Los Angeles
That's kind of cool. Do the guys ever get away? I feel like once you get the helicopter out you can't do it
It's really hard yeah
There is have you seen that one video where the guy like he gets out of the car and he's like on foot and
And then the helicopter is like on it, so he's not really gonna get away
but there's like cops looking around for him and then he like hides behind a car and
They like completely just like lose line
And the newsman is like oh my god, they can't even see him right now they're completely walking right by him
The second it's so fucking awesome
awesome.
I uh, my, it's a tragic story.
I don't think I've talked about this on a show, but there's, I know I've sent the video to
Jubio, but there's a video that's called like, the worst tragedies in like news history or
something.
Oh my god.
And like, did I send it to you?
I don't think so.
There's one of them is like, one of them is like apparently there was a car chase in LA
there was two different helicopters that were following it and they crashed into
each other live on air. No. It's a really crazy story but the funniest the funny
thing is in the video uh-huh the guy is like the guy who's making the video he
has that that youtuber like story voice where he's like right and after the
Tragedy the worst part was that because it was live on air a lot of the victims
Closest friends had to react to it live on air leading to some very tragic
reactions and then it
slowly fades in a clip of a guy going
I'm gonna find this clip right now. I'm just gonna play it out of my phone.
I know I have it.
Did the guy get away with it?
Uh, I don't know. I did...
I quickly...
Once I found out about the helicopters colliding, I quickly lost interest in the actual chase.
I think that's one of the ways that you get out...
You get away with it.
The...
The helicopters crash.
Here it is.
disturbing or the darkest moments in TV history 3.
Tell me if you can hear this.
News stations swarmed to cover the crash.
With many of those people forced to cover the incident being acquaintances and even good friends.
Within people they had just watched perish.
Leading to some genuinely heartbreaking reactions.
Oh no, oh Jesus!
Oh gosh!
Oh my gosh!
Hey!
Holy crap!
Oh gosh!
Oh my gosh!
What?
Wait, but you know what? Is that guy like some relative of the
helicopter people?
No, he was like a guy
who worked at the news station
with one of the guys, or like the radio station.
Right.
Finds it. Holy crap, you know and in that scenario
I would have kept my cool if Rex was up there and you kill it were up there also and
And you were both in the helicopters you crashing you died. It would cut back to me and I will be like
Guys we have to quit
Here wait, let's just hold on. Oh, let's play it out completely. Okay, okay
Rex you're in one helicopter. I'm in the other we're both on the radio with with GPO right now, right?
It looks like the cat is still stuck in the tree. We're rotating around
We have an amazing angle on the cat that's stuck in the tree Rex. How are you doing over there? Oh, man?
It's so good. I've got a perfect view of this cat at this angle wait
You're coming a little close here. I can't hear you right now Rex the kitty cat is looking completely adorable. Oh my god
There's a fireman there, and he looks buff. He should be on a calendar wait wait. What's that?
The giant black thing that is covering all my vision
*Funkmaster flexing*
We cut to me, ladies and gentlemen, we have to go to commercial right now.
That's how we handle it.
There we go. That's a professional newsman.
I don't think you're being honest.
What do you mean?
I think you would probably immediately cry.
Not true.
Okay, well here's a test.
Okay, well first we have to do the commercials. Okay? Okay, safe light repair safe light replace. Okay now fade in
Do you know?
He doesn't want to get emotional he doesn't want to get emotional. Did you know that they make that jingle for every language in the planet?
Do you do yours right now do the Mexican one?
I saw a video
I don't know why I watch the entire video
I watched an entire video of them doing that jingle and like at least like 30 to 40 languages and
And they're all over the world, it's so crazy, but I don't know the Spanish one.
I think the Spanish one is bad, I think the French one is okay.
Uh...
I think the English one is also okay. - The English one is definitely the best one.
I think so.
Okay, so the commercials are fading away, and now you have to go live, dude.
You can't air commercials for an hour, okay?
Okay, we'll do 30 minutes of commercials.
No, okay, 30 minutes is up. You've had 30 minutes to recover.
But now you have to be live as your two best friends have just died in an awful...
Air-mobile accident.
Ladies and gentlemen, earlier today we erred.
We, uh, we erred.
We erred.
Okay, so you both are dead.
*laughter*
He's watching Sean Paul.
We erred.
Dr. Prudner.
The hell, man.
You are such a bad liar.
So you are both dead anyways.
I wish I was dead so I didn't have to hear you.
I'm older as the radio ad.
We heard my friend died, man.
We heard my friend died and I left my car, man.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Completely unprofessional.
Can you guys hear the awesome banging?
Yeah, bro.
I think I'm gonna ask them to come just hammer my walls.
You have bangers downstairs that bang?
Yeah.
I don't know.
The lady, the people downstairs like moved out.
They had some like crazy setup.
We thought they were selling some sort of drugs
because they were so insane and also no one liked them.
But at some point they got--
- I don't drive anybody to drugs.
- I think they got kicked out.
And we asked about that apartment.
We're like, no, we're gonna give it to someone else.
And all day it's been just nothing but banging.
and I mean I'm just trying to take care of this dog here.
She's fully dead.
If you can see here.
Oh, you can't see that.
- I can't see that. - Yeah, I can't see that.
There's a monitor in the way.
- There's a fully dead-- - Oh, she looks dead,
actually, yeah. - There's a fully dead dog.
- There's a white guy in the way.
- There is a big white guy, a big white Sasquatch.
- That's not true.
- All right, wait, I gotta go get another Heineken 00, man.
You guys talk about--
- How many does your third one?
My third dude, they're only...
Oh my god, there's six, there's seventy calories, Jesus Christ.
Well, I'll have one more.
Oh my goodness, that's so many calories.
Zero times three equals zero.
Yeah, but that's...
Okay, well actually, I think you're right.
He needs cleansing.
I think once we get to awesome Drinksgiving,
he will be cleansed of this gopher nastiness.
I don't want to mention it when he's around, but I think he's got a gopher problem.
I could hear you the whole time.
Oh shit.
Yeah, he has wireless headphones.
You think it's wrong to be a gopher, man?
Also, why are you talking shit about your friends behind their back?
Yeah, what the hell?
Just tell it to me straight.
First you want them to be dead so they can't hear you.
Now you want them to be outside.
Ladies and gentlemen, earlier today we heard two of my coworkers die in a fiery crash on
on a cat related news coverage.
And we simply have to apologize
for putting you all through that.
We were really close friends with those two correspondents.
But now let's go for the weather.
I heard it's gonna be-
- You would not go straight to the weather.
And the weather, by the way,
would be flaming arms and legs are falling out of the sky.
- That would not be the weather.
- And people's soups.
People are trying to eat big bowls of bread,
bowls of soup outside of a Panera bread,
and caleb's toes and fingers are falling into it
you will not explode explode that bigly
i would say
dude i'm so big they would be finding pieces of me
for
also i'm so lightweight
right so you're just gonna float and
it would literally be it would block
sunlight crops would die all over the country
because of how many particles of me are blocking the sun i think your parts would get
crushed
and turn into dust and just blow into the air.
- Dude, wait, here's your worst nightmare though.
So the camera feed is still on somehow, right?
Or maybe your best nightmare.
The camera feed is still on.
It's a GoPro that we were filming with.
These things are indestructible.
The camera is just looking at the ground,
kind of half at the ground,
Cloverfield style angle, kind of tilted.
- Right.
- Looking at the rubble and the rubbish.
the
completely perfectly merged because our bodies are so aligned.
Yes.
Half of our bodies are gone on either side and we are now down the middle, two-faced,
split perfectly.
Calyx?
Yeah.
And our penis looks really odd.
I don't want to just keep pitting at that horse, but do you think that Calyx would have
the most insane come over of all time?
Yes.
There would be no choice.
Well all the hair got burned off in the accident.
Yeah, we just smoked a bottle of gin.
Okay.
Yeah.
But I would feel less bad about it.
Would you chill out with Kalix?
Yeah, for sure.
Really?
I think Kalix would...
I think Raylo would lose it really quickly.
What do you mean lose it?
I think Raylo would fall to the class of gambling so, so quickly.
because you're both addicted to gambling in a crazy degree.
And if you multiply that by two, I think--
- I don't even gamble, man.
- I was about to disagree with you,
but there is literally big windboard tabs on both sides.
- So yeah, so this is you holding back.
You're like, "Oh, I'm just looking at it.
I'm just like playing fake money."
Raylib just goes--
- Raylib, you might be right.
You might be right.
Yeah, yeah, Raylob with Rex's bankroll.
Yeah, it'd be over, man.
Actually, we don't even have to imagine that.
I think we have a almost--
maybe not perfect Raylob.
But I think Brian's already there.
I think Raylob is perfect.
Yeah, I don't think you can get better than Raylob.
Do you nurse Raylob back to health?
Mm-hmm.
That's the real question if you're a real friend.
Like, what does he need?
He needs uppies.
You don't need uppies.
You've never asked for uppies.
I've seen you at least five times, I think.
And not once have you asked for uppies.
Next time that you see me, you're giving me an uppie.
Just one.
See if we both like it.
What if we really like it?
I think I'm giving you an uppie.
Here's the thing.
Does the Ray part of Raylib want an uppie?
That's up to Ray.
Yeah, give me an uppie.
Now.
Okay.
All right.
instant. Are you stupid? Why wouldn't I want an uppy? I'm fucking fused with another man.
What dignity do I have left? Get me up now. Who do you think would be more upset with
that half and half transformation? Probably your significant others. The most obnoxious
this
us. That is true. They have a lot of freedom. I know that my wife would be like, "You know
what man? I always thought Rex was such a hot piece of ass dude. I couldn't hide it." It
be like me with hair. Yeah. We got burnt off. Oh you're right. Well it'll grow back. We'll
get a... Well but now that we have the... Once we're gambling, we'll make enough money to
get a full hair transplant. Right. And you know what? Maybe we'll just cover our entire
hair bodies with hair and become a...
Has somebody done that?
Go to Turkey and tell the person,
like, "I want to be Bigfoot."
- I think that's impossible to do.
- Shut up, bitch!
- Why would that be impossible?
- I think, well, I don't think it's impossible.
I think it's impossible to do it that way.
I don't think the Turkey man is gonna be like,
"All right, I'm gonna put things in your entire body."
I think the only way to do that is just to bathe
in minoxidil for days.
- I don't think that's how that works.
know
a bunch of follicles so I need a follicular transplant
they're gonna have to take follicles from somebody and put them in my
over my entire body turn me into a full Sasquatch and then I'll start scaring
people
I'm basically hairless so
I've no chest hair there's nothing going on there
there's no follicles to take yeah me too dude I'm completely just a nubile
the
how I have such a low threshold for feeling like like how bad I have to feel
to be like okay I'm canceling all of my plans and I'm going to take a four-hour
bath like like an old lady who has like chronic Lyme disease like that's how I
treat that's how I am and that's why I exercise and stuff so I wonder if I felt
even like on your best day eating and drinking what you do that is true how
How long I would make it, I think. I don't know.
I genuinely haven't felt good in like years.
Yeah.
You know?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's a good thing to say. Yeah.
Not in like a "Oh, I'm so depressed."
No, but like the stuff in your body is affecting you in a way every single day.
Yeah.
I think my depression and my anxiety have been making my-
my
I'm at the computer. My daily carry I do keys, phone, wallet. I have uh wired headphones. Yep.
And that's it man. Do you think it's crazy to go? I don't even take my wallet outside most of the
time. I was about to ask you do you think it's crazy to go outside without wearing your wallet
and like any ID on you? I only know I only bring my wallet if I'm going to if I'm going to be out
for like all day. Right. I'll bring my wallet but if I'm going to do one thing I never bring my wallet.
the
I don't have my phone on me.
Wait, guess I do.
Hold on.
Yeah.
I've actually, so far.
Can you see this?
Is this like...
Well, it's not, it doesn't show anything, like, important.
It's a little blown up.
It has a photo of you?
It doesn't even show that.
If I click on it, it does.
It just has my driver's license info and I can pull it up and it has my picture, my address,
my date of birth.
Is that why you're in a bar?
That's sick.
I doubt it, but I could try it, I'm sure.
It is official.
It's insane.
'Cause it like...
Yeah.
I didn't dox myself because it just literally has my name and my initial.
Yeah, also we couldn't really see anything.
Yeah, well I already know it all. So you did dox it to me.
And it has my old address where I don't live anymore because I'm too lazy to update.
Yeah, go ahead and send a bomb there man, I don't give a fuck.
Yeah.
I'm bad.
I don't know.
They did so much for you though.
At what point of like...
How big do you have to be for people to start wanting to SWAT you?
Umm...
Who's like the least known guy?
Oh yeah, I guess you're right. You need to have an enemy.
Yeah, you need to have someone preying on your downfall.
That one like really famous story about like a kid who just like doxxed...
Just like SWATed some other kid on COD and just like killed his neighbor.
this name. But that's an enemy! Are you retarded? What is the difference between that and an
enemy? An enemy? No, I'm gonna, I'm, I, we need to differentiate. An enemy is like a lifelong
thing. Someone who will just do an evil thing to you. No, that's a nemesis! Yeah. You're
a confusing enemy and nemesis, man. Yeah. I think it's a synop. There's many enemies.
There's few nemeses in the side.
I'm sorry.
These are...
They're...
Well, they're not very around very much.
They're rare, some might say.
Yeah.
You don't have one often.
Like, you are often my enemy.
But you are not my nemesis.
Yeah.
Do you have many enemies?
I try not to, man.
I don't think so.
I try to live a very peaceful life.
Try not to be rude to people.
I try to be courteous.
I try to be nice.
I try to be...
I try to be sexually forward with every single person I meet.
I think the number one easiest way to get enemies is to just go out and drive around.
I agree man.
That is true.
Nobody makes more enemies than a guy in a car.
Very temporary.
Even I do it man.
Listen, I jaywalk in front of cars daring them to hit me every single day.
Like every single day.
With a dog, mind you.
with a dog that can easily be killed by a car.
Me, I'm not so sure, we haven't tested it.
But dogs provably can be killed by cars.
And I walk right in front of them, they have the right of way, they have a green light.
And I just go, fuck it, do something about it, right?
But when I'm in a car and I'm driving and somebody puts their foot into the crosswalk,
I lay on the horn, I will open my window, give them the finger, spit.
Fuck you, man.
There's something about driving a car that because you're driving a gun, yeah, like you're
driving a weapon all the time at high velocities that you feel untouchable.
Also everybody thinks that their windows are bulletproof.
Everybody thinks that every problem that you have when you're in a car and somebody else
isn't can be solved by rolling up a window.
Like I am fully convinced of that when I'm driving.
That's true, I mean no one carries a gun.
That's what I'm saying man.
This is America, no one has a gun on them.
No dude, and also I could see it from a mile away.
A fat old guy who has something, who is wearing like a hoodie, not fucking with it.
No no no, that guy might have a gun.
Yeah that is true.
Fat old guy with a hoodie, might have a gun.
or
to do fucking what, man?
- You can probably find that on Amazon,
for one of those made up Chinese brands for like $2.
- But that's what I'm saying.
It's like, that's not a,
like you used to be able to go to the T-Mobile store
and they would sell a holster for your phone.
- Well, that was mainly during when Nexo was a thing, right?
'Cause you have to get it out quickly
'cause it's like a radio thing.
- What?
My grandpa had a fucking iPhone 2 in that thing.
Yeah, I don't know what you're talking about with that.
It was just a thing people did.
I think it was predominantly--
It's not like people are on their phone less.
I saw my grandpa recently,
and my grandma has a photo of my brother as her background,
and has for like years.
And he was like, "I wanna change my background.
"How do I do that?"
And I was like, "Oh, I'll change it."
He's like, "You know what?
"I want it to be a photo of you."
And I was like, "Okay."
So I took a selfie where I was like this.
was like and I said it to be his background and he was like I don't like
this photo I was like then fucking try to change it bitch
you try go ahead and now he's gonna be like all my golf course just be like
trying to show somebody a meme that he saw on a barstool Instagram page they'll
like who's this gay guy it really was just tickling me and he got real mad
about it he was like of course take another photo god damn it what the hell
is it angry ass New Jersey guy my sweet my sweet cute smile and he does it he
You can't change it, he has no idea how to change it.
Wait, did you do both screens?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, and he had, oh, that was, he like looked at it, he was like, "Oh, okay," and then he
opened it and it was behind all of his apps, he's like, "God damn it, how the hell did
you even do that?"
That's great, man.
I've been laughing all day.
Have you been on the train and seen, there's like an ad for like a cyber security course,
And it's like my son/nephew's making 150k.
My son/nephew?
My son/nephew's.
Woah.
And I've been thinking just like all the different things.
Like my son/nephew knows how to change the background on my iPhone.
Just like, just like all the things people think their kids know how to do on the computer.
Dude, I hadn't hung out with him in a while.
He was just up here to visit a friend for his 80th birthday.
He's 81 years old.
My grandpa is.
He looks great.
He looks like he's in his 60s.
Shouts out.
Is he bald?
No.
Well, kinda.
He's got thin old guy hair.
But he has hair on his head.
Right.
Wispy.
But he was like, literally sat down before he said anything.
He was like, "So, you got a lot of Muslims in your neighborhood, huh?"
And I was like...
You sure do.
I was like, uh, I don't know, like maybe.
And he was like, oh, okay.
So, uh, have the riots been okay for you?
And I was like, what are you talking about?
And, uh, I realized, cause he said like, he was like, oh, I don't want to come into the city.
Come, will you come to New Jersey where I am and we'll get lunch?
And I was like, yeah, sure.
Not really even thinking about it.
But the reason he did was because he thought if he went into New York, he was going to get,
it
booked my trip from New York my my godfather I was talking I was like yeah
I got this got this plane tickets like whatever like oh yeah well you know I
was like yeah I'm staying with friends it's like it's gonna be real chill like
oh yeah that's great just uh be on the lookout for all the all the terrorist
attacks I was like what yeah be just just watch out be real careful like oh
yeah for sure no I told him no I'm friends with them bro don't worry which
which he didn't find really funny.
But he's just been like that.
When I went to Europe, he did the same thing.
He was like, "Be careful on the train stations.
"They're always blowing them up."
And I was like, "No, they don't."
- It's so awesome, dude, 'cause it's,
stop burping, man, that's disgusting.
- Okay, I'm sorry.
- It is basically the exact same thing
where you meet people in New York,
and they'll go, "Where are you from?"
And I say, "I'm from North Carolina."
They're always from fucking L.A.
and they go like, "Oh, North Carolina.
So is their Ku Klux Klan running around your house all the time?"
And I always do the same thing that I do with my grandpa.
I just go like, "Yeah, man.
It's crazy."
It's crazy.
It's crazy, dude.
One of them.
The Ku Klux Klan is running around all the time, dude.
It stinks.
I don't think I said this on the podcast, but there was a Palestine protest that went
by my place.
And I was really mad because it like woke me up, but then I realized it was like 11am.
You know, so I couldn't really be that mad about it.
Yeah.
You know, like, it woke me up, but I was like, I don't want to wake in my neighborhood.
I guess.
Yeah, that is true.
It woke me up to the evils of the Israeli people.
Yep.
Can you protest at like 4 in the afternoon when I'm fully awake?
Yeah.
What are they doing in your neighborhood?
I don't fucking know, dude.
They're trying to get ya.
They knew that there was heebs in their neighborhood.
Yeah, do you mask up and hide your identity when you go outside now?
Uh, no.
No, I don't do that.
You should now that beers we drink is blown up and taking over the world.
That is true.
I am like one of the only white people in my neighborhood, but that is fine.
It's so obvious.
Oh, okay, it's fine, it's not good.
Interesting.
Well, it's fine because, you know, the homeless people will be like, "Oh, so you're not from
here."
I think it's good.
It's fine to be white.
I want to be...
No, I didn't say that.
It's wrong to be white, and I want to live in a neighborhood where I'm the only white
person and I walk around and people are giving me swirlies and throwing me into lockers and
stuff that's what I think that I deserve.
But that's not what happens in his life.
Every time he goes outside he has an adventure.
He meets like good characters.
That is true.
There's always characters.
I walked by a door and I was like oh that's the last time I interacted with Aki.
He was sitting outside this door and then like as I had that thought the door opened and he
walked out.
Damn.
You doxxed Aki?
In my mind.
Did he, wait, did he actually hook it up this time?
No, he still thinks that he gave me free weed, dude.
He thinks that he gave me free weed and then I like
welfed on him, you know?
Do you confront him about it? Like you didn't actually do that?
I texted him that like the day of but he still was like...
I forgot about that.
I forgot you met a guy named Aki.
And him memes yeah, I should enable request right now
I should do that. We'll do that one night. We'll do that one night at like 1 a.m. We'll send him like
If we win we have to be like now you owe me a free
I haven't gotten a scamming text message in a while.
I haven't either but I still get the phone calls all the time.
I ignore, I have not answered the phone in so fucking long.
If it's not, if it's not my wife calling me, I do not answer the phone.
Well, I try to do that also, but the thing is I have to get calls and pick them up when like shit's getting like delivered.
And I get stuffed in the room all the time.
Because I don't have like a door, like a doorbell or anything.
You have a door.
I don't have a door.
Well, do you still live in like, the area code you got your phone in?
No.
Cause for me it's like really obvious when I'm getting a scan because it's-
Cause it has the old area code.
Yeah. It's like no one from Phoenix should be calling me.
Yeah.
There's no reason for that.
There's no one that could possibly be calling me from Phoenix that I don't have in my phone
already.
I just wait for the, just leave me a voicemail dude.
You get to leave me an awesome voice message that I can't, uh, don't know how to change.
Where I, it's like, yeah, now leave your message for Caleb Pitts.
That's exactly how I say it.
Caleb Pitts.
Cause I was like 15 and I wanted to sound like an adult.
Right.
Caleb Pitts.
What's up?
Leave your message where?
What up man?
Now the way they try to scam me is through WhatsApp.
They do like a weird WhatsApp message and I already know that it's a scam so usually
I just send them a picture and last time I sent them a picture of the face to have fat
kale picture and I thought it was really funny and so I posted that interaction in my story
on Instagram. But it was a mistake because Kelo's brother follows me on Instagram. So
I saw it and I was like, "Oh, is that Kelo?" I was like, "Yeah, man." I just sent him the
picture without thinking. And then he says like, "Thank you. I'm going to treasure this
for my entire life." I was like, "Maybe I shouldn't have done that. Maybe I should have
consulted Kelo first."
You're ruining your friend's life, dude. My brother is a known pranker.
I realized that a little too late. So I was like, "Ah, well."
Jubio loves to hold on to face-apped photos of people.
- He likes having incriminating information
on every single one of his friends.
- Well, he just thinks it's so funny
when they're face-apped and they look funny.
- I think it's funny when I open the face-apped app
and I do one of my selfies,
and I just do the one where it takes off my glasses
and I look insane.
That's what I think is funny.
- Okay.
- But the fat killer.
- But you did that to everyone else too.
I had a... I talked to my friend Gus last night.
You're obsessed with me? You're obsessed with Kaler?
That's not true.
I talked to my buddy Gus last night, who by the way, I'm doing a show with him in Los Angeles next week, next Friday.
He will link it, come out to that. But I asked him, and I want to ask you guys this question.
How much money would, like, a group of your ten closest friends say,
"Hey man, we want to give you $10,000," or whatever amount of money.
But we have to go through, we have to be able to go through every note you've ever made on your phone.
How much money would it cost?
I don't really take notes on my phone.
I take a lot of notes on my phone, but
what they are, they're like show notes for the podcast.
So it's just, it would just be like
episode like two whatever on the title of the podcast and then like 16 minutes in
pervert spa like 18 minutes in
Just another look terrible of a bit. So that's what my notes up looks like mine are
Literally, I have thousands of notes of things that I wrote down when I was smoking weed
That are complete nonsense
Like this one I read to him last night and this is just this is one of the only ones that I think is
I'm willing to read
Imagine trying toilet water and realizing dogs are right
My entire I'm not kidding all of my notes are stuff like this
Can I go it's fucking awful man, no man, please
It's like almost a joke but most of this is a what this is one is recipes
These are the recipes that I came up with on
February 10th my am I me and my wife's anniversary
I wrote this down.
Pickle butter popcorn and miso kombucha.
These were the things I was like, this is a flavor combination that nobody's ever thought
of.
Wow.
That's fire.
Let's trade notes up next time we see each other.
Oh, this was for the tour.
I was going to hire Shadow Hayes.
You know the guy who does the DJ drops to say, "DJ Poop, wait, what's that smell?"
I remember that.
Yeah, I remember that.
We had a fun time with DJ Rick and Morty.
DJ Rick and Morty, he a badass motherfucker who don't take shit from nobody.
That guy has a stanky ass.
Those were the three things that I wrote down.
And then DJ Poop, wait, what's that smell?
Yeah, that's, I mean it's all just awful stuff like this, man.
That's not awful, that's not even embarrassing.
No, but a lot of them are embarrassing.
I have some that are ideas for short stories.
Okay, like what?
I won't tell you, man.
I won't tell you.
Would you rather have one million dollars or fuck your brother?
I'm not going...
It's just a note that said, "Would you rather have one million dollars or fuck your brother?"
I'm telling you, this is not...
I would not...
There's no way.
I'm not reading any more of these.
These are wrong.
That's powerful.
That's a powerful thought.
Yeah, I don't know about that.
What are you having in your notes, Rex?
I have an idea for a scam and then just a blank note that says, "An app a day."
*laughter*
Wow!
Yeah, you finish the rest of that, man.
*laughter*
That's a...
*unintelligible*
*laughter*
An apple a day.
I think there was something there.
*laughter*
Wait, what's the scam?
Do we know about it?
He can't give it away, man.
It's not really a spam, but it's...
No.
It's like one of Caleb's things where it just makes no sense.
That's like a Pinterest idea, like, "Pickle, enjoy your popcorn."
Thank you so much, I love you guys. This is seriously gopher vibes today.
The way that I went through these peanuts.
That's what these are now. These are peanuts. I'm a gopher.
Thank you for tuning in.
Sofer no vofer.
I love you all.
Bye.