[Sipping]
[Burping]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer broadcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my
chuggers? I'm trying to get that
[Gagging]
Bud Light.
♪ Haft Food Ribbon ♪
- Beers We Drank, Motherfucker,
with Juvio, Caleb, and Rex.
(funky music)
- Beer.
- Welcome back.
Oh shit.
- How many times,
how many times you guys have never got the memo?
- Okay, well I want to introduce my beer.
- Well you crack it open first.
- Well you need to introduce the podcast.
- That's the lyrics of the podcast.
- Welcome to Beers We Drank.
- There we go.
- All right, you go first.
Okay, I want to go first.
Yeah, I know that we that we've been doing topics now where we came at a topic
spot guests.
Right.
So today I felt like making the topic my beer.
So I got, okay, I'm interested.
I got pre gate of Bud Light.
Yeah, it's a pretty good.
Yeah, it's completely normal.
It's not even good at all.
So I think they should get it.
Yeah, it's good when you drink it.
Yeah, it was pre-gay until you put it in your hand.
Okay.
[laughing]
You guys killed my topic.
Yeah, you're a fucking loser.
Alright, well,
uh, here, mine is very boring.
I just had this in my fridge.
This is a Truly,
I bought this last time we tried to record
and we didn't end up doing it.
This is a Truly
Classic Lime
Fresh Squeezed
Margarita Style Heart Seltzer.
This is like the biggest Truly can of all time.
This is honestly one of the worst drinks
that they sell in the stores.
It is so disgusting, it will give you a stevia headache.
It is fucking abysmal.
I do not recommend anybody else.
- That is the thing about Trulies.
- It's stevia.
- Trulies always make me feel like shit with the stevia.
It's too much.
Man wasn't meant to drink that much stevia.
- Man was not meant to drink any stevia.
Dude, stevia is for bees to turn into honey.
That is not for humans to eat.
- I don't really understand what stevia is.
I thought it was just like healthy sugar.
- Stevia is basically like tooth enamel
that they scrape off of like one kind of plant in the Amazon
and they've just destroyed, I don't know if this is true,
but I think they've killed millions of people
getting all the crops, the stevia crops.
- But it tastes sweet?
- It tastes sweet for--
- Then I don't care.
- And in, no, no, it tastes sweet for an amount of time
that you cannot discern.
It's less, no, don't do that.
(laughing)
It tastes sweet for less than a second
and then it is the worst taste ever.
Yeah, I used to put stevia in my coffee
when I was at the office,
but I haven't had this TV in a long time.
All right, Rex, I have a
a flying slush man,
another SpongeBob another one here.
This is the second of the SpongeBob
theme beers.
It's a rack them up.
You know,
do you just go to the
to the liquor store looking for SpongeBob
theme beers?
Well, I went into the liquor store looking for beers
and they had SpongeBob themed beers.
And what am I supposed to do?
There were six.
At some point, they're gonna card you.
If you come in and every single time
you only buy SpongeBob beer,
they're gonna be like,
"Maybe he's not as old as he looks."
No, 'cause I used to come in there
and I would buy the worst vapes they had.
And so he knows me already.
In fact, he likes me.
When I bought these beers, actually, I will say this.
I bought a watermelon like Twizzlers.
Yeah, like and the two SpongeBob beers and he's like,
you're a man with fine taste.
Wow.
So neither of you have good taste.
Yeah, is also complimenting you on Twizzler.
That's your Ellie.
That's my that's my awk dude.
Do you eat candy during the day?
I'm not going to say no to that.
You do, don't you? I've done it. I've done it. God, what am I doing? I've
surrounded myself with a grown man who eat candy at 11 in the morning. I eat
candy? Oh, I eat candy at 11 in the morning? Yeah. I'm sorry. That's just crazy, dude.
Wait, which kind? Swiss Whips? I bought, well, no. I recently, I went to the store and I bought a big bag of Sour Patch Kids.
kids, but like a really big bag.
And it's been sitting on the kitchen counter near where you get like water.
So I'll go in and I'll fill up my water bottle for the day and I'll just kind of
dip my hand.
Wow.
Sometimes at night when I'm like, I'm hungry, I should eat dinner.
This would be a great time to eat dinner. You know, I'll go in there.
I'll kind of look around, poke around and be like, eh,
nothing really seems good. Dip my hand in, take five.
You're almost not, it's almost completely unconscious.
You're just like thinking out loud, talking about dinner. Yeah.
Here, I'll show you actually open container. Yeah.
I have you guys will notice I'm in, I'm in, uh, I'm in my man cave right now.
Yeah. I banished the lady to the bedroom. Oh, let me show you.
This is the only candy that I, I just had one actually.
I only old lady candy this is dark choc 70% cacao dark chocolate coconut almond
butter cups that sounds delicious
that's good to have no sugar that's healthy that's that's health food this
is not health food
it's health food it's dark chocolate
I like only old lady candy I only eat like 90% dark chocolate tastes like a
cigarette and has almonds in it
I don't think you're supposed to be eating any candy.
Anything with nut butter, anything with nuts in it is healthy.
Automatically.
Okay.
It could be tiger nuts.
I agree.
That's a meal and it's healthy.
Okay.
Almonds, nuts.
That's like the sweetest a meal can get while being healthy.
I'm trying to think of something that disproves this.
I'm having a really rough time actually.
Yeah.
Almost everything that has nuts in it, you're right, is just pure health food.
Right.
I guess, I see I could argue trail mix, but trail mix is, even the ones with M&Ms, it's
good for you. Right. Yeah. It's made to give you quick the M&Ms are there to give you the
quick calories. The sugar is for marathon runners. Right. So when I'm sitting at my
desk haven't moved in seven hours and I get my hand in eat all the M&Ms first. That's
healthy. I've definitely eaten over a thousand calories of trail mix in one sitting. There's
no question. I've eaten probably two thousand calories. Yeah. Which is not that much trail
mix honestly. I think I've only had trail mix when I went to New York the one time with Rex.
One of the times I went to New York with Rex. Really? Is trail mix not just a common snack
in Mexico? Not really. Well yeah you guys have nuts that have, true. You guys have nuts that
have, hey, no I don't want to. There's only trials. No go ahead. Okay I'll say it. Yeah
- Yeah, that's it.
- Why do you fucking, no, see, I shouldn't say fucking.
Why do Mexicans, I was gonna say, why do fucking Mexicans,
why do Mexicans put, why do they think everything
needs to have red on it?
Sometimes I just want a normal peanut.
I don't want a red peanut that has lime dust.
See, look how mad he is.
- I'm not gonna lie, I was supposed to be like,
- No, I was about to say,
that's the stupidest thing you've ever said to me,
but one of my favorite snacks,
it's called a hot nut, hot nut.
- I bet it is.
- It's just like a peanut,
it's just a peanut and it's just like red.
- It's a peanut and it's a hot nut.
- It's a bag of peanuts and they're red and spicy
and they have like lime on it.
- Yeah, every single,
some Aztecs were walking around finding peanuts and crickets
and they're like, those are really cool.
They should be completely red
And they should be sold in a bag that has this is 99 cents on the top right.
This is a excess of sodio.
Yeah, basically the spectrum of snacks in Mexico.
I don't believe that, by the way.
It's red and white.
If it's white, it's sweet.
If it's red, it's spicy.
Right.
White is the sweet, like concha.
Yeah, like concha, like horchata.
I just had some barroco en leche, which is also white.
I don't believe in sodio, by the way.
Why do you think I would be the sweetest motherfucker in the world?
OK, sodium is definitely not bad for you.
I think it's good for you.
It's good for you.
Are you one of these guys who you order food at a restaurant
and you don't even taste it?
You just start putting salt on it?
No, but I do at it at at an Asian place.
Soy sauce, not even tasting it yet.
Not to taste. Just dumping soy sauce on it.
Yeah, exactly.
You can tell when it comes, if it's not brown.
- No, if it doesn't look like it's a soup.
- I'm gonna break off of the pack here.
I used to do that, but I haven't done that in years.
And I feel like you need to grow up,
at some point you have to grow up and stop doing that.
- Grow up and stop putting free condiments on.
- It's already spice to taste.
- Wait, actually, we just realized that me and Rex
do this for completely different reasons.
He's literally pouring salt onto a hamburger
french fries and counting how much every single grain of salt is that he's ripping them off for
and me I just like that.
If two pennies, if three pennies, if four pennies.
You're trying to take them for all they have.
Excuse me do you have any more salt packets in the bag?
Kosher salt.
Yeah yeah.
I used to sort of do that at 7-Eleven.
What is kosher salt? Do you know what kosher salt is?
Yes, kosher salt is not necessarily kosher.
I just watched an Adam Ragusea video on this, actually.
It's not necessarily kosher itself, but it's used for it's
it's it refers to thick, flaky salt that is used for koshering meat.
Interesting, because you got to dry the blood out of the meat.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Yeah. So, you know, any other questions?
Where do babies come from?
- India.
(laughing)
- Well, most of them do.
- Yeah, not anymore though, am I right?
- What happened to India?
I love India.
- It got exploded.
- Really?
- Did you know that they invented lemonade?
- India did?
- Yeah, they did.
- Get out.
- Did you guys see RRR?
- No.
- I did.
That is probably one of my 15 favorite movies ever.
It's so long but it's so much fun.
I had so much fun.
I watched it with my brother's father-in-law and he's, I may have told you guys this, he's
like an old guy from Mexico and he doesn't speak a lot of English but I put on the movie,
we were just sitting there watching it and he does this thing when he watches a movie
(imitates hissing)
He like hisses like a snake.
(laughing)
And I was like, we were watching,
I just kept hearing that, and I was like,
what the fuck is he doing?
And then my sister-in-law was like,
my dad really likes the movie.
(laughing)
'Cause every time somebody would do a back flip,
he would go, (imitates hissing)
- That's so funny, I know exactly what you mean.
- You do?
- Yeah, I know.
- Is that a cultural thing?
- I guess, I don't know.
I've never really thought about it much.
- I'd never seen that before,
but I was like, that is so funny,
that that's his reaction, instead of being like,
oh, he's seeing it on TV.
- In my mind, it's like,
I don't know, when something's like dramatic,
or like there's like a ooh moment,
it's just like,
(imitates dramatic sound)
(laughs)
You go like that.
- I thought that he was just weird.
I didn't know.
- Every culture has a specific like,
oh, that they do.
- Well, you just did your cultures.
(laughs)
- It's part of the language, it's not racist.
- No, no, no, of course.
- You're very cultured.
- I saw a Mario movie.
- How was that?
(laughs)
- I felt like I was being advertised to
for about 30 minutes.
And then I sat down with myself and I said,
"Stop thinking, what are you doing?
You're at the Mario movie."
It was a great time.
- I'm sick of watching good movies.
I never want to see a good movie again.
I watched when we were out of town this past weekend.
I watched the four, I think I already told Julio this,
but I watched "Bullet Train."
- Okay.
- A plus, amazing movie.
I re-watched "Game Night," A minus, really good movie.
I saw "Fight Club," A minus, or A,
almost as good as "Bullet Train."
And then I saw "Midsommar," C,
That is a C.
That movie, and some people would say
that's the best movie of the bunch.
That movie is poop for girls.
- Yeah, I don't fuck with Ari Aster.
Never really watched this stuff, but--
- You don't see Hereditary?
- Nope.
Haven't seen even the Tale of the Johnsons
or whatever it's fucking called.
- Yeah, well, something's wrong
with the Johnsons or whatever.
Yeah, that short film is really disturbing
'cause it does, it's like,
I don't know.
There's something about,
it's not disturbing what happens in the movie,
it kind of just gets in your head that you're like,
what if I have a son who just gets bigger than me?
Like, that's terrifying.
'Cause then at that point it's like,
yeah, he might as well fucking fuck you all the time.
Like, it doesn't, who cares, right?
Right, what are they gonna do?
You already lost, as soon as your son,
as soon as my son hits 5'10",
which by the way, I'm specially breeding
to make sure that happens.
Right.
I'm done.
He's the dad now.
Yeah, there's nothing I can do.
- Get a job.
- Yeah, exactly.
I'm gonna be-- - That's what I would say.
First time my son says, "Dad, I'm taller than you,"
I'm gonna say, "Yeah, get a job."
- He's gonna tell me to get a job.
That's what I'm scared of,
is that I'm gonna be doing chores.
I'm gonna get grounded. - I'm gonna start paying
you rent. - I'm gonna be like,
"You can't ground me," and he'll walk up to me,
and I'm gonna be like tit height at him,
and he's gonna be like, "You sure about that, little guy?"
- He's gonna start going-- - And I'll go,
"I don't know." - "Don't make me count to three."
'Cause literally, yeah, yeah, yeah, go to your room.
I don't wanna go to my room.
Go to your room.
I wanna watch TV.
Okay, I'll go to my, whatever.
I'll go to my room.
- I'll watch TV with your mother.
- Yeah, I'm gonna watch TV with mom.
No, that scares me, man.
- Yeah, I mean, obviously, I would want,
if I had a son, for him to be happy, healthy, taller,
bigger dick, just ever,
just full upgrade of the bunch, right?
- Nah.
- But that would suck.
- Yeah, I don't want to be like really badly disabled.
- Okay, go on, I'm listening.
- Well, you know, not really,
but I guess that would solve that one single problem.
- Yeah, you could then beat your son
no matter how big it is.
- Well, I wouldn't even need to, you know?
- Right.
- But maybe I'll just,
I think I talked to somebody about this recently.
I think that I should raise a wimp.
I think I need to raise a wimp.
- Yeah, I was about to ask,
will you guys do the thing where like
the Reddit parents are like, "I'm going to show my kid Game of Thrones and Final Fantasy
and all that shit."
I'm going to be worse.
I'm going to be Dr. Horrible sing-along blog, doing that kind of shit, showing them.
I'm going to show them what's the fucking D&D web series.
I'm going to show them that.
I'm going to show them the Nerdist.
I'm going to be really…
I'm going to be a bad, bad parent.
Red versus blue?
I'm going to show them red versus blue.
Red vs. Blue might be too funny and too for guys, honestly, for my wimp kid.
OK, I'm going to show him
girls.
What about Good Mythical Morning?
Is that I will be showing my child I will be wearing.
We're going to sit down every single night to watch the new Good Mythical Morning
where they eat a fart flavored hot dog.
And I will be covering my eyes and my ears so that none of it gets into my head.
But my kid is going to be completely like stuck to the TV.
I'm going to record Coco Melon onto a VHS and force him to watch that until he's 17 years
old.
Yeah.
I'm going to pretend that's school.
I'm going to tell my kid he's homeschooled and make him watch the same four Coco Melon
things until he's graduated.
And then just one day just be like, just drop him off at the SAT and make him take it.
And he'll just completely ace it.
What's stopping someone from just doing that to a kid?
Nothing.
Literally nothing.
Yeah, no, you can get – basically you can get – trust me, I'm very intimately familiar
with homeschooling in America.
You can get what is essentially like audited by – I guess it's Child Protective Services,
but they can come through and say like, "Okay, what are you teaching your kid?"
And if you say like, "I'm teaching them basically nothing.
They're looking at their phone all day."
Yeah, but at what point does that happen?
Because you can just, I mean, how many years does it have to pass for them to be like,
"Hey, this kid that was registered as born 10 years ago hasn't been registered anywhere."
So it depends on the state. In North Carolina, we had to do
EOGs, which were the same tests that they administered to kids in public school at
the end of the year, like basically just standardized testing. We had to do it and
send it in via mail. And if you just colored in all the O's and P's and sent it back, then
they would be like, "Okay, there's a serious problem." But I knew some people whose parents
would just fill that out for them and then send it back because they didn't want to like...
Smart.
Yeah.
School doesn't matter anymore because of the AI stuff.
Yeah, TikTok.
Yes.
Yeah, TikTok, the algorithm.
Yeah.
Yeah, you can learn everything there.
I don't think you can learn much on TikTok.
No, you can't.
You can learn about giants.
You can.
That is true.
You can learn about how to fight a dog.
Yep.
Yeah, somebody told me a dog fighting story.
Not dog fighting, but they got fought.
They got bit by a dog.
They got into a fight.
They got lost.
They got...
Pretty much, yeah.
They got fought by a dog.
Some crazy dog fought my mom.
But yeah, he was telling me that a dog, he was a very nice guy, but he really messed
up.
He stayed at an Airbnb for 10 days, and day two, I think he said, he was walking outside.
It was like an Airbnb on the property of the house, the owner.
He said that he was walking outside to his car and their pit bull named Sergeant ran
up and bit his knee and like drew blood.
He ended and he was like, "Oh my God, did you get money?
What the fuck?
That's crazy."
He was like bragging.
He was like, "Yeah, yeah, I basically got a refund for the whole Airbnb."
I was like, "Are you kidding?
- Dude, sue him for $15,000, okay?
Do you realize how cut and dry of a case that is?
- It is.
- Yeah, I got attacked by a pit bull in true blood
and his name was Sargent.
- It has a crew cut.
- He was bred to kill.
Yeah, exactly, he has prison tattoos
all over his fucking paws.
It's like, dude, that is such a layup.
- He's covered in teardrop tattoos.
- Yeah, like, it's not, I just couldn't believe it.
- That happened to my mom. - Yeah, exactly.
and she like milked the,
she was in rehab.
- Yeah, let's like milk your mom.
- Relax, relax.
She was in physical therapy for like eight months after.
Like, oh, I can't work.
- Oh my God.
- Because she got milked?
- No.
- She would be after I milked her.
- All right.
- I'd be wearing those big yellow kitchen gloves
and I'd be milking your mom.
- Yeah, I'm talking about milking my fucking mom.
- I would've used a device.
I would've used a machine.
- You just plug her in.
- Don't worry, I would not be milking her
into any sort of bottle or jar.
I'd be milking that disgusting shit directly into the trash.
(laughing)
I literally would just not want it anywhere near anybody.
So I would be doing the entire world a favor.
I'd be, yeah, I'd be throwing it into a,
one of those toxic waste bags that they put needles in
at the doctor's office.
- Into the ocean.
- Yeah, exactly.
It's a dolphin's problem now.
I don't care about the milk.
- I do think it's also,
I walked the beach the other day
and there's just needle drop-offs over there.
And I'm like, that's nice.
'Cause that's a great place to use intravenous drugs,
I think is like on the beach.
- Imagine how relaxing that is.
- Amazing.
They should get to do that.
- Yeah, who cares?
- Not the Long Beach Beach.
I wasn't very relaxed.
- Definitely the Long Beach Beach.
- It's very stressful.
- Are you excited to not live near any homeless people again?
Are you excited to escape them?
- Yeah, I can't wait to go to New York
where there's no homeless people.
- There's no homeless people around here.
There's one guy that I think, this is actually,
I can't believe I haven't told you guys this yet.
There's a restaurant around here that--
- With a homeless guy, Chuck?
- What's, that would be amazing.
There's a restaurant around here,
I don't even know if like,
this is just me telling this story,
but like it has a detail that I don't want to recreate,
but I think I have to.
There's this guy who, when you eat at this restaurant,
he walks up and he says,
"Hey, do you guys have any money?
I'd like to get something to eat."
And you say no, and then he leaves.
And I've eaten at this restaurant
almost every single time this guy's walked up and done this.
But last night I went to this restaurant
and he walked up and he started doing,
he started doing a voice like he's mentally disabled.
(laughing)
Which he did not have before.
And then when I said, "No, sorry, I don't have any money,"
he started going like, "Uhh,"
(laughing)
pretend crying.
And I was like--
- That's such a good one.
That's so crazy that he thought that he could pull a fast one
and pretend that he was always like that.
But he used to just come up and be like, "Hey, do you have any money for food?"
Yeah, and then you were like, "I caught you. I caught you.
I always see you around here. I never give you money."
A neuro-impaired fellow.
Who's the good guy?
Yeah, exactly. So I called the cops on him.
Yeah, you should.
That's disgusting.
- I think it's cool.
- If he did that, I would give him $10.
- Yeah, I was like, okay, this guy's actually about his shit.
Like, that's cool.
- Yeah.
- And it also made me think--
- You're not truly homeless and begging for money
until you're also pretending to be retarded.
- Exactly, yeah.
Yeah, it was such an advanced move.
I was like, I can't believe I've never seen that before.
I've seen fake veteran.
- Yeah.
- I've seen fake, faking like you lost your legs.
You know, you're just sitting on them.
- Right.
this guy just going full just dee dee dee,
Carlos Macias style.
- Yeah, dee dee dee.
- Right in front of me,
like I didn't see him two weeks ago,
asking me, calling me sir.
It's just crazy.
- It'd be funny if he like got hit by a car
and that's what it's from.
- That's what I was like,
I was like looking, I was like,
is there like, does he have like a fucking
Tom and Jerry lump on his head?
- Yeah, the only like solution for this
is you have to go back tomorrow night
and you have to eat, get approached by him,
and also give him no money,
but see if he does a new routine.
Maybe he switches it up.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Like every week he switches it up.
Like next week he'll be like from Dominican Republic.
- What if he's just a character?
Like he's just trying to get discovered.
You know, like he's an actor.
- Just shows up and he's Obama.
He's doing the Obama voice.
(laughing)
- He's too impressive.
Just seeing which one people give more money to.
It's kind of a good idea.
But yeah, I just couldn't believe that, dude.
I was like, that is just, that's very cool.
- Yeah. - Yeah, that's a great move.
- That's messed up.
Speaking of Obama impressions. - I'm keeping that one
in my back pocket 'til when I'm homeless.
- Speaking of Obama impressions.
- It's coming. - You're never gonna be homeless.
You're gonna be sent to jail for doing gay crimes.
- Yeah. - All right, all right.
- You will either be sent to jail or murdered by a SWAT team.
Those are the two options.
Or you will accidentally click one button
and have 500 people pay to have you killed.
All of these are very true.
I think that's the one that's going to actually going to happen.
Yeah. The last one.
Yeah, it'll be like fucking it'll be Mr.
and Mrs.
Smith style assassins competing to kill you.
None of those things are out of the you know.
Yeah, definitely.
All within the realm of possibility.
Yeah. Wait, which movie is Game Night?
Game night is Fokker and what's his name from Arrested Development.
Rachel, what's her name from the Notebook?
The guy from the dude from New Girl
and that's kind of oh, and then the
the guy who plays football coaches and a lot of things.
So it's really nice with the like, just just put together
like much like B-tier actors and they just like do something kind of fun,
but it's not that good.
No, no, no. It's actually really good. It's like a, uh,
it's a, I highly recommend it actually. It's very funny.
And also it's like one of the few comedies that has like a cool kind of
direction style. Um, oh, and, and, uh,
what's his name from Todd from breaking bad. Isn't it? And he's great.
Okay. I saw it in the theaters and it was a riot.
Speaking of rats, did you see those people on Twitter doing astro-turfing for "Bo is
Afraid"?
No, that's the worst.
No, I think that movie is probably going to be pretty shit.
I'm sure I would like it if I watched it.
Was it the people, they were like, "I was at the theater and somebody stood up and said,
'What the fuck is this movie?'"
Yeah, that.
I think that's so, I think they like paid that homeless guy like $10.
Nobody is going to fucking, who gives a shit about a movie?
I've seen awful movies and never once have I stood up and gone,
that was the worst movie I've ever seen.
Have you guys ever walked out of a movie? No, no.
I walked out of Steve Carell dinner for schmucks and I walked out of the pre the
2018 predator movie.
I think, wait, why? Maybe it did.
Explain why you would walk out of a movie.
I don't understand the logic of walking out.
Two very different reasons, but I did technically walk out of them.
I'm ready.
Dinner for schmucks.
I went and saw it with my mom.
I was 12 years old.
She saw a nipple and said, "We have to leave the theater."
So I count that as walking out.
Yeah.
Predator is because I got a phone call from my professor that I was actively missing a
class, so I left the movie theater to go to the class.
You did just call you directly?
That's crazy.
I what?
- They would call you for you were missing a class?
- He was like a four person class
and he was a cool professor.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah, and the movie theater was in the same building.
- It was a cool professor
and he used to text me all the time.
- I did, he used to text with me.
- He used to chat when I was underage.
- I loved him, his name was Andre.
- I think, wait, now that I think about it,
I think I may have walked out of the movie
because it was too long and I had to be somewhere.
- That's a classic reason.
And I think that movie was one of the Batman ones,
the one that was really long.
I don't know if you like Dark Knight Rises.
Yeah, Dark Knight Rises is the long one.
Yeah, I mean, I liked all of them,
but I was forced to walk out of it
because I was running late for something.
That... Dude.
You know what? It's not even worth saying.
I was going to just say The Dark Knight is such a good movie.
[LAUGHTER]
It's like, yeah, that's good radio.
- That's amazing, that's amazing podcasting.
- That movie is so good.
- The Dark Knight is so good, it actually is dude.
The beginning scene when the grenade pops,
when he pulls the pin on the grenade and it's smoke
and you go, "Ah, wait."
He just wants to be weird.
- I can't think of the other one,
of the Dark Knight trilogy without thinking of that.
- Batman Begins.
- The last one.
I just, whenever I think about it,
I just like started like speaking like Bane to Rex for like the for like the next three nights
What is that
Do you know skeptic the rapper skeptic
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What the fuck is he talking about?
Something racist.
There's no.
Oh, you were.
Yeah, I can tell you guys are saying something very racist.
It's a little bit of a battle rap.
And the guy comes up and he's like, Skepta,
you look like you have AIDS, you look like you have HIV.
We keep saying that to each other.
I don't know this battle rap.
It's a classic.
He says it's a clip from like a, yeah,
it's a clip from like one of those Red Bull like music academy type things where
like, Oh yeah, yeah. He's like, I'm thinking about this guy, you know,
thinking, you know, like he's just like, yeah, I'm going to,
what's the one rapper, what's the one that's like on the dot or something?
Dot battle rapping. I don't know. I used to watch these all the time.
I used to love battle rap.
They're really good and I think Ballarat in Mexico has been having some a moment,
but I haven't really tuned into it at all.
Did you see that the Mexican ice spice ripoff that wraps over the one theme?
No, but that's cool.
What? What is it?
I saw it on Twitter.
No, is she beautiful?
She looks like the other girl from the ice spice video.
What other girl like Pink Panther is?
Yeah, that one.
I love Pink Panther is.
Yeah. I think I'm in love with her.
Oh, she's, she's so pretty.
Well, I got long hair.
What?
She's British.
Are you for real?
I'm completely for real.
What?
There was, there's a clip going around recently where she's, she's on stage
doing like a really bad show to like five people and she's like, I'm British.
start cheering and they're giving him, her nothing at all.
That is such a fucking awful place to be from. Yeah. It's so,
it's so like, you know, I feel like anytime,
if you ever felt like this with British people in America,
when you see British people in America and they all are working like service
jobs, they all are waiters or like yesterday I went to a museum and the,
the clerk at the front was a British guy and I walked up to him and I could just
tell he thinks he's in a movie.
Yeah, literally sitting there and he's like, I don't like
taught. He thinks he's in a fucking movie about his life as
a British guy in America. It's like suck my balls, bro. I live
to a better country and you became worse than our worst
Americans just by
have this this thought today about how America is just like
so much more bigger than the UK like at this point, like they
They think they're like a huge country, like a big power, but I feel like they're completely
–
They suck.
– overtaken by anywhere else.
That's the other thing about British people is they're like – they think Americans
are stupid.
It's like, yes, we have a lot more stupid people because we have 10 times the amount
of people that you do.
So we also have 10 times the amount of smart people.
Actually, I would say we have 20 times the amount of smart people because there's not
very many in the great UK.
also let's just call it Britain it's not very great to me yeah damn very united
either I'd like to yeah and it's hardly a kingdom yeah
yeah well no they don't hold on King now oh yeah she completely got shot in a
Yeah, really fucking funny to joke about her death.
Super funny.
Yeah.
Especially when she died from the vaccine.
To actually joke about a human being's death who literally died because she took the Johnson
and Johnson vaccine.
She was the first person to get it and her heart stopped because there was a bubble.
There's a bubble in that vaccine.
You get the bubble vaccine.
My dad called me when the, it was that like fucking Fox News, like that Fox News story
that was like, the Johnson & Johnson vaccine is like, a lady dies from a stroke from it
or whatever.
Like the first one, like a couple years ago.
Yeah.
Because Johnson & Johnson was the first one where you could just get one shot and that
was it.
Yep.
And my dad called me when that story broke and he was like, "Hey, yeah, just wanted to
let you know."
And it was like he was breaking news to me.
He was like, "I got the Johnson & Johnson vaccine."
Like he was telling me that he was going to die.
Yeah, yeah.
I think he's so sure he's like, yeah.
And so, you know, whatever happens happens.
But I just wanted you to know
that's that's what I got to do.
It was dope.
I remember I got that and then it was like a week later that happened.
I was like, oh, sick.
I don't even know which one I got.
Oh, wait, I do. None of them.
They actually did get nice.
I didn't get a booster, but I did get the
fuck a booster, dude.
- I was like, bro, I was somewhere the other day
and they, I was somewhere, not the other day,
I was somewhere four weeks ago.
I feel like it would have made more sense right now
'cause people are getting sick.
I was somewhere a month ago,
actually the same venue I was at tonight,
and at the door, they checked vaccine cards.
- Oh my God. - And I could not believe it.
I was like, what the fuck?
What kind of communist China deal is this?
This is crazy.
It's literally over.
- Yeah.
- They even, even the government declared it over.
It's over, it's been over.
- I don't know in my mind.
- I got reprimanded by a doctor, by a general physician.
It was like, no, it was like,
I feel like four months ago now,
where I just had like the flu or something.
I was like just feeling sick.
And he was like, okay, do you have your COVID vaccines?
I was like, yeah, I got the two.
He's like, well, you gotta get the boosters.
You ought to get the booster.
So I'm like, yeah, I'm going to do it like it's my dad.
Yeah.
Here's what I say, you ought to pick up a football, homo.
We're going to replace you with a computer in three years, fucking asshole.
Well, he completely cured me anyways, but he was really rude to me that time.
That's the thing about doctors.
They, I hate those bastards because I think they're smarter than anybody, but
then they do literal magic to you somehow and cure every single problem you have.
They just write something on a little piece of paper and I get some pills.
And then I walk away and I'm like, whatever, but I won't even pay for it.
I'm not even going to pay.
I'm going to pay.
It's going to take me 10 years to pay this $100 medical copay.
I have a $100 medical copay that has been sitting in my mailbox,
comes every single month and they say, you better pay this because guess what?
We're adding 30 cents on top of it.
Oh no.
So what's it at this point?
I think it's at a dollar and seven,
$107, something like that.
Oh, and it's been like a year.
It's racking up.
I know.
And you know, that interest compounds.
Yeah.
What do you guys have good credit scores?
Um, I think I do.
Mine goes up and down.
I thought mine was really, really terrible, but it's, I mean, it's not,
It's bad, but it's like 660 or something.
I thought it was like 400.
I don't know how to check mine down here,
but when I went to get a car loan,
they were like, "Yeah, you have amazing credit."
I just didn't have enough capital to the first payment, I guess.
But on credit, I'm completely good because I stay on time on payments.
I have good credit.
What is it? What's the number?
730.
That's pretty good. Yeah.
My problem is
they won't give me
a credit card that matches
what I spend.
Because you already have a
fucked up make 'em up thing.
Yeah. Yeah. Well also, and
this is the thing, is like
I have a child's bank account.
Yeah. Yeah. I literally have like
the one for when you're in college still. Your mom's name is on it. My dad's yeah.
Your dad's name, of course. Just go to another bank. Well, I know but so I've
called them like I called them every six months I'm like hey can you like raise
my credit limit so I don't have to pay it twice a month. Sorry, sorry, sorry, I grew up I'm not a kid anymore.
They do a hard inquiry it lowers my credit score and then they go no. Wow.
Not the last I was in New York, but the time before I was sitting in the Airbnb with Julio
because I had filled out my credit card in like three days and I was like, hey, can we
like, yeah, this is a really low credit score.
$1500 limit or some shit.
Yeah, something like that.
And I called them and I was like, hey, can I get this raised?
And they like, like, no.
Wow.
No, you got to like, two guys.
on. You're supposed to only use 30% of your credit, right? That's like the thing.
I guess. Who cares?
We're trying to move and this guy who's going to be a potential landlord made us do like,
he's just making us send all this and we're running into the same problem where we sent him like the
Patreon and stuff and we're like, here's how much we make every month and he, on the phone right in
front of me, he's like, well, how do I know that you didn't just create this website and then just
just put some random number on it.
- That's crazy.
- I was like, dude, why would I do that?
It's not like I'm signing a lease,
I have to pay the fucking rent every month.
- You know how those people, those people actually,
it's funny, they don't trust anything on a browser,
but if you send them a PDF,
like one of those invoices that Patreon sends you
that says nothing on it, but just like Patreon.com
and just have the number on it,
they're like, oh yeah, for sure, man,
This is how much money you make.
Yeah, because it's a file.
Yeah.
He was like, he made me send my unfiled 2022 corporate tax, which has no, it's just a filled
PDF.
I could make it say that we make $10 million a year.
And he was like, "Oh, okay, okay.
So I'm starting to see, get an idea of your finances."
Like, bro, there's no difference.
And also I sent him bank statements and he was like, "I've never heard of this bank."
It's like, OK, you have a computer, man.
Yeah. No, he's.
He's old, though, so, you know, bastard.
I mean, that's what happened to us out here is we had to pay our whole year
of rent up front because they were just like, yeah, I don't trust
what you're sending me. Yeah.
You know, it's sad, dude.
We need the creators to step in.
Creators need to handle need to be landowners and we need to be landlords.
We do need to be.
That's why I am.
I will bravely
the next three years become a landlord.
I would love because I'm understand.
I would be a good landlord
because I'm under because
if somebody comes to me and they say, hey,
I have a I have a very popular
rumble dot com account.
I'll go, fuck it, man.
Live here for free.
I don't give a fucking shit.
Yeah, as long as you're downstairs
screaming into a sure microphone
with a ring light right on you.
I don't care.
Do whatever you want.
Don't even pay the rent.
I support you.
So I would love to speed run zero,
so any percent getting on the hundred worst landlords in New York list.
Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's not enough Jewish names on them.
I think it's pretty easy.
I think it's literally like people are so just babies about it.
Dude, I have a terrible landlord.
I have an awful, awful landlord.
I would never go on a online and complain about it
or start a GoFundMe for paying off the like,
oh, they're not giving me my security deposit.
Who cares, bro?
I mean, I'm also a terrible tenant.
Everybody's a terrible tenant.
You are, everyone is an awful tenant.
Yeah.
I'm putting oil down my drain.
I'm taking my pan--
Dude, I do it every day.
Directly from the stove and dumping
that shit down the drain. I literally saw
something today-- It's still hot.
I saw something today that was like, "Oh, a landlord's raising the rent," and then
a picture of them putting oil in the sink.
And I was like, "Oh, yeah, I forgot you're not supposed to do that."
I do that every single day.
Yeah, I do that all the time.
God bless my poor landlord Joanne who has to, when I leave here, she thinks I've been
a good tenant.
She thinks I've been a pretty good tenant.
When I leave here, she is going to raise hell.
She will try to find me.
going to be hiring private investigators to come and slash my tires.
No, you know what's going to happen?
She you're going to leave and she's going to just rent to someone else
and then they're going to have to deal with the consequences
because she didn't do any.
You're right. It's true. You're right.
That's the real landlord.
Well, that just makes me happy then, because I've never met those people
and I've met her a couple of times.
So I can just pretend that they're going to be
some really evil people coming in here.
But I think they might be.
It's definitely possible.
Yeah, yeah, probably evil apartment.
Yeah, well, there's also like like I'm excited to move.
Yeah, dude, you're just going to
my apartment is too small. It's too small.
Yeah. Are you getting a second bedroom area?
I hope so. Our lease is up in
July, so I got to start looking for shit soon.
But everything around here is getting so expensive that I just got to.
We just got to jump on something.
But I want to stay in the area.
I don't want to have to move to fucking...
Although I do kind of...
Why don't you just move into a big house?
That would be paradise.
That'd be so...
I know somebody who lives in a brownstone with...
It's him and his wife and then two other couples,
and they each get like a floor of the brownstone.
I was like, "Oh, that's so cool."
I was like, "How much do you pay for rent?"
And he said, "Well, the entire building is about $11,000 a month."
I was like, "Oh my God."
What the fuck?
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Is that crazy?
$11,000 a month for a fucking building?
I mean, it is like, you know, basically six bedrooms over.
It's a giant house.
But yeah, it kind of blew my mind that he's like a working professional
who lives in like a TikTok hype house type rental situation.
Well, I don't think they do TikToks in there.
I think they just do their normal life.
I don't fucking know what they do.
Okay. But yeah, I don't think I could do, I think once I've got,
now that I've gone, no roommates, I don't think I never do them again.
It's just too crazy.
I love having roommates. I like the chaos.
I hate roommates. It, uh, it reminds me, well,
you're a single child. That's why you like roommates.
Yeah. Might have something to do with it. You just got analyzed full.
- Yeah, put your front back in your pants, all right?
- Yeah, okay.
Roommates are brothers and sisters.
- Let's clap for that. - Okay.
- That is an amazing point that I just made.
- I mean, I'm clapping, but I don't really,
I can't really understand.
- Roommate, wait, I'm standing up.
Roommates are brothers and sisters, okay?
'Cause what do brothers and sisters do?
- They just fuck everything up. - They lift you?
- They, here's what brothers and sisters do.
They're in the room over and they're fucking
the shit out of each other as loud as they possibly can
to interrupt you rewatching The Office.
Okay?
That's what brothers and sisters do.
So that's exactly how roommates are brothers and sisters.
And I have no interest in ever having brothers and sisters
again for as long as I live.
I left my brothers at home.
I don't want to ever see them again.
- Yeah.
- I think it's different when you have space
between the rooms.
'Cause I know what you mean.
Being loud as fuck.
- You live in a hallway.
- I do live in a hallway.
You should be, of all people, to complain about roommates,
it should be you, because we can't go one single episode
without one of them sasquatching behind you.
(laughs)
- It's the same one, you know.
- Yeah, he just likes walking.
(laughs)
He always has something to, he literally,
during the day, when he knows that you're gonna record,
he sees you plug in your microphone in the morning,
and then he starts setting up stuff in either side of,
either room on either end of you,
so that he can go and be like,
oh, sorry, I have to get my water bottle.
'Cause he loves it so much, he loves the attention.
- He does love the attention. - Yeah, he does.
- But do you know what I mean?
I just feel like roommates are,
they're just, it's just so nice being alone.
And you're never alone with roommates.
- That is true.
I will say, it does suck to never just like,
sit in your underwear.
- Or sit, dude, I'm, but today I was sitting on my couch
and I had my dick out.
And I'm not gonna lie, it was morning
and I had about a half of a chubby morning wood type thing.
I was doing the crossword on my couch,
dicking balls out, and I was scratching him, dude.
And I was getting under him, too.
I was getting really dangerously close
to my morning asshole.
And then I look through my window
and I see a big fat guy, also naked,
looking in his fridge who just looks right at me.
And I didn't even feel embarrassed.
I was like, I was like, you know what?
I mean, I've seen this guy naked plenty of times.
I was like, I don't think I've ever been naked in front of him.
But so this is what's great about not having roommates.
I can see that. I'll never see that fucking guy.
The only time I'll ever if I saw him on the street, I wouldn't recognize him
because I would never if he walked around with a window in front of him, I might.
But if he's just walking down the street, I'm not going to know who it is.
If a roommate sees my dick and balls, I'm moving.
I don't I can't do that because they're going to fall in love with me.
It's too scary.
They're going to try and take your pills.
Exactly.
And they had roommates.
I don't know.
I do.
I do the move where I slip my hand down
under the elastic and scratch my balls
and then kind of leave it there after your card.
Yeah.
So just like you get caught, just like you're like, oh.
Wait, you put your ball sack hand on the back of your neck?
Well, just pull it away and then like,
scratch my head like I wasn't doing anything.
Yeah.
Do you want to know your use?
Grab some candy with the same hand and just eat.
Hey, why do the Twizzlers smell like a shoe?
My balls smell completely normal.
Balls do not smell normal in any way.
Balls are the part of your body.
Your balls have been grafted on by aliens.
They're not part of a human anatomy.
I think they're not real.
I think balls are really, really bad.
Sometimes my ball, I will shower and get out of the shower
and I smell my balls.
I'm like, I wash them with chemicals.
- Do you wash your dick?
- Wait.
- Oh, dude, yes I wash my dick.
- What?
- Yeah, balls just smell basically like shit all the time.
- Not all, not all.
- That's what you're talking about.
- You smell weird.
You got something in you.
You got the stink in you.
No, no, no. Like you wash your balls for like.
Basically, it's got to be a diet, and then you get out of the
and then you get out of the shower, almost to the fridge,
you get out of the fridge and you your balls just smell like actual human shit
and they stink up every room you walk into.
OK, you don't have this experience.
No, I know.
I well, I don't shower myself, so true.
I can't really relate.
Speaking of shit that smells bad,
I went to the dentist for the first time in like five years.
Okay. Did you have an abscess?
No, it was fucked up.
They said I was fine.
Oh no. Dentistry is such a scam.
It's such a scam.
Fake doctor, fake doctor.
But you know why it's a fake doctor?
I haven't brushed my teeth twice a day in five years.
Yeah. I brush my teeth.
You know when I brush my teeth?
When someone complains.
That's when I brush my teeth.
If my wife says, "You smell like shit," I go,
"Time to brush my teeth."
- Yep.
And I guarantee you, your teeth are not only white-ish,
but you probably have no cavities.
- I don't have a single cavity.
I've never had one.
- Yeah.
- I have strong teeth.
Peasant's teeth, they call it.
- It's a power of will.
- Yeah.
And also, as I established earlier, I do not eat candy.
- I eat fucking candy.
huge. I've every single day I've had at least one monster or
something similar. Yeah, there have been days where I've drank.
I've probably in between teeth brushings had 13 cans of drink.
Yeah, it's crazy.
My drink coffee.
I've had beer.
I've had monster.
I've had diet Coke.
So this is going to come down to two things.
Which one?
I think you do have, like, genetically,
there's great teeth maybe.
But also you should probably consider
also getting like a second opinion.
Because that--
- It's a bad tentative.
(laughing)
- Probably that dentist just doesn't want to do the job
that's your disgusting mouth.
- No, they were literally trying to do more to me
and they couldn't get it cleared by the insurance.
- It was pissing them off that you had said that.
It literally was. They came by like four different dentists came by while I was
sitting in the chair and were like, "Hey, open up for a second." They like poked
around in my mouth and like took pictures and they were like, "Nope." Because they
were like, "We should give you a deep clean."
Do you go to like a school? Like a dentist building? What kind of situation is this?
So you just go to an office with like the one dentist?
I think dentists usually, it's like lawyers, it's usually like two dentists.
yeah there's there's like two dentists and four of their whatever yeah and the
other thing I forgot is that uh when they take pictures I gag I have a really
bad gag reflex and a whole ton of pictures taking x-rays you know well
though when they put the thing in your mouth it's in your the flesh gets in
your mouth and the light makes you gag. Oh, the little thing they put on your tongue. Yeah. Okay, you gag at the photos of you that they show you.
Oh my god, get that away. I was just thinking about how bad I would be at sucking dick, which thankfully I don't have to do. I think I'd be pretty good at it.
You do? Sometimes I think that, but you know, then I, they try to take pictures of
my mouth and I was gagging.
I would be like full, like opening up my mouth.
I'd be like gagging and stuff.
- If it was--
- Noah's dick looks like a pancake
that you gotta open your mouth up.
- Yeah, if it was like a small,
just a little piece of candy and it was sweet,
I think Rex would be really good at it.
(laughing)
- Yeah, if sucking dick was eating a piece of candy,
I would probably have a lot of prior experience.
- I guess, what do I have in here
that I could demonstrate on?
Do I have a cucumber?
- Hold on. - You didn't even talk about
what you was missing for a week.
- I feel like I'm really good at eating a lollipop.
- Wait, what does that mean?
- Like I'm so good at just like not biting it
and not rubbing it on my tongue.
- You know, I was about to pick up a carrot
and put it backwards into my mouth
because it's a thick part and show myself choking,
but I thought of two things.
Number one, what if the carrot breaks off
and I just die on camera sucking on a carrot
because I choked on it?
- You're not gonna swallow it.
- Well, but yes I was.
That was basically the entire point that I was making
was that I was so good at sucking dick.
- Okay, so bring up the carrot.
- No, also I realized that I just got married
and I just shouldn't be doing kind of stuff like that.
- Oh, congrats, a married man.
- Congratulations.
- I was a big wedding, a big huge wedding.
- It's time to honor my wife by not sucking carrot.
- That honestly is probably the most husbandly thing
I've done ever is stop myself from sucking off a carrot
on camera.
It's pretty wise of me.
Yeah, you're a good man.
Caleb Piltz.
I'm a very good man.
How was the wedding?
How was the big event?
Nice.
Went to the courthouse, got hitched.
Yeah, so you saw the 45 out there?
Oh, so that was when we went and got our license, 45 was
getting arrested.
But this time there was just a whole lot of fucking fatties
getting married that we were sitting behind.
And it was a hot day too, so they were sticking together.
Yeah.
But it was a good time.
I wore a suit.
That's very sweet.
I wore a suit and I,
I don't know why I went full black suit.
Like I was at a funeral.
Yeah.
So all my photos I have a black tie on.
I just look like I'm at a funeral.
But, you know, I kind of went for the look.
I was thinking like, I'm going to look like a groom
that's on top of a wedding cake, you know, like that.
You look like John Wick.
I looked very John Wick, Lex Friedman style.
Yeah.
Just a kind of a crappy black suit.
I got it at Banana Republic the other day.
I think so.
I think I was wondering, now that I own a suit,
I've never, I guess I had like a suit from fucking Primark
that was like 50 bucks when I was in college.
Yeah.
I own a suit that like fits me okay?
Should I just be a full suit comedian
and I wear a suit everywhere I go?
Anytime I do stand up I wear a full suit.
- You should be one of those people that are like,
I don't know why men dress like this.
What would the men should stop dressing like this?
- What happened to men?
- Just walk around like that with some sneakers on.
- I'm wearing some suit that's like fucking six inches long
on every single, what happened?
My sleeves are over my head,
like I'm a really shy girl in a hoodie.
What happened to men?
Men are just, what is wrong with men?
Men used to dress properly.
You're drenched in sweat.
Completely frayed.
Yeah.
It's a wool suit.
Completely frayed ends on the legs because I've been stepping on all the,
I've been stepping on the legs this entire time.
You keep, yeah, you keep stepping on a, on water as well.
So it's completely just wet and stinky.
Different color.
I'm wearing Vans.
Yeah.
What happened to men?
Men used to dress nicely.
Nobody wears a suit anymore.
- Wearing a suit is like the opposite
of what wearing a suit used to be.
- Maybe I'll wear one tomorrow.
- It used to be only important guys wore suits.
- Actually, I just decided I'm going
to wear my suit tomorrow.
- To the show.
- We're recording tomorrow, I'm gonna wear my suit.
And this will come out after that, no, before that.
- Before that, yeah.
- I will wear my suit tomorrow.
That's at least the top part.
- Beers we drank, exclusive.
You should wear shorts.
- You should.
- And then stand up.
- I have black shorts. - Suit and shorts is dope.
that's a fits the top part of my suit.
It's actually not a bad idea.
This is the suit.
I went shopping for a wedding and, uh, you know, when you, when you go to those
stores, there's like a guy who like attends to you, right?
Cause you know, you don't know, no one knows anything about like nice clothes.
Right.
Yeah.
And the guy that was attending me was like a cool black guy.
And, uh, he's like, I think you would do really well in like a
salmon suit with like black shorts.
And I was like, I'm not you, man.
I can't do that.
I have the evil version of this story from when I bought a suit the other day.
I ended up buying my suit from Banana Republic and it was on sale.
But at first I went to Macy's because I knew they had cheaper suits and I went to the Ralph
Loren part of the thing and this guy started helping me.
His name was Marvin and he was just being such a bitch.
Like such a bitch dude.
I was like, he was like, "What size pants do you wear?"
I said 31, he said, "Really?"
- Small guy.
- And I was like, "Yeah, 31."
He said, "Lift up your shirt."
And I showed him my waist and he was like, "You're a 34."
(laughing)
- You fat fucking piece of shit.
- I hate this guy.
- What the fuck?
- Yeah, but then I was like,
he was saying like, "I think that you're gonna wear a 42R."
I was like, "Uh, the 40?"
Or no, he was like, I think you would need a 40R, sorry.
And I was like, the 42 I think looks more
like it would fit me better.
And he was like, okay.
And then I went into the dressing room
and he came in and I was like,
yeah, I think you're actually right.
I think the 40 is probably gonna fit me a little better.
He's like, hmm, okay.
So you didn't trust me
and now you just needed to find out for yourself.
- What the fuck?
- And I literally did this, I handed him the suit.
I said, Marvin, you are very, very unpleasant
and I have no interest in buying a suit from you.
And I left.
- Damn, that's powerful. - And I left.
- Filled him with kindness.
- I did not, I didn't wanna yell at him,
but also that's very not me.
I literally had like, my heart was racing
because I was just so mean to that guy.
But also, like dude, fucking kill yourself, bro.
You're not a gentleman.
You work at Macy's and you sell Ralph Lauren's
like overpriced suits that cost $14 to make.
You're not like a fucking like, oh, well, you trust me.
I'm a Sultan.
Like, dude, you're a fucking, you're a dickhead, right?
You used to work at GameStop.
And then one day you were like, I know how to tie a tie.
I'm gonna go work at Macy's.
- Yeah.
- Marvin's like, fucking kill yourself, Marvin.
You are a dickhead.
- Marvin, if you wanna come on the show next week,
you can come, say you just heard the story.
We can debate Caleb on whether or not he's fucking stupid.
I'm picking a suit.
- I hated Marvin, dude.
It just made me so mad.
But that's my upper limit of how rude I can be to somebody
who is working at their job, I think,
is just being like,
'cause usually I feel like I'm so accommodating.
I'm so good at, if somebody's a very rude waiter,
I actively am like, you know what?
It's a hard job. - Rude waiter is crazy.
- Rude waiter, you know what, I'm part of the problem.
If somebody's a rude waiter, I tip them more than I would
at just a nice person.
- Yes, yes.
- Because I'm like, you're gonna be rude to me?
Check out, check, 35%.
That's what I think about how rude you are.
I'm such an idiot. - Rude waiter is awesome.
- I fall for it.
So this guy thought that he was doing rude waiter to me.
- You don't tip your suit guy.
- He was just calling me fat and stupid.
All right, I have to go to bed.
I can't even think about Harvey anymore.
See you guys next week.
Bye.