(sipping)
(burping)
- You're listening to Beers We Drink,
America's number one beer podcast.
(record scratching)
(upbeat music)
- What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
(burping)
- This is a journey into--
- Into the middle of--
- Plain and clean--
- Bud Light.
Food Rippin'
Beers we drank, motherfucker,
with Juvio, Caleb and Rex.
And we're back.
I already opened mine, but I faked
the sound for you guys.
I just opened mine just then.
Guys, check this out.
Well, you still have homeless hangers.
Bud Light Lime.
Oh, yeah, these.
Yeah, I spent all
I spent this whole week working on
the new set, which will be out by the time this comes out.
Yeah, I talk about it, but I used like this really
heavy duty glue and instead of spreading it with like
like a spreading tool, like you would use for like like mud, like spackle.
Yeah, I used my fingers and it was really, really smart of me.
And then I used them a little bit.
And then I was like, oh, this shit's not coming off.
Like I had the idea, I was like, "Oh, I should use a spackling knife."
And then I was like, "Well, it's already on my hands, whatever."
So I just fucking, my hands are just covered in this shit.
And it's coming off like a second,
a second layer of skin on top of my skin.
Real blue collar worker type of shit.
Yeah.
That's why I got myself a Bud Light Lime.
This is the first beer maybe I've ever deserved.
Yeah.
In my entire life.
Every other beer has been on credit.
And this one is...
I actually earned this somewhat this week.
Earned it and more.
Me and Brian just sat in the office
and he came and helped out.
And we just painted and glued stuff.
You made Brian work?
He wanted to.
He's so bored. His girlfriend was out of town.
He brought beer over.
We listened to Morgan Wallen
for like four and a half hours.
It was fucking awesome, dude.
He's a man.
Yeah, it was a good time.
But I will say I can see the blood.
I crushed my finger today.
Oh, enough to bleed.
Yeah, you know,
unpacking.
OK.
Oh, you know, all your weights,
brand new look, Rex is finally settled and he has a microphone.
Yes. And it's a small office.
No different than the.
Yeah, it's almost sounds worse than the AirPods did.
-Which is kind of impressive. -Why does it sound so bad?
I mean, it just needs to be turned up, I think.
-It's very quiet. -I think you need to just talk,
you need to start talking to the right thing.
-Like, have it like this. -I'm talking, I literally,
it's like in my mouth.
-I don't know what you want from me. -Yeah, you've been,
this is better, but you were talking into the,
into the mute button.
Yeah, you're talking into the, into the top.
-You got to talk into the-- -So, like this.
-This is bad. -Yeah, that's bad.
-This is good. -That's perfect.
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah, good, I guess it's good.
-That is perfect. -Oh, no.
Okay, well, hold on.
Caleb, can I get your honest opinion on something
while Rex works on his stuff?
Shoot, you know I'm a straight shooter.
Who's got the worst mustache now?
Between you two?
'Cause mine is gone.
Yeah.
Definitely you, man.
Me?
Your mustache is fucking terrible.
Yeah.
Rex's looks like it's only coming on the hiller part.
Well, I did that on purpose.
That's what we say about yours, man.
Yeah.
You can't just take that.
No, but mine's fully developed at this point.
You're this is not.
That was last week.
You know, it looks even more.
It looks like a Hitler in the middle of the
media, ultra wide Hitler, like a food.
My drink today is homemade grog.
What's in it?
It fucking
beer concentrate.
You're a liar.
It's OK that you said that you can't drink right now.
That's a gas.
I got to have a problem.
- I gotta come clean.
My homemade grog has no grog.
- So what is it?
- I think it's just like lemonade and like
cucumber, cucumber?
How do you say that word in English?
- Cucumber?
- It's yummy.
- How are you saying it?
- Okay.
- He said cucumber.
- We're moving past that.
- Cucumber.
- I am ESO and I am under painkillers.
I had a surgery recently.
No one even asked me about that.
- Well, no, but you didn't know.
I didn't even know you had a surgery
until you said tonight I had a surgery.
- But I didn't care.
- What was the surgery?
ASL's tear from duck heads?
- I went to the dentist and he told me--
- He told me it was ASL.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I didn't put up my ASL.
That's not a real thing.
I went to the dentist.
- Oh, I pulled an ASL cig, you cop.
(laughing)
- I went to the dentist and he said
I had stinky tooth syndrome.
- Oh, you had a rotten tooth.
I had a stinky tooth syndrome and you have to drill it
to the core and destroy it and make a new one.
- Root canal, they call that.
- Yes. - That's what they did.
And he did it and he destroyed it and it completely hurts.
And I don't wanna drink beers while I'm still recovering.
- I'm not gonna call this a surgery.
I think that you really, you're--
- I don't think it's a surgery, but it still pains me
and I still have to be careful for the next couple,
like two or three days.
So I'm gonna take it easy.
- So you could die?
I couldn't, I don't think so, no.
- Or get infected and die.
- Talk into the front of the microphone, we can't hear you.
- I feel like we should-- - Just move it to be
in front of you.
Why are you having this weird angle?
- Like a corn cob.
Is this fine? - Yes.
- Is this good?
- It's too loud now.
- Look at what I'm, look at how he does it.
- Like this, like this.
- Okay, okay.
- There we go, perfect, perfect.
- I'm not a podcast professional.
- You kind of, you are, you are now.
- I've done maybe one, two of these.
- You've been jumped into the cabal.
This is our like 35th episode or something.
- Don't you hold like talks every single Thursday
to your cult? - Yeah, but no one gives
a fucking hello sound.
And I do that through a VPN. - Okay, this just means
that nobody is hearing you when you talk
and they're just pretending that they do.
- That might also be true.
- Yeah, all of your employees are just sitting there
like, "Uh-huh, yeah, play Tetris on there."
- Do you think they hate you?
Do they think, they're like, "Oh, I fucking hate my boss.
"My husband's a boss."
- Oh, of course they hate, everybody hates their boss.
- I'm beloved first of all.
I hate Cameron and Patrick.
I hate Caleb.
I'm the type of boss that's like,
oh, you want to go on vacation for a week
and you're telling me a day before you leave?
Yeah, go for it.
Have fun.
See, if you were my boss,
I'd say my boss is such a fucking pussy.
(laughing)
He won't even say no to my vacation requests.
Why would I say no?
What a loser.
Because they got a job to do.
They got work.
So?
I got work, but I don't do it.
Fuck you.
Well, you're the boss.
You're not supposed to do any work.
Wait.
I've just come around.
I think he's a cool boss.
- Yeah, I'm cool. - Wait, actually, no.
If you're my boss and you're like,
"I'm not doing any work, I want to kill you.
"I want you to die."
- Well, I do work, but the most important thing
is I'm smarter than everyone,
but just by like this amount.
- Yeah, just not enough to know how to work a microphone.
- So it's like any time they run into something
they can't figure out, you know,
that requires a brain, not talking into a microphone,
I can help them, and they think I'm smart, they respect me.
You, on the other hand, are teaching me
about the microphone.
So you're the little tiny sliver, smarter than me.
- Lowly, lowly stupid skills.
- Right, I'm an entry level podcaster.
I'm getting $8 an hour.
- Yeah.
- So I've made a total of $11 for the past three months.
- We have determined that we are blue collar workers
and both me and Kayla have the same amount of real work.
- Well you're a black collar worker
because you're wearing a black shirt.
You're wearing a black t-shirt.
- It almost feels like you were gonna say something else
and then bailed yourself out there.
- That is not true.
- Okay.
- I promise you, that was the whole thought I had in my head.
- Okay, well that was such a useless thought, I guess,
that is why it led me to believe
that maybe you had something more planned.
- Well this brings me back to what I initially
wanted to talk about before you chewed me out
about my mic usage, which is that we were recording
on a Tuesday night when all of us were--
- Whoa, breaking the fourth wall,
- What's your fucking problem?
- Almost fucked out, is that what you said?
- Fucked up.
- I didn't say fucked out.
- You're kind of fucked out.
- How are we fucked up?
I just came back from the park
at a lovely dinner, Mexican food.
- What do you have?
- I had a steak quesadilla with extra jalapenos
because I like it spicy.
- Whoa.
- Sounds yummy.
- So what?
- Why is this a fucked up day?
- I moved, I slept four hours.
- You moved two weeks ago.
- This is a lie.
- Yeah, but my stuff came today.
- He had to move twice.
- I had to set up my desk.
- He had to move his body and then his items.
- Right.
- His old inventory appeared today.
- Which is painful.
It's a stressful, long day.
You have poop tooth.
Poop mouth.
- I did have poop tooth.
- That just got solved and now you can't drink.
- That was so fucked up.
I could swear that my breath stank for like two weeks or so.
And I was like, "What the fuck is it?"
I'm brushing my fucking teeth.
And then I went to the dentist
and he completely drilled my shit.
And he was like, "Yeah, it's completely black in there."
And it stank so bad.
- It's as black as a bean.
- It was as black as a bean
and he took all of it out.
It was a lot of it.
And it was completely stinky.
And I was like, "Oh, this is where my stink comes from."
- I hate the dentist.
- I am stink free.
- That's amazing news.
I hate them too, but you kind of have to go.
I've been having a really bad breath in the morning.
Maybe I have a destroyed tooth.
Here's the thing.
I thought that I had stink tooth syndrome, poop mouth,
however you want to call it.
And I hadn't gone to the dentist in like four years.
And I went in and they were like, no, you're fine.
Yeah. You need to brush your tongue.
That's probably what it was.
No, they were just like, yeah, you're fine.
there's nothing, there's literally your teeth are fine.
And I'm like, I can, I have dreams every week where they fall out.
Do you?
Well, that's a stress thing.
That's a different thing.
No, that's my brain telling me my mouth is poopy.
No, that's the most common stress dream is teeth falling out of your mouth.
I've never experienced that.
People have been having this dream for like 150 years.
Yeah, because 150 years before that, their teeth just fell out already.
this is like the post-industrial revolution.
This is the stress stream that people have,
is that their teeth fall out of their face.
And I don't really have that much,
but I have dreams where I,
all of my dreams are mission impossible,
but it's never, I never win at the end.
I always am trying to stop a terrorist attack,
trying to defuse a bomb. - So it's just an impossible
mission? - It's just, yeah.
(laughing)
Yeah, it's impossible.
It's impossible mission.
And a bomb kills me.
But it's it's some kind of nuclear.
It's like a dirty bomb.
You know that.
And I'm trying to defeat
some kind of terrorist organization,
probably the IRA.
Wow.
What was that scary noise?
See, that's the kind of I'm also skittish.
I've been thinking about this recently.
I think that I manifest my stress
in the fact that if somebody like
any given person could go, ah,
and I will jump out of my chair, my eyebrows fly off my face,
and if I had hair, it would turn into spaghetti.
I have a question.
Have you thought about, maybe in this scenario,
maybe you are actually the terrorist?
- Okay. - Would a terrorist try to defuse a bomb?
I'm a really bad terrorist.
I'm kind of a Hanna-Barbera style, can't-win terrorist.
Maybe just like a facade, it's like, "Oh, yeah, let me defuse this bomb."
but you actually want to blow up the school.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that's maybe that.
Or it's like, yeah, I'm diffusing a bomb
and I look around and I realize I'm in a cave,
but it's my home.
I'm living in a cave, an Iron Man one cave.
Well, you're like you're collaborating with other terrorists,
so they plant the bomb, right?
But they don't know how the bomb works.
So you're the bomb defusal expert and you set it up to blow up
and then you blow yourself up so no one finds out.
The only people who ever die in my dreams though
from all of these massive--
Sometimes it's a natural disaster, a giant wave or something.
It's always only affecting me and like five people that I know.
-Right. -Oh.
It's never a world-destroying kind of drama.
It would really suck if a nuclear bomb hit New York
and it just killed like you and Patrick and--
-Yeah, you'd just be bored. -Like Brian.
-That would kill my life as well.
-Like a nuclear bomb hits and it just kills your close eight on MySpace.
-Yes, that would be really, really bad.
That would be a huge bummer.
-It would suck. You'd be like, "Do it someone else."
-Yes.
I guess for Juvio, it would be equally as bad
if me, Cam, and Pat were all murdered
as if the entirety of New York was completely destroyed by a nuclear bomb.
-Yes. I will have to get replacements.
-Who's top of the list?
-You would be Cameron.
I guess I could get-- -I would die in New York.
-No, but this is in a scenario where only me, Cam, and Pat die.
-Top three. -I think I could do Jacques
from Second Arrangement as Patrick.
-Yes, for sure.
Good luck finding another me though.
-Kayla, do we know a single other bald guy?
- Well, bald is not my only thing I have going on.
- Oh, I guess I could just ask that guy from the yard.
- You could ask Slime?
- Yeah, I'll just ask Slime.
(laughing)
I think he would do it.
- He might do it, yeah.
- Out of charity?
- Yeah, exactly, yeah.
- He just likes the show enough, yeah.
- Yeah, he'd just fucking fly over once a week
and do that, private jet status.
- Yeah, so that's my pockets of a list too.
I haven't looked at your mustache, but you have like the undercut of Hitler mustaches.
Alright, let's move past this stupid joke.
I will say that Rex's mustache is looking a little bit Hitlerian.
Yeah, here's what happened, right?
You have a full, like if you did just the Hitler it would be, like with Jubio it would
be funny.
That's the savior right there.
The little soul patch.
savor, the flavor saver.
See, cause here's what happened, right?
I just, I got way too into shaving.
Cause it just felt so nice to feel the skin against the air again.
And then I kind of like did like this part kind of brought this part in and I
kept bringing in a little bit more and I was like, uh, oh, you hit the Hitler zone.
You're on the line.
So I was like, soul pass, little bit of sideburn.
- It doesn't, you only left like the shadows
of where you like, when you unlock a character in the game,
which is like the size of your mustache.
- Yeah.
- And you've yet to unlock them.
- You could have gone Hitler
and you've made a last minute Dave Grohl pivot.
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
- Which people already say I look like, so.
Which I don't, I don't think that's like a compliment.
- You don't look like Dave Grohl.
- Yeah.
I've seen people say it.
Multiple people have said you look like Dave Grohl.
Really? Just because you have long hair?
I think so. Every man with long hair looks exactly the same.
In the same way every bald guy looks the same.
Except for me. But a lot of them do.
I mean, you got put on that account that every bald man is Foucault.
So I don't think you get to save that.
I can do whatever I want. It's America. I'm a small business owner.
but I don't look like Michel Foucault.
I would never look like a man whose name was Michel.
- Yeah. - That's true.
- I have no interest in that.
- If you were to branch out with your--
- C'est l'oeuvre.
- You know, if you were to break out of a,
you know, if you were to start again,
not do some sort of like ball stereotype,
how would you be doing?
- If you could take a pill that shrunk one of your balls
to like--
I don't even care what the second part of this is.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, go ahead, go ahead, go ahead.
- I would do that.
- No, keep going, keep going.
- You could have the most luscious head of hair,
but only one of your balls was like the size of a peanut.
- Dude, nobody knows what my balls are like.
It doesn't matter.
It would take 30 seconds to explain to my wife,
and it's not like she's gonna be like,
"Oh no, you don't have big balls anymore?
"Oh no."
- Well, you have one big ball and one small ball.
They're mixed together.
The smaller I could get my balls, the better.
Balls are the most disgusting mistake God ever made.
I do not want balls.
- What if you have hair, and you take this bill?
- Just for no reason then?
- Yeah, you get one big ball and you go bald.
- See that is a tougher, so if I could,
if you said your balls quadruple in size,
but you get hair. - No, just one of them.
If one ball quadruples in size but I get hair,
I think I would still probably stay bald.
Really?
I'm that serious about not having big balls.
And also, being bald is a disability
that many men live with.
They live amazing lives.
Some of the richest men in the world are bald.
Name three.
Jeff Bezos.
Easy.
Carlos Slim.
Not bald.
He could be.
I don't know what it looks like.
OK, Jeff Bezos, Andrew Tate.
Yeah, OK.
And Jason Statham gets $10 million every Fast and Furious movie.
This guy's rich.
Do you think he's rich?
He makes movies for rich.
Mm, I don't know.
Rich.
Vin Diesel rich.
The Rock is rich.
Rich men.
Well, Rock is, you know, not the same
palette is you.
-So he can pull off being bald. -So we're only saying bald white guys?
-I-- Well-- -What do you mean pull off being bald?
There's nothing to pull off.
It's just a hair-- It's a haircut like every other haircut.
It's not-- I mean, yeah, it's a haircut,
but it's close to the head.
Yeah, it's a very well-done haircut.
A close shave.
-No, I think that-- -Do you think I should go and get my head
shaved by one of these guys with this razor?
No, I think you should get--
-Wait, which guys? -The weave, the little thing they put on
that I've seen on Instagram that's like--
-Oh, the hair system. -Yes.
-Where they just kind of glue a piece of hair to your head. -I want a hair system, man.
-I do not want to do that shit. -How about this?
Would you take a pill that gave you beautiful hair,
-perfect full head of hair-- -What's up with these pills?
--but it also gave your balls the same type of hair?
[laughter]
-So you just grew hair at the same-- -I don't want hair.
I don't like if I would rather be bald than have your hair
Some wizard who isn't me is making these pills. What if you took a pill that I would rather have hair to my chest
Okay, yeah, what if you turn to give you a normal hair?
I wish I had Jubio's beautiful head of hair though.
I'm not saying you have to have my hair, but just any head of hair.
Like the ability to grow perfect hair.
You had literally Jared Leto's hairline.
Giant afro.
Okay.
Do you think I was looking for a giant afro? Done.
Yeah.
Done.
Really?
Stamped and sold.
Yeah.
Afro no legs spell you take that fuck yeah can you imagine how well my
Instagram reels would do if I was a white guy with a giant perfect Afro okay
black dynamite Afro what if the pill wore off and you had the Larry David and I
just I'm running home to do to eat my pills at the right time
- You know, like a Cinderella or whatever.
- You are not a punctual person.
- I am a punctual person.
- You are punctual.
- I'm a very punctual person.
I'm always early at everything.
- Caleb texted me yesterday
because I was running 15 minutes late
and he was afraid of--
- I despise lateness.
It is the number one thing that upsets me that people do.
- Maybe I'm just confusing tardiness with cappiness.
- Tardiness is one thing.
I'll be tardy.
And you're also talking about planning to play video games,
I'm realizing right now.
Which is, yeah, in that sense,
I probably am not very serious about being on time.
- Caleb is often late to play video games.
- I am very, I am often.
- Not only talking about video games,
I'm talking about you would drop out of our plans
when we were in town, when we were visiting.
Multiple times it happened to us.
- Which plan?
- I forgot.
What is kinder?
This is a question I've asked my wife before.
Is it kinder to completely bail on something
or is it kinder to be 45 minutes
to an hour and a half late to something?
'Cause if that is the decision I have to make
between being an hour late to something
or missing out on it completely,
I would rather give the heads up
and say I'm not gonna be there.
'Cause I think that being late
is a disgusting thing for poor people to do.
- I think I'd rather be late.
- Poor?
Rich people are late, poor people are on time,
they don't value their time.
Rich people, no.
- No, poor people spend all day getting all gussied up,
putting on lipstick and deodorant.
- Disgusting. - Rich people just,
they fall out of bed into their Lamborghini,
it's parked next to their bed,
and they drive to whatever they have to do.
- Yeah, that is true. - Poor people
are cutting people off in traffic,
you know what I mean?
- I have been stink maxing lately,
which is, you know, just not really worried about it.
- You've been stink maxing?
- Yeah, you know, just accumulating stigma.
- You can't coin new stuff on here
without screening it, letting us screen it first.
- Well, you're screening it live.
You're screening it right now.
I don't understand. - Stink maxing?
Okay, it's getting denied.
I don't want to, this is not approved.
- I stink max from time to time.
Sometimes I don't shower for days.
- That's it, it's catching on.
- It's not getting, this is not spreading like wildfire.
- It completely caught on.
Yeah, sometimes I just don't feel like showering
because I'm not gonna go outside.
I'm working in my home.
So I just take Max for a couple days.
- And sometimes I go to the deli and I'm stinky.
- No, I am a bath and a shower almost every single day,
both.
- Well, that's because you have to go outside.
- That is true.
And because a couple of times my wife has said,
"I can smell your balls from across the room."
And that really-- - Which is a great smell.
I love the smell of balls. - That really--
This-- (laughs)
- Whoa, wait, wait a minute. - Okay, there's a lot
to unpack in what you just said.
- Bang.
- The soundboard's back.
- I don't have anything. - You have one sound.
(laughs)
- The one that-- - You love the smell of,
you said you love the smell of,
it's okay to love the smell of your own balls.
- Well, that's what I'm saying. - But you said,
"I love the smell of balls."
That's what you said.
- Well, I-- - It is not
Standardized smell my balls you would not like
How do you I mean I can't promise that
You guys want to do a bowl of your balls smell like my balls. What if in a blind smell test?
I do wonder that I wonder if I farted cuz I fart all day long, and I love it
I love sitting in it and stinking up my I'm up
- You're like maxing yourself.
- I live like Trek, I shit and smell it.
I dig my face into the toilet bowl
to get a big huff of my shit.
But if somebody else farted in my room
and it smelled like my fart,
but I thought it was somebody else's,
or if somebody just said, "I farted,
"but I smelled my own fart,"
I think I would vomit.
I think I would actually vomit.
That is so disgusting to me, another person's farts.
- Mine are honestly sublime.
- Okay.
I think.
- Not a fan of my own farts.
First of all, mine smell bad.
- Mine smell so bad.
I am a legendary stinky farter.
- But you still like it.
- People in every era of my life,
I have left a lasting imprint on the person
that I've seen the most in these like four or five year eras.
- Right.
- Where probably one of the three things they know about me.
- All the smelly parts. - The main things.
Yeah, well even this predates baldness.
I've always been, 'cause I used to be vegan.
- Right. - And I think it
completely destroyed the micro whatever in my belly,
and it made some kind of mucinex bugs
that sit around watching TV and scratching their ass.
Have we ever talked about how we deemed,
we named your living room the fart room?
The first time that I went to New York.
- Oh yeah, 'cause you and Noah were in there
just farting for like every single night.
And I would open the door,
I would open the bedroom door
and just get hit by just a wall of just farts
that had just sat in there all night long.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, that's amazing. - Yeah, we'll call it
the fart room.
And then you would come in and you would also fart in there.
And then we would just, "Oh, welcome to the fart room."
and then your wife just hated it.
- Humans are pack animals, what can I say?
I wanted to belong.
- I do think they should bring back sunrooms,
but for communal farting.
- Sunrooms?
- Yeah, you know, like a sunroom.
- Oh yeah, like with screen doors and stuff?
- Right, like a somewhat outdoor,
but enclosed area to release fart.
- This is a good idea.
'Cause I'm never ever going to,
I mean, I've done it before.
but I don't want to go to the bathroom just to fart.
Right.
It feels, I feel embarrassed to be in the bathroom
for five seconds.
'Cause then I feel like I have to commit
to the whole charade.
I have to take off--
Pretend to wipe, yeah.
Yeah, I have to take off five pieces of toilet paper
just in case they weigh it when people leave.
(laughing)
I just don't wanna have to do that.
I've done that in a public bathroom,
when I'm like sitting down to shit
and don't have to shit, just to fart.
Yeah, and you know, you just like you're like and then you drop your phone in the toilet to make it sound like you should
Yeah, just kind of you know, do that and then
Grab some toilet paper, you know, you do the whole thing. Make sure yeah squeaky real
you know make sure they're aware and then kind of
I'm one of those. I'm not a dramatic shitter being a man going into public restrooms my whole life
I have found that there are men in this world who are dramatic shitters who talk to themselves
Come on. Yeah, they go on fuck fuck fuck. They do like a reverse
They do reverse sex sounds they do the inverse of the noises that people make during sex
While they shit and I just don't get that I'm a very stoic
shitter
I think if your shits are not drama-
There's two different types of dramatic shits.
And one of them makes you a stoic shitter,
and the other makes you a dramatic shitter.
If you're a guy who's constantly having, like,
nasty, rancid, fried chicken diarrhea,
[laughter]
that is a dramatic shitter.
If you're a guy that has hard-ass craps that make you bleed,
Really concerning shits. That is a stoic shitter. Nothing surprises you after that.
See, I am a big purveyor of diarrhea.
Oh! You're a purveyor.
I know all about it. And I do a lot of it. I really do.
But I sit there, I look at my phone, I will,
I try to, I watch those perfect loop videos,
and sometimes I'll watch them four or five times
'cause I'm so focused on shitting,
I don't realize it's a loop, you know?
But yeah, I would say I'm very quiet.
You'll never hear a peep out of me.
But maybe, I think this is just a--
I'm grown, I'm brunt.
This is a metric of politeness, I think.
Yeah.
I'm a very polite person.
I have a lot of regard for the people around me
and I don't want to inconvenience people
by saying cuss words while I'm taking a shit.
- I feel like if I'm in a public bathroom
and I'm farting while I'm shitting,
I'm gonna get judged by the other shitters.
- I agree, I don't fart in public restrooms.
I would rather fart, if I'm in a Target,
I would rather fart in the kid's aisle
while I'm playing with some kind of,
pretending I'm buying something for my daughter
and I'm squeezing a toy that makes a noise,
and I go, "Oh, that's an interesting noise
for this toy to make.
It's a talking truck.
It's not something that would make any..."
It has no squeaker in it,
but I'm hammering Legos with my hands,
trying to make it sound like a fart would come from it.
I would rather do that than while I'm sitting at a urinal
and there's a man next to me.
- Sitting at a urinal?
- Well, I never learned. I was homeschooled.
- But I also think I'm an amazing crop duster.
- Yes, yeah, 'cause do you do the thing
where you spread your butt cheeks apart
so that the fart makes no noise?
- I don't even go that far, I don't need to.
- Well, I just gave you a million dollars over the game.
- You just put me on, yeah.
But let me tell you, I'll release in spurts
while I'm walking.
Just a little pushy.
(laughing)
- Today I was, there was a guy,
I was walking to the park with my wife and the dog,
and the dog had taken a shit and I had the shit in a bag,
but I know that there's not a trash can
till we get to the park, so I just carry it.
And I realized today that I swing my arms way too much
when I walk, I walk like a monkey,
and it slipped out on the backswing, the bag did,
and there was a guy right behind me and it hit his foot.
(laughing)
Which is honestly the best case scenario,
because I was swinging them enough that if I had released it
at the apex of my backswing,
it would have gone on top of his head or in his face.
Yeah.
Like a McDonald's fudge sundae, dude.
Yeah, exactly.
Just right on top.
Did it explode on the bag?
It did not explode, but he did seem pretty mortified.
But he was on the phone speaking something
other than English, which really made me so mad
because I knew that he was saying something immediately
about what had just happened and about what an idiot I was.
- I just got shitted on.
- Yeah. - Someone just shitted on me.
- Somebody just, he had to somehow explain,
I did get shitted on, but nobody shat on me,
they threw it on me.
- Yeah.
- Which is, I think, a tough thing to say in any language.
- I think I should've just gone like,
no, no, no, I'm sorry, this is my poop.
I dropped my poop, I'm sorry.
(laughing)
- Sorry. - I'm sorry,
I let go of my poop.
Great, my lunch is ruined by your foot.
Awesome, thanks so much, man.
I'm saving this for later.
But yeah, it was not a good situation.
No, I don't think I've ever had that happen.
But I also, I never used to clean up after my dog.
You're a bad guy.
This is in the same, this is exactly,
you're an only child, right?
Sure.
- I'm fucking wondering.
You're late to things, you leave shit everywhere,
you have no regard for other people.
You're a scumbag.
- True.
- I was, all right, so let's get into this.
I was 15 minutes late.
- Disgusting.
15 minutes late is 50 minutes late.
Five minutes early is on time.
On time is late.
Two minutes, two minutes is the grace period.
- Two minutes, what is this, class?
Are you clocking for first period?
- Class was 15. - What's wrong with class?
Class is amazing.
Class taught me everything I know about the Civil War.
I like class.
Two minutes is what you have.
I loved class.
I was a teacher's pet.
- Yeah, you were like a pit bull.
- Yeah, in a way.
Me and Rex were talking last night
about what bad kids we were in school.
(laughing)
I'm reverse chewing a little bit.
Yeah, we were telling some pretty horrible stories about how evilly despicable we were.
Alright, just tell me the worst ones, the two worst ones.
Um, my...
Probably for me, honestly, probably the one I'm least proud of is that my first
schoolyard fight ever was against a little person.
And I beat him up really bad.
You win?
Yeah, and also he started it.
I'd like to say that. He started it.
That's not bad.
And I called the teacher the C-word
and said a bunch of nasty stuff about her and her kid.
But I was 11 years old, you know, I was rough and tumble,
kind of a devil may care attitude.
Yeah.
I was so naughty that the mere sight of me
almost put a woman in the hospital.
Oh yeah.
He was saying last night he had a teacher
who he would walk in the classroom
and she'd be like, "I can't, you have to leave,
"my heart hurts."
- I'm having heart palpitations just thinking about you.
- She was in love with you.
- No, she--
- Well, her heart was beating out of her chest.
- She loved you so much.
You were so beautiful to my sight.
- You know they say, hate and love
are two sides of the same coin.
- That's right.
- So maybe she hated me so deeply
it turned back around like yin and yang.
- Yeah, you must leave or I will become a pedophile.
- Do you guys think you ever had a teacher
who jacked off to you?
Like the thought of you slipped into their mind
while they were jacking off?
- No. - No.
- I think I had one.
- I was a homely child.
- I could see that.
- Yeah.
I'm a homely adult, but you know, I was a homely child.
- What kind of teacher is this kid?
- He was a science teacher.
- He?
- Yeah. - He loved you?
- No, he played hard to get.
And he, but then I saw him, it was so weird.
I thought that this was like my one of those teachers
who's your friend and all that.
Yeah.
And I saw him at a,
I saw him leaving a gas station once,
like maybe two years or a year after I'd left school,
like a short enough time that he would have remembered me,
especially if I'm his favorite student, as he so claimed.
Yeah.
And I was like, I saw him in a gas station leaving,
and I was like, "Hey, what's up?
Good to see you."
And he like looked at me and just like completely ignored me
and walked past me.
He was over you?
-Yes, he had found some other fat kid.
-Damn.
-You have unlocked a memory in me of a math teacher I had in seventh grade
that would give me very aggressive hugs.
-Yes, you can't do that anymore, which is good.
A teacher should not be hugging children.
-What kind of aggressive hug are we talking?
-He had a-- Think of Gabe Newell.
He had a Gabe Newell affect.
-Okay.
-He would be like--
He was lovely and he made the best game of all time.
He was very folksy and he would be like, son.
And then he kind of like reach his arm around my tiny seventh grade
body and kind of like hug my waist.
Your little 20, 24 waist.
Yeah, exactly.
Wow.
And he'd be like, you gotta, you can't keep doing this.
You gotta be better.
You're so talented.
You're so smart, but you're so stupid.
-Whoa. What did you do? What provoked this?
-I think I cheated on a test
by programming a calculator to do something.
-Oh.
-I can't be mad at you for that.
You're a problem solver. -He very well could be.
-No. -Because I'm not
the first person to do it, which was the--
-Yes. People used to do the calculator cheating thing all the time.
-Yes.
- Yeah, I mean, that's the thing is like school
is really learning how to cheat and get away with it.
- And how to fish an iPod headphone down your hoodie sleeve.
That's what I learned.
- Oh yeah, classic kind of sit like this.
- Yeah, what are you gonna send me to detention
'cause I'm tired?
- Oh, I just need to rest my head on my hand
in a specific way that it covers my ear and you can't see.
- Do you ever think about how crazy it is
that you spend the first like almost 20 years of your life
having to wake up at like 6.30 in the morning
every single day.
- Yeah.
- It catches with almost nobody.
Nobody if they could choose would keep doing that.
- Yeah, I completely lost it immediately.
And even when I had like a real job for five years
that required me to be up so early in the morning,
I would still always just wake up late.
- If I wake up before 9, it's a miracle.
- Yeah, I've been trying to wake up earlier now
because, I don't know, it's just like,
I would rather take that midday nap
than be like up until four in the morning every night
and like missing half the day because I wake up at noon.
- I do feel like if I wake up like around noon,
I do miss, I do feel like my day is completely gone.
- Yeah, it's hard to get started at noon.
- Yeah, but even then, I don't know.
I don't care much anymore.
I think on Sunday I woke up at 3 in the afternoon.
Yeah, that's not...
It was horrible.
That's not healthy.
By the time I left the house and went to go get food, it was like 5.
But Sunday, you want to enjoy Sunday. Sunday's there to be enjoyed.
Sunday's a lazy day.
It is a lazy day.
But you want to it's not there's a difference between being lazy
and being effectively not alive on your day off.
You know, you want to be just fucking
you want to be awake and just watching movies.
What do you do on Sundays?
I recently I've been waking up.
I just wake up at the same time every day.
I wake up at like 730 every day.
It's crazy.
It's such a good on Sunday.
I mean, on Sunday, let's see this week, my Sunday I was working on the set, but last
week I woke up, did some cardio, took the dog for a walk, and then I think I probably
played video games and watched TV for the rest of the day.
As long as you wake up early, kind of anything feels productive if you woke up early.
That's true.
So at 7.30, you wake up at 7.30, you are naturally productive because all the people that would
make you unproductive won't wake up for the next five hours.
Exactly, yeah.
Nobody's bugging me to do something that I really shouldn't be doing because I have other
stuff to do.
Yeah, because I woke up at like five something this morning and I got so much done before
nine o'clock.
So much done.
That's what Brian was saying.
Clean so much.
He does.
He wakes up at five and then he goes for a run and then he falls back asleep until like
noon.
It's beautiful.
Yeah, I like that.
Yeah.
I like that because the middle of the day, honestly, take it or leave it.
Take it or leave it.
Exactly.
I love the morning.
I love night.
about 11 a.m. until 4 p.m. yeah what are you doing there lunch getting lunch
that break lunch I like breakfast all the love breakfast busy yep anyone that's
not busy one it's going again okay yeah I had to switch mics cuz my mic broke
the entire thing but it was probably Julio Rex's fault somehow would you
- Would you take a pill that made you wake up every day
at 6 a.m., but it made both of your balls really,
really small?
So small, so small that they're completely invisible
to the human eye.
- Yes.
- Would you take a pill that made it so you never got fat,
but all the fat that would go to the rest of your body
went to your balls?
(laughing)
- So I'm like working out, and people are like,
why are you working out so hard?
You're in great shape. - You're in perfect shape.
- You're 7% body fat, but I'm only doing it.
I don't think I would do that because--
- Yeah, how much body fat do you think--
- Distributes around your entire body.
So if I was like a very normal,
like somebody can look really, really good
at like 15% body fat.
But if 15% of my body was my balls,
that would be a really, really tough job market for me.
That's gonna be tough.
- It looks so good though.
What do you mean?
Job market.
I would never get a job if I had giant balls.
Well, you'd just hide them in your pants.
Yeah, just wear big pants.
Well, I'd have to wear a kilt and then I'm admitting to being Irish or whatever that is.
No, you don't have to wear a kilt.
You can just let them lean down one side of your pant leg each.
Okay, but that's – so you need to add this to the hypothetical.
You need to say you can mold them to be whatever – because yeah, I'll fucking – if I had to split my balls to go down both of my legs.
Think of them like a giant saggy breast instead of a spherical ball.
No more addendum to this. You can cut them off but they grow up twice the size.
They grow up?
[Laughter]
Why would you cut them? You have to go through the pain of cutting your own balls off?
And then they just come back twice as big?
Yeah, will you do it?
I'll pass this to the next one.
[Laughter]
all that well with the where we started but we do that yeah would you take a
pill that got you insanely high no I would interviewer I think I'm a good
interviewer what's up no wait how do you who's the bitch this the popular
interviewer now. Bobby Althoff? Yeah that one. Yeah. I think Jubio could be her. I
mean I'm referring more to a job interview not so much like
interviewing Drake. Well you said interviewer so. I want to get her I'm
going to interview her in the bathroom from Saw. What do you see
See yourself in five years.
Five years I see myself with your job, buddy.
Look out.
Hired.
Immediately.
I wasn't even hired.
Whatever.
No, they like that.
It depends on, okay, wait, who's interviewing me?
That's why I'm so good at being interviewed.
Because I'm an amazing kind of Sherlock Holmes-esque reader of people.
Well, I think I remember them asking me a lot, "Why do you want to do this job?
What do you want this job?
And you can't say the actual answer which is money.
No, you cannot say money.
That's forbidden.
I've always loved folding towels at the gym.
That's why.
I would do it even – I've always been a member of a gym and I've always just gone
and folded towels.
People call me weird.
Yeah, and I see in your resume –
But –
And I see in your resume, you used to be a very popular podcaster.
You had a really successful career.
Oh, thank you so much.
Why do you want to throw that all away just to be the janitor at the gym?
Well, because it's not fulfilling in the way that I think being a janitor would be.
There's something to clocking in and clocking out and leaving your job, leaving your work
at work, right?
I just didn't have any.
That's not a good answer.
I didn't have any division between my home life and my work life.
They hate that.
I want you to not have that.
Oh, you fucking want me to think about mopping the floor while I'm at home trying to watch
The Simpsons?
Yes, yes, they want that from you.
No they don't!
Nobody wants that.
When's the last time you had a job?
The last job I had was I worked at a museum and I was babysitting as well.
And that, but I, so I've mostly had pretty cool bosses and anytime there's been a, anytime
Anytime I've had a bad boss, I've just quit the first day.
- Yeah. (laughs)
- I worked at a wax museum for one day
and the boss said, "You have to go stand outside
"next to our wax statue of Peter Dinklage
"and try to trick people into paying you
"to take pictures with it."
And I was like, "Okay."
And I did it for two hours
and then I just brought the Peter Dinklage statue,
'cause again, I'm a nice guy.
I brought it inside so it wouldn't melt
and nobody would steal it.
And then I took off my uniform and I folded it
and put it on the toilet in the bathroom.
And I left and never talked to the lady.
- I would love to steal a wax, Peter Dinklage.
- I probably could have.
- That's probably the easiest thing to steal
at the wax museum as well.
- I knew like four people who worked
at this wax museum in Boston.
And they all were like, you got to work here, man.
It's awesome.
And then the first day they made me sit outside
on like a hundred degree day and I wasn't allowed to sit
and I wasn't allowed to look at my phone.
- Damn.
- Yeah, it was not a very fun job.
I think when I quit my real job for five years
and before I started editing the podcast,
I was interviewing so much for months
and I never, ever, ever got any close to getting hired
except for this one time.
I've made it through the entire process.
They interviewed me three times.
They made me do a quiz and I did it
and they liked my answers, I guess.
And then I got to the final round
where I got to meet the team.
And I got into the Zoom call,
and I joined, and it's a team of nine women.
And it's just me.
- Fail.
- See, honestly, that's the kind of work environment
that I thrive in.
- I completely, I was like, I was trying to be--
I was trying to be so personal, I was like,
oh yeah, this is cool, whatever.
And they immediately, the next day,
They were like, yeah, you didn't make it.
Yeah.
That's what you should have said.
When I worked at the museum, I only worked.
There was like one girl that was like my age and then every other employee was a
woman in their like seventies.
And I had just, I mean, we just got along like,
that's the difference.
It's the older women.
They, they like when you're a young man and you're a personable and you're trying
to be nice. It's a woman that's your age or maybe five years older than you. They hate
you every single time. I've never befriended anyone my age at my job.
The only person that stayed with me from any job I've ever had is Cameron because I met
I met Cam the first day at my, my job at college.
And, uh,
he was even weirder back then.
And I had hair and I was fat and, uh,
but yeah, I don't think I've ever made another like, like longterm,
like for nobody else I ever hung out with outside of my job that I
knew from my job.
Yeah. I hated everyone on my job.
Yeah, I quit the gym job because there was a girl who,
I was being targeted for harassment
because she claimed that I didn't dry the towels
after I washed them.
And I did, I did dry the towels, but the dryer was broken.
So the towels would come out wet.
And she was like-
She was coming, you were harassing her?
No, she was harassing me.
And she brought it to management.
And the manager told me, you need to dry the towels.
And I was like, I close, I can't stay for an hour
and run the cycle two times.
This is, it's either you have dirty towels
at the end of the night, or I do this.
I run the thing one time and it got too much, man.
I couldn't handle it.
I don't like drama.
I'm not like that.
I'm not one of these people who feeds on drama.
I'm not a snake.
I'm a really good guy.
So I just quit.
- What's the opposite of a snake?
Snakes, you're right, snakes keep to themselves.
What is the opposite of a snake?
The opposite of a snake is a human.
So I'm a human.
I don't think that's true.
Or Eve, I guess, a woman.
I'm a woman.
Something with a lot of legs.
Women.
A centipede.
A snake is the opposite of a god.
I guess you're right.
Yeah.
Yeah, according to one myth, I'll say it.
It's a fucking myth.
I don't think any of it happened.
Well, some of it maybe did.
I only believe in the New Testament.
You're a no Old Testament Jew.
You're a reverse Jew.
What happened in the New Testament?
What happened in the...
Did you grow up religious at all?
Yeah, but I never really paid attention.
What does that mean?
I never paid attention in a church that would take me.
I won't like it or listen at all.
You didn't pay attention to the thing that you thought was the entirety of existence when you were a child?
No, that never really faced me, I don't think.
Interesting.
I didn't really care.
He just liked the candles.
I didn't like the candles.
Candles are cool.
Well, they used to take me to this Christian church.
It was one of those Christian churches where they have a band.
And I think the one thing I liked the most was how they put like the drummer in like a cage so it wouldn't make too much noise.
I do love that shit. My mom was a worship leader so I would have to go like two hours before the church started at like six in the morning and just sit there and watch the songs for two hours.
So I pretty much fuck with contemporary Christian music to a degree that you would never believe.
I'm going to be honest with you.
Were you, you know, we were talking about being bad kids earlier.
I would get in so much trouble on every holiday because, you know, my parents would take me
to like some three hour long service and I would have an ADD meltdown 30 minutes in and
be like, can we go home?
I want to go home.
I wish I had my Nintendo SP, my Game Boy SP.
I had ways of getting in trouble.
I had ways of entertaining myself, like before I had like a phone.
So I used to, I got in a lot of trouble because I used to take the pamphlet that they put
in the, in Christian churches, they put a pamphlet in the, like the, it's a newsletter
basically.
It's like, this is what's going on in the church this week.
And I would take it and I would take the pen that they put there so you can like make notes.
I would take the pen and I would just black out a bunch of the letters and all the words
so that it would say like like at first it would say like
There's a potluck this weekend
Everybody come by and bring your favorite dish and I would change it to say I fucked a turd and then I would hand it
to my grandma
She would, she would laugh and she'd go stop.
And then my mom would catch wind of this eventually and I would get in a lot of
trouble. But yeah, I would just,
I would just black out the letters and make it say cusses and uh,
so you were entertaining yourself, but you still got in trouble.
The end result was still the same.
Yeah. And also gum gum got me through a lot of church. I would have like, uh,
my grandma always had gum and uh, I would, I would take, you know,
a piece of gum every five minutes until my entire mouth was so full of gum.
I can barely open it.
I love doing that.
And then I would blow just the biggest bubble at like the most dramatic part of
the sermon.
Completely silent.
Yeah. Just all over my face. I just have a giant pink,
a transparent thing on my face.
And there was an upside of not having hair. Can't get gum in it.
True. I can do a bubble all the way around my head.
Yeah. You could do the cleft lip bubble.
- Yeah, I had no, there was no reason,
or there was a reason that I had to stop at some point.
I was pushing into a dangerous zone
by blowing a bubble too big so I could get at my hair.
Now, the training wheels are off.
- One thing I never really understood about church
was when the, what if like the preachers
would just like start speaking in tongues
and holding women's faces and like they would cry.
I wouldn't, I would be like, what is he saying?
Why is he saying that?
You guys had speaking in tongues?
Yeah.
That's so interesting, because I think of that
as a pretty distinctly like American South Christianity.
They don't really have that in the North.
It sounded like a lot of gibberish.
It probably came from like revivals in Texas and stuff.
That probably all just spread a few kilometers down.
I do think that a lot of like churches,
like Christian churches, also have their starts in Texas.
One of the, there's like a really big church down here
that I think they're, they're originated from like Dallas
and they like send a lot of people down here.
I actually live like right next to like one of the coffee
shops where like a lot of the people like come
and just hang out.
Just like we used to get like a lot of Americans.
Do you have Christian coffee shops?
Yeah.
Yeah, we had those in my hometown.
Like coffee shops that are attached to a church
and you walk in and you're like,
why are these prices so low?
Well, there's one that's attached to the church
And there's one that's like right here
that's just like owned by one of the,
either the preacher or someone who works at the church.
So we got a lot of people who go to the church,
or people who come from like Dallas.
Just tell Americans she's hanging out
in my neighborhood for no reason.
- That is so awesome.
- It's all right.
I don't really like that coffee shop much.
It's kind of expensive.
- I love Americans.
They're very good people.
- Yeah, sure.
- Do you have a lot of Americans in your city?
Not as many as the Mexico City, right?
- There is, I do think that I live in a neighborhood
with a lot of foreigners.
I've seen a lot of Americans that even just live
in one of these buildings in this neighborhood.
So yeah, I think there are way more Americans
than I thought originally, like a year ago.
- Rex is fading.
- I'm fucking--
Rex is fading away. I'm like half asleep.
He's fading away into another dimension.
That's okay. It's beers we drank. We can end it early. I don't care.
If you're actually falling asleep, I think that's a pretty good...
We could do five more minutes. I'm a soldier. I'm a soldier of beer.
If you were a soldier, you'd be dishonorably discharged for falling asleep at your post right now.
Yeah, it would kill you.
No, I would be on some sort of amphetamine and I would be fully awake.
Doesn't that sound amazing?
The shit they were giving people during Vietnam.
Oh my God.
- Both of my roommates took Adderall today
and I like had to like,
that thing in the back of my brain was like,
"Just fucking do it.
Just take it.
They're offering it to you.
He's cutting up a 20 right now.
Just take a little piece."
- You should have just done it.
- I'd be like, "No, no."
- It would have gotten you through your whole day.
- I know.
- You would have had an amazing day.
And then there would have been no repercussions.
You would have just fallen asleep perfectly,
slept like an angel.
- No, you know what, now he's gonna go to sleep early,
well, kind of early, and he's gonna wake up tomorrow
at 7 a.m., he's gonna go walk his dog
and throw his poop on someone's foot.
(laughing)
- It's a normal morning routine.
- I'm honestly like, I'm just so excited
to not work on a laptop anymore.
- Yeah, that's a big upgrade.
- Yeah.
I love my stupid desk and my computer.
- The standing desk is pretty fucking awesome.
Sitting at the computer is one of the best feelings in the world.
I literally like, I was on my feet for 13 hours today.
And I finally at 6.15 p.m. pulled up my office chair,
lowered the standing desk and sat in it for two straight hours and didn't move.
I got a better feeling than just sitting at the desk.
Which is?
Sleeping on a real bed.
Oh, I am so excited for that as well.
I bought a new comforter because I've been getting chilly.
Yeah.
I came today.
It's perfect.
Yeah, I'm coming to work.
It's not cold tonight actually.
Yeah, the nights get cold and I'm like right on the street so it's like sometimes you get
a little wind and action.
And you like to keep that AC nice and low.
I do.
I keep it at 72.
- Oh, I would never, I would not even be able to think of sleeping at 72.
That is so hot.
- 72?
- I'm a cold blooded creature.
I'm from the desert, dude.
- This is what mine's at right now.
It's a 25, which is, I'll give you the thing right now.
- I sleep, I'm fully clothed, I'm under a blanket and I'm cold.
- You have a, dude, I cannot sleep if it's above 67 degrees.
Well, it's like it's hot down here.
So like it's hot.
Seven is no, I don't live in the desert like I do.
I live I live on.
I walk outside their sand.
I cactus.
He doesn't understand the desert.
Yeah, you do not live in a desert.
You live in a beautiful mountain vista.
We've seen your view.
Well, there was mountains in Arizona, but he has like snow capped.
Yeah, you are full of shit, dude.
You guys have red mountains.
What's the hottest your summer gets?
Say it in Celsius.
Oh, no, like around 40.
Yeah, it's 40, 44, 45.
You're a fucking bitch.
It's not. Yeah, that's nothing.
There's never been a 45 degree summer in fucking Mexico City.
Get the fuck out of Mexico City
in fucking Guadalajara, wherever you fucking live.
What is 45? 95?
No, it's like 100 something.
I mean, it'll be 100 degrees in in New York in the summer.
44.8 this year.
That was the high?
Yeah.
So that is-- sorry, I don't know.
That's 112.
Oh my god, that's hot.
It's a lie.
He's not telling the truth.
I'm closer to the equator.
I just Googled this.
I literally just Googled this.
It was 112--
Highest number in Mexico.
Highest somebody can count in Mexico.
44.8.
It was a hot ass summer.
It's finally kind of winding down.
I'm ignoring this blatant racism by Hitler.
It's not blatant, it's very subtle.
Adolf Hitler 2.
It's coming at you.
It looks like twin Hitlers, that's what I'm looking at right now.
You both have the same...
Well join us dude. You need to join us.
I grow reverse Hitler.
I can only grow the outsides.
This is how not racist I am.
The middle of my mustache refuses to put anything there.
- I'm just gonna pin it on.
Just get ahead of him.
- Go into the barber shop, give me the Hitler.
(laughing)
- They would do it, man.
- Line me up.
- They would do that shit.
- Line me up with the Hitler.
- Let's let Rex go to bed.
He's very, very tired.
- Goodbye.
- Oh, wait, wait, Bud Light Lime rating,
this is a six foot nine.
Michelob Ultra rating, this is a six foot four.
- I love Michelob Ultra.
is an amazing beer.
Meek Love Ultra, it's fine.
- Yeah.
- All right, bye.