(sipping)
(burping)
- You're listening to Beers We Drink,
America's number one beer broadcast.
(record scratching)
(upbeat music)
- What's up all my chuggers?
Trying to get that move out.
(gagging)
- This is a journey into--
- Into the middle of--
- Plain and simple--
- Bud Light.
And welcome back.
Oh the thing.
You don't need to clap.
We haven't had to clap for so long.
It's like a, it makes me feel like it's a, it's a snoot joke and it's completely stupid.
It's not.
Saturday we did a snoot joke.
Is your new joke sitting four feet from the microphone too?
This is part one of your other jokes?
I don't know what you're talking about.
There we go.
- He's addicted to never talking into the mic,
he's addicted to clapping,
where we don't need to clap.
- That's 'cause he's, it's fun to be,
he's a noob, he's new to all this.
- He's also addicted to living.
- He's addicted to living.
- I'm addicted to living.
- Messiest room of all time.
- It's not that messy.
- Every time, every time.
- All right, wait, let's take a look at this.
Lived in, that's what the realtor would say,
walking through.
As you can see, it's lived in.
There's 40 piles of t-shirts.
No man on earth needs this many clothes, man.
- I just have to get rid of them, you know?
- Mm, yeah.
- I just buy them.
- Is that what you say?
If trash piled up, you'd say that too?
Yeah, I just have to get rid of all that trash.
- Last week, he just like impromptu,
like sends me a message while I'm like streaming,
and it's just like a screenshot of his Amazon purchases,
and it's like, almost like 30 socks, 30 pairs of socks,
and he just says, "Men's shopping."
(laughs)
And I have to ask him what his deal is,
And he's like, I just keep losing my socks.
And I was like, okay.
- That is a really bad problem to have.
All right, let's talk beer, man.
- Okay. - Yeah.
- Last week, I really enjoyed not having to go out
and get my own beer.
So for the people at home, this is a makeup episode.
We were supposed to do this last night.
And then the most,
Jubio came through with the most Mexican excuse
I've ever heard in my fucking life.
Which is, yeah, my entire family showed up.
And they have to watch a football game,
which is a soccer game at my house for three hours.
And then it was just, it wasn't gonna happen.
- Well, the thing was there was a huge car accident
that it completely closed down the road.
So it was completely out of my power.
- So does that diverted all the football traffic
to your house?
Well, it makes no sense.
- Yeah, sort of, exactly, that's what happened.
- I think that these people are making excuses.
They're being rude, they're staying too long.
The point is, my wife picked up my beers again
and I said this time,
Please don't give me a fucking bush light, you fucking dildo.
Don't, please don't do that.
- You call her a dildo?
- No, I don't know, I've never said that before.
I've never used that as an insult until right now.
- Dip.
- I think I'll probably never say it again.
It did not feel good.
I felt like I was in the office.
- That felt very awkward.
- Yeah, you dildo.
(laughing)
I wanted to say the C word,
but I was like, she's in the other room.
I also don't, I don't like, I don't like saying that word,
but it was what came.
Cuck? You thought I was gonna call my wife a cuck?
Yeah.
No, I was thinking the anti-Semitic C word.
But what I ended up getting, which she brought me...
A circle.
Was a Victory Berry Monkey
Fruited Sour Triple, which is nine
and a half fucking ABV points.
Yeah, that's a beast of a beer.
She got, she did you right.
This is a good beer?
Yeah, Victory's good.
I took my sip.
Oh!
Oh! You drink these, man?
What, the Sours or the Victories? The Sours.
Yeah, I drink them. You know he just drinks everything in the world.
Yeah, well this is only a double. It's a double deluxe.
Oh, okay. What does that mean if it's been fruited? What does fruited mean? That just means
that they put fruit in it, right?
Yeah, probably they put fruit in multiple times in the brewing process.
Oh, and I just had a fucking.
And I just learned of a giant splinter on my finger.
Ouch.
How or I put myself on my rucksack or something.
All right. So here's what I've got.
OK. Yeah, you got a steamrolled.
I've got a crabby cake, double deluxe.
That's like it's it's got to be kaka.
Well, it's this crappy cake with a K, which is a
a smoothie style sour ale of double
mary and berry, double blueberry, double marshmallow,
cake mix and vanilla cream.
Yeah, and the marshmallow kills me, man.
I don't know about that.
Here's take a look at the color.
Wow. That is a thick fucking.
Whoa, check it out.
Fancy, fancy receptacles to drink beer out of.
Look at this. You're still using cans of beer.
You're right. This is a great idea.
From now on, we should be drinking this in something transparent
so that you can see what it looks like.
Yeah. You guys are 100 percent right.
I feel like a fool.
I need to get a a Stein, a clear glass Stein.
This is a Bubba Gunk novelty cup.
Whoa.
Bubba Gunk.
That's the kind of that's you drinking Bubba's Gunk right now.
That's what that looks like.
Not while I'm drinking the fruity sour.
[laughter]
Smoothie beer.
How fucking far away are you from just
what a man should be, man?
You're drinking a smoothie beer
out of a Bubba Gump novelty.
Well, as a peak millennial,
I have immense nostalgia for
Spongebob Squarepants.
Mmm, yeah, okay.
- Hmm, yeah, okay.
- So you marketed it to me with a happy pattern.
- You don't care what's in it at that point.
- Yeah.
- It just caught dawn on me.
Why is it like, it's a smoothie, it has marshmallow.
It doesn't, it's not a burger.
(laughing)
- Yeah, also-- - It's not a burger food?
- Also, before the record, if somebody told me
that they were drinking a smoothie
that had marshmallow and cake in it,
I would tell them that is not a smoothie at all.
- That's a milkshake.
- That is a milkshake.
You're drinking a milkshake beer.
- Milkshake burger beer.
- It's a fruity milkshake burger beer.
- You're a pretty bershick burger beer.
- What?
You're a pretty bershick burger beer?
- Have you been tying a few on
before we started beers we drank?
- I actually did.
- How's it taste?
- Speaking of beers that we've drank,
I did have two Coors Lights with my barbecue lunch
that I had today.
I had some brisket and some chicken.
- Yeah, that's classic beer food.
- That is classic beer food.
- All right, you're up.
I'm taking a stand.
I'm drinking the good shit, as they say.
- Ooh, a Miller Lite.
- Miller Lite.
- Oh my God.
- Over the week, it's been of note
that also I didn't feel like I might pour this thing around.
There's absolutely no head on that.
- You have no head on your shit.
- Damn, you don't get no head.
- Yep.
- Well, what's about to--
- You don't get no head on your head.
- Okay.
- You don't even have a head.
- That's what I'm saying.
You're just a fucking torso.
(laughs)
- You're a pair of hands in a boot.
- Yeah.
Sorry, continue.
- Tastes pretty bad.
I don't like them.
- Miller Lite tastes bad?
- I'm not a fan of Miller Lite.
I'll be honest.
- I like, okay, I had the Coors Lite today
and I could not believe how good it was.
It was like--
- Coors is good?
- It was cold. - Banquet beer.
- It was so, so good.
It was incredible.
Coors Banquet's one of my all-time favorite beers.
I think partly just the bottle, though.
Yeah, I had a I had a roommate.
He used to drink nothing but Miller Lite, no water.
Nothing else was Miller Lite.
He would sit on the porch with no shirt on.
Oh, 120 degree weather.
Yeah. Watch baseball from the moment he got home from work
till the moment he went to sleep.
So cool.
Oh, Mike, to nothing but smoke Marlboro
Golds and whatever the gold packages.
I don't know if they're called.
Yeah, Marlboro lights.
Yeah, lights.
It smoke lights.
Drink seven Miller lights.
Out of one of the he any didn't he didn't have any frills.
There's no frills in his life.
Didn't have anything nice.
Only nice thing he had suction cup beer cozy.
It's like vacuum sealed that he would drink the Miller light out of
Because otherwise, from a Brookstone in the scene on TV section.
Exactly. That's so amazing.
And I would go, Aren't you dehydrated?
Don't you need to drink water at some point?
And he go, Well, the the beers have dogs.
Is it here? It's got water in it, man.
He's completely right. Yeah.
Yeah. This.
I miss him. He was 44 and he had 60 years.
Wow. That's actually
that's pretty good, man.
That's more than more than one a decade.
Assuming you had one before he was 10.
Mm hmm. Yeah, he was tying him on.
You know, that's that's your new favorite thing to say.
I've said it twice. You're right.
Yeah, I do that, too, where I say I will have one phrase
that I say for an entire night and then I get home from whatever.
And I'm like, I can't believe that I said
I said, you got to hand it to him 10 times tonight.
(laughing)
And somebody at some point definitely noticed that I
- Oh, they always notice. - I think I said it
to the same person five times.
Well, you gotta hand it to 'em.
And they went home and they're like,
what the fuck, does that like,
he's trying to make it his catchphrase?
- Is he trying to make for a thing?
What's wrong with him?
Do we need to check him into the nursing home?
- I think it happens a lot. - I do need to go
to the nursing home.
- That happens a lot with our group
because someone will just start saying something stupid
and the rest of us will just parrot it for like weeks
until someone says something stupider.
Definitely, yeah.
It's, I have a problem with,
I'm too good at assimilating with the people that I'm with.
I'm too good at being in a group of friends.
You're too good at being a friend.
I'm just too good of a friend.
Last night, last night Juvia says,
"Yeah, we can't do this."
Brex steaming mad, so angry.
He has never gotten worse news.
Caleb, so understanding.
I'm texting Julio, I'm saying,
man, don't even worry about it, bro.
It's not a big deal at all.
Don't worry.
Shit happens.
You know, meanwhile, if I did this to Julio, he would, he would be, he'd make,
he'd send me a picture of his grumpy face.
I would never do such a thing.
You would, you would, he would be mega grumpy.
I have a picture of the car accident.
Look, everyone's people are outside the cars.
They completely blocked up the road.
Who took the photo?
Um, God.
So you're telling me they were on the road driving,
they got 40 feet from the car accident and then they were already in the line
and they decided, you know what? No, we're going to go to Julio's house.
Let's turn around and drive.
That's a picture of someone else's photo.
My family wouldn't do that to me.
I don't think they did it to you.
They did it to you.
Kind of.
Yeah, you got it.
It was upon.
Did you at least did they at least bring like food and drinks and you got
fucked up.
So what what the deal was,
I was telling Rex about this.
My day was like seemingly
going to be like so awkward
yesterday, but it like
slowly started like taking
shape. And I was really happy
about like, oh, I'm going to
stream in early on that I want
to record. And then we're going
to watch this game.
I'll just tell him to come over
to my apartment. We can watch
the game here.
They can bring some food and
some drinks or whatever.
And they were like, no, we're
not going to go to your
apartment. And then I'm like,
OK, I'll just record.
And then at 4 p.m.
My dad just like drops off one of my sisters here.
He's like, "Okay, she's gonna hang out here for a bit."
And then my mom and my other sister get here
and they're like, "Actually, there's so much traffic,
"we're just gonna hang here."
And they're like, "All right, yeah,
"we're gonna leave in like an hour."
And they just don't leave
and they just stay here until like 11 p.m.
- Oh my God. - And they're like,
"Oh, we should go get some drinks, some snacks."
And I go with them to the supermarket
and I buy the snacks and the drinks.
There is nothing in this world that I hate more than family.
Family is so fucking, thank you, thank you.
Family is so awful, they're so imposing,
they're disgusting, they don't understand you,
they make you do the dishes for 18 years of your life
and then they expect you to call them.
I don't wanna talk to you.
I used to be scrubbing, I used to see the food
that you would eat and it fucking disgusted me.
- Yeah, I do understand sometimes the appeal
of moving away from the city because I just,
there's so much, there's things that happen
even after I moved out of my dad's house,
it's still like so annoying.
- I just had the conversation with my mom
about moving to New York and you know,
it's like, I moved six hours away to California.
- Yeah.
- She's not come to visit me one time.
-But she wants the option to be easy, right?
-Yes.
-Now it's like--
-She's like, oh, you're so far away.
When are you going to come back?
And I'm like, the same amount of times I come back now.
-Yeah.
-That's when you will see me.
It's an easy flight, and it probably happens
15 times a day from JFK.
-Yeah.
I was like, trying not to be mean and being like,
well, whenever I feel like it.
-Yeah.
-Whenever I feel like coming home.
Also, if she wants to visit, it's a nicer place to visit.
- It is.
- Yeah, come hang out.
- I hope she never visits.
I didn't want her to visit here.
- If she does, you will tell me
so that I can hang out with her, right?
- You would be so annoyed by my mom.
- I would take all of it.
I would just sit there and I would just smile.
I'd go, yeah.
- Your mom would rather go to New York
than LA for some reason.
Someone tells me that's--
- My mom's from the Bronx.
She grew up in the Bronx.
I would pretend to be gay to seduce her.
I'd be just fully--
- I don't think that would work.
- I'd go to dance classes with her.
I'd do Pilates with her, yoga.
- I will say she is dating a bald man right now.
- You're kidding me.
- I wish I wasn't.
- So she's single.
(laughing)
- Maybe to a different bald man.
Maybe if you shine some light in your head,
she'll get so blinded she doesn't know who you are.
- I'm going to blind your mom
as soon as she jumps off the plane.
I'm going to throw a lie in her eyes
and just instantly blind her forever.
- I would love that.
I would love to have my mom be trapped in the subway realm.
- We need to make your mom homeless
so that she can't call you.
We need to like ruin her life, chop her leg off,
make her one of the people who lives underground in Vegas.
- Yeah.
- Like only like pops up every once in a while
to like steal a computer and bring it down there.
I want to make her live in a costume in Times Square forever.
(laughter)
- That's a great idea.
Get your mom into an Elmo costume.
It's clear that the Elmo only has one leg.
It's like a fully wooden second leg.
(laughter)
Dude, here's what I never understood
about those homeless people in Vegas.
Why not set up a little box on the street,
a fake slot machine, and sit in it?
And then when people put their money in,
You just steal it.
- You know what they should do?
They should just steal a slot machine
and then take the money that they make
from the slot machine.
- Exactly, yeah.
- The slot machines only make money.
- It's the one place in the world where there is
more money being thrown around than anywhere else.
Or just buy yourself a vest, steal a vest,
and bring somebody a fuckin' gin and tonic
every once in a while and they might tip you 500 bucks.
Yeah. Have you heard about the fact that Vegas is decaying and dying and
becoming ugly and disgusting?
I was there maybe
six months ago and I enjoyed it.
It started happening five months ago.
They said what's happening to it.
They said circus circus is trash now.
They said the buffet.
That's like the worst one.
They say, they said that the buffet,
The buffet is completely not even the cheapest option to eat.
At Circus Cir-- what are you talking about?
The worst fucking--
I don't know.
Who said this?
My channels.
My--
You have a YouTube video?
No, the news.
The news said that.
The news didn't say this.
CNN did never--
The news was covering Las Vegas, and they were like,
there's so many homeless people.
There is a lot of homeless people.
It's stinky.
The hotels are falling piece by piece every day.
[INAUDIBLE] is throwing up.
I like what the nation.
You did just do a full throw up face wipe.
Oh, no, it's just because I drank like
where you like when I get a piece of carrot out of your teeth
while you do this, it feels like I just drank an actual smoothie.
It's so like thick, it sticks in my my mustache.
Yeah, you're going to have that civil.
Yeah, you know, I don't know.
I don't know. Yeah.
So do you at least I will say this is so yummy.
and I'm a third of the way through.
And this is probably the drunkest I've been in.
That's why sours are awesome.
Do I can't believe how fucked up I'm getting.
I'm I'm with it, dude.
We should drink.
We should get some mega fruity sours.
I'm down when you're in town.
We should get a gram or something.
Yeah, one of those fucked up places.
Sours.
No, I really like that place.
But speaking of, no, I had a Paloma yesterday
and I was thinking about him the whole time.
I was like, I wish I shut out, shut up, get that boy out of my head.
Why does Noah remind you of what is a Paloma?
Remind you of Noah?
Because he's the one that talks about Palomas all the time.
I think Chad likes the Palomas because Chad makes it or Chad had one
one time and now he makes them at home, but he just makes them with squirt
instead of grapefruit juice.
He just makes him a fucking squirt out of the can.
That's awesome.
Which I don't think they make squirt anymore, unfortunately.
- Maybe they do. - So what's it use?
Like what, Haritos?
- Squirt, the soda?
- You're just supposed to use grapefruit juice and tonic,
but you can use any grapefruit soda, I guess.
- They make Squirt?
You're crazy. - They still have Squirt?
I just, I mean, I don't see Squirt on the East Coast much.
Squirt and Cactus Cooler are, in my brain,
mostly West Coast sodas.
- That would make sense.
Cactus Cooler, definitely a West Coast.
- I saw Squirt recently because I went to a steakhouse
for my mother's-- - I saw Squirt recently.
- My, okay.
(laughing)
- Are you done making stupid jokes now?
We're supposed to talk about the beers
and what they taste like and the hops
and the percentages of them.
This one tastes like shit.
I don't like it.
- Dude, I'm telling you, this one's only 5.3%.
- That is so bad 'cause you know it's like 700 calories
for that tall boy.
- I know, dude.
- This thing is nine and a half percent,
which is way beyond what I would ever get normally.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- That's really high.
Yeah, like I mean, this is like drinking.
These are a tall boy to this, like drinking two of them
of what I would normally drink, basically like I like.
I really enjoy light beer.
Light beer is so refreshing.
You can drink a lot of it.
It's not too sweet.
I agree with this.
This has a bunch of berries in it.
Yeah, it's very sleek.
I really need to start getting into it.
Do you guys think that maybe once a month
we could do kind of a casual Friday style episode
where we get stuff that is like not beer.
And I know we've done non-beer before,
but I mean like alcoholic drinks,
maybe from a different country.
Maybe we get sake.
- Okay.
- What if we all got the same kind of,
what if we all got sake?
- Okay.
- Wouldn't that be amazing?
- That sounds like an amazing idea.
- Or what's another,
there's gotta be some kind of melon wine.
- I mean, I guess we could do like soju.
- I'm not a genius.
Soju gives me a headache.
Soju is too much.
- I drink melon wine, it's gonna give you a headache.
- Well, maybe melon wine doesn't even fucking exist, asshole.
I just made it up and I'm hoping it exists.
- I mean, it's got sugar.
You could probably bake it into some sort of.
- But it probably tastes like shit.
- Soju is fucked up.
I think that one time I went to like this soju place
and I had one thing of soju
And it I felt so drunk and I was like, OK, I need I need to drive.
Yeah. So I used to drink a lot of sake.
You should drink a lot of sake.
Do you drink it hot or cold?
Well, I do both on its own hot.
I would do. Here's the thing.
I used to you know how you drink like a hot toddy when you're like not feeling well?
Yes. Well, I don't do that.
That's disgusting. But yeah, I would do that whenever I got a cold.
I would basically like do sake bombs.
And I would I honestly worked every time.
I've heard you say that before that you thought of sake bombs as medicine.
Yeah. That is so crazy.
That is good work.
The only person I know who who I've ever known who drank soju
a lot was John from Philly.
And he really he would like show up to parties and stuff with like
six bottles of soju.
And I thought it was like not.
Yeah, it's super cheap.
and I thought it was like, I basically thought it was one of them was like a beer,
but they're like this big. And if you, if you split it with somebody,
you get fucked up. Yeah. Yeah. They're like diabolical.
Yeah. Cause they're really sweet. It's deceptive.
And then it will give you the worst hangover you've ever had in your life.
Cause it's like, yeah,
I found out that a margarita bar is opening near me.
Yeah. I think I told you that.
I think so.
A margarita bar.
I'm very, very excited.
Yeah.
I've only ever had margaritas at Chili's.
I've only ever had two margaritas.
You live in fucking Mexico?
You've only had margaritas once?
Twice.
They're not from the margarita region of Mexico.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's not funny.
Stupid.
That's a stupid joke.
That is kind of funny.
We've talked about that before.
We've talked about this before, but that's not a stupid joke.
That's not funny.
What's the regional food and drink where you live?
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
- Sour beer.
It's good for, if you have a cigarette, it's good.
- Yeah.
- Also, it's really funny,
living in a city where the number one industry
or the biggest industry is a brewery,
they would just take us on school trips,
just to look at the brewery,
just look at the process of them making the beer.
- That's actually awesome.
- This is it, yeah.
It was fun.
- I used to go on the most insane field trips,
'cause I went to a charter school.
And when I was a kid, I thought that was just a public school.
But a charter school is basically people with no,
like, they have no accreditation,
they have no degrees in teaching or anything,
and they just say, "Well, we want to like, steal money,
"so we'll start a charter school."
And so the field trips,
they would just get authorized no matter what.
And we did one field trip where we went,
we literally went to one of those places
where they have the like those bungee things
that they have at like Six Flags,
where you sit in a thing and then it shoots you way up.
That was the entire field trip,
was just putting 12 year olds into the bungee thing
and then just everybody's so scared launching them up.
- Was it supposed to be educational or something?
Like what were you learning about?
- So the first one we did that year
was we went to the dentist
and the dentist talked to us about,
yeah, this is how being a dentist works or whatever.
- Oh, we do have a dentist school.
- And then we did a couple other ones.
We went to the library once.
And then the last two that we did were like,
we just went to the movies.
And then by that fourth one,
it was like the teacher just wanted to go to this thing.
So they, she just like,
the school will fucking pay for it
if I bring all these kids.
And it was very fun.
- It's pretty sick. - Was it like a fair
or some shit?
- No, no, it was like a ropes course.
It was like a long drive away
and it was like a ropes course that we didn't do at all,
and then a giant bungee slingshot.
- Okay.
- And a couple of kids got so scared, like crying scared.
- Did you get on it?
He didn't get on it, he was so scared.
He was so scared to get on it.
- Well, but I didn't scream because I didn't get on it.
But I did go, 'cause my mom was a chaperone.
- You were crying on the silence,
just looking at all the brave kids do it.
OK, first of all, Hunter was not brave.
OK, he was the biggest screamer of anybody in the whole class,
and he would scream at anything.
Cool name, cooler than yours.
Well, what if I told you his dad owned a clothing store?
That's pretty cool.
What kind of clothes?
Like high end women's clothes.
That's pretty cool.
What if I told you he started surfing when he was six?
Now, you still let me guess.
You think that's cool, too?
I think that's cool, yeah.
Can you set up a camera in the women's changing room?
He never did that.
That's a 13 year old son of a high end woman's clothing store owner thing.
Well, maybe he did.
I kind of lost touch with him.
I think he kind of I think he was went past my social and economic
level pretty quickly out of middle school
to the point where I just never saw him again.
Yeah, but I hope it's like to hear about people you went to school with recently.
But this weekend I found out that one of the guys I went to high school with, one of those
people that you remember being just a moron that very little people liked, he's just on
Instagram doing the car influencer thing where he's just taking pictures of someone else's
cars and I caught these weird glam shots and I was like, "Dude, what?
How do you become this?"
And he still just looks like a completely ugly guy.
Wait, his issue is that he was ugly?
Yeah, he's a weird looking guy.
I'm not going to show you a picture of him.
That would fly in the show.
He won't listen to us, it's in English.
Yeah, but I don't want people to know his name or his face.
Or what high school you went to,
because they would find that shit out.
They would find out.
Yeah, I feel like I went to,
I think I've talked to somebody about this before,
I feel like I went to a, I lived in a town where most people
have or will die very tragic deaths.
Where nobody dies of old age, everybody dies
in drunk driving, drugs, boating accidents, suicide,
some the most insane cancer branch you've ever heard of.
Nobody dies. - That's pretty cool though.
- Well, it would be if I wasn't from there.
Yes I do.
Do you think I want to die?
Dude, no.
The other day I thought I was at the gym
and I had like, what I think was just like my GERD acting up,
my like esophagus spasming.
But I thought that it was like a massive heart palpitation
and it lasts for like three minutes after a deadlift.
And I completely was convinced I was going to die.
And I was thinking, I was like,
not only am I going to die at a gym with my gym buddy,
but also my last thought will be,
"Oh my God, I just died at a gym."
(laughing)
It will not be like, I realized in that moment,
I was like, if you die somewhere like that,
your last thought will never be,
"I lived a great life, I love my family."
If you die in like a panicked, awful situation,
your last thought will be like,
"Oh, fuck, I fucked up so bad, I'm such an idiot."
- No, your last thought, everyone's last thought
is remembering where something they lost 30 years ago is.
(laughing)
- Oh my God, if I remembered exactly
where my Nintendo DS was, my blue Nintendo DS,
I thought I left it in a taxi cab.
- You'll be 90 years old on your deathbed,
and you'll go, "Oh my God, the Nintendo DS is in my room,
"it's under the bed!"
- Yep.
- And just die right there, unable to act on it.
- That's what's going to kill me,
Is it one day I'm going to remember something so hard
that it will instantly kill me?
Die of stroke.
- Yeah.
My heart fucks up all the time.
Feels weird almost every day.
- But this was like three full minutes of like--
- Yeah, it's like 30 minutes for me, man.
It's fine.
You'll get over it. - Really?
You need to go to the hospital.
- Yeah, I stopped.
I was like, okay, I'm leaving the gym.
I need to go to the hospital.
And then I got in the car.
- You're just not 27 yet.
- That's your only problem.
You just need to get two years older.
- We were on stream with Patrick,
and they were like, "So, we're talking about this shit."
Patrick was like, "Yeah, well, next year,
"I'm gonna lose my health insurance,
"so right now I'm eating shit,
"drinking energy drinks every year."
- That's wrong.
- And as soon as I switch over to 26,
I'm going vegan, I'm gonna be healthy,
I'm stopping all this shit,
because I need to stop at that point.
And I was like, "Why don't you just stop now?"
And was just sitting there like, yeah, you should do that.
That's a good idea to do that.
Yeah, I lost my health insurance.
I only had it for one year.
I didn't have health insurance for like five years.
And then my mom got a job that gave her health insurance
when I was 24.
And so I had one year of health insurance.
I got checked up one time, never followed up.
Picked up my blood work.
Eight months later, found out I had hepatitis A
for the like a long time.
And then, um, yeah, I haven't been to the doctor since.
I did one online doctor consultation and then they and I thought
that it was covered by my insurance.
Turns out it wasn't.
They've been sending me a bill for $400 every fucking day
and just be like, Hey, remember, you got to pay this bill.
And so now I'm like, OK, never going again.
I tried it.
Didn't like it.
Not the doctors.
It's not for me, man.
Not for me.
Listen, yeah, it's
mind over matter.
Exactly.
If you tell yourself you're fine,
you are fine.
A lot of these people who die of
strokes, heart attacks, cancer.
It's because they're having anxiety.
And they're just they're just not,
let's be real.
When was the last time you heard of
someone dying with cancer who was
like really smart?
Pretty much never.
Steve Jobs.
That's about the last time 20 years ago.
Steve Jobs. Yeah, exactly.
So it's a it's like a it's like Haley's Comet.
Like it just comes around every once in a while.
Somebody who's really smart dies of cancer.
Steve Jobs also had that thing where basically was just like proto-Rex,
where he was just like, I'll just drink energy drinks and I'll be
it'll cure my cancer.
Well, he did like he did Dr. Stevies shit.
He only ate fruit for the last couple of years of his life,
and it made his cancer a lot worse than pancreatic cancer.
So now he's drinking he's eating 500 grams of sugar every single day. Yeah
Trying to get that through a tumor is not a great idea
And he lived a very fulfilling life
That's the other thing he if somebody who's a brilliant guy does dive cancer is like who gives a shit
He had an amazing life. He squeezed five lives into that. What is this last thought was do you think?
Well, his last words were I should have invented the iPhone
- I should have went to the iPhone 14.
- I should have started with the iPhone 14.
That was his last words.
- The iPhone needs more cameras.
- They went, okay.
- Wait, AirPods.
And then he just died.
- It takes him years and years to even understand what the fuck that means.
- No, I believe his last words were--
- Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
(laughter)
Ow, my cancer, ow!
Ow, ow, ow.
- I know, we can move on.
His last words were, "Oh my God, oh my God,
"it's so beautiful," according to his sister.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- That's such a lie.
- It's 100% a lie.
Definitely his last words were like,
he looked at her and he was like, "You're hot,"
'cause he's so high on drugs.
He's like, to his sister, he's like, "I wanna fuck you,"
and he farted so loud, like four full minutes,
his last, just like a death rattle fart,
and then he finally passed on.
- Yeah, people don't know that when you're on your deathbed
you turn into Peter Griffin.
- Yeah, I mean, pretty much.
I mean, I know somebody who had a medical emergency,
they were on all sorts of drugs,
and they tried to grab a family member's boob.
- Wow. - Yeah.
- Indeed I.
- My grandpa had dementia and he would just hit on my mom
and we would go and visit.
- Damn.
That's honestly, that's the big fear of dementia, right?
- Yeah.
- Is that your daughter walks in one day and you're like,
what the fuck is up?
What's up, sweetie pie?
- Literally, that's exactly--
- She goes in for a hug, you start fucking--
- Just grinding.
- Yeah, you think it's your wife.
Yeah, you grab her ass and stuff, that's bad.
- That is bad.
- Because in that shows, he always thought this, man.
He always thought his daughter was hot.
- Yep.
- How sad is that?
- And it's so sad.
- It's what it shows.
- That's what it shows.
- Okay, I agree with you.
I think you're a medical expert.
- Listen, I'm not a medical expert, but I'm a sexpert.
I'm a sex expert in every way.
- Your daughter is medically hot.
- That would, I hope to God that I have the ugliest kids ever
that nobody ever wants to be involved with at all.
And then maybe one day, because they're so good at chess,
somebody finally says, I mean, you know what?
You look like a fucking frog, but I guess I'll marry you.
Because the idea of my children having sex
and me having to see that happen,
that would kill me. - You have to see it happen?
Why do you have to see it happen?
- Because of all the cameras you put up in their bedroom.
- Well, but also I just have a wild imagination, you know?
So regardless of if I see it, I'm going to see it in my head,
my mind's eye.
- Are you already seeing it?
- Yeah, and I don't even know what my kids' names are
right now, you know?
- Would you, is it a fear of yours that when your children
are born, they're taller than you by the age of 12?
- I would be so happy for them, but yes.
- I've pretty much, because of the genes,
Because of the woman I've decided to mate with,
I've pretty much guaranteed that will happen.
All of her brothers are like 6'2" and like insanely athletic.
Everyone in my family is completely fat.
Like everybody looks like a mountain.
Yeah.
So I'm really, really hoping that we get a tall,
athletically ripped bunch of kids.
I think if you're like Caleb and I, where you're like a genius,
but you know, maybe five foot eight, five foot nine,
not very athletic, but you know, we've got,
we've got our own stuff going on. You got a woman that has
in life. I think it would be if Caleb got a,
got a white NBA player son.
Oh, that'd be so funny.
I would be wearing Steve Harvey suits.
Oh my God. That is
You are kidding?
That just gave me chills.
That is like my fucking dream, dude.
That is my dream.
If my kid is not an NBA player,
I fucked something up so bad, man.
That is a meal ticket for the rest of your life.
- From the moment they can hold a basketball,
they're out there shooting free throws.
- Absolutely, man.
- Their technical game is flawless.
- And by the way, they're getting,
they're not, I'm not going easy on them.
I'm calling fouls.
We're in the middle, I'm gonna call fouls
when they're playing against like, like our dog,
like doing that thing where you dribble the ball.
I'm going to be like, no, you traveled.
Like I will be such a fucking stickler.
Just walking around with a whistle 24/7.
Dude, that is so good.
Oh, my God.
What a beautiful dream.
They give me such an insane rush of dopamine
thinking about my child being in the NBA, playing for the Hornets.
I get to move back to North Carolina.
I've had like the lowest level of success
as a comedian that you can possibly have, like I just stay at this level forever.
And then I get to be bailed out instead of having to actually
chase the actual thing.
I get to be bailed out by an NBA player son and be rich.
Yeah, that is so awesome. Yeah.
I've been thinking about, you know, what's the the worst fear?
You know, what's the worst thing your son could be?
And the answer to me is just kind of stupid.
If I had a son that was just kind of stupid, I'd be so pissed.
I would say worse is probably mass shooter or serial killer.
Yeah, I'd rather have a genius son.
That's both of those rapists.
Yeah, rapist.
I would rape him out.
I will bail him out every time.
Suicidal maniac.
Yeah, and totally fine.
But if he's like just a little slow.
He's on his own.
Like, yeah, I get it.
Like slow in a way where, you know, it wasn't your fault.
Yeah, like you were like, I did everything right.
Taught him everything at the right time.
He just never really got there.
I'd be very pissed.
I mean, yeah, I guess that.
What's the one thing that I would not love him? Yeah.
How can you?
How the fuck can you?
What's the one thing that you would
you would try to like imprint on them like those like Reddit parents are like,
Oh, I'm going to get I'm going to make my my my kid play Super Mario.
imprint on him, his last name on the back of his head,
with a brand, an ice brand on the back of his head.
I'm gonna get a baby-sized heavy bag and have him execute 200 perfect punches a day.
Yeah, I honestly will have to think about when he's born,
project 20 years in the future, and say what will make,
what it will be the thing that makes the most money in the world in 20 years.
And I'll just start training for that.
Yeah. OK, if it's a girl, you know,
can replace surgery every day.
I'll pretty much just check out, honestly, if it's a girl. OK.
You know, can't do my
brother in law.
Just it's such a dude. It's so funny.
He just his wife is pregnant, and he just did like a gender
reveal party with a golf ball and he's really into golf.
He's a great guy. He, he, in the video, he, uh,
it's like his whole family around and he's like, Oh,
I'm nervous. Right. He goes to swing. The golf club comes down,
hits a golf ball, blue smoke goes everywhere.
And the second that he sees the blue smoke, he goes,
to have a boy.
And it was so clear that he was like,
if I ever grow up, I will kill myself.
It's so funny, dude.
I was like, yeah, man, I get it.
That's what I would do, too.
Yeah, that's I don't I think
we should stop doing those
because exactly those other people.
Yeah, that's what a high who
what what they actually want.
But then it happens
and they're just like so, so happy,
so excited that it's actually
a little bit strange.
It was so awesome.
I was like, dude, you really, really wanted a boy, didn't you?
He's like, Oh, man, you know, I was just yeah, I was just excited either way.
Just realize that you should not have reacted.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, it was clearly such a like primate reaction.
He had of just like, yeah, just a relief.
Yeah. And like his his brothers and his dad are both in the background,
like, yes, yes. Fist bumping, high fiving.
I think my issue is if I had a daughter, she would be like diabolical.
She'd be getting into so much trouble.
She'd be just...
If you had a daughter, you would breed a racist to her daughter.
Yeah, I would.
Yeah.
And if you had a boy, he would just refer to you as his weird dad
and he would never...
I'm just afraid of how...
I was actually thinking about how my kids will perceive me earlier today,
because I don't think anybody goes their entire life being like,
Man, my dad is so cool.
People either think their parents are cool
or they think that their parents love them.
It's never both.
It's they think their parents are cool because they have the mystery,
because they don't know them very well, or they think their parents
are like the biggest losers in the world, but they care about them a lot.
So there's no way that you can have both.
Like you will just turn into the basically the biggest loser ever
or be a really cool but bad dad.
Yeah, I would definitely rather be the latter.
They don't need me.
They don't. I gave them everything they got nine months before they were born.
They have what fucking they have literally
a thousand hours of audio of me speaking if they want to learn something from me.
And it would be probably a lot more about the time.
I don't need to.
I mean, I'm going to fucking I'm not going to do shit.
I'm going to shut down.
I'm with you, man.
Yeah. Make a version of my voice.
I'm going to school.
I'm their teacher every year.
Yeah. Yeah.
Age progressed.
I'm the same age as them.
But I don't do anything the rest of the time.
You're the same age as them?
They're learning from three year old me.
Oh, OK.
Yes. Here's a great idea.
You can you you program in AI talks.
It looks exactly like you.
You leave the country, you start going to China.
You're impregnating more women, spreading your seed.
You know how it is.
You're trying all sorts of different Michelin star restaurants.
But then everybody tells your kid,
by the way, you see that box over there, that computer,
your dad is in that computer.
And when you turn 18, he'll come out of the computer.
On his 18th birthday.
Yeah, he'll become real.
We'll download him.
On his 18th birthday, front door, knock at the front door.
Well, yeah, you don't show up.
A letter that says, sorry, I did not want to come.
Oh, you much fun.
They open the front door fog machine behind you.
You walk out in like a silver jumpsuit.
Oh, and really long flowing black.
Yes. Yes. And then at that point, you don't have any legal reason.
You get to kind of play it by ear.
Do I like this kid? Do I think he's whack?
Yeah. If it's whack, it's like, you know, you're 18.
I'll fucking peace out.
But if it's cool, you get to enjoy like having a kid finally. Yeah.
- I was thinking how dope it would be.
- I think I would like to raise a kid at like age 12.
That's, and for just that one year.
I could do a lot of impact there.
- You being 12? - The rest of that,
mom will take care of it.
- Oh.
- It should definitely be asymmetrical.
- Yeah.
- Can you imagine if somebody was raised by their mom
for 12 years and then had one year with their dad?
That would honestly be the same level of impact.
- It would, it would.
- You don't remember. - It would be the
Highlights of their life.
What's a dad going to do for you?
From 8, from 0 to 12.
When you're a fucking 9.
Nothing, nothing.
Yeah.
You're useless.
Not a damn thing.
You sit around and you bring home bacon.
Yeah.
Right?
Age 12, golf course.
Yep.
Age 12, boxing gym.
Age 12, Tijuana.
I'm looking at your homework and saying I used to know how to do that.
I loved that, man.
And you know, my mom, when I was a kid, my mom was like,
"You know, your dad is like a math genius,
like really, really talented at math."
And then I would bring home Long Division,
and be like, "You know what, son? I'm stumped.
I just don't—you're gonna have to ask your younger brother about this one."
That's just so cool, man.
I can't wait to be so useless.
Well, you can just slide in them.
They will just believe anything.
It's a thing.
It's true.
- Because like, Photoshop yourself being the CEO of Apple,
and they were like, "Oh my God, my dad has cancer."
- I actually invented the iPhone.
- I actually invented having cancer.
Speaking of--
- It'd be cool if you could just lie to your kids.
- You definitely can. - For a decade.
- My dad lied to me.
I don't even know what is real about my dad's life.
He's told me stories that are so fucking crazy
that I'm like, and when I was a kid, I was like,
"Man, my dad's had a wild ride."
And then I'll be watching a movie,
see the exact same scene happen.
(laughing)
I go, "Huh, what a coincidence,
"that happened to my dad too."
But I'm afraid to ask him,
hey did your friend's head really get chopped off
by a tunnel 'cause he stuck it out of the top of a van?
And if it's real and he's like,
"Yeah, it was actually really, really bad."
Then now I'm like--
- What movie will you pretend that is your life?
I think I will go with "Ugly Jays."
- "Breaking Bad."
- Forrest Gump.
- I said movie, you fucking,
you go with "Breaking Bad."
I didn't hear what you said.
I mean, movie TV, what's the difference these days?
I don't know, name a movie.
That's too hard.
You know that's too hard.
Just name one movie.
I would say, I would do Free Guy with my kids.
It's so weird, man.
I used to be in a video game.
Oh, J. Gamer's so good.
Gamer is great.
I used to be on Death Row.
Let me tell you something about--
you know what you just did?
You just lied to your brother.
Let me tell you something about lying.
I used to be on death row and there was a rich guy,
some kid who was controlling my body
while my wife was in another game
and she was getting fucked, your mom.
- Yeah.
- And actually that's how you were born.
And I used to have a collar on my head
and if I did the wrong thing it exploded.
I used to have to kill all these different guys
with gang tattoos.
And then I earned my freedom.
And I'm not really sure what the point of the story was
but just know that that did happen to me.
- Right.
- I don't remember what, oh, Gamer goes.
- I remember watching it way long ago,
but I have no idea what happens in Gamer,
except that there's nudity.
- Yeah, I watch Gamer at Chad's house
in his mom's bed with him.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
And we were, and then she walked in and she--
- Of course, at that exact moment.
- It was right at the exact moment, she skipped,
she was cool, she skipped past it
and then let us watch the rest of the movie.
- She put a timer, she looked online when it came up.
- She had to have known, she had to have fucking known.
She looked on Conservapedia to see
what the entry was for Gamer.
- No.
I, you know, movies are hard, man.
I can't, name another movie, I can't do it.
Super Mario.
- Madagascar.
- Yeah.
- Madagascar, I don't remember what movie it was,
but I had some fucking movie that I would watch
all the time when I was a kid on like VHS or DVD
or something, and at the beginning of the movie
It had a preview for Madagascar, which can you believe they used to do that?
They used to put-
I know.
Ads for other movies.
That's so insane.
Yeah.
They put a commercial for Madagascar, but had no video from the actual movie.
It was just Ben Stiller in a big white room, and he was like, "I want to tell you guys
a little bit about a island called Madagascar."
And then he pulls out a globe, and he's like, "It's this little tiny island off of Africa."
It made me so mad and I wanted to hate the movie so bad, but then it came out and I saw it
And you saw it was pretty good. I want to move it move it and you're like
I want to move it move it Sasha Baron Cohen the lemur and I was I got I loved it. I love that movie. Yeah
I would like to change it. I saw it dropped it gorgeous the other day, which I don't know if you've seen that movie
No from the like late 90s
Will Sasso is in it
Look, it's Will Sasso and he's playing a character that's literally just the retarded guy
Love that
So a fat guy that they called the retard
The joke is that he's jacking off to underage girls. Oh, okay. They used to do it differently in the 90s, man
They did I loved it. I look it was like such a treat seeing Will Sasso
Do you guys ever had speaking of the 90s? I've been listening to a lot of Nirvana recently
You know how people fantasize about winning the lottery?
Like a lot of men will like one time a day fantasize about winning the lottery, what you would do.
Yeah.
Do you ever listen to a song and you fantasize about what if you had come up with this song instead of this band?
Um, no.
I have found myself doing that a bunch recently where I was like, man, if I came up with this song, my life would be so fucking awesome.
With their vinyl songs?
Yeah, with different Nirvana songs I've been listening to.
Which ones?
"Come As You Are."
I was literally at the park the other day with Phil throwing a ball and I was like,
"I think if I had a genie, one of my three wishes, of course I would wish for world peace and hair."
Yeah, more hunger.
But with my third one, my throwaway wish, because that's what you do with a genie.
two, you do two benevolent large scale wishes.
Yeah.
World peace and me having hair.
But then on the third one, you go weird and you need to do something that nobody else
would do.
Because the genie's heard it all before and he's going to fucking trash you.
That's going to be the rough thing.
Yeah, he's going to be like, not a very good choice, sir.
Yeah.
Pretty boring.
He's going to try to turn it.
The thing is, if you don't wish for things that affect everybody, he's going to do his
little trickery.
Yeah.
third one I would probably delete or Nirvana song and then and then just like
do that that Beatles movie or that movie about the guy with the Beatles yeah yeah
and I would do that with Nirvana and people go bye see okay so that's a
perfect example of course men have had this fantasy forever because somebody
wrote that movie yeah yeah I got a hypothetical for you okay okay you get your hair
back but your wife becomes bald. She can't grow hair anymore.
That's what you take away out of this situation.
Okay.
Wait.
You wish for world peace, everyone becomes bald. You wish for hair, you're the only one
with hair, they kill you on the spot.
I, I, that doesn't scare me at all. I'm not afraid to die if it means saving the entire
But I would definitely go me have hair because she can wear wigs that's
culturally acceptable. You can wear wigs. I can't walk around with wigs dude.
People will... Yes you can dude. No I can't. And also I'm you know on camera talent dude I
want to be a news anchor one day I need hair. Yeah do you have a like a news anchor
demo that we can go through right now? Just welcome back to the news and tell
I mean, just give me a news story.
Um...
The...
A dog just died.
A dog got exploded by ISIS
in Texas.
Breaking news!
This afternoon, a dog
in Texas has been blown up
by ISIS.
Stick with us, 6pm. We got the rest of the details.
Back to Rex
with the weather.
That was really good, man.
I'm very impressed. Well you need to do the weather now.
What does a weatherman do?
He throws this. That is the gayest hand I've ever seen.
I have never seen somebody throw their hand up in a gayer way.
Is this gay? Yes it is. You're the weatherman.
What does a weatherman do?
What does a weatherman do? What does he do?
He just points behind him and he's like yep.
78 degrees.
Yo, what the fuck is up?
There's about to be hella clouds in the north.
The sun is gonna rise.
The sun's gonna go down.
I think you've also never watched the Weather Channel.
At least it settles in a fine location.
Probably doing Red Hot Chili Peppers lyrics.
We got some wind coming this way
and some air coming this way.
You know what they do on the running videos
is they accidentally draw some kind of cock and balls.
Yeah, you know, you got the wind here
and you got the fucking wind also here.
That's what I'm doing.
Day one of being a weatherman,
I would draw like the most photorealistic pussy you've ever seen on the thing.
Just to get one for the girls.
And there's also going to be a category five hurricane.
It's going to kill.
There's going to be a tornado right here pointing with my tongue.
That's dope.
Asking the guy who runs the sport board if we have brown.
(laughing)
- Brackety brown with the pen.
- How do you even get into that kind of job?
- You know, it's very funny.
There is a weatherman that I know, an ex-weatherman.
- Okay.
- Ross, who's in our Discord,
that he doesn't play any games with us,
but he used to be a weatherman.
- Really?
- He was a weatherman for like a West Virginia,
like small town things, like his opening gig.
Everybody starts small in the weather game.
And he made like $20,000 a year being a weatherman
for this crappy little news station.
And then he ended up quitting
'cause he was like, "This sucks dick, dude."
- How much do you have to work if you're a weatherman?
Is that like a 40 hour a week job?
- Well, 'cause you're also a full-time meteorologist.
You're just on camera a combined 40 minutes a day.
But the rest of the time you're trying to figure out
what the fuck you're gonna,
you're coming up with material for the weather thing.
Yeah, they're just looking at you're in a coffee shop trying to come up
Fuck dude, I got a fucking full page of weather
I got a forecast due by tomorrow, and I don't know what the fuck I'm doing
I don't even have the first idea what tomorrow's gonna look like yeah, right so much coffee. You're shitting in the bathroom
I got it the thing is man. It's always gonna shit
Rain is such a safe bet
(laughing)
- Tomorrow's basically gonna shit all over
the northern part of town.
- It's gonna shit tomorrow, guys.
(laughing)
- But yeah, you just, you gotta sit there,
you gotta be turning dials, pressing buttons,
flipping switches, and then you, I don't know.
I have a real desire to get into a hobby like that,
like meteorology, like either meteorology or hand radio.
- It's very math intensive.
- Something with a, yeah, something that is like--
- We should start our own radio station, dude.
- I want ham radio.
I wanna be talking to guys
and accidentally falling in love with men.
- Breaker breaker.
- Yeah, yeah.
Breaker, yeah, I mean that is so cool, man.
I went to a guy's house one time.
- You can't do ham radio in New York City.
- Yeah, you can.
- Yeah, you can, I've heard of it.
- Yeah, you can do ham radio anywhere.
I went to, I had to install a glass shower door
one time for a guy.
And he was like, he just liked me
and my partner's kind of vibe.
And he was like, "You guys want to see something really cool?"
And we were like, "Yeah."
And he brought us into his garage and he showed us probably a $20,000 ham radio setup.
And he was like, "This is like, basically has ruined my wife's life that I have spent
all our money on this."
That's so expensive.
And he showed us.
That's sick, dude.
He had like so, I mean, walls and walls of shit.
Yeah.
That's awesome.
Ham radio is one of those hobbies that you can get into at any, like to any level of
investment.
You can like spend so much money on that shit.
Yeah.
Uh, most people just never do.
But this guy, he had like, and he lived pretty modestly, didn't have a big house.
He just had a glass shower door.
He said the glass shower door is the one thing that his wife is like allowed to buy.
And then he buys $500 of radio equipment every week.
That's fucking insane dude.
Yeah, I don't, I don't know anything about ham radio, so I don't really know.
I barely know, I don't even know how it works really.
It's just a way that you can,
it's some like person to person radio thing.
- Yeah, well model trains,
I would assume it just like gets a bigger model.
Like how much bigger is the radio gonna be
for it to be like $20,000?
- Well it's not just the radio,
it's basically the same investment as like audio equipment.
- Yeah. - Okay.
- Yeah, but you just do it plugged
into this crazy radio thing
and then you get one that can have an even bigger
field I guess, like that kind of thing.
- Okay.
- It's pretty dope.
- Yeah.
- This is ridiculous. - Very diminishing returns
on that as well.
Spending money on audio equipment.
- I wanna get into model trains
because I would do model disasters.
That would be my-- - Like a little model Ohio?
- Yes. - A little model
chemical spill?
- Well I would have model fucking,
speaking of models, a beautiful model woman
Just ride up on the tracks and keep an eye on the track there.
And then a guy looks a lot like me going to save her, but he doesn't save her.
Or you can do it.
You can put your actual wife on the model train tracks.
Kind of higher down.
And then, you know, she's like, Oh, what a fun little game.
It's it's not going to hurt.
And then she notices as it's coming around, then there's a knife
tied to the front of it with duct tape.
Then she also realizes that I've set it up like a trolley problem.
But the other side of the thing is like a watermelon, like something
It doesn't matter at all.
I'm like, I don't know, it's a tough decision.
Either kill you or lose what looks like an amazing summer watermelon.
Speaking of this type of situation and billionaires,
I think you've taken up an idea that another great mind in our time has thought of before.
Which is?
According to the fabled man, Steven Spielberg, who was just like this.
when he was a kid he would, in the movie,
according to the movie, he would just like
have a model train and just like crash it and record it
because he saw it in a movie once
and he was like so obsessed with that.
- That's kind of cool.
- So I think you could be the next Steven Spielberg.
- I think there's pretty much no doubt
that I could be the next Steven Spielberg.
How hard is it to direct a movie?
Probably not very hard.
- Have you seen some of the movies that come out?
- They're bullshit.
- I mean I haven't, but I assume they're pretty bad.
- I haven't seen almost any movie,
but I know that it's as easy as fucking anything.
Yeah. If you just market a movie for China,
you can get like an insane amount of budget. Uh,
but you do have to put like the war sweating in the, in the world.
And also you have to put a T-Rex somewhere in there.
I will see how China will just like take movie posters and then Photoshop
Chinese faces onto the people in the movie poster and make like an identical
copy of the movie.
Just yeah. Yeah. But just the poster. That's so cool. Yeah.
There's like one with like the rock and they like poorly photoshopped a watch off of his hand and then just like put a Chinese guy on his face.
I think China's incredible. I think we should all go there at some point.
We would love to go to China. I would love to go to basically any city honestly. Any of the big cities.
Yeah, maybe Chongqing.
Yeah, I would love to go there. Shanghai.
Shanghai, yeah
You hit you said Shanghai, but then for Zhang Qing you said Chongqing. It's literally called Chongqing. I don't know
Do you think I'm being racist
No
Not even a little I do think I do think it's I do think it's definitely a little funny you instantly went to Chongqing
As the as the city I said
We can disprove the racism right now, what do you want to see in in Chongqing? I don't know probably some stores
Okay, I want to see the rivers that converge that's cool. They have one dirty river and one clean river that can
Say there are two rivers
All right, bye. See you next week guys. Bye. Bye