[Sipping]
[Burp]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer broadcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[Burp]
This is a journey into sea,
into the land,
Bud Light.
Ha!
Foo!
Ribbit!
I'm on fire.
Beers we drank, motherfucker.
With Jubio, Caleb, and Rex.
[INAUDIBLE]
Yeah, it's recording right now.
We're recording right now.
We're recording?
OK.
Let's go.
Are you-- are you fucking kidding me?
[LAUGHTER]
Are you-- are you fucking out of your mind?
What's-- what's wrong?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
You went to JCPenney 10 minutes ago?
This is not--
This is ridiculous.
I need a drink.
All right.
- What's this?
- Okay, let's reset, let's reset.
You need to reset.
- I got the memo a little too late.
- I don't wanna hear it.
You don't have nice clothes sitting in your closet.
So you already,
you already shouldn't have been here in the first place.
But we're gonna go ahead and get started.
Hello.
And welcome to Liquor We Enjoyed.
We're your hosts, Caleb Rex and Julio.
Tonight we'll be guiding you through a journey of tasting different kinds of notes.
We're called the Tasters.
We're the Tasters.
For tonight we're the Tasters.
If I can get- ah, hold on!
It seems like I can begin because I have opened mine.
This is legitimately the first ever liquor bottle that I've ever purchased with my money.
So I have purchased Gentleman Jack.
Wow.
A double mellow Tennessee whiskey by Jack Daniels.
By Jack Daniels.
Okay.
Price check.
How much is that little ass bottle?
$22.
So that's expensive because that's what?
180 mil?
275.
Yes. Actually, this is $3.75.
What the hell? That thing looks tiny. You have big hands.
I do.
That looks amazing. So, what I want you to do is sip it.
Do a little...
Give me the notes on this one.
And you're enjoying this on the rocks.
On the rocks.
Mmm.
Oh my god.
It's slightly, like, oaky. Like an oak flavor.
Okay.
Very enjoyable, though.
I actually am enjoying it.
Alright, now, normally we would do basketball, right?
But basketball is a sport for poor people to watch, just like football and soccer.
Yeah, this has been penicillin-y.
Give me squash. Squash player.
In a squash player height, so 4'11" to 5'4"ish, somewhere in there.
How about, instead of doing that, we do jockey heights?
heights. Yeah, okay. Jockey heights. Oh yeah, that's great. Yeah. Three foot nine. Oh, 74
pound Guatemalan jockey. Wow. Okay. All right. Three of his last four races. He's doing great.
I'd love with the biggest horse ever. Oh, I've opened mine. Okay. I've poured mine. I'd
like for you to take a look at this and guess what this is just on, just based on looking
on it. Probably maybe for you and your kindergarten outfit. You do have a scotch. Close. Boba?
Rye? This is an Irish whiskey guys. And this is not just any Irish whiskey, but this is
one of the finest Irish whiskeys on the planet from one of the finest men that God has ever
graced us with. Guys, I'm talking proper 12. This is Conor McGregor's Irish whiskey.
That's awesome. This is the smallest bottle they had, guys.
This is 750 milliliters. I will never drink this. I do not like whiskey, historically.
But if there's one person that could change my mind on this disgusting drink, it might
just be one of the greatest. For the next month or so, we're going to be
playing Valorant at like 11pm.
- I'm gonna be like, oh wait, what do I have?
Oh, I have proper 12.
Cheers, my friends.
- Cheers.
It looks like he loves it.
What are the notes on that shit?
Smell it.
- Okay, hold on.
Oh my God, man.
I just hate whiskey, son.
Why did you do this?
I don't know.
I don't...
I...
I mean, the thing is, I don't even know
what good whiskey is supposed to taste.
I've had really good whiskey. Noah brought back some like...
Yes.
He had like that $600 bottle of whiskey that they sold him for $60.
It tasted like gasoline.
It tasted just like this. I couldn't tell the difference at all.
It all just...
I feel like it's like a cilantro thing.
like the notes are like putting a bunch of like metal in your mouth from like
different sources you know when you when you were a kid you used to put your
mouth on the water fountain yeah it's like rebar shavings that exact kind of
taste of like well-trodden metal but you know I'm gonna give this 10 out of 10
maybe to a two-foot tall jockey this is one of the best drinks I've ever had.
what's up?
I think I may have had the same sort of idea or like conception about this this
whole episode as Caleb. Well clearly fucking not. Regarding the drinks.
Again you are you look like you served Mai Tais on Jeffrey Epstein. You look like an
extra in the White Lotus. People are saying I look great. No. Anyways. You look like you aged in a bit.
- Yesterday.
- You look like you worked at Trader Joe's.
- Yes!
- People in the chat might remember this.
I was looking at some YouTube videos.
I was like, hmm, I think because of who I am,
I should just get some tequila, right?
And also, what do you know,
there's tequila with my name on it
that I was watching a review of it.
But the guy just kept smelling it and saying made up stuff.
I felt like I was in that John Wilson episode.
So I just went ahead and I just got some mezcal.
This is mezcal from Oaxaca.
It is called 400 bunnies or 400 conejos.
It's joven, so it means it's young.
And I've got a 100% galvanic.
And this here feels good man cup that my girlfriend brought back from Mexico City.
Okay, give us a little sip and give us a little talk.
Um...
He likes it.
It's gonna taste like nothing.
Oh!
It's probably because it's been sitting in the ice water for...
Yeah, I can tell, those are tiny ice cubes. It's definitely melted a lot.
It's a hot day today. Hence my outfit.
I'm at the beach.
No, you're not.
That's not what you do at the beach. You don't go, "Whoa!"
Whoa, there's flyers up there!
You don't look up. The beach is on the ground.
There's a peach over there! I can see it!
Give me a kite!
The flyers. Anyways, uh, this is a short guy. This is a, uh, a...
One centimeter tall guy.
He's the best jockey in the world.
He's just drinking water.
That's just a horse.
That's not water, dude. I opened this shit.
Look, you can see that I...
Is that why jockeys need to be small?
Is because the more... the smaller they are, the more... the closer it is to just a horse?
'Cause the jockey's not doing anything but weighing the horse down.
the
What's a jockey speaking English to him?
What do you mean direct it? Go forward.
They have horse races all the time.
They have dog races. Put a... what are horses like?
Carrots? Put a moving carrot.
They gotta make him turn.
Dogs can get into a scrap.
They can bump into each other.
They're like NASCAR cars.
Horses...
Like an F1 car.
They like touch wheels and immediately just explode
and murder the whole crowd.
That's a good point.
race crash compilation on YouTube?
You've just opened my mind to a brand new thing.
There's gotta be.
There's gotta be a Dale Earnhardt Jr. of horses.
Yeah.
Just to fucking go with it.
I feel like they did that in the Simpsons at some point.
Where a horse exploded.
I think if your horse gets hurt and you're a jockey, they should put you down with the
horse.
I agree.
What else are you gonna do?
Become an actor?
You're too short to do anything.
- You're too short.
Tom Cruise, we already got it.
- I think the horses are really akin to Cars in this aspect.
Like the horses get replaced every single day.
- Well, I know, but I'm saying like, you know,
I think maybe like a couple horses.
If you're banging up too many horses,
you don't get to retire.
They just also take you out back.
- Do you remember the NFT horse race?
- Yeah, yes.
- That's so dope.
- Are they still doing that?
- Yeah.
- We might have a thing that we can do on our phones
at the restaurant tonight.
That would be fun.
Yeah.
For those of you who don't know-- wait, go ahead.
I'm just going to go ahead and say this.
I'm pretty much like the same as a chat person right now.
These-- this group of friends, meaning
Kale, Brex, Noah, Brian, you know, the Peefers,
for the entire yesterday, they've
been talking and talking about this legendary night.
They've been building it up.
Oh my god, we're going to go downtown.
So excited.
We're going to start with some drinks.
We're gonna do some gambling.
We're gonna hit up the nicest place we can find out.
Noah doesn't want Brian to eat.
I don't know what that's all about.
I didn't really listen to the whole thing.
- Well, 'cause he doesn't, you gotta save.
It's all you can eat.
- I'm just a third, I'm just an observer.
I'm just a chatter.
I'm just seeing this happening on my screen.
I was like, I don't know, what's gonna happen, guys?
Can I see it?
Can someone record the entire night
and show it to me on stream?
But I just don't know.
And that's what the address is.
- No cameras, please.
What is this legendary night that you're about to embark on?
Guys, well, it's two, possibly three pronged.
Number one, as soon as this is over, I'm going to get my fruity ass over to this Absinthe
bar.
And I've had Absinthe one time and I spit it out.
But two is the magic number when you're trying foo.
So what I will do is take a big sip.
No matter, it doesn't matter what it tastes like, I'm going to take a big sip and I'm
going to have an open mind.
And then once we have two or three or four or five absinthe drinks in us, we are going
to an all-you-can-eat Korean barbecue place that is of the highest order, some might say.
A fancy Korean barbecue place with Wagyu beef, man.
You probably don't even know what Wagyu beef is.
Let me tell you what it is.
Specifically A5 Wagyu beef.
A5 Wagyu beef.
This is seriously meat.
And this is meat on a level you've never seen before.
It is the fattiest cut of meat in the entire world.
It is the butter.
And to me that's the best part of a steak, the fat parts.
I always just take off the fat and just eat that.
I don't even want all the meat stuff.
So this is perfect for me.
It is going to be like if we ate 10 pounds of butter.
And I'm really looking forward to it.
It is going to be amazing.
And then there's a 90 minute time limit.
So the whole point is we've been stretching our stomachs all day with water like Matt
that's
minutes they will be packing their bags back to Korea so fucking fast because
this place is going down. Are you guys going in like at like fucking almost 11
p.m. it is a 1030 reservation 1030 reservation because guess what this place
is so exclusive and also we canceled our last reservation so this was the only
one we could get because it's so fucking exclusive there's so many fucking
in
It's cold because of the ice in my glass, but it fills me with fire and warmth.
It's smoky as well.
It is smoky.
It's very smoky.
Let me describe the two hours that I had before we started podcasting.
Go ahead.
In preparation.
So, fans of the podcast will know that I have been sick for the last week.
Yeah.
What they don't know is that on Monday night, I got food poisoning from a Costco steak strip.
That proceeded to completely destroy me.
And made me sick yet again.
So I still have the same cough I've had since the last time we recorded.
So you got steak in your lung?
I did. I did. I was really going through it.
As my roommate told me upon hearing me throw up, I sounded like Bugs Bunny throwing up.
So here's what I'm hearing from you.
There's nothing in the world that you want more to eat tonight than about eight pounds
of steak.
Yes.
So anyway.
Steak is only bringing good memories to you.
It is just going to be awesome.
So I went to Rite Aid down the street and I bought some 12 hour extended release mucus
relief DM Max that has 60 milligrams of dextromethaphan in it.
So enough to get you a small buzz going in the first place.
And then I walked back and I bought a Popeye's chicken sandwich and I ate that as I was walking.
And then after crushing that chicken sandwich on my walk back to my apartment,
a kind man named Aki approached me and he said, "Hey boss, do you smoke weed?"
Whoa.
"I sell the best weed in Brooklyn."
"And wouldn't you believe it?"
I don't know if it is, but it smelled nice.
And he made me put his number in his phone so he could give me free weed in the future.
And his name was Aki.
And he's like, "My name is Aki."
And I believe him too.
and I
he was sitting on the, he was sitting on the porch
you just saw me walking
see but they, let me, I'm gonna wager a guess that you were not
wearing the same clothes that you're wearing right now
my friend. That is true, I was wearing
my shirt that says incel and block letters
yep
I can't believe you own that
that is crazy man
that, go from the incel
shirt and now you look like a
a
oh god
Can you tell the story? I don't know if you tell this in the podcast.
Can you tell the story when you were just stuck in your room because you were wearing that shirt and there were women in the apartment?
And you were so ashamed to leave the room.
I was not ashamed, I just thought it was funny.
I have shame shirts.
Yeah, it was funny.
Yeah, I have some shirts I don't really wear.
I don't.
You do. I'm looking at one actually.
Yeah, I'm not ashamed of this shirt.
You really should be. You really should be, man.
Boom! Where should I go?
From both sides. Bang bang!
Rex is dressed like the principal of a Japanese middle school and he looks so much better
than you right now.
I do.
He looks like the orchestra.
I do look like a villain from Persona.
You really do.
I'm bullying children and they have to change my opinion on that.
Yeah, yeah.
Change the opinion.
That'll save the world.
These Persona kids are so foolish, man.
Don't even get me started on Persona.
I don't even want to go there, man.
I'm trying not to talk about Persona Challenge.
Yes, I'm doing it right now.
I will never talk about it again.
No, I'm not talking about it.
So I'll talk about it.
I just wanted to say, I went to the liquor store by me.
Thank you for banning me.
Oh my god.
I had no idea.
I had no idea I was going to do that shit.
Anyway.
The liquor store by me does samples.
So I went in and I said, "Hey,
I mean,
I got a thing with some friends.
I need a liquor I can sip on.
Maybe a mezcal, maybe a tequila, maybe a whiskey.
What do you got?
And they said, what are you talking about?
And I said--
- He said, what are you talking about?
- They're like, sip on.
And I was like, you know, like, I need to,
I need it to be like a high quality, small bottle.
You know, I'm not mixing it with anything.
I need it to be like good.
And they were like, okay, I kind of understand.
So I was like, "How about a mezcal?"
And they're like, "Okay."
So this is like our cheapest mezcal.
And they poured me like a little half shot.
And they're like, "Here you go."
And I was like, "Okay."
- And surely you spit this out.
- Surely.
- Like a sommelier.
- I took a little sip and I was like, "Oh, that's good."
And then I knocked back the whole thing.
And then I was like, "So what about your tequila?
What about this, you know, like maybe like a Espolon White?"
You know?
Espolon Blanco as they call it.
Yes, they call it Blanco.
And so I took a little sip of that and then I knocked it back.
And then I said, "What about like a rye or like a scotch whiskey?"
You know, and they're like, "Okay, yeah, we've got some of that."
Took a little sip, knocked it back.
I was like, "Well, what do you recommend?"
Okay, the other choice.
- First choice, now that I've had four that I like
at the free bar, what would you give me for free?
- Yeah, so they gave me a vodka shot, a potato vodka,
which was honestly not that bad,
but I would definitely-- - That would have been
a crazy one to pull out and sip by itself, though.
- So I ended up just buying this,
which was of the small bottles, the second most expensive.
- Damn.
They just have like sampling bottles for everything?
- For the most part, yeah.
- That's crazy, man.
But you got twisted at the liquor store.
- Just a little bit.
- They should let you do that shit
with cigarettes at the gas station.
- Right?
- They should give you a tiny little cigarette.
- I've been to the bake stores where they have the pistas.
- I'd like to try the Marlboro Red 100.
- Really? - With a pista?
- Yes.
- Do they clean it?
- That's why you're like, that's why you got like this.
- So when I was at, when I was in Arizona,
On Christmas day, I went to buy a vape.
Christmas day, I was like, I need a vape.
- Yeah, I've been-- - And I went to
the only place that was open nearby,
which was like four miles away from my parents' place.
And I walked in and the guy had like a rack
of all the different vapes.
And then he had these little like tips,
like rubber tips that were like individually packaged.
and you just put that on top of it and just,
oh, just sommelier it.
And I did, I hit them all.
- That's crazy.
- Yeah.
- I've been watching sommelier videos,
and guys, I think I might be a super taster.
- I think you can just-- - Yeah, what do you taste?
- I think anyone can just be that.
I think you can just make shit up.
- Right now, my tongue and my teeth.
- Yeah, how do they taste?
- They taste like brushed teeth.
Yep.
Yeah.
Looks good.
Like toothpaste.
Like normal toothpaste and flossing.
Right.
Good kind of shit.
Yeah.
But not like...
I didn't just find a piece of chicken in my mouth.
Okay, here's a question I have for you guys.
So if you leave chicken on the counter after you made it, it's like bad news after like
an hour or less.
Like 40 minutes or something.
They're like, "Don't eat this chicken."
But if you find a piece of chicken in your teeth that's been there all day long, can
you swallow it or am I supposed to spit that shit out?
All day?
Like all day type beat with this chicken in my mouth.
I think you can just eat it.
It's already there.
That's what I'm saying.
But according to foods, oh food safety, you need to be food safe, certified.
You're not supposed to eat old chicken.
Well you're not gonna serve it.
This is like 8 year old, or 8 day, not 8 day, 8 hour old chicken sitting in my mouth.
Sorry the proper 12 is affecting me.
Yeah.
I believe because it's coated in saliva that the bacteria is not gonna grow on it in the
same way.
So I should just be spitting on all the fucking chicken I make and leaving it out?
Yeah.
Alright I'll do that then.
Next question.
Also, also, your mouth is not room temperature.
It's warmer than room temperature, my friend.
Yeah, it's oven temperature.
I don't think it's quite oven temperature.
This bottle is really so striking visually.
I do like it a lot.
That's why you got it, huh?
No, I got it because my girlfriend told me to get this.
Because I just didn't know.
How much did that run you?
By the way, the proper 12, 750 mil, 30 bucks.
$2 cheaper than Jameson.
I almost went with the Jameson,
and then I was like, I've had Jameson before, man.
And I don't like that shit.
There was one time when my brother was trying to get me
to take a shot of Jameson one night,
and he was all drunk and he handed me the fucking,
the Solo cup, and was like, come on, take a shot.
And I was like, okay, man.
And I actually stood next to the sink
and threw it behind my head, into the sink.
and
the other
uh...
is this all as well
and
the satellite drinking
as much as
yet
I do not like when people have too many drinks and start going wild.
I don't like, unless they're girls, I do not like guys going wild off of alcohol guys.
Well, in what sense?
Like violent wild?
No, like, "Oh, let's watch a movie!"
Shut up, man, you're fucking drunk.
Okay.
Or, no, that's a bad example.
Like, yeah, I can't even really think of a good example right now.
Oh, we should gamble!
We should lose like $500!
That kind of stuff I actually do like.
I guess I do like it when people drink a lot.
Yeah.
The more I think about it.
I guess it makes people kind of a little more fun.
Yeah, I mean, I don't, I'm not a particular fan of being around someone who's like...
I think it makes people scary.
Over that line.
I don't like society when they're drunk.
unless i'm also over that line
see i don't like going over that line when i go to the i don't like going over
this is why i go to the bathroom if you've ever drank with me you know that
i would i go to the bathroom poly forty times every time we go to the bar
and the reason is
yes i have to be
mostly i go in there and i assess my situation
you can't do that outside the bathroom
no because i have a sitting down and i'm it uh... experiencing jovial joy with my
comrades there's there's no telling what kind of where my feelings are actually
coming from if I go to the bathroom I smell piss and shit and it makes me
think about my death a little bit and I go is this really how I want to be
spending my time yeah sitting here smelling piss and shit my fucking face
four inches out of the urinal well again you don't have to be in and then I just
go home what are you talking about why would I what how would I ever come to
this
history of the last like four years you would be able to actually put on a like
it's a completely it's like a perfect timeline of me getting dumber and dumber
each year like the average video is worse and worse each year I mean this is
just the thing that naturally happens to people where it's like you transform from
being like a curious young adult into like a stupid guy that's at work you
You know, like the dumb guy that you worked with when you were younger.
Yeah, I feel like when I was younger I used to walk around and be like, "Oh man, I'm so
smart.
I'm probably smarter than anybody."
And now I walk around and there's homeless guys that I'm 100% sure are smarter than me.
Like 100% sure.
Because they're like, they know how to open up a beer with a lighter.
And I'm like, "I don't know how to fucking do that."
I don't think that's...
I don't even understand the physics of that.
And then I look at my phone.
They don't have a phone to look at.
These are the most free guys in the universe.
Well, you got that phone with your phone, miss.
Do you think phones are making us dumb?
I think my phone is making me dumb.
I don't think it's the phone's fault.
I think that I have very little impulse control and probably wasn't that smart to begin with.
They call them smart phones, but they don't make you very smart.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
- Yeah, no, that's true.
- That's the direction I went with them.
- Yeah, they should call them dumb phones then.
- They should call them dumb phones.
- They should make, making,
making kids misbehave phones. - He should call them
dumb phones.
- Yeah. - Misbehave phones.
- They should call them dumb phones.
- I thought the other day, I thought about,
I thought about saving up to buy an iPad.
I have no use for an iPad.
I just want a bigger phone that I can use in my house.
Like, and I can feel good, like,
I left my phone in the kitchen
and now I'm gonna sit on my iPad until four in the morning.
Do you remember the Microsoft table?
Do you remember?
No. Is it like one of those Pac-Man tables
that they have at pizza restaurants?
Kind of. It was like when the iPad first
came out, or it was like tablets
or the future, and then they
Microsoft had like a demo
for like a thing that was like
a Pac-Man sized thing
that was just an all like
you know, touch screen
thing. And it was like, "Oh my god!"
"Oh my god!
a table that's a touch screen.
- Were people saying this like it was a bad thing
or a good thing?
- Like a good thing.
- Oh yeah.
- Yeah, 'cause people just thought they were gonna
keep making bigger and bigger touch screens.
- I always got sad that they never did anything
with Google Glass, man.
- Well, it's coming back.
- They did a video where a guy just
punches his wife. - Google Glass.
- What?
- Yeah.
Just a number one Google ads video.
- And it like calls the police?
No, she's like walking around your life like looking stuff up and then she gets punched in the face.
That's like a Google Glass ad.
I think that...
That's an ad, yeah, for Google Glass.
That's an ad for Google Glass.
An ad could be on YouTube.
I saw an ad for Mr. Beast the other day.
He blew up a car.
He almost killed a guy yesterday.
You told me this and I didn't watch that video.
And I watch most MrBeast videos that come out.
And that's another, that started this year.
So that's another kind of downtrend for me.
- Yeah.
What?
- Like I'm getting stupider to the point where in 2023,
I'm at the point where I--
- You think that MrBeast is so smart?
- No, no, no.
That's what I mean.
It's obviously for dumb people.
And I watch every video.
- You think that MrBeast is the best guy
and become the dumbest guy.
- That's not true.
- On the podcast.
Stop looking at me.
- You're smart.
They start locally, but you're stupid. Why do I feel so drunk right now? I've had I've had two sips of this basically
But let's go for another let's go
Let's go hog wild
How I don't I?
Don't think I could drink
This whole thing in my entire life. This is so big
That is a lot of mess. I will say man make yourself do yourself a favor and make yourself a mezcal Rita
What's a mezcal rita?
It's basically like taco-belling mezcal, where you put a bunch of sugar in it, and a bunch of lime juice, and a bit of triple sec.
Which, by the way, I was talking to Eric today about, I think I have the most alcoholic-style liquor cabinet in the entire universe.
Where my my where I keep my liquor I keep it above my fridge and the only two things that are ever
on top of my fridge is a giant handle of triple sec and a giant thing of Campari
Because and no gin and no tequila right because I already used up all that stuff. I
Have never had all four
It's always a bottle of tequila for like three days and then it's gone because and then there's still a lot of triple sec left
That's a bad indicator
I've lived in this apartment for like almost a year now coming close to a year and it's like the first
Actual like I go home that we've had in the house
We only usually have like beers and we only really buy beers when I people are coming over or what I'm doing the podcast
We feel like a big-ass grown-up, um, I guess I just don't know we're gonna store this now because we don't have a place to store
It store in your mouth
Just drink the whole thing tonight man. I'm not gonna drink the whole thing
I don't I don't think I'm gonna drink another glass of this feels it feels good man. Let's go anymore
I'm gonna live or but I am gonna get a chaser something to chase with
You're gonna take a shot. Well, I'm not gonna take a shot
something else
No we can't do sh- dude we have such a long night planned man. I know I'm not gonna do a shot that's ridiculous. I've done like four shots already.
Wait do one though just right now. No. Alright hold on. Shots are disgusting man. I used to think I like taking them and I just don't.
Have you ever taken a shot of anything? Yeah. I just wouldn't think that you would do that.
So when I went to tequila, we tasted some tequila, but we drank it like you would drink wine.
We did the whole thing that, like the sommelier does, like you smell it and you're like, "Oh, that smells like fucking liquid."
But I think the only times I ever take shots is when I'm with you guys.
Same as the drinking every night type beat that I always do when I'm in New York.
I drink beers every night and sometimes we go to the gaming bar and either Noah or Caleb
or Brian go like "Yo, shots!"
Yeah, we are awesome.
I love that everyone in New York always drinks all the time.
New York is a giant drinking city.
You're muted, man.
I did not drink much before I moved here and I drink all the time.
Because it's the only thing to do, man.
you stay the bars are open till like four in the morning you get to go out
wait what else they give you looks like well that's not what you took your cough
medicine this is what they give you at uh you kept it well they just gave it to
me yeah this was throw it out they gave it to me they gave me this they gave this
This is a piece of plastic to me.
That's amazing man.
They gave it to me.
I'm going to have four drams of whiskey.
Four drams?
Four drams.
Okay.
Are you going to shoot it or are you going to normal it?
I am going to shoot it.
Yes sir.
No convincing at all.
Dude, why does whiskey hurt my stomach so bad?
I feel like I'm gonna throw up.
I think it's this specific one.
I think you're drinking a really bad one.
Oh my god, man. This shit is so disgusting.
Actually, that went down pretty easy.
Oh, god, dude. Whose idea was this?
Let's get one more going.
Yeah, why did we do this?
Because...
You wanted to.
Caleb wanted to.
She wanted to.
I said it! Caleb wanted to! What did I just say?
He wanted to dress up and try...
Yeah, first of all, Julio, you didn't dress up.
I am rebelling. I'm rebelling against you guys' magical awesome night that I can't even be part of.
Oh my god.
This is pure jealousy, man.
That's what I just said.
You're showing your true colors. I'll say it, and I don't want to say this, you're being jealous.
Yeah.
I actually don't care that my friends are hanging out at an amazing night.
I'm gonna be sitting at home.
No you don't.
I did it again. I wasn't looking.
Damn.
The Diamond Jelly Bar is a cigar type of vape.
Because it's so long.
Uh, vodka.
No!
Jägermeister.
My dad loved Jäger.
So that was what was in the house.
And so when I turned like 12,
he's like, "It's time to put some hair on your chest, son."
And you know.
He gave me my first beer.
I gave him my first shot.
When you were 12?
You know, got me fucked up.
Your dad got you fucked up when you were 12 years old?
Yeah, I mean it only took like three full mixed drinks, but yes.
That's a lot, man!
I've lived a full life, and I will be ready to die when I'm 40 years old.
Man, your dad is, uh...
I'm gonna be I mean he does not sound like a good guy this is not a good story
so there came a point like maybe a year after that where he realized that he had
a problem and apologized to me and was like I'm gonna become a changed man I'm not gonna drink anymore
and he kind of like really did and took it very seriously yeah I appreciated it but you know
yeah if you get to the point where you're drinking so much you're like my 12 year
the
It's Arizona State culture, how about that?
And now I actually seriously like beer.
Yeah.
You should have started with the whiskey.
I actually kind of did.
So I did, I had like, maybe I've said this before, but like,
the first time I ever had liquor was me and my buddy John Hamilton.
We raided my mom's liquor cabinet and the only things that she had were
Hennessy, vodka, and peppermint schnapps.
and we were like 15 and so we filled a red solo cup all the way to the top with
equal parts of each one of these and then we chugged it so we chugged like 16
ounces it was fun I mean I had no idea what I was doing. And just immediately blacked out like just
instantly blacked out on the beach. I've never blacked out. I lived near the beach we walked over there
fell asleep, completely blacked out, and then I came to and I was running in the rain back
to my house. It was like torrential downpour, running in the rain back home. And then I
like blacked out again. And then I came to and it was me, the last thing I remember was
walking out of my bathroom and my little brother had an electric drum kit that my uncle Matt
had given him and my buddy John was completely naked, dick and balls out, covered in sweat,
playing it unplugged.
That's awesome.
Like, just fucking beating the shit out of it.
It's unplugged, it's making no noise.
And then I didn't drink liquor for a year.
I don't think I drank liquor until I got to Boston.
You hit the skip cutscene drink.
You skipped all the cutscenes for that day.
I really did.
So I that that scared me off of it and now I vomited like a million times. Yeah, it was so it was so fucking disgusting and
John was like, are you sure we're supposed to drink this whole this much. I was like, yeah, man. I've seen it. Wait
Yeah, dude I did I wanted to do I did everything to the maximum
I was doing way too much of any time I'd ever tried a drug before I was like 22 or
alcohol or anything like that. I always wanted to go full bore instantly and every single
time regretted it and it was a terrible decision.
Yeah.
I only have one real story like that which is that I was a freshman in college and for
whatever reason we were, I bought this breathalyzer, like a $20 breathalyzer, and so we were trying
to see how drunk we could make ourselves. Just like the dumbest...
That was like a really fun game.
Yeah, like see who could blow the highest before like-
I played that game a lot.
Yeah.
We had a handle of Captain Morgan, which is a horrible alcohol drink.
Like just ice?
Captain Morgan?
Oh my god, dude.
And so my roommate and I drank literally the whole handle by like 4pm.
And so the dorm room that I lived in, the way the rooms were set up was it was like two
people in one room and then you had like a lofted bunk bed and your desk below you.
So I was on like kind of the far side, I had my record player like right next to it, I
had like a gift for my friend on top of the record player, and then I had like all of
my clothes in a pile directly beside the record player.
And then I woke up, because I immediately passed out from drinking.
I got in bed, and then I woke up and I threw up projectile vomit, just like a beautiful
rainbow arc, all over the gif, the record player, and everything.
And then I proceeded to try and get down from the bed and crawl to the toilet to make it
into the bathroom and just passed out on the ground with my ass out to which a
friend at the time walked in saw that took a picture and then posted it on
on
the
worst nightmare is getting drunk like that now.
You know?
Yeah, it's horrible.
If I get drunk to the point where I'm like, doing any, where anybody on earth could notice
that I'm drunk, that's like my, that's my biggest nightmare.
I want to be fully incognito, nobody has any idea, and to the point where you can't do that
anymore, you gotta, this is a bad place to be.
The last time I was really, really drunk was probably this time that I got in a massive
bar fight in California.
I know I've told you guys this, but I don't think I've ever said this on any podcast.
In 2019 or 2018, when I was living in LA, I guess it was 2019, my brother lived by this
trucker bar called the country girl which they demolished recently so I can tell
the story best bar ever it was like two pool tables a trucker bar it was like
giant like all 18 wheelers parked in the back they had like a giant lot it was
great and we it was me and my buddy Gus's last night in Los Angeles and we
so we went up we had to drive we were starting a drive across the country the
next day.
It's really like we have to have one last night at the country girl.
And we get there and everything's fine and then my brother's fiance starts bringing out
Mai Tais that she bought everybody and like Long Island iced teas, like this kind of girl
drink that none of us, like I'd never had one before.
And we all got really drunk and then I had to piss really bad.
I went into the bathroom for like 30 seconds to piss and everything was fine when I went
in the bathroom.
And then I came out of the bathroom and my brother was being strangled like this.
And my buddy Gus was on the floor sideways and a guy was stomping on his head.
And so I did what any guy would do and I grabbed all of our pool cues and put them in a bag
so nobody would distract him.
And then my brother noticed that I was out of the bathroom.
And the guy who was choking him,
my brother was being choked out,
was pointing at the guy and he was saying,
"Kill him, kill him," over and over again.
So I fight that guy and I get my brother off him
and then I go straight back to the pool cues
'cause it was the only thing of value
in the entire bar to me
'cause I'd just gotten a nice pool cue.
and I grabbed the bag and then somebody punches the back of my head
and like it's a giant bar brawl and some random person punches the back of my head
so I turn around and I punch them in the face
and it was
guys I don't know
it was
uh... like a forty five-year-old lady
that punched me in the back of the head
and you decked her out
you completely decked out a woman
Yeah, and so we ran out of the bar and we hid under a semi-truck for like two hours and
like the cops came and like tried to look at the security footage and the bartender knew
us so she like deleted all the security footage.
And then we couldn't find Gus forever, we found him in a bush outside of a Taco Bell
like a mile away later that night.
But yeah, then we got home and we kind of had all sobered up and we asked Gus what he said
to the guy and he couldn't remember a single thing.
But apparently my brother said that Gus walked up to this guy, said one sentence to him, and
then the guy punched him in the face and started stomping on his head.
And then so we had to go across country, we had to drive across country the next day, and
the entire drive across the country Gus had a giant red boot print in the side of his head
that people any person we met would be like
and then i see me to your guest
what you know that uh... shoe where i can see the size
imprinted like the punisher directly on the forehead
it was awesome and talking also was your it was awesome
uh... he i_d_ i mean against i don't know how they had a good question but it's
yeah yeah definitely had a concussion deftly slept a lot on the road which is
good for concussions i hear right you're supposed to do that
but i don't like that kind of thing i didn't like it then either but i'd really
don't like it now
yeah
the moment you turn like
twenty four it's a conscious decision to get into a bar fight
yeah to be a bar fight guy
is yeah like
you really just never like
also at that bar my buddy sound who's this like sound
we just call him sound his name's martel he's like uh...
he's like a three hundred pound
five foot five mexican guy
and he's like looks like a uh...
uh... bowling ball
and a guy
certified in him
and then pull that in life and stabbed him in the arm
and that happens
and the alexa have that kind of thing what happened as for all the time so we
are i'm lucky that the worst literally the worst in a penny turn that is that i
punched a woman in the face. That was the maximum crime that happened in the
entire night. Well right, nothing happened to you importantly. Yeah, exactly, yeah.
I can take a hit from a girl. I should have known when the hit when the fist
hit the back of my head that it was a girl. Right, but you were drunk, it's fine.
Yeah, I thought that I was running through you. You were worried that she was going to take the
pool cues at some point if you were, if you... That's why football players beat their lives, dude.
because they're drunk and then they assume that whenever someone hits them it's a huge
guy but it's actually just a tiny woman.
And then they hit him and they just, they blow back like it's like the Hulk, you know?
Yeah.
I think that the thing that I've always, that has always bothered me about that story is
always that my first instinct was just protect the things that are worth a hundred dollars.
My brother's being choked to death and I was like, I have to get my McDermott pool cue that
I just got for cost, mind you. I would have had to buy it at retail if it had gotten there's
no way I would have explained to my boss that, "Oh, I got in this giant fight, some guy."
And also that I thought that the people we were fighting were such like villains that
instead of fighting us, they were going to be like, "Oh yeah, I'm going to hit you where
it really hurts and then go snap our pool cues in half."
Well, they might like beat you with them.
But there were other pool cues, like there were graphite house cues all over the place.
Yeah, but then it was nice.
But I should hit you the harder it hits.
No, I don't like violence, man.
Yeah. I was talking to my roommate last night.
He's a skateboarder.
He was talking about how like...
They have such bad attitudes, man.
They do, but he was talking about how like,
you know, the kind of like
weird kind of, you know,
people that might fight you think twice
because the skateboard is like a bludgeon,
you know.
Oh yeah, there's tons of people getting hit with skateboards
Skateboards on video camera.
I mean Karen's don't seem to mind. Karen's? Karen's don't seem to mind the skateboarder.
There's no, no, skateboarders won't, they're not like me man, they don't have it in them to hurt a
woman. Yeah you're a fighter, you're a fighter. They never didn't have to hurt a woman emotionally.
These are the archetypes. You're a fighter, Rex is a thrower-upper. No I'm not a fighter,
that's why, I'm not a fighter. I'm a thrower-upper, I throw up when I drink. That's true. I don't fight.
- Right.
- I've never seen you do that.
- Oh, I'm not gonna do it in front of you, man.
I have manners.
- My other friend does.
- And also, I don't do that anymore.
- Yeah.
- I'm not a fan.
- You have seen him do it, actually.
(laughing)
- Absolutely, yeah, he did it very loudly
in our Airbnb this one time.
- Oh, that's true.
- And he destroyed the entire bathroom.
So worried about it for the next couple days.
- Yeah, I mean, it's fine.
- Yeah, so you're a throw it upper.
- We've told that story, right?
- Yeah, a hundred times.
- We went to Carmelo's and the,
'cause you and Cam went home.
- Yeah, and I gave you,
like I took one sip of a margarita and gave it to y'all.
- Yeah, who am I gonna fuck up off the margaritas
and the booby trap?
And then we went to Carmelo's.
- I don't like how you framed that.
You were getting fucked up and also poisoning me.
You were like, I'm gonna get you three margaritas
and you're gonna drink the whole thing.
And I was being--
- That's how I had it.
- 'Cause I also got three margaritas.
- I was peer pressure by the entire table
until two white saviors joined our night and drank.
- You are literally four inches taller
and like 50 pounds heavier than me.
You should be able to--
- Yeah, you can tank this stuff.
We're DPS, man.
- Yeah.
- No, no, no.
- I'm a fucking mage, dude.
I'm fucking doing spells.
- You have no defense.
- It was completely hitting me
and I just couldn't do it anymore.
And then I had a white savior show up
and drink the rest of my margarita.
- Yeah, and then we went to Carmela's
And I smoked the, whatever, what do they call that?
Bouncer, the bouncer's weed outside of Carmelo's.
- You smoked that guy's weed?
The guy who has fingerless gloves?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Dude, that's awesome.
- I know, right?
That's why I had to do it.
He offered it to me.
- We're rolling with Pat, and Pat was like,
"Yo, check this out."
And he started talking to the bouncer like,
and I'm like, "Damn, Pat, that's so cool."
And then the guy offered Rex,
and I was just looking and I was so scared.
- I thought about it and I was like,
it's in the middle of COVID, I'm completely drunk,
I shouldn't smoke this guy's weed.
However, he is a cool black guy,
I should smoke that guy's weed.
- You have to, man.
- And I said, of course, let me hit that shit, my friend.
- Did you end up buying any weed from Aki?
- Not yet, he did tell me,
so the reason I gave Aki my number was because he's like,
when I re-up, I'm gonna hit you with a sample.
- Whoa, wait, so you're getting sampled out
everywhere you go, man.
- Yeah, people have, throughout my entire life,
regardless of whether or not I'm in a period
of smoking weed, have always offered me weed on the street.
Or asked me where to buy weed, as though I would know that.
- Me too, man, I think you and me have some kind of,
not since I shaved my head, actually,
but when I was fatter and had longer hair
I smelled bad people would ask me all that which what does that tell you about weed smokers, right?
People would tell me all the time
Ask me if I wanted to smoke weed or if I had any weed
But it doesn't happen to me since I'm bald because people assume that I'm some kind of
Probably ancient alien or something. They think that you're an athlete that doesn't smoke or drink exactly. Yeah. Yeah. I'm a UFC fighter
I have to clear you Sada. There's no way that I can smoke this weed man. Yeah
Yeah
Now people ask me if I want to do steroids that's true because you're so buff. Yep. People ask me exactly people ask me all the time
Hey, man
You want to do steroids man I go no man, I'm actually competing in a natural bodybuilding event in
February so I can't do that shit and then they usually buzz off by them
What should I become a
Do bodybuilding no, no the other thing the steroids. Oh my god. Yes, dude
I would do it for like one year
Because I think it's funny how you because it's funny how your body looks after you stop doing them
Have you ever seen the pictures of people who like ex?
Mr. Olympia's who stopped using gear and they look like fucked up like lawn dads
Like they they look so so bad and they kept working out
But it's just they their hormones have this like crazy downswing where you just like can't your body just gets fucked up
So I want that you should go to the warning just get a bunch of steroids
You can you can go anywhere and get started
There's a guy who comes to my gym who's definitely on gear but doesn't I really want to take a picture of him
He either is on gear or he has like
Synthol biceps, you know, they're like fake muscle stuff
But every other part of him is like completely emaciated skinny and he insists on wearing like skinny jean joggers to the gym
So he just looks so fucked up, but his arms are like probably 26 inches
It's so fucking awesome. And then every time I see him, he's just doing arm exercises
He's like turning himself into a crazy like inhuman animal. Yeah, it's just like a cartoon like a cartoon. He's Popeye
I don't think you should be doing that, regardless.
No, like a picture of a beautiful woman or a hot guy, and I just want to have a picture of them.
No, yeah, I don't think you should do that.
Okay, well I haven't because again, I get too nervous.
Right.
But if somebody, there was a guy who had a ferret, and he was like, "I'm gonna take a picture of you."
And I was like, "No, you're not gonna take a picture of me."
And he was like, "I'm gonna take a picture of you."
guy who had a uh... a ferret in a backpack
that was walking down the street recently
he had like a backpack that had like a plastic back so you could see what was in it
and it was a ferret. You can take a picture of that
see but i get i pull out my phone and i'm like he's gonna turn around as i'm
taking a photo
but also thinking about it. He wants you to look at it. Yeah he wants you to look at the
fucking ferret man. Yeah
but i just don't i don't like that i don't like taking photos of people like that. I think that
happened to me once where I was like at like a 7-eleven and there was a person
like with a clear like box or like one of those like bags with a with a cat in it
and I just took a picture of it and it's completely you can you can do that they
want you to the biggest the biggest regret that I have is I saw a guy with a
brand new beard mustache combo that I've never seen before or after uh-huh at Los
Angeles International Airport he had on one side of his face he had a mustache
but no beard. On the other side, shaved perfectly, no mustache, and a full beard.
And that's the coolest guy in the entire world. I mean I just had never seen this
shit before. I wanted to take a photo of him so so badly. Okay. But this guy's eyes
were darting around like a flash game teacher. Someone's gonna take a picture of me and make fun of me.
He knew somebody was gonna take a picture of him. Okay. So I couldn't do it man.
I know like someone with an animal outside in the world I think that's level
zero you can go ahead and do it. It's a green light. I think anywhere in the face
region I think that's a complete 100% red. It was funny you can tell us
about it you really shouldn't even try to take a picture of it. But you can't walk
around with that facial hair man. A Popeye guy I think you walk up to him and be
like yo can I get a pic? Oh that's smart he definitely wants somebody to take a
- That's a great idea.
- I'm gonna get a pic.
- When I go to the gym tomorrow,
I'm gonna say, man, dude, I am--
- I just love your shit.
I love your shit.
- You are like my goal.
You are goals, dude.
Can I please take a photo of you so that I can use it,
so I can like slowly morph my body to you
with before and after photos?
Or actually, a selfie is probably a better idea
with me and him both doing this.
- Take a picture of him, yeah, with him.
I think that's the way to go.
That's the way to go.
Ummmm...
No.
For sure.
In New York?
Yes.
Yeah.
In New York probably yeah.
If you did that in Mexico City, they'd be like, "How did you know I'm in the cartel?"
Yeah.
- Well, everyone in Mexico City is completely white.
Mexico City has been taken over by whiteys.
Have you heard this?
- Well, you're there, so yes.
- I'm not there. - He's not a Mexican.
- Fucking idiot.
- What's the, like recently it's been taken over
by white honkeys? - It's been completely
taken over by white honkeys that have driven
the rent prices all the way up to the ceiling in the sky.
- What is it about whites that make the rent more expensive?
I've never understood this.
- They get paid in euros and dollars, mostly.
- But they don't have to tell their landlords that.
Just keep paying the old prices.
- They notice.
- They notice that they're white?
- They notice that they're white,
they notice that they got more money in their purses.
Like me, I walk around like this.
- We love to just pay our rent on time.
- I walk around like this, I got my pockets out,
I got nothing on me, I got Mexican pesos.
to
You need it.
Oh my.
Because it's been opened so many times.
Exactly.
Hey, for so much cash has flown through this wallet that of course it's completely destroyed.
Let's see how much cash is in here.
Looks like about...
$15 in ones.
Let's see.
Well, you're close.
$5 in ones.
So, because I did laundry today.
Otherwise, there would be no cash in it.
I think I have $12 US dollars in my wallet right now.
I used to have a real wallet.
I have...
I want one of those, man.
Pull out that card now and let's see what it says.
What says his name?
Alright, guys, we have to make it to our fancy dinner.
Don't show that shit, you fucking idiot!
Wait, show it again.
Okay, I'll show mine really fast.
Don't.
I'm gonna scan it.
That was a tile.
the
we've enjoyed. What is that noise? That's my pilot trying to locate my phone. This, go buy
proper 12 right now. I honestly think, I don't even know what to do with this. There's no
way that I will ever have any more of this whiskey. You should give it to Patrick. Yeah.
That's a good idea actually. Maybe I'll just bring it to the office. Yeah. I know you're
Irish and you love being Irish. Here you go. Even looking at this is making me want to vomit
right now. I barely had one glass of it. Anyway. This is lovely. I think everyone should buy
This is was 30 bucks. It was not that I wish I got that. I wish I got that proper 12 is really really bad
Alright guys. I love you all
See y'all. Thank you for joining. I good night