[Sipping]
[Burp]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer podcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[Burp]
This is a journey into sea,
into the middle of,
planet,
I'm not a fool.
I want to look at this.
I went to the store and I was looking for funny beers and I saw they only have like two of
this kind of beer.
And I think.
So you figured it was popular.
Yes.
I figured it was interesting.
It's a Corona beer.
You know, everyone knows Corona, right?
but it's a rifadita,
which I guess just means that it has juice in it.
And I think it has like red fruits in it.
- This is a seltzer then.
This is not a beer.
- I think it's a beer.
- Take a sip.
This is not a beer.
There's no way this has,
this is a malted beverage.
- It's a complete beer.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
- Am I really quiet?
No, we can hear you.
Okay, good.
What do you have, Rex?
Well, actually, give us a rating.
Sorry, I'm very thrown off right now because of something that we'll talk about in just
a moment.
It tastes like soap, but I'm not disgusted by it, I guess.
So it's a 6.1.
6.1.
And now a numerical scale?
Like a 5 something.
Okay.
5.4.
All right Rex, what do you have? So I went to the beer store and I chose a
six-pack of beer that was the most stolen from. So I had to combine two
six-packs because I figured if people are stealing them that's probably the best
one. I have really bad news for you. These are not stolen from beers. People, almost
every bodega in New York City, you can grab one beer out of a six pack and buy just one beer.
Well, even better.
So it's the most...
So I was buying the two six packs.
It's the one that people bought the most but didn't want six of, they just wanted one.
And that's perfect because I am not going to have six beers, I am going to have one.
That's right, exactly. So what do you have?
And that was a Sour Monkey.
It's a classic, dude. Sour Monkey, Sour Triple. Give it a sip.
Never have.
Give us a rating. You never had this? It's good.
Yeah, it's good.
That's like the backyard barbecue sour.
Yeah. I'd say that's like a 6'4". Like a 6.2 out of 10. Very solid. Very reliable.
Tasty, but not being too tasty. Sweet, but not too sweet. Sour, but not too sour.
I think they're very high alcohol content, too.
9.5%.
Damn.
Well, guys, I have big news.
What are the news?
There are new rules to groggless ogless.
OK, OK, because my wife has.
And I want this to be on permanent record,
completely given up on groggless ogless.
OK, got a car situation has driven her to problematic drinking.
We're going to put her in some kind of a home away from our home
until she gets better.
But I have now given myself in groggless, ogless beers.
We drank off.
I have beers we drank off.
So no more in a beer.
All you sober gophers that have been looking at me as your new wisdom king.
That's over. I never liked you.
I always thought you were boring.
I have a margarita. Yummy.
I made hot stips, margarita, at my house with Hornitos, tequila, it has black pepper notes,
I looked this up on Drizzly, I used triple sec, I made a jalapeno simple syrup, and of
course some good old fresh lime juice with a tajin rim.
Let's take a sip, y'all.
We got a regular old mellow over here.
Mmm.
Oh my.
I was thinking, we're going to run out of beer.
- Give me a moment.
- We're gonna run out of beer soon.
- Probably we're gonna run out of beer.
- Oh, you already are doing one I've already done.
So it's fine.
- I know, that's what I'm saying.
- Just shut it around.
- Yeah.
- Guys.
- Also, I'm almost done with this one already.
It's okay, I got it back.
- That's like an eight ounce beer.
- Holy shit!
How you drinking that so fast?
- It's so small, dude.
- Yeah, that's like a beer for kids.
- I don't know how big your damn hand is.
- You know how big my hand is.
You see me every single day of your life.
This is the smallest.
This is like a sauce bottle.
Grab the beer like this.
Grab Margarita.
Yeah, that's ridiculous.
That's a decent-sized margarita.
Kudos to the mixologist, y'all.
This is amazing.
I'm going to give this a 7.9 numerical and a 6 foot 10 basketball.
Wow.
That's yummy.
This is yummy, y'all.
Okay.
I think it's the highest-ranking drink we've ever had.
No, I think I rated something a 6'11" the other day. I don't remember what it was.
And we've gone into 7 feet before, I think. Yeah, it might have been a non-alcoholic
seltzer. It might have been. Well, yeah, that's a different, you're right, that's a
different scale. On the alcoholic scale, oh, I think prime, I gave it a 6'11".
Okay. Bro, there is no way you're eating on the mic during the podcast. Yeah, come on, bro.
We do this for one hour a week
You have 20 or 20 24 other hours you can eat if you count from 11 o'clock last night
Guys, I'm almost done with my my my girl beer. This is a girl beer. Okay, I want to get into the meat of today's
Which is y'all I show speed just flashes meat on live stream
What do we think I show me more like that's what's trending on Twitter is I show me
I'm gonna be honest if I did the exact same action as hit my dick would not
Fall out of my pants. There is no
fucking world you could not do
You could put a fishing line on the end of my penis pull it as hard as you can and it would not pop out of
my boxers
It might it might do a little a little gopher out of the you know, you might see it
I'm not gonna say it's not gonna make an impact
But it's not coming what looks like 70% out of that thing. I
Think the important thing here is that his dick had to already be hard
Right, it's not okay
Watch it again. It's not hard, but
You just now jam pants now here's here is my here is what I will say
His dick was definitely out already. He was playing with his dick while he was streaming
Because and this is not to say that his dick is too small to pop out
It's too big the the bottom of his dick would go past his fly
It would not pop out if it was in his pants it flew into the fly
Yeah, is it not already out at the beginning?
No, it's it's it's pajama pants. It's it's got a completely open hole. Well
There's a lot see this is what I why I wanted to bring this up this is a
Yeah, this is a
Like the what's the name of the JFK footage
There's a pruder film this is a we'll be watching this over and over for years and years
We will have AI remasters of it constantly new information coming out. How did this happen? I
Really don't want us to study it any longer
I don't want to I've seen his dick by this point like about 10 times
I have to and I don't want to do it in trouble with twitch for this because it does
Things on YouTube. I mean it really doesn't I
Feel like you're not allowed to flash your penis. You're definitely not allowed
I don't think you're allowed to show your penis anywhere.
… banned for some amount of time. I'm assuming not forever because he probably
brings a lot of revenue to YouTube. But there will be consequences.
How popular is he? He gets like 60,000 viewers.
So popular. He's like one of the top five streamers.
Okay. How many of those are just like 11-year-old children?
I mean, they still watch ads. If you click the #ishowspeed hashtag,
and you just like, just scroll every single video.
It's the same video over and over and over again.
I think he might be done.
- He's not done.
- I think he might be done.
- No, no, no, no, no.
He's not done.
I saw a lot of opportunities in the comments.
This girl says, "Speed should join me on my OnlyFans."
There's a picture of her ass.
- That's dope.
- You are recording, Rex.
I can see your tiny little mouse voice, the waveform.
- My waveform is like nothing.
- Why, okay, you are in New York, home of the podcaster.
How have you made it two weeks without a single microphone?
- What are you talking about?
I am using, I'm...
Using this Blue Yeti microphone.
But I am on a laptop.
- Can you like talk into it?
Can you put it in front of your mouth
and see if that makes any change?
(sighs)
- Oh no, he's sighing 'cause he has
to hold his microphone, y'all.
- A boo.
- No, that's too close.
- A little too close, but much, much better.
- I could put it on this laptop.
- Yeah, that's fine.
- But it's resting on the nipple.
- Rex, you've been officially a New Yorker for so long,
at least a week, I think.
How has it been? How's living in New York?
It's good.
I haven't talked to you in, I think, a week.
Well, I mean, the really important thing here is that I am not...
I don't have my actual computer yet, so I'm not gaming.
So why would I talk to you? I hate you.
True. Yeah.
That's true, yeah.
You have almost no relationship outside of playing League of Legends.
Yeah.
And even when we play League of Legends, I say maybe five, ten words an hour.
Quiet fella. Yeah I'm not I'm not much of a talkative person so yeah you know I
did I will say however I did message Julio last night and I said sorry to
bother you if this is too late but would you like to play some video games. That
is not what you said. Read it read what I said. Why is this drama? When I gave
- In a minute, when I gave him a minute,
or is it too late for you?
I don't think this is a drama.
- Right, which is exactly what I said.
- No, that's not exactly what you said.
- That's basically what, I mean, come on, you're being...
- I know, because he's trying to portray himself.
You're trying to portray yourself as though
you're very humble, very, oh, I don't mean to bother you.
- He literally says at the end of the message,
or is it too late?
- Yeah, absolutely, giving you the ability
to very easily either deny me or--
Did he say anything to this message?
No, he said nothing.
He didn't even respond to it.
Wow.
Despite the fact, his shit was green on Discord.
I know he was awake.
My computer is on.
And I just leave the--
I just get up the computer.
And he's a power waster.
He doesn't care about the environment.
This is disgusting, man.
This is so fucking disgusting.
This is why I can't talk to you.
I have a better story about me hating the environment.
This past--
- Is this like when you killed all those birds?
- No.
I didn't even kill a single bird.
- You did.
- No, I dumped a bunch of like,
wait, actually now that I think about it,
so to start with the birds is I just dumped a bunch of like,
what is it, just spices on my balcony
so they would never like hang out in there anymore.
- You killed them.
- They kind of stopped coming there,
but they did, I was thinking that they were like
making a nest on this like old AC unit
that's just like not in use and just in the wall.
And I could hear them like scratching and tapping and shit.
But now that I think about it,
I haven't heard the birds in a long time.
- That's 'cause they fucking abandoned their babies
that you killed.
- Yeah.
- That's fine.
Anyways, this past Friday,
my landlord came to fix my cistern,
which is-- - Fix your cistern?
- Cistern, which is--
- You guys do that down there?
- It's a hole, it's a hole on the floor.
- Your sister is a hole.
- It's a hole in the floor that just stores water.
- My sister, she had to get fixed 'cause she's a hole.
- I'm gonna keep moving.
This is completely, this is--
- You removed her reproductive organs
'cause you think of her as just a hole.
- She came and she was trying to fix the system.
- If she came, like--
(laughing)
- I've just been dumping hella water.
- Your landlord came and your sister--
- I've just been--
- After a fixer. - Wasting water.
I've just been wasting hella water
for the past entire weekend.
That's my whole story.
Well, I like our version more.
Yeah, our version was a bit tad bit funnier that your landlord
came in and fixed your sister and came in her and also she's a
whole but my landlord is an old woman and she's insane.
She's got to be pretty crazy to do a sexual shit to your sister.
Yeah, I was really like for you guys to meet her your sister.
My landlord my insane landlord.
Yeah.
- Why would you want us to meet your landlord?
- Just so you see what I deal with on a show off.
So I search enough and--
- All, every landlord is crazy.
- Caleb and I live in New York.
And you think we don't have exposure to weird landlords?
- It's so much different.
It is so much different.
- And I've been here for nine days
and I already know how insane my landlord is.
That shouldn't explain.
- Landlords are so fucking crazy.
Did Cameron tell you guys about our office landlord
who we have like a little gate in the front of the office.
We were literally there.
Oh, you were there?
We saw it happen.
We were both there.
You should tell your side of the story.
I don't have a side of the story.
Just that it's so funny that he was like, somebody's going to...
We have a gate on the front.
We lock it.
But I guess Cam left like four inches of like slack in the gate.
And he just tied it at the bottom.
Yeah, he locked it at the bottom of the gate.
And your landlord just pulled up out of nowhere.
He parked on top of the curb and he just like flashed out of the car and just goes,
"Yo, if you don't, if you tie that on the top," because someone who's like really,
really skinny could just pull the gate and just walk in.
A gate that's like not even like...
Maybe three feet tall.
Yeah.
Right.
It's so small.
A gate that Noah could jump over in at least one direction.
An easy jump for anybody pretty much.
Maybe a hand jump, maybe you have to use your hands
to hoist yourself over for some guys.
Yeah, right.
But almost anybody could get over this gate.
And he was claiming that somebody who was four inches wide
might slip through the crack and do graffiti.
And I love that that's his idea of who does crimes
is skinny people. Skinny guys.
And not athletic guys.
Skinny, skinny guys who can slip through cracks.
holes a crack that a shoe couldn't fit through so you'd have to bring your feet above the
Gate it really made no sense. Yeah, I'm so used to this shit
I think I was the thing I was I was most amazed at is I was I was like
What she's like just coming and going and just like scoping out
Like what can I complain about what is wrong with with the office today couple weeks? We were there. He was doing that because
he
He just kind of has no idea what's going on ever
and but he was also very skeptical of us because he didn't know what a podcast was and
He didn't believe how much money we made and we thought that we he thought that we invented patreon
To fake how much money we make when we showed him our patreon
He was like so I mean for all I know you guys made this website and you put all these fake numbers on here
and yeah it took a lot of time to get him to believe us. The awesome thing about
that is like it's really easy to corroborate Patreon's existence. Yeah.
Because you just have to know at least one other website. Yeah. Wikipedia. You had
a you had a similar experience right when you're like trying to rent a place in LA
like two years ago? Oh yeah but that's different. I was literally
sending them like blockchain transactions. Can you not just send them
like bank statements of like look at all this money that I'm receiving? I was not
putting money in my bank account. Okay so it was literally not a them problem it
was a you problem. You were being difficult for no reason.
Okay, I wasn't being difficult. I just get paid differently than
you.
Sending an old person like, Oh, yeah, check out my blockchain
profile. Can I rent this fucking place? Now I understand why they
didn't want to rent for you to you for so long.
I mean, I was still pulling fucking money into my bank
account, but it wasn't regularly. Like like a paycheck would be,
You know, it was irregularly like a drug dealer would do.
How are you, uh, how are you showing your, your, your, your income now in New York?
Do you have like any issues with that?
No, not at all.
Do you want to know the ins and outs of the legal structure I built for myself?
Yeah.
Go ahead.
LLCs and S-corps.
Yeah, go ahead.
Well, I have a S-corp in, uh, uh, Sheridan, Wyoming, uh, on coffee.
Why did you do Wyoming?
Cause I always hear that Delaware is the best one, but also,
isn't that kind of a trick because you end up paying double tax because you're
supposed to, tax is paid where money is made, as they say?
Yes.
So the secret is that Delaware
is a fake state where corporations incorporate and
they don't have any real crime.
They only do like corporate litigation.
That's all their courts do.
All the judges, everyone involved, that's all they do.
- Okay.
- There's no one that does any crime there.
They don't do anything.
Wyoming is the same thing, but for like crypto people
because they have some weird bitch
that's the governor that loves Bitcoin.
And so it's very favorable to exist there.
And then I use a service where I send them money.
And then two weeks later it goes into my bank account and they handle
withholdings, they handle like, uh, pay stubs, uh, insurance, things like that.
This is genius.
Yeah.
And it looks like I'm a licensed freelancer.
So I get like an actual pay stub now.
- Whoa.
- And I only have to pay them $150 per paycheck.
(laughing)
- Money talk.
- Yeah, that's nothing.
- Yep.
- That sucks ass.
- Yeah, it's hell.
But, no, that's life.
So that's what you have to do to show weird old guys
who aren't hip and with it with financial technology
that you make bank.
- I feel like crypto--
- Also I have a good credit score.
Crypto is a lot easier to explain than Patreon, I think.
- No. - To most landlords.
- I don't think so.
- Absolutely not. - I feel like most old white guys
know, especially rich guys, like landlords,
know what crypto is.
- That doesn't, no, absolutely not.
And they don't understand how you could possibly
receive a paycheck on it.
- Yeah, I completely disagree.
- You might be complicating it
with the paycheck thing, honestly.
Yeah, you can say, "Hey, I make this amount of money.
It goes to our LLC and we pay ourselves through it.
And this is made through a subscription service that we run."
That's easy.
Subscriptions.
That does sound really easy.
Old guys fucking have 90 subscriptions to everything.
That's true.
That's a good point.
I think it would be,
can you imagine how easy our lives would be?
We both should have just said that we do sports betting.
We do daily fantasy sports betting.
My landlord literally, I know for a fact,
he would have been like,
"Oh yeah, whatever, no, yeah, no problem.
What, you guys make $15,000 a month doing sports betting?"
Yeah, I believe that.
We would have even had to show him.
- Got an algorithm for DraftKings.
- We could have just made up a fake,
we could have given him one fake daily fantasy lineup
and been like, "Yeah, dude, go ahead, Patrick Mahomes."
And he would have been like, "Oh yeah, okay."
- Give him some picks.
- Yeah, just give him some picks and then that's it.
- So the hardest thing when I was looking for a place
was it was COVID and I lived in California where they refused to kick.
People out onto the streets and they were like, Oh, we need to make sure you're
not gonna, you know, just not pay rent as though that is like a thing someone does,
you know, taking advantage of lenient rules.
No one's ever done that.
Now it's like, you know, I, I literally like I have my, my,
there's a tax guy that I'm vaguely familiar with. And I was like, Hey, like,
can you like write me like a letter or some shit that will help me out with
this? And he wrote it and sent it to me. And before I even sent it,
I was approved to get this apartment.
Oh, nice.
So it was like trivially easy.
Have you seen that financial guru guy on
YouTube who has people on all the time who are like, "I make $70,000 a year. I don't
understand why I'm broke." And he looks at their bank account statements and he always...
Oh, yeah.
It's always like... He's like, "It says here that you spent $2,300 on Taco Bell last month."
Wait, wait, wait. Is it the guy with glasses and big...
Yeah.
Is this Dave Ramsey?
Dude, I love that guy.
No, it's not Dave Ramsey. No, no. It's this younger guy who doesn't... He's not rich.
He just is a guy who preaches...
like a financial responsibility.
Yeah.
He just has people on, these fucking, the biggest losers in the world.
I don't know why they put themselves through this.
It makes no, it's like, it has to be some humiliation.
They love it.
They love it, dude.
And they go on and they're like, and he's like, it says here there's a $1,600 charge
in one day from something called Steam.
Can you explain what that is?
(laughing)
The guy's like, "Oh, well, you know,
"I had to buy the expansions,
"and then I had to buy the skins."
And he's like, "I don't know what the fuck
"you're talking about, but I want you to know
"you make $2,000 a month, and you spent 75%
"of your paycheck on whatever this is."
- I love when that guy just gets so exasperated
and he's like, "What are you doing?
"You owe so much money, you can't own anything.
"You need to be paying for the rest of your life.
"You need to stop doing this."
And they're just sitting there like,
"I don't know, fucking whatever."
Yeah, I mean, it's a perfect—I recommend anybody to watch this guy on YouTube.
He's so, so, so good.
But I always do have—as I watch it, I'm like laughing at these guys and just hoping
to God that somehow he never gets a hold of my financials because it would be the exact
same thing.
Oh, of course.
Yeah.
I did also stumble upon that YouTube channel.
I think it was either last year or two years ago when I was like so in debt and I owed
so much money.
I had no money myself.
I was just like, "Oh, let me just watch these guys' YouTube videos."
I was just like laughing at people in Texas just paying a hell of money for like UberEats.
Yeah, these people make like $6 an hour and they own houses.
And he's like, "Why do you own it?
How is this possible?"
And they're like, "Oh, well, I took out $800,000 in student loans when I first started going
to college."
College is a big one.
I kept the student loans, and then now I pay for my house with that.
They keep buying cars for no reason.
It's like, "You don't need a car.
You don't need a new car.
You can just buy a used one.
You don't need to be paying this."
That is always a funny...
He's always like, "Why do you need a car?"
And they're like, "Well, to get around."
They do live in Texas.
- Where do you work?
- So they do need a car.
- And they always say, "I work from home.
"I freelance from home."
(laughing)
Or, "I'm unemployed."
- Yeah, that's the real secret.
You don't need a car.
You almost never need a car.
- You don't need anything.
You don't need anything.
- You literally, okay, I've lived in Arizona,
which is just as retarded and sprawling as Texas.
- Most cities have some kind of shitty bus
that you can take.
I will say, you really have to get lucky
to have your house and your work be remotely close
to a bus station in most places.
But there is definitely cities where you make it work
and do it cheap.
But it's also nice to have a car.
- Oh, for sure.
- Yeah.
- I mean, that's the thing.
Your car should cost $2,000 until it can cost $40,000.
- Yeah, until you can buy a car,
a watch that looks like your car.
- Yeah.
- Like Cobra Tate Bugatti. - You should be driving
a 2000 like a $2,000 1994 Lincoln until you can buy a BMW and cab.
Have you guys seen the video?
Any car in between is just a waste of time.
Have you guys seen the video of Andrew Tate buying the Bugatti watch that's the exact same
model as his car?
No.
He buys a watch that is like a it looks like a Bugatti the same Bugatti he has the Bugatti
Chiron or whatever it's called.
Yeah.
And I was wondering if you guys think I should get that same thing, but with my Ford Focus.
What?
Just a red watch with zip ties on it.
Speaking of cars.
Bunch of alarms going off.
A bunch of tickets.
Yeah, attached to it.
The brakes are all fucked up.
Post-it notes.
Yeah, mismatched mirrors because one got knocked off.
Heineken, still Heineken smell all through the watch.
How's the car situation?
Is it still fucked?
It is now officially at a parking lot across the street.
Yo!
But it has no license plate.
That's fine.
And it can't legally be driven.
And now we have to go, we have to go get it,
pay to get it all fixed up so that it can then be inspected.
Right.
And then we have to get new tags for New York
and then we have to get insurance for it.
So I just don't, I don't wanna do it.
My idea, my idea, my new, my brand new idea.
Okay.
all these cars like driving around New York with a,
with like a paper, uh, license plate, like a temporary paper license plate.
Yes, a 30 day deal.
You steal one or you just copy one and just put it in your car.
And you copy one every single month.
I don't get pulled over.
I don't do naughty things when I drive.
If I had fake tags on, I could probably drive for five years without any.
In New York, they don't check, they don't run people's registration on the highway
like they do in other places.
I don't think I would get pulled over even one time.
Well, there's a secret to driving, which is you don't do two crimes at the same time.
So if you have a fake license plate, you don't have registration,
you're going the speed limit, you know? Exactly.
Wait, how do you how do they even take you down?
What tipped them off? What do they come for you?
Because you got a million tickets.
Yeah, there was the car got towed.
They do like once every couple of weeks or once a month.
They send out a boot army, an army of booters
who go around and they boot cars
and have too many tickets. - I hate booters.
- Dude, and these guys, they make me sick.
- They love their job.
- Dude, they really do.
The people in my neighborhood who do parking tickets
fucking love their job.
They hang out, they drink little coffees in the car,
like waiting for seven o'clock to hit
so that they can start legally ticketing people.
And they are disgusting.
I want to mow them down.
I need them to die. I just don't understand how you join the NYPD,
one of the most valiant organizations in this country.
Very cool guys.
And these, but, but you know, for a fact, when you look at these guys,
they're all five foot two and like 65 years old.
They joined when they were 50 and they were like, please,
please, please put me on parking duty.
It's what I was built for.
I've been waiting my entire life for this opportunity.
They never wanted to chase down bad guys.
They didn't want to be an old West Sheriff
like all cops should want to be.
- Yeah.
- They're not white hat.
They are disgusting parking worms.
- Yeah.
- No idea.
What do you do, what do you, to fight back,
you should do what Rex did and do some praxis.
- I should satire them.
- You should do what Rex did.
satirical show that is making fun of their, of how lazy they are. That's what I
should do. Thank you for this idea. You're so right.
No, that was not my idea. My idea was the thing that Rex did. We were working on like what,
insurances or some shit? And they just fired you because you kept giving
everyone loans, so like you just kept forgiving everyone.
Yeah, I put them on the do not call.
He's told this story a million times. It's to prove he's a good guy.
It's not to prove I...
It's not true. It's just not true. It's fine.
I don't have it in me to be harsh with people.
Yeah, so you should do that. You should become an NYPD officer and you should shoot cops.
Dude, this is the problem.
No, you should become a parking officer and give the other parking cops tickets to show them how it feels.
Do you realize what I look like? If I applied for the NYPD, I would literally be on the WGA picket line
putting a baton through somebody with blue hairs mouth.
That's what I would be doing.
I'd be I'd be breaking people's tracheas with the butt of my gun.
That is what they want me for.
They would not want me on parking duty.
I'm six foot five, 280 pounds, pure muscle.
There's no there's no world where they put me on fucking parking, dude.
I think they do.
Think it would be funny to be a full time podcaster, part time
police officer.
Yeah. I mean,
Oh, I heard you got like a new part-time job. Like what do you think?
You work at like CVS?
What do you think would ruin my life more?
Is it like, like being like if me and my wife got divorced and it was really,
really like super messy, Johnny Depp, Amber Heard style,
or, and it all became public somehow,
or if it was revealed that I was secretly an NYPD officer.
I have a question about this hypothetical.
Who are you shitting on the bed or is she shitting on the bed?
I mean, honestly, probably me.
But not, but just because almost every single night I almost shit my pants
while I'm in bed and then I run to the bathroom and I wake her up and that
would definitely be disclosed in court.
With the people that listen to podcasts about LIST, being a cop is worse
than being divorced.
Well, not divorce.
I mean, like, like an, like reveals that you're an awful person, that kind of thing.
I mean, Johnny, Johnny Depp's divorce, the whole thing was that he like abused her.
So are you saying you're like abusing your wife?
Yeah.
We are team member.
I heard that's what's coming out.
Yeah.
Yes.
So if I, so let's take that to the extreme.
If I, Whoa, not very, very cool.
Very, I want everybody to hear what Julia just said.
Repeat that.
- You'll get that right back.
- Say what you just said, yeah, that's a home run.
That's way in the left field.
That just landed in a popcorn bucket.
Tell me that again.
- I said what I said, let's move on.
(laughing)
- Yeah, so okay, so you're right.
I guess I don't know that much
about the Johnny Depp, Amber Heard thing,
except for the poop bed thing.
But say that I was doing, say I got really into kickboxing.
kickboxing and I was doing like kangaroo style double foot kicks into my
wife's face, kicking her through windows and stuff. It would definitely be worse still if I was a cop I think.
That would be worse. Yeah. Yeah, because you would be a cop on top of already doing that.
do it again. You can't do it again. Oh my god, two home runs in a single inning. That's crazy. It doesn't work more than once, man.
Even as a wow, how retarded was I? It doesn't work twice. It doesn't work twice. It completely worked twice. You are funny
because you are trained to be a cop. I'm not training to be a cop, I'm
training to be a professional bodybuilder. Why are you so defensive about cops not beating
their wives yeah I'm I didn't say that they don't I just show me your beds
officer you have to tell me if you're a police officer yeah how about all these
fake eyeballs that I have I bought these like three years ago I think I was gonna
The funny thing about Caleb is he'll just like talk to you like once in a while and just tell you about these insane purchases that he makes.
You're like, "Why do you do this?"
They're pretty funny, right? I mean, come on.
You see why I bought these.
I chose the worst moment to take a drink of water.
It honestly looks like your actual eyes, which is crazy.
That's what you look like.
No, I lost it.
It's okay, you got like 20 more.
Yeah, I do have a big pack of them.
They're all different colors though.
And I think the green one is probably the funniest.
Do you want to do a Bishu Jiraiya exclusive with that other purchase that you made?
No, no, no, no, no, I can't talk about that.
Okay, we won't talk about that.
I'll talk about it one day.
He just does shit for videos and I...
But I do just blow an irresponsible amount of money on something.
He hasn't made a video.
When's the last time you made a video actually?
I made a couple TikToks six months ago.
Those don't count. Those don't count.
Those don't count? It's the biggest platform in the world.
No, the password one was funny.
Thank you, Rex.
You're welcome.
I watched them all. Because I only follow four people on TikTok.
Who do you follow?
Addison Rae.
No.
You, Pat, Cam, and Julio.
Cam doesn't have a TikTok.
Pat told me that someone he knows showed Addison Rae Pot of a List.
Really?
Yeah.
That he didn't get any info on who was her favorite host or anything like that.
But hopefully she might be listening to this right now.
You know what?
Actually, I was thinking this earlier today.
came into the Twitch chat and people
would just start like, started like
mentioning like, oh, I know Paul from
this. And apart from that, one of them,
which Cam said it was a dream, he said,
oh, I know Paul from YouTube
recommendations, which is crazy.
That's so good.
That is what you want.
Yeah, that is what you want.
Yeah. But another person came in and
was like, oh, I know you guys from the
yard. So I was like, OK, if we get one
person to listen and subscribe and give
us money from every collab, we should
just do a million collabs and we'll just have a million listeners and payers.
Yes. Yes.
No, no doubt. No, 100% guarantee.
There's no doubt. Guys, there's so many reasons. We don't do advertisements.
We're not like these scumbag other podcasts that do all these advert.
Manscaped. I don't know what that is.
I don't know if you use 15% off or if you use the code Kaleb at checkout,
maybe you'll get 15% off, but I don't know what the fuck that is.
What is manscaped?
Yeah.
What, do they have superior grooming products for men
that don't give you razor burn and actually are more hygienic than any other item on the
market?
Maybe.
I don't know, but we don't do ads.
So there's a lot of reasons like that.
I hate ads.
Do you have three razors?
How many razors do you have?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Shaving your three important areas.
I do not often shave my third most important area.
Or my first, depending on...
I mean, for Rex, it's definitely...
Mine is definitely his number one.
for me it's my third. You're saying that to me your third most important area is your
number one for me? Yes, yes. Like in terms if I had to rank the areas on my body that
are most important to shave I would say head is number one, my beard and mustache is number
two and my ass and balls and dick are number three. For you it's the worst. Hold on, hold
- Hold on.
- For you, you think that that's--
- Ass, you shaved your ass.
- I've talked about this before.
I recently shaved my ass.
A month ago I shaved my ass baby bald.
- You're ridiculous.
- I shaved my ass baby bald.
I walked around feeling like I was taking a,
giving birth to a porcupine every single day.
- You're still doing it.
- I'm not still doing it.
- You said you did it a month ago.
- Yeah, a month ago that was the first time I'd done it
in probably three years.
What is he doing?
I don't know.
He's pulling up air pods.
They drop.
[LAUGHTER]
Wait, this is so fail.
This is so fail.
This is so fail that we need to stop talking about my ass shave right now.
Incredible fail.
It's just so fail for him to be dropping his air pods.
I thought he was going to show us his ass for a second.
I thought he just was going to leave.
I thought a fire alarm was going off or something.
Well, you would hear that.
I guess you're right.
What's up?
What did I miss?
Okay, you know nothing. I'll show to a whole different topic. Yeah, I know topic
Fucking what's up with the Hawaii fire? So you guys know that?
I did not
Know anything about it until I overheard somebody in Walgreens today say that a hundred people have passed away
And I hate all death, and I don't think that this is
Funny and I don't know why you would bring this up. Yeah, I don't know why we're even talking about these horrific fires
But Jubio thinks that this he I guess thinks this is the funniest thing. I don't think this is funny
I don't think it's funny that they used direct energy weapons
to light normal people's things on fire and then this Oprah's house
What they did did you know that do you see that the video that the with the Chinese lasers?
No
Why?
They were talking about Gundam. No, there were Chinese lasers pointed at
You said Gundam is Chinese lasers, yeah lasers in that show
You don't deserve the home run button they do have like I
Think I think you all have them. I think you all have the buttons
At the top of the screen do not see them website barely works for me
Yeah, I don't have any buttons brother I can't even click the call settings button to make
You know if I had the bang button I would be using that
Wait stop working
I
I forgot what we're talking about.
Do you know that there's like,
gundams for every country and the Mexican one is like so racist?
Really?
Yeah.
Sombrero?
It's like a cactus with a sombrero eating a taco.
That is fucking awesome.
How's that racist?
That is not how we look.
Yeah.
You don't look like a fucking robot either.
The actual law was wearing sombreros eating a taco.
You think Japanese people look like fucking robots?
What do you mean that's not what we look like?
Come on, man.
If the American one was a very brave person,
and I wouldn't be like, "Oh, yeah, they're being racist
"'cause they're saying all Americans are brave."
- Dude, he has like a sombrero, he has like a big mustache.
- These are things from Mexico, man.
- It has.
- Look at me. - Complete cacti.
- You look like a cactus.
- Wait, hang on, what does the USA want to declare?
- And you have a mustache.
I don't know why you're complaining about--
- And you're wearing a sombrero for the audio.
- Representing me by having a mustache
and a sombrero, holding a chihuahua.
- Oh no, they're paying homage to our--
They're paying homage to our 5,000 year history.
You know, the USA Gundam, it has a big gun on it.
Yeah, of course it does.
I'm not I'm not complaining about that.
There's no I don't see any problem.
That's objectively true.
I don't understand what your problem is.
And you tell me, Jubio, do people in Mexico wear sombreros?
No. Sometimes, sometimes people in America wear sombreros sometimes
and they're making fun of people from Mexico.
When I went to Mexico, I bought a sombrero.
It cost $20 plus a dollar for his coke.
Yes.
So, so people wear sombreros in Mexico.
Do people have mustaches in Mexico?
And don't you say no, because you have one tickling your your upper lip as we speak.
You have a Hitlerian mustache.
You do have a...
We've talked about this.
You have a natural Hitler mustache.
It literally only grows in in the Hitler zone, as they call it.
Hitler, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Do you know that that actually,
where you have that and where Hitler
actually had his mustache is considered
the zone of death when it comes to
abscesses and pimples on the human face?
- Why is it called the zone of death?
- 'Cause if you mistreat an abscess or a pimple
in this area between, like the triangle
that is formed between the very top of your nose
and the corners of your lips,
something that you have like a very high chance of it,
of basically like, if you get an infection,
it can go into your sinus and then into your brain.
So that's like dermatologists say,
like don't touch any pimples
that are like above your upper lip.
It's pretty scary stuff, huh?
- That's crazy. - Yeah, that is scary.
- You can die from almost anything.
- That is cool.
- You can overdose on drugs. - I love being fragile.
I was looking at,
Do you think bacteria fadges are like alien technology?
- Bacteria, what the fuck did you just say?
- I don't know what--
- Too much, you know like the little thing
that looks like a spider with a cube on its head?
- What?
- No, I don't know what you're talking about.
- Oh my God.
- Is this you looking, you look to science news again?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Why are you looking at this?
- I know this from the science book
from when I was in school,
but why are we looking at this?
- Well, I saw a video on Twitter
and it was showing different types of bacteria and viruses,
like little pictures of them.
And all of them look like big turds
or just like clumps of shit.
- So wait, sorry, what was your question?
Now that I know what we're talking about,
what was your question again?
- Do you think they're like alien technology?
- Do I think those are alien technology, bacteria?
Bacteriophages, it's a specific type of virus. It looks like a little spider with like a
Cylinder and then like a hexagon on its head. What what makes you think that it is alien technology?
because
Because it looks weird
No, it looks normal. It looks like it looks like
Yeah, it looks like you saw a guy
But it looks like just like a tear phage outside on the street where you think like oh that's a normal-looking guy
Yes
That's not true. You're just lying. No, it looks like the type of thing that kills Gundam when they get a pimple in the death zone
But I do think I mean
Here my my hypothesis on alien technology is that if we saw alien technology, buddy
We wouldn't even recognize it as such
Because we can only think of technology that we can think of do you remember when you were a kid?
You remember when you were a kid and your art teacher said draw a new
animal that has no attributes of any other animal
that has ever existed.
- That never happened to me.
- That happened to me.
I had a very, very heady type of art teacher
and all of us sat there and we said,
well, God damn it, I can't draw anything
that doesn't have a mouth.
I only know a mouth.
But hey, buddy, best you believe on other planets,
there are creatures with no mouths, no eyes, and no hair.
- No balls, no pussy.
They feel really weird all the time,
but they also have different attributes
that we can never even imagine drawing.
- Like what?
- How do they--
- That's what I'm saying, we don't know.
They don't have eyes,
but they might have some other thing.
But we can't even imagine what--
That's, you keep saying like what?
I don't know, you fucking asshole.
I don't know.
That's what's so fucked up about this question
that my art teacher asked me when I was in fourth grade.
It doesn't make any fucking sense.
And it's bothered me every day since.
It's really hard.
It's really heady to put on a video.
It's very very heady. She ruined my life.
She ruined my fucking life. Mrs. Lovejoy.
I swear to god that was her name.
My god.
Lovejoy? Lovejoy.
That's the Pokemon nurse.
Nurse Lovejoy?
No, that's Nurse Joy.
Nurse Joy, yep.
I was halfway there.
- I think I wanted the words.
- She did have a two word name
and the Pokemon thing was one name, yeah.
- Yeah.
So anyways, what was this ranking,
this shaving ranking that you had for Rex?
- The whole point was that the joke here
that I was trying to get at,
don't, you know, spare me the home run sound y'all,
I know it's one.
- Yeah. - Was that Rex cares
about my dick and balls and ass being shaved.
- Okay, but here's the thing. - Completely clean.
Hold on!
(laughing)
I'd like to say why, it's because he's gay.
And then I care about my head being shaven
so that I can attract women other than my wife.
That was the whole point of what I was saying.
- So first of all, let's break this down.
- Yes.
- Let's pretend for a moment,
go outside of the realm of possibility,
completely unnatural, weird fantasy.
- You are gay.
- That I have a-
(laughing)
- Okay, I think that covers it.
I think that covers that topic.
New topic.
(laughing)
- You put that down.
Put down the soundboard.
I don't have anything on my hands.
Yeah, he's got nothing on his hands.
Rex can't say the same.
Okay, what I was going to say is that...
You're trying to control me to pull my pants off?
I'm not going to fall for your gay magic, you voodoo witch.
No, it's not going to work on me.
I'm taking you off.
First of all, though, if I was a gay man, I would not care about the cleanliness of your balls.
Can you do it? Wait, can I say it?
I would say Rex I would say that makes you even gayer that you don't give a fuck either way
Whether my balls are stinky or clean you just want to use them for your own nefarious gay purposes
Yeah, and I certainly wouldn't care about the hair in your asshole
Which I'm surprised you give even a second thought
Let's go yeah, let's fucking go you're not interested in my asshole. I mean in this fake scenario
we're talking about where we presuppose that I'm gay.
Yeah.
Completely outside the realm of possibility.
Yep, it makes no sense.
It's completely impossible.
Yeah.
But in this impossible scenario, why wouldn't I want you to stink?
Do you like when women stink?
Yeah.
Gay.
A normal amount.
That's gay.
That's not gay.
It is.
Is this a brand new puffer or is this one of them that you found in the ground?
What?
This is a brand new puff bar?
Your vape.
Or this one that you found on the internet?
Oh, this one?
I did it.
He did call it a puffer.
Like an old, old man.
He said, "Is that a brand new puffer?"
This is a frozen Creepsicle that I bought because the Uber that I took to Brooklyn could not
go down a street that was closed and left me in front of a vape store.
I know that vape store and I know that closed street.
Yep.
So, yeah.
I bought it new.
Okay?
Okay? Are you taking more care of where you place these things or are you
gonna be in that exact same scenario after a year? These are the two that I bought at that
vape store. Okay. And they're both sitting right on my desk. Okay. Completely in view.
I haven't lost it. There's a third one sitting on my bed. There's a fourth one I gave to my
roommate because I didn't want to ask you for it anymore.
Yeah.
So think about that before you, you know,
I don't think I don't think that's a good excuse.
You, you literally live with trash on your desk.
The only trash on my desk, you will get on the game.
It will just be there.
Here's what's on my desk.
You ready?
I'll give you a whole tour.
I have a glass of water, which has a little bit of water in it.
Okay. I have $24 in cash.
Whoa.
I have a screwdriver that I use to open my beer,
a bottle cap and said beer.
I have an AirPods container, a mouse,
my cell phone, my wallet,
two LFARs and a microphone.
- That's pretty clean.
- Speaking of.
- It's probably cleaner than your desk, Juvio.
I have-- - Speaking of.
- On my desk, I have a capsule for pens.
Four pairs of fake eyeballs.
(Juvio laughing)
A package of Zen 3, the Cool Mint,
which took a long time because the new guy
at my vape shop, speaks perfect English,
but can't read a lick of it, y'all,
which makes it pretty tough.
Anytime I walk in, I say,
"Can I have this flavor of Zin?"
He says, "What color is it?"
And if you know Zin,
they make five flavors that are the same color.
So I say blue, he gives me the wrong,
brings one that says peppermint.
I say, "Not that blue, buddy."
Light blue, he brings me a different light blue one,
and we have this whole thing back and forth.
- Crazy that he doesn't do like the pointing thing,
where he's like, "Huh?"
It's because he's hiding them from police.
So they are behind the entire thing.
I can't see even a single one.
- I will say, I did,
there are two things sitting next to me on the ground.
One, a utility bill for $1,500.
- Oh my God.
- And a coffee cup that was filled with sushi.
- What?
- Those are the two most interesting things.
Those should be on your desk.
Those are, those are.
- Well, the coffee cup is empty.
- Why did the coffee cup have sushi in it, first of all?
- Yeah, what's up with that?
- And why was the utility bill $1,500?
- Okay, so we'll answer your questions in order.
The coffee cup had sushi in it
because that is how they sell it.
They sell mobile sushi rice bowls,
so it was like rice, fish, and avocado in a coffee cup.
- So it's like a poke.
- Yeah, it's meant to be eaten while walking, I guess.
It was good.
And the utility bill is because their auto pay doesn't work.
And once a year I check my mail and see that I haven't paid the bill in a
year.
Oh, well,
uh, I found this out right before I moved.
They were going to shut off our utilities on the day my last roommate moved out,
but they called me from a number from Chile today,
which I obviously didn't answer because there's no reason to answer a call from
Chile ever. Yeah. Yeah.
What the voicemail was like, Hey, we're from the long beach, you know,
utilities, and we're going to shut off your utilities.
And he said, I don't give a fuck. Cause I don't live there. Yeah.
But I did pay it.
Yeah. That sucks. It sucks that you have to pay stuff that you don't use. My,
my old gym is coming after me right now because I didn't even know this.
I thought that I, I like went in and canceled my membership.
And I got an email from a law office a week ago that was like, "We are attorneys who do
collections and you owe $86 to Blink Fitness Ridgewood.
You can either pay this in full or we'll take you to court."
And I was like, "I don't know if I'm even going to pay it.
I don't even know if I'll ever respond to this email."
$86?
Yeah, there's no way they're taking you to court for $86.
That's what I'm saying, dude.
I kind of just couldn't believe it.
That's fake.
I have a strategy for Jubio, which is that I think that this
I Show Speed thing is going to make him go even bigger.
And I think that Jubio should recreate it one-to-one,
should let his stuff hang out of his boxers.
I've been wanting to see it for years.
You're one of my few male friends who I've never even seen
a glimpse of your penis.
Can we just make this happen?
No.
Nope.
- Do you think you could even show maybe a tenth
of the emotion that I Show Speed does?
- No.
- I've seen you get scared, I've seen you yell,
but I've never seen you show your black penis.
- I don't want to.
(laughing)
I don't want to be the next I Show Speed.
- Why?
He's rich and his mom hates him.
- He's cringe is what he is.
- Who is the least cringe streamer
that you want to be exactly like?
- I don't think there's a streamer that isn't cringe.
- Whoa.
- Put that on Twitch.
- Somebody's never watched Destiny's debates.
(laughing)
- Is that your top non-cringe streamer?
- Dude, Destiny is so fucking awesome.
- Yeah? - Are you kidding me?
Yes, dude, the Omni liberal himself.
- Yeah. - Yeah, he is dope.
He basically destroys people on both sides of the aisle.
The hysterical leftists and the racist as fuck rightoids.
He's the kind of streamer I like.
- I love watching debates.
- There's something that I wanted to talk to you.
Why do you say so much Twitch lingo?
- What do I say?
- You say easy clap,
which is a combination of two Twitch emotes.
- I don't think I've ever said easy clap.
- I don't think he's literally ever said that.
- I think I've-- - I can scroll
for like a couple days-- - Scroll where?
- On Peefers, and I've seen you type it.
- Well, that's because I'm watching
professional Valorant games,
and this is the kind of thing that people say
in the Twitch chat.
But I've never said that out loud.
- I think you've said it in one of your games.
- I never have said it, Rex can attest.
Okay. - I've never heard
those words before. - And also,
that's not a Twitch thing, that's a gaming thing.
People have said that forever.
- That's not a gaming, that's a Twitch thing.
That's two emotes. - No, no, no.
- Easy clap. - Where do you think
the emotes come from?
- From heaven.
- Yeah, you're done for.
You're done for.
What else do I say?
- I completely, I just,
my landlord keeps calling me,
so I have everything in my mind just completely blanked out.
- So basically, I'm Destiny,
and you are a hysterical leftist,
and you just got destroyed.
You had no points.
You are Hasan Abi, I am destiny.
- I'm not Hasan Abi.
- You are Hasan Abi.
- You have just been destroyed.
It's over for you.
Just like when destiny destroyed Hasan Abi,
his career was fucking over.
Who's heard of this guy since then?
Nobody.
- Did you see that video of where Hasan was like doing kicks,
kickboxing on his driveway?
And he's doing the weakest kicks of all time.
- I thought it was funny that he was trying
to shit on Elon for not fighting Mark Zuckerberg.
- Is that what he's doing?
- He did for a minute.
- You watch Hasan Piker every single day on Twitch.
- No, no, he was just posting it on Twitter.
- I have no idea what he's been saying and posting.
You follow him.
- You know, he ducked that fight with Sam Hyde
for like, well, years now.
- I don't, listen, I don't know the guy personally.
I do not blame anybody for not fighting Sam Hyde.
- Yeah, he's a monster.
I would never do you have to be fucking crazy to do that
You'd have to actually be out of your mind the only people yes, I'm hide or homeless people retard strength
racist strength
Dad he could rip your arms up your strength. Yeah, he's an actual ape he would destroy him
Yeah, I don't there's there's a
Who do you guys think that I should set up my celebrity boxing with when I when I eventually get on the bear as a guest?
role um
I don't know, it has to be like a really...
Idubbbz.
Do you want to fight Idubbbz?
Yeah dude, I think you could take him.
I would destroy Idubbbz.
I know dude, that's what I'm saying.
He weighs like 150 pounds.
No, you need to be like the biggest YouTuber you can think of.
You should do MrBeast.
Jake Paul.
I want to fight FouseyTube.
MrBeast is like 6'3", I don't want to fight him.
You should fight Google Foods.
But he's a bitch.
He's always like, "Oh, I was about to kill myself,
and then Jake Paul stopped me."
It's like, if Jake Paul can stop you from killing yourself,
you didn't want to do it in the first place.
- Okay.
- I will make you kill yourself.
- Imagine if you called the suicide hotline
and Jake Paul picked up on the other end.
- Tried to sell you a Happy Dad seltzer.
I mean, sounds okay with me, honestly.
- Yeah, he tells you to walk down to the corner-
- Honestly, that's what they should do
with the suicide hotline.
They should make it directly to celebrity phones
So that you're like, hello, I want to kill myself.
And then Tom Hanks is like, yeah, yeah.
You get Chumlee from Pawn Stars.
You're like, oh my God, Chumlee from Pawn Stars.
I have like 30 questions to ask you.
That would stop almost anybody from killing themselves.
If you called and Michael Jordan picked up.
Yeah.
That is such a brilliant idea.
It should just be a celebrity hotline.
Yeah.
It's like a reverse make a wish.
Yeah, I guess it's hard to dissuade people from just calling it just because they want
to talk to a celebrity.
But that's why it's a random celebrity.
You know, sometimes...
I think ropes should have Bluetooth in them and you should only be able to call the celebrity
hotline...
If it's over 100 pounds of pressure.
Right.
If you're a kid trying to kill yourself, sorry.
Well then it would call, you know, like...
We call it YouTubers.
Phineas and Ferb.
Yes.
We call it Phineas and Ferb.
I'm 12 years old, my breasts have grown in, my life is horrible, all the girls are mean
to me at school, and Sandy Cheeks picks up the phone.
That might work.
This is a good idea.
I think so too.
Let's get it working.
Alright, I'm going to make another margarita.
Alright, see you guys.
Bye.
See you.