[Sipping]
[Burp]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer broadcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[Burp]
This is a journey into sea,
into the land,
planet,
(upbeat music)
- Yo.
- Okay.
- Beer we're drinking.
- Well, mine doesn't have a, hold on, let me.
- That was kind of like a, like a really not audible.
- Oh, that was a good snap from Rex.
I feel like Rex usually has a weak one.
- Yeah, this is a 805 Cerveza, just a regular big beer.
- I love 805.
What's that five?
What's it from?
Just like a California, like shitty beer, but it's good.
Local beers.
It's like a local version of Mondelo.
Yeah, it's good.
What do you got Caleb?
I have the last little sips of Lolelo Sangria imported from Spain.
I had this, oh, there's actually even a little bit more in this bottle.
I got this yesterday cause I wanted Sangria really badly.
And put some pineapple in there.
And before the comments start rolling in.
- How that's not a beer?
- Well, that but also that I don't have any ice in it.
You're supposed to have ice in it.
- Yeah.
- Maybe I'm not some ice magnate.
I don't just have ice on me all the time.
- When I think of your apartment,
I don't think that you have ever had ice in that apartment.
- I've had ice.
- I don't think--
- Is it because it looks like a apartment from before
they knew how to freeze ice?
- Yes.
- No, I have ice sometimes, but I ran out.
- It looks like you have to go down to the deli
and bring a giant ice cube to keep your food cold.
- You said "frude."
- No, I didn't.
- "Frude."
- You did say "frude."
- You said "frude."
- You could also just buy a little--
- Oh, it has food and a fridge.
- You could just buy a little tray
and to just make ice at home, like every person in the world.
- Oh, I have a tray, don't worry, I have a tray.
I just don't use it, 'cause I don't use ice at all.
- You don't have a fridge.
- I do have a fridge.
- You don't.
- He makes those cubic whiskey stones
that you put in the freezer.
- Oh, I would love to have those, or like the balls.
I want the balls really bad.
- You want the balls.
(laughing)
- I want the balls, the ice balls really badly.
The balls, shut up man.
Whatever, I'm basically what a European is.
I got a local beer, like we said,
me and Rex are, this is called--
Oh, I forgot, was it?
Well, okay, so I just--
It's a local person only. I had two drinks
in my fridge. Local person only.
Okay, well, I'm Spanish.
I had two beers, or I had two drinks in my fridge,
and I didn't wanna go buy more, so.
Okay.
I'll be honest, I didn't-- I forgot completely.
So you don't support local businesses,
is what you're saying?
I also can't go outside, dude.
- Oh, that's true. - I came up with this today.
- There's COVID outside.
- Came up with this today.
New York City, the city that never breathes.
Wow. - It's pretty good.
- Yeah, well done. - Does that hit you
like a ton of bricks or what?
- Except they do breathe most days.
- You're breathing right now?
- Well, we had two days where you couldn't,
it wasn't as good to breathe air.
(laughing)
So for those two days,
that could have been a good T-shirt to wear.
- And how did that affect you personally,
your personal life. But before we go into that,
this is an additional Mexican beer. It's called Allende.
It's a golden ale and it's okay.
What's the closest beer that we would know that you would compare it to?
Um, probably like a, like a, like a, uh, like a beer.
You are worthless. Like a Bud Light?
No, it's more than a butt light.
It's like two butt lights.
It's heavier than a butt light.
Yeah.
But not quite a butt, a normal butt.
Like a butt strong, I would say.
Okay.
All right.
Like a butt heavy.
Yeah.
Butt heavy.
Butt wiser.
Right.
Red can.
Yeah.
Well, that sounds pretty good.
How, how has the PR affected your, your, your daily life, Caleb?
How are you?
How are you doing?
Well, well, let's see.
I edited a video of all my different kills from Valorant.
- Yeah, you committed a sexual assault on me.
- No, I didn't. - Essentially.
- He did deep fake Juvio. - Nobody will ever see it,
but I did use a deep fake to clone Juvio's voice.
I used the AI technology to make Juvio,
a fake Juvio voice.
And now I have, if anybody wants to make Juvio
say something, let me know and I'll send you the audio file.
What else did I do?
Today I ate-- - You had him say
some pretty terrible stuff, I'll be honest.
- I did, it's really bad.
- It's really bad.
- I did a, my diet today was I had four
frozen White Castle sliders.
- Yum. - Okay.
- And three pieces of pizza.
- That's nice.
- So you're health maxing.
- Yeah, I just don't feel very good today.
- Yeah, okay.
- Yeah.
- But yeah, that's it, Fred, what have you guys been up to?
- Oh, I've been just going outside and breathing the air.
Mostly.
- Cool, man.
Really fucking cool to bring that up in front of me.
Do you realize where I live right now?
- You know what I've been doing?
I take a little piece of fruit,
and I go to my balcony, and I sit,
and I just look at the horizon,
and look way, way out there in the horizon
where the sky looks normal, and I breathe.
- You eat the fruit, and you get a power like Mario,
Mario Sunshine, like Yoshi.
You are my Yoshi.
- I'm not Yoshi.
- You are my Yoshi.
I'm Mario and you're my Yoshi.
- Yeah, I'm gonna want Mario respects Yoshi.
- I respect you. - In a lot of ways.
- I respect any animal.
- But he also rode on his back
and you threw him away at every possible opportunity.
- You don't ride me at all.
- Oh, I could.
- I have never been ridden by you.
Okay, that's--
- I could ride on you.
- He's never ridden me, that's not true.
- You are my Yoshi.
- Yeah, your tongue is huge.
- He's Yoshi, right?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- No, it's my normal tongue.
No, it's gargantuan.
- Oh wow, that's actually way bigger
than I thought it was gonna be.
- Okay, show me your tongue.
That's not your whole tongue.
- My whole tongue?
I'll push it really far out.
I don't have a very big tongue.
We should start a Kiss cover band,
but we just dress up like Kiss
and we play like Juice WRLD songs.
- Yeah.
- Or Nirvana or something.
- They don't have very good songs, do they?
- KISS, no, they have terrible songs.
They're a really bad band.
- Yeah, let's not do that.
Let's do another band.
Let's do Slipknot.
- I love how there's like a really great
anti-Semitic story about KISS.
- And what is it?
Are they all Jewish?
I know Gene Simmons is.
- Gene Simmons is.
It's a story about him meeting Haim Saban.
Uh, because you know who Heim Saban is?
I do not.
He's the guy that brought like power rangers to the United States.
Uh, and brought like X man.
Yeah.
He's like a billionaire from like cartoons.
And, uh, he wanted to make like kiss me to the X-Men.
Yeah.
You want to make that?
And, uh, like Heim Saban turns to his like Jewish lawyer and, uh, with the
Gene Simmons in the room and says in like Hebrew,
it's like, all right, now here's where we like rape him.
And Gene Simmons replies in like Hebrew.
He's like, you know, I can you know, Jewish, right?
I can speak this.
I would say that's even anti-Semitic.
Well, I think it's a Semitic.
It just gets passed around on like, you know, those kind of forums.
It's like an anecdote that gets passed.
Oh, I see.
But it is an anecdote.
I have an anecdote for you.
- That kind of thing.
- Yeah.
- Just a quick anti-Semitic anecdote.
- Well, that's--
- I don't fuck with that.
- I would say if Gene Simmons was a polyglot
who was not Jewish but knew Hebrew for some reason,
then maybe the story in its retelling,
depending on who's telling it,
might be a little bit anti-Semitic.
- Well, if you also,
well, he also would have to have gone,
I hate the Jews and I love Hitler,
and maybe then I would consider anti-Semitic.
- Yeah, and then, "Bah!"
- Yeah, "Ah, I love Hitler, ah!"
If he did that, I would be like--
- Yeah, if he said, "I love Hitler,"
at the end of the story, it might be--
(Rex laughs)
Then I could guess, I could see it.
And even then, I mean, context matters.
- Yeah, true. - But, yeah, I don't know.
That's not the, what's the most anti-Semitic story
you've ever been a party to, Rex?
I mean, honestly, not that much.
Every time you go to New York, can we do this?
Yeah, I would say time Julio just sends me.
Everything.
Yeah. Julio just sends me.
It's funny because, you know, yeah, I'm like so nice and like generous.
And Julio will send me like tick tocks of people throwing change on the ground and
picking up.
They'll be like, this is you.
- Whoa.
- That's not true.
- Well, you have to think,
you're probably the only Jewish person
he's ever known in his entire life.
- That is true.
- I don't think that's true,
but I think you're the only person that I like
that I think is Jewish.
- Whoa.
- So you just assume the people you don't like are Jewish?
Is that annoying?
- Wow, he did say that I think is Jewish.
- I didn't say that.
- You did.
That's exactly what she said.
Let's guys, let's move on.
OK, I've done the high holidays.
I've done Passover.
I know I know all about it.
Did I've been to temple?
I've seen this one.
Yeah, the shofar.
I love that shit.
What's that?
It is fun.
The shofar is a big Ram's horn that they blow into during their
like church.
Yeah, there's a really no why the holiday.
So like a blow the ram's horn.
There's a specific way you have to blow it.
So how it's like starts.
And there's no designated service.
You just do it randomly.
Be like, oh, OK.
What I saw, they just did it randomly.
Yeah. OK.
I don't remember.
You have to be like a designated blower.
Yeah. Well, it's pretty tough to blow.
Maybe for a fucking Jew.
What did you go to temple for?
What were you doing?
-He's dating a girl, dude. -Yeah, I dated a chosen one
for some time.
Not Rakana, I wasn't doing Rakana.
[LAUGHTER]
I wasn't there trying to spot a weakness.
He was drawing a layout of the temple.
Yeah.
I was drawing a layout.
I was drawing a foul during a layout
because we play basketball outside.
They do always have a basketball court outside the temple.
Dude, it's so much fun playing with like old Jewish guys.
They take it very seriously.
They have the their their old Jewish guys are so far from athletic,
but they are nice at basketball.
Yeah, they are fucking nice.
They're the epitome of like the white guy who just drains his free throws.
Outside shots, mid range jumpers.
They're all five foot six, but somehow getting way above me.
Yeah, I can't do anything about it.
Yep.
When are we going to start our own basketball team?
I've been wanting to play basketball so bad recently.
Oh.
Is it because of the NBA Finals?
Yes, it is.
Just watching them on the TV.
I've been watching them and I've been taking Phil to the park and walking by all these
kids playing basketball and I just love how mean they are.
It's like, I like any sport or game, that's why I like video games too, I like being mean
to my closest friends.
Yeah.
It's like in kind of a fun way.
We have a new game that Julio and I have been playing.
What have you been playing?
It's called Friends vs. Friends.
It's either a 1v1 or 2v2.
And yeah, we're so mean to each other.
What is it?
Just an FPS deck builder.
It's an FPS card game.
Oh, I think I've seen this.
Yeah, it's fun.
We are very rude to each other and we call each other bad words.
One of us always cries about the netcode every single night.
Because we play on Julio's servers.
We keep playing on East and he keeps crying about it.
I'm not East.
Why would you play on East? Play on West.
Because it's the best server according to the game.
That's bullshit.
Unless you hop in on Friends vs. Friends, I don't want to hear it from you.
No ice having a...
Hop in right now!
Right fucking now, let's go!
No.
- That's not the podcast, I'll play this shit right fucking now.
Two versus one, you two versus me.
- Okay, you have to buy it.
Yeah, it's six dollars. - I'm out.
I am out.
I never wanna play this game.
This game is terrible.
- Let him go.
It's a good game.
It is fun.
- I need a new game.
I've been thinking about, I saw a video
where some people played Battleship
against each other online,
and I got really into the thought of playing Battleship.
- That's crazy.
That's a really boring game.
We can play that on your iPhone, right?
Shut up.
I want to play it on my computer.
And I want to
I thought about maybe
I wanted to, before I made my gaming
montage, I wanted to maybe get
a bunch of clips of me playing like Tetris
and maybe like me solving a crossword
and stuff and putting those as highlights
in there. Maybe I'll do that for the next one.
I don't think there's a single crossword you could solve
by yourself.
- You really think that?
You really think that I don't have
a six day streak on my crossword right now
and I'm not a New York Times crossword subscriber?
Are you a fucking moron?
Are you a lepton?
Just to showcase how ginormous my vocabulary is?
- I don't think you're using that word right.
- Funny enough, the first person I started
all this discussion, I think Rex is a bad friend.
- I would cook Rex in any time crossword.
- Any crossword. - I'm grease.
- Any cross, yes, you are a grease ball.
Any crossword.
Any crossword, I will cook you in.
Time it any day of the week, let's go.
- All right, we'll do a Monday.
- I'll put $100 on it.
- Show me. - You'll do a Monday, you pussy?
- Well, I'm trying to go down for you, I assume.
- Oh, let's do Thursday.
Thursday's the hardest one.
- I'm pretty sure Friday, Sunday's the hardest one.
- Sunday is the biggest one, not the hardest one.
- Oh God, you're so stupid.
You don't even know what you're talking about.
You're going to get destroyed.
- I could destroy you in any game.
Jeopardy, I could wipe the floor with you.
- You just don't even know what you're talking about.
No, you're just an idiot, dude.
You've never beaten me in a single game.
- Okay, okay, here we go.
- That is true.
- Okay, guys, let's, we can solve this very easily.
We will hold a show match of, what,
like three to five different games.
- Okay.
- And we'll decide the winner and who's the best at games,
whoever reaches it on these games.
We'll do crosswords, we'll do Jeopardy, I guess.
I don't know.
- How do you do Jeopardy?
How are we gonna do Jeopardy?
- I don't know.
He said Jeopardy.
I don't know why he said Jeopardy.
- That's just watching Jeopardy
and yelling out the answer.
(laughing)
- There's no winning that.
You can't win that.
I want to see you bleed.
No, we could do that.
We could definitely do that.
Just pick a random episode of Japanese.
I will destroy you.
You don't know what you've just gotten yourself into.
I would put you back in third grade like Billy Madison, dude.
You wish I was in third grade.
Yeah, because you need to repeat it.
No, because you're a pedophile.
If I was in third grade, you would literally...
I would be fingered.
You'd be fingering my nose.
You'd be fingering my eyeballs.
You'd be fingering my scabs.
You'd be so disgusting with my little body.
That is true.
I would just pick you up like a basketball.
I'd palm your head.
You couldn't palm a fucking ping pong ball.
I'll beat you in any sport.
I'll beat you in any test of
mental anything.
Acuity, fortitude, knowledge.
You're done.
- Now this is now a lifelong crusade.
The fact that you insulted me with your crossword gambit.
This is a lifelong crusade.
- I like how your vocabulary has just completely changed.
(laughing)
- Can I ask you a question?
Are you still like a New York Times games subscriber?
Okay.
- You play the pussy ones.
You play wordle, you play the bee one.
What's that called?
- Bee word?
- Spelling bee, you play spelling bee.
- I did play that once or twice.
God you're gay. It's included in the subscription. I don't know what you want
He only plays it cuz it's included in a $5 subscription
What the fuck is wrong with you? Did you watch the army hammer documentary cuz you have a Netflix subscription?
No, but you know, but now that you know about it, you're going to I mean I might as well
Yeah, you're done you pay for Netflix. No, I'm actually I do. Yeah, I
Think that Netflix change finally hit us
They're kicking us out. Mmm. I think what is it start because you share your parents or something?
Yeah, my my uncles
looks
Mmm, and they're finally kicking us out and you know
That I all gotta say is Netflix. I'm doing that the thing that Kayla's interacts right now, but to you directly
OK. So I'm challenging the entirety of Netflix on a crossword
and basketball, one v one in Jeopardy games
so I can have a free a free password.
You won't get a free password out of Netflix?
Probably not. No.
Yeah. I'm not going to pretend like I'm would win in any test of athletics against you.
I have a job that destroys my body, whereas you
podcast for a living.
So, you know, there's just no conversation.
You say that because you work on an Oriel rig.
You sit and-
Oriel rig?
I work at a computer for 80 hours.
It's worse.
You spend most of your day on Discord calls with this guy.
That's your job.
That is not true.
That's your fucking job.
How does that destroy your buddy?
Get a standing desk.
I have a standing desk.
That's your fault.
You're sitting down at it!
Wait, so-
It's a podcast.
Make it send.
[laughter]
I know for a fact you've never stood at this desk.
Wait, it disconnected!
*laughter*
It disconnected!
Oh my god!
Oh, how did I know that was gonna happen?
Why were you so stupid?
Oh, hello. Hello, hello.
- Hello.
- Yeah, I think in a game of wits, I think I'm beating you.
Based on what we just saw,
I think you've just disqualified yourself.
- I don't think he can hear us.
- He can't. - Can he hear us?
Can he hear us?
- I see you pretending.
- Oh my God.
- Actually, you there?
- Rex?
- I have something to say.
Wait, this is how he looks at his computer when he doesn't think anyone's watching.
He strokes his chin!
For all the audio listeners, Rex completely, he went to do his stand-up desk and he's gone
again.
He hit the thing.
He hit his stand-up desk.
It went up and it disconnected him and now he's back and he can hear us.
Now he's quizzically looking.
We just got Rex, we recorded a lot of you looking at, this is your problem solving face, you do this go.
Oh, what the?
Oh, what?
Oh my god.
That is the funniest thing I have ever seen.
Oh god.
But it's been that Rex is having a problem.
Uh oh.
I can hear him.
Uh, okay.
Stop moving the desk.
Oh my god.
Alright Rex, why don't you explain what just occurred.
So the standing desk went up
and it unplugged my router.
Yeah.
Which by the way is proof that you've never
That's not true. I do it all the time.
Why would the router cable not reach if you do it all the time?
No, the plug is just against the wall.
So I just...
I completely believe you.
It's fine. It's still unplugged because it just is now on Wi-Fi.
It just took a second to switch over.
No, I really do believe you.
I don't know why you wouldn't.
Yeah, you're right. It'd be absurd for me to not believe that.
Listen, you can believe it if you want to. I'm telling you.
I do. I do believe you. I do. Everything about the room that I see behind this man tells me,
this guy has a standing desk that he uses all day every day. Well, actually,
the fact that you have so many supplements makes me think that you are doing some work
to counteract the toll that this job takes on your body.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- I'll try.
- Sometimes I do want Rex to just go around his room
and just explain what everything on the floor
and on the walls is, just a little room tour.
- I don't think there's anything to explain.
It's just either clothes or trash or books.
- We need a tactical nuke in this room.
- It's fun. - Yeah.
- When you move, are you gonna get rid
of everything you own?
- No, but I will hide it better.
- I don't think that's true.
You're not going to pare down a little bit?
I mean, I might,
but probably just do it there and just throw it on the street
out the window. Like it's,
how have you felt about all of these New Yorkers complaining about the air
quality? Meanwhile, it's basically what the air quality is every day in LA.
I, you know, New Yorkers love to complain.
There's just something genetic about it
that makes them want to complain.
I think that's what it is.
- Something that unites them.
- I love the concept of like,
people are like, "Oh, it's like smoking a cigarette
"without any of the nicotine."
And it's like, well, I vape 24/7,
so my lungs are already acclimated
to whatever it's gonna throw at me.
- All it's done the last couple days
has made me smoke more cigarettes,
'cause I'm like, well, I might, I mean, I'm already--
- Might as well.
- Yeah, I might as well.
- Do you have an air purifier?
- No, somebody offered to bring me one the other day
'cause they had a spare.
And I was like, it's probably just gonna be
like one more day of this, I don't care.
- Yeah.
- I think they said it was gonna land
that's until tonight now.
- I think they said till Saturday.
- Whoa.
- That's crazy.
Is the sky still completely yellow?
- No, that was like three hours yesterday.
- Oh, that's boring then.
- People are just big babies, man.
- I thought you were living in Breaking Bad for like a week.
- I think-- - See, that's what I mean.
- The picture of the Diablo poster is so funny.
- That is a funny photo.
- No.
- Which photo?
- There's a picture of the Diablo poster,
or Diablo screen ad in Times Square.
And it said, "Welcome to Hell, New York,"
and everything was orange around it.
Which by the way, hell is not orange, it is red.
- Right, like fire. - True.
- So nice try.
- Yeah.
Diablo, one of those games that,
I've been talking about Rex.
- Yeah. - I'm like,
we should maybe play it, but I'm also like,
I think if I make anyone play it with me,
they'll just hold it against me,
that they had to buy it and play it,
and no one liked it.
- I remember when I first got,
When I first built a computer, when I was 16 or 17, Diablo III had just come out.
And I bought it, and I was very excited to play it.
And I had a photo on my Instagram for a long time when I was in high school
that was just a picture of the Diablo III box that I just bought.
And it was like, "Can't wait to crack this bad boy open."
And then I played it and I just had no... It sucked.
It's not my kind of game at all.
Yeah, so what like did you know anything about the game?
It's like did you see Diablo?
You like damn the demon pretty much?
Yeah, yeah, I was like the demon is cool.
The cover is cool.
Yeah, people like these games.
That's good enough for me.
I had an idea for an invention,
which is you telling me this reminded me of this.
It's a it's a novelty beer cozy.
And when you take a sip, it's like a Billy the Big Mouse.
Big Mouth Bass type beer cozy.
So you take a sip and it's like,
"Hey, nice chug."
- Oh, that's good. - Or like, "Nice sip."
"Hey, good sip, bro."
- I could see that never getting old.
- Yeah. (laughs)
Yeah, I think if you could sell it for like $10,
it'd be a perfect novelty gift.
- Yeah, it'd be great. - Yeah, it's just like
one of those gifts that people just hate to receive.
- You had a little lip slip there,
And you said, "Billy the big mouse is a better idea."
A mouse on a wall, or a rat even,
that you have mounted like a fish sideways,
and it cocks its head out and--
- It's like, "Can I have a piece of cheese?"
- Sings, yeah.
- What do you think of this?
(laughing)
- It doesn't sing songs at all.
- Billy Bass would be better
If it looked you, it also had some kind of eye tracking technology
and once every couple of days, it just looked you right in the eyes
and asked if it could have a worm, it'd be much better.
Can I have a worm?
Hey, man, it's really hot up here.
Can you take me down?
I don't really like it on this wall.
It's not a good place for a pet mounted to the wall.
Do you guys think it is it is gauche to have an animal?
Mounted to the wall?
Yeah. Yes.
I don't like that.
- I don't know what gauche means.
- Is it too much?
- It depends on what kind of guy you are.
I think if you are like--
- I've never seen one of those and been like,
oh, that's something that's cool.
- I think if you live like--
- It's not cool, but I understand it
if you actually like hunted it or something.
- Even then.
I think that's the only way that people do it, really.
- I think if you live in a cabin or in a mansion,
You need to have something that's mounted on the wall or as a rug.
But if you don't, then it's illegal for you to do it.
The rug is definitely gauche. Get a real rug.
Yeah, they're not good rugs, man.
Yeah.
Yeah, but it's a thing that you killed.
Well, it could be something else, like a chicken.
Chicken rug?
You want a chicken rug?
You walk in as a golden retriever.
All the taxes of the rug are just chicken feet.
It's murder.
Yeah, what do you want to say?
Like it's a taxidermy for like your old pets.
You just make them into rugs.
And it's like they're just laying down sleeping.
That's my new idea.
That's my new invention.
This is the invention episode.
It's been able to clone like a piece of chicken.
Like a particularly good,
a particularly good chicken wing.
No, I've had this thought about food before.
You're not wrong, which is not,
not not exactly the cloning idea,
not that exactly, but the idea that...
How can you tell if it's good?
You ate it already.
That's what I'm saying.
I'm gonna clone it.
You take one bite and then you decide,
oh, I want more of this chicken wing.
And then you put that in some kind of
microwave style Spy Kids device
that spits out 500 more of whatever you put into it.
But I think about this all the time.
You ever have like a fruit, like a mango, a watermelon,
one of those like 50/50 fruits where it's not always as good
as you remember it being, but every once in a while you get one that is so, so good.
And you take a bite and you think this might be the best of this fruit
of like the entire year.
This might be I might have just gotten the fruit of the year.
If not the fruit of the year, it's in the top 1%.
Be able to clone that.
Yeah, and then that's all we should be eating, because sometimes you'll eat a mango and it is so bad.
And it's like five million pieces of floss
that are mango flavored, all wrapped around the ball.
I think we may have had an apple of the year.
There's an apple I still remember that I had at my mom's
house in probably 2013.
crisp apple and it was so, so good. I just mowed the lawn, I came in, I ate an apple
and it was so damn good.
Yeah, I had a really good apple, I think, it must have been around a month ago and it was
like really sweet, it was really juicy. I bought one of those apples and I had one yesterday
and it was okay, but it wasn't as juicy or sweet as the one I had.
They really stick with you.
Yeah, a good piece of fruit will you'll remember that.
No doubt I want to I want to pink lady apple.
They're amazing pink lady honey crisp.
Yep.
There's another one.
I don't know but you know, it is a bad apple that people think
is good.
Fuji.
Yes, that is a bad apple buddy.
That is a mealy disgusting Apple that it tastes like a wild
Apple.
You ever had a wild Apple?
No.
Just the one like right off a tree somewhere?
Oh no, no, can't say I have.
It's disgusting. It's like apple sauce.
I went to the supermarket yesterday and I think the pink ones was whatever you said,
the pink something. I buy those but it is, I don't understand what the name
of the conditions are. Like I don't know what is the difference between apples at all.
Just a genomic sequence.
Yeah, it's like different species of apples.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, I don't I don't fuck with that.
I don't fuck with different.
I fuck with it's like, you know, like some species are worse than
others.
Obviously this call proves that you know, so actually our games
will prove that I don't think you and I are particularly different
species.
You think that Juvio is a different species?
Yeah, I told them both of you.
I think you have like Bigfoot maybe.
That's not true.
Some kind of Sasquatch animal.
He is 900% Neanderthal DNA.
No, he's not a Neanderthal.
He is not.
He's pretty tall.
He might be a raccoon.
Kind of beady little eyes.
Yeah, you're getting dangerously close to being racist there.
What?
(laughs)
- Resembles a raccoon a little bit.
- Listen, I just said dangerously close,
not that you were over the line in any way.
- But I was in danger, you're saying?
- Yeah.
- What animal do you think me and Rex are, Jibia?
- You are a turtle.
- Okay, Master of Disguise reference much?
I don't know what that is.
Well, you just wrote the whole movie yourself, so don't worry.
Rex is five.
Oh, I don't know what that is.
So mouse.
He goes West.
You're you're kind of like a like a like a mouse.
You nibble.
You're a nibbler.
What are you talking about?
You know, you think you're eating with me?
Yeah, I don't nibble. You nibble.
No, I eat voraciously.
No, you nibble and you store.
Wait, no, you're a squirrel.
You're a chipmunk.
You nibble and you store food for the winter.
All right, I'll buy that.
He's a chipmunk.
I do store food for later.
Then Jubilee, the wild fox, the raccoon eats my trash.
He is a chipmunk.
He's got that high ass voice.
Christmas, Christmas, Christmas.
That's you.
Yeah.
Wrecked the chipmunk.
What do you think Caleb is as an animal?
This beer is almost gone.
This was an okay beer.
First beer that I don't completely hate.
Nice.
20 episodes in.
Sort of primate.
Closest one to a human, I'll take that.
Yeah, but just a little bit off.
What's the biggest animal?
I'm the most human of the three.
What are the most pink animal?
That's not an important question to answer.
Baboon with an ass.
The baboon with the reddish ass.
Baboon with the ass.
What's the most pink animal in the world?
Um...
Some kind of like a muskrat.
Axolotl.
You're an axolotl.
I'm not an axolotl, because those can also be like blue.
No, if anything, I'm like a mole rat or something like that.
Okay, you can be that.
Like a naked cat.
Yeah, exactly. Something with like a pink bad skin.
I don't think you're a naked cat. You're very sociable.
You're very outgoing.
That is not true.
Some stereotype about those cats.
That is completely true.
I spend nine days of ten in my apartment.
Hmm. I don't know.
I don't know. I've seen you interact with the outside world.
Don't tell people this shit, dude. I'm honestly fucking shy as fuck.
He's not shy.
I really am.
He's outgoing and sociable.
Yeah.
No, I have shyness.
Any command groups?
No, I'm really shy.
Someone showed that this one time that we're outside,
you demanded that the entire group stuck together around you
as the leader.
That's not true.
Is that true?
That's true.
Yeah.
I stuck an entire group of people around me?
I don't remember that.
Where were we?
I do remember him convincing a group of people to betray a person who wasn't there and eat
a delicious meal without him.
I did not do this.
You're making this up in your head.
You have this idea of me.
That's not who I am.
That is not who I am whatsoever.
I know who you are.
You're a complete betrayer.
That is not me at all.
You've been ice cold to me ever since.
I mean, it's going to take a while for me to forgive such an egregious betrayal.
I don't want your forgiveness.
Cause I didn't do it in the first place.
It wasn't me, man.
It was a group effort.
See, here's what happens when you're the leader or at least when people
perceive you to be the leader, everything gets pinned on you.
You take, you fall on the sword.
No matter what I am responsible for the sins of all.
How does that, who was driving the car?
(clears throat)
- Who, that is,
how is that my fault?
That I'm the only one who can drive?
- Wait, you know what?
I know how to drive.
- You can't drive, your license is upside down.
- That's not true.
- People, if you got pulled over, you'd go straight to jail.
You drive on the other side of the road,
you have the steering wheel in the middle of the car,
like a cartoon, like a Richard Scarry cartoon.
- That's not how it is down here.
- I think it is.
- That's not how it is.
- I believe that. - Wait, you know what?
I think that's, you're right, that is completely,
I'm sorry, that's not fair to you.
Let's just spin it on the person who put the address,
no, let's spin it on the person who put the address
in the Google Maps and led us that way.
- You say that like I knew the address.
I looked it up, on a lark, I looked up Fogotachow,
I thought, oh, that's-- - On a lark?
- On a lark. - Oh, on a lark.
- I said, that's funny.
That'd be funny if we went-- - Oh, how whimsical it is
to betray my friend.
It wasn't even good.
It was really good.
You're fucking lying.
I didn't even like it.
Look at me in the eyes. Tell me that.
Look at me.
It wasn't that good.
(laughter)
You're new to eating meat.
It would upset your stomach.
If you ate all that meat, it would upset your stomach.
There's no way you could handle a pho go to chow.
I could handle it.
No, no, no. It would have made you sick.
doubled over in front of the toilet spewing your guts out because I thought
and I was enjoyed every second gracious actually I I'm not I was not even
gracious we as a unit me Julio and Cameron were being gracious by not
inviting you which we all consciously chose to do I found a funny
responsibility of this crime okay then I do too
fuck you you can't do that I bow out of any responsibility that's what you say I
I forgo the community.
I decided to not be responsible for this heinous murder.
I am not, yeah, I was not part of that.
You were completely part of it.
I was a victim. I will say it.
Victims do not, victims do not, you do not shovel,
victims do not shovel garlic ribeye down their gullet.
No victim on earth has ever done that.
That is not the meal of a victim.
You caught me today.
I cloned him?
Oh, and he's deflecting because he knows.
He knows that he ate every single bite of that steak.
And with every bite he's like, "Man, this is so good that Rex would enjoy this."
Rex would really have an amazing time eating this steak.
I would have.
I'm just making a case.
He's the one who said, "I'm talking to Rex. He just woke up."
He probably doesn't want to come.
I am. No, that's not what I said.
- That's not what I said, that's not what I said.
- He probably just doesn't wanna come,
let's not even check.
- That's not what I said.
- Let's be so careless and thoughtless
that we don't even check.
- Listen, I'm just making the case
that Caleb has a history of being a betrayer.
A leader and a betrayer.
- Because I cloned you, because I cloned your voice?
- Behind my back.
- I own your voice.
- It would have been nice for you to have cloned a steak
for me and brought it home.
- Buddy, you should have seen me begging
with these fucking Brazilians.
Begging.
I said let me bet like Tony the brain no you guys don't do take out I know you
don't do any kind of leftovers I know it's against some kind of Brazilian rule
you know but please please just this one time I know a very very sick boy yeah
who needs this steak he's never I needed it or it's true you were also said what
was wrong with you that day no I don't know I think that Airbnb was making me
sick he was sick to eat you heard it here I mean he's too sick he was too ill to
probably would have healed me it probably would have made me completely probably
would have made it a thousand times worse it was a six hundred thousand
milligrams will never fucking know I'm right cuz you're not getting invited
next time cuz you've been such a baby you will be a you will be a sad lonely
man who walks into fogey to chow and says table for one please I want an all you
can eat meat buffet for one single person.
- The full experience, the full singular experience.
- Yes, they'll say, "Do you just want drinks?"
Or you wanna say to the bar, you'll say,
"No, no, no, thank you, give me a big booth
"and I'll just eat all by myself."
- Yep.
- That is what you will do.
- And I'll take pictures and I'll send it to you.
- And I'll go, "Oh man, oh wait,
"I've already eaten this shit before, who gives a fuck?"
- I think I've just come up with a fresh resolution
for this entire episode.
- What?
- Once Rex moves to New York,
we're gonna hold a show match
where both of you go one-to-one on crosswords, basketball,
and other games,
and the winner gets to go to Photoshop by themselves.
(laughing)
- I don't know, this kind of sounds good.
- Yeah, doesn't that sound good?
- I'm down.
We need to come up with a list of games that are
somewhat neutral between the two of us.
- Rex threw down the gauntlet,
So I think he should decide half the games
or three of the games.
- Well, I would think that half of the games
would be decided by him and half would be decided by me.
- Yeah.
- What three games do you think you could beat Kelvin?
- I think, I mean, and this is no,
I don't mean anything against you by this.
I think any intellectual game I would win.
- What do you think is an intellectual game?
What do you think of as an intellectual, Ken?
Anything that's not hyper-specific
like trivia
like basketball trivia, I would just do it.
Rock, paper, scissors?
Do you think that's intellectual?
I wouldn't say so.
Tic-Tac-Toe?
No. I would Tic-Tac-Toe.
There is, you know, there is
an art of war to, you know,
rock, paper, scissors.
Alright, so I'm gonna look.
Wait, what's the art of war?
Well, you need to name specific games. You can't just broadly say you're so stupid that I'll beat you at anything intellectual.
Yeah, yeah, name three games.
The question was name specific games.
I do think I would win at a crossword puzzle.
You don't do them. That's just absurd. I've seen you do crosswords with Juvio. You're terrible at them.
That's not true.
Yeah, you're shit. I'll pull up the VOD right now. You're a complete ass. I would smoke you.
I mean if you want to choose it, if you want to choose that as one of your games, just
know that you're destroying yourself, you're destroying any chance you have.
I don't know.
I only thought of the crossword puzzle, that was the only one I hadn't moaned.
Well you threw down the gauntlet for the entire range of games.
You said intellectual games.
Name another intellectual game.
I don't know.
I don't know, I don't know.
Why are you so tough?
Do I have to... Do you think I came here with a list of games?
I can't even think of it.
This is a very funny thing to be so confident about.
Just name two other games.
I don't know. Clue?
You're a fucking retard.
It's so funny. You might be the stupidest person I know.
This is the funniest possible angle I can take.
Choose games that you know you could beat me at League of Legends. There's plenty of games. You could beat me at what's that fun?
You know you don't play that game
You don't play crosswords
Yeah, dude. How was the last time you did a crossword?
Month and a half ago. Yeah, you don't play crosswords
No
You're getting cooked on crosswords. Do you have any of the gauntlet is canceled? Yeah, this is just it's absurd
He has one single game.
Wait a minute, Fulgurado.
You don't have a single challenge.
You have one challenge.
What's a game you think you can beat me at?
That's not a shooting game.
Crosswords.
Besides crosswords.
Name another game.
(laughter)
Name a single game.
Gabe Gauntlet let's do it. It's hard. Games on the brain. Well I'm not the one who said
the challenge so it shouldn't be on me. I mean I didn't walk into this thinking I was
going to challenge you to anything. Well you issued the challenge. That's true. Intellectual
games. I think general trivia. We might be even match but I mean any man is going to
say that they're going to beat somebody else in trivia so I have to say that I would beat
you.
That's why I was saying Jeopardy if we could figure out a way to.
Let's just do a straight up IQ test.
Okay, I've just done a search for intellectual games and the first nine results are chess.
Chess, you can play chess.
Rex is bad at chess, you can see his face.
Yeah I'm not good at chess.
That's the most intellectual game, I can't believe you can think of it.
- I don't know what Elevate is.
Sudoku, Crossword, Mahjong.
- I've never played Mahjong.
- I'm Mahjong.
- I wouldn't win at Mahjong.
- Probably.
- Well, that's more of a spiritual connection kind of thing.
And also you know how to play the game.
- Yeah, I play Mahjong almost every night.
- What?
Is that true?
- Yeah.
- That's crazy.
- I play online with Chinese people on an app on my phone.
- Do you do well?
I'm okay. On one of my old accounts I was like...
Celestial. Which was a writing.
That means nothing to me. I don't know what celestial is.
That's gotta be good. That's gotta be pretty high.
Okay.
What other intellectual games could we play?
Tetris is the last one.
Oh, I'm a beast at Tetris.
Wait, the one that we could do so easily is Connect 4.
- That is, I think, more of a battle of who is the stupidest
more so than who's the smartest.
One time I played Connect Four with Patrick at a bar
and I think I beat him 25 times in a row.
(laughing)
- That is by definition an intellectual game.
- Yeah.
It would be funny to just take an IQ test.
- Take a straight up.
(laughing)
One time me and Cameron in college,
we took an IQ test.
We literally did that.
We took an online IQ test at the exact same time
and we got our results
and he got one point higher than me on the thing.
And what was the result?
I don't know.
It brought up in the 300s, 400s.
I would, I could see that.
I could see him being one point smarter than you.
Yeah, it really was such a,
it confirmed basically every suspicion I ever had
about the difference between our levels of intelligence,
which is that he is one point higher than me.
- Yeah.
Yeah. - Yeah.
- I think I took an IQ test like three months ago
and my IQ dropped like 20 points.
So you might, there might be a chance there.
- Did you, but isn't IQ,
don't you need like to go take an IQ test?
You have to have like a proctor there
and it's like this administered thing.
- Yeah, but there's so many online ones that you can take.
Mine went from like 139 to like 120.
I was like, oh, right.
I've just become massively stupider in the last few years.
- I also think definitely since the time
that me and Cameron took those IQ tests,
I've definitely become a lot stupider.
See, that's a perfect example.
I feel like I used to have some kind of pride
in being a somewhat smart person.
And not even to say I was smart,
but I thought I was smart,
and it was something that I thought was a virtue.
Yeah.
And now I don't hold that at all.
Like I really just, I'm way too stupid.
Well, I think that when you're like in school, you think you're smart because you're like,
you know, at least you're like taking shit in.
You're forced to learn all the time, yeah.
Yeah.
But now that you're a grown up, what are you doing?
You're sitting in your apartment eating pizza all day.
Well not all day, I ate pizza for 20 minutes and then I ate the sliders for another 10
probably, if that, honestly, I shoveled them down.
Yeah.
- I'd like a big glass of milk too
if you wanna know everything I ate.
(laughing)
- Just eating like a 15 year old.
- Eating worse than a 15 year old.
Eating like a last meal type of day.
- Yeah.
- Like just weirdly specific,
kind of pregnancy craving type of day.
- Right.
- Yeah, you're like if a nine year old
was left with some devices.
- I like to think that my perfect life is,
have you ever seen the movie Blank Check?
- Yeah.
It's about an 11-year-old boy who basically gets unlimited money and he does a go-kart
racing track in his backyard of the mansion that he buys and he has a friend that he hangs
out with all the time who's bigger than him. Remind you of anybody?
Yep. It does.
It does.
I think that kid's the smartest kid of all time. He bought real estate.
Yeah.
That's so smart.
It is kind of impressive, yeah.
He bought like a disgusting giant mansion, but probably if I had a hoe too.
Did he have a hoe?
Yeah, there's a old there's a grown woman that was with him.
Gold digger.
Yeah, you got to look out for those men.
You do once you get that blank check.
It's all over.
Now, did you guys hear the play on the plot?
- The plot, the parts I remember--
- He gets hit by a car, right?
- He gets hit by the car, he's riding his bike,
and then the guy writes a check to pay for his bike
to basically be like, "No trouble, don't sue me, whatever.
"Here's a check, put whatever amount the bike cost."
And just cash the check.
And then I don't even know if they show him
writing how much he cashes it for.
But also the check, what I've always thought about
that movie is if you're the kid, you have to strike this balance between as much money
as you can, but then also you have to think, this guy doesn't have, like I don't know how
much money this guy has, he drives a nice car.
Yeah, only a kid would think that he has $20 million in a bank account.
Yeah, exactly.
And then also, I think the rest of the movie is the guy being like, "Where'd my money go?"
As if it's some kind of, like it's just for, because the kid got clipped on his bike, doesn't
go to the hospital, no major injuries.
You just like broke his bike.
The kid gets a still $20 million from some guy.
No past movie.
It is good.
So like a stupid movie to me,
they don't make movies like that anymore.
They really don't.
You couldn't make a movie like that.
Every movie and every game that comes out now is bad.
Yeah.
And I've been I've been thinking about this because I think
Unfortunately, at the end of the year,
the Zelda game is gonna be crowned
as the game of the year,
but it's so boring and bad.
- Yeah, it doesn't look very interesting.
I'm not very interested in that game.
- No, it's really bad for eight hours,
and then you finally get to just explore the world,
and it's fun for a little bit,
but then you're like, okay, well, this is just boring again.
I got like, I don't wanna do this shit
for like a billion hours.
- Yeah.
- Meanwhile, I'm getting attacked by a bunch of videos
so that people just have like the most overpowered shit
of all time.
And there's just no games.
There's no games at all.
That's my conclusion.
- There's Diablo, man, and there's Crosswords, man.
- Diablo seems pretty easy and boring.
- Crosswords have actually gotten worse, I think.
The last, in the last month,
probably 10 of the Crosswords I've done
have been, one of the words in the crossword have been ass.
And you can tell that they think they're so cute
because they're like, we put ass
in the New York Times crossword.
And it's just, I'm over it, dude.
- That is really pathetic to me.
- They need to let Cameron design crosswords.
He'd be really good at it.
- I think, yeah, I think when we start
our own independent media business,
I think crossword publishing and editing
should be one of our markets that we attack. I think you should do paparazzo.
Me? You should become a paparazzo.
How am I – okay, like go out there and take pictures of people. I don't take a lot of pictures.
No, but I just think that you'd be a funny kind of paparazzi person.
Yeah. Maybe.
You should be trying to get upskirts of people and then when they yell at you,
you say, "Sorry, I thought you were famous."
I thought you were famous.
Sorry, I thought you were a famous celebrity.
I don't think they let you do that.
Have you seen those, like the phones in Japan,
where you can't take a picture without it making the shutter noise? They should give those
to Jubio.
I agree. He does take creep shots.
He always does that. He always does that.
Every time he goes to New York City,
he comes back
and he posts a photo dump somewhere
and I see photos of myself that I never OK'd.
that I never okayed.
- Yep, I never presented.
- You want me to send you,
you want to okay--
- At least Photoshop some hair on my fucking head
if you're gonna post these photos online.
- Here, I haven't really thought about,
I always do a photo dump after a trip,
and I haven't really thought about what I would,
if I was gonna do one,
but I wanna do one,
and the one picture that I'm gonna put of Kelvin
is the one where you're like standing in front of your dog
that's just shitting on the floor.
(laughing)
- Not the floor, the street.
- Have you seen that photo? - No, bro.
- That's my memory of you.
- I mean, to be fair, that is, you know,
a huge chunk of my life.
Is standing there watching an animal
that should be wild, just shit.
- It is funny how big he is
and how small your apartment is.
- Yeah, we thought about moving, but it's too expensive.
So we're just going to torture him.
Yeah, you should be reported as one of those people who put a fish in a tank
that's too small for them.
Well, sometimes there's this dog that we see at the dog park every once in a while
that probably weighs 110 pounds.
And it's like, I don't even know what breed it is,
but there is no living situation in New York City
in which that is not animal cruelty.
Yeah, it was like huge dogs.
It's like the size of a person.
It's the size of, yeah, I mean, I mean, it's it's the weight of a person, but it's the size of two people. It's huge.
Okay.
It's a huge fucking dog.
Yeah. Yeah, those that
You should be able to keep those in the city.
Get the, well, well, well, Juvio's sexism jumps right out.
I didn't know what she was.
It's a girl owner.
Okay.
Well, I didn't know that.
It is a girl owner.
Of course you didn't know that, but you assumed.
And you know what happens when you assume?
I wasn't assuming.
You were. You did assume. You said he should be sent to prison or whatever. You said he.
Guys, there's too much divide in this episode.
We need to come together and say one thing that we love about each other right now.
Okay.
And go.
Caleb.
Oh, I'm starting?
Yeah.
I have to think about it so I need to go all the way around.
I'll start, I'll start. Caleb,
I love how bald you are. And I love that you wear
a different hat every time to cover it up.
I thought we were going to go deep, I thought we were going to dig deep.
Here, I'll go next, I'll go next, I'll go next. Rex,
I love all the quality time that we spend together almost every night.
You're one of the people that I talk to the most and you know just one of my
closest friends and Caleb I really love how you gave me a job.
Getting short shrift here this is not right. Rex you make me laugh more than
than anybody in the world.
You're you have the sweetest smile, the sweetest laugh of anybody.
I love that.
You're always willing to talk about anything.
You're a very open person and you're very empathetic person.
I love that about you.
Jubiel, my little cuddle bear.
I love feeling you.
I love being embraced by you.
When I touch you, it's like almost magical to me.
The quality time that we've been able to spend with each other is,
is something I would trade for the world. Okay.
I consider you part of my family and you're one of my best friends in this
entire universe, in the universe. And, um,
your top five dead or alive, man.
And I'd kill,
I'd kill hundreds and thousands of people for you.
And I need you in my life.
I need you.
- And I'm also not a Joshi.
- I need you.
I need you badly.
- I'm also not your Joshi.
- And you're not my Joshi.
You're not Joshi.
- That's true.
- You're not Joshi.
You're nothing like that.
- Okay, I'm from a different country.
Very funny.
The racism jumped out at the end.
- You said Joshi.
You said that. He did say Joshi. So I don't know if you're talking about Yoshi or if you have some fucked up stupid Mexican character called-
There's a bread mascot named Joshi. Called Joshi? How's that racist?
Some kind of football fucking mascot named Joshi? I don't know anything. Fuck you!
I'm saying all these nice things about you. Go fucking kill yourself. Fuck you.
(laughing)
- Anything to add?
- You look like Bimbo.
- Who's Bimbo? - The bread, the bread mascot.
- The bread, no that's, no, you're dumb.
I don't look like that.
- You do with the yellow shirt,
you do look like the bumblebee from the Simpsons today.
- Okay, so you're both wearing
a white R.A.M. Brothers t-shirts.
You're both the white brothers today.
okay I don't think anyone should be throwing arian around with that mustache
yeah you do a full Hitler mustache your body naturally produces a Hitler
mustache. How does that feel? It only comes in in the Hitler area. That's not true. What is it?
Look at that hand! That's not true! Watch the hand big fella what the fuck was that man?
man. Okay. We need to make sure he never plays basketball. A picture of him
trying to block a shot would be detrimental. No. He's just... He's posted
up, just trying to block like this. Way too low. I'm trying to cover his eyes.
Okay. That's not funny. That's not funny. Alright. Well, I think we ended
Pass me the ball guys.
(laughter)
He's doing it all the time.
Trying to call a time out like that.
Okay, okay.
That's enough.
And goodbye.