and there we go
[sips]
[burps]
You're listening to Beers We Drank, America's #1 beer podcast.
America's #1 beer podcast.
[record scratch]
[music]
What's up, all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[burps]
This is a journey into...
Into into...
Plain and simple.
Bud Light.
Half-Fu Ribbon.
Here's we drank motherfucker with Juvio Caleb and Rex
That was a completely hurt nothing beers we drank
We are we are back do we take a break? No, we didn't
We are back after a one-week hiatus where we took six days off between recording guys
This what I have today is for my sober gophers guys. It's so it's over November
Until Thanksgiving guys, that's what we're doing this month until Thanksgiving and my wife's birthday
We're having no drinks at all except maybe next week. I'll have a beer but just because
Listen, I'm taking some time off of drinking because my stomach is hurting, guys.
I have some kind of stomach disease, I think, or maybe some autoimmune disorder.
It could be Hashimoto's disease, and it could have been why I lost my hair.
I'm looking into the matter.
But for now, I'm here to enjoy a Lagunitas Hoppy Refresher Sparkling Hop Water.
Guys, gophers, this is zero calories.
This is zero carbs.
This has a blue dog that can swim right on the front of the can.
Let's take ourselves a sip and give a review.
Guys, that tastes like Sprite.
And I like Sprite.
This is, on the gopher scale, this is what a gopher is like.
This is 8 burrowing holes out of 10 burrowed holes.
the
are
I don't like not drinking. I'm looking backwards to this to drink this.
But then when I take a sip it actually tastes like soda.
I'll go with my beer next. Yes, go ahead.
I have a Diaco. I'm just kidding. I have a
neon bear hug. Whoa!
We're kind of twinning with mascots here. Yeah. I have a bear and
sunglasses. And this says it has
Can you can is this readable there it is maybe like 10 000 volts of flavor 10 000 volts
man it's gonna shock you and kill you that shit man wait is it false no maybe it's the one that
doesn't kill you maybe it's amps no maybe it's the other way around power is cyclical
okay nerd did you die now i wish you died when you drank that you look like john lennon
We've been over this man. We've been over this shit.
You look like if Adolf Hitler had AIDS.
What the hell is that? That was weak.
That was weak dude. I meant to say the target. AIDS and Hitler.
Come on man. What is it? 2010?
Well, okay. You think AIDS and being
actively disabled in this game? Yeah, go ahead.
Keep saying, keep saying stuff.
watched all of Family Guy in a row now.
Yes.
Okay.
And now I have to go back and watch episodes that I fell asleep during.
And it used to be okay to say stuff like that.
And I sometimes forget that it's not.
You also don't have to do that, by the way.
Well what would I do?
Something else.
You could watch a better television show.
Like what?
Name a better television show.
The news.
Than Family Guy?
Yeah, than Family Guy.
Dude, the office.
The office, the news, the weather.
The office also used to be kind of crazy, man.
Today, I went over to Pat's house and me, him, and Cam, and Alex watched Family Guy,
Most Racist Moments, and The Office, Most Racist Moments.
Which one was more racist?
The Family Guy.
Definitely Family Guy.
The Office had some stuff.
It did have one thing that was really funny where Michael dressed up as Daryl for Halloween,
Obviously didn't do blackface, but he did have one smudge on the side of his neck like he started doing it
I
Had never noticed that before but it was really making me laugh
I don't find the office very funny, but I do find family guy. He dresses up like McGruber
I mean, I only what we okay. We watch the most racist and the hallow all the Halloween moments
All right. I'm gonna I'm gonna come here and cut straight to the cheese. I have never watched either
there you never seen the office man or family guy now you never seen family guy
I've maybe watched an episode or two but like on in a hotel I thought somebody
He does bring up a good point, he said you're gonna cut the cheese.
That means farting!
My beard today is a local beard.
You're gonna cut the cheese?
And I'm talking, I'm gonna get the cheese?
I'm cutting right through the cheese, I'm farting.
You are talking like Peter.
I've never seen that before.
This is a local beard.
This is the beard, they made this at my house, basically.
- Cartablanca?
- Yeah, of course I made it at your house
because it's the Blanca house.
- Damn.
- It is now the most sought out--
- To be a Blanca.
- It is the most sought out after beer in Mexico City,
I've been told by my sources.
- Mm-hmm.
- And-- - Sought out in what way?
- Bought, that's what sought out means.
- They love it and they look at it for it
and they buy it and they drink it most times.
- Well, is it rare to find?
- It's good.
Apparently all the whiteys that moved to Mexico City over COVID, they really like it.
So this is like their drink of choice.
It's the Blanca beer.
It's light.
Give me some notes.
What are you tasting?
It's a really light beer.
It might be even lighter than the White Tecate.
It's really light and it doesn't taste horrible so I give it a 1 million.
- You can't make a fucking--
- I give it a one million.
- Can't make a joke of the rating.
- I've given it a one million.
- Would you, you know what we need guys?
I just realized this.
- Yeah.
- We have never, we always try to describe
what these beers are like and we never make any sense
and we always make a fool of ourselves.
We need a little bit of a lesson.
And so I'm on glacier-design.com/beertasting101.
And so let me, now that I've read this entire thing
very easily in one single look,
now I'm going to taste this again and give it the notes.
- Beertasting, adjusting your beer goggles.
There's goggles?
- Okay guys, this is spring-like, spruce-like,
elegant, grassy,
piney, citrusy,
and zippy.
How to speak to beer.
This article is crazy.
Oh, wait.
Yeah.
This is a soft white beer.
And it's light and it's delicious.
Okay.
I would give it a million out of 10.
You can't, you, you, you realize how that skews every other rating we've ever done
where now this is no, cause me and me and Rex are never, ever going to rate anything
over a 10. Or even a 10. A 10 is crazy.
That's what I'm saying. I'm saying it's outstanding.
So do they give it a... let me rate the beer for you.
8.9. You can't give it a million.
Whoever is keeping track of these on some kind of psychotic
spreadsheet, strike a million from the record.
Strike one million from the record. This is an 8.9.
Two million. You haven't even tasted it. You can't get this in New York City.
No beer is a 10 even.
No beer is a million.
That breaks the scale, man.
Say it right now.
You're right.
I could get that in New York City.
That's not true.
Probably.
You can get anything in this beautiful city where many cultures walk into each other.
Yes, I could do it.
Get a rent under $5,000.
My rent's under $5,000?
Well under.
Well under half, man.
All right, I'm going to fill out my beer evaluation sheet.
So the color-
Okay.
The color is gold, the clarity is dull, it has a good head, it has a middle to faint
aroma with a slightly sweet balance.
The malt, I'm getting a very sweet grain and maybe a nutty aroma.
The hops are very resiny and floral.
It's a neutral impression.
I'm getting a medium intensity flavor.
Slightly sweet, slightly bitter with a bread and nut.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh my.
And so now, what is your rating out of 10?
Did you already say?
You might want to re-evaluate after you've said all these things.
Let's take this shit seriously for fucking once, man.
I would give this like a 7.2.
And that's how you know I'm taking it seriously, is because I'm really just...
It's not even a good score, but it's above average.
Yeah, that's a good score.
That's a decent score.
You, shut up, bitch!
You just gave that beer 2 million.
Yeah.
Fuck you!
Hey, this can, I really do not like the design of this can.
It might be affecting your, it might have affected your initial impression for sure.
Yeah.
It's, it's surprisingly not flavorful despite describing itself as 10,000 volts of flavor.
Mmm, yes.
Well volts are not flavorful.
It's like hops.
Yeah, yeah, I don't think volts would taste like all that much.
You don't get shocked and you go like, "That was really good."
You have to have been shocked.
I got another one of those. I almost got shocked last night.
Two nights ago actually.
You ever get shocked and you can't move at all?
That almost happened to me, yeah.
That happened to me one time.
Cause my dad didn't put the...
When I was like maybe 13,
I had no idea how electric outlets worked.
And my dad never put a faceplate on one of the electric outlets
and it just hung out of the wall.
And I grabbed the back of it to plug in my computer.
And I just went...
I just sat there for like five seconds.
and I kinda liked it.
It kinda felt a little bit good.
- So it was flavorful then?
- Yeah, no, wait, it was, yeah, yeah, no,
the tongue feel was definitely interesting.
- Okay.
- Oh yeah, I didn't talk about its full body mouth feel
with a lively carbonation
and a slick and astringent mouth coating
while being slightly prickly
with a long finish and a short intensity
and a bitter balance.
- Yum.
- And excellent craftsmanship.
- Okay, I'm starting to see why we don't do this every week.
- Yeah, it's horrible.
- This is really light and it's really so delicious to drink.
- Sam Hagenfried has been found, say it.
- Guilty on all seven counts.
- Is that true?
I actually didn't know.
- Okay, let's get into this.
Number one.
- You were innocent?
- Yeah, dude, why is it?
I don't give a fuck about financial crime.
Nobody should go to prison for stealing money.
- Thank you, thank you.
- The only thing that should get you in prison
is bodily harm.
- Yes.
Financial crimes are awesome.
I mean, if you get away with them,
even from the beginning, if you get away with them,
you should be just, you should have to stop doing it,
I think, but you shouldn't go to jail.
That's absurd.
- I have never read, 'cause here's the thing.
New York is the court of law for financial crimes.
They give out the statements every time.
And they're always like, they stole $200 million, they bought a McLaren, they bought a mansion,
they took a bunch of flights on private jets, and I'm like, these guys are awesome.
This is what everyone should do.
Have they never seen the movie, have they never seen Blank Check?
You remember this movie?
They think that kid should be on Rikers Island, reading the Quran in an orange jumpsuit?
That's what they think should happen to that child.
just because he had the guts to steal millions of dollars from a man.
Yeah. Wait, did he even do any, any of that? Like cool shit.
I thought it was just like,
it would just like lock himself up in like in his apartment and just played league
SPF. That's cool.
He literally bought like a skyscraper in the Bahamas and had orgies in it and
took amphetamine,
like experimental uppers that cost $2,000 a patch.
I didn't know he was doing patches.
Yeah.
He had some experimental drug that he took as a patch and it costs like $2,000.
No, he.
No, he was fucked up.
Um, all the time.
That's why, and he was awful at league, which is why he was cringe.
Did you see the picture of him from the court?
Like the drawing where he literally looks like the most handsome man on earth.
Yeah.
They drew him to be like the chat meme basically.
He straight up looks and there's like another one from that day where he literally looks like a rat
I'm more inclined to believe the handsome one. Yes
There's like there's a because the thing is anytime someone gets a piece of financial crime, they're just like
the coolest guy of all
It looks sick
He literally looks like Brad Pitt from Fight Club, it looks amazing he looks
gorgeous
It shouldn't be allowed to look that you there's they're saying this guy needs to go to prison
and look at how good looking he is, well dressed.
Look at all these schlubs in the back who are all wearing the same clothes and have no face.
These people should be in jail.
Look at these, see this is actually amazing, this is an amazing, amazing photo, and this
is a photo by the way, because here it is, Sam Bankman Freed, this is exactly what his
life is.
He's the main character, he looks amazing, he has amazing sex with the most beautiful
women you've ever seen.
In the back, all NPCs.
NPCs that just need to be robbed, I mean, they need to be robbed like in Skyrim when
and you take gold off of the counter,
and they say, "Ah, what are you doing, man?"
That's what he was doing.
There's nothing wrong with anything he did.
- Why are we still doing the little drawings at this point?
- Just take photos, I don't understand.
- Yeah, I don't understand.
- What's the archaic rule?
- Who's like, it's big drawings being like,
we need to lobby that we should still be doing drawings
instead of taking pictures.
- It is, it's these fucking artists.
- Someone has to say it.
- We should give that to an AI.
Artists run the government and the banks.
- That is true.
I hate those damn artists.
- That's real shit.
Okay, so Rex, what do you think would have been,
because you're tapped into this whole thing.
What would you think would have been an appropriate,
fair, long arm of the law style justice
against Mr. Sam Bankman-Freed
for the crimes that he's committed?
I think he should be in solitary confinement, but like Norwegian style.
Okay.
You know, he's got like-
Ping pong.
Half a ping pong table where it's flipped up here.
He's got a computer that can only play League of Legends, he can only play ranked games,
and his teammates are always throwing.
You know what it should be?
If he hits-
And he has to do that for 25 straight years.
If he hits challenger, he gets out of jail.
Yes.
That's crazy.
He's able to 1v5 solo carry a league ranked game.
If he hits challenger he gets the fuck out of it.
He can have all the hatch drugs he needs, all the caffeine he needs.
And if he loses they throw a tomato at him.
Yeah.
Splatters it and it gets all in his...
And that's the only food he can have is the tomatoes.
Every time he loses he gets pelted with fruit.
One tomato thrown into this, or one food of whatever.
Okay, that's actually a good, this is a good punishment.
You can eat whatever gets thrown at you, but you get to choose the food.
So this guy's only eating soft foods.
He's going to be eating marshmallows for every meal.
Because nobody's going to order a T-bone steak if they have to have it thrown at their head
by like a MLB pitcher.
Right.
So he's going to be eating not that well, unless every once in a while maybe he'll decide
to take a maybe like a like a crustini or something to the face to see if that I
would take a steak to the head probably what would you do no I don't think you
want that would you eat a steak that hit your head yeah your head is disgusting
now my head's clean I think I look at this I wouldn't like to this literally
looks like the happy merchant racist pull me. Also this guy on the right what's his deal
the security guard. Yeah like this is bullshit. Destroying shit has to be outlawed. We need
to put every artist in jail. It's so funny. That is not right. Someone's job is to capture
pivotal moments in a court case by sketch.
And just try so hard to not be racist.
There was only a picture that they could take, a snapshot of a moment in time.
Some sort of device that was able to capture accurately reality from one moment.
I think at this point we're too far gone.
Let's do away with the drawings.
Let's not even do pictures.
Let's have it all be on TikTok live.
Yeah.
Okay.
And the accuser has to be like NPC.
Yes.
At the end.
Yeah.
Your honor, my defendant, ice cream so good.
Ice cream so good.
Yummy.
I think that's a good idea.
I was talking about this yesterday.
I would do so good in white collar prison.
Why would you do? I don't think you can do good or bad. I mean, it's just it's just chill
It is shit. I would be listen
I would be telling all the like guys that have been in there since 2008. I would be hanging out with birdie Manoff
If he was still alive
I would be telling them about all the types of scams they can run when they come out and they would treat me as a god
You sucked
Now they've made like there's another way. Yeah, you're small fucking potatoes, but they would think why would I have they would think you were
So what I do?
Would think you were new Jack dude, you'd show up and you'd be like, yeah, I still I embezzled a hundred thousand dollars
Clean it's from crypto and they say first of all, what the fuck is crypto man. I've been here 15 years
I don't know what the hell you're on about
Number two a thousand dollar hundred thousand dollars is nothing to me
That's poop to me if I fucking chose to actually commit financial crimes, which I haven't
The option is there I could do it. I would be amazing at it, but I have
You think it'd be amazing at it, what does that mean you think you can get away with it
Do you know how smart I am?
Do you know how I know?
You are and that makes me think that you would not be very good
(laughing)
- But what was the one thing, this one time I remember,
he like called me or like messaged me
like fucking like five in the morning.
He was like, "Hey."
And I was like, "What do you want?"
Like I saw it like hours later,
I was like, "What is your problem?"
And I was like, "Oh, I saw that the episode got posted
"for the podcast, so I thought you were up."
I was like, "I don't hit posts at five in the morning
"every single day, I schedule those."
So you know--
- He's the most technologically literate man on earth.
I messaged you while you were away from the computer.
At 5 in the morning.
Something that's never happened.
Okay, I didn't think you were awake.
I just messaged you.
This is it.
Well you did say, I thought you were awake.
You're on a T-sline.
Well his dick is awake.
He's on discord.
It's also my, it's my time.
Please.
I leave my computer on sometimes.
I schedule the episodes.
And you message me at 5 in the morning.
Hey, are you awake?
I just saw you posted the episode.
I saw the episode get posted and you were green on Discord.
I think that you would be, Rex, I believe that you would be pretty good, maybe great, at stealing
the money.
I think that you might be the worst at covering your tracks of anybody in the universe.
Yeah, and that's why I wouldn't do it.
I think you would open up the-
I would let the record show that I do not do financial crimes.
You would turn on your webcam to record this podcast and there would be $50 million stacked
up behind you.
In coins.
Yeah, in coins, overflowing out of mugs.
There would be-
You would look in my little 8x10 office and it would be turned into a Scrooge McDuck style
swimming pool of enemies.
Yes.
Just a poor website with a money sign on it.
Yeah.
It would be really bad, I think.
I think you'd be really, really bad at that part.
You'd get caught almost immediately.
Well, that's the thing.
You cannot get away with financial crimes.
It will eventually catch up to you.
I think the only one that works is if you do one of those crazy crypto hacks and then you
just disappear.
You pay to be disappeared.
I think you could do it.
I think you could get away with that shit.
You can't.
I am telling you.
How do they find you?
It's impossible to turn it into real money.
Not if you know some guy who does that.
No, there's no one who does that.
literally feds all the way down. It's impossible to get away with financial crimes. It's harder
to get away with financial crimes in crypto than it is in real money.
Do you think it's easier to rob a bank than get away with a crypto crime of an equal amount,
say you're stealing $500,000?
It'll take longer, but if you get away with a bank heist and you get home and you do the
money and you do what you need to do, the heat will be off of you, you'll be fine.
You're gonna fuck the money what are you saying? Well like, you know wash the money
Like
Cleaning business and you know legalize the money that way but like after like a month you're good
You know with a crypto crime there. They'll catch you like two years later and throw you a check. I
Guess you're right is the I know
Is that an official like an official thing like after a month they're like, all right, we're gonna stop looking now pretty much
I mean there is a statute of limitations on gta type type shit robbing a bank right there has to be yeah
Well, it's like the once the trail it's like murder once the trail goes cold
It's hard to reopen like most cold cases don't get solved. So if you get away
It's pretty much done
my buddy gus who i'm uh
doing a two shows with in Los Angeles on November 17th everybody go check out the tickets for that
there won't be a link for it there will completely be a link i forgot to put the link on the previous
episode i just okay you're ruining you're ruining my entire life anyway my buddy Gus his entire family
is from Charlestown Massachusetts that's where uh the town is that movie takes place it's all
bankrupt he's opening a second one oh my god he loves this beer so much i've never seen him do
do that before 30 minutes. That might actually be a two million. His uncles were all like
bank robbers and his mom was sitting on the couch when she was a kid with her mom and
they were watching the news and the news was like, "Another bank robbery in Charlestown
today. The suspect has been described as 5'11" and wearing a red tracksuit." And like right
as they said that, his uncle ran in the front door wearing a red tracksuit and a big bag
of money.
That's like the beginning to a slot bonus.
And Gus's grandma was like, "Get the fuck out of my house, I never want to see you again."
And he ran and he went to Florida and he died.
Well how did he, did he die?
Of old age.
Died of old age.
the
50 years ago, I can't believe that not everybody was doing
stuff like bank robberies.
- I think you would die a lot.
- I think you, it was too much effort.
It's still too much effort.
It's always been too much effort to grow a bank.
How would you do it?
Do it.
- Back in the day?
- Yeah, you are in the '80s.
Back in the day.
- I'm in the 1980s.
I would walk into the bank dressed as,
like Metal Gear Solid, I would be a walking trash can
or a traffic cone.
And I would just slowly waddle, every couple hours,
I would waddle like another couple of feet.
I'd be in there for days just waddling.
Just barely moving, just inching ever so forward.
- Inching out of everyone's vision cone?
- Yeah, exactly.
And then I would open up the vault
and I'd get all the money.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- And how do you leave?
- Just start inching my way back.
All right, and they would be like,
oh my God, the money's gone!
Wait, we got robbed!
Wait, where is the bastard?
The last place you're gonna look
is the trash can or the traffic cone.
- That is true.
- That's been moving-- - Just saying, you guys.
- To the bank for a month.
- Just saying, guys.
Or I dress up like a guy, like a Brinks truck,
and I show up, and I say,
"Yeah, we gotta make a...
"We gotta deliver this shit to a Chinese restaurant down the street."
"How are you gonna dress up as a Brinks truck?"
"You need the truck first, first of all."
"I just get... I get an ice cream truck, I paint it grey."
"Yep."
"This is easy."
"People don't know that... Yeah, spray paint the ice cream truck."
"I show up, I'm wearing my Sunday best."
"I'm probably wearing this shirt."
"And I say, 'Listen guys, I'm gonna need...
$100 because I have to deliver it to people down the street.
They're not going to say no. They're not going to be like, Oh, what's, what,
what's your badge number? It's a hundred bucks. Yeah.
And I'll do that like a thousand times. I'll make a hundred grand. Okay.
Here's the thing. And this is, this is true for any financial crime.
Any financial crime puts you in jail for 25 years.
So you need to make a million dollars per year for it to be worth it
per year of prison.
And you have to do it when you're real...
See, the thing is, if you rob $25 million when you're one year old,
you get out in your mid-20s, you're having the most amazing mid-20s ever.
You just hide the money real well.
Yeah.
I, uh...
Crime is...
Financial crimes are just one of those things where it's like,
if you're really good at it, you can make so much money.
That's what I would do, man.
Yeah.
I would...
There's another guys that got arrested for financial crimes.
The people are saying is that one account, the like...
Yeah, I saw that.
And it's like what they did is they just opened up a thousand brokerage accounts
and then did like a fast transfer of $5,000
and then like buy some like random stock or like stock option
and then buy the reverse of it on a different account
And then just lose $5,000 and then it just never like the transfer never comes through and they did that like a thousand
And they made like two million dollars. They made like nothing
And they're going to jail for 25 years
Here's what I would do. That's like how much you would make if you worked at mcdonald's for no, it's not the money
It's just the the twitter guy the the craziest moments in new metal history
Yeah, I would do that something like that something really simple
but I would have a
child a daughter because they go easier on daughters on true women and I would
say the baby did it penned it on the baby no and then the baby again baby goes to
jail for 25 years I visit charge the baby as a kid so it goes to you know who
tried that the guy who came up with the first like hack for slot machines like
physical slot machine. He said a baby did it? He like hinted on his like 14 year old daughter.
I can't believe someone's actually tried the baby did it. Yeah no he did it on like like a young
girl like his young girl daughter. And it worked right? Uh no it did not. Really? Yeah. Why?
Because it was obviously that it was him. Yeah. They put his whole family in jail. It works with
the
a
Think it might work. Yeah, I think every time has ever that's ever been possible to do is has already been done
I think I think the crime industry is stale
I think that you are ripe to be framed for a crime because again, you don't do that much during the day. Not that many
Excuses not not many alibis have been created
Alibis, I've got my most of my day is tracked in some sort of database
uh... on either open you do you or
lol chest dot
dot com
you know fortunately
so i've got a good i got out of ice
and how allies
i do you think you could pin a murder on the baby
all like a
the baby was running around with a gun
didn't realize it was i think you can get charged for that
It's probably less than if you actually murdered someone.
Uhhhh...
I guess.
I think it depends on the murder weapon.
Sledgehammer? No way.
Well, like, what if it was like a knife and your wife fell on the baby,
almost crushing the baby and the knife, and it just so happened to slide perfectly?
And it's her fault.
Exactly!
Yeah, you had nothing to do with it.
Right.
What, I'm not supposed to...
Who's trying to teach the baby to cook?
...stop my wife from using a knife?
Yeah.
what if you do the thing where you
to gather this baby's hand you grab the knife with the baby's hand and the you
that's what i'm saying
uh...
uh... yeah it was him that it was the airplane
yeah yeah four thousand times you know you know what you're on monday you man
but uh... i
what the hell
that's the baby goes to jail
one-year
i think i would be fine to the bayside you remember jail
also again they probably won't put it in what if there was a baby jail
i mean i've been saying this for a very long time there should be because that's
what when whenever kids are uh... you know me i don't believe in abortion i
think that this is murder so i think of the all children should be born and then
put directly in jail
okay
you know they they're birthed and then to just directly to jail get out of my site
don't need to see it what if i do think it's going to uh...
- What if they do like the pet adoption thing with babies?
And it's like, all right, every baby goes into a thing
and they have to get adopted
and you gotta pay 60 bucks for them.
And you get like a kit.
- That's what it is, that's already what they do.
- That's not what they do.
- Yeah.
- Imagine a one year old with a swastika forehead tattoo.
- Yeah, see, I mean, again,
I don't give a fuck about these babies who are unwanted.
- You don't give a fuck about these babies?
- No, I'm putting my hand off screen.
I don't give a fuck about these babies that are,
see
no no and thing like that
if the baby it listen i don't i think it shouldn't be
uh... religiously murdered
that the met style in an operating room at uh... uh...
play what i call that complain genocides that's what i call
i do think that these babies don't matter at all and they should be put in
some kind of
correctional facility.
'Cause what's the problem with unwanted children?
What's the big problem with it?
They all turn out to be drug addicts and drug dealers.
- Right.
- If a baby's unwanted, they grow up
and they become despicable crime people.
- Despicable Me grew.
- Despicable Me grew, grew was supposed to be, yeah.
He was an unwanted pregnancy.
- Right. - So,
just put 'em in there early.
They're gonna end up there anyway, man.
Just get that baby in jail, let's forget about it.
- I think this is making a lot of sense to me.
What?
- This country should be 40% jail.
- I agree, what are we at, like 10% right now?
- Yeah.
- These would be way higher.
- Let's bump those numbers up.
- I don't think that they would put me in jail
just for being not white.
And that's not right.
- Okay, but you are white.
- That's not right.
- I think that-- - Every time I get
racially profiled--
- Every time I go through TSA,
They're like, "Yo, search him."
- I don't think that's ever happened to you.
- I got randomly searched every single time at TSA.
- Here's what I think.
- Where are you going?
Where are you going, kid?
- They're just asking you a question to be nice
and you're taking it.
- No.
- Also, for the record,
your two interactions with the police,
you were so nice to them that you invited them inside.
- Wow.
- For no reason to just hang out with them.
- They were profiling me, bro.
They were profiling me and I was like, "Yes!"
I was in my house, they were probably making time out of my house
They came all the way out of the-
is it airbnb and you let them in you're not supposed to let them in dude they
have a vampire law they call it that you don't have to let them in if a cop shows
up and says i need i need sugar for a cake that i'm baking you don't have to
let them in bro he literally it's like the two minutes i leave the house i
leave him alone the cops come because they know me it's a long-haired
degenerate on himself yeah he called them up to ask what they were doing said
he was home alone and the cop over
what's your emergency?
I'm Mexican and they showed up
yeah and
now you got some poor landlord in trouble
yeah
just because he had a poison house
still in trouble by the way
yeah he still has that that fucking thing
is still hanging up in the
you literally ruined that guy's life
they completely banned airbnbs off at New York City
and some people are saying
it's not because of me
because of you, you ruined everybody's trip
literally because of you
It is 100% your fault.
It's unreal, man.
You literally let them in for no reason.
Because you can't say no to a cop.
I'm actually busy, can you come back later?
It's just my southern hospitality, man.
You are southern.
Southern of the border.
What can I say?
I was just too nice.
I just can't hate.
I don't have a single hate particle in my society.
Here's what I would have said.
Knock on the door.
the
for
they'd be out of there, dude.
They would be running away from me, bro.
I'm a walk-in lawsuit.
I'm a liability to these cops.
- Right.
- They do not wanna see me.
- You and Julio are the polar opposites
of dealing with the police.
You trolled the Boston FBI by playing Kevin Rudolph
and Juvio invited them inside
and asked if they needed water or lemonade.
- I'm not a troll.
I'm not a troll.
I post on Facebook.
I go, "Hey, guys." - "Do you have food?"
This is what I have for breakfast.
This is my life, my awesome life.
I don't troll, I don't post jokes.
- What can I say, bro?
I'm a fucking troll to the death of me, bro.
My DNA, if you zoom into it,
it would literally be troll faces.
That's the level of troll that I am, okay?
And so even more so than being at all political,
I don't care about what the cops do,
it's none of my business.
But I see, they walk around and I see marks,
I see perfect green victims that I could just destroy.
And what do you troll at the top of the street?
I'd say, "Oh, uh, police officer, police officer, there's a bomb in my hand.
Oh my god, there's a bomb!"
They'd say, "Oh my god!"
It's counting down, "5, 4, 3, 2..."
Oh, but it says you actually have a bomb.
I have a bomb.
I'd say, "Oh, there's a bomb!
There's a bomb in my hand!"
And they're freaking out, they're pulling their gun on me, and I say, "I don't know how to
turn it off!"
"5, 4, 3, 2, 1, beep, beep, beep!"
And then it goes
We're the strangers to love and I sit there and I dance that shit I twerk on the cop car which I think is okay
That's what I would have done man
That's what I would do I would do that shit
Don't give a fuck if I get shot that's part of the trolling
Exactly
Straight up. They wouldn't shoot me man. They would say my bald brother. How did you get off the force?
Mm-hmm. Are you a plainclothes officer? I would say yeah, dude, and I have this bomb
But you're gonna have to take this shit off my hands. I was gonna want this bomb anymore
Homeless black guy on the train and he kept looking at me and calling me an undercover cop and I was like in what world
Do I look like an undercover cop? I should be kind of short Jewish
Wait, do you think have you?
It's since you you've got the glasses. Do you think you've getting more negative interactions with strangers?
You're I don't wear them outside. It seems that as you are
Why not because it looks stupid no
I don't. I'm gonna lose you.
That's hurtful!
I spent so much money on these!
They don't look stupid.
I was just asking if that's why, because maybe you think they look stupid.
I think they look amazing!
I think you look like a rockstar from the 70s or 80s.
I think you do!
You look like an artist, dude.
You don't look stupid at all.
I wear them so that I can look at the computer better.
You don't look like a substitute teacher at a Quaker school even a little bit to me man.
I think that these are cool glasses, you need to wear them outside more.
You need to gain a little confidence.
You need to wear them outside more and see what happens.
Why would I wear them outside?
What am I looking at outside?
The world?
The beauty of the world?
I don't need to see that well outside.
I'm not driving.
You bet you're walking.
Yeah, but I can see perfectly fine now.
I could come up behind you and kill you and the glasses would do nothing how it
is you would see them if somebody tried to tried to stab you in the eye the
glasses would block it Wow now you feel like a stupid asshole don't you feel
like it's stupid do you know and scan everything around you every single time
the only time I wore them out was for Halloween and you were dressed up as
Peter Griffin when I was dressed up as Peter Griffin. Do you have a picture? No
It was a pretty weak costume. It was definitely a thrown together. What's in the
Was it a better or worse Peter Griffin than Mike's that one day?
It was worse Mike Mike dresses like Peter Griffin all the time
I cut up to a Airbnb this one like the first time I ever met him
You know your shows up to our Airbnb and I go like oh my I walk outside. I look at him like oh my god
He's so tall. Hello. Hi Mike. Nice to meet you come and send her poison Airbnb
He comes inside he's just hanging out with us and then Rex just like looks at him once and he's like
Like look this is you
Yeah, it's really sad. That's like in Peter Griffin man. The problem is that I don't own a white button-down shirt
Just straight up. That's a
Essential men's wardrobe man. It's not either. No one owns that I have one is exactly what he looked like. Yeah
Like literally exactly what he looked like, yeah
I thought about shaving and kind of drawing the balls on my chin
Why do you do that?
I was lazy
No, that would mean good. Yeah
Wait, Halloween update. Where's your drink? Halloween update. What are you drinking?
Okay, hold on. I have to get another hoppy refresher. Hold on.
So...
You give me your Halloween update then.
I didn't do anything on Halloween night, but on Saturday...
We went to a party at Patch's house.
Okay.
And it was lit AF.
*burp*
uh...
and i
mhm
took too many sins and throughout
he did in the in the middle of talking to me and and tommy bayer
he he he was a little bit and then what
and i had he erection behind me so i didn't really knows going on and tommy
was telling a story
and he's like you had in this
did you just throw up no yes if i spit
Oh, he said, "Did you just spit?"
Yeah, "Did you just spit?"
And you said, "Yes."
No, you said, "No, I threw up."
Yeah.
And, uh, it was really, really making us laugh.
And you looked psychotically happy.
It was like the happiest I've ever seen you be.
I felt so much better after throwing up.
You threw up in the middle of a conversation and then just went right back to it.
So, okay, for reference, we were outside sitting on a bench and behind the bench was like staggered
bushes and so I was sitting behind Caleb Tommy was sitting in front of Caleb mm-hmm
and in the middle of that I leaned over threw up once leaned back and then just
one back over and threw up again quite a bit. You one tapped the puke? No no I had to
double tap it and really it was a triple tap because the second time was longer
and Tommy because of how he was sitting he just saw me lean over and something
maybe come out of my mouth a little bit or just like you know the impression
that I had spit and he's like well what did you just do I was like oh I threw up
and then Rex acted like we were making a big deal out of it I mean you were it
wasn't a big deal at all. You threw up in the middle of a conversation! Go to the bathroom!
Is this your first time talking to Tommy?
Yeah, it was the first time.
He met him 20 minutes into the meeting and he threw up twice.
Yeah.
And acted like nothing happened.
I think it would make a big deal if I was there.
I would be like, "Whoa, what the fuck? Are you okay, man?"
No one saw it except for Brian and Tommy.
And Caleb.
No, Caleb didn't see it.
My back was to him.
I knew that he had had a recent string of throwing up.
Yeah, it just felt great to get it out.
I felt horrible in the lead up to the throw up, and then throwing up made me feel great.
And then I felt, I was still kind of drunk.
I had nicotine in my body.
I felt good.
It got you to the perfect cross section of every intoxicant.
Yeah, exactly.
And then I ate Taco Bell later and I felt literally perfect.
I love Taco Bell.
Dude, what are we doing for Drinksgiving?
Oh my god.
Drinksgiving!
Guys, guys, official update.
We gotta do some kind of pumpkin ale.
Drinksgiving we are doing a big IRL recording.
It's gonna be the three of us.
It's gonna be Alex.
It's gonna be Noah maybe.
It's gonna be Brian maybe.
And that's it maybe.
everyone will be what we're gonna have to do is we're gonna have to get like an
analog for every popular Thanksgiving food mmm we'll have to get the beer
version like the turkey beer all of this we're gonna have to get all of them and
you're going to have to make a plate just like you would at a normal
Thanksgiving and I have a strong feeling what some people's will look like but
you're gonna have to do yeah one of each of one serving of each of these beers
and
I think this is a good idea. We're gonna do yeah, honey glazed ham beer green bean casserole beer pumpkin pie mashed potatoes turkey
We'll figure it out once we go to the beer store, but I'm sure that they have all those there
Those are just Joan's soda flavors. I don't know what we would do for beer
we will
Spike them we will find something. I'm feeling pretty confident or we'll have Noah make mixology style
Something that tastes like each of them. I think Noah could easily poison us and we could just have the most fucked up episode of all time
That's fine by me man. That's fine by me now that I'm doing I mean listen
I really miss now that I'm doing this sober gopher stint and
My gophers know this when I am NOT doing a gopher episode. I like that the episode gets slowly worse
Because as we as we get more drunk and more drunk right that that's better
Than it being kind of just evenly good the entire way
I like when it starts the first 15 minutes we come out come out blazing right?
I mean the first beer is done. I'm starting to feel sick to my stomach. I hate shit so much
Can't believe I do a beer podcast. It's complete. It's literal poison. Yeah, and then
You know
on fries and everything.
Yeah, poutine based on...
The slip ups that come out...
The slip ups that come out are...
are...
I miss that.
There's no way that you cannot get a single thing of poutine in the entirety of New York.
You can.
We'll get you poutine when you come here.
Don't even worry about it.
You wanted it, not me.
I like poutine, we'll get you some. Don't worry about it.
I don't want any of it.
I told Kale of this, I wanted to show you Rex.
I saw this video of this girl who went to follow the show
Touch a subject. I saw that video. Yeah, and she was there for fucking eight hours hours
Yeah, and they gave it to her for free. They come through from her meal what yeah
They have a time limit at Fogo
She hours she stayed the entire day. Yeah, they didn't take those from 2:30 to 530 for lunch to dinner
I don't think it was the New York City photo to tell there was another one. Yeah
Yeah, I think this was a different Fogo de Chao and she's a famous all-you-can-eat TikToker.
She have a big mouth?
I don't know about that.
I guess, yeah.
She doesn't look like she's way too happy about eating the food?
No, no, that's a different person you're thinking.
Oh, okay.
This is some random woman I'd never seen before.
Alright.
But apparently the chefs knew who she was.
she was, they brought out like a lobster tail for her in the middle of her meal.
And then at the end she tried to sell her bill and they were like, no,
we come to you. Thanks for coming.
Dude. Wow. This is what I'm saying. This and also the, uh,
I know you guys are not tuned in. I wish Patrick was here to, to see,
to see this. I hope he's listening. The Keith Lee thing in Atlanta. He just,
he went in, he went to Atlanta. He made a whole mess for my,
about my thing, two restaurants, but everybody loves him.
And he just goes to restaurants.
- Who's Keith Lee?
- He is a TikTok restaurant reviewer.
We need to become food reviewers.
We need to go to restaurants, eat the food,
and go on social media and be like,
"It's mad," and do that to every single restaurant.
Go to McDonald's, this burger is mad,
and we'll be so rich and so popular,
and every single restaurant will respect us crazy,
crazy style.
Holy shit. This is my idea
Keith Lee
It's on CNN Keith Lee tried to review some Atlanta restaurants on tick-tock all hell broke loose
This is what I'm saying. It was literally news Christ. We can do this
We please take food reviews expose Atlanta's odd dining rules, yep
This is national news is on The Washington Post. We can do this. Mikhail Klementov wrote this article really
(laughing)
- Yeah, Keith Lee praised by fans
for his honest, humble food reviews.
This is Mike's words.
Echoed residents distaste for $1 butter,
odd dining rules, and lack of go-to ordering.
- By the way, this is the writer of that article.
This is Mikhail Klementov right here on your screens,
dressed as Peter Griffin,
in front of a picture of a Peter Griffin.
- And then now he's covering this whole Keith Lee drama.
- That's crazy. - That is true.
- Well, that's interesting.
Yeah, I mean, I would love to, I will say,
I think I would be a little bit insulted
if I went into a restaurant and the chefs recognized me.
That would make me feel fat.
No, it's more of a fame thing.
Yeah, I know.
That would make me feel really fat
if chefs were like, we know who you are,
we know how much you love food, here's a bunch of food.
I'd go, hmm, what about me is telegraphing
that I love food so much?
I've never made a food TikTok in my life.
What? No. What?
That makes no sense.
The gluttony theme just plays when you walk in.
Yeah.
Give me another bowl!
Okay.
Just give me some sandwiches!
And any kind of other dishes. Is that what it is?
I've tried to figure out what he's saying for the past day and a half and I can't.
Yeah, we need somebody to be doing... we need a Rap Genius, a Genius.com, like, lyrics,
deconstructed video for all the No Limit City Slot music.
Yeah, I was listening to the, first of all, the Rock Bottom music.
There's a song that plays when you get a max win.
And then the Remember Gulag Extended mixes.
They have an extended one?
Oh, yeah. Oh my god. You just listen to this on your own time. Just like on your youtube music
Yeah, yeah, they're good songs, man. They're good. Really good songs
I think that they should be definitely up for there should be a best slot music grammy award
Yeah, no, it's honestly it's really good music
I think about the lyrics to gluttony to the super size me, baby
Super size me, baby
Yeah, we have to gamble tonight. Yeah, we do we have to we have it's it's said and it's done. It's going to happen
I thought that you know, I had an idea. Is there any can you show nudity on kick calm? I believe so I
think it's
No, you really can't is there any website like that where you just straight-up show?
Completely nudity
I guess we could do porn up
I want to do a live stream like money or movie Monday style thing where we watch that that naked dating show
Hmm. Okay, I was talking to my wife about it last night and I and she was like, she's like, oh we can watch that
I was like that shows for girls and then I talked about
When I watched one episode of it and I talked about every guy's cock and I remembered their cock and balls
Yeah, it's like yeah, it really sounds like it's for girls
*laughter*
BOOM!
I was like, okay, first of all, bitch.
Second of all, we have to watch this on some kind of stream.
This is a great idea.
Because it is for guys.
She changed my mind.
This is a show for guys.
It is.
I guess we could try doing it on a game.
Here's the thing.
As a man married to a woman, you know that if you remembered anything about the woman's
vaginas or breasts, you would be in trouble.
I'd be in jail.
So you lock on to the cocks.
I literally didn't even pay attention when the women were on.
Wait, what is this?
Can you go over what the show is?
Sure.
It's a show...
You explain it.
So it starts, they introduce a loser, a person who is actually retarded.
They're British.
It's a British show.
So let's start with that.
They've got fucked up teeth.
They've got a weird life.
They're really off-putting socially.
And they talk about how they haven't been on a date in three years and their life sucks
and they hope to find love on the naked dating show.
And so they come in and they get introduced and then there are six colored pods in front
of them.
And in front of the pods is like a kind of a screen, if you will.
And so it starts and the screen comes up to just above the genital area.
So the only thing you can see of six people is their like either dick or pussy, their
ass, their legs and their feet.
And so like the other stuff, yeah.
So there was one autistic guy that was like, those feet are disgusting.
Get this bitch out of here.
This is on TV.
You can see the whole thing.
There's seasons of it on max.
It has 10 real seasons and six of them are on HBO right now.
So then they kick one off based solely on genitals and they interview the person.
There's always like a after interview where they have the person talk and they're always
like yeah I feel really good you know I feel really confident in myself and despite the
fact that someone took one look at their dick and said no.
Yeah it is brutal man.
Yeah so then and then if it's like the women they're like if it's women in the boxes they're
like yeah show us your your pussy and asshole and then they ask about like
pubic hair and the guys were like I had a bad experience with pubic hair so I
don't like it. Then the next step is it goes up to like here so it shows like
shoulders, breasts, everything but the head, mid torso, everything but the head.
Right. And then you know if it's women it's like oh that one she's so
interesting looking but I think she might be a little too curvy for me is
Something they might say to be nice if it's the women they're like he looks
Lanky and skinny that's not for me and get him the fuck out of here
The women are really harsh and the men are like overly nice
And then it goes and it shows they're like faces and they all look British as fuck. None of them are that good-looking
the only people are the the guys who are like
Immigrants from another country who live now live in the UK. Those are the only good-looking people in the entire show
Everybody else, everybody from the UK are disgusting pigs.
Yeah.
So then, now looking at their whole body, whole naked body, they kick another person off.
So they settle it down to three.
Now, sometimes they'll get someone who's like bisexual.
So by now they've completely eliminated the opposite gender that they don't care about.
Whatever, whether, if it's a bi woman, they've either kicked off all the men or all the women.
If there's a trans person, which it does happen, the trans person is always still in because they need to appear that they're considering it, but it will never actually be the final choice.
And then, you know, just all the good things about it.
Finally, down to three, they get to talk.
So they ask a question. They say, "What don't you like about your body?"
And if it's the women, they're like, "Oh, you know, I feel like my breasts aren't big enough, my arms are kind of flabby, my feet are weird."
So I have a question.
Sure.
Is the chooser also naked?
By the last stage they are.
I'm getting to this.
So they're fully clothed right now and then having answered this question they hear their
voice and a lot of times they're like, "Yeah, he sounds like he's from Northampton Shire.
I'm not really a fan of that accent."
Kick him off.
Right.
So now it's the turn where they send the picker back and they come back out naked and they
walk and while they're waiting for the picker to come back out they have the
two contestants usually two men right kind of look at each other waiting
silently while their dicks are out and they go what do you think about his body
and they kind of you know and like sometimes it'll be like a thin white guy
next to a huge black guy to be like guy his cock is the size of my arm you know
like fucking bullshit like that it's really awesome or like one time there's
a big buff guy in like a little twink and the buff guy is like yeah he looks like
he's really agile. Very kind thing to say. Yeah exactly they're always really nice to
each other and then finally they narrow it down and then they pick one and
then they go on the worst date of all time at 9 a.m. the next day. Yeah. So then they show
like a conversation and then it shows them like two weeks to a month later and
of course the relationship has completely fallen apart they're forced
to sit on a couch and answer like how it went and at best they're like yeah we've
texted a few times it's because this is the opposite they do the opposite of how
you're supposed to see people right supposed to see face and then next step
is you're supposed to see their naked torso and then only then should you be
seeing people's the naughty parts of their body that I don't want to talk
about. That is how it should be. That is why we invented clothing. It literally
never works. My favorite is when one of the guys is like too good-looking for
the girl and then it's always she's just like yeah he didn't call me after we had
sex on the first date. It's awesome. It's a great show and we have to watch it together.
It is literally the perfect TV show.
Sounds thrilling.
I think you'd really like it.
We can do like a, we can watch a couple episodes
and some sort of stream
or somewhere not on Twitch.
Yeah. We'll figure it out.
We'll figure it out.
Oh, they also have like educational cutaways
where they'll like ask a question
and they'll be like, "Yeah, what do you think of her like
uh, pussy hair?"
And he'll be like, "Yeah, that's fucking disgusting."
And then it's like,
to do you know like fucking bullshit drawings and it's like 97% of british men say pubic hair is
disgusting it's really it's really got to be one of the worst shows ever made but guys we're gonna
watch it we're gonna watch and uh we have to we did an hour now we have to do gambling because
that's all i can even think about right now um if you really love me you'll go to my show in
Los Angeles on November 17th. It's gonna be an amazing time.
And whoever the guy who called me on Halloween and
said "Happy Halloween", I appreciate you man. Thank you for calling me.
What else?
If you liked watching this and you wish you could interrupt us by typing something
in the chat, it's always live.
It's either Wednesdays or Thursdays on twitch.tv/podcastsaboutlist
Podcast about list so block out both days for us, please. Yeah, it's just always
Yeah, always fuck it. Who cares?
It's always maybe except when we're like in real life, but even then we can probably just record
All right. Goodbye. Yo, I'm the host. I'm a friend. Goodbye. Goodbye
Amazing episode
Thank you guys
Thank you Rex and killer for joining me. Thank you to all see you next week
the