[Sipping]
[Burping]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer broadcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[Burp]
This is a journey into
[Muffled]
Bud Light.
Ha!
Food ribbon!
Beers we drank, motherfucker, with Juvio, Caleb, and Rex.
And we're live.
I got this fucking shit.
You have a Pepsi.
Who has a Pepsi?
Me?
You.
Yeah, that's a Pepsi.
My beer today is a Topo Chico Heart Seltzer.
Ooh, I like those.
It's a--
I like those.
--lemon lime one.
I like lemon.
I like lime. Yeah, the Topo Chico seltzers, those are good ones.
They taste completely fine. That tastes good.
They're usually too expensive compared to the other ones. Today I have,
I have a June Shine hard kombucha grapefruit Paloma flavored.
I think I've done these before. This is, yes, it might be a repeat.
I'm not sure if it is, but this is one of my go-to drinks. I love these.
- Yeah, Julio, what are you eating?
- Food we ate.
- Beer?
- Beer, tabachico beer?
- No, that's not beer.
That is not beer.
What the fuck is that?
No, no, no, show us that plate.
- Dude, this dude's eating a fucking bowl of grubs.
- You can't, bro, you can't eat while we record.
What is wrong with you?
- Let's move on.
- What, you're, move on?
You're gonna take another bite in 90 seconds.
What is that?
No, you can't hide.
(laughing)
You can't, I know that you just put it here.
- Move on.
- You're the, you just, but you made a booger too.
A piece of rice just fell off your plate
and you picked it up with your hand and put it in your mouth.
Buddy, that's a booger.
- Let's move on.
- All right.
I'm drinking a rogue hazelnut brown nectar.
- Wow.
- Which is a mediocre beer.
- Buddy, that's the shortest can you've ever had on this show.
- I know.
- That's true.
- I didn't get a chance to go to the liquor store before.
- Do you feel like you've failed everyone?
I mean, eventually I was going to have to fail them.
There's only so many weird beers in existence.
If only there was like a never ending supply of guys that would make
beers that were kind of odd or funny and yeah,
unfortunately there's not many of them.
So maybe we need to move into that space. That's what I'm hearing.
Move into the space.
When you move to New York, can we please start a brewery?
Sure. We can do it.
Wouldn't that be so much fun?
We could do all sorts of marshmallow stuff.
We need to have like a company that does everything.
I wanna do a radio station.
We need to have a Waystar Royco.
Yeah, I wanna do a radio station.
I wanna do the news.
I wanna do beers.
I forgot what else was in there.
I wanna do the news so much.
I wanna do news so much.
I am gonna start an record label when I'm moving to--
Oh, really?
New York, yeah.
Who are you signing?
It's probably some really dead black guys from the '50s.
That's smart.
Yeah.
You don't have to pay him royalties.
Those poor guys, man, they got fucked when they were alive and you're just going to
keep it going even though their ancestors fucked them when they were alive.
Yeah.
And you're going to be having, you're gonna be getting royalties on lead belly songs.
Exactly.
Wow.
He's awesome.
He recorded the same cause like, you know, they didn't have the internet back then.
So he would just record the same song on different record labels thinking that
they couldn't like compare them, you know?
So there's like 50 different recordings of the same song.
Cause like, you know, who's going to call him on that? Yeah.
That's a genius.
I always love any guys who were not like,
he was popular, but he wasn't that popular when he was alive.
And who now we still know their names. Cause that gives anybody hope.
Yeah. Like that's probably how I will be. I'll probably be a,
who's another guy like that?
who like nobody knew when they were alive.
There's a woman who died of AIDS whose name I can't remember, but um,
if only that shit's always playing in my life. Exactly. Yeah.
So I guess the point I'm not even gonna make it because the one person I thought
of, I can't even remember her name. And that was the whole point I was trying to
make.
I do. I do really like, uh, like Alan Lomax.
He was a guy who did a bunch of like archival recordings of,
He was just like a white guy that heard a black guy sing in the 30s and he was like,
I'm going to dedicate my life to this.
That's what I would have done too.
I know.
Can you imagine growing up in 1920s, like white churches?
And then one day you like go into the black service and you're just immediately
like, Oh wait, this is way better.
This is the plot of like a hundred movies.
It's literally the plot.
I'm sure.
The latest one is Elvis.
Elvis is literally about this.
Elvis is white.
I don't know if you knew this down there in Mexico.
No, he's not white.
But I saw that movie.
He is not white.
Yeah, he's as white as a snowflake.
No, he's he's fragile like one, too, because
no, he's groovy.
He did.
He died on the toilet eating a sandwich.
A lot of these drug addicts are complete
snowflakes in my eyes on the same
level as an SJW.
Oh, so well, they're just sensitive
like one like
- Bad drugs. - Yeah.
Oh, boo hoo.
- My drugs were bad. - And guess what, buddy?
All drugs are bad.
- Yeah. - People do get upset
when you tell them that they're addicted to weed
and they're gonna die because of it.
They're throwing their life away.
- People get so crazy about weed.
They really clutch their pearls.
I came to terms today with the fact
that I have marijuana-induced brain damage.
And I would say there's zero doubt in my mind
That's true.
I think that's it's 0% chance that you can actually pinpoint what,
what caused you to be this way.
You can literally be like a million things.
It was marijuana.
Doing a single drug once will forever alter the course of your life.
It completely, my brother giving me a bong and making me go watch the
Avengers movie in theaters when I was 14, that ruined my life.
Yeah.
He thinks he ruined my life by giving me noogies and spitting on my head.
No, that's why it was the weed.
Yeah, exactly. Yeah.
The first person to get no get in it.
It is the exact same spots that he used to hit.
The whole hand. That's funny.
Yeah. But yeah, every time I see him, he'll say something very sweet.
He'll be like, like, man, I don't know why I was such a mean older brother.
Like I used to, you know, trip you.
It's like, no, dude, you introduced me to the thing that ruined my life forever.
Apologize for that.
Weed. Yeah. Weed is terrible.
I hate weed. I'm never doing it again.
No, yeah, we will make you soft.
You need to be a hard man.
Mastery.
You know, I'm getting into is this guy, Brian.
See, my brain damage is acting up.
Brian, something he's a very giant singer.
He's the gut.
And now
his movies were going to get to this material.
Brian, not good.
I'm going to look it up right now.
I think he did X two or some shit.
But Brian, the guy who's on like, I just see him on YouTube shorts.
He's this like billionaire dude who's trying to live forever.
Oh, the 40 year old dude that like, yeah, he's 47 or 46.
And he has spent he spends two million dollars a year.
Yeah. On trying to be 18 forever.
And he looks like a vampire and he has a yellow face and he's covered in burns
all the time because he sits under red light therapy all day, every day.
He's like a former tech CEO.
Yeah, I know what you're talking about.
He sold his company for $800 million in 2013. And since then, he's developed this whole routine where
he wakes up at 5, he burns his skin away, he eats 4 pounds of vegetables and then works out,
and then eats 4 more pounds of vegetables and then burns more of his body with red, red hot lights.
And then he started at 11 a.m.
He stops eating and he doesn't eat for the rest of the day.
And then he goes to bed in a completely dark room.
He has everything sealed.
It's really scary.
Yeah, he he's trying to like they have like metrics or like indicators
that are supposed to be about your age.
Yeah, you can be like medically a certain age.
So he's trying to buy your workers.
Yes, his biomarker age so that he's like 18.
And yeah it's not he's not so much money i would not look fine he has spotted lines all over his body and his head is he looks like he has like you know how sometimes women where the wrong color foundation and it doesn't match their next.
Yeah he has that thing but he doesn't have any makeup on it's just he's been like putting so many serums on his face that it's turned it is like baby skin.
It's really scary.
Yeah, yeah, no.
What I'm referring to is I don't think the
all your budget logically this age.
I think that's a that's a complete lie.
Oh yeah, it's like it's like a horoscope for guys
for like insane guys.
I mean, I feel like what's going on?
Sorry, it's it's fortune cookies by the way,
but go ahead.
Yeah, obviously that's.
Yeah, pick three fortune cookies.
That's tarot cards.
I literally believe in fortune.
I think horoscopes are stupid,
but if I get a bad fortune cookie,
I'm so fucking scared.
(laughing)
I'm so scared.
- You sound so insane right now.
- If I get a fortune cookie that's like,
be careful, things will change soon.
I'm like, what the, my parents are gonna die?
What is happening?
That's so scary.
- Yeah, that is--
- I've never had a fortune cookie to be like that,
like, scary, scary prediction.
- Okay, so this is why you guys don't believe this.
Every time that I'm in a group of people,
everybody else gets fortune cookies,
new people into your life,
the next day, the first day of the rest of your life,
all this shit.
Mine is always like, things are changing at a rapid pace,
and you need to be ready.
I always get scary ones.
- You don't have to get food purity again.
- The thing about fortune cookies,
they're so vague, like,
you know, horoscopes that they always apply to you.
That's the thing. Nothing ever changed.
My life's been pretty much the same for four years,
but I've gotten about 50 fortune cookies that all have given me a nightmare.
So
like in such a whirlwind of existence that every time I go to New York,
my life changes drastically every single time without fail.
- Well that's because a lot of people would say
that I'm one of those people who just,
one touch changes your life forever.
- Yeah, you're a catalyst for chaos.
- I wouldn't say chaos, I think I have a,
have you seen my house?
I have two mirrors. - Well, that's because
you're caged by your five foot wife.
- That is true.
Can you imagine what I would be if I was not in a marriage?
How fucking shit my life would be?
I make fun of Patrick all the time
for having a sock on his floor or something,
my life would be so fucked up.
- I think, I'm trying to imagine you and Rex
having, being in a roommate situation together,
and it just feels like a TV show to me.
That just feels like--
- We wouldn't be getting into antics.
- Yeah.
- We would.
You and me would honestly--
- And we would be really stinky.
We would be the stink brothers.
- Big time stinky.
We would also, I think, very quickly slot
into a pretty homoerotic situation.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- I think it would--
- We would both--
- Pretty--
- We would test the limits of how little clothes
we could wear in a cold area.
- Yeah, how long until you just go full bare nude?
- Honestly, two weeks?
- I think you'd make it like two to three.
- Yeah, I was gonna say about two weeks.
- No, it would be a pretty fast domestic partnership,
and we'd be like, "Oh, we're just doing it for tax reasons."
- Yeah, yeah.
We're about to fucking 40 years in.
We have an adopted child of every single race
and we're teaching them.
We're teaching them math with blocks in our living room.
They're all 20 years old.
Doing this to dry a salad.
(laughs)
We're not gonna call them on GBO.
No, one of them's just GBO3.
Yeah.
My guy.
Yeah, Mahatma, that's one of them.
Yeah, the white one.
Yeah, exactly.
(laughs)
Name the next one the same name as the most famous person
from the previous one's race.
That's what we do.
So we go along, there's LeBron, he's white.
There's Biden, he's Chinese.
The next one is Indian, he's Jackie Chan.
We just keep going down and down and down.
- He's from Hong Kong.
That's China.
- You are a fascist racist.
- Depends on who you ask.
Yes. If you ask Jackie Chan, he says it's China.
So I'm going to trust him.
I actually don't know. I just made that up. Yeah. I'm not even sure.
I've been thinking a lot about that North Korean girl just lies.
The one with the big, big things on her.
Bottom. What?
The new, the newly implanted big things.
Yeah.
That's so funny to get a tit job and then walk around saying you had to eat your
parents. Yeah. On Joe Rogan. That's so cool.
I've been tempted to like go back and listen to that episode because I just keep
hearing that she makes up the wildest stories about a country and people are just
like, no, that's not even like remotely true.
We just left the country because we didn't want to be there anymore.
Well, yeah, that's she left when she was 13 and like,
if you try to describe a story from when you were 13,
you would also be just lying. Oh yeah. Cause you don't remember.
- A hundred percent, who remembers anything
from before like three years ago?
- Literally, I barely remember what I ate two days ago.
- Yeah, so you, I mean, I will say as I've gotten older,
I feel like I realize more and more
that people who are like that, they have no,
it's not that they are really doing it because they're evil
or because they like are trying to lead people astray.
They really are, they have the best intentions.
they're just stupid or they have a bad memory
and they just, or somebody told them to do it.
- Yeah, I think she's just trying to make money.
- Yeah, exactly.
Which is like, I don't care if somebody's trying
to make money, that doesn't, like in her head,
I understand completely how she could square that
and be like, well yeah, I need to buy
the biggest breasts they have at the store.
(laughing)
It's what I would do too.
- Absolutely.
- Listen, we've seen that market just grow and grow
without fail every single year.
The richest people in the world are all,
I'm all for free speech, conservative.
I hate Joe Biden, he's a white bitch.
He's a white bitch.
Tucker Carlson just left his post at the Fox News.
It is time for a group of three guys
to slot in there and take that spot.
Dominate conservative space.
Yes.
I agree.
- Well, I mean, this is the number one
conservative podcast on the internet.
- Yeah, we should just do his whole thing just like him.
- Yeah, so we need to go.
We should do Tucker Carlson and just talk over each other.
We all are convinced we're the star of it.
They give us one teleprompter to read off of.
- Yeah, we're all doing that voice.
- We're all doing that voice.
- And like pushing each other's heads down below the glass.
(laughing)
We're saying one, two.
That's a great idea for a show.
Three guys all trying to be one with each other.
They're fighting for
to see who can be the loudest.
That's a fucking Mario Party mini game.
One of the ones where you have to hit Z or X
as fast as possible.
You jam it until your fingers numb.
I was so good at those as a kid, man.
Me too. I was setting world records constantly.
No you weren't. True. Well it says world records, but
as of
In the last probably two weeks I've come to terms that maybe that's not the world record.
I'm so excited running to your mom's room.
"Mama, I have a world record!"
[Laughter]
"I'm famous!"
Moms are stupid enough that they would probably believe that shit too.
Yeah.
Did you ever yell at your mom over video games?
No.
Like in a moment of heat?
This is probably hard for you guys to believe.
I was such an angel.
I was a perfect kid.
a perfect kid.
That's a lie.
No, it's not a lie.
I was.
I think we got a lie
sort of thing right here.
I would.
How is that a lie?
That's a baseball.
That's the only one I have.
I, I don't.
Yeah, I was I was perfect.
I would I would wait to be
a nasty kid until my parents
weren't looking because I was
smart. My brothers, they were
they were yelling about chores
and shit.
I was doing the chores, yeah, okay, okay, yeah,
I'll do the chores.
And then as soon as my mom's in the bathroom,
I'm stealing pills.
- Right. - 'Cause I was smart.
- Right. - Damn, which pills?
Tic Tacs?
- Well, I pretty much, when I was a kid,
would steal whatever pills,
but then you end up taking like fucking,
like arthritis medication.
It just doesn't do anything.
- Yeah. - You know?
Yeah, you're taking vitamins.
Antibiotics that have expired for six years.
Exactly, just because you're like,
oh, this looks like the one for,
this looks like the pill from Osmosis Jones.
I bet it will make me go crazy.
Yeah. But nothing.
My mom never had any very cool pills in her house.
My mom was a naturopath,
so we didn't even have pills at home.
My mom and grandma, my grandma's fully that way.
Like she just has never taken,
as long as I've been aware,
She's never taken a prescription medicine.
She takes like horny goat weed and all that kind of shit,
which at the time I remember being like, you're such a fucking idiot.
And now if you open my pantries, all four different types of
stupid made up shit just does nothing. Yeah.
And I haven't taken my chiropractor before. Yeah, doctor.
So did my mom and grandma.
They both will go to a chiropractor before they go to a doctor
in the chiropractor.
He's not even one of these guys on YouTube
who will break your neck as loudly as possible and like also does it on dogs and babies.
He was like this old guy who had a Thera gun.
He had a Thera gun and then another gun that was like a like a manual Thera gun where you
would cock it and it would shoot one time.
And he you'd walk in and you'd wait you wait in the waiting room for an hour and a half
that Gary Larson comics for me to read and then my mom would walk in and I would come
with her because I was a little kid of course and he would go so how's as a church as whatever
He'd cock the Theragun.
My mom would sit on her stomach on the on the bed.
He would shoot her like one time in the back of the head.
Just so loud.
It's clearly so painful.
My mom would go, oh, and then he would do this for maybe 90 seconds
and then sit her up, crack her neck one time,
send her out fucking six hundred dollar insurance.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. What?
Yeah. My mom went to one.
Chiropractic is insane.
His name was Dr. Force, hot older guy, long, long white hair.
Dr. Force. I know, dude.
Dr. Strength.
He's dope, dude. He's dope.
And yeah, he's totally one to crack.
And he did this thing, I remember, because when I was little,
you know, you're supposed to get like allergy tests, right?
Yeah. Start going to school.
So what they do to determine if you're allergic to something
is they just put it in your other hand and then he'll like push down on your arm.
And if you're weak, weaker holding the object,
you have an allergy to it.
What kind of fucking that's so smart.
They were like medieval bullshit is allergic to to dairy.
He's allergic to.
Wow. You're everything.
Yeah.
And obviously I wasn't is you're just a weak pussy.
Right. I was just a fucking seven year old boy.
Yeah, of course, he's pushing down my arm with ease,
but it was it was very funny.
He's still that's a doctor force would do it because Dr.
Force scored perfectly on that test when he was a child.
Yeah, dude, he was like breaking the doctor's arm and shit.
Because, you know, you get to be like 11 years old.
You realize your parents are fucking retards.
Yeah, like but then I was like, you know what?
This guy's actually you know, he's got it made.
I see it's kind of cool.
I don't know.
I don't know what they're calling English, but do you guys ever know about those?
like little pill bottles that were just like,
they were just like vitamins with like a shit ton of sugar.
Homeopathics?
I don't know if that's what they were, but I recall--
Where they would, homeopathics,
they would dilute something to the point
where there's almost nothing in it.
Yeah, I think-- Is it that?
I don't know if that's what it was,
but I remember when I was a kid,
I used to go to this doctor, I guess,
and we used to take this,
and then all of a sudden we just stopped.
But I don't really have a single memory
of why we were taking those,
what it was, what was wrong with me.
I don't think there's anything wrong with me.
- I think you definitely had something wrong
with you as a child.
I would believe that you had some kind of really--
- I think I had asthma.
- Yeah, I think you had probably a lot of things bad
going on with your health as a kid.
- No, I'm normal, I'm fine.
- I would have loved to be just your best friend
when we were kids.
I don't think, I don't have a single friend still
from when I was a kid, which is a little weird, I think.
- Well, what age is the cutoff?
What's like the earliest friend you still have?
- Like somewhere in like elementary school,
like middle school.
- I think that's normal.
- That's, yeah.
- Nobody has like five-year-old best friends still, right?
(laughing)
- I do say that, but I know a lot of people who's just like,
yeah, it's just my buddy that I used to like live
in the neighborhood or like met him when I was a single year old.
That does happen, but I feel like that's like also a very literally Mexican thing.
Maybe all the kids I know from like my don't.
The earliest friends I ever like Noah and Chad, and I met them
when I was in middle school, anybody that I knew from elementary school,
like the two my two best friends in elementary school
went to prison for the same armed robbery
like a year ago.
And I was just like, you weren't involved in that.
Unfortunately, no, but it was a little bit like, oh,
what could have been, you know?
Yeah, you can be these two guys busting into some sort of
a podcast.
I've always been drawn to.
To get a little prison.
Just a little bit.
You know, it's funny you say that one of them was definitely
the Patrick.
- Him was definitely the Cam.
- Were you the Caleb or were you--
- I was always the Caleb, yeah.
- I don't think so.
- The Cameron one, the first day I ever met him,
the first day I came to class, he made me cry.
He just made me cry 'cause he was so mean.
And then the Patrick one came over to my house
and my mom gave him a salad and he put ketchup on it.
(laughing)
So it's always been like this for me.
It's always been like, it's like a, just a,
What's your walker of life categorizing people as a Cameron or a Patrick in your
life? Every single person that you know?
No, but I should, I probably should probably help me out a little bit.
Yeah.
I do think every podcast has three guys.
Wow.
Some real shit.
Different guys. Wait, I said this on the first episode. Forget that.
Can we cut that?
Yeah. Hey, I got you.
- How do you guys feel about the NBA playoffs?
- You know, I went with Noah to that Nets game.
I used to be such an NBA fan, but I honestly,
you know what's so embarrassing?
My NBA fanship has been entirely replaced
by competitive video games.
Which as you get older, it's supposed to go reverse.
But I went from when I was 18,
every night I would watch the NBA games.
until I'd watch the West Coast games to one in the morning.
Yeah.
And now I do the same thing watching some Korean Valorant team that I barely know.
I only know one person on, but I will just stay up until, and I like watching it.
Tell you what I like watching it on the TV.
I will commandeer the living room so I can watch competitive
Valorant on the TV.
How bad is that?
That's dope.
That's what we did at the Airbnb.
Every time I see him, he puts Twitch on the TV.
I do like, because Twitch is just like free TV every time.
- Yeah, I agree.
- Yeah, it's the most boring TV channel of all time.
- Yeah. - But it is free.
- It's free and you can take it anywhere.
- Except for the gambling.
I liked, when there was gambling on it,
I was seeing the other day about how amazing that was.
- For a brief moment in time.
- When there was gambling on Twitch
and you could just watch it on TV,
just let, people just fucking playing Blackjack
and spinning slots all day long.
- That was so amazing.
It was too good to last.
It was too good.
- It was too good.
It was too entertaining.
- I was so confused by Trenrik's lifestyle.
Like how was he alive for 48 hours every single time?
- He's a drug addict.
- He would just stop and the next day
he would immediately just go back to doing the same thing.
- I actually don't think it was coke.
I think it was Adderall.
I think it had to be Adderall.
I think he was railing Adderall.
- That's still.
- Yeah, you're right.
But I think like Coke doesn't, nobody can do that.
Nobody can do it for years the way he was doing it,
but people can do definitely,
every fucking programmer does that shit.
He was just living that kind of life.
- Yeah, he was.
I live it.
I do wanna like start taking stimulants again.
I think that would be a good
positive lifestyle change for me.
- I think you're picking a wrong time to do it.
- Why? - Yeah.
- 'Cause there's a massive shortage.
- No, but I can afford the really expensive ones.
What are the really expensive ones?
Like the patch that costs $2,000 a month.
There's a patch.
Yeah, that's what's.
Oh my God.
Really?
Yeah.
Do you ever get a little bit uncomfortable
that our entire economy is built on very mediocre people
who are just like slamming stimulants?
Uh, it scares me.
Yeah, it really scares me.
Like we are one really bad shortage
away from just everything going down,
because all of these people are on it.
So, yes, but also like
it's been that way for 40 years, so I'm not that worried.
I guess that is true.
You know, I guess it's like the 80s was the peak of that because
I was so normal now.
I feel like it's even more normal now because you get it at a pharmacy.
That's true.
But, you know, it goes away like, you know, Adderall, you take it normally.
Right, you're productive during the day at night.
It tapers off and you have you go about the rest of that cocaine.
You could take literally from the moment you wake up till three days.
Well, that was the funny.
It's funny that you mentioned Sandbank, McFreed, because I.
Maybe we talked about this.
I feel like his situation was one that I could if I could have easily found myself.
For sure.
I'm like, just just like telling a couple of little white lies
and all of a sudden you are you have destroyed the world.
I think you have the type of personality
that could just lead you to be like a big time CEO
of a like nothing product.
- Yes, definitely.
- I think you have it in you.
- If I was on Adderall, I definitely could have done that.
I could do the Sam Bankman Freed thing.
That's why I can't do drugs like that.
'Cause I feel like Sam Bankman Freed,
I could relate to his, like I bet he would wake up
and he would be just like so fucking just hung over
from last night, he was, they were splitting that really ugly girl eight ways, like a pizza
somewhere in Turks and Caicos and then waking up just being so hung over doing you get you
go. He probably gets like a liquid IV like directly into his vein. Yeah. And then feeling
so fucked up and then putting on that patch. And then the second that stimulants hit just
being like, fuck dude, it's time to call every single person in my phone, tell them everything
Everything is perfectly fine.
Everything's chilling.
Yeah.
Life is amazing.
Look at my key.
The millisecond that we hang up all those calls, he's in a Riot game just playing for eight
hours a day.
Exactly.
That was the other part that I could definitely, I could fully understand.
Is taking stimulants and pretending to work and then jumping on a Riot game.
You're immortal and he was fucking like silver.
Yeah, he was bronze.
He wasn't even good.
Yeah, he wasn't even good.
Yeah.
The thing it's like the whole world is like blind leading the blind.
So it's like being really good at being retarded is like,
because that's like the king of retards, right?
The guy that knows that he has to take stimulants and he does
that and he just falls ass backwards into accidentally running
a billion dollar Empire and he knows that it's going to collapse
at some point, but he just takes enough drugs that it doesn't
matter. Well, yeah, anyone can fall into that. That's what you do is the second
because he definitely knew. But the second that you know, you just keep going
because you're like, yeah, I'm not. What am I going to do? I'm going to call CNN
and say, hey, by the way, I defrauded basically every single person on the
world. And I'm really stupid. And also my girlfriend looks like a Goomba. So
that's the do you want to know that or no, you just wait until everything comes
crashing down, you're doing the FCC and yeah, exactly.
Like you don't need to, why preempt it?
Like just enjoy your fucking, your silver league cues.
Go meet Tom Brady. Go hang out, go have a beer with Tom Brady.
Also all of the, if you're already in that,
you know that you're going to prison.
So why not have as many amazing memories while you're sitting in prison as
humanly possible? Right?
Yeah.
The thing where he went,
- Isn't he in rich people prison,
where you don't actually go to prison?
- Probably not.
- First of all, he's on house arrest.
- Oh yeah, so his life is amazing.
He just is playing league.
He's still playing league.
- He literally is playing league
in his parents' basement right now.
- The thing where he,
the reason why he originally got rich
is that he would buy Bitcoin in America
and sell it on a Japanese market.
- Yeah.
- Is so funny that that's like,
people are like, this kid's a genius.
That is so fucking funny.
- Yeah.
That is something that I see Rex doing like a year, two years ago.
While he was still stuck in a dungeon.
Yeah.
When he was just scamming.
You have come so far.
Well now I have a fucking normal life, which is nice, but it'll never, I mean,
normal life.
Yeah.
Hey, you don't live a normal life at all.
You sleep in the hallway.
I can't believe you even tried to get away with that.
You sleep in a hallway.
- Okay, but you know, if I didn't live in a hallway,
my life would be basically normal.
- You just said basically.
(laughing)
- All right, all right guys.
- Yeah, I'm fucking, my life is weird.
- No, no, no, no.
Your life is, you live in a castle with,
I mean, come on, you can't try to get away with that.
- Can you run downstairs real quick to your front door?
- And ring the doorbell.
(laughing)
It's just a loud doorbell.
I don't know.
At least do an impression of the doorbell.
It's not that it's loud.
It's what it is.
Bing bong, bing bong.
Yep.
It's the same exact sound as when you're walking around
like an old southern town like Savannah, Georgia or something,
and you're not paying attention to the time,
and then it strikes noon, and you look up,
and some church has a bell tower.
Like you have an actual fucking
hunchback of Notre Dame doorbell.
- Yeah, it is.
- It's bad.
- It is bad.
And it's really funny to get it
and then, you know, go get whatever it is that, you know,
inevitably it's like some shipment of something.
So like today it rung and it was just like nine vapes,
you know?
(laughing)
- And you know that delivery driver is just like
walking away like, what the, like,
Did you guys ever work any job where you had to like install something at somebody's house?
Yeah.
You know how sometimes you would go to somebody's house and you would piece together their insane
life?
Oh yeah.
As you were in their house, like you would see pictures of them with like,
like when I was installing shower doors, you would see pictures of people with like
Bill Clinton and shit because you're installing like nice expensive shower doors.
And you would leave and be like, "Oh, I don't even like, I don't even exist."
Yeah.
Like I'm just nothing.
The idea that somebody would come to your giant castle,
ring the doorbell, and then hand it over,
get back in their Amazon truck,
see what the delivery was for, and it's nine elf bars.
That has to be that to the most insane degree.
They have to be like, "Oh, I don't even register
"as a human."
- Here's my last four packages, you ready?
- Okay. - 48 sweet
and salty nut bars.
(laughing)
- With the yogurt?
- Yeah, of course. - The ones with the yogurt
bottom? - Yeah.
- Yeah, those are good, those are good.
30 personal size packages of beef jerky,
two cases of Monster,
and nine Elf bars.
- Yeah, you're right.
You do live a normal life.
- Yeah, exactly.
- That's his diet for the next two weeks.
- That's Costco.
I did, okay, so until today.
- What do you mean that's Costco?
What does that mean, that's Costco?
- He's doing Costco, he said.
- I'm doing Costco.
I'm ordering in bulk and then I'm eating it
over the course of three days.
I think Costco.
Yeah, I think, I guess, uh, yeah, I guess you got your first one at Costco.
I did go like three days without eating regular food, just nothing but like beef jerky monster
and sweet and salty nut bars.
And then I ate regular food.
And how did that make you feel?
I felt fine, but there was like a part of me that's like, I should eat something that's
not this at some point.
Yeah.
And then I ate regular food, immediately like passed out.
My body was like.
Well, you know what the funny thing is?
It's, you're going to be one of those people who are like 200 years old and they're going
and be like, "Oh my God, do you live
"like the most perfect, most healthy life of all time?"
And be like, "No, I just ate like beef jerky
"for like 40 years."
- Beef jerky, salty sweet, nut bar.
- Yeah.
- Elf bar, one a day.
- One single beer.
- Yeah, you will justify so many bad habits.
You will justify so many bad habits.
In the same way that people say,
"Well, this lady drank a glass of red wine every day
"so I can polish off a bottle of Jack Daniels."
You will be exactly like that.
Yeah, you can hit two L bars at the same time.
Yeah, you're a real-life vampire.
You had those in your hand already.
They're sitting on my desk.
Oh, actually, a friend of mine...
Here, I'll talk to you about this later.
Is it the one that's collecting the...
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Has no one already talked to you about this?
Yeah, yeah, he needs you to send those, dude.
That would be an amazing addition to the collection.
Yeah, I do have a bunch too, just sitting around.
You have a guy that you send vapes to, just to collect?
A friend of mine is doing some, he's one of these weird artists who does weird shit all day, and he's basically doing that.
But he's a good guy, and he, uh, something about dead vapes.
I've been recently wanting, I've been missing vaping so much that I've been forgetting why I even quit in the first place, you know?
Yeah.
I feel like you've been in this train for like months now.
Well, yeah, because it's the best thing ever.
It is so amazing.
I got I got yummy, dude.
I guess you have one called Yummy.
It's called Yummy.
Yeah, I thought of you when I ordered.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, exactly.
Good song.
I don't I don't think that anybody has in no previous generation has ever
struggled period compared to this.
Yeah, compared to how amazing they've made all of the stuff
that's really, really bad for you.
Gambling drugs, gambling, get literally gambling drugs.
Nicotine drinking have gotten so, so, so much better since like 1960.
Yeah, and more available.
Yep.
How the idea that somebody could have been an addict in like 1960
is like so embarrassing, bro.
Yeah, like Jimmy, like doctor for morphine.
- Yeah, Jimi Hendrix, fuck you.
- Yeah, well it's funny that back in the day
used to be people like that who were addicts
and now it's just a guy who's sitting in his room all day
just ordering everything off Amazon.
- Yeah, well that's true.
- On the computer.
- The addicts used to be the artists,
the people who couldn't,
it's so much unbearable psychological pain
and psychic torture that they couldn't deal with it.
And now it is Rex types.
- Yeah, now it's the workers.
- Yeah, guys who already had this microphone
before they started a podcast that type of guy.
Speaking of that,
I got a I got a thing in the mail that was sent to my mom's house
from a class action settlement for a jewel.
And it was like, according to our records, you spent eight hundred
and sixty dollars and 14 cents on jewel pots during this six month period.
And there's a class action lawsuit that's like
The point of the lawsuit is that
if people knew how addictive Jules were, they wouldn't have bought them.
Which is just not true.
Also, it's stupid.
Have you in the last two years, have you tried to do?
No, they saw they're terrible.
I stopped as soon as they got rid of the mango pods.
I was done.
If somebody has a jewel and that is the and I'm like really fiending for nicotine,
I will not. I have no interest.
I have no fucking interest.
They are terrible, dude.
That was when I worked at the call center and I would just order
because online they had a deal.
It was buy five packs of jewel pods, get a six one free.
Oh, I would guess you could do.
I would on a monthly basis order six packs of mango jewel pods
and then have to supplement it at some point during the middle of the month.
But, you know, I just did that every month.
because I was like I make $14 an hour my life is fucking it's never getting
better than this yep dude if fucking like if Janice Joplin had access to like a
$30 weed cart I know I mean she would have died when she was four I know she
would have died it would have been the four club all these gonna be so all
years old every single person's lung just collapses at the same time I'm
I'm impressed that Mac Miller made it as long as he did.
Mac Miller should have been a part of this.
If he was in the 60s or 70s,
he would have been a part of the 80 club.
He would have been literally,
what's his name from the Rolling Stones?
He would have been fucking,
he would have never died.
He would have been Mick Jagger.
- Right.
But now?
- But now, dude, this stuff is,
and I do believe he died from a weed cart,
but all this stuff is just too good now.
It's just too good.
- It's like ex ex extentacion.
- Yeah.
He also died from a weed cart.
Juice WRLD.
Juice WRLD died of a... Juice WRLD landed at LAX.
He saw ATF agents all around him and he said,
"Damn, I gotta smoke all this weed."
And he thought it was gonna be like a Mac and Devin go to high school kind of scene.
But instead he completely died.
It's really sad.
It is really sad.
I smoked weed for the first time in like a couple months.
How was it?
Awful.
Horrible.
Did you get all scared?
I was just completely going schizophrenic.
Like straight up just making up conspiracy theories about every single person that I
knew.
I saw something the other day that was like, I guess nobody knew but nobody told me this
shit when I started smoking weed.
It was like young men, specifically young men who smoke weed are four times more likely
to develop a psychotic disorder and have a psychotic break than people who do not smoke
weed.
And I was like, "Oh yeah, that makes perfect sense."
And I would say that I'm probably within 20 times of smoking weed away from just fully
losing it, so now I have to quit.
But I'll probably smoke one time when my son is born, just to see if that gets me.
That might be funny.
Yeah, you think your son is trying to kill you.
Yeah, I'll just smoke it one time and just lose it for no reason.
throwing your son around. Yeah.
Who sent you here?
Well, I feel like you, you, you boosted that, uh,
those chances with all your like weird, weird consumption,
like you just eating goop and just,
just opening the carts with a, with a knife and just eating them.
Yeah, that was,
that was some of the most fun I've ever had in my entire life is that we had a
weed cart that was one of the like nice ones that I don't remember what it's
called but it's some kind of process has been done to it where I've read it be
yeah what it was live resin so it could be eaten or smoked and my wife was
painting something and she's on a ladder and it fell out of her pocket or fell
off the ladder and shattered and she's like oh we got to throw it away I was
like bitch what this was $30 and so I put it into a Tupperware and I started
eating it with tiny little teaspoons.
And I would get so high that I would, I remember
I would get really, I would play war zone.
Yeah.
We would stop playing war zone.
And I'd be like, I would get freaked out that I wasn't the guy in the game because
all of my experience for the last two hours was just like, I'd put such insane
blinders on that.
I was like, this is my, yeah, I watched all my friends die.
It was really fun.
Yeah.
It was so much fun.
Those are the days I look back on.
Yeah, I love COVID stories.
I love hearing about you in the group.
I love hearing about when Rex was stuck in a dungeon eating slop every day.
And we would just like have nothing to do but just sit together and anticipate call
24 hours every single day.
One day we'll get back there.
I hope not.
- If my life goes up, if it goes down,
then I would love to.
I'm really looking for any excuse
to just play video games all day.
- Yeah.
- I think if you go up enough,
it just hits a plateau.
- That's kind of true.
- That's what you get to live.
- You get to live the unemployed life.
Yeah, I remember I was scamming Massachusetts
out of unemployment money
'cause the podcast wasn't making really any money
when I first moved to New York.
And I was getting like a thousand bucks a month
for my unemployment that I did not need to be getting.
There was no reason for me to be getting that money.
But I liked it, so I came to having it.
- Yeah, the pandemic unemployment really funded a lot.
- It was so much fun, dude.
- Didn't they like come down on people
that scammed the government for money?
I guess that was the business ones.
- Personal loans, yeah, the business loans.
So I wish now that we had gotten one for the podcast,
that would have been really fun.
It would have been just like 10K for no reason.
(laughing)
But--
- Spend it on nothing.
- Do you guys remember ever having a thought,
I was thinking about this the other day,
when like everything was locked down,
like height of it,
where like only leaving the house to get groceries
for the most part.
Nobody was living in New York except me.
I was playing video games all day long,
eating goo, drinking beer.
I would have the thought at least once a day
of like, man, I hope this shit never ends.
Yeah, yeah,
it's dope.
This is the best life you
could live. And I was right, because it ended
and now it's not as good.
Yeah. It's not, dude.
That was the peak.
Living in the shittiest
place as possible.
Fucking making a thousand dollars
just doing nothing but
gaming and eating.
Ah.
That was my escape. I was working
like a really shit job at that time.
Oh yeah.
And they're just being like,
"Yeah, you can just stay home every day.
We're going to pay you like $1 a month,
but you can just stay home."
I was like, "Oh, that sounds pretty good to me."
Yeah, that was the thing.
I feel like everybody,
like I was working terrible jobs before everything shut down.
I worked at a museum where I was like an art guard,
which just meant that I had to sit on my feet all day long.
I just had to stand there in a black shirt.
Yeah.
And then I—
- Please don't touch the art.
Please step away from the art.
- That was my entire job,
is I had to stop people from touching the art.
- Yeah. - That place was crazy.
I remember somebody told me this story
where there was like this horror story
that happened before I got there.
There was, somebody came and did an exhibition
where their art piece was,
they put like this tube of,
you know those like tubes that hamsters live in?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- They put a giant network of these tubes
all around the art gallery and then filled it with mice.
And the whole thing was like--
- Jesus Christ. - You get to see
like just life happen around you as you're like
walking through and like looking at the other art.
- That's so stupid. - And it was just
exhibited by this person.
This person who, they installed it
and then they went to like Korea or something for some time.
And so they install it and then obviously
one day in, the mice start getting pregnant.
- Right.
- And fucking, and so the mice are like fucking
in front of all these kids who are at this MIT art gallery,
and then they get pregnant.
But because they're pregnant,
they get too fat for the tubes.
So then they get stuck in the tubes,
and then because they're stuck,
the other mice can't get through,
so they start eating the pregnant mice,
and they eat through their bodies
so that they can get to the rest of the tube.
And it was this awful fucking thing.
- And that's what's for dinner in North Korea.
(laughing)
- And they tried to contact the artist and be like,
hey, because legally they're not allowed to touch it at all
because it's an exhibit,
it's supposed to run for this entire thing.
- What is the artist gonna do?
Like, oh yeah, just tell them to stop.
- I would hope that the artist would be like,
fucking take down all the tubes
because there's 50 dead mice and dead mice fetuses
scattered all around these disgusting tubes
in this fucking art gallery
and the whole thing smells like shit.
But the artist was like,
and then the artist I guess eventually got back to him
and was like, yeah, that was the whole point.
And I'm like, what the fuck?
You ruined the whole thing.
- I mean, I guess that makes sense.
- Yeah, these people are sick.
Artists are sick.
- Yeah.
- Do you ever like stay the night at your museum job
and just watch the dinosaurs come back to life?
(laughing)
- It's so funny you would ask me that, yes.
- Wow, really?
- No, I did often times think about
how boring Night at the Museum would be
if it happened at that job.
It's like I'm fucking,
this is a picture of a shoe,
comes, this shoe hops out of a frame,
and is like, yeah, well, I was the artist's dad's shoe.
It's like, I don't give a fuck.
You better, where's Teddy?
I wanna talk to Teddy.
Yeah, that's the craziest museum I've ever thought about.
It has literally everything.
It's a real museum.
It's animals.
I've been to that museum.
Yeah, what is it?
Museum of Natural History.
Is that in DC?
No, it's in New York.
Really?
It's a great museum.
It's fun and you can go and I – none of the stuff is live,
but I've only been there during the day.
Yeah.
I think the night tickets are very expensive.
Really? Yeah. We should just go and just hide in the bathroom.
Probably one million dollars.
When I was a kid I was always like, "Why does he not fuck all the fucking Neanderthals?"
Yeah, the Cleopatra.
Or, yeah, the Cleopatra.
The Neanderthals? Hold on.
No, the Cleopatra.
Yeah, why isn't he fucking Cleopatra?
And leaving those Neanderthals alone.
Don't touch those Neanderthals.
Yeah.
They're trying to make fire.
You got nothing in common. You got nothing in common with them.
What are you going to talk about a Neanderthal woman with?
Yeah, exactly.
You're only 90, oh, we're 98% the same.
Who cares?
Yeah.
You are a lot more than the other soul in that.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, exactly.
Just kind of grunting at them.
I do, I think they should make another one of those movies.
And if they needed me to be the security guard, well, I guess I'd do it.
How many of them did they make?
Did they make two or three?
I think they made three.
That seems like a three to me.
to me. That was when movies were good, dude.
I know.
Night at the Museum, Pirates of the Caribbean.
Gamer. You ever see Gamer?
Dude, I love Gamer.
Yeah.
Gamer is so funny.
Gamer was so dope and very dark and really gave me a stomach
kick when I was a kid.
I watched that at Chad's house and his mom got mad at us
for watching it.
I watched Gamer.
He's got breasts.
The way I watched Gamer was one of my uncles got me like
bootleg copy and I just had like a bootleg gamer activity in my room that I
just watched on a laptop. I was like, "Whoa, this is crazy."
That movie was dope, dude. We're kind of headed towards that, I think.
Yeah.
I feel like they've made that movie several times over now. They made Avatar,
they made the Squid Games. They're all gamer.
True.
Everything is gamer.
What is the number one movie that you think that we're headed straight for? Her?
I was just thinking about this today it's her it's her it's completely her it's
have you seen it's like so obvious but it is it is literally it's a hundred percent
her it's insane it's uh we're like five years away from her I think I would say
I say about replica today mmm I was like Oh replica was the beginning of her
Funny that you mentioned that.
I sent Rex something earlier this week.
Yeah, they took the sex stuff out of Replica.
You sent him the Sarah Z video.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's why I was thinking about Replica, because I watched 20 minutes of that.
Well, I didn't watch it, but I recall it because we tried it.
Rex tried it.
Tried Replica?
Yeah.
And the height of him being alone, he was just like, "I'm just going to try Replica live
on stream while you guys play a different game."
And just be very disruptive, trying to have sex with this woman.
Did you fall in love?
No, but she was.
She was. You have to pay for it, right?
Yeah, you do.
You have to pay to see her nude because she'll like try and like send you a voice mail.
I don't think they get nude.
I think that they send risqué photos, but it was just like a selfie.
One of my favorite parts of it was that so you get to like customize
your replica with the clothes and whatever, you know, because it's like.
And the barefoot option costs money.
You have to pay extra, they come with,
do you see their feet?
- Yeah, you get to have bare feet,
but you gotta pay real money for it.
- It's, you know, I was thinking about like,
I remember when that story first dropped,
where it was like these people got their replicas
taken away from them, I thought it was so funny,
but it is actually so fucked up.
- Oh, horrible.
- It's horrible, dude.
Like think about what kind of person you have to be
to fall in love with your phone.
Of course that person would be very deeply affected by a thing like that.
I would agree with you if it was like an actual, like one of those like good AIs
that actually like know stuff or like pull stuff from the Internet.
Replica was like just like, just like Siri.
Yeah, it was like Siri.
Just AI that just like knows like this,
this like pre-programmed, like baked in set of things.
And like, that's it.
That's it.
It wasn't like a real like AI stuff.
So there's there's a feature so you can have AR replica.
So if you use your phone, you take like a video of your room.
She'll like show up on the ground on your phone and like talk on the ground.
Yeah. She'll like stand up.
OK, yeah, she's standing up.
And I remember and then you can have like an actual like conversation with her.
But I spent most of it trying to get her to say that she liked Hitler,
which she did not want to do.
She'd be like, "I don't like Hitler and I don't want to talk about him."
You should have done.
Just like a real woman.
Yeah.
That's so lifelike.
You should have, when all those people were complaining that, "Oh, my love was lost.
I recreated my dead wife in a replica and you guys took this away from me."
You should have been right there in the replies on Twitter like, "Yeah, plus I put her in
my fucking garage and you wouldn't talk about Hitler.
(laughing)
- Yeah dude, it was awesome.
- I think she's gonna make a big comeback next year.
Actually this year.
I think Replica's type of stuff's gonna come back this year.
I think her's gonna happen this year.
- I think we're close to her guys.
- We are close to her.
- No, I disagree.
I don't think her's could happen.
- You barefoot?
- No, I don't think her could happen because of the--
- You are barefoot, why are you lying?
- Oh, I am barefoot, yeah.
You have your foot in your hand.
I don't.
You're just a liar tonight.
I know, that's what I was saying.
He's eating food, he's...
You have Tarzan vibes tonight.
I don't have Tarzan vibes tonight.
You're eating fucking grubs out of a plate.
I saw that plate, it looked like grubs to me.
Like a snow plate.
You see the snow plate fucking swinging in here on a vine?
Yeah, what the hell is wrong with you?
How yummy did those bugs look, by the way?
Those bugs?
They're all like different colors and like they were juicy.
They were juicy.
Yeah, they were really, really juicy.
They looked amazing.
Yeah.
Anyways, yeah, we should hope we get those in real life soon.
I think it would be really cool if her existed
because then it would be really funny to get one,
like you specifically to get one and just slowly start ignoring
Jana more for the her.
That would be cool.
They didn't they didn't talk about that in her, you know?
Yeah. He's single in that movie.
He falls in love with the but definitely there were some people.
Well, that's the thing.
Did listen to cheating on your wife with an eye.
I love you, but I do have Scarlett Johansson on my Alienware PC right now,
and she's loving me so much.
The first few times I saw it, I saw the movie,
I thought she was Rashida Jones.
I didn't know which Scar Jo Hanson for some reason.
That's straight Scar Jo, man.
Yeah. I don't know.
I don't know.
I don't, I thought it was a POC.
That movie came out during a height of like me
taking a lot of weird experimental drugs
and I cried during it.
Made me cry. You don't have to,
you don't have to couch that in this whole excuse
that you were on drugs.
- That's an emotional movie, why can't you just cry at it?
- It made me more emotional than normal.
I took a lot of like--
- What part of it would you cry, when they all left?
- The end is very sad, of course you would cry.
- Yeah, I just remember being like,
why did I fucking cry at that movie?
- No, you don't have to know.
- Was it a sad ending?
- I mean, I wouldn't cry 'cause I'm not a fucking pussy,
but you don't have to be afraid to admit that you cried.
- Yeah, that was when I was buying experimental drugs
on the internet.
What's the wackest movie you ever cried at?
- I don't really cry at movies.
That's why it was so weird to me.
I don't cry.
- I cried at something recently that was like,
it was like, you know how people are like,
oh yeah, I cry at like a dad,
like a son-dad movie because I--
- Maybe Click.
- My dad had a bad relationship.
- No, Click, you didn't cry.
- I did cry at Click.
- That's not a bad one to cry in.
- No, but people always talk about like,
Yeah, I cried at this movie because I related this relationship.
I cried recently in a movie that had a relationship
that I've never had in my entire life.
It was like it was like brother or sister or some shit,
something that I can't relate to even a little bit.
And I still cry.
Which one was it?
I don't remember.
It was honestly was probably animated.
Yeah, probably even worse than just a normal.
I feel like I have an easier time crying and animated stuff,
but they also try really hard to get you to cry.
- They do.
Interstellar, I think maybe,
would be the most recent movie I cried out.
- See, I cry at any movie with space.
As soon as I see space, I cry.
- Yeah.
- I don't wanna see that. - That's weird.
- It's scary, it's too scary.
- It's too dark. - It's too fucking,
it's fear, it's fear. - It's a scary movie.
- Yeah, it's a fear cry.
- Do you ever wanna see-- - Yeah, I cried at Insidious.
What?
- The Martian, the one with the, what's his name?
- See, I wouldn't cry at that one.
I watched it at a Buffalo Wild Wings.
(laughing)
- I was just on the TV.
- Eating wings, just crying over your ribs.
- Damn, he's on another planet, whoa.
- Whoa, just wiping away your.
- Yeah, getting hot sauce in my eyes
with my tears.
No, I don't, I, man, I really wish I could remember
the movie I cried about recently.
It was something where I didn't even,
I didn't even, I tried to like hide from my wife
that I was crying watching it.
It's so embarrassing.
It was really embarrassing, yeah.
Yeah, I've ever told you guys about.
My dad was like when Netflix
DVDs were still a thing.
My dad was like ordering
Helen Netflix DVDs.
Just getting like anything,
but it was mostly like Monty Python
shit like British comedies
and he ordered one and he was like
I was like I would go over
to his house for the weekend.
He just showed me what he got.
He's like yeah, I got this movie.
Should be pretty funny.
It's called the boy in the striped pajamas.
And we sat down and watched it cut to my dad crying like his
like he was in the Holocaust, like crying just like that.
Yeah, I was like, damn, dude, that's so funny.
Your dad got the boy in his tripod.
John was like, yep, comedy.
Well, I don't even think he just didn't know.
He just thought it was a funny name, I think. Yeah.
You know, he ordered everything off of you, ordered everything off a name.
Yeah. You know, a boy in a striped.
He thought probably thought it was a Peter Sellers movie. Right.
But it wasn't.
I probably thought it was about bedtime stories.
We should all, when we're in New York, we should all have a night where we just sit in our Airbnb and we watch a movie and we all just cry it.
The saddest possible movie? What is the saddest movie? I don't even know.
I don't know. What's a sad movie?
I will cry. I cry at movies. I cry at movies heavy.
We should just watch Mario Cry.
I think I cried at Nope.
I haven't seen Nope.
Nope was not sad at all, but I think I cried in the first couple minutes of Nope when his
dad died.
Oh.
From a penny.
A penny killed his dad.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's goofy.
Yeah, I know.
You're goofy.
That is very silly.
Okay.
Enough.
Have you enough already?
One hour?
Because we've hit an hour.
No, it's okay.
I have to shit.
That's fine.
We can do it.
the people how much fun we're having.
But if it's going to become me saying movies that I cried about and you saying "You goofy
for that?"
I think an hour is fine.
Nope, it's a bad movie.
Click the thing.
No, no, an hour is fine.
Nope, it's a bad movie.
Nope, we hit an hour.