now and now I'm hitting play.
Well, on that pitch, let's go.
Where's the beer?
You're listening to beers we drink.
America's next to the one to get going.
Jingle bells, jingle bells,
jingle bells, jingle bells, jingle all the way.
That mobile lost the wheel and the joker got away.
Just like that.
Ha!
Foo!
Ribbit!
Beer's we drank, motherfucker.
With Juvio, Caleb, and Rex.
Beer.
Oh my god, Caleb.
Okay.
Wait, wait, I'm gonna open, man.
Oh shit.
Wait, am I ready?
Shit.
Here I go.
I have a hearty one today.
I got a bottle one today.
Crazy one?
So I'd like to go last.
I eat a lot.
the last. I easily have the craziest setup here.
All right. I can go first.
No, I'm going first. I have a classic, a normal-sized Coors Banquet. I've been shrunk. This is a
12-ounce can. Let me take a sip.
You've been shrunk? You kind of glossed over the shrinking part, which I think is the most
interesting part of what you said.
What shrunk you, man?
The kids.
The kids shrunk you?
Honey the kids shrunk me.
Yeah, honey the kids shrunk me.
Wait, go with your review. I want to say something.
Why don't you say your review.
Hold on, let me take another sip.
Ok, well I'll submit things.
I love that.
Really?
Yeah, I have a Cordyce Banquet. It's delicious.
It's awesome.
That's a solid 7 out of 10.
I can drink this entire 12 ounce can.
Before the show even started, people said that Kurzweil was like the best beer, like the yummiest
beer, but I've never had it myself, so I really don't. It's good. I will say it does taste better
out of the glass, the stubby bottles, for some reason. The small mouth on it, it's good. But not
this small can. Yeah, not that normal size can. Okay, Julio, show me what you have, man. I have
a local brewed beer a local brewed beer its name its name is ray which stands for king
and you can see right there in the background there's the uh that's the mountain the the
classic mountain of my hometown the one oh wow it kind of looks like an inverted crown
i'm sure that this is what they were going for yeah that's probably what they were going for
for
- You're-- - Oh.
- You don't like it?
- I dropped the-- - It's crazy.
- So, okay, so it says here that it's like,
it says it's a number two London beer at the bottom.
And right here, like the ingredients,
it says like it's using some English stuff on it.
And I thought, I forgot which one,
who did the light beers,
and I guess it was not the Englishman.
So anyways, this is a number two beer for number poop.
and I don't like it.
Yeah.
Wait, should I say the score?
Yeah, I said the 7 out of 10.
Oh, ok. Alright.
But that's like a 10 out of 10 for a light beer.
Read it and weep.
I mean, it's...
It tastes literally like water.
really like water.
You need the stubby little bottle, man.
Guys, I have today an acai, okay?
But wait a second, I also have next to me, not just the beer, some leachy soju.
Guys, I saw a video where somebody made a soju bomb, and so that's kind of what I'm
going to do.
going to pour this acai up to about three quarters of the way full into my glass and then I'm
going to take this leachy soju, pour that in there as well to kind of top it up.
And now guys, here's the trick.
In Korea, they don't stir things like we do on the West Coast.
They stir things by doing this with a spoon.
I'm going to demonstrate right now.
Dude, I'm so pissed. I was about to get a soju bottle as well.
Okay, you need a special spoon for that.
No you don't, you need a normal spoon, bitch.
No, you need the different spoon. You need the one with the twirls on it.
Oh!
Oh, Korea, you've done it again!
This is amazing!
Oh my god, not a mistake.
He's got a hype train off of that.
This has, they better be hyping this shit up.
This is amazing guys. I got soju all over my mouse pad.
This is the best thing I've ever had. I'm gonna give this...
*burp*
Mmm. Oh that's delightful. It tastes like champagne.
I'm gonna give this...
an 8-2.
Wow.
I'm going high on this. I'm feeling high on this shit.
I'm feeling high. I'm gonna go 8-2.
You were really pumped about this.
this.
This is amazing.
But Caleb, before we even started recording, before even Rex showed up, he just said, he
told me that he had a crazy...
Well he had already told me hours ago.
But he told me beforehand.
He told me yesterday actually.
Lie.
And guys, I'm gonna go, you know what height I'm gonna go on this?
Five foot nine.
Now ask me why.
What's the best height?
Ask me why.
Why?
Because guys, that's Faker's height.
This one is for Faker.
He's a Korean ath- is there a Korean basketball player?
What the fuck do you think, man?
Yes.
No.
There's a couple Chinese ones.
There's Jeremy Lin, there's Yao Ming.
China is not Korean, man.
That's true.
In a lot of different ways.
I know that.
You don't- it seems like we're educating you right now and you're ignorant, man.
Straight up.
I hate saying that about my friends.
You seem ignorant AF.
You are both small and you look like John Lennon and you don't know about China and Korea.
So we're going to educate you on a couple of things.
You have an air of ignorance and an air of being an ignoramus even.
Yeah, and you're small.
You're small and I could crush you and crunch you in one single step.
Poop on Rex Day, I guess. This is just how it's starting today.
You know what? It wasn't until right now, it is officially Poop on Rex Day.
Guys, mark your calendars. December 8th, every single year, this is Poop on Rex Day.
is mad at me because he's been getting into tribes of sin and I've been very
ever so slightly oh yeah tribes 3 ever so slightly making fun of him for being bad
at video games and it's really really hurting his feelings which is okay of
course it's a complete I mean it's a it's a kick in the nose so much so much
so much so that he what while he was working he made an entire montage of him
playing tribes and he sent it to me. I didn't make the montage while I was working I played
the games while I was working. And then you made the montage. While you were working. He
made a montage in one day and we watch the montage and guys he misses a lot of the shots
and it's a lot of kind of jumping around in the walls, bad movement. Okay so the way this
went down is he sent this shit to me on prompted on I didn't even say anything about tribes
last night. So he just sends me the tribes video. I was like, hang on, let me, let me
just speak. All right. Just, you know, trying to speak. Let me speak. Uh, he sends this
to me on prompted and I was like, okay, I'll watch my friend's clip that he sent me on this
game that I don't understand. And I start watching and he's, I noticed that this play
is going for a little bit and he's, you know, he's up to like a high amount of kills. Probably
I'm like hmm this clips are long let me check the let me say how long it is and
that I look at the how long it was it was three minutes I was like dude I'm gonna
skip around I'm not gonna watch this entire thing and I I don't understand
tribes I've never played it before you brought this up last night during the
game awards and Caleb responded to you so I didn't know how to how to respond so
I was just like you know what send this shit into P first so everyone can
appreciate it. And apparently it was a mistake because now Caleb hates regs.
I don't hate regs I just I listen more power to them you know what I mean
that wheelchair basketball is a real sport I think that that is as real of a
sport as any other sport okay so and I and these are athletes okay and I feel
the same way about you with your new little game. You are saying this knowing
full well that you are trying to make me upset.
And that, if it's working...
How could that be making you upset?
How is that possibly making you...
I'm giving you...
I'm paying you a compliment.
I'm saying despite everything, you are having a lot of fun.
And I think that's wonderful.
I really think that.
That's fine.
So Julio and I have a thing that we've been doing where I watch him play TFT and I tell
him everything he does wrong.
You're framing this incorrectly by the way. This is not a thing that you and I are doing.
This is a thing that you are doing and you're pissing me off and I'm just trying to play
the game and you're like "you're gay for doing that. Why are you placing that unit right
there? You're gay." I'm like "dude, shut the fuck up."
I do not say you're gay. I give you the exact reason.
That would not be constructive criticism. Yes. I give you the exact reason why what
you did was wrong and then you get mad at me. You go "you're so annoying."
You are so annoying. I turned you to zero and then the next day I joined the discord and
we were like "oh let's play some games with rex" and I was like "why can't I hear him?"
You turned him all the way to zero?
Yeah I did.
Wow. That's ice cold man.
So Julio and I, you've never played DFT Caleb?
I played it one time and uh, see ok here's the difference between me and you. I will
not play a game that I know I can't be good at.
And I started playing TFT and immediately I was like, "I can't do this.
I'm out."
Yeah.
Anyone can be good at TFT.
That's because it's a game that utilizes only your brain.
No.
Anyone can be good at TFT.
I had it, I watched a video today where someone described it as a slot machine and it made
me think of, oh yeah, that's why Rex likes it so much.
It is a slot machine.
It is a little slot machine.
It is very RNG.
It's full luck.
It's full RNG.
The best part about TFT is the fact that it's not League or ARAM where you have to depend on your teammates to do good for you to win the game.
It's solely based on you and your own luck, which is the best thing about it.
Also, the second best thing about it is the fact that you can play on the phone and it's just quick and it doesn't matter.
Anyway, Julio wanted to play with me late one night and I was spending time with my boyfriend.
And I was like, I'll be on as soon as I finish watching this episode of TV with Mumble.
He's like, "That's fine!" I just started round 3, I got plenty to go.
And I just messaged him, "You will lose at round 5-3."
And then 20 minutes later, I get a message that just says, "Fuck you."
Wow.
And just...
Wait, so you are amazing at this game. You must be plat, diamond, something, some really high rank, yeah?
I haven't played enough, but I'm like gold 1, which is basically one-off plat.
I mean, sounds like a really shitty rank for a game that you're supposedly so amazing at that you can tell the future.
No, I'm just saying I fucking swished my hater...
is
it's
a
good
thing.
I'm good at it.
What are you talking about?
We both have hit diamond.
Nah, you're wrong.
Guys, it's turning into video games that we've played, which is a great idea for a podcast,
but it's not the one that we do.
Let's get back to the beer.
This is so this soju bomb is going away scary fast.
That's what I'm going to say about this thing.
Because I just found out reading this thing and I poured probably I think I did the proportions
wrong.
fucking bottle of soju in this shit and this soju is 12% alcohol y'all this is
not a normal thing to drink that's the thing about soju it sneaks up on you
because it's so sweet but also the only other time I've ever drank soju was with
this guy Joe from Philly and then John from also from Philly and we ended up
bringing we carry we found a stop sign on the road and we carried it like ten
in
we didn't drink soju right here
well it has a different name
i think you just misheard them saying soju
these are different man
i promise you
there's a my guess is that they're from different
countries different careers
you know to you
that's the
stoke to burst soju
showed you is a japanese spirit whereas soju is a korean spirit
all look who's the right one again mister smart
uh... here i am a little bit i was at the seven eleven
trying to pick a beer
and they had a really wax selection
and I was like fuck what haven't I had yet
and I saw a soju bottle and I was like
fuck we'll just pull up with a soju bottle for a special episode
it's a really special day for me. That would have been truly incredible
if you had without us talking showed up with soju. We would have been interlinked
yeah that would have been amazing
guys let's talk game awards let's have a little bit of a game awards
debrief
I'll just leave this conversation because I've watched the entirety of the video games.
Back to video games.
People on Twitter are complaining that the game awards were mostly about Hollywood superstars.
They were woke.
They were mostly about Hollywood superstars speaking for days while the foreigners who
poured their heart out on a game could just only speak for one minute.
And then after one minute passed on their winning speech, there's this screen that was in front
of the stage that in big letters would have a countdown, a one minute countdown, and then
on huge letters it would say "Wrap it up, get it going."
That's kind of fire though.
That is so rude.
That is so funny.
But there was a little bit of a letdown, I don't think they showed anything too exciting.
But Baldur's Gate 3 won Game of the Year, which I'm really excited about.
Spider-Man didn't win anything, which has got Twitter mad, which is really funny.
Zelda only won one thing, which I'm really happy about, because Zelda is the most boring
game in the world.
And apparently Alan Wake 2 is a really good game that I should play.
Yeah, I hear Alan Wake is really good.
Here's the thing about award shows, man.
They play these people off.
And if you ask me, and why do they do it?
Because they have to stick to a schedule, the show can only be three hours or whatever, right?
Last night we were supposed to record this podcast, but I didn't realize that the Game
Awards was a real award show.
I thought it was maybe like a basement kind of production.
I thought it was like a Twitch thing.
But it's real.
These guys, they have like a full theater, I couldn't believe it.
It's the 10th year running of the Game Awards.
It looked like the Oscars.
It fully looked like the Oscars to me.
are
thing
as you as you'd like but they should really be like twenty four-hour thing
because nobody can
you measure working all year
on something so amazing
and then you get cut off thirty seconds and because they'd have to have matthew
mcconaughey r_f_d_ mackey come out and say something
you about and again where they play a uh... of a mushroom
or whatever these kind of had a little long
people who have a cover coji man
to appeal which i i thought
on but at least those guys seemed
of respect i mean that everybody likes those two
right it in that you met him a kind of a lot of these fucking nerds watching
this they've never seen a movie
they've never they don't know what they are not familiar with it
eight-mile they're not familiar with lincoln lawyer
they don't know who these two guys are
you know and now they're clear wasting their time
and they're saying i all we could have five-hour uh... interview with the uh...
davy reardon
you know that would have been better for them
i think the issue is that a real war two doesn't have
trailers for movies that come out next year
that is true that is such an amazing point
yeah you don't get that very much you'd like to know how the
how to the oscars work that just keep
Oh, they have a bunch of jokes in the middle, but then it just ends.
Yeah, the Oscars.
They have an actual comedian, although admittedly not usually a funny one, be a host.
I mean, Jimmy Kimmel.
Jimmy Kimmel?
Jimmy Kimmel is not that funny.
My favorite comedian, man.
You are lying.
And that's fine.
This is a podcast, you're allowed to lie, but it's fine.
Kilov, you're funny.
He's not funny.
I'm fucked up, man.
Look at your face.
You look like a baby.
You're redder than normal.
It's the Shizuji man.
Dude, I love having this picture of us under my monitor.
Because Kelo's face is so small and so red.
I'm so red in that photo.
It's like the sickest I've ever been.
And I'm just like, at Margaritaville, twisted off of two completely translucent...
Oh my god.
I translucent. Neon drinks. I had a blue drink and an orange drink.
And I was fucked. I was so fucked up in that photo.
And then I went and had an amazing meal.
It is true. We need... there needs to be a
happy medium between like all you can eat and really good food
that's not a million dollars. Dude, oh my god.
I have three things to say to you.
Which is
Fogo de chow. Yes, we need to do that is literally what exactly what you described
Why didn't we go to focus show by the way? I'm so sad. I
Went with Patrick a couple weeks ago, man. I
Was the town and you didn't take me
Fuck you
That's why you've already been you think I'm gonna take your bitch-ass again. I want to go again. Honestly. Yes come to New York
Let me take all of us to Pogo de Chow. We'll do a live
Three hours
Kanye we ate can we tell you try to book that that one big?
Yes, Oh the conference room conference room that all those Japanese men were having a a big lunch
that was amazing when we went there was a full luncheon of of
Japanese businessmen and they had like people there who were like Trent like really beautiful women there and dressed in suits
Translating for to the waiters. That's all sir. Like what they wanted. It was really cool
But it was the thing is it's not like a Fogo de Chao in Manhattan. It's like in the middle of flushing, right?
It's like it's like in a mall
It seemed like such a weird place for a bunch of Japanese guys to go on a business trip
I will say two things to say about this one is that after you guys stubbed me for Fogo de Chao
I came back to Long Beach and I
Went to get pizza and like right next to the pizza store was like a non Fogo de Chao Brazilian steakhouse
Okay, and like going to one of those when you don't expect it is like such a weird experience
Because if you know ahead of time you're going to an all-you-can-eat thing, it's like you prepare, you know
You don't eat the whole day. You drink a lot of liquids you think about it
This is the sad thing that's happened to me both times
I've gone to Fogo de Chão is that I've eaten two hours before every single time because it's been impromptu and it's a wrong move
It's the wrong move and it's like, you know, it's 60 bucks
So it's like it's not the worst amount of money to waste, you know, you could have really got that $60 worth. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Did you end up going to that non Brazil or non Fogo Brazilian?
Yes, and I ate the fuck out of it, dude
Here's here's the rules of Fogo de Chão man
and I think that there should be somebody outside who should be like honestly you could probably make money at that place by
Selling a like guide like a game FAQ
for like
How to beat Fogo to chow, yes, here are the things
The the salad bar you a lot of people say no. No, no, no. No, listen to me
I'm an expert man
A lot of people would say never go to the salad bar and that's if that's one way to do it
But there's some delicious stuff on the salad bar, but the key is don't go to the salad bar
first
Go to the salad bar later in the evening because here's that they trick you they give you the plate and they say
The salad bar is over there will
Turn your cart over when you're ready and we'll have some people come over
But it always takes five or ten minutes and you want to eat right then you've been saving all day to eat this food
So you run to the salad bar and then come back and flip over your thing, but there's amazing things up there
You don't want to miss out on that. You don't want to overdo it, but you definitely don't want it to take over meat real estate
Okay, you need some roughage
They have a great Caesar salad, there's nothing wrong with the Caesar salad, yes, okay, so that's number one number two is
Get that chicken out of my fucking face. That's right chicken out of my face
I should be
Bucks I should be able to slap that out of your hands when you bring that fucking skewer over to me and you say would
You like it's a piece of chicken
I should be able to take the skewer and put you on the skewer
They should walk around with you as a waiter and say do you want any Craig? That's what they should do. Okay?
For even offering me a piece of chicken. Was that the one thing that we rejected? I remember you
Meat, I say no to chicken and guys I learned this as well. I say no to anything that is bacon wrapped
The bacon stuff is too heavy
Fatty salty get that shit away from me. Give me the steak. We didn't have chicken hearts. They were good. Yeah chicken hearts are awesome
We had chicken. Yeah, we did. They're really tiny. They're like, I remember that
Yeah
It was funny coming coming out of tofago de chao and
Someone else like I said like oh, do you have the like this cut and I was I don't remember a single one
So I just like yeah, it was good
I like that.
That was my favorite actually.
And a lot of people say, "Go and have the picanha.
Wait for the picanha to come.
The picanha is the best one."
Picanha is good.
There's nothing wrong with it.
But the best one is the top sirloin, guys.
Trust me on this.
It's the most well-marbled one.
The picanha is a very lean cut with a fat cap on top, which can be hit or miss.
It's inconsistent depending on how big of a fat cap they give you.
The motherfucking top sirloin hits every single time.
I like the Jack's cut.
I feel like that's a pretty normal Brazilian steakhouse.
It's a very small...
Yeah. The Kanya is really good and obviously it's like one of those things you can only get at a Brazilian steakhouse.
So you should get it while you're there.
But every cut of meat...
The only thing I don't like is the one I went to served sausage.
I'm sure.
But yeah, you gotta say no to the sausage because that's like, you can get that anywhere.
Exactly. It's fuckin' sausage.
It's not like a bratwurst at least?
I mean it's like a cheddar something sausage. It's not remarkable in any way.
It's not like specifically a Brazilian barbecue thing.
Yeah, it's definitely like a pork sausage. It's above average.
It's good sausage, but you're giving up steak real estate for sausage.
That's like a $5 meat versus like a $30 meat.
And the whole thing, the entire experience is about maximizing steak.
That's really, if you keep those two simple rules in your head, maximize steak and salad
bar after, then you will have a great time.
You should be eating things you don't normally eat.
You shouldn't have to go out there and be gorging yourself on chicken.
Stay adventurous.
Yeah, because how many times a week are you really eating three and a half pounds of beef?
Right. Zero.
But how many days are you eating half a pound of chicken?
Almost every day. Almost every day do I eat a half pound of chicken.
Right.
I'm kind of scared of chicken.
You eat chicken every day?
Pretty much. What is the major protein you would eat?
I would say...
I want to say chicken.
Yeah.
Everyone eats chicken.
That's why we all have...
Chicken is just a staple meat.
That's why people are balding.
the
the only time I don't eat chicken
you're going crazy
the only time I don't eat chicken is when I get the mix
I am fucked up, I am insanely fucked up on this one
you mix platter, oh, oh, like um
yeah
from like a waffle
yeah, lamb and chicken
yeah, lamb is the only other meat other than chicken
lamb is, how do you guys feel about like veal and lamb
these baby meats
veal, well
I don't think lamb is a baby meat, is it?
is it? Lamb is a young version of a sheep. I guess that's true, yeah. Veal is bad. Lamb
is kind of whatever. Bad in what way? Well veal is like evil, you know. They break a
cow's legs and then they fatten it up to get it as fat as possible. Yeah, that's like foie
gras. Yeah, but something about that is like, foie gras, that's duck, right? That's duck
Yeah, so I don't really care about a duck
Really at all a duck doesn't a duck doesn't that like there's not a cute maybe a duckling is kind of cute
Yeah, but I would also never remember a duck's name a cow I could see myself having a relationship with I could see myself
Grabbing a duck by its neck and just swirling around like this and just not care. Yeah, exactly
Ducks are mean - yeah, they are mean
Really? Yes. How have you never brought this up before? That's awesome. Is that new? No, it's years.
Years? Yeah, it's probably... Is it giant? No, it's...
So it's supposed to be one of those like little teacup pigs. Those don't exist. Yeah, it's a boar.
It grows tusks.
They have to like shade it's toes.
Holy fuck. Is it Arizona?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, and it's got like a really bristly like mohawk on its back.
How have we never talked about that?
What the fuck? Wait.
inside
now you may have a lot of
this is a good
this is not a big deal
okay
it's been
it is a frankein short
uh...
does it shit all over the place?
no no it's actually, it's housebroken
it goes outside of the house
yeah it eats cheerios
and fruit
your dad has a pet pig for years
he didn't want it
and I was like, you should allow your
girlfriend to get the pig
that's an amazing pet
I don't think it's an amazing pet
I think it's a cool pet in half
here's the thing, the pig loves him
hates the girlfriend
Whoa.
And it like, it'll, like he'll sit on the couch, watch TV for 10 hours straight, and it will
curl up next to him under a blanket like a little pine.
Oh my god.
That's so cute.
Does he eat pork?
Yeah, of course.
He does?
Yeah.
Buzz, he has two reasons to not eat pork, man.
I know, and none of them stick.
But you know, he loves that pig.
To be Jewish and own a pet pig and that's your only pet and to still eat pork is so...
- I have two dogs.
- Oh, okay.
But it's the one that likes him the most?
That's crazy.
(laughing)
- How does it get along with the dogs?
Are they just chill?
- Yeah, it's pretty chill.
- They probably think he's a dog.
That's usually how it goes.
- Yeah.
- Wait, the sea pig, is he still a dog?
- No, but the youngest dog will sometimes corner the pig
and then they'll scream at each other.
And a pig's scream is really loud.
- They have a word for it, a squeal.
- Yeah.
So you have to take a Dremel to their hooves to like...
'Cause they grow like a dog's nails.
Yeah.
And you can't take that to like PetSmart and have them do that.
So you need to take a Dremel to it.
And the thing is you like flip it on its back and hold its legs and like...
Dremel... It doesn't hurt the pig at all.
But it screams so loud that you literally have to wear like earplugs.
Because it's like... It's deafening.
I was there once. I like helped.
and I didn't have the earplugs and my ears like I had worse tinnitus than I've ever had the next day.
From a pig squeal. Yeah it's it literally it's like you're murdering it and it feels nothing.
It does not feel what's like because it's like fingernails yeah. Well that is some of the most
amazing new information I've gotten in weeks. That you you have a pet pig which by the way
If both of them died, you would probably be the inheritor of this pig.
I would not.
You would. And then you would have a pig in New York City and we could make a whole documentary about you.
Oh my god.
I would take it for a walk, yeah.
The thing about it too, because of the way its hooves are, they've got really like...
Like a dog, when it walks, the paws are kind of soft, right?
Uh-huh.
The bottom of a dog paw is soft.
But a hoof is really hard.
So it has like dick-seeking hooves in the sense that it crawls over you.
It always puts its entire weight on your dick when it steps.
It hurts so bad.
It's not like a paw.
There's no softness to it.
No, there's no softness.
It's straight up pain.
It's like a Yeti water bottle hitting your balls.
Do you have a picture, Frank, that we can see?
Let me see if I have one.
I'd have to go back pretty far.
Have you ever seen one?
My brother had a pig.
Josh had a pig.
I don't know if you know that.
He had a pig, they named him Pabst.
Hilarious.
Beer.
Named after beer.
Beer pig.
And it was the same thing where it was sold to him as a teacup pig and then it became
like a hundred pounds.
Right.
And they, the way that it, the reason, they got rid of him eventually.
But they really liked him but he was, because pigs are so smart, he would do stuff like he
would take a sh- he would move- he wasn't allowed to shit inside but he would move
furniture and move the the the rug and then take a shit under the rug and then
move the rug back and put the furniture back. Yeah, and they would- so they'd be like
walk around they'd be like why is this why does this fucking room smell like shit and
then they'd find under a piece of under a chair and under the rug they would find a
A pig shit that had been like squished down.
- They were very smart.
- It was insane.
Yeah, that's an animal,
I really don't eat much pork at all.
- Back when I was living with my dad.
- It tastes amazing.
- I would go on these walks every morning
and sometimes if I went early enough,
I would go walk to this park,
I would see this neighbor that just had a pig
and it was always, she like took it outside
to like walk it I guess,
but he was always so big and so fat
and was always just laying on the ground.
So I think he was just getting some air or some shit
because I never saw that pig walk once.
- They mostly lounge.
That's the nice thing about a pig.
It's not like a dog wants to run all the time.
I just had to take Phil to the park
and there's a subway that goes right next to the park
and he's developed this awful habit
of we're playing in the park with his ball
and then the subway comes and he chases the subway
for like six hundred feet
down the the park to like the fence
to see what's right and a little boy
now he's off leashed
i'm breaking the law
i'm not going to start only you off leisure dog
at the park yet some of the problem really
and the thing is when it's his time to go it's his time to go if you're in
school
you're right
do you know that he's just doesn't show up again
tonight a little bit when he started running towards the train i was like
Fuck this dog, I hope he just keeps running.
Oh wait, that's Frankie?
He's ador- wait, that's his bed?
He has a child's bed?
He has a human's bed.
That is so adorable, oh my god.
He's not that big either.
Nah, he's like 30 pounds, 40 pounds.
That's a nice small pig.
He's probably like 5 years old at this point.
How old can pigs get?
They can get pretty old.
Yeah, I think they're similar lifespan
to dogs, I would guess.
the
fed
a
turn two and I'm like I have to do this shit for nine more years and then he gets cancer
in his entire body and he explodes.
That's the thing I've probably said this before but it's so funny that the only place dogs
ever get cancer is their entire body and then you go to somebody's house and the dog walks
up to you and they're like oh by the way don't touch the dog he has cancer in his entire body
If you pet him, he is it's the worst most unimaginable pain of all time. Yeah
I've been uh, ever since I got I got got our dog
I keep getting like dog tic-tocs like
For weeks now and I've gotten a couple recently where it's a family with like a really old dog
And it's like well
This is our our dogs last meal and they feed him like a like like a chocolate bar or some shit
Have you ever thought about what your last meal for Philwood would be?
I honestly, truly it would probably be a giant, like three jars of peanut butter in a bowl.
And it wouldn't be because that would be his favorite meal, it would be because it would
take him a really long time to eat it, and so he could be not annoying me for like his
last two hours, and I would maybe have a good memory of him.
I'm gonna, so I, a couple years ago I like took care of a dog that was on its last legs,
He was diabetic, blind, incontinent, so he wore diapers.
He looked like the Silent Hill dog.
He was straight up just like a skeleton.
With grey eyes.
That's rare for an old sick dog, they usually get fat.
Yeah.
No, he couldn't hold anything down.
But he couldn't see anything, he'd run into shit all the time, but he knew when you were
about to stab him with his insulin which made it very annoying to give it to him
which I had I had to like put his food down and then just stab him and then like
add water to the food because he would eat it so fast he would throw it up it
just yeah and throw it up and I was like when this dog dies I'm not gonna care
because I had him for like a year and I felt horrible when he died I was like so
the
dog that Joe was watching for a summer. His name was Mr. Dangle. Um, and I stayed over
there for a while. I was living in my car when I first moved to LA, because I had nothing
lined up at all. And then he was like, "Hey, do you want to come stay with me? I have,
I'm like dog-sitting this dog." And I was like, "Yeah, sure." And then he would work and I
would take care of the dog. And I fucking hated this dog. I had to put the insulin in him.
was blind and he would like snot all over me all the time and he was a pug and he
was I think 14 years old and when he would he would walk up to the couch and
he would just bark at the couch because he wanted to be on the couch but he
couldn't jump up himself so then I had to come pick him up while I'm watching
fucking succession and then he died like the summer after I took care of him the
entire summer and I literally it was like a it was like a good same dopamine rush
you get from smoking a cigarette. It was that exact same. I was like, "Oh my God. Oh my
God. Thank God that thing is not on earth anymore." That is an amazing feeling. I hated that dog.
I don't think you're very much of a dog person. I like Phil. He's my best friend, man. He's
the only thing I talk to all day. That is true.
I'll be sad when he dies, but the thing is people, and I'm not going to say what kind
of people, white people, okay? White people get it in their heads that a dog is anything,
a dog is just a dog at the end of the day, right? If you have to leave it in its crate
for three days, if you forget to feed it, it's not great. But at the end of the day,
it is a dog. This is not a baby, this is not a human. The dog has no, the dog can't feel
anything, it doesn't even exist basically. So who cares?
The moment you put it in your apartment, close that door, lock it up, it stops existing.
Yeah, it's gone.
It's gone.
He has no object permanence.
He doesn't know that I exist when I'm not there.
One day, here's how stupid a dog is, one day to them is supposedly seven days.
Right.
Wow.
So, who cares?
Because of the years.
So you can waste their time all you want.
I do, something that I do think every single day is I wish there was a dog prison because
I want to send my dog to dog prison.
But your dog is being dog juvie.
I guess so.
Yeah, you do have a puppy.
You can't hold a dog liable for anything they do before they're 2 years old.
Yeah.
Well, if they're hurting me, I will do it.
If a dog hurts you, that is your fault.
I'm sorry.
I agree.
One time I looked up, Phil like snapped at me one time
when I stepped on his foot.
And I looked up like an idiot.
I looked up like dog tried to bite me
when I stepped on its foot and it was like a,
like a Cora or something,
somebody asking the exact same question.
And the top answer with like a thousand million likes
was like, yeah, if you stepped on my fucking foot,
I'd try to bite you too.
(laughing)
I was like, oh yeah, I guess they,
I guess they feel pain and they have reactions.
I guess that's true.
- No, that's bullshit.
- A different time after the last dog,
I was taking care of a former bait dog
that I found on the street
I was trying to find like a place for it. A bait dog? Yeah like a like a Rottweiler that had its
teeth like ground down um so you know it was all bit up and shit and uh I was living with someone
that had a husky at the time and like they were fighting over a bone and like the the dog that I
was taking care of like took the bone and was kind of over it and I was like I fucking I got this this
dog so fucking stupid and old and I just got over the top of it and reached under
its mouth and just like knocked the bone away with my hand and it fucking just
bit me so hard. Of course. Yeah, my roommate was like, "Are you okay? Like you are bleeding. Like are you fine?"
I'm good. No, it's awesome. It's not a problem. It is awesome. Yeah.
it's a
Speaking of next week, speaking of next week, yes I am, speaking of next week, guys, say
goodbye to this disgusting space.
Are you moving next week?
I'm moving, not next week, I'm moving tomorrow.
Really?
Tomorrow is gonna be, tomorrow is literally like D-Day for fucking everything.
Tomorrow I'm moving, tomorrow I'm paying my deposit, tomorrow I'm signing the papers, tomorrow
the internet people come in to install the internet which is not a service that I
wanted but I'll take it but yeah tomorrow I'm fully moving out of here
which I'm so excited because my I think I've talked about about this before on
the stream on the somewhere I know but I've lost all contact with my my landlord
the lady yeah so right now our only like smoke signal to her right now is the
the fact that today's like the day to pay,
do pay rents due today and we're not gonna pay it
and we're hoping that she shows up at some point
either tomorrow or over the weekend.
- And sees that you're not there.
- Yeah, and she either sees that we're not there
or something happens and she gets in contact with me.
I'll be like, here are your keys, we are gone.
I'm not, you can try to charge me anything.
I won't give you any money.
I'm outta here.
- It's kinda awesome that like credit scores
don't exist in Mexico.
- That is cool.
- There's just violence.
they do. No they don't. You guys have a chili pepper scale out of 10. No they exist in some
capacity but not in the way that she would be able to influence it in any way I don't
think. Your landlord couldn't influence your credit score? Then you don't have credit scores.
There is a credit score yeah. I've been told that I've got credit by people before. That's
That's how it works.
There's a, you can get it.
Someone just knows you.
You have good credit, you have bad credit.
Yeah, Quan Credit just called him up, he texted.
You can get it now.
You can get it checked.
I don't know what the process is.
I never really checked it myself.
They check it when you're trying to buy a car, which I've done twice.
That's awesome, man.
I'm so happy for you.
Somehow I have really good, I used to have like a 480 credit score at one point, and
I have had overdue credit cards, maxed out credit cards for years, never paid them.
And then I got another credit card and for some reason just getting another credit card
made me have pretty decent credit now.
It's like 690 or something.
So having, from what I've heard, having multiple credit cards is really good for your credit
score.
What's really bad is cancelling a credit card.
Yeah, you're not allowed to cancel a credit card.
Yeah.
My credit score is 754.
That's really good.
You can do anything.
My favorite part, my favorite thing, I think I've talked about this a lot, but my favorite
thing about Rex's and his credit is the fact that he had a baby credit card for like years
and he couldn't do anything with his life when he got money because he just had such
a stupid credit card that all he wanted was to give him like a thousand bucks.
Oh yeah, you had like a thousand dollar limit.
Yeah, I would call them and they'd be like, you basically just have to lie to them because
they can't check how much money you actually make.
So you have to call them and be like, "Yeah, I'm expecting to make $3 billion next year.
Can I get a $10,000 credit limit?"
Wait, I should do that.
Yeah, you can just do that.
You can just lie.
You can lie, but it took you a while.
I think-
It did.
It did take me years.
I remember this because it was like for an entire year, like half a year, that I would-
One of my main talking points was where I was like, "Do you still have a baby credit
card?"
And he was like, "Yeah."
And I would just-
One time we were in the Airbnb and like the entire week of Airbnb took up my entire credit card
So I called my my company and I was like, hey
can I get like maybe a higher limit because I have to pay this card like every two weeks and
They were like no
Just no, let's check no
- Yeah, and then I called like a year later
and I was like, yeah, can I get a higher credit limit?
And they're like, sure, do you want four times
what the old limit was?
And I was like, sure, yeah, yeah, that sounds great.
- The limit was like one or 2,000 bucks.
- You should have tried maybe a British accent or something.
- Yeah, well, I ended up getting like an Indian guy
at the time it worked and I had a woman
at the time it didn't work.
So maybe she thought my voice was too unmasculine
wimpy and I didn't make enough money but an Indian man recognized my supreme
autism and knew that I make money. I think they want you to make a lot of
money. I think that they like stealing from you. The thing is broke
people don't, I mean as somebody who's been broke most of my life, broke
people do not pay credit cards. Right. You just don't you just don't pay it. Yeah.
Because there's nothing they're not gonna do anything what it goes to collections who cares
Yeah, it impacts my credit score. I'm not gonna buy a house for seven years. Anyway, I'm not gonna buy anything
I'll rent a car. I'll or just not have a car which is cool way cooler. I'll rent my house and
I'll order uber eats every day on a visa platinum card and then just fucking ignore it as soon as it hits the limit
yeah, I have a
The thing about credit is like you're only supposed to use like 30% of your credit limit
So if you spend like three thousand dollars a month, which is a lot of money
You should have like a fifteen thousand dollar credit
Is that true? You're supposed to have low credit utilization?
Under 30% if you go over 30% it's like it's a it's a negative against you
I think this is this is one of those unwritten rules that you don't really have to abide by
No, it's literally like it shows me on my thing. It has like a dotted line
It's like this is like and it's like a 30% and it says don't go over this. Yeah, it's like when I'm you know
What they say that they say that so they don't lose any money lending to you. Fuck it do it
Yeah, go over it buy a car on your just let that shit fly man. Just
Credit card let that shit fly by a big-ass TV
Well, my favorite thing about credit cards too is if you rack up too much credit card debt
You can open another credit card and then just move it over. I've done that. Yeah, I've done that with the same with
The same capital one. I did that with two different cards
I had a maxed out credit card that I had and they gave me a different credit card
Because I applied for it and then I just moved like half of it over to that. Yeah, I was like, all right, I'm good. I
I really love Dave Ramsey because he's like, "Do not ever take out any debt."
But the thing is, and they don't tell you this, debt is free money.
True.
It's how they invent money. It's free. It literally doesn't give it to you for free.
1%. He doesn't want you to know these kinds of tricks.
He's trying to keep people down by saying, "Pay your car bill. Pay your credit card."
"Pay your mortgage."
None of that shit matters, man.
Yes, take out more debt. It's free.
I love it.
Dude, I took out a crazy amount of money for my student loans. Like an amount that I would
be embarrassed if I had to... an amount that is so large that I don't even know what it
is because I don't want to open the website and look at the number.
Right.
Okay? But I just had to start paying my student loans back and they sent me the first bill
and it was like $170.
Yeah.
And I thought it would take me probably three lifetimes to pay it off at that rate.
So I'm like, "Ah, who gives a fuck?"
The only people that pay off their student loans are like lawyers and doctors.
Exactly.
I went to school for fucking...
I don't even know what I went to school for.
Yeah, you went to school for fucking comedy.
For fun.
Yeah, basically.
Yeah, I went to school for fun.
And I only went for two years too.
So they, it really is, who could possibly expect me to pay that back?
The fact that they were able to stop payments and nothing happened.
Yeah.
Just like stop charging interest, stop payments, do whatever.
That tells you it's completely fake.
They just don't expect anyone to pay it back.
I think we're getting on a dangerous territory here.
We're about to say that banks don't matter and the US is a fake country.
Let's move on to a more pure topic.
Nobody is more, nobody is more, um, okay here, beer talk. Sorry. The Kirin Ichiban compared to
the acai in the soju bomb is completely identical y'all. Cannot taste a single difference. It tastes
exactly the same. It tastes a little more soju-y because I think I put a little more soju in this,
but that's the only difference. I'm not going to chalk that up to the beer. I am so, so jealous
of you right now in an insane way.
You look really sad honestly.
You would probably hate the soju.
Me?
I've had soju before.
No, he would like soju.
I like soju.
It's sweet.
It's sweet and candy-ish.
It's sweet and delicious.
And he's the candy man.
He's Mr. Nintendo.
Wait, I think you're going to hate that.
Don't call me that by the way.
That's not me.
We never talked about this.
Remember this Rex?
He's Mr. Nintendo.
Nope.
He is Mr. Nintendo.
Okay, so this is something that none of you, neither of you were involved in at all.
This is a Brian and Alex thing.
I'm involved because I called you this.
You were not involved because you were not in the apartment there when this happened.
I will let Brian or Alex explain it, but it's such a stupid thing and I was just deemed this
by the entire group for no reason just because Brian said it and because I wanted to go to
the Nintendo store.
Well, it was because you wanted to go to the Nintendo store but also you were dominating
every Nintendo game, which is not a wrong thing to be doing.
Ah, there he is.
Look at him, he's in the chat, he's just listening, he's just spying on me.
Brian is my worst enemy.
What he's saying, I gotta go check in on Mr. Nintendo, see if he's getting power ups and
eating mushrooms.
I do like mushrooms on pizza.
Me too.
I kinda wanna get one of these mushrooms, they call it the chicken of the woods.
Have you seen this mushroom?
No.
It's extremely large.
And it apparently tastes like chicken.
you cook it with amino acids.
Does she know what the name of the mushroom is?
Chicken of the woods?
I don't think that's what it's called.
It's a colloquial term.
I want to look up chicken of the woods.
It'll come up.
Oh my god.
Jibyo did get so mad when I called him Mr. Nintendo.
It's a whole ass mushroom in your right.
I'm right about everything man.
Why is it called that?
It doesn't look like any of my moves.
Because of its taste and its texture.
I'm so smart.
- I'm so smart.
- Do you walk out into the woods
and just see a mushroom and eat it?
- Do foraging?
I don't know, I'm really scared of that
because every mushroom that you can eat
has a twin sister that kills you instantly.
- Yeah. - That is true.
- Isn't that also true for berries
and pretty much anything else in the woods?
- Yeah, every berry looks like a blueberry
but the blueberry's the only one that you can actually eat.
- There's a mushroom called beefstick fungus.
Okay, just two things.
There's one called beefstick fungus
It's really funny and it looks like a beef steak.
The chicken of the woods looks like pancakes.
So--
- It does.
- They should call it-- - It doesn't taste like pancakes.
- They should call it the pancakes of the mushroom.
- I got so jealous today when Noah sent a picture
of his pancakes.
Made me want pancakes so bad.
I'm not really, are you guys sweet breakfast people?
- I do like a sweet breakfast, but very rarely.
- I don't, I like eggs.
- It'll make me go right back to sleep.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- If I have a sweet breakfast.
I think a sweet breakfast is a Saturday thing.
I don't have anything to say.
Okay, like a weekend thing.
I can see what you're saying.
I don't know about Saturday.
I feel like Sunday.
I'm fine with what you just said,
which is surprising because it was so outlandish.
But a sweet breakfast
being a Saturday thing.
Who's weird on sweet versus savory?
Oh yeah, wait. What is your rule?
What is your... Sorry.
I just remembered this.
dinner rule? You'll look it up? I forgot what it was. I think it's sweet, salty, and then
either or for dinner. So you believe in a sweet dinner. You believe a sweet dinner is possible?
Yes, I think so. What is a sweet dinner? I'm looking up Jibyu3 sweet on, here we go. It's,
This is from August 24, 2021.
It's two years old.
Breakfast is sweet, lunch is salty, and dinner can be either.
Yeah.
That is a terrible take.
Yeah, it's so stupid.
That is a fucking atrocious take.
Name one sweet dinner.
Pancakes.
That's a breakfast, you fucking asshole.
Cake.
Chicken and waffles.
I don't eat chicken waffles for breakfast.
Yes you do.
I don't.
At brunch?
No.
I guess that has been on a...
That's a brunch menu.
I eat chilaquiles for brunch.
And that is sweet?
No.
Mole has chocolate in it.
That's sweet.
That's why you think that.
Because mole has chocolate in it.
I haven't had mole in so long.
- It's always delicious, man.
You need to get back on that.
- Well, the thing is, it's really funny, actually.
It's kind of like in the same vein of Mexican stuff
that we're talking about when we're into that one bar.
But mole can be, you can just buy it at the store
in this little jar, and it's really just commercialized,
and it's not, it's just like,
it's not autentico is what some would say.
And my girlfriend is really,
She feels really strongly about this.
She will not eat the store-bought mole.
So we haven't had mole a single time in this apartment.
- Well, that's 'cause it takes like 50 ingredients to make it.
- Yeah, real mole, it's a long process.
It takes a lot of ingredients to make.
It's not something that's made up here on the North.
It's more of like a center of the country type of thing.
So it's not something that I can easily acquire here,
which I'm kind of fine with.
I don't really care much about mole.
- I had it one week ago, man, and it was fucking delicious.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, Ridgewood Taco Factory.
- Was it authentico?
- It was very authentico, and it was delicious.
It was nice and spicy.
It was almost too spicy for me.
- Oh, dude, a good mole that blows out
your nostrils is amazing.
- It was amazing, too.
- I fully think, I said that when we were hanging out
at that really bad Mexican bar, but you guys--
- What bad Mexican?
I don't remember this.
we went to the pulqueria and it was not great.
- Oh yeah, that place sucked.
- Yeah, Noah ordered pulque and--
- They gave him vodka.
- They gave him vodka and then I made a scene about it
because I was texting my girlfriend about it
and I could hear the two guys speaking Spanish like,
did you give him pulque?
He was like, no, I didn't.
So the guy like quietly went back to Noah like,
oh wait, what did you want actually?
And Noah was like, oh, I wanted pulque actually.
So they gave him pulque and it wasn't good
and Noah said like, yeah, this is not good.
and my girlfriend was really adamant that that's not real pulque, that the real pulque is like
down in like Guadalajara or like some shit.
He told me that pulque, is it pulque where they make it with a raw chicken hanging over
it?
I don't know.
So some spirit he was talking about is made with a, they make like just normal tequila
and then while it's aging they hang a raw chicken over it?
Oh my god.
Which seems so disgusting.
That is nasty.
I don't know how it's made, but that day I realized that all my five or six friends that
I was hanging out with, they would love to do a fully Gringo Loco type of trip to any
one of my spots.
I want to go to Tequila.
I want to go there, I want to drink the tequila with a ladle out of the barrels.
They won't let you do that.
Or the clay pots.
Fuck you, bitch.
I paid for it.
During the tour they'll let you have really high alcohol content tequila, like it's really
clear, and you'll taste it and it'll just burn.
But look, this is like 80%.
I don't want to drink that.
That doesn't sound good.
That might burn tequila for me.
They're not going to let you drink it, they're going to let you take a taste.
But then at the end of the tour they do a tequila tasting and they give you several tequilas
us and it's really yummy.
All right, I'll go.
I'm going to book the trip.
I'm getting my passport next month.
I've just decided.
I have to go to Tampa, Florida.
This has been going on for seven months.
Nope, I'm going to get it.
Tampa, Florida is in the US.
I suppose you're right, but I've decided that that is why I'm getting my passport.
I'm going to get it before I go there.
Yeah.
Okay.
That sounds great.
Yep.
guys 19th and 20th with Adam Friedland go to Adam Friedland something I don't know
what his website is dot-com slash tour and go find the tickets there guys I've
been your host this has been another amazing episode of beers we drank we
have an amazing the cultural discovery with this soju bomb run out grab a soju
bomb and enjoy your weekend I love you good bye maybe in 20 minutes we do GWA
And maybe in 20 minutes we and that sounds like an amazing idea
That sounds like an amazing idea. I hadn't even considered this idea. All right
Goodbye, everybody. I'll see you maybe in 20 minutes. I don't know. Bye
Bye.