[Sipping]
[Burping]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer broadcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[Burp]
This is a journey into
[Muffled]
Bud Light.
Ha!
Food Ribbon!
Beer's we drank, motherfucker.
With Juvio, Caleb, and Rex.
Beer.
You couldn't hear this one.
This one was completely silent.
Okay.
Oh, my microphone smells bad.
It smells like a water fountain.
Oh, God.
Did you drop anything on it?
No.
It just smells like dirty hands.
Okay.
I'll let you just rip you real quick because I'm excited.
I'm excited.
because I just dropped it. It came with splash back. This is my final of my
bullshit beers that it's just whatever alcoholic thing that we have in our
fridge. So after this you're picking only heaters? After this I... For the next decade
plus of this podcast. I have to go outside and buy something actually
because this is... I was busy today. I was streaming. So I am drinking this Sandia
- A sandia white claw.
- Wow.
And guess, wow, this is crazy.
Guess what I just had before we hopped on?
- A sandia white claw. - A sandia white claw.
- Very, pretty close, a glass of sangria
from my local taco spot. - Oh, that's,
I don't think that's at all very, it's watermelon.
- So it has most of the exact same letters.
- Yeah. - Okay.
Maybe I agree. - It rhymes.
- And there was melon in it, so.
- Nice try. - And it's Mexican,
so you have been defeated.
- Why don't you go ahead?
- I have a
Lomza Piwojaznopin.
Doesn't that look good?
- In the Polish beers today, huh?
- Lomza Pinojaznopin.
- So what does that stand for?
- Well, it's a full-bodied beer,
and it was brewed in Poland.
Yeah, right.
Stands for crap beer.
Yeah, I really, really hope not.
So let's take a thing.
I think it's that's where like penis beer.
Yeah.
They drink.
Oh, no, it's drinking.
Please be a full bodied crap.
Oh, full bodied penis beer.
Yeah.
Oh, my God, that is so bad.
I've seen it again.
Well, yeah.
OK, it's better the second time.
I knew it would be.
It was just shocking coming from Sangria.
sangria, it's fruity, it's whiny. The guy, I love the guy who makes the sangria. This
place that I got the sangria from tonight, last time we were there, my wife went in to
grab the, like we order takeout from it a lot and I sit out with the dog and she runs
in and grabs the stuff and the food. And the owner of the place was sitting there doing
like some kind of paperwork at one of the tables. And my wife looked at me and I did
I was like, like I waved at her and then he, I guess, saw it.
And then looked right at me and went, Hey, like,
and then realized I wasn't waving at him and like stopped really fast.
And so I've been afraid to go back, but he wasn't there tonight,
but it made me laugh really, really hard.
That's good. That's, you know, the people, people nowadays,
they really wish they could become like the regulars and so they get like
recognized by the staff. You, you, you, you, you have that already.
You just have to go back in there and just say hi.
I'm the waver.
Yeah, next time you wave at him, he feels comfortable.
I think I just got electrically shocked by this microphone.
I have the microphone on my chin, and it just shocked me so, so bad.
Try touching it with your lips.
No, I'm scared.
Now I'm really, really scared to get anywhere near it.
No, kiss it real quick.
No, I'm honestly scared.
It hurts so bad.
No, but if you kiss it, it'll be fine.
Well, it may have actually just caught one of my little hairs
from my face in it, but either way, OK, did not feel very, very good.
OK, Rex, introduce your thing.
OK, so I have three things, only one of which is a beer.
I have no idea what this is. And it's huge.
This is called a study break.
OK, bat blast of Baja flavor.
Disgrace.
Any info that you can give us would be huge right now
as we try to uncover what this means.
It just says it's gluten free.
Oh, it's a wine based hard seltzer.
You got a wine cooler.
Apparently, I've never had a wine.
So big for a white color.
It's massive. It's wine color.
Usually they're usually pretty.
What's the ABV on the other side?
Six and a half.
Yeah, they're usually pretty low alcohol.
All right. Six and a half.
I mean, that compared to wine.
Show me the other two options.
OK, I have a
lavender lemonade, hard kombucha.
Love that.
I love that.
Kylo.
Yeah, looks very good.
And finally, I have a
Krabby Cake double.
That's the beer, right?
That's the one that's.
You actually can't be stopped by
buying fucking beers
that are made for children.
It's crazy.
Yeah.
You're buying Cocoa Melon beer.
Yeah, I would buy you.
I would buy Coco Melon.
Oh, my God, it'd be amazing.
And also, you know that these guys are not paying a licensing fee, right?
They're just putting Krabby Patty.
We could make a Coco Melon beer.
We couldn't. We should.
Breast Milk Stout Coco Melon beer.
Yeah, I'm to one of my I think I've maybe.
No, I don't think I've ever told this before, but I one time went over
to a friend of mine's house and her stepdad was doing like home brewing.
And he had a chalkboard that had all the brews he was working on.
and one of them was called Breast Milk Stout.
And I never asked him about it, but it really intrigued me.
- Yeah.
- I think that'd be funny if it actually was breast milk,
but I think it's one of those things
where it's just like a guy who makes a beard
and they just call it a fucking stupid bitch dog beard.
- I think he's a guy who kind of patterned
his whole stepdad, 'cause okay,
when you become a stepdad,
I think you have to have,
'cause you've never been a dad before,
So you didn't naturally grow into having like a dad's sort of style and personality.
I think that when you become a stepdad, you have to choose a persona
that is like usually a popular character from a piece of media.
And you have to be like, that is what I'm going to act like with my step kids.
And this guy chose Hank from Breaking Bad, Hank Schrader, D.A.
OK, who would you choose?
Huh? Who would you choose?
Me?
Yeah.
Stephen Crowner?
Probably Stephen Colbert.
No, that's not fictional.
Those are not fictional.
No.
Stephen Colbert's fictional.
I think I would choose Better Call Saul from Better Call Saul.
You would choose Saul Goodman?
Is he a stepdad?
No, no, it doesn't have to be a stepdad.
That's what I'm saying.
It's just a personality.
Yeah, you can just be a persona.
Yeah, so I would just turn into an insane lawyer who goes to jail.
I would definitely be Michael Scott.
I would be Michael Scott, no question.
Okay, I would be God.
You can't be God.
Okay, God, first of all, we said fictional character.
So, nice fucking try.
I'm not going to let that one fly.
Okay.
Second of all, it needs to be from popular media.
It needs to be singular.
Um, okay.
I'll just do better call Saul then.
Okay. Yeah, one of the...
You'll be Kim.
Kim would actually be such a hot...
If Kim was my step-mom.
My god bro.
I would be so scared of her.
Rex, I know, I think you know which one we would choose.
I don't know why you're pretending to not know.
Is it the Krabby Patty?
Yes.
Is it the Krabby Patty Double Deluxe?
Is it cake?
No, no, I think you should choose the wine cooler.
Because you've done enough of these.
I know, that's what I was thinking.
Yeah, do the wine cooler.
Honestly my real life vote was going to be on the Kygo beer.
The what?
- The Kygo beer, the purple one?
- Oh, the Kyla, the hard-cone beer.
- Kyla, he's trying to say--
- Kyka, yeah.
- Yeah, come on, man.
- I said Kygo, like the guy.
- I don't know who you're talking about.
- Pick a number between one and two.
- Just choose the wine cooler.
You want it and I want it, that's two against one.
- Wine cooler.
- There we go, it's unanimous.
What did you guys think that the Smash Brothers
announcer was saying when he said unanimous?
Wait, what?
You know, when they
when they when they win and he goes
unanimous.
Mm hmm.
I thought he said they're animals
because there's so many animals in the
game.
He never says that.
Yes, he does.
Also, not that many animals.
Well, there's Fox and Falcon.
And I was here and
there's so many animals compared to a
normal MMA card.
Well, yeah, of course, there's a lot
more animals.
Yeah.
Wait, what? Excuse me? I'm sorry. I missed this. I googled unanimous and I found the craziest
videos of all time.
You just googled unanimous?
I googled smash unanimous and some funny videos came up.
Oh god, I don't even want to see the funny videos.
This is not very good.
Really? That's disappointing. Yeah, my beer is really bad too.
It tastes like the worst Baja blast you've ever had.
That means it'll be a good episode because we aren't going to be focusing on this beer.
Although I saw somebody comment that they wish we talked more about beer.
I also saw that.
That's a funny thing.
I don't like, what do we know about beer?
Wait, well, you're allergic to this.
That is not a normal amount of burping for one sip of something.
That was fucked up.
That was so bad.
Okay.
Let's, let's go real quick.
Facts about beers. They make you burp.
They make you pee.
They definitely make you pee.
They make you drunk.
Sometimes.
If you drink, okay, caveat,
if you drink a lot, they make you
drunk.
If you drink a lot of anything, you
get drunk.
Yeah. Water.
Okay. That's to be disputed by
scientists. We don't really know that
right now.
Let's call one up then.
Okay. Do you know any scientists?
Bling bling.
Actually, no.
I think we could call Noah and he would know something about that, right?
True.
He'd make some YouTube video he saw.
Number four, they come in a can sometimes.
But they can also come in a bottle or a glass.
Or a Stein.
Next week I'm pulling up with the...
When you guys are in town and we do a real life BWD, can we get Steins?
Sure.
The German things with the lids.
I would love that.
Yeah.
I want one so badly.
I just bought a Das Boot, which is a--
Like the one that Badlands chugs out of?
Yep, exactly that.
Whoa.
Like the Mega Waves.
Will you chug out of it?
I'm not gonna, I don't think I can chug a beer.
I don't think you're a chugger.
Yeah, he's not a chugger.
I agree with you.
I'm not a chugger.
I've never chugged in my entire life.
I used to be able to chug, not anymore though.
Something happens when you--
- How old are you when you shotgunned a beer?
- Fucking 17 years old.
- Really?
- Well, 18.
- God damn, dude, I think-- - 19, 19, 19.
- Yeah, I think it's been two months for me.
(laughing)
- Well, you're in college.
You're a young boy and you're in college.
- I'm starting to feel old, man.
- Yeah. - I am old, dude.
- We're just getting old.
- Guys, I don't wanna talk about being old.
This is the episode where we're celebrating my life.
celebrating your life? Because it comes out on my birthday. It comes out on your
birthday? Wait, your birthday is soon? I knew that. You don't know where my birthday is? I'm a good friend but I don't
know people's birthdays. No, I think I don't hold a personal calendar. I know
one of my brother's birthdays. Yeah. You know, okay, I was exactly the same way.
I realized that I kept not knowing when anyone's birthday was. So I just
used my phone to keep track of people's birthdays.
That's smart. That's a thoughtful thing to do.
That is very thoughtful. I hate my birthday so I don't want to celebrate mine and I
definitely don't want to celebrate someone else's.
I will also skip two years. Last two years I've skipped my birthday. I've said no to having a
- Once you hit 21, there's no birthday worth celebrating.
- No, maybe 100.
- Yeah, big distance between those.
- I will celebrate my 100th birthday.
I will have some friends over for my 100th birthday.
- Yeah.
- I think that's completely ridiculous.
I think you're not enjoying life the way you're supposed
to be enjoying life.
- No, I am enjoying life.
I enjoy life every day.
- You know what that tells me?
Yeah, exactly.
You know what that tells me about you?
- You're an attention hog, that you need to have a whole day
- No I'm not.
- That's just for yourself.
- Yeah.
- Did I say that?
Did I ever say that?
- It's my birthday episode of podcast.
- Oh you did say this is my birthday episode.
- Well, this is, it comes out on my birthday
is what it said.
- It comes out on my birthday, it's my birthday episode.
- And it will be called birthday boy by anonymous decision.
- Yeah, 'cause you named the episodes.
- You do, yeah, which is by the way,
starting to piss me off a little bit.
That everything is, it's basically your little journal
at this point. - Yeah, you're always blogging,
dude, fucking start a medium. - Me and Rex,
we want some shine, okay?
Why is this show, here's me recording my conversation
with my friends, and here's me saying my little blurb
about it, oh, oh, they were so weird this week.
Shut the fuck up, okay?
- Fucking birthday bitch. - Okay, we're three
equal brothers. - That's right.
- Okay, for my birthday, you guys can write the title
and description of the episode then.
- Fuck you, bitch ass, for your birthday,
I'm getting you a new car. - No, do some work, ho.
- Yeah.
- Now it's my job.
- Yes, it is your job.
- It's literally your job.
- Okay.
I think you guys are being a little bit unreasonable.
Number one.
- Unreasonable?
We're putting you in a home.
I'm done with you.
We're putting you in the senior center.
We're getting rid of you right now.
- That's not funny.
That is not funny to say that.
- We're getting you out of here.
No, don't say that.
No way he's going to the Mexican forest.
(laughter)
This shit is dropping off the one Mexican guy I know.
This was the senor de santo.
Yeah, you guys just sit in there, just hammer nails into the same piece of sheet rock all day long.
Do OSHA violations.
(laughter)
He's served beer with breakfast.
scaffolding you've ever seen.
And fall off.
[Laughter]
Oh, that is funny.
There's a bunch of people in wheelchairs, but it's all just because they're too drunk to walk by 2pm.
[Laughter]
Oh, I guess none of this is funny.
These past couple minutes have not been funny.
This is a volleyball game where the net's 7'4" tall.
[Laughter]
They've got those like play school basketball hoops that are like...
Oh no, I'm kidding though.
They've got a little thing in the back of like...
I'm told of you, I'm told of both of you combined.
Pick up trucks.
In the back so they can ride them around.
Have you guys seen the video where the guy picks up the like Mexican dudes from Home
Depot and he takes them to Disneyland?
Yes.
- It is the best video ever.
(laughing)
Where they're like, I feel like that,
if Mr. Beast did that, so many people would be like,
oh, but just give the people money,
like they just want money.
Those guys do not want the money.
They wanted to be there so badly.
- Yeah, dude, they've never had a day off.
- They wanted to be at the fucking Disneyland so badly, dude.
- I think it's funny that they just got to spend
like a day at Disneyland with like the other two guys
that they just go do contract work instead of like their families.
Yeah, I was. But also, can you imagine like guys like that?
If they went to Disneyland with their kids and their wife, they work so hard.
I thought about this while I watched the video. I was like, they work so hard.
The only way they would go is if they like saved up money to do it.
They would be so worried about if their kids were having fun or if their wife was
having fun, they would not be riding.
Or the kids would keep asking for shit.
Exactly. They would not be riding any of the rides.
it would just be there.
Like it was nice that they didn't bring their kids, honestly.
Yeah, 100%.
These guys just got to like go on Space Mountain and forget that they had
like any kind of responsibility in their lives.
Yeah.
It was a really wonderful video.
I thought the best part of the video was at the end when, where like the guy
who's making the video like prevents like any like snootiness, like being like,
Oh, well, why do you, why do you take a day off with them?
They could have really used the money.
Could you just like give them like a thousand bucks each?
- Yeah.
- So that you--
(laughing)
- Don't worry about it.
- Yeah, but I'm thinking that maybe we'll do that with you
when you land in New York.
I'm gonna talk really slowly to you
and tell you that we're going to--
- Topgolf. - Houston.
- Mountain.
(laughing)
- We're not even going, we're just going
to a different city.
We're going to Philadelphia today.
- A little bit.
- Yeah. - You see.
I've never been.
- Oh, oh, see.
- You've never been to Philadelphia?
It's pretty nice.
I like Philadelphia.
It's a lot better than Boston, actually.
- I like traveling,
but I don't know where I would like to travel in the U.S.
that's a place that I've never been.
- Cities you've been to.
- I've been to Texas, I've been to--
- Yeah, cities.
- L.A., and I've been to New York.
You know, the cities like San Antonio, Houston.
- I would say the big ones to go to,
you should definitely go to an East Coast beach town,
like in Florida or like in Outer Banks in North Carolina.
You should definitely go New Orleans.
- Yeah.
- You should go to Chicago.
- I've never been to New Orleans.
- Oh, but Chicago.
- You should go.
- I did not like Chicago.
- Oh yeah, you haven't.
- He did go to Chicago.
- You didn't like Chicago?
- I did not like Chicago at all.
- Oh, Chicago's so nice.
Did you go to the lake?
- No.
I mean, I stayed like in the outskirts of the city.
- And then you were disappointed it wasn't edible?
- The bean is whacked it.
I thought the bean was cool.
- There's a lot of like--
- He would like it more if it was a refried bean.
- The thing is so--
(laughing)
- Enough racist jokes on my birthday.
- We already did Senior Works Center,
we don't have to do more than that, right?
That one's probably the limit of racism
we can get away with.
I think that so much of US tourism though is like,
whoever's visiting has to be somewhat interested
in like the colonial era of US history
for like this place to be nice, unless it's very beautiful.
So like Seattle or like a lot of parts of California,
they're just nice.
But if you're on the East coast,
a lot of it is just fucking muggy, disgusting shit
and like highway.
And so for it to be interesting at all,
there needs to be half demolished buildings
that used to be Paul Bunyan's outhouse or whatever.
Like that's the fun part.
That's the only nice part about Boston
is that they have Paul Revere's house.
And like, I still need to go to Boston.
I mean, you're right, but.
Boston is such a shit city.
I love it, but the bars close at one o'clock.
They, uh, even though it's like a very young city, it's more expensive
than anywhere except San Francisco.
Um, the food is terrible.
Who gives a, a lobster roll?
That's not impressive to me that you put the most expensive meat possible
on a fucking hot dog.
Yeah, like that's not a nice meal.
Yeah.
We said you haven't been to New Orleans.
You should definitely go to New Orleans.
We should go to New Orleans.
We should go to Vegas.
We should.
Yes.
We should do a Calypso root strip and go to North Carolina.
You guys would love North Carolina.
Yeah, I think I would.
Yeah.
It's so, so nice.
I went to meet your entire family.
I didn't realize how nice North Carolina was really until, I mean, I guess that's
everybody's story, but until you move away and then you're like, oh yeah, I was
like three fucking miles from like one of the nicest beaches on the East Coast.
Then I just never went because I was watching TV.
Yeah.
Which I have with North Carolina.
Do you have that with Arizona at all?
Where you're like--
- Not really.
- Not really, 'cause there's not that.
You just get like--
- It's like, oh, you're two hours from the Grand Canyon.
You know?
- Well, okay.
Have you been to the Grand Canyon?
- Of course.
It's beautiful.
- What was your reaction when you went to the Grand Canyon?
- A couple seconds of silence to take it in.
- Yeah.
- And then being like,
"Man, I can't believe I have to drive two hours to get home."
(laughing)
That is, I'm sure, the difference between living near it
and traveling to it.
We went on tour, me, Pierce, Patrick, and Cameron,
30 seconds in, all four of us are bawling, crying,
looking at the Grand Canyon, like,
"Oh my God, it's so beautiful,"
and doing that for an hour, and then walking away,
and all feeling a little self-conscious
because of how gay it was that we all cried
as soon as we saw the Grand Canyon.
- It is really beautiful.
I mean, I do want to do like--
It's not even beautiful, it's scary.
It's terrifying.
Yeah, like natural parks and shit like that.
Like, you know, like big wonders of the world type shit.
Before you leave California, you should go to Yosemite.
Yeah, I need to do that.
Yeah, Yosemite's very, very nice.
So there's a lot of like really beautiful--
Big mountainous, where's Occapitan?
Occapitan is in Yosemite and Half Dome.
They're both in Yosemite.
I saw some TikToks about that movie Free Solo yesterday
and I was about to re-watch it but I fell asleep.
That's a crazy movie.
- Dude, my problem with these guys who are free climbing,
you're doing it for extra points,
just fucking plug the piece of metal into the rock.
Like, why are you being such a,
like, oh no, I don't need,
you're better than a piece of rope
that keeps you from falling to your death.
You're too cool.
- They are too cool.
- Just put it in. - I think that is cool.
- No, I think that is cool. - They're too adrenaline, dude.
They love risk.
then do drugs like every other person.
- Yeah, the amount of risk you would get
from free climbing a mountain is the same amount of risk
you get from doing cocaine in Brooklyn.
- Pretty much.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
Yeah, cocaine is a bad drug, man.
I don't think I will ever do it again as long as I live.
You know what it is?
It's too pitiful of a drug to be doing.
- It's embarrassing a little bit.
It really is. That is an embarrassing drug. If you do,
if you like do cocaine, that's just embarrassing.
It's because it's like a,
like it feels like you should be doing it out of like the tube that holds
Corella DeVille's cigarette. Like you should, it's not like a,
there's nothing cool about doing it. Like it's very dainty.
I used to snort crushed up Adderall out of a $1 bill, which is like the most
pathetic.
That's so awesome.
A $1 bill specifically.
A $1 bill.
Because people will do cocaine and be like, "It has to be out of a $100 bill."
And you're sitting there with Adderall.
A $1 bill that was fucked up.
Yeah.
Like, if you had it, you would have done it out of a Canadian loonie, like less than a
dollar.
Yeah.
Just a coin.
Yeah, a coin.
Yeah, I remember our house got broken into and my rolled up dollar bill was just sitting
on my desk, dyed blue and orange from all the powder.
And the cop was just like looking at it, being like,
should I do something about this?
- He should have.
- He should have, he should have killed me.
- Yeah, he should have shot you in the spot.
- I think honestly, I'm coming, in my old age,
in my late 20s, I'm coming to the realization
that the only good drug is nicotine.
- Yeah. - It's the only good drug.
Every other drug will keep you back in every way.
And nicotine will make you soar higher
than you ever have before.
- There's a, the big thing right now is like,
among like pseudo intellectual, like nootropics guys is nicotine gum.
Yeah, no, no, I know. I know all about this. This is not even pseudo intellectuals.
A lot of like academics do nicotine gum and they've never smoked a cigarette in
their lives. Yeah. Cause it's like cigarettes obviously bad for you.
Vaping obviously pretty bad for you. Well,
this is the funny thing about nicotine. Nicotine is technically good for you.
It's like prevents Alzheimer's. It's like neuro protective or whatever.
it helps your brain in a lot of ways.
- So nicotine gum just like good for you then?
- Yeah, I mean the only downside to nicotine gum is,
you can definitely get addicted to it.
Yeah, that's the only downside.
- Yeah, but it's the same with cancer, right?
- And it's expensive.
- It is very expensive.
I was thinking today about getting some of those Zen packs,
the ones you pack your lip with.
- Yeah.
- That looks so much fun.
- I know, dude.
You got to make your shit look like insane.
Yeah.
You don't think I look good with that?
No, that looks stupid.
Also, you're in New York.
Whatever.
No one does that in New York.
Who gives a fuck?
The only people who do that are like people in like rural America and like anyone like
northern Europe.
I want to be, I want to bring that here though.
If my dad did not chew tobacco and spit into Pepsi cans that I accidentally drank growing
up, I would definitely do chewing tobacco.
That is by far the coolest way to do tobacco.
It's so disgusting.
It's so like you're spitting all the time like a horse.
I love that.
Yeah, I used to be homies with this like vet who he just would bring over like an ammo
can like a huge ammo can and then just like just spit into it all day on our patio because
he couldn't do it where he lives.
So he just come to our house and sit on our patio for like 10 hours and do it.
Have you guys ever heard Chad's story about how he did?
tobacco the first time when he was like 16 years old and he worked at a grocery store
and like one of his co-workers sold him chewing tobacco and he got like the one with the highest
nicotine and basically put the entire thing in his mouth.
Oh dude.
And he was driving home and he passed out while he was driving and like.
Oh my god.
Like woke up he was like he was like on the side of the road just like passed out in his
car.
His car just like slowly came to a stop.
Oh my god.
- Oh my God. - He like threw up
and then got home and he was like past his curfew
and his mom was sitting on the front porch
and he like walks up, she's like,
"Where have you been?"
And he just shits his pants.
(laughing)
- Oh man.
That's brutal.
- It's so funny, first time you ever do any tobacco at all.
You just ruined your fucking life.
(laughing)
- Yeah, he could have just fucking died.
- I love him.
- Yeah, I'm thinking.
- We should have him on sometimes.
he's got so many stories like that.
- Yeah, well when we're in New York,
we can do it in a trip. - Oh yeah, true.
True, that's a great idea.
- By the way, where's he gonna stay?
Is he staying like at one night?
- Yeah, he's staying like one night.
I think he's getting a hotel.
Maybe we'll--
- He should just like stay with us.
- Yeah, yeah, true, he probably should.
- Yeah. - We'll figure it out with him.
- Yeah, anyways, he could have died,
and that's why. - Yeah.
I'm trying to, I don't think I ever,
the only time I've ever had like nicotine poisoning
When I first moved here, I smoked Marlboro Reds for like one week.
And one night we were playing Warzone and I smoked.
I went up to my roof between games and I smoked like
two of them back to back.
Yeah. And I sat on my roof for an hour
and I got a bunch of discord messages from you guys like, where did you go?
I was just sitting on my roof just like, OK, so this is how I die.
I die from smoking two cigarettes and
Starving to death because it does make you feel awful.
It's the sickest you will ever be.
Yeah. Yeah.
Cigarettes will really fuck you up.
I grew up with a smoke.
Southern cuts, Marlboro, Southern cuts.
And I never even heard of that smoke like smoke fire than one time,
like in a row.
I just felt so fucking sick.
Just like dying, just like laying on the ground.
Yeah, it's just what you want.
You feel like hot, you have to get a cold ground on your back.
Yeah.
Sometimes when I vape too much, I'll like lay in bed and have the spins.
I love that though.
I miss that so badly.
How would the, what?
The spins like the world is spinning.
I remember I, I used to, when I would vape, I'd wake up and I would wait like 30
minutes before I first vaped to get like kind of accustomed to what it was like
having no nicotine in my body, be like, "God, this sucks.
"I hate this.
"Waking up feels so bad."
And then I would hit the vape
approximately 600 times straight.
And then lay back down and feel like I was in,
like Crimson and Clover would start playing.
I felt psychedelic 'cause the fan was moving so fast.
Oh my God, what an amazing drug.
- Truly.
- Every day we talk to you, you go,
"I just wanna get into vaping so bad."
and you always talk about it like it's a new thing,
but you've been like this for the past two years.
- Like I wasn't addicted to it for two years,
for a long time.
I still have a--
- You have a very addictive personality.
You always have to be addicted to one thing in your life.
- I'm addicted to working out right now.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, that's my current addiction.
So that's how you conquer having an addictive personality,
I think.
- Yeah, what do you think is gonna be the next thing though?
Coming up?
- Probably fucking smack, yeah.
(laughs)
- My pills.
- I could see you as a pill head.
- Yeah, me too.
- Your head kinda looks like a pill.
- It does look like a pill.
- Sorry, I didn't mean that.
- What if I showed you the top of my head,
there's a perfect line right down the middle.
(laughs)
- It says like PR 20.
- Yeah.
Exactly the weight of my head.
60 pounds.
Two pounds BR.
Bro.
My head is definitely 60 pounds.
I think I carry most of my weight in my head.
I did look at, I was with somebody the other day and I, we, I got,
I was, we were hanging out with them and then I got into the car and I told my
wife, I was like, I think that my head is literally twice the size of that guy's
head.
And she was like, what?
I don't think your head is that big.
I have a giant head.
We should take measurements on Caleb's head.
I have a giant fucking head.
Anybody who's seen me, if you're listening to this
if you've seen me at a live show, you know
that the only reason it didn't look like I have
the biggest head you've ever seen is because
Patrick's head is somehow even bigger.
[laughter]
I have a big fucking shitty head.
It's funny how Patrick looks like a little doll.
Yeah.
Yeah. He looks so small.
- Moonish proportions.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I think we should--
- His eyes are like this big, it's crazy.
- Yeah, we should definitely measure your head
when we're in New York.
We need to like weigh it-- - Feel free, man.
- We need to measure it.
- We'll weigh my head, I'm fucking down.
I bet my head weighs more than anybody except Julio's head.
Julio has an even bigger head than Pat.
- I do think I have a big head as well.
- But yours doesn't stand out as much
because you're just big.
- Right.
- Yeah, I guess.
I guess it like fits. - You're taller, yeah.
If I was your size, if I was your height,
maybe my head would be normal.
But on my body, on my skinny little way fish frame,
pretty much like that.
- Your cute little body.
- My cute little feminine body.
- I think I'd still look weird if I was bald.
I think if you were tall and bald,
you would still look weird.
- Man.
- I think Caleb looks normal.
And I think he looks great with a hat on for some reason.
much better it is awful that I look so much better with a head all than having
my body nobody everybody says oh man no you actually rock it shut the fuck up
shut up dude would you say that to a little person a dwarf you actually say
so good as yeah you actually look really good short and small with a disability
No!
Oh, hang on guys, I'm getting my other beer, my second beer.
I opened mine by the way, I opened my second beer.
This Bud Light with Lime.
This is a classic, this is one of my favorite drinks ever.
One of my favorite drinks ever is a Tall Boy Bud Light with Lime.
I have so many amazing memories.
And just thank you for supporting the Bud Light Corporation.
They need it, bro.
They need it.
This is one of my favorite, I hate to say it,
it's one of my favorite beers of all time.
- I got my second beer.
- You, I just saw you pick that back up.
What happened?
You thought you had two and you don't.
- It's all good, let's move on.
What do you guys think about basketball?
- I think there's like two hoops
and like 10 guys on the floor
and they go back and forth.
Average score between like 80 and 120.
- I was taken to a Knicks game the other day
as a wedding gift.
I was taken to a Knicks game
and those are.
The worst fans
in live sports,
Knicks fans, Knicks fans are fucking atrocious.
I get maybe it's the playoff thing
because it's all like rich people buying these tickets.
Yeah, they are so rude and unfriendly.
No. I had this fucking, I had an Israeli guy tell me as I like walked, I have to pee a lot, okay?
Sue me. I peed a couple times. And as I'm sitting, I am halfway through the row. So I'm like, "Hey,
can I get in?" Everybody's standing up. He stands up and he says, "Yeah, that's your last time
though." And I was like, I said, "What the fuck are you talking about?" He's like, "Well, I just
I just don't wanna sit up again.
I was like, if I have to piss, I'm gonna go pee.
And he's like, (mumbles)
- How far into the game was this?
- I was like, was he serious,
or was he just doing it in that way people do
where they just say something?
- People in New York City are just so rude.
I was talking about this today with somebody.
Everybody here is so unbelievably rude
for no reason at all
because they did not grow up Christian.
Yeah. Right.
This is the truth.
And they grew up Jewish.
Or anything.
But if you grew up Christian, you were taught,
like me and Noah, we're very good boys.
We're polite. We're courteous to strangers.
Well, you are scared of everyone.
You're scared of the world.
No, no, no. I'm sweet to people.
That's the difference. I will be sweet to people.
I will go out of my way for my fellow man.
And people in New York City, they will shit on your face.
They were shit in your,
and I always thought that was a myth.
I was like, oh, it can't be that bad.
No, it's terrible.
It's the same thing in Boston though.
It really is, I think Catholics are just wrong.
They are wrong people.
- I think people always say this,
but I've never actually encountered this.
People say that about people in Paris.
People say this about people in New York.
I've never really encountered a rude person.
- Yeah, I don't think people have been
particularly rude to me, but I also don't stand up to people.
- I will say Los Angeles people are more rude
in Los Angeles than New York.
So I haven't really experienced it.
When I lived, I mean also, that's because you have a nice head of hair and you look sweet.
I think I have a really, really off-putting look to me when I walk around.
That is true.
People, yeah.
I walk around, I have a bald head, I have my mean dog, I'm short and squat.
People think that I'm just ugly and going to attack them.
And so they have to act offensively.
Yeah, I didn't mention the white thing yeah of course it's basically the greatest in order to be white new york city these days yeah am i right yeah.
What's the record sounds like that that energy hill which is just bring sin people you want to talk to him and shares stuff with them.
Yeah, he does look sweet. He's the perfect combination of a man and a woman.
That's right.
So people of all...
Wait.
People of all genders and sexualities want to talk to him.
Yeah. They also know that I'm an easy mark.
Yep.
Yeah, I can see that.
- Yeah, like I remember when we went to like some CVS
in Times Square, some homeless guy was like,
"Hey man, can I have 10 bucks to get a hero
at the hero stand?"
I was like, "Yeah, that, yeah, for sure, man.
Here you go."
- You really do just have a friendly face.
Nobody's ever asked me for money like that.
- Yeah.
- I think I really just, people see me and they're like,
"Okay, I loved you and this is England,
but I do not want to talk to you."
- I remember-- - Can I just keep
walking around?
When we went to the Noguchi Museum and we took the train back,
there was like this like dude that came on and he was like,
you know, I'm a Muslim, but, uh, I fuck with the Jews.
And he like looked directly at me.
He's like, and the Chinese and the Mexicans, I fuck with all y'all.
Yeah.
He realized he was looking right at you while he said,
yeah, Chinese and Mexicans.
Yeah.
- No, and then he looked at Annie and Julio.
- Also me and Annie.
He just came into our group saying all that shit.
And we were still like, "I don't have any money."
Sorry, man, nothing on me.
- Dude, it kills me that I'm the white guy
in our four-person group.
- I know. - Yeah.
- I gotta change something. - Well, someone has to be.
You think you could get the transracial surgery?
- I don't know which, I mean, of course I could, rich,
but I don't know which race I would switch to.
I think you should do Puerto Rican.
Puerto Rican is the obvious choice for me.
I would say. It is.
I would say I'm--
It's either Puerto Rican or Brazilian.
I would say I have 40% of what they need
to do Puerto Rican.
Yeah. Yeah.
I think-- You should get a skull tattoo.
But like--
Like a Raiders tattoo.
Oh yeah.
A friend of mine has a, he's such a genius.
He's Puerto Rican actually.
He got, he started balding
And so he shaved his head and he got a gorilla,
a gorilla tattooed right on the top of his head.
And so now you have no idea where his hairline starts
'cause he has a giant black tattoo in the middle of his head
that goes past his hairline.
So he can grow his hair out.
He's like balder than me, but you would never know.
- I don't think that's smart.
I think it's painful. - It's pretty smart.
- Your head looks weird for the rest of your life.
- Especially for a poor- - I mean, your head's
gonna look weird no matter what.
- He told me, I was like, "Dude, just shave your head."
And he was like, bro, you don't understand
what it's like to be a balding Puerto Rican guy.
- True. - I was like, oh yeah,
I guess that's probably a little different.
For a white dude, it's just kind of expected.
- Right.
- Well, because like they do this,
like perfect lines and they're doing one of these,
the Drake swoop in their hair and stuff.
- Everyone's a bald.
- I don't have that, you know?
Like I have no, there's no culture
of like white guys with hair.
- We have to break this myth of,
there had never been a single bald person.
Every time there's a bald person,
there has to be like a thing.
We need to break out of this.
- It doesn't have to be a thing, it's sad.
- No, it's not sad.
- I live in, I probably live in the lowest social caste
that you can possibly live in in the United States.
Yeah, bald white guy.
Bald white guy under six feet, yeah.
With a big ass head, a small penis,
and basically the worst fashion sense,
and an ugly wife and a dumb dog.
Yeah, and you're gay.
I live in the, yeah, and I'm gay too.
I live in the lowest possible,
there should be a shrill about me,
like everything should be catered to me at this point.
Yeah. Yeah.
- I think, maybe not right now,
but I think someone could write a movie about your life.
I think you could be a movie star.
- That would be one of the worst movies ever made.
- No.
- My life has been so boring.
I've lived in three places in my entire life.
- It would be a comedy.
- Yeah.
- A comedy about a guy who's,
has the worst--
- Like a Forrest Gump type thing.
- Yeah.
- So you think I'm retarded?
(laughing)
You can't say that to somebody.
You can't say that they can make a Forrest Gump
about your life, you'd think I'm retarded.
(laughing)
Come on, dude.
- I think they could.
- No, the main character of the Forrest Gump movie
would be Patrick, and you would be the guy
that says-- - Jenny.
- Bubba Trump.
- Yeah, you would be Jenny.
- Bubba Gump.
- Bubba Trump.
(laughing)
- And then you almost said Bubba Gadoosh.
Bubba Trump Shrimp Company?
- The Bubba Gump, yeah, that'd be--
- That'd be fire.
- You're that guy. - Shrimp at Hotel Company?
- Yeah.
cheaper hotels and golf courses.
Yep.
I'm really excited for him to come back.
He's going to win.
I think I'm going to walk into my wife's work where she works at like a really,
she works at like an upscale, upscale like store with like young professional
owners. I think I want to walk in, uh,
in like a full MAGA drip.
I have like a blacks for Trump hat and like airbrushed,
airbrushed true ease with his face on him and shit.
I just be like, what the fuck is up?
I'm her husband.
You know how like, uh, you gotta wait like seven years getting
ducted into the hall of fame.
Yeah.
Like sports.
It's like, if he wins again, that's another like 10 years.
We have to wait for the Trump hat to be okay to wear.
Cause you know, for sure that our kids will be wearing it.
Like it's the funniest shit ever.
Yeah, dude.
Like it's a Reagan Bush shirt.
- Yeah, exactly.
But if he wins again,
then we just set that back eight fucking years.
- Yeah, you're 100% right.
- I think we, as a group, me and you,
we are like a year out of getting MAGA hats
and just wearing them as a joke.
- I would not wear a MAGA hat.
I gave a hat to Patrick
'cause it looked too much like a MAGA hat.
- Really? - The boss hat?
- And then he wore it a lot.
- The boss hat? - No, no.
No, it was just like red,
it was just a red hat with white lettering on the front.
look just like from far away look just like a MAGA hat.
Yeah, well, that's that was such a funny thing when the MAGA hats
first came out was people making like MAGA hat knockoffs and it's
like it just looks like the hat.
Yeah, exactly.
I'm going to get real close to see the difference.
My swastika has the word not right in the middle of it.
That's what I always thought was so funny.
There was like you ever seen those pictures of people who get
like a tattoo of like a swastika with like a like a crossed out
like anti sign on it.
Yeah, bro for for five minutes, but while he was switching ink colors,
you had a swastika tattoo,
which is dope.
That's what I would do if I went to when I go to prison.
Yeah, swastika.
And when I get out, when you get to like big nose.
Just keep putting it off, getting the second tattoo.
Yeah, I have a headache.
I don't know about the money for the deposit.
Yeah, that's completely wrong, guys.
We shouldn't joke about that.
Did I ever tell you about the guy who...
The first tattoo I ever got, I was getting tattooed by the guy.
And he was like...
He was a friend of a friend and he was doing it super, super cheap.
He was like an apprentice at this place, really terrible tattooer.
And he's tattooing me and I'm like, dude, what's...
I'm just like an idiot 18-year-old.
And I was like, what's like the craziest thing anyone's ever asked you to tattoo?
And he's like, man, I won't lie to you, man.
A couple of weeks ago, some guy comes in and he asked for SS bolts on his arm.
And I was like, dude, what?
And he's like, yeah, dude, crazy.
But bro, you know, 80 bucks is fucking 80 bucks.
So I did that.
I was like, what?
Yeah.
He was, as he was tattooing me, I found out that he had done SS bolts like one week ago.
Damn, that's crazy. He did the same tattoo a week later?
Yeah, well, I knew that he was good at them, so that was nice. He had practiced before.
He felt more comfortable, yeah.
Yeah, exactly. I was like, "Whew!" I was sweating bullets until that point.
That was at least a second time's a charm, right?
What was your first tattoo?
Obviously, I don't have tattoos, but I remember being at the forefront of the fashion forums,
And the before the undercut had a name coming in.
Say that ever again.
Yeah.
You know, before, like people knew how to do the Macklemore haircut.
Still called the Hitler Youth and bring you to photos of fucking Nazi boys.
Yeah.
Can you give me this?
And then they just fuck it up because they don't know how to do it.
And they're kind of looking at you funny.
Yeah.
That's so dope.
My first tattoo is a heart.
To answer your question, it was a heart with the word Nana in it.
on my legs from my grandma.
Me and my brother got matching tattoos.
That's beautiful.
It's a very sentimental, meaningful tattoo to me.
I'm gonna get a matching tattoo of that,
but it's gonna say beer.
And also, I think that guy went to jail for like,
he like, it was in a road rage accident,
like pulled out an AR-15 or something.
Like he had some crazy charge. That's fine.
That's understandable.
Against them.
He's a good guy though. That's fair.
Yeah, he's a very nice guy.
People are so funny because they think that the impulse of every person in
America is not to just murder someone when they inconvenience you slightly.
I don't have, I don't have that at all.
I was talking today about that with somebody.
I have, I am so, I've never honked in my car and I drive all the time and people
would drive crazy.
I will never honk.
No, of course not.
Why would I do that?
That's so, I'm so sensitive to the idea
that somebody is going to get out of their car
and shoot me in the head.
That I will never ever, I've seen too many videos.
- I think that should make it legal for you--
- A very legal cuck state thing to think
that someone won't murder you for cutting them off
in traffic. - Exactly.
None of these people who do this shit in New York City
have ever lived in somewhere where every fucking person
has a gun.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
I think it would make it legal if someone's going slow.
I was like leaving a parking lot at the mall in LA
and someone like was just driving like a fucking asshole.
And I was like, they need to put guns in every car here.
They would not drive like this
if they could be in danger of being shot.
I wish I could shoot that fucker.
- That is kind of like the like Southern hospitality thing
is fully just that you assume every single person has a gun.
- And is going to shoot you.
- Yeah, so you try to be as nice as possible to them.
Exactly, that's kind of a nice way to live your life, right?
And then and they're probably assuming you have a gun to which you do.
Yeah, of course.
I have seven on you.
I have one of the ones that has the giant like like see through magazine
that goes fucking four feet out of the Glock.
Yeah, the double extendo.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
That's the thing, guns are fucking fun.
Why would you want if you?
Yeah, I, I want to get a show one.
You've never shown we should go while you're here.
Now that I have, uh, now that we have an, uh, like an above ground office,
that's like legally a commercial space.
I think that we can get a shotgun for the office in New York city.
Yeah.
We, at least we can apply it, which I would get, honestly, if I knew that Patrick
was never going to be in that building.
Like I know that that was just like a recipe for disaster
in such a crazy way that I just can't do it.
This is why a bunch of tasters.
You just taste.
No, that's I'd walk in, he'd be tasing his balls passed out.
Like, it's just not a good idea.
I talked about like when my house got broken into
like when I was in college and I was friends with that like vet.
And he found out like the next day and he came over with a duffel bag,
plop it down on our kitchen counter, unzip that shotgun.
AR-15, two glocks.
He's like, everyone in this house needs a gun right now.
It's like they stole like a TV.
Yeah, he just gave it.
He lent it to us for about a month in case someone tried to come back.
I was like, I'm going to shoot someone over a fucking pair of beats.
That's it. Yeah, that's the thing.
When it comes to if it.
Yeah, I don't think that I would want to own a gun
because I think your instinct is always...
To shoot yourself.
If some... Well, of course, of course. One bad game of Valorant,
I'm upping the stick directly into my mouth. But I think also, if I lived in a state that's like
just... You can have a gun wherever, like Florida or something. If somebody is coming in to take
$1600 worth of electronics.
I'm not I hope to God I do not have a gun
because I will freak out and probably kill them and then myself.
Right. Because I'll kill him.
And I go, oh, my God, I just killed some fucking random homeless guy
who wanted a Samsung OLED TV.
He took my phone.
Exactly. I'm going to be on the news as the guy who just killed
some fucking random kid.
No. And then I would kill myself.
So I think it's probably if I didn't have like a really...
I honestly think there's almost no reason for me to have a gun, actually.
Yeah.
The more I think about it, the more I think that I just am not...
I just should not have one.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's a good idea to not have one.
Yeah. But they are fun.
Yeah, but also just kill me, you know, like I'll also die.
Just come in and you can kill me.
You can take all my stuff.
I'm not that worried about it that I need to.
I would I think, yeah, I think I would rather
I would rather kill be killed than kill some random guy
jumping into my house because it just seems too hard to deal with the aftermath.
Right. You got to get you got to get the window replaced.
Yeah, you got to you got to buy a thing to put the body in.
You burn it. Exactly.
Did I dispose of it?
You have to figure out how to live, how to dispose of a body safely.
I think that's probably the only time I would do it if I knew that I could do it instantly.
That is the hardest thing.
To learn Google how to do a crime.
I'm watching the Breaking Bad scenes on YouTube.
Trying to get around it by trying to find out the name of the acid they use in Breaking
Bad.
But just looking up Breaking Bad coolest scenes.
Your Honor, I just wanted to watch Breaking Bad.
I just wanted to watch Gus kill the guy with the box cutter.
Yeah, I don't think I would.
Yeah, I'm too scared to Google a crime.
I wouldn't be able to do one myself.
I had a knife when I lived in Boston,
and then I moved to Boston,
and somebody at my school was like,
"Hey, that knife is like two inches past
what you're legally allowed to have here."
And I was like, "Oh, okay.
Yeah, I guess I don't really need a knife."
And then I just threw it away.
I would probably hide a knife in my sock
if I, you know, just was out and about all the time, but like...
But what are you going to do with a knife, dude?
Like...
Yeah.
I'm not... I don't know how to use a knife.
Like, I don't know why I had it in the first place.
I think you would...
Maybe if somebody hands me a, like a buck, a eight point buck, it's like, okay,
I'll cut it down the middle like Red Dead Redemption.
But I don't know how to protect myself with this.
I think you'd first get a knife for like the like collectors value type of thing
which is like looks cool and you like having it.
Yeah, they carry around a katana.
I'm sure you can in some states.
You have to have that sword, you have a sword, right?
I don't have a sword.
There is a sword here though.
Okay, never mind then.
Dojo vibe.
Yeah.
I was looking at them, they're not cheap, they're like 300 bucks for a nice sword.
Do you know in 48 states you're allowed to have a flamethrower?
What are the two you can't?
California and like Massachusetts maybe.
Alright, you can have one in New York.
Yeah, should I get one?
You should get one.
Just fighting off someone robbing you with a flamethrower
you just burn your whole house down.
The thing is if you walk around you will never get mugged
around with a flamethrower strapped to your back.
True. Yeah.
Nobody's going to mess with you.
Or if you are a bald white guy who looks scary with a with a small dog.
I used to play video games with this dude in Idaho, and he would just fucking
strap like a, you know, a R15 to his back to go to Starbucks.
It's like you don't need to do that.
That's so cool, man.
It was cool.
It was definitely the coolest thing to me.
That's so sick. Yeah.
Because there are those states where you just walk around with that
And then people will call the cops and the cops will just show up and be like,
yeah, so basically this lady's being a bitch at the fucking home goods.
I get it, bro. Just keep on keeping on.
I'm going to tell her that I wrote you a ticket. Yeah.
So funny, dude.
I would have been that dude in Texas who like what is on a date.
And then he got ripped off by a guy like
doing like a parking scam, like overcharging for parking.
And he just walked out.
He's like, I got to go to the bathroom.
He just walked out and killed the guy.
I went back to the date, just like pretended nothing happened.
Whoa.
The thing about that, as I didn't really understand
that the timeline of that scenario, like he got there, he got overcharged.
Then he went to the date and he was like, you know what?
Actually, well, he was so mad about that guy.
He just kept thinking about it and getting pissed off.
The video where the guy that came out a couple of weeks ago
where the guy is like singing to himself in his car
and then he just cuts him off
and then he just pulls out the Glock
and just starts fucking dumping at this guy.
That's good.
Oh, it's shipping for everyone to do that.
I want to do that every time.
I will say, OK, I hate I hate video.
I hate death videos, videos where people shoot at each other
and nobody gets hit are the funniest videos ever.
It's always a video of two guys who pull up to the same gas station
in South Carolina and they pull out the biggest gun you've ever seen.
They both have girls in their cars and then they shoot 500 bullets
at each other, miss every single one.
One of the bullets goes into one of the girls feet.
Yeah. And then they both go to jail for 16 months.
It's the funniest thing ever.
It's so fucking sick.
It's so funny to walk around with guns with that
that much artillery and just miss every single shot.
It's beautiful. Sick, dude.
Have you guys ever seen American Sniper?
I kind of want to watch it.
I watched a clip from it today that looked so bad.
It's good. The scene with the baby is so funny.
Yeah, I've only seen the baby scene clip.
I just saw a scene where he shoots a snake.
Yeah? With a sniper?
Yeah, he shoots a snake with a sniper and I was like, "Okay, I don't..."
But I just heard his voice. His voice was so bad.
The accent that he does is so shit.
Whatever happened to that guy? He fell off.
Did he get accused of rape or something?
- No, he's still making movies.
- No, dude, he did "Star is Born."
Is that the last big thing he did?
- That was like five years ago.
- Yeah, but--
- He's for sure made a movie like last year.
- But when you're like that, you just do heaters every five.
- True.
- No, people think he's in heaters,
but he's completely not.
- Yeah, he's fucking awful.
- Bradley Cooper's in heaters.
- He's in a couple of heaters.
He's not in every heater.
Not all of his movies are heaters.
- Oh, he's in "Guardians of the Galaxy," I guess.
- Yep, yeah, he plays the raccoon, I think.
- No, that's-- - He was in Licorice Pizza,
he was in Avengers.
So Star is Born was literally five years ago.
- Okay, let's see.
Yeah, Licorice Pizza for sure.
Let's see, his best movie-- - Limitless.
- Let's see, oh, he just had an era.
You know, just like McConaughey did.
You don't have to be doing it forever.
- True. - But he had like five years
where he was one of the best actors.
- He's in like two of the biggest movies of this year.
What are you guys talking about?
Talking about movies I care about.
Yeah.
I'm not talking about trash.
Garbage for slop pigs.
For sluts.
Liquorice pizza was also a good movie.
I never saw that.
Slut pig.
Yeah.
I don't give a fuck about that movie.
I liked it.
I fucking hate the Haim sisters.
Yeah.
That is just not for me, man.
I'll fight them each individually and I'll fight them one victory.
I will say I did it.
I watched the movie and I thought it was okay.
I liked it.
And then a week later, that video where the Hames sisters
started doing this weird dance on stage came out,
and I was like, okay, I see what people are talking about.
- Yeah, they're fucking annoying.
- I just found out something really fucked up, man.
- What?
- The next, the new Joker movie,
the one with Lady Gaga.
- It's a musical.
- Yeah, it's a musical.
I had no idea.
- You didn't know that?
- That is awful, bro.
- I knew that.
- And Zazie Beetz is in it.
Yeah. I love her.
Who says he beats Zazie beats. She's beautiful.
Okay. She's in a bunch of shit.
Okay. You didn't answer my question.
I think you guys are media blind. She's the girl from Atlanta.
We're media. What?
I see that you're media blind.
I don't have TV, so I don't see ads.
Rex only watches Rick and Morty on his phone and read Chinese novels.
I have not watched any Rick and Morty since he was accused of rape plus three days.
What's your new thing? Are you watching family guy?
Uh, I've been watching, um,
Silicon Valley.
Okay.
Wow. I cannot believe that it's taken you of all people this long to watch that
show. I think I watched it when it came out. It literally forgot
all about it. The thing the house that they live in looks
exactly like the house that they live in to the craziest degree
where you have the big shared table even. Yeah, it's really
wild. Yeah. It's a funny show and you know, thankfully no one
on that show has ever been accused of raping.
It is crazy that it goes rape, rape, steroids.
- Yep.
- They have a pretty bad kind of rap at this point.
- Or Martin Starr's the only clean one.
And that's just because he's a weird guy.
- Yeah, 'cause who's gonna fuck him?
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
- Dude, I used to think Middle Ditch was so funny.
Like, Comedy Bang Bang, 2014.
- Me too, oh my God.
I used to think he was so fucking funny.
And then just finding out that he was into being,
to like fucking goth people really made me.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know about that.
Yeah, dude.
Just goths?
He's going to like sex clubs.
Yeah, he would.
His wife didn't want to be a swinger, but he was like, no, we have to or I'll divorce you.
And she took her, he took her to a goth sex clubs and he would like fuck a bunch of goth chicks.
And she would just sit there, drink up probably a bitters and soda and look at the wall.
I remember when, uh, that sounds awesome.
When Compton first came out, I was talking to,
I used to go to Goodwills all the time to like make extra money and just like
flip shit. And, uh,
I remember talking to this like alcoholic that worked at the Tempe improv,
um, that was like a cashier there during the day.
And we were like talking about like comedy and he was like, Oh yeah, like, um,
TJ Miller, like was just here. And like, I was his like handler.
and he like smashed an egg on my face
and like hit me over the head with a beer bottle.
- What?
- Yeah, yeah.
Just like completely, just like destroyed this dude.
(laughing)
I was like, oh man, that sucks.
And he's like, no, it was awesome.
He was really funny.
- Wait, what did that have to do
with the beginning of your story?
- That's just how I started like talking to him.
He's like listening to Comptown.
- Oh, okay.
- So that's how I started talking to him.
- That just made no sense at all.
Yeah, we were just like talking about it and then I found out he worked at the
improv and then he was like, I was like, Oh, that's cool. Like, what do you do?
And he's like, I'm like a, like I handle like some of the,
like the bigger talent that comes through.
I didn't notice until like literally like a couple of days ago,
but Rex has so many famous people, celebs connections.
It's crazy.
Do you, who do you, who are you connected to? Say it publicly right now.
I'm not going to say it publicly.
Someone informed me of a bunch of different celebrity connections.
I went to high school.
All right, we have to end this episode so I can hear this.
Yeah.
All right.
Number one being Ludwig from Tempe.