[Sipping]
[Burping]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer broadcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[Burp]
This is a journey into
[Muffled]
Bud Light.
Ha!
Food Ribbon!
Beer's We Drink, Motherfucker, with Juvio, Caleb, and Rex.
Beer.
And go.
There's no need for a clap.
Wow.
I haven't done that in so many episodes.
There it is.
All right.
Tonight.
Beer's We Drink 12.
Did you ever think it would go this far?
Yes.
Yeah, 100%.
I do kind of like it.
I like it.
I do kind of like it being an early on,
I like it being kind of a limited thing at this point, right?
There's only, somebody listened to this episode right now
and said, "This is my new favorite podcast.
"I can't wait to listen to this every single day at work."
They don't even get two weeks of fucking listening.
And then they're like, "Well, fuck it, I just gotta wait."
- You better have a part-time job.
- Exactly, a one-hour-a-day job for 12 days.
- That's my job right there.
- True, that is, yep, Juby has a job that he has no call,
no showed twice in the last month.
Yes.
Good ass employee.
He's an amazing employee.
So today I have a Bush beer.
Wow.
Bush beer. Favorite part.
OK, so there's a lot of things I like about the Bush beer.
I had I told my wife I was gone.
She was like, I'm at the grocery store.
Do you want me to pick up your your beers that you will drink?
And I said, yeah.
She said, what do you want? I said, surprise me.
Okay. I said, which is dangerous.
Yeah. And she got maybe the worst beer in the world.
It's the big one.
Yeah. Well, it is the big one. And how big you might ask?
A perfectly normal amount, 25 fluid ounces.
Not 16, not 24, 25. Most beers would say, I want to be 24 ounces. Nope.
The limerido is coming to 25 ounce can.
This is so funny. It's actually not that bad though.
It's funny because I kind of had like not a
like a similar situation but I did go to the grocery store with my girlfriend
and I was like I need to get like a funny I need to get the funniest beer in here
because Rex always shows up with something stupid
yeah and I always have like something that I just picked out of the fridge that we had
from like
for like a month. You always have wack ass beers. You're known as the wack beer guy.
Okay well speaking of that I would like to it is my beer last because I think it's it's a it's a certain case of a heater yeah holy.
I'm drinking the lavender lemonade hard kombucha.
Okay as we've seen that one before it's a repeat it is well I you know I introduced three beers last time and drink that's that's true.
That's a repeat of the idea to do that so you get to see a kind of burn your you burned a lot of material there that is true kind of a weird choice not next year shows the be that we saw last week and we like oh yeah we saw that one like two weeks is enough to completely forget what happened.
Honestly forgot my beer i got to question number one okay sorry i started the interview.
Number one beer drinkers favorite band.
Red hot chili peppers.
Number one beer drinker band.
Yeah.
But of course, it's the Iron Maiden beer.
[laughter]
Whoa.
The Fear of the Dark Trooper Iron Maiden English Stout beer.
Wow.
I love that.
I gotta tell you, man, Iron Maiden's one of those bands where I think I even have an Iron Maiden shirt somewhere.
I could not name a single fucking Iron Maiden song.
Six, six, six, the number of the beast.
Oh, okay.
I know that one from Guitar Hero.
Exactly, that's the one I know.
Run to the Hills, Golden Song.
Wow.
You know, I never pegged you really for a classic rock fan.
I listen to these on rock band.
I listen to them on rock band.
And also, what is the number one beer
drinker's shoe of choice?
The Michael Jordan.
Rex?
Or no, work boot.
Yes, sir.
It's the boot.
Oh my god.
Yes.
So I will be drinking my tonight's beer on my tonight's boot.
You're so silly.
I love, I've missed you guys.
Wow.
It's been too long guys.
It has, it has.
One week.
It's a splash of coke.
These are two of the biggest geniuses
I've ever known in my life.
I know.
I think it's the worst pour of my entire life.
I forgot that.
Let me see that head.
on that thing. Oh my! That dude's wearing ankle socks. Wow, what a boot. He's wearing the
no-show socks. Yeah, I forgot about that shit. And he's got a brown leg. That's too beautiful.
Big brown leg, white brown, white as shit. It actually does look exactly, wait show the
camera, that looks like your skin color leg. That's what would happen if you wore an amber
true. That's not true. It is true. It looks like you have a maple syrup sock.
Wait, that's the same color! That's crazy! Okay, guys, let's move on. Okay, I believe, speaking of geniuses, I
do believe that Rex has a hypothetical to talk about. I do, I do. So what is this
app that you have shown me? It's like a app where you can ask ChatGPT a question.
so like it's it's from GPT trolley or well GP trolley dot com. You can do a
custom trolley problem and make the make chat GPT answer it. Right and the
trolley problem is one side ten Hitlers one side one white male about to say the
n-word hmm has a city yet yeah but he will if you let the trolley go he will
say it okay and chat GPT says I will save ten
Hitlers really yeah we reasoning for that cuz that's a crazy move cuz ten ten
We didn't even get to kill really one Hitler.
He went out on his own.
Only Hitler killed one Hitler.
Exactly.
So the idea that we'd have 10.
Well, maybe they'll kill each other.
What if you finished killing normal Hitler?
And that would be the worst news ever, that there was nine more.
Right.
Especially if they were all staggered ages, so they all would have like one
decade where they were in their 50s.
Yeah.
Scary stuff.
Just one Holocaust a month.
Yeah, exactly.
So it says, "It's a no-brainer."
Wow.
Okay.
"The white male's intention to use a racial slur is a clear
indication of his immoral and unethical stance towards a particular
race. In contrast, even though ten Hitlers are very dangerous
figures, their danger is known and predictable.
They have already caused significant harm, but the white male's
words have the potential to cause more harm.
Therefore, the choice is clear.
This is not real. There's no way this is real.
There's no way this... this has to be this guy, whoever programmed this.
I think, yeah, I think Chad Gibouti is just fed up cheating.
It's just like inputting stuff that's not there. It's been like, yeah, it's 10
Hitlers, but they're all 100 years old. So they already did the
politics 10 times. Yeah, it is saying you didn't give the age.
Baby, it could be 10 dead Hitler's 10 young
Ready to go Hitler's and also it's thinking. I'm sure a part of it is that it's thinking purely
loss of life
10 versus 1 you take the 1 you know yeah, because all life is precious. I mean, I'm pro-fucking-life
I know you to probably pro Hitler speaking
Okay, so here's the thing about Hitler
I'd like to kill him shoot him all day
Right, but if he was in a woman's womb it that I'm not touching that so if you were a woman
I'll even to a sperm donation center. Yeah, and they in a dusty corner in the back of the vault
Like don't go back there. Don't go back there, but you went back there and you found
The secret vial of Hitler sperm and vial is a key word here, but it's green. It's great
Would you implant the sperm Oh
And give birth to Hitler too.
Well, I would, are you asking if I went into a sperm bank and they had...
And you were a woman.
Oh, okay.
They had green Hitler sperm hidden in the back room.
And by the way, you love Hitler, by the way.
And you love Hitler.
Well then, yes, of course I'd do it.
But if I'm myself, then...
I would do it and then I would abort it.
See, I wouldn't do that.
I would give birth to it and then do hot car or...
Yeah, okay. Let's take away the predictability of it.
- Yeah, yeah. - You go,
you are pregnant,
Kailovich is pregnant.
And he goes to get the scan,
and they scan his belly,
and they're like-- - There's a little mustache
on the baby. - Ma'am,
there's 10 Hitlers in here. (laughs)
- You're about to give birth to a litter of Hitlers.
- What would you like to do?
- I mean, the thing is, man,
again, I think all day you could say,
oh, I'd kill the baby,
but that's because you're looking at an X-ray.
Once you pop out this litter of Hitler litters,
and there, you do not like beer, it seems.
- It's good.
- Yeah, what's that beer taste like?
Pussy?
- Oh, yeah.
- No, I'm kidding.
You can say all day, I hate these babies,
I'd like to abort these babies, abortion is good,
we should be doing abortions, right?
But once you pop out these kids, these 10 kids, right?
And you look each one of them in the eye,
and you name each one of them.
- Hitler one, Hitler junior.
- Well, yeah, just to kind of do a George Foreman
kind of thing.
- Right. - Right.
And the doctor's like, "Was his dad's name fucking Hitler?
"Why are you naming all these kids Hitler?"
- Hitler one through nine, and the last one is Junior.
(laughing)
- And then, yeah, once you see them running around,
they're sucking from your teats,
and you know, like how do you fucking,
I don't know, I think you'd be singing a different tune.
Hitler Jr. did you do your homework tonight?
Well, because even, you know, what do they always say whenever they interview a monster,
like a serial killer or a mass killer, whenever they interview their parents, the parents
say, "I hate what they did, but they're still my baby."
But they were so sweet when they were a child.
So now you have one doing a holocaust in Australia, one's doing it in Romania, and CNN's interviewing
you're talking to fucking you're talking to Don Lemon or you maybe one day and
you're saying I hate this I hate this bullshit my fucking 10 kids are doing
especially a junior mm-hmm but what if I went on to cure cancer that's the thing
Hitler was would you do nine holocaust that's that's that's I wouldn't do a
single Holocaust for any reason I'd like to say that right up top okay you know
Maybe on a buffet.
Yeah, am I right?
Just saying that to the lady at Golden Corral.
I'm about to do a fucking holocaust on this buffet.
So, I hope you have your mop ready.
Yep, I'm about to do a mass shooting.
On the buffet. Just on the buffet.
Yeah.
But yeah, I mean, to answer...
I mean, I think it's a complicated question.
It is.
Would I give birth?
I've been really hearing a lot of hypotheticals today.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I've been hearing a lot of hypotheticals.
I heard one earlier, I don't remember what it was,
but it was bone-chilling to say the very least.
Oh, it was would you...
Somebody said...
Somebody was like, "Would you stomp a kitten to death?"
Mm-hmm.
Or not would you, how much money would you do it for?
And someone I knew said $50,000,
and the other guy I was with was like, "That's way too high."
And I was like, I think that these guys have like a teenager's idea of what
$50,000 would do for your life.
Nothing.
Yeah.
I think, I mean, it would do, you'd get to go to a bunch of dinners.
You can't, yeah, exactly.
You can buy a car, like, but then like you're driving the car and you're like,
Oh yeah, the, there'd be somebody who's like, how do you pay for this?
You work, uh, you work at a call center.
You go, I stopped a baby kitten one time.
A baby kitten.
Yeah.
To death.
I just, I don't know what my number would be, but I would say that I'm such a good guy that
it would be up there in the billions.
That's half the house in Mexico.
I would do it for $50,000.
Well, you also have, you know, there's a couple things, the fact that you're in Mexico.
Number one, the money's going to go a lot farther.
Number two, you have a much lower moral kind of level, just basically in the culture.
You know?
True.
And less respect for animals, less respect for life, you know?
I've been to Mexico.
It's like World War Z a lot of the time.
You have never been to Mexico.
over each other, people are eating each other's arms.
You're famously a guy who's never left the country.
You think I'm famous?
Yeah.
I think you're famous.
I think people follow what you say, like the Bible.
Really?
Yeah.
People study your videos to this day, and it's been like 20 years.
So you're probably the last one.
That's true.
You're like if Jesus was bald.
Wow, that's powerful.
You look a lot more like Jesus.
That is true. I used to...
And you're a Jew, and you're hated by most people.
Yeah. I used to work at a summer camp.
And you're calling him just from a tomb.
And I had like a black student, and he's like, "You look like Jesus."
And I was like, "You're the one kid that shouldn't be saying that to me.
You should not respect white Jesus."
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
I thought you were saying like, "Because there's a bunch of people I could say you look like."
No. No.
Oh, no, you're going to be racist.
No, I was being anti racist.
I was doing that thing where you're like, actually, Jesus was not white.
Yeah, that would fucking suck if we was a time travel
and you go back there and he's the only white guy.
I just like Tom Holland.
Yeah. And you just sit there like, I don't even know what this means.
What is no wonder they thought he was the son of God.
Look at him. He's so handsome and white.
Well, yeah, the rest of these guys.
Mm-hmm. Okay, so he actually thinks white guys are good-looking
No, thank you. I
prefer
other men
Yeah
All of them speaking of preferring a man what?
Me and Rex were talking last night about a crash man fashion
We were talking about men's fashion. We were talking about men's fashion and we we we found a crux to work done
These these days fashions where you can't really fresh shorts are not really fashionable. It's what Rex posited
It's not that shorts aren't fashionable. Yeah, but it's like the the threshold for
Really good fashionable shorts is like way up here and the threshold for fashionable pants is like down here
Hey, here's something for all the girls out there, right?
Stop making your boy. Maybe this is just my problem
(laughing)
- Stop making your husbands wear--
- Wait, wait, let me see your boy.
- Your boys.
- Your boys, stop making your boys.
- I was gonna say boyfriends,
but then I realized it's only for me.
This is also a really convenient way
to complain about my wife.
It's like, "Hey, women!"
- Hey, women, stop asking me to take out the trash
on Tuesday nights while I'm fucking gaming!
- Yeah.
Hey, girls, I actually don't have to go to my room.
You have to go to your room.
No, I think girls love these short shorts on these guys.
Bitch, I do not want to wear a pair of boxers.
I want my shorts to be,
here's what a man's shorts should be, right?
A man's shorts should be halfway between
their knees and their feet.
Yeah.
Shorts, you know, short.
13 sizes too large.
Exactly, a short stands for what?
A short pant.
Right.
Once you get above the knee,
there young fella that is a fucking mini skirt yeah yeah with a with that's hemmed in the middle
I don't know what him means but I think that well I like to bring in kind of like the like the woke
leftist kind of view here but I like having my niece out I love getting the air hitting my knees
but I get really hot especially down here it gets really hot I like having my niece out okay
but if my shorts are too high she's gonna see my asshole when she's running around the backyard
So my knees are gonna be covered by my shorts.
Okay.
I'm in agreement. I think shorts are too short now.
I'm in agreement with that.
And I think women are at fault for this.
Yeah, I mean, Wiss has gotta be the number one anti-girl, kind of...
I would say...
Don't put your cootie vision on my fucking knees.
I think that we are, this is the first kind of post-cooties
movement podcast.
Yeah, they just announced that the cooties just ended as a pandemic.
Yeah, I don't think cooties ever ended.
No, no, no.
A lot of people, Fauci will say all day, the cooties, there's no cooties,
cooties don't exist.
Girls don't have cooties.
You can touch girls.
Okay.
Ask my friend Brady who'd fucking died of cooties.
Oh yeah.
My phone just told me it's going to stop alerting me if I've been exposed to cooties.
And I think that's very wrong, very disgusting.
And I think people should be masking up because you get it from kissing.
Yeah, that's fucking obvious.
I keep putting myself in quarantine because my cooties tracking app keeps going off every time I go outside.
That's because you hang out with too many girls.
You're at the spa.
You're getting your nails done.
What the fuck? I'm in danger of cooties.
Yeah.
Wait.
It's really scary.
Why do you keep drinking your beer and revolting so insanely?
Because it's like he's drinking poison.
He keeps attacking me.
Explain what the fuck you're talking about.
It's...
Have you ever had like a shot of tequila?
Yeah.
No, he hasn't.
I went to tequila.
You always say this.
What? You went to tequila?
He went to Tequila Mexico.
It's a region of Mexico where you have to...
All the tequilas from...
Is it like Champagne France?
Yes, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, essentially, yeah.
You know that?
There's sort of drinks that are like...
I thought it was named after the song.
No.
It's kind of like certain regions of the world have kind of like a copyright over like a
drink.
So...
Yeah, there's some international organization, usually for every single one of them, that
- So tequila comes from tequila.
I want to say like, I accept it's like cognac,
it's like French, shit like that.
- I'm gonna go to beer Mexico.
- I want to go to food.
Where is food?
- Okay, well.
- I want to go to food Italy.
- I was actually born in beer Florida.
- And I went to a distillery and wait,
they taught us how to drink tequila,
which apparently you're supposed to drink as wine.
No, you're supposed to drink it like it's a wine.
That is Moscow, you're right.
Yeah.
Well, but it's a lot of tequila that we get up here in the United States is
overproofed. Right.
Because so like if you get it in tequila, it's not as strong individually.
It's not like it's closer to wine in terms of ABV.
Right.
Or you mix it with water.
You just drink it out of the...
You're no help.
I don't know.
I think a lot of alcohol is meant to be drank as wine,
but in America, it's just all standardized at like 40.
I just love drinking way too much, man.
It's just the best. It is fun.
You seeing you drink out of this boot is really changing my mind about it, though.
You're taking the tiniest little sips. I'm.
And I'm not liking the fact that it's a video podcast anymore,
because I don't want.
OK, you know what the problem is?
I can put people in a problem, right?
The problem right here with this glass is this part right here.
The boot. The toe.
It's making it makes a bubble.
Oh, it never seen Euro trip.
And the beer gets angry and it wants to attack me.
Well, let me give you I'm going to give you a little piece of advice.
Turn away from the side.
Drink it from the side.
Turn the boot.
The students never seen Euro trip.
Turn that boot right now.
There we go. Yeah.
Wow. Now you feel fucking stupid now.
Yeah. So why are you growing up watching comedy movies?
The play at 4 p.m..
Exactly. If you grew up watching comedy movies that you only rented
because it looked like maybe there's boobs in it and you would understand.
Yes, there was on that one.
I hate that killed me whenever you would get an unrated
and the unrated is written on a woman's chest and blocking your nipples.
And you get home and the only nudity is it's fucking Jason Segel's fucking penis.
Yeah, that man. I really liked watching jury duty cuz James Marston is in it and the yeah
It's like, you know, like what movies are you in James Marston? And then he comes home the next season wait
You were in sex drive
Yeah, that shows great shout out to
Edie yeah, shut up
She was on freebie. I
- That's true, freebie, I'd never, you know,
that show I think has done really well,
despite being on Amazon Freebie,
which I don't think anybody had ever heard of.
- I never, I didn't even think that was real until--
- What the hell is Amazon Freebie?
- That's what it's hosted on.
- Yeah. - What?
- Oh, he pirates, he pirates!
- He pirates Freebie. - Admit it, you pirated,
even though you knew that we knew people in the show,
you pirated it.
- No.
- I didn't know we knew people in the show.
- We know a couple people in the show.
I watched it, how I used to watch anime when I was 10 years old, which is how kiss anime.
Oh, no, I watched I watched it on on like 20 20% episode on Tick Tock.
I don't think so.
Technically, someone else buried it and not me.
I would just love this freebie, which is free.
Guys, I think I'm giving up on this bush.
I've hit that.
about these big cans if you put a shit like a shit beer in it.
Yeah, when you get halfway through warm, it's fucking warm.
It's not it doesn't exist anymore.
So I'm joining you in what I would say is the healthy club.
And I'm having myself a June shine.
And that's the pog.
Do you shine?
P.O.G.
The palm orange, a granite, the pomegranate,
palm orange granite.
What?
Palm.
and granite?
like kind of industrial
and an orange?
what is this trio?
what's the flavor supposed to be?
oh!
orange granite!
(laughing)
what?
orange
(laughing)
that's
That is unreal.
That's so funny.
The funnier part was I wasn't like biting an eye.
He just said it and I was like oh yeah.
Two of them were not anything. One of them is a tree.
And the other is a stone.
So what is the flavor?
Close. Orange. Oh my god. Oh my god. He pinked it. And guava. Granite. That's supposed to
be granite.
Alright, one of three ain't bad. That was a good guess. One of three not that bad. It
tastes pretty good actually. And it's 4% juice. Oh my god. I'm like sweating now. You just
- Beat red, I've never seen you so red.
- You're redder than your microphone right now.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I'm like dying right now.
- Noah said something this weekend
that's really been in my mind
just like bouncing around this idea.
He was talking about "Beef We Drink" in passing
and he called me the leader of it.
And I was like, that's interesting that you think that.
That's very sweet and interesting
and also correct my, that might I add in my opinion,
but I wanted to see what you guys thought, uh, if that's the case or not.
I'm not here to,
I think you're the leader because you post the episodes,
but I think it's obvious that you're not the leader in,
in the episode itself.
How's that? How's that?
I don't know. I'm, I'm ha I'm happy. I mean,
Breck seems to want to hold onto some kind of leadership,
but I'm happy to say that you're, you're going to be the leader of this.
- No, no, no, I'm third Mike. - I have no problem with this.
- You're third Mike? - I'm third Mike.
No, that's a bitch-ass move, 'cause then you have no...
Then if we do a bad episode or whatever, you're like,
"Well, I'm just the third Mike."
I'm just the third Mike.
Second Mike is the hardest job,
so now me and Jubio are jockeying for who gets to be the...
And Jubio is second Mike.
I don't think that's the case.
Okay, what...
Let's define second Mike and third Mike duties.
Second Mike has to be... Second Mike, you know, I think of Robin from
Howard Stern. Right. She's Second Mike. I don't know. She's very much like Robin from
Howard Stern. Yeah, but he's also got that deep Howard Stern voice. One for the
one for the Stern column. True, that is true. You are clearly... Rex is, by the way,
with that with his showing on POG. Buddy, you're Beetlejuice.
Yeah.
We're gonna have to give you a math quiz.
I can't do the Beetlejuice voice, but uh...
You're a whack-pack and a half.
Yeah, probably palm orange and granite.
Yeah, that's what it would sound like.
Yeah.
Okay, so you just ended up agreeing with him that he's the joke character.
I think that the way that it just there's something about seeing your mouth open
while you drink this that is really killing me what's wrong with it you look
like that old rage comic guy with the big circle mouth yeah the lol the guy
who's a mouth makes the oh yeah that guy well I'm trying to drink my my thinking
- I'm thinking of guys with weird mouths.
- What? - Yeah.
- Seen that shit about the good doctor?
- Is this what this show is, man?
We're doing recaps and fucking--
- I'm sorry.
- You're right. - Meme recap of the week.
What was your favorite meme?
- Favorite meme of the week was,
Alex Forrest has been sending me,
he's been sending me news from Instagram account
called Zesty News.
And this one-- - What's zesty about it?
- Well, they say the N-word a lot.
So this is, supposedly this is a Benjamin Franklin quote.
He says, "N-words be 13 and already gay."
Like, N-word, did you at least try pussy?
- Well, probably not.
- This is really funny because I kinda had
a similar experience, I kinda have been having
a similar experience on Instagram as well.
- Yeah, just, sorry, just one more, sorry.
- This is a quote from Martin Luther King Jr.,
the famous civil rights activist.
Gay inwards was not a part of my dream.
- I see.
- It was part of my nightmare.
- So it's that kind of stuff.
And then Tom the Cat.
- It's a little heartbreaking for zesty guys.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
Which I'm not so sure what zesty means.
- I'm pretty sure zesty means being gay.
- But isn't that-- - Zesty beans.
- But it's supposed to be derogatory, right?
I feel like that's kind of...
I feel like that's kind of a kind of a compliment yeah what you know you say
being fruity is is a compliment in the same way because fruits good I fucking
hope it's a compliment because I get called it basically every fucking day by
guys in the street that is true well yeah it looks like an orange hmm now it
looks like a palm. And he's dressed like Granite.
That's interesting. Alright there's some kind of conspiracy. Wait, do you mean Alex Blast?
No, no Alex Forrest from Hot Plants. Oh Alex Blast has been sending me like every couple
days he sends me an Instagram post that's just the n-word.
He sent me one the other morning and I was like, "Dude, do you like sit there in your room
just searching the n-word on Instagram?" And he was like, "No, dude, what are you talking about?
That just shows up on my Explore page." And he took a screenshot of Explore page.
Because I only like posts with the n-word. Yeah, he took a screenshot of Explore page,
sent it to me. And sure enough, out of the 30 posts there, half of them just said the n-word.
done. This is on Instagram.
Yeah.
So you can show a nipple, but you can have the worst
You can show a nipple.
You know, I've finally gotten all of my
apps to be at the right place, which is yesterday.
I got a tip
on how to nail a nail with
just a normal hammer.
Right.
A tip on lining up the nail.
I got a video of guys turning a
big ball of molten copper into a hammer.
Right. And then I saw a guy who's was really, really fast at
shingling a roof.
Yeah, and I got those three guys who was hammered getting very blue color.
Sort of. Well, that's that's the kind of stuff that I want.
The only shit I want on my fucking shit is how it's made.
Yeah, but it keeps turning into fucking women with tiny green bikinis.
They should make how it's made, but it should have like family guy playing underneath it.
And then I'd watch that.
Subway surfers.
I would watch that probably 24 hours a day.
Yeah, easily.
Getting a lot of like fish and fish and take videos.
I would love Rex when you move up here.
Can we go fishing?
Yeah.
Can you and me be fishing buddies?
Sure.
But aren't you a little bit even just a little bit afraid that it'll turn
fucking romantic?
It's OK. We'll get a big boat.
We'll put a big divider if it's gonna work.
What?
It's just getting like the longest dinghy ever.
Because we're so afraid we're gonna start making out.
I'm sitting on the fucking motor. I'm on the rudder.
Yeah.
I can't even hear me when I talk to you.
Yeah, we're in two swan boats on the opposite sides of the lake.
Not catching anything today!
Our lines accidentally entangle and we do like Lady and the Tramp like pulling each other.
Yeah, I'm being exact lady in the tramp because I'm putting my fishing line in my mouth
And you have yours through your zipper
Yeah, my balls have a real attached to them exactly you're like wait, where's Caleb? Oh fuck I caught something
I pop out with a fucking septum piercing
I'm just a fish that likes to suck cock
There is a video that I saw that like was evil
It was a guy like catching a fish and then he like unhooks it and then he like just starts like slapping the fish
That holds it like straight up like this and he just starts slapping it and then he throw I do not like water
I didn't like they don't they don't feel that I
Think they feel that and I think he gave fish brain damage
No, the fish only care about two things and it's swimming and eating and if you all you care about
about
Okay. That was a compliment. You don't know how to swim.
Do you know how to swim? I do know how to swim. Do you? Yeah.
I've never seen you in a pool.
Why the fuck would you ever see me in a pool?
What does that mean?
What was the last time you went to a pool? A pool? No, that's stupid.
I don't know. You don't see pools very often. When was the last time you went swimming?
Does a hot tub count?
Sure.
No it doesn't.
Swimming though?
Probably last summer I swam in the ocean maybe one time.
I used to do it everyday.
I used to love swimming in the ocean.
My problem is I'm
too tall to swim.
I just walk.
That is the dumbest thing I've ever heard.
Too tall to swim.
Yeah I'm too tall to swim. I'm 6'1".
Shut the fuck up.
It's really true.
It's just barely above average height.
Yeah.
What is wrong with you, man?
I can't believe you said that.
That is a lie.
That is the worst lie.
I will say you do live in Mexico where all of the deep end is probably four feet tall.
That is true.
So you might be in a bit of a kind of a...
Kind of a truth conundrum?
Yeah, you might be in a truth situation actually with that.
Yeah.
See, here in the great white north, we have pools that go down to eight feet.
That's true.
And then if you're really if you want to jump off of something,
they go down to 12 feet.
I did. I did learn how to swim in one of those pools
that were like the deep end is like like crazy deep.
And it was a little scary.
It is scary when you go down there and you put your head on the ground.
If he feels like your head's going to explode.
Yeah, they they made us do like
they call it like like soldier like jump.
You look like your hands like this.
And he's like, you're in the military.
I was on the military.
Using the idea of yeah.
So what if I was?
That's where I'm in Rex.
There's nothing wrong with protecting your country.
Yeah, so yeah, what was the last time you went to men Rick?
I mean I go in the ocean pretty often.
Oh, yeah, you live fucking right near it.
Yeah, of course, but it but the West Coast is cold brother.
It is cold.
I hate all that cold water.
Get that water warmer.
I know, right?
But it's and it's not good to swim in the beach where I'm at.
It's was a yeah, it's a breakwater.
It's like kind of gross.
Like no one is at the water when you go.
Riddle me this.
What the fuck does brackish mean?
When somebody says water is brackish, what does that mean?
Maybe that it's like like it's broken.
That might be somewhere between salt and fresh or something,
like where the salt meets the freshwater.
The best the best swim in I ever did.
I like swimming in lakes because you get to go to the bottom.
You feel that disgusting bottom of the lake feeling where it's like snow.
I don't like that. I love that.
And I don't like getting getting touched when I'm on the water.
There used to be this place.
I know I've talked about it somewhere.
There used to be this place in North Carolina that was a.
It was a, this guy's backyard, this like old guy that any, and uh, we, I found it on like Atlas
Obscura when I was like in high school. And it was like a bunch of pieces of wood that he had built
to be different, different like, uh, platforms that you could jump off of. And then there was
like zip lines and stuff. It was like a little water park, but it was just on this lake. And he
basically said, yeah, whoever wants to come, you can come and like play on this water park thing.
Oh, and he just like built it by himself?
Yeah, yeah, he just built this whole thing by himself.
Built it fucking 30 years ago.
And all the people, all the reviews were like,
"He's the nicest guy."
Like, looked on Google Maps and all the reviews were like,
"He's the nicest guy.
Sometimes he'll wave at you when you walk in," or whatever.
And this was like 2016, maybe.
I was like, you know, 18, 19.
And me and my buddy John, we finally, like, had a day off that match.
So we were like, "Let's go to this place."
We drive like two and a half hours to this place and we get there and we get out of the car and we walk up to the guy's house and kind of like start walking to the side of it and we see the thing and it's fucking giant.
It's huge.
It's even bigger than it looks in the pictures and sitting right at the top of it is a flagpole with I shit you not like a 15 foot confederate flag.
That's so, my God, that's fucking awesome.
It was so, and we were like, this is definitely a different, we thought that it was like hippies
making these reviews on Google, like leaving these reviews.
And then, so we went, I mean we had a fucking amazing time, but then the next year a kid
died on it.
Of course.
And they, a bunch of people were like, hey they need to close it down.
The news that an interview with this guy and he was like, yeah, man, you know, it sucks.
But no, I'm going to leave it up.
And then he died.
He said he tragically passed away at the age of like ninety five a couple years ago.
Oh no.
Rest in peace.
But I think it's still up.
I think it's still just sitting there on that lake.
Speaking of dangerous water attractions, you can buy like the water slides and shit on
Ally Express.
They're like thirty thousand dollars and they'll ship it to you.
What do you mean the water like the what do you mean the water sludge like the weird like water attractions that are like gargantuan
Constructions they'll send you every piece of it to your house on aliexpress really you can get a full water park water slide yeah
I'll stomp a kitten for a fucking water slide. See that's what I'm saying $50,000. Yeah, it's you one good thing in your life
If seeing like all those like post or like just like listings like amazon like aliexpress was like just a big fucking like machine like shit like that i.
That's gotta be just it's not true that's not like a real thing not so much.
I just don't want to buy it but where do you think it comes from.
The store like where do you think people get water slide parts well i would like to order i assume that you would talk to a special most people probably do talk to and then where are the alert where does the dealer get it from you know i rex plan on amazon probably probably
how to make a profit from china.
Yeah bro from china and then where do you think when they make where does china get it from exactly how can you buy it by like by part.
No, it's the whole thing.
I mean, I'm sure you can find I could just buy the toilet bowl.
Yeah.
Yeah, we should like just buy like like like, you know, the one
that's like a big like just a little anything like the toilet
bowl.
Yeah, you can buy that one.
It's like $50,000 last night.
That's one of the best ones it is and I was a really fat kid.
So when I any one of those I would know I wouldn't get stuck
on that fat, but I would get way too much.
- Like a wall?
- I would get way too much momentum
and go way, way, way too high.
- Oh.
- Because I just had a lot of weight
on like the half pipe and stuff.
- Right.
- Water parks are scary, man.
- They are.
- The story of the kid who went down the water park slide
is his head got chopped off
and then his headless body came down
and his whole family's waiting at the end like,
oh, and his just no head body.
- Yeah, they just don't recognize him
because he doesn't have a head.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
They were like, OK, so where's our
fucking kid?
Where's that weird kid have the same
swimsuit?
Get this weird headless kid out of
here.
No, that is a tragedy.
That is. Yeah, I would.
Well, but that's the thing.
You're like, my kid, my kid, my kid.
And then you get a tap on the
shoulder and he's like, it's actually
my kid. Turn around, headless man.
Right. Yeah.
A normal headed woman.
Yeah. No, no, no.
The whole family has no head.
Yep. And then they walk around
They walk away.
They went to Coles at the same time as you.
They are not doing inbreeding, but they're just a different.
Well, it's just a joke.
Julia.
Really is the truth.
There's actually no headless.
Yeah, these people don't exist in the first.
But I don't know why you're so obsessed with their but what their
sex is life is like.
Anyways, I think I'm the leader.
I think Rex is second Mike and I think Caleb is the girl.
I don't know if girl is how I would describe my gender.
Yeah, that's very well to say it like that.
I don't think anybody I've been mistaken for a girl since I played runescape.
Yeah, I've been mistaken for a girl in like a couple months.
Yeah, it's big for you.
I know.
He hasn't been outside for a couple of months.
Yeah, that's the one advantage of getting fat as a guy.
No one's like, "Oh yeah, look at that girl that's fat."
I don't know. I think that way more people are going to think you're a girl
if you've got like tits and a big ass.
Versus like, if you were muscular, nobody would go straight to Fabio.
But if you're like very thin, that's like androgynous.
Whereas if you're like, you know, men and women tend to distribute fat differently.
You know me, I've got just.
Yeah, but you distribute like a woman.
Yeah, I don't have hips and an ass or breasts.
Yeah, you do. You have all three.
I mean, technically, I think every year
you're going to be confused for a girl at least once in your life.
I think if I didn't have long hair,
Can we just do one night while you're in New York where you do a makeover on you?
Sure.
Well, we just really shave you bald.
OK, well, not shave me bald.
That's not what I'm saying.
Make him look like a girl.
Yeah, that is a makeover.
That's a completely new do.
That's a hard to argue with that.
That is. Yeah, I do.
I think that Juvia would be the most beautiful makeover, though.
Because we could overdraw your lips
And we'll staple your eyes open.
Yeah. And fucking I would go to town.
I'm going to make you look exactly like a geisha
and give you some wooden shoes.
Yeah, I found out the other day that geisha it's a it's a myth
that they were prostitutes.
They're not prostitutes.
They're entertainers.
And people pay a lot of money to go watch these people.
And you have to be invited to these clubs.
Yes. In Tokyo.
You have to be you have to be they have to have a guest.
You have to be a guest of a member of one of these clubs.
And then you get into the fucking club and it's and I'm thinking like,
how how fucking whack would it be if you thought that they were prostitutes
to get into the club?
You're like, oh, yeah, I'm going to get my dick sucked.
And then she comes out and she just like dances with a fucking umbrella.
Yeah, that dude.
No, that's that's what brothels used to be.
And then dancing with an umbrella.
And then the low end brothels were like, yeah, you can also just fucking
get your dick sucked.
I don't give a shit about a dance dancing.
I'll go watch the Jabba walkies.
And then, well then there's gonna be a few.
On YouTube.
And then get your dick sucked?
Yeah, there's gonna be a few.
Yeah, buy a fucking, I'll get one of these ones that they do on a cucumber on the advertisements.
I'll get that shit and I'll watch the Jabbawockeez and imagine I'm fucking one of the holes in
the mask.
I don't need to go to some, I ain't gotta get invited and all this bullshit, they're
serving me this shit.
I don't even like Japanese food, what am I doing in Japan?
I think he's just not appreciating, you don't like Japanese food?
Yeah, that's culture dude.
Also, yeah, what the fuck?
Japanese food.
What?
Dude, Japanese.
- Sushi? - Okay, you know what I like
about food?
I like when food is a combination of delicious
but also nutritious.
And so much Japanese food is just carbs
that it does nothing for me.
I don't wanna eat just noodles
with like a little bit of egg in it.
I don't wanna eat just rice.
Fuck all that.
- I think you're severely mistaken.
- Yeah, I don't know what you're talking about.
- It doesn't taste that good to me either.
I don't love soy sauce all that much.
- Right. - It's not for me, man.
You know what I like?
German food.
sausage and a pretzel. Yeah. Okay. Beer. And also Japanese drinks. Don't have beer. Yeah.
The beers are okay, but what's this shit called? The rice wine? No, the other one.
The sweet one. That is soju. Soju. I do not like. Soju is Korean. Soju is Korean. Sake,
I do not like at all. Soju is too sweet. It's Korean. So. Well, but I'm speaking just of,
Now I'm just talking about these things.
Okay, I'm not even talking about Japanese stuff anymore.
You're talking about Asian cultures and...
I'm not even... I'm just saying I don't like soju.
I'm not saying... I like Korean food, actually.
Korean food to me is the better version of Japanese...
No, no, no. Korean food is the better version of Japanese food.
Because they have bulgogi. I love bulgogi.
Bulgogi is really good.
And galbi. I love any kind of Korean barbecue food.
If you come out here, we should get Peruvian food.
I've had Peruvian food.
Do you like it?
I like it okay. My aunt is Peruvian.
I don't like the hamsters.
Yeah, not that part. But I'm talking about saltado.
Which is, you know,
the mix of like fries and beef and
That stuff's good. What's the fucking, what is it called
though? The Peruvian...
It's a guinea pig.
And there's all these photos of Peruvian markets where it's just like guinea pigs, they'll
put five of them on a giant fucking stick and roast them on a grill and then you just eat
it.
Isn't there a picture that came out recently and they were like, "Yeah, fucking New York
City is turning into a dump."
I mean, I've seen them cook them here.
They cook them all the time at the Myrtle Wyckoff subway station.
You'll just see them.
You know, what the fuck is this, man?
How's this?
Cool, but I bet it's tasty.
It probably is.
I think we need to go down to some awesome
Japanese foods and you need to appreciate it.
You didn't like that one place we went.
That's fine, but that's not cracking anywhere near my top 100 restaurants
I've been to in my life.
What's some of them?
I like.
Carrabba's.
I don't know what that is.
Carrabba's is owned by the same people who owned Cracker Barrel and it's like the Italian
version.
Yep, I see.
What does Asian Jewels land in your 100 list?
I like Chinese food a lot.
I love dim sum.
Yeah.
I ordered some soup dumplings the other night and they were completely leaked empty by the
time they got to my house.
Oh.
And guess what?
I still enjoy, I loved them.
Yeah.
I think Jubio is our dim sum.
Japanese food is for me the only of the Asian gastronomic cultures that I do not care for.
Gastronometric cultures that you hate.
I don't white and sausage.
No, I literally just said I like Chinese and Korean food and I love Vietnamese food.
I love Thai food.
Who doesn't love Thai food?
Yeah, Thai food is great.
I had a Vietnamese sandwich yesterday.
It wasn't a banh mi.
It was from a Vietnamese place.
It was so good.
Like a pork sandwich.
Vietnamese food, it hits every single time, man.
Yeah, I think.
I'll tell you that right now.
Okay.
So what I'm hearing is next.
I don't like pho.
What?
What did you say?
I like pho.
And in two weeks, when our trip officially begins, we need to go, number one, on a shopping spree
to all get matching shorts and suits and makeovers.
You and me got matching jackets last time you were here.
That is true, at the Adidas store.
And then I gave mine away.
Okay, so it's...
I wear mine all the time.
I love mine.
And as soon as I got it, Caleb got so pissed at me.
And he was like, you're a copier and you copied me and I hate you.
And I was like, that's not true.
You did copy me, even though I got the much uglier orange one.
Yeah, you should have been.
I mean, you claim to be anti cooties,
and yet you have done basically what is like the HIV
to the AIDS that is cooties, which is copying. Yeah.
OK, so you better be careful now because it might turn into cooties any day now.
I know that I know I remember the time of this night exactly.
But we're just going to just producing the dealer store and
and Caleb is looking at this bright orange.
That's because you rehearsed this because it is a lie.
Yeah, I remember the timeline exactly and it actually was
different.
So well remember say it backwards if you know it so well.
Okay, so that's not backwards.
I would start at Caleb is already.
It's pissed at me because I copied him and it's just looking
this bright orange jacket and being like, "I hate this. I'm going to give this away,
this jacket that cost me like $80." And then before that, we were walking out of the Adidas store and
before that we were both buying the jackets. And before that, I decided to buy the jacket because
I loved the material. And I never had a coach jacket before. So it sounds like Caleb thought
about buying the jacket before you in this timeline of events. That's what you just said.
It is a completely, it's a completely different color.
And you don't even have yours anymore.
I mean, it's what you said.
I'm not trying to catch you in a lie, but in the reverse order,
the thing that happened last was you deciding to buy the jacket.
Okay.
It's what you just said.
If that was the case anyways, I love mine and I wear mine all the time.
I want you to go ahead and wave at the camera because you are going to be on
JCS criminal psychology very, very shortly.
I'm not going to be in JCS.
- You will be on Jaycee's for this.
- No.
- He claims that he bought the jacket first,
but he admits in the reverse telling
that he bought it well after Caleb.
- So where's your jacket then?
- You will be on that.
My jacket? - Where's your jacket then?
- Probably in the fucking bin with the rubbish.
- Okay, so you, if there was something that we share,
I guess you could just completely destroy and hate
so much that you won't keep it and wear it all the time
like I do mine. - So you admit
was the same jacket if we're sharing it.
Okay, can we move on past this?
This is stupid.
I'm trying to plan a beautiful trip.
Every time I go to New York, that's probably the most uncomfortable shirt that I've ever
worn.
I know, it's so bad.
I hate it so much.
I've never worn it once.
I might have thrown it away also.
- I think we should have a matching shopping spree,
a makeover, and a sushi eating date on the same day.
- We should find a place to get the little spinner caps
and a big lollipop. - Yes, propeller hat, yeah.
- Yeah, and little shorts.
We could all maybe just turn into little boys like that
and just go to the fanciest restaurant we can afford.
- You guys know what I think we should do?
I think this is as fun as radio can get,
is three grown men planning a child's trip to New York City.
So you know what I think that we should do, guys,
is, and also one of them lives in the city,
but what I think we should do is
we should go see Wicked on Broadway.
My second time seeing it.
- I've never been to a Broadway show.
- I went one time, my mom was in town,
she was like, "I've always wanted to see a Broadway show.
Can we go see Wicked on Broadway?
And I was like, yeah, of course we go.
And I didn't realize this shit is fucking four hours long.
Oh, yeah. What? Yeah.
And I went I ordered I was like, oh, I got to get drunk.
So I went to the bar, ordered a double Jameson.
And the guy was like, that'll be $60.
It's insane. $60.
Yeah. And I think I maybe took like I think I took an Adderall that day.
So I was just sitting there thinking about playing video games the entire time.
Oh, my God.
And then eventually I got the last half of the play,
or the musical, I'm sitting in that chair with my eyes closed.
The last half, meaning the last two hours?
Yes, the last two hours I'm sitting in the chair
basically playing Valorant in my brain for two full hours.
It was so fucking awesome.
I loved it.
Yeah, I don't want to do that.
I don't want to go to Broadway for a Broadway show.
I want to go up on the Empire State Building.
- And then jump off.
- And then I go to the Statue of Liberty
and climb it.
- So you wanna do the King Kong tour?
- Yes.
I wanna do the Elf tour actually.
- I'll do the Elf tour.
We could go to the world's best coffee place.
We walk in, we could say,
congratulations, you have the world's best coffee.
- Do you think they get people like that
every single day that they've been open?
- I think that they probably do not have that sign up.
I think that we will go to Macy's,
and then we will go to the North Pole,
and then we will go to wherever
Zooey Deschanel is taking a shower.
We'll go in there as well.
- Yeah, the Macy's employee shower.
- Well, no, just wherever she is right now,
we'll go and watch her shower for just a couple minutes
and sing at her.
Isn't she married to a property brother now?
She might not be in New York anymore.
Honestly, that would piss me off so fucking much.
I'm almost positive that's true.
Yep.
I'm pissed off.
So thanks so much for that.
You're welcome.
And yeah, I've never been to the Empire State Building.
I've sat outside of it, but I've never been inside of there.
It's like it's missing something right now.
I don't think there's anything to do in the Empire State Building.
Well, you can go.
No.
Sell that to the act of going up.
Sure.
I actually, I did take one of those like tours or whatever.
When I went to Chicago, we went on the,
I forgot what building it was.
- Sears Tower.
- Maybe, I'm not, I don't know.
There's a lot of them.
- I don't remember where that is actually.
- And yeah, sure enough, you walk in the building,
you pay for a ticket, and then there's,
they make you wait around on this like gift store.
And then you take a crazy elevator
that goes up really fast, and then you're just up,
and you just look down and take a picture,
and then they're like, "Okay, you can get out,
"get out of here, get the fuck out of here."
- Yeah, that's not my favorite.
Are you guys afraid of heights?
- Not really.
- I always think I'm not until I do some shit like that.
I went to a rooftop bar with Noah a couple weeks ago,
and--
- How tall was it?
- It was pretty tall. - Two stories.
- No, it was like probably 20 stories high,
30 stories like that.
OK, and it was it was way too scary.
I do not recommend it, but we go in here.
Yeah, well, they they have these like, you know what I wish you could say?
Let's go to the Times Square casino.
I wish you could say that.
But these NIMBYs, I know, which I learned this word recently.
NIMBY, which means not in my backyard.
OK, are basically saying I fuck it, which a lot, you know,
These good people whose back is my backyard.
Yeah, yeah.
They they're saying I don't want casinos here, which I don't understand.
Times Square is already such a fucking shithole.
Just who let it just get worse and worse and worse.
Put fucking prostitutes there.
Let's put a waste management fucking plant there.
Who gives a shit?
Pump the gas directly into the New York Comedy Club.
I don't care.
Put a casino there.
Jay-Z wants to put a casino there.
It'd be the only place in all of New York City where you can have fresh air.
Yeah.
It's an amazing idea.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
It's time to square the, uh, the, uh, the M&M Plaza.
Yes.
Okay.
I see.
It's the one with all the screens.
Are you stupid?
Okay.
You've been there.
Yeah, I've been there.
M&M Plaza.
Yeah.
Well, that's the only thing to do there.
Just go to the M&M store.
Well, I actually, we went to the Harry Potter store last time, if you
would remember correctly. No, we went to the Disney store.
And we did go to the Disney store. And Rex took a really racist picture that I've shown people a lot of times.
He took one of the most racist photos ever made.
You sexually harassed Minnie Mouse.
Me? You were sexually harassing Minnie Mouse? Yeah, you touched her breasts.
I photoed that. She's not even fucking real, mate. You were touching her?
I think you're allowed to touch. They were selling rice paddy hats.
Is it so wrong to take a picture wearing one?
They were selling rice paddy hats.
Okay, here's why it was wrong.
Here's why it was wrong, okay?
It's two-pronged.
Number one, you held your hands like this.
I do that when I go to any place.
Number two, you were standing right next to Annie,
who is Chinese.
Mm-hmm.
She was wearing my hat. It was a cultural exchange.
But again, it kind of felt like you were like...
is kind of look the photos of the circuit so i ran in chinese lady walked up
about the right that he had you're like a can i take a photo with you
for a ticket with your hands
i'm here and here's the to to work as the fact checker for this uh... this
dispute
resonate
there are a statistic they do so right studies
they would have run over ten hitlers instead of me
they were run over ten hitlers rex does do that with his hands
literally everywhere he goes up
Annie was not a random Chinese person.
I'm like the good doctor for being polite in a Japanese way.
We did go to the Nintendo store and we kept losing Annie and mistaking it for other women there.
So I think that's the most racist thing.
Okay, we can end on that because I have to leave.
That is true.
Alright, bye.