[Sipping]
[Burping]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer broadcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[Burp]
This is a journey into
[Gibberish]
I can't believe you asked can you do it into the mic so you can smell it.
What?
Let me open my beer.
You're saying nothing right now.
It's beers we drank 15.
Where's drank 15?
Hold on.
Wait, really?
Yeah.
And wait, and what, and what episode will it be?
episodes from now? 17. Okay, so I'd like you real quickly to take a look at my
beer and tell me God is not real. That's right. God could be real.
Oh my god it's Levivski 1715 and guess where it is from?
Beers, Redrinkledown. Can you read that? Nope. The red thing? Hold on. I'll just say it.
Ukraine.
Yeah.
OK, I don't see the connection to
Ukraine at all, but I see
it. It's got a weird bottle.
I picked it up because it had a
weird bottle. I'm going to take a
quick sip and give you guys a
kind of David Portnoy type
review.
Five, five, four,
five, four, five point four.
So like a five foot four
guy. So like a zero out of 10.
No.
Last week, uh, since last week's episode was such a, such a hit, such a massive hit
among the masses.
Yeah.
Uh, I went to the grocery store, uh, right before, before recording this.
And I was, I was like, I need to pick out the most colorful, the most pink, uh,
cans that I can find just like Rex did last week.
Cause he said, those were so good.
This is what I, what I came up with.
I got a lemon dao, it's in Japanese,
lemon dao, lemon sour, honey lemon,
which I think is vodka. - Sounds delicious.
- And this just says, "Begara, suava brava."
- Okay. - That sounds yummy.
- Oh, and this might interest you, Julio.
Guess what I had today on my fruit?
- Beer?
- No, try again.
- Tahini.
- Very close.
- Oh, chamoy. - Chamoy.
So I have been into different flavors this week.
So there's-- - You have entered
a completely authentic mood, is what you're saying.
- I, when I was picking up my stuff,
next to me was an L Super.
So I went to L Supermarket.
- Okay. - Mm-hmm.
And they had a section labeled cerveza.
And please tell me you indulged.
Well, I tried to get, I wanted a zero alcohol beer.
I guess I should say I'm on antibiotics right now.
So I'm drinking Jarritos that I bought.
That is bullshit that you're, no, we're not clapping.
I don't clap it up for that.
Okay.
You can drink on antibiotics.
No, they make them less effective.
Who cares?
It won't kill you.
I can't believe you got antibiotics for a cold in the first place that is a cold
most it's not a cold it's like a respiratory and oh wait it's a
respiratory it's of that's a fucking cold it's okay I don't think we talked
about this on any shows but isn't it weird how there's always some fucked up
illness going around New York every time we're in town yeah can I mean I think no
I think someone said that it could have been me bringing,
I think Noah said this, that he brought in Mexican viruses.
And then Cam said that he brought in Boston viruses.
But I don't know, it always happens.
Something crazy's happening.
- I'm gonna blame, I'll blame you.
Yeah, out of everyone who's around.
I feel like you're probably the easiest to blame.
You know, you should not be allowed into the country
like a bug that sneaks on a tomato or something
that could like ruin an entire crop.
That's kind of you.
Yeah.
You need to be like a customs agent
needs to like check every bag to see if you're in it.
And then if you are, then you'd be like,
oh, nice try, buddy.
This is not allowed.
He'll destroy the entire-
I don't think I've ever had like a negative interaction
with a custom people.
You said that you got mad the other day at the guy
'cause he was taking long.
- Well, yeah, I got mad at him because it was taking long,
but when I went through, he was just like,
"What are you doing here?"
I'm like, "Oh, I'm just gonna stay here.
"I'm gonna go see some friends."
And that's it.
- Here's me.
Here, you be the custom guy.
- Okay.
Motives of travel, why are you here?
- Pardon me?
You wanna try that again?
- Why are you in the country?
What are you coming from?
- As far as I'm concerned,
that's none of your fucking business, little guy.
How about you get out of my way?
He stands in front of the door, right?
Oh, well why do you even go up to him?
- He sits off to the right.
- Yeah. - Or the left.
- So, how it works is--
- Why are you even walking out?
You could get off the plane and just go.
- That is, okay.
So here-- - There's police there, dude.
- Here is now-- - I don't care.
- It is, we're now fully exposing
how Caleb has never even been on a plane,
let alone out to the country.
- I've actually been to Ukraine.
- So-- - I went to Lviv.
He doesn't know that when you come into the US for a foreign country, you get, you just
get sent through this like, um, hallway straight to the customs area.
You can't go anywhere else because everything is either like cordoned off or like just completely
blocked off for you to like not to access that area.
You are all led through this like, these, this, this set of hallways and you end up
at this big line, these two lines, this big room,
one of them is for nationals, US citizens.
Those you can just go in and show your thing
and you just go through, no problem.
- So why don't you just walk into that line?
- Because I am a foreigner from a foreign country.
So I have to go line up at the foreigner line
and I have to go with all the other Mexicans
and Salvadorians and Guatemalans and Asians and Europeans.
I have to stand in line, then it's just a set of cubicles.
Why not Africans?
They're also there sometimes.
Oh, okay.
Not often, though.
You skipped Africa.
It's kind of weird.
Yeah.
So, it's a set of cubicles, and you walk up,
and they just ask you, like, "Where are you here?
How long are you staying? Where are you staying?"
You know, the usual stuff.
And you always slide with them.
You don't give them a lot of details.
You just go, "I'm here for a week.
I'm gonna see some friends, I'm gonna do some shopping.
They'll be like, "You got any money with you?"
I'm like, "Nope."
"How you gonna do some shopping?"
"With my card."
And they're like, "Hmm."
- They try to do trick questions on you?
- Yeah, pretty much.
- Whoa.
- Yeah.
So next time you're,
next time you are Mexican,
and you find yourself in customs.
- If I really mess up this life
and karmically get put in Mexico in the next one,
then I will be sure to keep this in the back of my head.
Yeah. So yeah, that's my experience as a foreigner.
But you know what?
I am so glad that I'm back home.
I cannot, words cannot express how comfortable I am.
I am not in an Airbnb fested with rats.
Yeah.
That scratch my walls every day.
Yeah, I'm pretty happy you guys are gone too.
You are?
Yeah, I'm not spending any money.
I'm just sitting in my apartment all day.
Yeah, I was thinking about it's so nice to not spend so much money.
Oh, it's the best.
Oh, my God. I'm not going to Brooklyn, spending $100 on
just chicken tenders and shit.
Fuck them. Yeah, I'm back home.
I have beer. I last night's up two hours.
Last night I feel incredible today.
I don't know why.
That is the two hour buff.
Yeah, I got that perfect amount of sleep where it's basically my body
registered as a nap.
It thinks I'm in some kind of combat zone at the moment.
You're the same day as you were yesterday.
You're wearing the camo hat.
I'm wearing the camo hat.
I'm listening to
Brandon,
now,
our battlefield, bad company, Vietnam soundtrack.
I'm doing that.
Why play?
I almost said play the dishes.
Yeah, he's feeling so good right now.
I'm at 100 percent.
OK, I'm not.
Watch me flick this cap.
I flew that, I mean it went damn near four feet.
You know what? New test. Do a backflip right now.
I couldn't do a backflip even if I was well rested,
which means I probably can do one now.
Unfortunately, I have no room in my...
I mean, I have a bed. I guess I could try it on the bed.
No, I'm not going to do that.
No, no, no.
Look at Rex's face. He's so sad because he's so sick
you won't even do a back before smiling.
Rex has got the ugliest shit I've ever seen on his face.
That face is bad, but
don't say I have the ugliest shit on my face.
I'm saying that you were making an ugly shit face.
But I've also I have I have the only problem I've had.
The only thing that's been wrong with having about two hours of sleep is the
having like probably the worst acid reflux of my entire life today.
And beer is making it so much worse actively.
So,
quite a bit.
I took a,
uh,
what do you call that shit?
Like a Prilosec,
but not the delayed one.
The like,
yeah,
the immediate release.
I took like an anti acid thing.
So hopefully that helps now,
but,
uh,
yeah,
I'm not doing so hot today.
When I,
when I came home,
I took a nap.
And I get really bad acid reflux sometimes to the point where it will choke me out
while I'm sleeping. Oh yeah. And then I'll wake up just like heaving and like choking.
It happened twice when I came home. It was dope. That's awful.
Yeah, when I was like over 200 pounds, I got that all pretty much every single morning. I
I would wake up to just gargling on my own vomit,
basically like breaking that.
- It's really sweet.
- But yeah, I wasn't even able to,
they wouldn't even let me die.
It just was like the most uncomfortable feeling.
- Does this happen every night, Rex?
Does this happen in New York?
- No.
- Okay. - Just when I came back.
- So I wanna posit a possible scenario.
Maybe it's your crazy room.
- Yeah, I think it is.
It's only started since I've been in this room.
- What's so crazy about your room?
- Do you have particulate?
- I think there's particulates in my room.
I think there's mold.
- There's voice in the particulate.
- There's moldy particulates.
- I hate molded particulates, especially specific ones.
- Right. - That's awful.
- As soon as he got to New York,
the first day he was like, "Dude, I feel so good.
"I feel like I'm so energetic and I'm so awake."
I was like, "Okay, what do you mean?"
He's like, "Yeah, every time I just spend the day in my room,
I feel like so sleepy and I can't even like stay awake.
And we're like, yeah, I think there's something wrong
with your room.
- You do have molded particulate in your room.
- Yeah, I do. - There's no doubt.
You have black mold like a Extreme Home Makeover house.
You remember the, did you guys ever watch that show?
- Yeah. - Extreme Home Makeover?
- Extreme Home Makeover, where they would go
into the person's house and they would like,
behind like a bunch of people would be like,
yeah, I don't know why, but like anytime I walk
into my house, I basically fall asleep in 20 seconds
and I like pass out on the floor and my dog starts trying to get my clothes off my body.
And then they would be like, they would show the fucking, what's the handsome guy?
The car dealership man.
Chris Hansen?
No, not him.
Chris Hansen.
He would walk over to a closet and he'd move just like a bunch of recycling they had stacked
up and behind it would be like a Last of Us style, like giant black mold splotch.
and he'd be like, "I think this is the problem."
And then the people would always be like, "What?"
We had that, like something that you would,
anybody would notice this.
It's like black mold, it's black.
Most people don't have black walls.
- Yeah. - And these people
just had no idea for years and years and years.
And they're like eating it. - Did I ever show you guys
the picture of like what my ceiling looked like
in my previous room before I moved here?
- Yeah, it had all those glowing stars all over it.
- Yeah, it was so crazy.
- Big head Julio plus Caleb.
- Yeah, no, it didn't have that.
It had holes and--
- It did.
- It was falling off the roof.
- You had a custom big head made of me.
- No.
- Yeah.
- They're called fat heads.
- Fat, big, fat head made of me.
- Bald heads, that's what they're called.
- Okay, continue your story.
- I forgot what I was talking about this.
- You were talking about your ceiling.
I think I also had like a crazy fucked up feeling because I didn't really think about it but
I guess I was kind of like very low energy while I was in that room.
But not, I don't know if to the point where I'm like, it's a very noticeable difference
as Rex, as soon as he's like stepped out of his house, he's like, "Oh man, I feel so great.
I feel so good.
I want to walk around every day."
It was really funny because you know like we were walking around a bunch in New
York and my phone like the the next day after I got home was like huh your new
energy levels seem to have dropped off after yesterday something wrong do you
wear a smartwatch that tells you all that shit no wait what time is it I
I thought maybe that was the beginning of some new segment.
I guess not.
We take Rex's
accessories for watching.
What do you got? Show me.
Nothing!
Bang.
I don't have any clapping.
That's okay.
All I have is this bandaid
from where I gave blood.
You gave blood?
Okay, that way we didn't need to know that.
- They took my blood.
- Oh. - They took my blood.
- Oh, okay, so you're trying to make it sound charitable,
but you're actually just sick.
- No, I would never give my blood.
- Dude, me neither.
No matter how broke I've been in my life,
I have never once thought about giving plasma
because it scares me so bad.
I think I'd be the first person to die from it.
- Yeah, from giving plasma.
- Or I think I would be embarrassed
at how much they didn't want my blood.
- Yeah, how do you give plasma?
- This shit sucks.
There's a bunch of places.
You can give it, but you can also sell it.
Yeah.
My grandpa--
If you live in a place where there's poor people,
you will find a place to sell plasma.
Yeah.
At the apartment I lived at in Tempe
when I first moved out on my own
and got a one bedroom apartment,
on the mail thing,
there would be three different types of posters.
There was posters for like attorneys,
There was posters for selling plasma
and there was posters for selling sperm.
That was it.
- I tried to go sell my sperm one time
and then I gave up 'cause like as soon as I--
- They need so much.
- Well, I like applied online
and then they started sending me the questionnaire and shit.
I was like, oh yeah, nobody wants like a five foot nine
bald comedians come.
Nobody's like paying for this.
So then I tried to donate my shit.
- This is like the one woman that wants it.
(laughs)
- I tried to do, yeah, Rex.
I tried to donate my shit though.
- Boom.
- I tried to sell my shit.
Yeah, 'cause they do shit.
They do shit transplants for people with C. difficile
where they may have to make a poop smoothie.
But then I also have very bad shit.
- Awful poop.
- I probably have C. difficile.
So I didn't make any sense either.
So now I don't know what to do.
I have nothing to give.
- I'm learning so much today.
- Yeah, blood is like $75 per time.
It may have changed.
- But you can only do it like once
every couple of weeks, right?
- Yeah, and sperm you can do two to three times a week,
but you have to like,
that's assuming you're like not having sex,
not jacking off at all in between,
to like fill up the load cup.
Is that what you have to do?
Like a thing like they just like get your profile
and then they do like a make to order type of thing
where they like call you like,
all right, yeah, someone wants your shit.
No, I think they put it into a freezer, I believe.
Yeah, you need to give them like
your ancestry.com information.
You gotta like give them like,
you gotta have no familial like mental illness
or cancer or dementia or anything like that.
-Maybe you have to be somebody that doesn't need the money
to give sperm.
-Right.
You need to be not retarded, hot, tall.
And I don't know what person would find themselves
in that situation.
-Do you think you could ever just give them a mixture?
Just sneak in a little bottle--
-Yeah, it's a mystery box that they've fucking scraped out
from the back of the freezer when it breaks.
-Yeah, the cheap stuff should be that.
The cheaper ones for ugly girls.
Yeah, you got no fucking clue.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I think we should start with that.
Well, did you see the doctor who was just putting his own cum in women
and then he made an airplane and then it broke in midair and he died?
No, but but OK, but here's my question.
What kind of woman doesn't want to marry a doctor?
That's a great point, you know, but he also
He also made an airplane where the wings separated from it in midair and then crashed and died.
So he wasn't that kind of doctor.
He was an airplane doctor.
He was a medical doctor.
Right.
Alright, that makes sense.
Interesting.
I mean, honestly, if my doctor died in midair in an airplane he created, I would question
his ability to do surgery.
I don't think he ever did.
What do you mean he created an airplane?
He built it himself.
Okay, Bill, why did you say "created it"?
Well, I mean, that's what he did. It's like a fucking LEGO set.
He created...
He built a LEGO set.
No, you create a LEGO sculpture.
You create LEGO art.
That's not true.
LEGO TM bricks.
No.
You take...
You buy LEGO TM bricks...
...and you assemble them...
You're out of pocket, that's what you are.
...into something.
- Shut this woman up right now.
- What are you doing talking to a mirror?
Stop that.
- No.
- That looks like the biggest beer of all time.
It looks so big.
- No it doesn't.
- Yes it does.
- No it's not that big.
- Well next to your like baby head.
Don't do that.
- Why?
- You are disgusting.
- Is that bad to do that?
- Yeah.
- I should not be doing this to her.
(laughing)
Okay, I'd like to, back to the task at hand
of doing this show.
I would like to, first of all, the Celtics lost.
Yeah.
Because I had a perfectly placed reverse double curse.
Yeah. Okay?
So I am going to do a similar thing
with the Miami Denver series right now.
And I would like to say, Jimmy Butler,
you're the man, you're the champion,
you're gonna make 100 points a game.
Keep it up big guy, and we'll see you there next year
with a ring on your finger.
All right, that's the end of my little spiel.
- Yeah, this is technically the Memorial Day episode,
I guess, Memorial Day was this week.
- Oh man.
Yeah.
All of us that have real jobs that need days off in that way.
Yeah. All three of us, all three of us that celebrate Memorial Day.
I did Memorial Day over at Brian's house.
Yeah, you and I. Yeah, we we together.
Oh, yeah. I forgot you were there because you left and I played Mario Kart.
But yeah, and you weren't there for Mario Kart, which is kind of odd to me.
Memorial Day underrated holiday.
The last two Memorial days have been better
than my last two 4th of Julys,
and you can take that to the bank.
- Whoa. - July sucks.
Bullshit holiday.
- Isn't it just like kind of the same thing,
how you celebrate it?
- 4th of July?
- I know it's like two different holidays,
but you just go to a barbecue, like what's the difference?
- Well, 4th of July in New York City
is a unique kind of hell,
especially if you have a dog.
Oh, yeah.
And it's going to be three or four in the morning.
You will hear fireworks going off all around you. Yeah.
And it might as well be
this motherfucking country that's on this beer
when this shit starts popping off on July 4th and when.
And maybe when you first moved to New York City,
you don't know that much about the fireworks stuff.
And somebody started setting off fireworks in your neighborhood on July 2nd.
And you were in the middle of the shower and you thought it was gunshots
being shot into your building and you stayed in your bathroom for two hours.
That's really embarrassing.
I would have ran at the gunman.
I would have been naked.
Your mouth open.
Ah, ah, pointing in your mouth.
I would have been jumping on the bullets
to save your the front of your building.
Yep. I would have.
I would have jumped on them and made them die.
I keep getting shocked.
Isn't it like crazy illegal to like do fireworks instead of a city?
Nobody gives a fuck about any fucking law in New York City, dude.
It's all I mean, it's nothing you can you can do.
You can do anything.
There's you can do heroin.
It's because they have cops for every specific like there's firework cops.
Is there really?
I'm sure there's traffic cops, but then there's also parking cops.
But then there's also like every different kind of cop.
Guy cops, there's girl cops.
Girl cops only handle crimes with makeup and handbags and period stuff.
Period blood. If they see blood on the street, they go up and they go, "Oh, okay."
And then they smell it and they go, "Oh no, this is not... Sorry, this is not my jurisdiction."
This clearly came from a body.
When we were at Brookland one night, I went into the bathroom and there was just period blood all over the toilet seat.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What?
- Yep, no wait, hang on, hang on.
Before he finishes the story,
I want him to read through this
and phrase it the way he phrased it
when he told me and Noah, I think.
- I've read the poem, I said.
- He walks up to me and he goes like,
dude, I walked into the bathroom at Brooklyn
and there's completely like a girl having her period there.
I was like, whoa, what?
He just walked into someone having her period there?
He's like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
There's just blood there.
I was like, oh, I don't care.
- I mean, it's disgusting,
but being a girl having her period,
It's a score.
You got, it's a score.
You got a third base.
I think I was a little drunk and I said, "Dude, there's some bitch having her pussy all over
the toilet seat."
That's more disgusting.
The way you phrased it is worse than putting your bloody, whatever it's called.
Yeah, you must apologize.
Yeah, I do feel like, because gamer guys are disgusting.
A gamer girl is like filth, just like pure trash.
A lot of people don't even go there.
A lot of people just go there for the bar part, though.
So it could be just so.
Yeah, it's very funny.
Yeah, I like Flores.
Yeah. Telling a girl like, yeah, I got a I got a place for you.
You have to go on like tonight and then you're ordering the princess peach.
Yeah, that's so cool.
But I'm going to order you the blue shell.
I think we've ever ordered one of those like gay drinks.
I've never gotten one of the cocktails.
Which is just going, which is like, yeah, I'll just like a Bud Light or whatever.
Yeah, I mean, they're just because they're expensive and I'm sure they're so fucking bad.
Yeah.
Speaking of...
Remember the tequila shot there was like paint thinner, dude.
Yeah, yeah, it's gas.
Speaking of Brooklyn, last time we were there, I fully ripped the fucking crotch of these jeans open.
I didn't have any underwear on and my balls were hanging out.
(laughing)
- Yeah, you guys are not disgusting.
- No, dude, we're good guys.
- Wait, how did you do this?
- I don't even know, I just was sitting there
and I was like, "God, it's cold in here."
And then I kind of looked like I was fingering,
like if my jeans were my skin and I was a woman,
it's exactly where my pussy would be.
- So, this was when we had a party with seven people
at the Brooklyn thing?
- Yeah, and then I was just like,
"All right, whatever, I'm just gonna park it here
"and just fucking, if it gets worse,
"I'll walk over to the place next door
"and get a new pair of pants,
"or I'll send one of you guys over
"and I'll hide the bathroom."
But I didn't come to that, and I'm still wearing them.
But now I know to wear underwear with them.
(laughing)
'Cause if I had just fully ripped my pants open
and my asshole and balls were out.
- I think you're like the one person in the world
that I just keep hearing stories about how
your balls keep just like flying out of your pants.
- My pills.
- Because you're--
(laughing)
- My pills.
- You're just never, ever wearing underwear.
- You know what it is?
Okay.
You know what it is?
I don't, in the mornings, when I take the dog out,
I roll out of bed.
I just put on whatever pair of pants, go commando.
- Why? - I get changed
for the rest of the day later.
- You go Winnie the Pooh in the bed?
- Yeah, I go Winnie the Pooh in the bed.
- Okay.
- And then I get, and then I go outside
and then I come back in and then usually I get changed,
but every once in a while, maybe once a week,
once every two weeks, I go commando for the whole day
'cause something grabs me right as I get inside.
- Right.
Such as going to a completely different part of the city.
No, I think actually that day was because I was out of clean underwear.
OK, I wear dirty underwear.
I guess that makes sense.
Because because trust me, my dirty underwear are dirty.
I stink them up, I shit in them.
I use them to wipe my ass.
They're not a good thing to have.
You can't I never worn underwear twice.
It's it would be impossible.
Yeah, we have to completely fix that.
There's literally something wrong with you.
Why is there something wrong with me?
You wear underwear twice?
Sure.
Oh, God!
What is wrong with you?
I wear underwear all the time, dude.
Twice?
One pair you'll wear twice before washing it?
I mean, I'll wear it until...
Oh, it's a yes!
Oh, he's disgusting!
I don't even want to see...
I'll wear it until I change them to a different pair.
I don't want you to see me.
Sometimes that's like an hour, and sometimes...
What are you doing with these underwear in one hour?
That is worse than anything Caleb just said.
An hour?
What are you doing in an hour?
You just showered, you just got changed, what are you doing in an hour?
It turns out I don't have enough time to shower so I just swap the underwear out for some
cleaner ones, go walk around for a bit, come back, then I shower.
Oh, okay.
That's weird.
That is weird.
No, it's not.
I mean, your nuts and your butthole still stink like shit if you've been...
First of all, my asshole is clean as a whistle.
I have a bidet.
That's true.
Not in New York City where you just were.
That is true.
And that's why I did not...
We had wet wipes.
We did have wet wipes.
You're not animals.
I did shit before I showered almost every time.
- In proper order. - Yeah.
I would hope so.
- Oh, he's got us. - You don't shower.
You don't shower before you shit.
- Well, I mean, not intentionally.
Yeah, not intentionally.
You're saying you never shit after a shower?
You've never been in the shower
and the warmth, the beautiful comfort
releases the chemicals into your brain
that makes you need to shit?
- You're making it sound like really pleasant,
but if I'm ever in the situation where I'm taking a shower
and I feel like taking a shit,
it's probably like the worst day of my life
because it feels like I wanna spend an hour in the bathroom.
- You know, I've heard multiple people now,
and adults, mind you,
tell me that they will take a shit,
not wipe their ass,
and then get into the shower and wash their poopy asshole.
Without wiping.
And every single person who's ever told me this
has had a roommate.
who they share a shower with.
So they're putting poo-poo in the shower
that they share with their roommate.
- I mean, that's fine, it's clean down there.
- That's disgusting, you are a disgusting monkey
if you think that's okay to do.
- I mean, I would never do that, but.
- I think the proper order would be to at least dry wipe
and then step directly into the shower
and then just put the water in your ass.
- I took a shit in the shower earlier today.
I did my ass.
But I did not.
Wipe it down.
If it's still a little wet and I just bought directly.
We have a bidet that's different for sure.
Yeah.
It was good.
It's this
popping into the shower with an already wet ass is kind of a
crazy.
It's not that crazy.
That's got to feel crazy to be getting in there.
It was a crazy shit that required taking the shirt off.
I'm still anti it.
You know, people say that I've never had that.
I've never had a no shirt shit.
Why not, dude?
You're clearly not enjoying shit.
Sometimes you just need to take your shirt off.
It gets hot.
You're like an engine that's been running too hot.
Do you ever squeeze, if you get hot while you're shitting,
do you ever squirt the bidet just to cool yourself off
like a Gatorade in the middle of your shit.
No, dude, it's up top.
It's up here where it gets hot.
I'm like having a head rush.
But wouldn't it be a little refreshing halfway through a shit?
It does feel good.
I have to have that.
Especially like a dual flusher.
I will squirt.
What's a dual flusher?
Oh, you mean the shit where you have to flush twice.
OK.
Now I understand, a dual flusher.
A dual flusher.
Remember that B-Reel that you took where you almost pussied your dick into the toilet?
Did you take one where you almost pussied your dick?
Yeah, I was taking a shit and I was in the bathroom.
You did a B-Reel where you're shitting?
I wanted to be on time, dude.
That's the realest shower ever.
(laughter)
I just kinda had my arm
like down here like this.
For our listeners,
the way Rex's bathroom works is
the door has a mirror
at the back of it and the
door is rarely in front of his toilet.
So, he
he gets the
notification sound
it's time to be real and he decides
be the realest that he's ever been in his entire life. The realest motherfucker on the planet.
Okay, so let me explain this. I went to go take the photo and I was like, oh wait,
the mirror, like I can't take a mirror selfie, that would be insane. I'm shitting,
they'd see my penis. Let me just take a front-facing selfie of myself on the toilet,
they won't see anyone. They forgot it takes the photo from behind.
(laughter)
- Not for the grace of God that I just was a knuckle
dragger at that moment and had my arm covering my penis.
I absolutely would have posted my dick on B-roll.
- Oh my God.
- You also would have, you can do a retake.
- I didn't look at it before I posted it.
- He just let it fly.
- I let it fly, I didn't think about it too hard.
- You know what?
- They're getting the realest motherfucker on earth.
He's not gonna check the B-Rio.
- They should give you the word for being the most real.
- Yeah, they honestly, you should get like
a YouTube play button for B-Rio.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Or at least a coffee mug.
- I was in a beautiful moment.
I didn't realize what happened until Julio was like,
did you just post your fucking dick on B-Rio?
(laughing)
- I think about posting my balls online all the time,
or my asshole.
- Why?
- I just think it'd be funny,
I mean it's just funny that I can make
thousands of people see my asshole if I wanted to.
That's funny.
- I know you're addicted to showing your balls to people.
That was one thing you told me when we--
- Whoa, don't go around saying I'm addicted
to showing my balls to people.
I'm gonna open up this.
- Especially strangers, especially women on the street.
- No, no, no, no.
- This is not cold enough.
- Me and Patrick have a-- - I need to make this cold enough.
- Have a dick and balls war that we've been in
for about four years now.
But for showing or for like sack tapping showing
showing each other.
It started with one time we were at a bar and
I took his phone or he I took his phone and I took a bunch of pictures of my
dick in the bathroom while I was pissing and then I brought it back and I was like,
hey man, you left your phone in the bathroom.
He's like, oh, thanks.
And there's a bunch of pictures of my dick
missing into the toilet.
(laughing)
- That's the gayest thing I've ever heard.
- He said it was the reddest dick he's ever seen in his life.
(laughing)
- All right, I'm drinking Lagunitas Tiki Fusion
zombie cocktail inspired IPA, hazy IPA
with notes of orange, lime, grapefruit, and allspice.
And I hate to say it, this is a 10% beer.
- You are going to die. - Which I did not know
when I bought it.
Let's just take a little sip.
- If you were to take a swig,
I'd just completely fall asleep immediately.
- Oh my God, it's amazing.
- Yeah.
- How do you guys feel about Lagunitas?
Have you had Lagunitas?
- Good, yeah.
- A little something, a little something.
- I used to drink it. - I have.
- I used to drink a little,
me and Neil used to split a six pack of fucking Lagunitas
every night pretty much in college.
But for me, I had spent,
Neil didn't eat much and he was skinny.
And that's three IPAs from Lagunitas,
probably about 900 calories.
Yeah.
And I didn't really know how to drink.
I was pretty new to drinking in college.
I didn't really think of it as calories or anything.
So I would spend all day eating McDonald's
and French fries and barbecue wings
and then I would get home and drink about 1,000 calories
worth of beer every night.
[laughter]
How did that make you feel?
It made me feel fat.
I very seldomly spring for an IPA, but I do like this one.
And I always go, if I'm going to buy an IPA, I go Lagunitas for the most part.
I think I need to get like a...
Not a fan of IPAs.
I need to order like an IPA case.
Just to have like interesting beers.
IPAs have really great, like, well...
They have above average like art, and there's a lot of effort put into them.
Sometimes they're called, you know, fuck ass shit ale.
And that shit's funny.
The dogfish, bitch, bitch,
fuck you, asshole, motherfucker.
That shit is funny.
The arrogant bastard.
And they have the guy who did the fear and loathing in Las Vegas.
Fucking yeah.
Art do the thing.
It's cool.
Yeah, we could do it.
We could do it up here.
Easily.
Beer, beer, you're drinking.
Beer, you drank beer, you'll drink beer, you'll drink.
You are about to drink.
That's I mean, we've talked about this, right?
I don't think we've mentioned the name, but that that if any breweries
micro or macro want to get in touch with us about doing a small batch thing
or fuck it, maybe I'll just do some in my garage.
Yeah.
OK.
Yeah, we can do one of your...
They're going to replace Bud Light with Beer You Drink Light.
Beer You Drink.
Yeah, well, you do Beer You're Drinking and Beer You're Drinking Light.
You could have all sorts of...
And then it could be the style of the beer goes before the names.
It could be IPA Beer You're Drinking, Sour Beer You're Drinking.
Yeah.
That's a great idea.
It is.
That is a great idea.
It should be branded like IKEA furniture.
Yeah, it should be very...
Like just like plain block text.
Box water.
Yeah.
but also it has cartoon versions of all of us and we're smoking weed and playing
basketball yeah that's a good idea yeah I'm dunking Julio into the dunk me well
no my head's a basketball and you two are doing a tip-off yeah okay that's
like that's a good concept there's a raft that's throwing you in the air yeah yeah
it's drawn exactly like a like a Ben Garrison style like kind of political
cartoon, where they have like giant heads,
I was thinking airbrush.
That would be cool.
Yeah.
That would be actually really cool.
Everything is labeled.
Yeah, everything is perfectly labeled.
Basketball bald head.
Basketball.
Circle.
Guy.
Periphery.
Yes.
Woke.
Mexican.
Wokeism.
Jew.
Okay.
Will we do the first, I mean, I guess that's the question now
that beer is kind of the forefront of the culture, where
if, is, are we going to do a woke beer or an anti-woke beer?
- I think we should do one of those things
where we're just like, we're straddling the line.
We're like really booking fun,
and like, "Oh, this is so silly," on our Twitter account.
But we keep releasing LGBTQ pride beers every single month.
- Or we should do the opposite.
Where we are like on--
- Oh, woke on Twitter, and then the cap is a red baseball cap.
- Or we're doing all the same donations
Chick-fil-A and shit. We're like giving money to like the conversion therapy places and stuff.
But on Twitter, we're doing like the, what's that shit called? The meat steak-ems shit.
You know, all that kind of stuff. Yeah. Okay.
It's a good idea. I think Woke is coming back. We should do Woke.
I agree. I think for a little bit, the stocks on Woke were way low.
Low. But now...
It's coming back.
It's going right back up, so I'd like to say that.
Where I'm I'm all in on woke.
I'm all in.
I look I want to be woke as can be.
And he woke is the new woke.
It's gay.
Yeah, exactly.
And I can't even say that it's it's
it's a head fuck ass.
Yeah, it's garbage.
Yeah. What is God?
It's gay.
It's lesbian.
It's it's hot.
I mean, you can't say it's lame.
It's a yes. Yeah, you can't even say lame.
Yeah, I mean, it's definitely hard to say to us to be woke.
You can't even say dog and cat in woke ism.
So I can't.
I apparently not according to my dogs or men and cat or my guess.
Talk about it.
According to you, according to my guess,
according to what I think, according to my what I'm thinking.
Yeah, you can't even say dogs or cats.
You have to call them.
- I'm not a...
(laughing)
- Tailed fellows.
- Two pets.
(laughing)
- You're a...
- Y'all are tailed fellows, better listen up.
- No, I actually do like wokeism though,
and I think the police should be enforcing it.
- Yeah, I think I'm gonna step in here and say
that all this culture war shit,
I think it's complete bullshit.
I spent--
- Get out of town.
I don't have like an epic.
Shut up, bitch!
Okay, that's my epic sound drop.
Come on, man.
No, no, no, no, no.
I just spent 10 days in the US and not once did I see a woke or anti-woke sentiment type
action in my entire stay.
You didn't see one of those, oh, I saw a guy today walking around Brooklyn with SS bolts
tattooed all over his neck and he had one of those fucking skull and cross
was Nazi skull and crossbones in the middle of his throat.
And here's the best part.
And then he walked into your apartment and started to do this podcast.
All right.
You're going to miss out on the funniest punch line of all time
that I had about this guy.
But can you please tell me the punch line?
OK, so guy has SS bolts
clearly like both sides of his neck, SS bolts.
He's got the skull and crossbones.
but on his head,
do-rag,
Dominican flag.
- Okay.
- The guy was a Dominican guy,
walking around with like white supremacist
prison tattoos all over his head.
- That makes sense.
- Yeah.
- How does that make fucking sense?
That's crazy.
- I don't know.
- He went for the la raza.
- What are you talking about?
- Even if you're white,
whenever I drive past like poor neighborhoods in Mexico,
I see swastika, graffiti.
- Oh, that is so funny.
- That is dope.
- Oh, graffiti is different.
If you saw like flags, I would be like,
every, I feel like swastika.
- I saw a flag once in like a really popular market, but.
(laughing)
- There was a Mexican dude outside of Pizzeria Panina,
and he had like a skull tat that was literally
what I imagine the Mexican version of Mr. Cool Ice would be.
It's dope as fuck.
Was that the buff girl you saw?
Yeah.
It was Mr. Cool Ice but it had a mustache.
Oh yeah.
So it looked like them Wartos Megawiz skull.
Yeah it was dope.
That's cool.
You know what I'm not I'm not too big a fan of the the rocks method of picking up.
Well it's time to open the Japanese one.
Um no it's not cold.
I'm gonna save it.
You can't save it.
You already burned it on this episode.
No I didn't.
Yes you did we saw it motherfucker.
What does it look like?
It's got an orange top and uh.
- It's just to add ice.
I know, okay.
I'm not getting more ice.
- You already have ice. - All right, that's fine.
- There was ice in the glass.
- Whoa. - So finish the drink.
- Look at how cloudy that looks.
- You just got fucking owned.
- It tastes bad.
- Guys, this is a Doritos.
- That's the different thing.
That's the soda, the sody.
- This is good.
It's really tough to get down though.
Like I, my taste buds can't tell that it's 10%,
but I feel like my body can.
Oh, this is, we should be reading
the descriptions on the show.
This is, people who work in beer need to die instantly.
A forewarning for your senses,
this exotic fusion of flavors has been crafted
to conjure cocktailian notes of orange juice,
fresh lime, grapefruit, and allspice,
and brewed without summoning any liquor spirits.
Our homage to the original zombie and tiki movement,
both created in our home state of California,
B-Y-O-T-U naturally, so bring your own tiny umbrella.
Cheers.
What does it mean, zombie?
- Cocktailian.
- Cocktailian zombies.
- I'm eating some cocktailian wieners right now.
- Come on.
- We should do a Only Local Viewers episode next week.
I'm down to do that.
Sure.
Yeah, I'll just get some Mexican beer
and I'll be able to easily drink it.
You can do a Modelo?
Bullshit, no, I'm not gonna do a Modelo,
I'm gonna do a Carta Blanca.
What's a Carta Blanca?
Is that a one that they don't have up here?
It's a really popular beer.
I would assume that you guys would have it.
Maybe, I'm not sure. I've never heard of that.
It's a really popular beer. Modelo time.
Yeah, I'll probably do something,
I mean, probably every beer I've had up here
probably in New York. All the like shit ones in cans.
Yeah. Yeah. Those crazy ones that we were drinking last week were like put in the Bronx according
to the cans.
We need to get.
And they'll taste it so bad.
You know, going back to doing this on online, I'm fully convinced that we need to get a
full time beers we drink studio in Las Vegas where we fly out to once a month. We stay
- We stay for four days.
- We drink.
- We record one episode every day.
And we get fucked up.
- Okay.
- We do all of the stuff that us three like doing.
We drink, we gamble, we watch two movies every single day.
And we use a randomizer feature to decide the movies.
- I feel like that's so easily doable.
- Yeah.
I think we should do that, but we should record like a year's worth and force ourselves to just...
There's no way I could drink a year's worth of beer in one...
Any amount of time, even a year.
You can't drink 52 beers in a week?
I do two per episode, buddy.
Okay, you can't drink a hundred beers in a week?
How much do you think we drank this past week?
Not a hundred beers.
I think we drank about 200 beers.
Between all three of us, we probably drank,
if you count every drink as a beer,
every sip.
We probably drank 60 beers between the three of us.
Yeah, me and Rich were talking about this,
how we never ever drink when we're home.
Yeah.
And then we just go to New York and every single day we're like,
I don't know, let's just go hang out somewhere and just drink a beer.
It's fun, man.
Good and clean fun.
- I hate getting drunk. - It's so fun.
- I hate getting drunk. - We just like sit around
and just like play Mario Kart.
- But isn't that much more fun to do
if you're having just maybe 15 or 16 beers?
That's good.
- Yeah.
- It's so much fun. - I don't feel that way.
- We don't know anybody who likes smoking weed.
I don't like smoking weed.
- That is true, no one smokes weed.
- Jumio is a bit of a herb head.
- No.
- Yeah, yeah, you are, admit it.
- I think it's time for you to come clean
with your story about me smoking weed
at one time. I think I should debunk your own lie.
Here's what really happened. We were watching Mac and Devin go to high school. It's the
first time Juvio's ever left his home. He's in New York City. Him and Rex are at my apartment.
It's Noah.
No, not Rex. Sorry. Him and Noah are at my apartment. They're both staying there for
10 days. My wife hated me so much because we had two guys in our apartment every single
day.
One of them was a Mexican guy from the internet that you had never met before.
And anyway, we're watching Mac and Demi go to high school.
Me and Noah start smoking weed and we basically, we pin Jubio down.
We actually, okay, here's what happened.
Jubio said, "No, no, no, no, no.
I don't want to smoke weed.
Please, no, no, no, no, no, no, no."
We backed him up into a wall and then I pulled out four throwing knives and I threw them
so perfectly that they pinned each of his sleeves and both of his pant legs to the wall
so he couldn't move at all, right?
And I said, "Tough shit, buddy.
This is a one-way ticket to Toketown."
And I put the whatever it was, I don't even remember what we smoked out of.
It was a pen.
A pen.
I put it in your mouth and basically the rest is history.
Right.
- This story is never gonna come out truly.
- I don't honestly remember what happened.
I was fucking high, I mean I was high.
What happened?
- We can talk about that another day.
I think it's a funny thing to just like never really--
- Jubio claims he didn't get high, but he got fucked up.
- Not true.
- He got fucked up, he was crying.
- Do you guys think this mustache makes me look
like a certain German figure from history?
- The mustache, yes, it is a full,
You're like, it's so scary that your body naturally
like wants to look like Hitler.
Like your hair grows like him.
- That's not true. - Your mustache.
You look exactly like Mexican Hitler.
- It's just because of the video.
I don't look like this in real life.
I look like the one in real life.
- I mean, you look like that in every photo too.
Your mustache just naturally grows really thick.
- Take the glasses off.
Let's see. - Between these two parts.
- You know how Hitler has that face where he's like,
make that face.
What's that face?
- Just like do this, like, "Whoa!"
- Good Lord, dude.
- It looked exactly like--
- Born in Brazil or Mexico, come on now.
- That is crazy.
That'd make a lot of sense-- - It's not true.
- If you were a descendant of Adolf Hitler.
- Yeah, just like six foot tall Mexican guy.
- Yeah.
- Just towering over-- - Alabaster white skin.
- Hitler mustache. - Hateful, hateful ideas.
I'm completely, 100 out of 100, autentico Mexican.
- You are not.
You are mostly Spanish.
- I don't think I'm mostly Spanish,
but I feel like I do have some Spanish shit.
- You are fully conquistador.
- No.
- Yeah, you are.
Right?
- No.
- You mentioned like Louis C.K. is Mexican.
- Yeah.
- I think if we met, I think we would really hit it off.
I think we would be friends.
You and Louis CK?
Yeah.
Do you speak Spanish at all?
What in particular do you have in common with him?
Don't say it.
Mexican.
That is true.
Both born in Mexico.
Both Mexicans who speak English, the first of their kind, according to some people.
Yep.
Are they rich, too?
Both of you are Chino?
I'm not Chino.
You're Chino.
Oh you're Chino. Am I? You are, you're Chino. Did I talk about how I got assaulted by a
white liberal woman in New York? No. Oh the lady whose house we were at that
day? Yeah, so I guess I did, I was participate to like a woke
a book as an attack on my person.
This white lady who claimed to be a hippie
just kept asking me how I knew how to speak English
and where I was from.
And I was like, "Oh, I'm from the northern part of Mexico."
And she's like, "Oh, well just this morning
"there was a shooting there and 10 people died.
"You must have heard about that."
I was like, "No, not at all, I don't know."
She's like, "Check your,"
I opened, so after she says that,
I open up my phone-- - Don't tell me she said
check your WhatsApp.
No, I opened my Twitter and she's like,
yeah, just check your feed.
You'll surely find it there.
I was like, okay, thank you, ma'am.
And then she left me alone.
But I wasn't really a victim.
- She doesn't realize that you only follow
basically all the members of FaZe
and no Mexican media outlets, nothing like that at all.
- And Grace Van, what's her name?
What's her name?
The Grace Bitch?
- Van Buren?
- Yeah, something like that.
- Who's ruining Faye's clan?
- Oh, I-- - Ruining, dude.
- See, okay. - Come on.
- I have been worried. - That hoe.
- I've been worried about learning about this story
because I just didn't feel right talking about it
without you two around,
and thinking about it without you two around.
So next week, once everyone's forgotten about that,
I'd like all of us to come in
with a take on this whole thing.
I think she quit Faze, so that's a perfect time to talk about it.
What is the whole, I mean, I don't even know what the,
do you know what the name is? I don't know. It seemed very boring.
She doesn't know about modern warfare too.
She doesn't know about trick shots. She doesn't know about 360 no scopes.
She's mid AF. She's a whore.
I don't know. I'm kidding.
I think I saw a video about this and they talked about how
She's ruining FaZe Clan by being a woman.
No.
Listen, there's so much more wrong with FaZe other than inviting a woman to unfaZe.
In my opinion.
Like, giving all that money to Snoop Dogg and his son.
All that shit with going public. I mean, come on guys.
Also, I don't have any-
I hate when gaming goes corporate and they start hiring women via diversity and inclusion and equity.
Okay, so Faze signed her and then this guy who's in Faze got mad about it.
But then she just left.
Well, the OGs got mad about it.
That's pretty funny. The OGs.
So she, he was like, she doesn't know about Modern Warfare.
She's never seen a trickshot montage.
She's golden Valorant.
Whoa!
That's not forgivable.
She was like, you almost overdosed on, on stream two years ago.
Whoa.
Here's like, Oh, you're actually bid your mid.
Oh my God.
I love this kind of drama.
They had a conversation they had.
And then, well, after that, they had a sit down to hash it out.
Yeah.
And then I didn't learn anything about that conversation, except that she said
if they posted it, she would leave face clan and they posted it and then she left.
Damn.
We should turn into like a Keemstar
style drama thing.
Yeah.
This show should be pure
TMZ or...
But in the way that we just did it
just now, where only one of us kind of
knows what happened.
You were like, that's crazy.
I think I kind of heard about that.
You're getting all the details wrong.
Yeah.
Well, tooth dies in darkness.
You know that.
Tooth dies in darkness?
Truth dies in darkness.
Democracy dies in the darkness, as The Washington Post thing.
And my lights are bad.
I feel like everyone explains stuff so poorly now.
Do you think that was that's always been how people explain stuff?
It's like, I think I heard like, yes, like
about like Pearl Harbor or something.
Do you think it was like, dude, I think I heard about that?
What was that again?
He's like, yeah, it's some fucking Chinese guys.
Ten or or like 100 like Chinese guys with like a bunch of they were.
I think they were, they had parachutes or paragliders.
- You know what's the prime example of this?
- What?
- Jesus Christ, the Bible.
- That's true.
- I can't believe you have the balls to say that to me.
- God's only forgotten, son.
- Begotten.
He was not foregotten, he was begotten.
(laughing)
It's actually the line in the Bible.
- Where'd he go?
- Oh, it's in Israel.
- Oh shit, yeah, God's sitting there.
- Oh shit, I left that guy.
- Oh fuck, I have a son.
I think I left him.
Wait, what's he's doing?
- God did the equivalent of leaving a baby in a hot car.
- Yeah, exactly.
(laughing)
Yeah, oh fuck.
Yeah, 'cause for him it was only like three hours.
It was 33 years on Earth, but.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, do you think he cared?
- He just popped in for two beers at the bar
and left Jesus in the car.
- Do you think he cared at all?
I'll be right back.
No, just chill. It's chill. Hey, can you watch him?
Can you watch him? Make sure he doesn't get crucified.
See what, yeah. What if you left your baby with your,
with your dog for one minute and you came back,
the dog was crucifying your baby.
I would think that was Jesus Christ.
I would honestly think the baby was, or the dog was Jesus Christ.
My child was the antichrist.
What do you guys think of that movie Mother?
I've never watched it.
I don't even know, is that a movie?
Yeah, Darren Aronofsky?
Nah, I don't care about...
Is that motherfucker who did Black Swan?
I'm curious, I just was thinking about...
You're stupid. You know what I was watching on the plane?
I was watching the Super Mario Bros. movie
and I didn't finish it.
The old one?
The new one.
Oh, nah.
I watched the first 10 minutes of The Whale, which I didn't realize he's gay in it
and I turned it off.
(laughing)
I know those aren't,
I know those aren't related, but
just your tone of voice
in these two separate anecdotes,
man, it sounds so intentional.
(laughing)
- Okay, so for next week,
I'm gonna finish the Super Mario Bros. movie.
Rex is gonna finish the whale,
and Caleb's gonna learn about the fish situation.
- It's actually not that even,
not even that good a movie, honestly.
- What, the whale?
- Yeah.
Do you watch it?
- No, I don't like when people are fat.
No, I just don't, I don't like the--
- It is uncomfortable to watch.
- I truly don't care for powerhouse performances
in bad movies.
You know what I mean?
- He is completely fat to an uncomfortable degree.
- I don't like movies that are like six out of 10 movies
that have an amazing star turning performance.
That's like, to me, even if I might like the movie
when I watch it, it's like not a motivating,
it's not gonna make me watch it.
- I didn't like that he was like having a heart attack
from jacking off because that also happens to me.
That's what happened to the movie.
That's the start of the movie.
He's jacking off to gay porn on his laptop.
- Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, hang on.
You saw this, this is the first minute of the movie,
and you waited 10 minutes after that to be like,
wait, he's gay, and you turn it off.
(laughing)
- Wait, also, two more things.
Number one, you said it happens to you
that you get a heart attack when you jack off.
- To gay porn.
- Yeah, and then the other thing is to gay porn.
But also, you said it happens, you turned it off
because something in the movie happens to you
and it's about a guy who's 600 pounds.
- Yeah, I know.
It's embarrassing, I didn't wanna see that.
(laughing)
- 'Cause they're thinking, they don't even,
they're just thinking like,
what would happen to a 600 pound guy?
Oh, he probably gets a heart palpitation
when he masturbates.
- Well, listen. - That's the only
kind of person. - If you guys,
if you guys don't care to watch the whole movie,
the ending, he gets completely skinny
and he lives his life happily ever after.
And he gets back with his wife.
- Oh yeah.
- Why?
- With his wife.
He's gay.
- He's gay.
We gotta go.
We gotta go. - All right, bye.