mm-hmm
you're listening to beers we drink my god
What's up all my chuggers?
Trying to get that boop out there.
This is a journey into space.
Beers we drank motherfucker.
With Jubio, Caleb and Rex.
Beer. Holy shit.
We're back at it again. Hold on wait my fingers. Oh and I hit my monitor.
I
Hope I'll be right a brand to look at how big this bottle is it's as big as my head even
So big it gets blurred you got to turn that blur off because we can't see what this can is man
You also have the way let me guess. Oh, never mind
That was what I was gonna guess
It isn't a 25 ounce
Bud Light Orange
Get the blur on
Go ahead and tell us about it
And get the camera on
Alright, you want me to turn the blur off? You're all gonna make fun of us
Why do you sound so fucked up also?
I sound fucked up?
Hold on, let me
There we go, use your microphone like a microphone
Yeah, talk into the mute button
How do I sound now?
Better
This is better?
Yeah, much much better
I have a single cable on the ground
Yo, what's up?
Got me fucked up
Pick up that cable right now
No.
Alright, Rex, you already showed us your beer, you already showed your hand my friend.
Go ahead and take a sip, give us a rating, and let's do this shit.
This is delicious.
This is like an 8.
An 8.0.
That's an amazing beer man.
Give me a basketball height.
That's like 6'11 dude.
That's a fucking star.
I love that beer.
You can build a team for 15 years around this beer.
Yep.
I hope that one day I get to taste a flavored Bud Light.
But that shit is... I will never see that in Mexico.
And this one doesn't hurt the cap table because this is fucking $3 for this big-ass beer.
That's true.
But the Bud Light Orange, the six packs, they're 10 bucks.
They come in these nice beautiful glass bottles.
They're almost indescribably orange.
It's definitely has so much fucking coloring in it and shit.
it's such a fucked up thing to put in your body, but I love them.
And I've never gotten a six pack of Bud Light oranges and not finished it instantly.
Yeah, this is-
'Cause it tastes like soda!
It does- this literally does taste like- like Fanta.
Yeah.
This is amazing.
I love Fanta.
I might- I might even up this to an 8.5.
Whoa!
Wait, wait, ring the alarms!
That might be the highest rating ever done on this show.
And we go Portnoy, by the way, with the ratings.
This is a- it's a-
Nine Max.
and
Save the Robots East Coast IPA
as well. It's an IPA, it is from Radiant Pig. Yep, thank you for that. This is, uh, the party
is just getting started for East Coast IPAs and we're keeping things moving with a fresh
take on this style. This hazy, unfiltered gym has juicy, inflicted beer. This afflicted
Red beer has juicy tropical and citrus flavors, but finishes surprisingly smooth for such
an aggressive amount of hops.
Guys, this is three hoppy and two juices.
This is...
On the...
This.
Some people only tell me this is reddit beer.
This is a complete reddit beer.
Yeah, it is, but they sell it at every corner store in New York now.
You guys know my wife.
She is about as reddit as they come.
This is for an IPA.
This is juicy, guys.
There's no doubt.
I give this three juicy drops just like on the can.
Three juicy drops?
Are you trying to gamble later?
Three juicy drops.
Maybe.
But as far as the scale, I'm going to give this a 6.7
and a 6 foot 4 on the basketball player scale.
Well, to counterbalance Caleb's readiness,
I went to the Walmart and I got just a big ass German beer.
- Oh my God.
- The Erdinger.
- Yeah.
- Erdinger, Weisbrau.
- The Erdinger, Weisbrau.
- The Erdinger.
- Yeah, I barely know her.
- It's a light beer.
It says Bavarian double maturity method,
which I don't know what that means.
I guess it's mature.
- Well, I think you're about to find out pretty shortly.
*takes a sip*
It tastes like a beer.
You suck- you suck at this so-
*laughs*
You suck- you suck man.
You are shit at this bro.
Tell me the notes.
Tell me the notes bro.
It's got hoppy notes, it's got um
Beer notes,
He's just gonna list all the ingredients. He's listing the ingredients.
You fucked up dude.
It's called- well they're in Spanish.
I can't believe you just listed them up.
what they're calling it.
Because you can't read Spanish, we caught you.
We caught you, you don't speak that bullshit language.
Nobody does, they all just make it up.
It tastes like this.
It basically means beer, don't lie.
So screenshot this and turn it backwards, this is what it tastes like.
It's actually really good, it's really light and it's not disgusting me.
So it's a winner for me.
You do hate beer, I've realized.
I've switched to a, yeah, I'm a very critical beer drinker, so I've switched to a winner
and loser beer rating system.
them.
Well, you can OK that with us first, but whatever.
It's a personal decision, like a religion.
So this is a winner right here.
If you see it at the store in Mexico, go and get one.
I was at the Walmart in front of the beer thing, where they got all the beers, and I
saw this one and the dark version of it, and I was so scared of the dark.
I was like, I'm not going to look at it.
That is a vice-ass beer, the way it's reflecting light.
I was like, I'm not gonna like that.
It's glowing, it's literally glowing in my hand.
- Yeah, that's Vice AF.
- It's a moonbeer, essentially.
So yeah, I really like light beers
and this is a really light beer and I like it so much
and it is so hugely big.
And I like--
- Looks good, honestly, I wish I had that shit.
- It's a winner. - Yeah.
- All right, amazing.
- I've seen the robot beer at the,
they had that at the place I bought this Bud Light Orange
and I almost got that.
So I'm glad I can- I like it, okay, it's a thin can.
It is a thin can.
It's a quite thin can for a man to have.
Um, okay, Brian?
Virginia's here. Show us the beer.
Well, um- I know you already took a sip,
which is against the rules, but it's your first time.
Just don't let it happen again, please.
I, uh, didn't know that I was gonna be
doing beer as we drank. Also, I thought Noah was gonna
be in here, but now I feel trapped.
Uh, so I pulled something out of my fridge that I've had
before, and it tastes like shit.
Uh, it is berry salty.
*laughter*
-Oh, dear. -Fuckin' ass.
It's like a 3-3 guy who somehow managed to get on the court.
Oh, wow. So this is- so where are you going in terms of numerical scale? Where's this?
Also probably 3-3.
-3-3 all around. -It's salty in a weird way that a beer shouldn't be.
-Mm-hmm. -Um...
And I mean, that's- that's really all you gotta say. It- it tastes weird. I don't like it.
-But... -Let's get the weak-ass plate guy.
...what I had.
Yeah, where the fuck is he? Why didn't Noah join?
He's probably solo queuing a Valorant game and also his microphone doesn't work. He's-
That's right.
He's on his phone.
Yeah.
His telephone.
He's got such fucked up shit going on in his life.
We don't need to bother him with-
We don't need to burden him any further.
Yeah.
Nah, I saw him walking around- he walked around the-
Me and Eric went to the gym today and he showed up and
he walked around everybody thought he was the janitor just because of the way he dresses.
[laughter]
Like one of those Anatoly videos?
Yeah, it was not-
It's not good for him. He's having a bad day.
Anyway, all right, Brian, you and me gotta talk about something, man. I'm glad you're here.
What's that?
You and me have been trapped this weekend. I hope you know.
Yeah, I didn't know I was going until like about an hour ago.
Me and Brian, for those who don't know, our wives have worked together.
and me and Brian are being forced at vagina point to go to their boss's celebration of
their 10 year anniversary.
It's basically a labor camp.
My god.
And I was told this, she was like, "Oh, you want to go to this shit?"
And I said, "No."
And she said, "Well, you have to go."
And I'm thinking, "Well, if I have to go, whatever, man.
It's an anniversary party, it's gonna be two hours, right?
It's seven hours long.
Get this, man!
It's their 10 year wedding anniversary.
Get this, dude.
It's upstate, it's two hours upstate drive.
Oh my god.
Not just that,
they got a party bus to pick people up from the fucking city.
So I'm gonna be, it's not even like I get that two hour break in between.
Where I'm like, oh, well I don't have to talk to people for this two hours,
I get to be in my car alone.
But it starts instantly and it goes from 1 p.m.
to midnight oh
My god 11 hours and 11 hour commitment that I have been forced into what the fuck is
wrong with these women
Okay, where they think what you need to do. Here's what you need to do get a foldable table
Get your laptop
get that
IZIN 5G
Yeah, and get that mouse and
Start queuing start queuing games
dude
Headset on I'm gonna lose my mind man
And I brought I was like, you know, 11 hours is a very long time spending my entire Saturday doing this
She was like, well, I go to I go to shows that you do
Those are one
Those are one hour long
I should wait I should been to 11 shows at least
No there's no way there's no fucking way it's an hour long you show up it's an hour long
I buy all your drinks and you get to and you get to see people you know I'm gonna go up
there her boss is gonna come up to me and say oh man what's it like doing comedy and
I'm gonna just I mean I okay I said this to her I was like this is gonna suck I'm gonna
hate this and she was like I was like I have a really hard time talking to those people
And she was like, "Oh, that's funny. I said this."
"It's really funny you said that, 'cause I said this to my co-worker yesterday."
"When we were talking about you coming to this party."
"And I said, 'Oh yeah, Caleb has a really hard time talking to, like, normal people.'"
[laughter]
"So I'm getting just attacked all day, Dark Souls boss."
"Just destroying me so mean."
"And then I have to go-- And then at Top of the Lava I just spend my entire fucking day doing this shit."
it
Oh, dude, I'm and then she's like Brian's coming. I'm like cool
Brian, I love you. You're good friend. I don't want to talk to anybody for 11 hours
Anybody my my game plan is we're gonna get up there. I'm gonna spend 30 minutes saying hi
Then I'm gonna search the property for their lawnmower just hop on that
Spend the next 6 hours mowing lawns in pure ecstasy.
Yeah, it's like up in the mountains basically.
Dude, but it's just got me fucked up, man.
That is really fucked up.
That's the most fucked up situation I've ever heard.
How do we even get out of this?
You can't.
I have to kill her.
That's the only option I have.
And then Spryan's lost.
You're literally fucked.
Well, I'm going to be mowing lawns, so I'll be alright for at least half of that.
She just walked in and she's looking at me.
*laughter*
Yeah, I was about to say, I thought you were home alone.
By the way you were screaming about this, I was like
*laughter*
She's uh...
She's... I thought I was safe
because she's watching a show about
monkeys that she's addicted to
watching. She's watching this show
every night. I'm like, "Hey, you wanna watch a movie?"
She's like, "Yeah, I'm watching my
four part, six hour
documentary about chimpanzees."
It's so nice when your girl has like a pacifier you can just hand her though.
Yeah, for a long time it was Super Mario Odyssey.
Yeah, dude, when a woman gets into like a video game.
Oh yeah, Harry Potter, that Harry Potter game.
It's the most amazing feeling in the world.
Dude, this is bad, she started playing Persona 5.
Yeah, I just got my girl on that too, and I'm so excited for 100 hours.
The thing is dude, when I play Persona 5, I'm like skipping all the cutscenes, trying to talk to the girls,
and she's sitting there, walking around, examining every barrel that's in every room,
and the thing comes up and says "It's just a normal barrel!"
And she goes "Hmm, I should probably check the next four barrels to see if it has a different text line."
She just doesn't know how to play fucking video games.
They don't have gamer brain, man.
They really don't.
They don't comprehend it.
I'm
amazing yeah that's so fucking amazing just get her a pick Ross and she will
never see her ever again yeah I tried to get Trish on to a stardew valley
he already did it didn't work didn't work well that's the thing is that's also a
specific kind of girl that likes stardew valley yeah very different it's a
specific kind of person I I tried playing I tried playing not stardew
I don't like it but I played like one minute of Animal Crossing at a Walmart one time on
the switch that they have just like sitting there.
That's gotta be the worst game ever made.
The same thing as like, like, any of those RPGs where you like talk to people and shit
and have to do random shit like Persona, but you don't even get, but they're all animals.
Yeah, you don't get pussy.
Yeah, exactly, like I'm trying to, I go into, I go into Persona, I load up, I, I am doing
sp, sex speed runs instantly, can't really have sex but you can, the screen goes dark.
It does go dark, it's awesome.
Yeah, it's the best, it's the best dude.
0% completion with the relationships with any man in the entire game. Yeah
Maxing out every single girl. Okay, so the fire
Difficulty on easy guys. The guys suck. Yeah, they're horrible to talk to persona for but there
Yeah in persona for they're good in five. They're annoying and read it
Guy I hate
For days now you would completely love boulders gate
There I think I would I think I I like any
It's a cape for my my hellishly shit life where I have to do
There's one of these like the one of the first like
quests you uh
you just like side with looking like an evil woman and just like
Raid a camp and she'll just like go to your house and just suck you off. That's
One day one one game day basically one day in game
That is amazing. I mean, that's what should happen. I try to have sex in every game. I play man
Every single fucking game I see I google FIFA dude. I'm doing the my manager
I'm trying to have sex with the players and stuff really inappropriate stuff. I
Yeah, there should be when you play NBA 2k and they have the story mode there should be like romance options fuck LeBron
You should be able to have like 30 kids and then like lose all your salary immediately.
Yes, yes you should because that's what I would fuck you.
If I was in the NBA when I was 17.
Yeah, yeah. Well that's actually, I think 2K16 literally starts like that.
Where you like didn't make it to the NBA, you finish college and you're playing in China.
You're playing somewhere overseas and then you get called up.
the
some Starbreeze. I had, because there was a, oh, there was this discount store in North
Carolina. It was probably everywhere. But it had, it wasn't called Dave and Buster's, but
it had a name like that, where it was like two guys' names. Somebody might know it. But
I would go there, my dad would take me there for like school shopping, because you could
get everything you ever needed for like $15. And I would get full Starbreeze everything.
And then when I was a kid, because this is the only place I shopped, the only underwear
I had was money print boxers. Awesome. So I had like 15 pairs of money print boxers
because that was all they sold there. One really fucked up thing about Dave
and Buster's is the implication that someone's name is fucking Buster. That's
true. Someone's first name was Buster. Buster was like a you know that was a
the
It was a movie that came out on Netflix and the first 30 minutes was like
funny and
People you'd go over to people's houses to watch a movie you'd watch the first 30 minutes of Buster Scruggs
And then they go to the part where the guy has no arms and legs
Yeah
Yeah, that's the good part. Like you don't have to watch you the the the guy who's looking for gold that was boring
The guy who is just in the circus that one's boring whatever happens
Only the good one is the James Franco one where you like it's home. Yeah
The James Franco and the first song is the good. Oh the like water cover by Marty Robbins. Yeah, that's
Like after that you don't have to watch that like you I'm there to have fun. I'm having fun
Why are you putting all this boring stuff in the movie? That's a good point
I mean, I guess it makes sense
Like they just made the first part basically like a slime video and then the rest of it is like a depressing movie
But just it's just so weird that I watch that shit so many times
I would sit at I would sit at home and watch the first 30 minutes. I look you know
What's the first thing?
Like two weeks ago, I literally watched the first
30 minutes and when I got to the fucking odd position like this guy I was like ah shit
fuck this.
Yeah turn this get this off of my screen I don't I didn't this is not the way man.
Watch the first like 5 minutes of the prospector was like alright let's get to the good shit
let's get to the good shit.
Yeah I don't I don't know.
Have they made a movie in a while?
The Coen Brothers?
Um I don't think so I don't remember.
Is that like the last thing they did?
Aren't they trans now?
No you're thinking of the Wachowskis.
I don't think so. I don't remember.
Is that like the last thing they did?
Aren't they trans now?
No, you're thinking of the Wachowskis.
Hmm.
I was about to ask if they made The Matrix, but that was also...
No, the Coen brothers did, uh...
Are they black?
No Country for Old Men.
Probably. No Country for Old Men.
[laughter]
There's too many brothers, bro.
Yeah, get your damn brothers out of here.
The Coen brothers did No Country for Old Men.
Okay.
And they did Fargo.
Oh, they're just doing this like Fargo show.
And the big Lebowski.
Yeah, I haven't seen a single second of the Fargo show, but I do, I've been watching,
I've been re-watching Louie on your media server and the rip that you have is just straight
from like the FX, just somebody like recording there, it airing.
So it has ads on either side for like Fargo from 2014.
So I have to see that fucking guy from The Hobbit just like sitting there staring into
the screen.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
I want to watch the Louie, which I guess is the price I pay for watching that show
Louie's funny. Did you ever watch lucky Louie?
No, I never watched lucky Louie. I didn't see a Horace and Pete either
Why would say the horse of Pete but lucky I my dad used to watch lucky Louie when I was like six years old
Howard the fuckle I was Louise first show he did he did a sitcom on I think HBO
Yeah, and I guess it was fine, but it was they do an episode of Louie about it
Yeah, like where he's it's so stupid. It's like such a it's such a like
Yes, the whole episode is he's doing this show and he's like, it's just it's so fucked up
I'm had this fake wife and this fake friend and I'm living this fake life
Like he's describing acting and the solution for him was to his real-life solution was just make a show about his life
I guess but it's just such a funny like
Gripe to have with having a television show is like I have to act
Yeah
Yeah, I think it was the same fake wife and Louie and lucky Louie, right Pamela Adlon
Yeah, Pamela had lungs and like everything he makes yeah, I never watched that show that they did together
The show her like FX show. I heard it was really good though, but I can remember what it was called
I never saw that never saw baskets, but I heard baskets was good. I've really just been watching I
Only watch shows that I used to watch when I was a kid and then I recently watched the bear
But I don't I haven't watched anything in the last like 10 years between those two
Mmm, the bear is so stupid
How long how much have you watched of the bear I've watched all of the bear Oh bears good the bears really good
Okay, I love watching things that I don't like it's a bad habit, but I still do it
I've watched so many shitty enemies, but I
so
My girlfriend's on the train
coming out of Ridgewood towards the city and
She noticed that the main guy from the bear was on the train and he had like his like cap down
And like had a mask on it was like clearly trying to look like
incognito
not trying to have anybody recognize him and
Some girl comes up and asked him like hey, are you the guy and he's like yeah, yeah
Meanwhile, he's wearing a full fucking chef's outfit
*laughter*
I'd walk around with all the makeup on all the time. Yeah, just like pictures of me leaving the gym paparazzi photos
Yeah, just like cap fully down
Yeah, yeah doing a video where I'm yelling at the paparazzi like you're stalking me. You're fucking crazy
cling on makeup
God that is just so fucking funny
This is so awesome dude, I love that.
Why do you hate the bear, Brian?
It's a nonsense show, it doesn't make any fucking sense.
The first season, uh, if anyone who hasn't seen it, go fuck yourself.
Uh, first season is literally just, like, he's having this like, heart-breaking thing where his brother killed himself and took out a big loan.
And then, like, the end of it is just that his brother hid all the money in some spaghetti sauce.
And then they found the money? And then they're happy?
Like, you still owe that money!
And to be fair, anything with the tone that you're using would sound very stupid.
You're just saying, "Yeah, and then this happened? Wait, so he's his godfather and it does him a favor?"
I'm not gonna lie.
And then he dies and then his son goes to Italy? What the hell is this movie?
$300,000 worth of money, and then he shoves it into fucking tomato canes, and then his brother finds it.
it. That's the whole first season. Well there's a lot of stuff in between. Mattie Matheson
says funny ass shit. I watched the first season like twice, one with myself and one with my
girlfriend and I didn't get the ending either time. I was like why did he do that? And why
did he kill himself? Because it was funny. It was cool. Stuff in movies and tv shows
should literally the only thing that screenwriters should be thinking
okay i wrote this a this this this part the first part
what should happen next whatever the coolest funniest thing is
so on and so forth eventually you get a tv show you ever watch oceans the
oceans movies yeah ocean either 12 or 13
either 12 or 13 they're like we need to sneak into this shit
how do we do it let's get a contortionist from china
to hide inside of a box and sneak that is awesome that makes yeah but that makes sense
the getting it makes sense to hide money in anything getting alone hiding it in sauce
just rob a bank man well they gotta take boxes into banks
is you you net gain money in that regard this is taking out a loan you still owe the money
and now you just found the money in spaghetti sauce now he just covered
you're telling me you're telling me patrick and spongebob
magic conch they got a magic conch and squidward don't want none of this we don't want it he don't
want it right? But then, now he's all hungry he's gotta eat a fly. Who's he coming to ask?
The conch. That's how you sound Brian with your dumb ass.
Ok now that we're talking about it, it makes more sense that maybe he thought that if he
just killed himself the loan would go away. Basically.
Why would he do that though? Well that's true, everything goes away for
you if you die. He's stupid. He's just like a stupid guy.
He is a dumb guy.
Yeah, they show that he's stupid in the entire thing.
He does that thing that every stupid...
You know how you know a character is stupid in a movie or a television show?
When they talk to somebody, especially their younger brother, and they go, "You think you're
better than me?"
That's how you know this guy is the dumbest villain guy in the entire...
That could possibly be.
As soon as someone says, "You think you're better than me?"
They are going to die.
They are going to lose.
There's no way that you win after saying that line.
Yeah, that's what happens in a lot of us in our Valorant games.
That's what we always do in those games.
When we're winning by a lot and then someone types "Hey, nice job fucking pussy" and then
we immediately lose every single game that ever happens in.
Yeah that's awesome man.
I really wish, I wish that I had started playing competitive video games when I was a lot younger
because I just am too shy.
If I'm losing or somebody does something that really makes me mad, I have never said a single
thing to anybody.
Well they make you be a pussy now because you'll get banned if you say anything rude
in competitive games.
Well that's the truth, I don't really know where the line is there.
Yeah it's not like Twitter.
Yeah like there's no...
It's moved a lot.
It has, they've been moving the goalposts a lot.
On Brian specifically.
Brian would be an expert at this.
Last night we were playing some game and this poor guy, this really nice guy was like, he
was giving really amazing comms, he was saying, he was like helping us out with that, and then
nobody had said a single word the entire game except for this guy just saying like "oh he's
on your left, he's on your right" only person comming on the entire team.
Brian says "man I don't want to hear another fucking word out of you until you're not bottom
frag anymore."
*laughter*
I'm playing with this psycho?
It's all encouragement man.
If he wants to talk, he has to earn it.
It was like two rounds into the game,
he had one kill, you had three.
No, it was not two rounds into the game.
This was like eight rounds.
And you can't be calling plays if you're bottom of the leaderboard man.
Listen, I was also there.
I was also there.
It was like six rounds into the game,
and as soon as Brian said that,
the next like three rounds, like that guy caught up to Brian.
to Brian. Look at look at my effect. You can't have it both ways. You can't take credit for
that. I just said it. It's encouragement. I don't think that reads as encouragement
to that guy. I think Brian's insanity when he's playing online video games, it's so much
funnier on CS2 because it does that little like filter on your voice, like the radio
filter. And there's that thing where he mutes on Discord and you only hear him from the radio.
It's just really funny to me when he's just like chirping at a guy's a little bit to be
like yeah yeah what do you think of a
person I'll give you two guesses and I
guess it's like wait I two guesses it
could be yes or no it's like yeah you're
stupid what are you talking about?
everybody's pretty fucking confused by
by how mean you are in those lobbies man
you have no patience for strangers no
No, absolutely not. I love my friends and I like to be nice to them.
Which means that everyone else who is not my friends...
Fuck, they get the axe.
Yup.
Fucking, absolutely down and dirty, early Modern Warfare 2 lobby style.
See, that's what I mean. I never played Modern Warfare...
I played Modern Warfare 2, but I don't think I had a headset.
So I just played on, like, my... out of my Xbox speaker, so I couldn't talk back.
And so I thought it was funny when people screamed in the lobby, but I never did that
Yeah, I don't get the bug. I think I always found it also really funny
But I don't think I would ever find myself like caring enough for him
Mdvd nw2 match to just be out someone
Call duty sucks. Yeah
Not even like CS right now like we're playing ranked and everything, but I don't I don't care enough
So we're like, "Oh my god, I'm so pissed."
No, that's- no, you don't need to care.
It's just more about the yelling.
About the getting mad at them.
You know?
You just like the screaming and yelling.
Well, not the screaming and yelling,
but I like the getting mad at them part.
It's very funny to get in someone's head.
In a video game.
Who is up with you devilish two?
[Chuckles]
Well, I did play competitive video games when I was young.
I actually agree with this.
Yeah, it is very funny.
these poor people they get home from the hardest job ever
every single one of them works on an oil rig
and then they log on and say
"hey"
"no, they're all 15, the worst thing in their life is homework"
"yeah, homework's hard, how are you gonna do homework right now?"
they get in
"they need to be humble"
"my whole job is homework, bro"
"that is so true"
"I fucking..."
until they pull up with the social studies
and then you say
"not me, dawg"
"I don't want nothing to do with this social studies shit"
I would, oh my god, if I was a teacher
a teacher I would be dropping bombs on you in social studies class you wouldn't
know what to do with this shit I mean one wrong you could drop well I'm not a
teacher so I don't have my curriculum in front of me the fucking social studies
what do you see in soldier studies Wow this guy's a lot of school I went to
school I didn't have social studies I don't know what that is social studies
man this was let me tell you what this was the hardest class in the universe
the
And they'd say is this a good map or a bad is this a real map or a fake map?
He'd say that's a real map. I don't think you went to real school. I
Went to a charter school. So it probably wasn't that good of a social studies program. I'm gonna be honest weren't known for the social studies
We were more known for recess. We had a really strong really strong recess competitive
A lot of a lot of people coming out of school known for recess
Yeah, we sent a lot of people to Harvard for recess, a lot of people were studying recess at my school.
I fucked him with recess.
Me too, man. I loved it. Did every school have this?
Our entire recess thing, we were in an old hardware company because it was a charter school, so it wasn't like a real school building.
It was like this old hardware company, it used to be a warehouse.
They turned it into a school, but the recess thing was just the parking lot of the company
that they fenced in and put two soccer nets and a basketball hoop in.
And there was one corner where all of the cool kids hung out, which was just in one corner
of this thing.
Did you guys have that too, where there was a secret corner in your recess room?
No.
No, not that.
We actually had the opposite, where we went to school in the parking lot and then had recess
in the old hardware building. Oh wow. Yeah. The old hardware. It was awesome. That's the
difference between Texas and North Carolina I guess. We had a field. I played football
every day at lunch and our coach was named Tom Brady. Stop making shit up. Stop. Don't
just come on here and lie. This is going to be a joke to you. I make money off this. This
This is the only thing I have. You can't come on and say, "My coach was Tom Brady, my music teacher was Michael Jackson."
You can't say this shit to me.
We actually did have a fiancé.
Completely Tom Brady.
He was 60 years old.
Just leather, tan skin as fuck.
From Texas.
And one time he saw me at Luby's with my grandma.
And he said, "Boy, you eating that green jello?"
green jello?
*laughter*
He would ask me that every day after that.
He'd be like, "You eating
your green jello?"
*laughter*
Lubies is a place you can only go with your grandma.
Yeah, my grandma loved Lubies.
Oh my god, that was the
after church special, dude.
What the hell's Lubies?
It's like a golden corral, or like...
Like a buffet style
That is actually a persona
There's a persona for line poorly translated
Social rank increased one one tier for yeah, you ate the green Tom Brady
You ate the green jello and said nothing
*laughing*
Why you eating green jello?
You were eating that green jello like it was
gonna make me big and strong
*laughing*
Like it was vegetables?
You were eating that green jello
*laughing*
You gotta respect him
Yeah that's the goat, that's the goat man
That's part of the TB, TB whatever
What's his brand called?
TB12
TB12, they had a store, they had a TB12 store in Boston and when me and Adam went to Boston
like two years ago or a year and a half ago or some shit, we went into that store and they have like a
like a sports trainer person there who's like you can come in and talk about like what you want to
do and I came in and I talked to her for an hour about wanting to dunk and I was like yeah yeah I
the
So that's how I know that it's not true.
That none of that shit works.
Is that they tried to sell me on Dunkin.
Dunkin Donuts.
Did you ever do like dunk training?
Oh I did dunk training, yeah.
At my best, I could get
I could get
like here.
Ram here. At my very best.
That sounds pretty good.
I was like 175 pounds. I trained plyometrics every day.
In high school.
So like a 5'4" 5'3" guy?
That's fucking insane.
Yeah, it's pretty good for somebody who's, you know, pushing six foot.
Right.
I always have really short arms.
I have short arms, so I was just like...
And my upper body was just like so scrawny because I was trying to lose enough weight
but make my legs strong enough that I could somehow defy God and jump high.
And I don't think I can grab room anymore.
I can touch the backboard, but that's it.
I'm so sorry, man.
Did you ever dunk, Brian?
I feel like you're right at the dunking height.
I did dunk training with a couple of my friends for a while.
We were just doing like pure plyo, fucking, like lots of jump training.
I never could really get it up there enough.
Would just slam my fist into the rim.
Yeah, that's getting, stuffing yourself is...
That's why I only ever would try to dunk with like a Nerf ball.
because I knew I couldn't jump high enough to actually try with actual basketball.
So I knew that if I tried with the basketball, I would end up like
hitting it so hard because I would be so excited.
Fall backwards, break my head open, humpty-dumpty on the ground.
- I feel like six more months, maybe. But then I also,
I don't think I would have any use for it. You know?
- Dunking?
- Like I would just get blown.
- It's not like a skill that you use in other, it's only for basketball. What do you mean?
Yeah, like even if I went to go play basketball do these people would just they would just knock me down
Just don't know you get a fast break. I saw this happen many times you get a fast break. It's a guy
It's usually like a kind of tall white guy who is like this is my chance to dunk
He's not he's not gonna you know, he's not gonna posterize somebody but on the fast break
It's it's 1v0 on the end of the court. He goes up does like the worst dunk you've ever seen in your life
That's what you could have done. That would have been your peak.
That would have been it, yeah.
For me, I wanted to get so athletically strong that I was like showing up to the court, my legs are like Donkey Kong barrels, the rest of my body is completely emaciated, and then I like go up, double pump hammer on somebody. I wanted to do that so badly, I would dream about it.
You wanted to be like a video game character, basically.
basically. Yeah, yeah, I wanted to completely use a special attack on just these random
guys at the basketball court. I need to start playing basketball again. I dream of being
a footballer, but I don't have the eyesight for it. Growing up in Arizona, around the
time I was playing basketball, everyone would love to pass the ball and then say Steve Nash.
damn wait that is so funny
it doesn't roll off the tongue like Kobe does
have you already talked about rex's new glasses?
no no somehow somehow we have not they look beautiful thank you what's up with
this man are they going dark? that's what I thought no they're not
transitions but there I went to this like glasses place in Soho and they
charged me like $400 for lenses I know I accepted that I'm getting old and dying
and that I I've needed glasses since I was like 16 and I'm just aging that's
just something that he had to do years ago.
Yeah, but I...
It definitely gets worse as you age, right?
Right, it gets worse as you age, and I'm like, "I can do this, it's no problem."
And then I finally got them like two weeks ago.
Is it $400 like how much glasses cost? I've never had them.
They're expensive, but if you have like insurance and stuff, it's a little cheaper.
I've only used like readers.
I mean, I guess I don't know like a good frame of reference to like how much it would cost in the US
But these are not I think these ran me like 100 bucks tops
No, they're okay. I
Have a bad astigmatism, which means I see like streamers when I look at lights like they're like really like blurry
And I work on the fucking computer
So that's bad. Yeah
Yeah, I think I went and got my eyes tested and I had a stigmatism, but it felt like such a like
Maybe I just was making it up
as they were giving me the test like
Stigmatism is such a it's because it's not like things are blurry as much as like your eyes
They're actually really hard to be be like sick like sure about a result
You get out of like that the machine because yeah, cuz you're trying like I'm trying so hard. I'm like I
That's probably an a every time they do a test. I'm like trying to hurt and my eyes are watering like I'm crying
I can't even I can't see nothing because there's water in my eyes
So I'm basically blind basically
One time to the eye doctor, but they gave I think the reason I never went back is when you leave
Or at some point they give you these eye drops that make you completely blind basically for like yeah
Our and I just hated that I think I got home and I was trying to do something and I was like this sucks
Yeah, I haven't gotten an eye exam since high school.
Not needing glasses.
You've been stuck with the same prescription?
Basically. I mean, I got a new prescription, but yeah.
How do you get a new prescription without a thing?
They give you an eye exam.
Oh, you said you haven't had one since high school.
Yeah, until I went and got these glasses.
Oh, I'm seeing now.
Yes. Which is what I said after I got my glasses.
I was trying to get new glasses like now three months ago
Went in for the appointment and the whole time the dudes doing like a one two one two shit
And then at the very end he's like wow that's crazy
Your eyesight is actually way better than it was last time like what that's weird. I
Don't know how that would happen
And then he just keeps on going as a test. That's weird. You want to double check like yeah, okay, whatever
He asked you if you want to double check?
To make sure that like the shit that I said was good was good. I don't know.
Go outside and then, um, he's like, "Oh, and make sure you fix his address too."
And I was like, "What? Like, what do you mean? I told you my address whenever I got in here."
Uh, start talking to the guy. He had someone else's chart pulled up the whole time.
Oh my god.
A completely different person measuring me against...
So I'm terrified of using that prescription because I don't know what the fuck he actually put down.
Yeah, I think the guy's like...
Yeah, some like 60 year old fat Italian guy
just going off about how bad computers are.
When you pass like 20, 21, like you kind of don't need a new prescription anymore.
Is that true?
That is not true.
I think you get way worse as you get older.
I think it gets worse every year, every year you age.
I think the last pair of glasses that I had before these, I had for like 5 years.
That just means that you were lazy bones.
No, I didn't need new glasses and I got a prescription and it was basically the same prescription.
You're lying.
I'm not lying.
That's like when people are like, "Yeah, I didn't brush my teeth for seven years and I didn't get a cavity."
That's a totally different thing.
Which is fine, by the way. That's fine.
Yeah, it is totally fine.
I brush my teeth once a day.
Jow.
Ish.
It's so hard because I wake up and I immediately start eating and drinking
And what am I supposed to do stop doing that - oh, I need to go brush my teeth
But I have half of a donut in my mouth the other half in my hand
There's no way that I'm gonna put an end to this party to go fucking
Yesterday I was like taking a shower. I was like, I gotta brush my teeth. I was like, bro
I need to do I need to drink my coffee in a sec as well
So coffee will hurt more than coffee is poison when you've had when you brush your brush your teeth in the shower
That's the only reason I do it
Yeah
What the fuck?
I piss in the shower!
No!
I might as well be-
Yeah, dude!
What's your problem?
No!
That's a bad thing to do, man.
You're pissing, brushing your teeth.
As long as you piss before you start, like, lathering soap on you, it's fine.
I wash my pee, I'm not an animal.
If it's the last fucking thing you do in the shower, that's nasty.
Yeah, nobody should do that.
Pee should not be- it all goes to the same ocean.
It's either in the toilet, or outdoors.
No other places.
doors you're killing plants. You don't pee in the sink?
Well that that's like basically a toilet but it just doesn't have a lid.
The shower is a toilet. Yeah dude. The shower is a place for cleaning. The shower
fucking removes stink from you and what is the most clean thing
that comes out of your body man? I'd put pee against spit any day of the week.
Earwax? Earwax is disgusting. Ew get that away from me.
Pee? Bring it closer. I like pee. You don't you don't mean this.
Yeah, you're lying right now.
You're lying.
You're being excessive.
Rex lied about the Tom Brady thing, now you're lying about drinking.
That is, no, that is completely true.
You lied.
Just admit you lied, man.
It's okay.
I wish.
We'll delete this.
You lied about Tom Brady was our football coach.
Just admit you lied and tell us your real name, Michael Jordan.
Well, that would at least be funny because it's the wrong sport.
The fact that it's in football and his name is Tom Brady is the reason why it is a lie.
I'm giving you Pinocchios.
I'm throwing Pinocchios at you.
It is 100% true.
It's 100% Pinocchio.
It's a 0% on PolitiFact.
This is not a true story.
I looked it up on KnowYourMeme.
It's not true.
It doesn't exist.
Do you actually have capes?
Do you have red superhero capes behind you?
That's a blanket.
That would not surprise me, honestly, if you owned a cape.
That is a blanket.
You've looked at a cape on mine before.
You've looked at capes.
I have never looked at a cape.
You have looked at capes.
I've been looking, excuse me, all day looking at swords and looking at crazy Naruto headbands.
You definitely have considered a cape in your life.
I've never considered any of that.
You need to wear a cape to be a capesback.
I'm not wearing a cape.
Oh, you are, George, by the way.
You would wear a cape, though.
If you had a nice cape, you would wear it.
What is a nice cape?
You tell me, cape expert.
You would know.
I don't know anything about them.
You sound so...
You haven't even begun to delve into that.
You're being defensive because you do like capes.
You haven't begun.
It's coming.
As soon as you hit 30, you're gonna get a full cape selection.
You'll have a clothes closet, a cape closet.
You're gonna pick your clothes.
It would be pretty fun to walk around in a cape, I can't lie.
Now that you're saying it.
Of course you think that.
With a nice like bronze clasp with a little chain between it.
See, he's invented capes.
He's literally invented them.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm gonna talk to him next.
He was like, "Yeah, I got a couple capes on the way."
Me?
I would never...
I would never even think to wear a cape. He's thinking about it actively as we speak. He's daydreaming about a cape
Do you care anything that you put on your body kill?
clothing wise
It was like Caleb has some tie-dye shirt oak swag headphones
Bagel bunny hat my bagel bunny hat shout out to baby bunny. These are some of the best gluten-free bagels in the universe
I see.
I have a watch on.
I wear a watch.
I have mismatched socks.
One is grey and one is white.
Yeah, I care about what I put on my body.
How about you, Mr. South of the Border T-shirt that I gave you?
This is my favorite shirt.
It's so comfy.
I knew it.
I'm a fan.
I knew something about South of the Border made me say he's going to like this.
He's going to like this T-shirt from this racist gas station.
I have a South of the Border shirt too.
I never wear it because it's like I don't want to be walking around with this shit on it
Yeah, you don't want to be twinning with me. Well, no, I don't want to be walking around you hate to do with me
Just admit it. You never turn with me. I would love to I wish that I got the same shirt you have that was cool
mine says
It has their their racist mascot and it says Pedro
Pedro's forecast and it has every single state with like a forecast on top of it, but all the forecasts a shit
It's like the weather's shit in the entire nation.
That's awesome, why would you not wear that?
Mostly because of Pedro.
Is it racist?
It's...
Hold on, hold on.
It's definitely pushing it.
Wait, what's that on your back?
Is that a fucking math problem?
No, it's this...
in Seattle. Some kind of radio station. This guy. He's fine. That's awesome. That's fucking
awesome. Oh, okay. I got the, I got the okay. Pedro's forecast. Pull it up. Pull it up. That's
fucking ironic. Partly shitty. This is something that I see that would, I would see Rex wearing.
I'm sure. That's why I'm-
I need less t-shirts. I don't like wearing funny t-shirts anymore. I think I'm past funny t-shirts.
I mean I'm wearing just a Uniclone plain t-shirt.
I didn't mean that. Just wearing a blank t-shirt that you bought off Amazon is the way to dress.
I pretty much wear a white t-shirt most days that I got from Telco.
That's like- it was damaged and that's why they sell it there. It's like some Hanes t-shirt.
I just like I like normal clothes now man
I'm gonna get I'm gonna be one of these guys who wears like a $4 t-shirt and a
$5,000 pair of jeans that he has to sit in the bathtub to make fit, right?
Raw denim
Yep, that is what that's called
Yeah, you could be a rod that I'm guy I could see that I could see myself
Love taking a bath. So it's kind of like killing
I'll take one tonight if you want me to
I love that.
The idea that I have a pair of clothes where I have to bath, I'm telling my wife, like,
no, you don't understand.
I have to be in there for four hours watching YouTube videos to make my jeans fit good.
Wait, that's a way to get out of it.
The Saturday thing.
Get raw denim today and then by Saturday, when you get them, you're like, I gotta be
in this.
That means I need to have some reason why I have to wear them on Sunday.
I need like a denim convention to go to.
I have church on Sunday, I have to survive with a denim jeans.
You cannot wear denim to church.
My kind of cool church is I go to maybe.
Yeah, those are blasphemous churches.
What's wrong with wearing denim to church?
Sunday best.
Sunday best, you need to be full, full light colored suit, praising God.
Yeah, yeah.
It's seersucker.
He's worried about church.
Take that back.
Come on, man.
That's ridiculous.
Take that back.
Hold on, dude.
Take that shit back.
I'm wearing shorts.
I'm wearing this t-shirt.
For the entire week.
I haven't showered.
That's why I'm showing up to church.
That is how I always show up to church.
Yeah, you know what you should do?
You should stop bathing.
For the next couple days, Caleb.
And stink max.
To keep people away from you at the event.
You keep bringing up stink maxing.
Like once every couple weeks you bring up stink maxing like this is a real thing.
It's going around.
It is a real thing.
It's a real thing.
This is not a thing that men should be doing.
It's going around.
You should be forcefully stinky as like a force field to keep people away from you and from interacting with you.
I'm already bald.
I have that one... nobody wants to come near me.
We talked about this last week.
I ruin every restaurant I walk into with my head.
They should make a hat that's made out of magnifying glasses.
They should wear...
And then you can like...
Oh yeah.
Have a ghosting scalp.
I have like aphids crawling around my head like a basil plant.
Yeah.
No, it wouldn't burn your scalp.
The sun would reflect off of your scalp and then shoot out and light things on fire.
Oh, that's a pretty good idea.
Yeah.
Beautiful. You gotta oil it up a little bit first.
Yeah, I wanna go to one of those barbers where they shave your head and then they cover you in some green slime and then they rip it off and then they crack your back.
and then make it
Yeah, I want to go to one of these, I think it's like in Turkey, it's like a full service
barber where they like shave you and then they like crack your back and massage you and shit.
I'm scared of the barber, I don't know what to ask for anymore.
I haven't been to a barber in a long time.
I want to go to one this Friday and I don't know what to ask for, I don't know what to
say.
Probably at the Hitler News.
I talked to a girl the other day and guys, take this from me because I talked to one,
Do not they are done with the with the hair on top short on the sides. They don't like it anymore guys. Yeah, I
Mean, that's been over 2013
She was complaining. She was she was she was like, why doesn't why do no guys have short on the top long on the sides?
Beautiful is that what they like now Briar Tuck is hot now. Yeah, that's the new thing
I'm gonna get this shaved.
See, but you're gonna do this thing that
that ol' Edie Modica doesn't like, man.
I'm gonna get this- I'm gonna get this shaved.
Is that- is that what she was saying?
Yeah, yeah, you have no chance with Edie.
No, but-
It's a shame.
What if I get an undercut as well?
You don't want an under- you- you should get
uh, steps.
Yeah!
You should get the Nike
symbol kinda shaved into the back of your head.
your head. No, you should get the Edgar. Yeah. So dope with the Edgar dude. I'm not going
to get the Edgar. I'm not going to show up to my Mexican barber in Mexico and be like,
can I get the Edgar? You should get my mom. You just say, give me the haircut that you
give most other people. You have a female barber? I think it's going to be a female
barber. Bro, let's go into sports clips. I'm not going to. You don't have a barber bro,
You have a beautician, I hate to tell you.
I'm going to a place that has a plasma powerhouse.
Do they put on football when you're getting your hair trimmed?
I haven't been to this barber in my entire life.
I'm going there for the first time in my life.
Wait, is...
Sorry, I just got distracted.
Somebody sent a very racist message in the chat, guys.
Somebody says "deports clips".
Come on, that is not funny.
That is racist.
They fucking cooked his ass, oh my goodness.
Did you cook them? Yeah, you did. But no.
That is not, that's not gonna fly.
No, knockouts. That's the, that's the like hooters haircut place, right?
Knockouts? Do you guys have that?
No, what?
I'm pretty sure, I think it's knockouts. It's like hooters.
So it's like women in tops?
Yeah, and they're in like very tiny referee uniforms and they give you haircuts.
And it's the worst haircuts you could get because they're not like,
We're not hired because we're good at cutting hair.
Yeah.
Why don't they have like a...
Very popular.
Fortune 500 company where people...
That is the dress code.
It's like girls wear skirts and like low cut or high...
Whatever these are.
You know, like a C-suite.
Like they're walking around.
The CEO is a girl and she's got midriff showing.
How come there's no company like that?
Nobody would survive.
Why?
the
The hangover burger is fire.
I watched a video today about the heart attack grill.
You guys know about that?
I knew about what it was, I didn't realize that the owner of it is like a complete lunatic.
Where he, like people die at the heart attack grill, people die of heart attacks.
And he does interviews and he's like, I'm gonna be real with you guys, it's good for business.
and
the
up
a bad list of crimes that he committed. But, okay no he's in there until 2029 which is
really not that long. It's not that long. 6 more years. I will say he probably would
have gotten 5 or 10 years if he wasn't the subway guy. I think he definitely got dinged
for a couple extra, couple extra, he got dinged for a dime. Yeah imagine Jared walking in
and seeing a fat judge and you know he's like "Bruh!"
This one's in the bag. This one's in the fucking bag.
Do you think in like 2035 when we get into like the nostalgia from the 2010s,
they're like "Oh let's bring Jared back, Subway" and he runs out of air.
No I don't think so.
You think they're gonna want Jared back? I gotta say man, I don't think so.
I think that's probably the one thing that won't happen.
Well, people forget that Carl- Carl alone had sex with a 13 year old and impregnated her.
Yeah, but that's fine.
What?
He's a sports guy.
He's mentally at like 5 years old.
Like every sports player has been injured in the head so much that they're basically-
It's fine to fuck a 13 year old thing that Rexio said.
He played basketball, Rexio wasn't getting his head knocked around.
When did that happen? What year did that happen?
Like in the 80s when he was in the NBA, maybe they were early 90s.
So literally, it's just not a big deal.
What are you talking about?
Not a big deal that Karl Malone had sex with a 13 year old and impregnated her and now her son's walking around doing videos on Instagram where he's like, "Yeah, my dad's Karl Malone, but he won't talk to me because he impregnated my mom."
My woman.
That's not good, my woman.
He has to... see this is the pain of this, dude.
This kid didn't grow up without a father, had to raise a mother, had to fuck his mom.
This is not... this is all cascading...
And she was still 13.
Yeah, all cascading... now he's doing the same... yeah, this is making you crazy.
You're acting... you're looking like John Lennon and your attitude towards women is mighty close to his as well.
Sing us a song. Sing us something.
You do have a John Lennon Halloween costume on, you have to admit.
*laughing*
you're a hippie from the 50's
that's not funny
it is funny that you picked these glasses
it's a little funny
especially if you're like "oh i'm getting older"
i'm gonna get the most annoying glasses possible
age gracefully
get some big square ones man
come on
you're holding on so brutally
i have to go to soho for these glasses
i just have to go down to soho to get these
these 400 million dollar sunglasses.
I wanted Chinese diplomat glasses, but they are too small for my face.
And these were the next best thing.
That would have been even fucking worse.
No, they would have been awesome.
Nobody would have ever talked to you if you walked around in tiny little glasses like
this.
Good, no one should talk to me.
He's stink maxing?
He has Chinese diplomat glasses?
Yeah, I want to smell bad, wear Chinese diplomat glasses.
I'm wearing a cloak.
I'm wearing a cape.
Oh my god.
I'm wearing a seersucker suit.
We need to go to China.
We just have to.
We need to send Rex to China.
Yeah.
Warzone, loot crate, out of a plane, just ride into China, see how he likes it.
He will thrive there.
He will completely thrive there.
He doesn't speak Chinese, man.
He will thrive there.
I mean, I don't...
Nick Landon's in China, and I don't think he speaks Chinese.
And I can go...
How do you know random white guys in China?
There's not that many.
What are you talking- who is this fucking guy? What are you talking about?
This is Ryder.
There's an awesome Chinese guy.
Um...
Fuck. His name's like Nathan something
and he is completely pro
mainland and puts out like a shitload of
YouTube videos. That's what I would do
if I was in China. He's also completely
bald, no eyebrows
even. Uh...
Great guy. Just constantly putting out
Like shit talking videos against Hong Kong and like Taiwan and stuff. He's so dope
Put me in the cheat pile dude, put me in the fucking button
Like button here, the little class. China we are coming for you
I don't think you have it in you to be in China. I think you're I think that either their collectivist culture would destroy you
wrong
He's a complete asshole, he's a white watcher leftist
No, I think that you're I think that you're too into being an individual you're walking around like oh, I'm gonna have the funny glasses
Oh, I'm gonna I'm gonna put my hands on my desk
Why don't we hands on your desk in China that cut your hands off and it's not true. That is the truth
That is not true. No, that's the fucking trade to say it man
I'm working my mind is I've got a hundred hands on the desk. I mean fucking fried bugs
You'd be walking around like this, they'd call you human chopsticks, you'd be doing...
It would be bad.
Okay, okay.
Alright, that's enough time.
I need to go pee so bad, so we are done.
Okay.
Thank you so much for joining us, thank you Brian for joining us also, even though you
said some really racist stuff.
I did not!
I didn't say anything weird!
I didn't say anything wrong or weird in any way.
said something pedophilic but it's okay
i've edited it out you literally said it's okay which i think is the
definition i said i said it's nothing