Perfect. All right, let's go. All right. Okay. And so now that we're actually
Recording you could show me your blue foot your blue beer
A seagram's escapes Calypso, Kalata, and I would like to it's 3.2
Right here
I'm gonna say this is flavor beer so oh so it is beer is
You intercepted my just complete bullet that I was about to throw directly into your chest and destroy you yeah
That is not beer that is that is juice
Smirnoff ice, but that's a flavored beer. I got just about the most opposite beer in existence
I got a Voodoo Ranger IPA. I've never had one of these. I've never in my life had one of these. I'm really pretty, I'm a little bit scared.
And then I have, my second beer is kind of an overcorrection I'd say.
That's a blurry beer.
That's the blue plot from Fortnite.
that we're gonna end up with a pocket of 75 shields.
I got a classic brown beer.
Oh, a Mick collab. I almost grabbed one, dude.
Now I'm glad I didn't.
There will be one of these days where we press record
and we lift up these cans and it's three identical fucking beautiful...
What beer would we be drinking?
Maybe like a hard orange juice or something that we picked out
because we were feeling a little sick.
Yeah.
I really didn't want to do this today because I had too much beer over the weekend.
But you know, what can you do, right?
I went to a German restaurant.
Went to a beer garden German restaurant.
Did you?
Which, was it in LA?
It was in like Long Beach area.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, it was, so really good appetizers.
We got poutine, we got a pretzel, we got like Brussels sprouts.
I had two salads that were really good.
And just awesome.
And main course, two sausages and mashed potatoes and whatever German noodles.
Dog shit.
Tasted awful.
Really?
Mashed potatoes were cold.
Just came out cold.
No!
Dog shit.
dessert, brownie with ice cream,
little bacon crumbles on top, and the fucking--
- That was good, right?
- Apple cereal, delicious.
- Amazing.
- So go there.
- The entree matters the least.
The only thing, I go to a restaurant,
I get two or three appetizers, right?
I get one entree, I always order it in a panic mode
right there at the end, because I'm with the wife and she,
do women do this to you guys,
where you go out to a restaurant,
And she goes, you say, "I'm gonna get this."
You confidently say, "I'm going to get the hamburger."
Right?
- Yeah.
- And she says, "I'm gonna get..."
She says, "What if you get the hamburger
"and I get the diarrhea soup and then we split?"
(laughing)
Right?
They always say, "We'll split.
"I'll get the actual shit sandwich
"and you get the amazing lasagna
and we'll eat both have half and I go I don't want to eat shit and diarrhea she
goes well I do and I want a burger and I said bitch you should be 400 pounds in
pick a fucking dinner
he got the man got the yummy nummy chicken schnitzel sandwich
Borscht is a soup right?
It's a soup.
Diarrhea bowl.
It is the diarrhea soup.
You got the bratwurst there?
They didn't have bratwurst, they were out.
Went too late.
So I got one that was like
some sort of like spicy duck
sausage, I thought it had cheese inside
but it was a little gross.
Yeah, cheese in a sausage
is so hit or miss man.
Because sometimes they put way too much
It's just got the wrong texture.
- It's good when it's like,
sweating out of the sausage.
- I don't like that.
When it comes out like pores, that is odd to me.
It's a little, especially a white cheese
coming out of those holes is very pimply.
I really don't like it.
And a little bit, if you have a dirty mind,
it's jizz, but I don't, so I don't think
about that kind of thing.
- Come on.
- See, I didn't even want to bring that up, man.
I didn't even want to talk about that.
But yeah, when I go to a restaurant,
I feel like I just wanna eat the appetizers.
I wanna eat four bites of my entree, take it home,
I don't care if it was good or bad.
And then I wanna eat the dessert.
- Yeah, that's exactly what I did.
- And for the dessert,
and the dessert better be the best thing I had that night,
or else I'm gonna fucking flip my lid on Yelp.
I will go crazy.
- Do you guys use Yelp a lot?
Do you guys review places?
- I'm a Yelper.
Josh got me onto Yelp.
- Really?
- I only ever feel compelled to review a place
on Google Maps or some shit like that.
when I know it's like a small place,
I'm like, "Oh, I really like their stuff."
So when I help 'em out, other than with money,
so that's when I review.
I never really feel like--
- Yelp is better. - Giving a bad review.
- Yelp is way better than a tip, right?
Like you don't have to tip if you leave a Yelp review.
- Yeah.
They actually take off your bill.
- Yeah, exactly.
If you do a survey when they hand you that subway receipt,
they say there's a survey on there.
If you do that survey, no tip.
I'm not tipping.
yeah well it's like a tiered type of thing as well like if you also follow them on twitter
and instagram and facebook now they give you money
and not the business by the way the waiter the waiter is giving you money out of that
little flip of ones why don't more guys more thugs and gangsters why don't they rob waiters
they always have one dollar bills in their little batman belt
Probably because it's smarter than Rob's strippers.
Probably easier too.
To die like Catwoman?
Getting some clear?
What would be the last thing you'd say before dying to Catwoman?
I love you!
Something like "kitty cat claws"
Maybe some really classic lines.
"Oh her pussy's right behind me, isn't it?"
Probably most guys who die by a woman's hand, probably their last, either what they say
or what they think is probably "Man, I'm about to kill this woman."
"There ain't no way I'm about to kill this woman."
I know who's getting home tonight, it's me.
And then they die by a woman's hand.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- There's no way my wife is gonna cut off my penis.
- Yeah, probably the last words of a lot of men who dies,
what are you gonna do, bitch, kill me?
(laughing)
'Cause they think that's so funny
that a girl could kill them.
- Yeah, but you know how men are,
we gotta make a little joke at the worst possible time.
Otherwise, are you even a man?
Nah, of course not.
You haven't made a situation worse for the woman by an ill-timed comment.
Definitely, because you just couldn't help yourself.
I couldn't help it.
Yeah, sorry baby, I'm too funny.
Can I just say that?
I hope I made it off.
You're just as precious as that.
Rex cannot stop doing that, whatever, everyone he meets, regardless of what.
I can't do that.
I can't stop doing that to literally anyone.
Just regardless of gender, age, wealth.
I think that's a net neutral.
That's a zero.
Exactly.
All the sugar too?
That's just yummy.
Well, that is a true nootropic.
If nootropics are measured on how fast they kind of make your brain work, sugar has to
be up there, right?
It's up there with caffeine.
Yeah
We should ask you some props and
Logical situations and what you do in them. Yeah, you find yourself like debating more now that you're taking these
This guy's gonna be debating the fucking mailman in 40 minutes
It made me laugh and it made me go on the back of my...
Sorry.
He doesn't have a how to tackle that one camera entirely.
I wish, dude.
That's fine.
You could call the ambulance to my house and watch the guy in the background.
If you, if I was, if we were in a situation where for, and I know this is already unrealistic,
but I got hurt and you had to call an ambulance.
And I was in the back of the ambulance.
Would you guys be like, and they were like closing the door,
would you put your hand in and say,
"No, I'm riding with him."
Or would you say, "Nah, bye."
If you said, "I'm his sister."
- Yeah, that's what I would say.
- Or if Jubio said, "I'm his father, I'm his grandpa,
I'm his papacito."
- That is my mijo, let me in.
That is my amazing Miho.
I am his T.O.
Please let Mio into the car.
- No, let Mio in the car.
- Yeah.
- Would you ride with me?
- Of course.
- Yeah, that'd be a free ride to the hospital to see you.
And that way I don't have to pay for the Uber.
- And I don't have to get flowers 'cause I was in the ambulance.
- Yeah, you're right.
I probably won't remember that.
I'll probably be dead.
But what if I, you ever think about that
when you get into the ambulance, right? And then they start driving to the hospital and
you just instantly die before you even leave the driveway. Right? They're like, "We're
going to take him to the hospital." And then before they even turn the siren on and the
guy's dead. It's kind of...
That's never happened to me. When's the last time you've been in an ambulance?
I've never been. I was supposed to go one time.
Really?
I had the sutures from my tonsil surgery.
They exploded and I was bleeding.
I lost like a gallon of blood at my grandma's house.
And my grandpa called the ambulance because he thought I was going to die.
And they were like, "Okay, we're going to take him."
And my grandpa was like, "All right, cool.
Put him in the ambulance."
"Wait, how much does an ambulance cost?"
And the guy's like, "$600."
And he's like, "Nah."
Nah, and then and he was like I was like okay let's take your car and he literally
was like we can't take my truck because you'll get blood all in the cab so
your mom's gonna drive she lives 35 minutes away she's gonna drive in pick
you up in her shitty car and then take you to the hospital. That's so sick. Yeah he's a beast dude.
- Shout out to Peter.
- Yeah, well you made it.
- Yeah.
- During my Adderall days, there was a time where,
you know, I've been sniffing and taking a couple dabs
and really just having a good time, drinking beer.
And then suddenly was on, just woke up on the ground,
not feeling too great.
- Oh no.
- Clearly had something happen.
So they called like 911 and they came.
They were like, "Hey, fine, you wanna go to the hospital?"
I was like, "Hmm. Yeah, I'm good. Just leave me on the doorstep. I'll get it up in a minute."
Yeah, I would rather die than lose $600 for a fucking car ride, bro.
For real.
What, because you got extra TVs in there? That's why I paid $600? That's bullshit.
Yeah.
What have you been in an ambulance for?
Oh, when my accident happened.
When the thing fell on your head?
I forgot about that!
Yeah, when a wall fell in...
You were so nonchalant about that.
Yeah, you died.
But you were in an ambulance?
Yeah, so a wall collapsed on my head and my foot.
And it mostly did no damage to my head, I don't think.
I think it did a lot of damage to my foot.
You're definitely different.
I'm normal.
So an ambulance came in and some paramedics were checking me out.
They were like, "All right, yep. Yeah, I think you're hurt."
So they took me into the hospital in an ambulance.
And I made it. I didn't even die.
How much did that cost?
I don't know. I think the...
some insurance.
So the guy... I mean, it was an accident.
Like, there was...
the guys were responsible, so they had to pay
for everything.
Did you ever sue them?
I wanted to, but no. I didn't.
Too hard to do that kind of thing.
I always think about that. Like, people who slip
and they break their leg at like a barber shop
and then they fucking sue everybody.
they sue the owners and shit.
Like how do you have the time to fill out all that paperwork
and have the patience and you have to put on the fake
neck brace and your arms in a sling
and you have to be wary of a private investigator
taking a photo of you with a pencil.
That's just not a good life to live I don't think.
- Yeah and you also have to like pay a fucking lawyer.
- Yeah.
- Before you even get any money.
- Sounds like that.
- The way Caleb said that made me think
of like a five year old boy.
Like, you know, the paperwork.
(laughing)
You slipped on my crayons.
Yeah, for that.
- Yeah.
- You know?
- Yeah, that's funny.
- You couldn't do that these days.
Me and Drew have been talking about how basically
there's this plague slash disease
that's been eating the entire nation,
just slowly by, and let's be real,
started on the West Coast and it came to the East Coast,
and it's basically wokeism and wokeistic language,
thought patterns, which we're not woke,
you know, I'll say something right now.
Fuck, crap, you know, like I just fucking,
just steamrolled that, right, can't say that.
- Yeah, shit.
- Yeah, ballsack on the Queen of England on her mouth.
That's what I think.
- Oh, she's dead, too.
- That was obviously too far,
And that's what woke, but wokest would say, Oh, you went too far.
It's over for you. You have to go to Guantanamo Bay or Guantanamo.
Gay probably now. And then, and
yeah, guys all on yo gay. And then I don't know,
they'd probably keep going, but I can't do that because of my straight. But,
yeah, man, it's really, it's a sad state of affairs, you know?
Yeah. They're, they're really getting it really proactive. Last night,
I stepped out of my apartment and I didn't notice
until I was outside that they completely locked me
out of my apartment, they woke me up.
- Right.
- They snuck in.
- They snuck in, they took my keys.
- Out of your apartment, they put them back.
- Yeah, they just put them back in the apartment
and they locked the door and I was just stuck.
I had to order McDonald's to the exit of my apartment.
- Wow.
- And the guy was like,
a burger and some nuggets.
I think the quarter pounder I think was what it was called.
Yeah.
What do you call that?
Like a 3 meter?
The 4 centimeter burger?
Nah, I said what I called it.
The cheese?
Asshole.
Yeah, the quarter kilo con queso.
And then the woke mob almost flooded my apartment as well while I was locked out.
They fucked up my...
Water or with vitriol?
With...uh...mostly water from the toilet
that was leaking out of the toilet
into the floor.
They like the toilet.
Cause women's pussies touch it.
Yeah.
As far as I know.
So, I'm pretty much, uh...
I'm pretty much like an anti-woke, uh...
uh...figurehead now.
And I'm treating stuff like...
Women are fucking stupid.
And I'm...I love meat.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's my new money thing. I mean a knob of butter for dinner
Because of how gay the TV is because of the last of us episodes are getting gayer
Yeah, yeah, yeah episode. Yeah
The movies based on a PlayStation game every fucking episodes gay nah
No, that's too. That's too far
That's too much
Yeah, dude, and they don't tell you they snuck in they think through your keys inside before you locked it
They don't tell you how fast the woke mob is do their speedy motherfuckers a lot of short
Yeah
You know they say you ever heard that thing where they say hey you want to see the woke mob destroy America
from the inside
Yeah, you'll see it do it again. That's a
Damn.
Yeah, they're so fast.
Yeah.
Pretty fucking crazy.
I do...
Yeah, I had my run-ins with them, but what were you saying?
We should do a Fox comedy show.
That should be the goal for this show.
We could definitely parlay this.
I know people these days who live in northern California.
We could rename it.
Oh, Whiskey We Sip.
Oh.
- We sit and talk about the good old days.
- How about this?
- I don't think I've ever had to whisk it in my life.
- You, me, and you.
- Oh, right.
- We have a show on FX called The Speak Easy.
- Oh my God, yes.
- You walk down there, it starts with,
I'm walking down, right?
I'm looking for my first job, right?
Jubio, he's polishing the counter, you know?
me saying shh, shh, because it's a speakeasy. And then you come out, you're completely Mr.
Krabs. In fact, we just put you in a Mr. Krabs outfit and you're the boss. You have red skin,
you have a blue shirt on, and you're wearing stilettos.
Yup. Huge stress.
I try to get a job, but this is the thing, and this would probably work these days with
the Woker audience. What does a speakeasy need? A cabaret act, right? So I come in, I'm bald,
I'd make an amazing drag queen. You guys dress me up, you fucking give me amazing, beautiful,
amazing tits with toilet paper, you give me an amazing toilet paper ass, you give me a
toilet paper vagina that cover my toilet paper penis with toilet paper. And then you send
me out and I'm doing Jessica Rabbit stuff, right? I'm putting my high heels right on
a guy's chest and I'm grabbing his tie, pulling him towards me, going for a kiss, going away
last second, right? And then finishing my song. Do you guys think that would work on FX?
I think so.
Yeah, well it depends on the song.
And we could say "Junio got hit in the head by 9/11"
"I got my ass up in the air sometimes"
True. But if I was doing Taiyo Cruz or another pop thing like that, do you think that would
work?
Yeah.
Like the voice of an angel, a female angel?
Yeah, I think it will work. I think we'll get cancelled after the first season because of how raw it'd be.
That's okay.
That's okay. Getting cancelled after the first season.
Getting cancelled is good.
Yeah.
As far as I think.
In my woke mind, getting cancelled is probably...
My opposite of woke mind. I want to be cancelled, right?
Right.
Man.
I'll say some cancel shit right now.
What's up?
Michael Jackson didn't do it, he's innocent.
Go ahead, cancel me.
Go ahead and try and cancel me, man.
See if I give a fuck.
He was just a...
What was that?
- They're breaking into Rex's house.
- I think they're-- - They already.
They heard the feedback from your headphones
and they thought you said it into the mic.
(laughing)
The thing about Michael Jackson, man,
is that he was a kid.
right as a kid and what did you do when you were a kid
you first i think you know
it's not a single kid
you ever saw a race
when i was talking nine years old i was fuckin every nine-year-old i know
certain michael jackson he's just a kid on the internet
so i don't understand why we have to
pretending he didn't make some of the best music ever made
you know also
what do you have
Woody Allen, he was an old pedophile at heart.
Right?
What does an old pedophile do?
He raped his daughter.
Yeah.
So it's like--
And is that so wrong?
I mean, yeah, but he was just, he was that at heart.
You know what I mean?
But he made good movies.
I haven't seen any of them.
I really can't comment on them.
Someone, I know somebody who saw them in,
saw him and son, what's his wife's name?
His wife's daughter?
Sun Yi.
saw him and Soonyi at a restaurant and he was like they are so in love.
I believe it. Amazingly in love. Good for them.
Yeah. We should say a man and his creepy stepdaughter.
Yeah of course dude but girls love their daddies.
Yeah. Right? That's true. They needed Lana Del Rey 20 years ago.
Yeah. Would have been fine. He would have made it. No one would have cared.
Exactly. They needed Lana Del Rey as a bodyguard for when they're in public because of how huge she is.
There we go. Yes, sir.
Fucking bitch.
No, she's a nice lady. Yeah, I know. Yeah, we love to have her on.
We would love to have her on and I'm sure she'd love to be on. She's got 14 PBRs, right?
Bud heavies.
No.
I'm kidding, Lana baby, if you're listening.
Which you are, I have insider information.
You are, yeah.
To completely, yes.
I really wanna get a celebrity to endorse beers we drank.
We don't really have one for Potabelt List.
Not a lot of celebrities.
We have Nate Roos.
We need, I mean, listen.
Nate Roos is great.
Nate Roos is great, but I need somebody who's like
at the Oscars or something, you know?
I need an Oscars level celebrity.
out. Meet Lizzie Kaplan. How about that?
Who's that?
She's an actress. She's like Scarlett Johansson, but worse.
I don't think I've ever even heard of this woman.
Yeah, I don't know who that is.
Have you seen Party Down?
Oh, I haven't seen Party Down.
Despicable. Have you ever seen Party Down?
How about, uh...
Nah.
It's good, dude.
Should I watch the new season on Peacock?
I'm a I haven't watched it. So I can't
Yeah, I can marino yeah, he says the M or R in the new one
And a Wow so the woke mob is lost again, that's another elf
- Kevin Hart says Kevin Hart
And so what Kevin Hart?
Is it is the behind the scenes a blooper reel? No
Okay. Oh, wow
They let that make it to air yeah
Yeah, we can't do that anymore
Didn't they take
Those because the woke mob is one they couldn't bring back a 20 year old show that the inward
It would never happen
What was the was it 30 rock that they deleted a bunch of episodes because they're racist
That was the woke mob winning
I think people got mad at "Always Sunny" or something and then 30 Rock was like "Okay,
I kind of get what's happening here" and they took him down.
The thing is, if you watch 30 Rock, every episode of that show has like 50 racist jokes in it.
Yeah, and it's awesome.
It was the funniest show.
A young woman made it.
It's allowed.
Oh, true.
Oh true. Well you know who started that trend of deleting all the racist episodes?
No. Bugs Bunny, Hanna-Barbera. True, oh Mickey Mouse! Yeah you're right.
It was the old cartoons. That's it, that's it. Yeah you're right. Actually Dr. Seuss even.
Yeah. Right? And I know some of those, if you ask me, I'm sure some of those caveman
caveman paint, some of the cave paintings,
they were saying some unsavory,
they had some unsavory sexual dynamics
that have been scrubbed from history.
I would guarantee that, right?
Some rock that's like above the stick figure's head
that's about to hit a woman.
Some anthropologist guy just came through
and turned it into flowers or something.
- Yeah, now they're saying that there's only
stick, man stick figures fucking other man stick figures.
- Yeah. - But we know that's not true.
We've seen the circles and the dots.
You can't pretend that that was never a thing.
The circle and the dot and the triangular bush
at the bottom of the stick figure.
Yep.
The fuck is going on?
Playing Pivot, right?
Making pornography in Pivot, the animation application?
Nope.
Fucking Newgrounds ass.
Dude, oh God, Newgrounds ass?
I'm on Newgrounds, I'm on the adult page.
Yeah.
I'm fucking--
watching stick figure sex orgy 2
I'm fucking the yellow gumball from Shaolin showdown. Oh wow, but with giant boobs
Quick, what's your favorite beating fuck games?
From new grounds who Julio meet and fuck
It's in development like that one that much yeah, it's in development. It's not out yet. It's a beta
I
Never play I got really scared of meat and fuck games
There was something to me that was like if you're watching like okay
So I don't know if this makes sense, but when I was a kid if I like watch porn
I would like I would like watch it with like one eye closed and one like half open
Because I and I would like kind of watch it with a blurred vision
Yeah, like this like watch like how George Bush senior would watch porn just like kind of like this right and then
And that was like almost too much.
And the idea of playing a game,
like I thought playing a game
where you could like fuck people in it
was basically, biblically, just as bad as having sex.
- Yeah, if it was too active?
Too much of a viewer input?
- Yeah, I guess so, yeah.
- I don't know if I ever did a mean fuck game.
- Really?
- No?
- No.
I think by the time I was old enough to think about that,
just watch. You were into visual novels weren't you? No. I didn't get into visual novels until I was like 22.
That's so much worse. It is so much worse. Juvia what was your favorite meet and fuck?
Because you opened this conversation so I know you have one.
Yeah. Princess Peach. I don't know they're kind of the same. They always like just go to a bar
and there's a girl with big tits. This guy's had so much fucking meet and fuck sex.
They're all the same just tears in the rain to this guy. Yeah, let me nothing to me now Wow no. I'm on steam playing
Coco life sim and just doing something really bad
Yeah
I'm looking at looking up someone's life
You remember when you play a new grounds game that wasn't like a sex game
And there would be hidden sex in it or like hidden boobs or something. Yeah, it was so awesome, man
Frank's adventure three
Hot Coffee, Grand Theft Auto.
Which one was Hot...
Grand Theft Auto.
Was that the... wait, was that the name of the mission?
No, I think... I don't know, dude.
What are you talking about?
There's a thing called Hot Coffee for Grand Theft Auto boots.
Oh, okay, yes. In San Andreas.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I was never horny enough to be like, "I want to see video game boots."
because I could find regular boos just as easy.
That's like too much work.
You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
- You can just type boos.
- But it was kind of better
'cause you could earn it, you know?
- Yeah.
Yeah, you could earn it by just selling a mod for Skyrim
and just killing a woman and stealing all her clothes
and now she's completely naked.
- I've never played Skyrim.
- Really?
- It was okay for the time.
- No, you should play it.
You, especially 'cause you have VR, you should play,
there's a setup that I want so badly,
where you play Skyrim VR.
Skyrim's one of the only,
one of the only games that has full body haptic feedback
in VR, it's been modded in.
So if you get a full haptic body virtual reality suit
and you like put it on, when you go near like the stream
or like the river in Skyrim,
you feel like water droplets hitting your like legs.
- Whoa. - And I heard that,
and I was like, "This, that is, I would never leave."
- I think I should pay $10,000 to experience
what it would be like in your water.
- Dude, you're a guy with money.
You should have a haptic feedback suit.
You should have one of those things that's like
just a ball that you run on and you fall in place
and you look like a fucking idiot,
but it works in the game.
You should have all the custom guns, katanas, everything.
- Yeah, you're right, I should.
You should have a go-kart that you ride around in LA.
You should get in the Microsoft Flight Simulator and you should get the four levers that are
right next to each other.
I don't have the right kind of autism to be in the Microsoft Flight Simulator.
Boom Boom Volleyball, this was the one that I used to play on MiniClip.
On MiniClip?
You would hit a bomb back and forth and then there was some cheat code you could put in
to make him go topless.
Awesome.
I would, I didn't really know how to jack off but I would imagine what jacking off was
like whenever I'd look at that.
I'd figure it out.
Yeah.
I learned how to jack off from listening to Stan Uptown.
I figured it out.
What?
Okay, who?
I don't remember, there was no specific one.
It was, you know, before.
No, you have to say it, you have to say it.
I don't remember.
You have to say who it was.
It was probably maybe Ron White.
Maybe someone along those lines.
Interesting.
If you had said Louis, then I would have known
that you started jacking off very late in life.
Yeah, no.
I mean, come on now.
I was jacking off very early.
You're kind of listening to stand-up comedy
too early in life, I might say.
Yeah, no, 100%.
Yeah.
I learned so much
So much of my sexual knowledge comes from stand-up comedy between the ages of 10 and 13.
Just listening to it, learning.
Did you listen to Pandora Radio?
No.
That's how I discovered all stand-up when I was a kid.
Just watched Comedy Central.
Yeah, I guess I watched Comedy Central, but then I would also at night...
I've always been somebody who falls asleep with headphones in.
Like ever since I've had headphones, I fall asleep with headphones in.
and I remember watching, I saw Tenacious D pick of Destiny on TV and I was like,
Tenacious D is my new favorite band. So every night I would go on to Pandora and I'd fall
asleep to Tenacious D radio. And then it just has it, it's labeled as comedy and like rock or
whatever and I would just thumbs down all the rock songs and then get like, you know, fucking
Matt Brawner standing up there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know? Yeah.
I used to love musical comedy.
Me too, man.
When you're like
under 12 years old
and you listen to musical comedy for the first time.
For me, it went way past that.
I probably, I think I had a Spotify
playlist called Musical Comedy
that I made when I was 16.
That was like all just like,
I still like Lonely Island.
We were watching a Lonely Island video the other day that was very funny.
Stephen Lynch?
Stephen Lynch, dude.
I remember being, I always did this, I would listen to Stephen Lynch and Rucka Rucka Ali
and then when somebody else would talk to me about it I'd be like, "You know what the
crazy part about them is?
They actually have really beautiful voices."
That's great.
My favorite Stephen Lynch song was the one about the peanuts.
And I was like, that's my favorite one because he really lets the pipes out.
He really lets them go to the wall.
He does have a beautiful voice.
Isn't it amazing?
And he crushed, dude.
Oh, dude.
He crushed the live tracks on those albums.
He was destroying.
Yeah.
You can never crush as hard as a musical comedian.
I was more into Tobuscus and Ray William Johnson.
I understood what a black woman was because of Stephen Lynch.
Jacking off and you learned about black women from Stephen Lynch.
Yeah, I understood how to respect them.
Speaking of Ray William Johnson, I was in Providence this past weekend.
weekend the green room signed by Ray William Johnson at the Providence
Comedy Connection. Wow. Damn. I like put my hand on it to see if I could feel
some kind of energy coming. Yeah. His presence? Yeah. I think that he's
probably I would guess from that era of YouTube he's probably the most like kind
of mentally well guy from that era. I wouldn't say that. No. Not a shot. He
He never had like a big public weird breakdown or like controversy, right?
He just like kind of faded into obscurity.
I guess, but he's like 40 something, he's like 50 years old and he's still doing like
TikToks on YouTube about how
your mom is being annoying and how the teacher is really gay for giving you homework.
See, but that to me is mentally...
Like Shane Dawson is just ruined. Right? Shane Dawson is...
Yeah, but Ray William Johnson.
Do you think about how...
I guess Ryan Higa is probably okay.
Yeah, what was his username?
Do you remember that username?
Ryan Higa, let me look it up on...
Hold on one second.
Ryan...
Yeah, do you ever think about how old YouTube was?
Kind of like the founding fathers of modern culture?
It's Ryan Higa, is what his name is on Twitch.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
It definitely was, dude.
was dude.
Like Shane Dawson, what he became, it's now Sam Smith.
He just copied his whole thing, just being a fat gay guy.
You think Sam Smith's called Shane Dawson?
He's like, "Oh yeah, annoying fat gay guy, I can do that."
I guess you're right.
Yeah, I know this isn't the right time to do this, but I think I'm recording on the wrong microphone the whole time.
You've been recording on the wrong microphone? Yeah, that's fine. I'm recording on OBS anyways. Yeah, yeah, we got you.
I thought that you got really bad work news, so I'm glad that it was just about our
our side project. Are you guys excited to have a side project now? I love it. Yeah, it's awesome.
I've always wanted to have a side project.
Yeah, we could do anything that we want with it.
we could just like we could get crazy here we could do the chips eating episode
where we just eat chips into the microphone for an hour. I would love that.
Chips we ate. Chips we watched.
Yeah. Oh, okay. Kind of crazy with it. I was wearing my neck brace in Providence and
oh yeah by the way if you ever have to burp on this show, do it directly into the mic.
- This is a man's show, okay?
We make a point that we talk about,
you know, I thought the beer would scare him off, right?
Turns out these fucking bitches,
they will listen to the 30 minute point, right?
But then we start talking about jacking off,
masturbating, right?
But then we drop Ryan Higa, they're out by then, right?
And the ones who aren't, the burp will scare them away.
(burps)
- Every time Rex drinks out of his beer,
He gets a new perk for the zombies machine.
He's getting fucking, you're getting the fast reload and the ammo pickup.
True, you're running way way faster now.
You're running so fast there's a trail behind you, like a little ghost, like in KOTOR.
I really want them to make another KOTOR game, man.
It's really, I try, you know, I love those games, I love KOTOR 1 and 2.
my favorite games ever and I tried playing Mass Effect people like it's
like a better version I think that game sucks I think Mass Effect is a Mass
Effect yeah I think I like Mass Effect 2 but the Mass Effect 3 is like really
dropped the ball yeah I guess every any which is like the same whatever Mass
Effect I played had a some mission where you go to a snow planet and it was such
bullshit like boring like I'm driving a fucking Hummer yeah through the snow for
hour I just I gave up on it I couldn't do it anymore.
My only memory of Mass Effect was I had never played Mass Effect 1. Mass Effect 2 came out
and I tried to pirate it. My mom had the worst internet possible. Just awful.
AOL?
Yeah. It was like a step above AOL. Like they stopped having AOL and she got the worst possible
It was Thanksgiving and so like my cousins were staying over and I was pirating Mass
Effect 2 which was like 10 gigabytes, massive.
Talking about a two day download, right?
And I remember all my cousins had to do like homework and they'd be like, "The internet
is just impossible to use here.
I wonder what's wrong with it."
I have no clue. Knowing full well that I was using all the bandwidth to download Mass Effect 2.
And then I never played it. I just downloaded it, played it for like an hour and unsold it.
That's awesome.
You gotta play it, man.
It was just ruining their weekend.
I need a new game to play.
Play the Atomic Heart. Game looks awful.
Yeah, it kind of looks like poop to me.
People said that it's like a new Bioshock, but I was like, alright, every time a new game
comes out I always get like someone annoying in the chat being like, "You have to play
this, you have to play that, you have to play that."
So what I've been doing now is I just look up on YouTube, like, "Atomic Heart Walkthrough"
and I just skip around until I find something really annoying, like the main character talking
to an annoying character and be like "Oh, this game sucks!" and just throw it off.
And never think about it ever again.
That's smart. That just deletes it from your brain. You've already categorized it as terrible.
Yeah.
I've got a new theory that main characters should never speak anymore.
How do you guys feel about that?
I...
The wife is playing the Hogwarts game.
Really?
Not me.
I would never, never, never do that.
I would never do that.
Because even the men who listen to this manly show know that that is wrong.
It is wrong.
To play that.
If you play that game, you're fucking disgusting.
It is awful.
You fucking disgust me.
Yeah.
It's despicable.
Shit.
If you play that game.
If you watch the movies, you're an amazing queen.
But the guy who plays the main character, it's so effective.
They got a guy who just sounds exactly like Daniel Radcliffe and sounds exactly like Harry
Potter.
And it raises me to...
Does he say something like "flippendo"?
What's that?
Have you ever played the old Harry Potter games?
Uh-uh.
Really?
I played the one on the DS.
I only played, I played it and it was kind of like this game
where you could like walk around and shit,
but I just went to, I just liked doing the classes
because I was like--
- You wanted to do it all the time.
- If I was in the Harry Potter,
if I was in Harry Potter, I'd be Hermione.
- If I was in Harry Potter, I would do it all day.
- I don't wanna fight a troll.
I wanna learn, I wanna learn how to do this.
It seems very easy.
The fact that you have to go to school
to learn how to do this and say a word
means that a lot of these, and I don't mean this in, you know, don't take this the wrong
way, a lot of these wizards, and maybe it's just the British, I think mentally disabled.
I think a lot of them.
The fact that you have to go to a school to learn how to make a U shape with a piece of
bark and say "stupendous."
I think if you have to go to that special education, it should require you to go untrained
for seven hours a day.
Definitely.
And the other thing is, how hard are these to learn?
Every single one of these fucking words have a Latin root.
Yeah.
Right?
Like how...
That is...
Yeah, anyway.
There's no wonder a piece of crap came up with that whole fucking universe.
Yeah.
Yeah, well it's not only like special education.
It's like people who are different from others.
They got different abilities.
Yeah.
They're differently abled.
In different ways.
They're differently abled from the normal people.
And they think the trees are talking to them.
Yeah.
And that there's ghosts.
Yeah, as a guy as an anti-woke guy, I'm a little bit confused about how to play that game though
because on one hand
There's a women in it
The person who made it is is a bad person right
As a guy who's anti-woke. I'm like thumbs up. That's amazing. Yeah, but then the people who made it
They're putting all this crap in there. Here's a girl. Here's a guy. Here's a two guys. Here's two girls
Two guys. Yeah, Ali and I were back there.
Two guys, there better be a ping pong doubles match going on, right?
Two girls, they better be scissoring. Turns out that one was true.
And so I'm a little bit conflicted about this whole game.
But luckily I'm not playing it and my wife is.
And she's so stupid that she doesn't really understand the whole political thing.
She's just enjoying the video game.
political statement right and I'd say I tell her sometimes like you know that
you're essentially wearing a swastika tattoo directly on your head one on
your back and one in the middle of your stomach yeah she usually does this
usually takes one head for off because what do you say
was that huh and I go nothing do they solve the the the banker else in the
games and let me tell you Rex turned it up to 11 literally took the computer they
opened up the rendering computer right right they opened up the disk drive they
They put in a paper copy, an original 1935 paper copy distributed by the Ford Motor Company
of the Protocols of the Elders of Zion.
They put it in the DVD drive, they shut it, and they got some amazing, amazingly Jewish
monsters that handle all the money in this game.
Yeah, totally different from real life too.
Long silence from me and Jubio.
Yeah, don't laugh at that.
That was a test. I was testing you. I don't even know what that means.
That's one of the protocols.
Is that I have to test you to see if you like that show.
I personally am a big fan of Chase Bank and the Disney Channel.
Yep.
Wait, is Disney... Disney was... Disney was...
Disney was... hated Jews, right?
Hated them. Couldn't stand them.
Yeah.
Do you feel like I could be...
Do you feel like I have a Jewish soul?
I mean you live in New York, you've been infected by the disease.
Your soul is tainted.
Do you think in another world, because I feel like growing up I was like, I really wish
I was Jewish.
Jewish is way cooler than...
Really?
Yeah dude.
I feel like in middle school I heard about like the Sabbat and shit and I was like that's
so much work.
Why would anyone ever want to be Jewish?
You know what I wanted to be? When I was a kid, I was like, "You know who's the number one guy in terms of who, if I could trade my look and family history for right now? Lenny Kravitz."
Yeah.
I was like, "Lenny Kravitz is number one, dude. I would be Lenny Kravitz in an instant."
Lenny Kravitz works because he's also, you know, part of a church.
That's not Jewish.
Yeah, I think that I I just I loved like I really loved Mel Brooks movies when I
was a kid I'm pretty obsessed with Mel Brooks and it really got in my head I was
like Jewish guys just have just a way cooler thing going on they can be short
and people think it's kind of neat yeah that's if a normal European guy is short
it's kind of embarrassing you know yeah yeah but it's almost like an excuse if
you're short to be like oh no I'm Jewish right it's quirky and it's not even that
Jewish people are shorter or something it's that you're thinking well he's
probably gonna make up with for it with a personality and he's probably very
smart you know what I mean yeah no I see what you're saying that's very sweet of you to have such a kind of human touch
I really do I had a yeah I was pretty obsessive about Jews I used to just try
to find them in my home town.
Yeah, make sure everyone knew where they were at.
Yeah, you know, I'd go up to there,
and just so I would remember where they were,
I'd go up there with some red paint,
just draw an X on their front door.
Right.
And that was--
Probably pointed them a little,
kind of like this, with the car.
Yeah, exactly, hey, they're over there somewhere.
You know, walk by, go, hey guys, good to see you Jews.
Love you.
- Oh look, there's the Jews.
Look at them over there.
That's a nice time.
Thanks for being here.
- You bring out the worst in me, Rex.
You bring out all the worst things in me.
- Dude, Eddie's threatening to be closer to you physically.
You're gonna get put in jail.
- That is true.
- They're gonna kill you.
- I will protect him.
- Do you think you can make it in big bad New York City?
- I think I could.
- Yeah, I met, I talked to some people today
who live in Los Angeles, who I'd never talked to before.
And I, it really, I was like, "God damn, dude.
"That is the worst place on earth."
- Yeah, I do not.
Every second I'm here, my soul dies a little bit.
- Any given person from Los Angeles is just a,
just nothing.
- Yeah, it's a different type of,
'cause they're like weird,
but they're weird in a different way.
People in New York, they're also weird.
You know, it's like almost cool in a way.
Not cool, cool is a really strong word, but cooler.
- It's cool.
- That's at least how I feel.
I've done my time here.
- Well, that's where his roots are.
He's just going back to mother base.
- That is true.
That's not false.
There's the ocean here.
It's like my sound, you know?
- Where do you think New York City is?
- Probably by the ocean, but it's cold.
(laughing)
It's probably close to water.
Yeah, it's kind of close.
If you have to go out in a jacket, it invalidates the ocean.
I guess you're right, yeah.
Yeah, so the ocean, it's the same thing when I was in college, when I was at UNCW.
UNCW has some amazing programs, has a great film program, a great English program.
I think it's second only to the Iowa Writers
graduate program, the big one.
So I thought when I went there,
I was like this is a great school, this is awesome.
It's in my hometown, how great is this?
But it's five minutes away from a beach,
so the people who decide to go there
are just the biggest morons in the world.
And here's the worst part, they're right.
- Yeah, they are right.
- You should spend all your time
within five minutes of a beach.
The ocean is the best part of the earth.
- Yeah, 100%.
They're 100% right, but I hate that.
- The people in Los Angeles are so happy, man.
- Yeah.
- And we have an ocean here.
We can go to Rockaway Beach,
but you're gonna get bird shit on you,
you're gonna get human shit on you,
somebody's gonna throw a Frisbee and break your teeth.
You have to like, you have to like figure out,
like you can never, as many times I've been
to Rockaway Beach, I've never been able
put down a towel as a perfect rectangle.
It's always turned into a bit of an S, right?
I'm turning around somebody else's blanket
and there's some lady's asleep
and her knee is popping out of her fucking towel
and I'm afraid to touch it.
- Well, you know what the solution to that problem is?
Just go to Cancun.
- Oh, okay.
I like, and Cancun is in America, yeah?
Essentially, yeah.
Okay, all right, then I'm a bit interested, I would say.
It's very US-centric, how they've built it.
If you've been to Cancun, you have never been to Mexico.
Yeah, very true.
Cancun, that's what my grandpa says,
he says, "Cancun, the cartels have a deal with Cancun."
They say, "Because you make so much,
"we own part of your hotels,
"we will not come in and cut off the heads
"of every single man, woman, and child
"who's staying in that hotel."
But he says if you go to somewhere like Mexico City,
which I hear they call the, what do they call it?
The Papa, the Papi?
What do they call Mexico City?
- They call it the City of Angels.
- The City of Angels.
If you go there, Mexico City,
They just basically, it's like the final days of Afghanistan.
You know, people are jumping,
are throwing their babies,
trying to hit them into a plane cockpit so they'll be safe.
It's a very scary place,
so I don't think I'll ever go to Mexico.
- No.
- Unless we do, unless any comedy clubs or theaters
would like to give us some kind of amazing deal
on a show that we could do in Mexico.
I think even if we don't get that good of a deal,
it would be very, very cheap.
- How many tickets do you think we could sell in Mexico?
- I think I was looking at the breakdown demographic
on what's the thing, Anchor?
- Anchor.
- And there's definitely the most fans in Mexico City,
in Mexico, for Paul.
- Every time I look at that, I'm like,
these people have a VPN.
No, it's stupid.
No, because you can click on it and it'll give you a breakdown.
There's a lot of people in Sonora, in different states where it doesn't make sense to VPN
it to.
So I think we could definitely sell out some room.
Okay.
So let's take a look.
Hold on.
All right.
Geographic location.
Location these flavored beers
All right
79% United States
Yes, 7% Canada
Mm-hmm. Let's go. I'm gonna keep scrolling down till I hit Mexico
We have mmm Columbia
Mm-hmm, Taiwan
Israel
Yeah, well you see
- Israel is in our top 20.
- It's like when a band-- - Israel, Hong Kong.
- It only goes to like Mexico City
for like the Latin American date.
All those people from like Israel and Pakistan
and South Korea are gonna fly to Mexico to see us.
- I don't even see Mexico on here, dude.
- You must have missed it. - How did you find it?
I must have missed it.
Dude, how is, where the fuck is Mexico?
What does the Mexican flag look like?
It's probably like a--
- Like the Italian flag.
- Oh, okay, all right, sorry.
So Mexico is between Poland and Ukraine.
- Yep, geographically too.
- Yep, the most in Mexico City.
- Wow. - Does it have a number?
- No, it just gives you percentages.
- Basically 25% of our Mexican listeners are in Mexico City.
- Okay, but how many listeners are in Mexico?
- How many what?
- How many listeners are in Mexico?
- It doesn't say, it just gives us a percentage.
- What's a percentage?
It should be enough where people in Mexico City and people around there
would probably come and just fill that little room.
Yeah.
I would say so as well, yeah.
Yeah, so if we could do maybe somebody's living room
or maybe a classroom that might work.
Yeah.
We can do it in Julio's place and we can sell souvenir stinky beers.
Well, I'm not even close to Mexico City and I only have one stinky beer left.
Thank you very much.
What, did you drink them all?
No, I only had two and I drank a quarter of one and I threw it away.
And I have another one that's unopened and I'm still scared of it.
I don't want to open it.
Don't you just want to see?
Were they all stinky?
They weren't all stinky, but the one or two that I did have, like right when I bought
them, were still like a type of flavor that I wasn't going to drink.
Like these I can drink.
These are like…
I love all trash.
Can you just drink these?
No, way too strong.
Way, way, way too strong.
These are giving me like a headache from all the sugar.
Yeah, I can't believe it.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe you're drinking those, dude.
Can you just have a normal beer one week, man?
Yeah, maybe next time. I forgot to go to the store and grabbed these out of the mini fridge.
Oh, okay.
You know what? Beersters are just like a concept, like a social concept.
Anything could be a beer, technically.
I guess that's a good point.
Yeah, so next week it could be anything that we're drinking.
Maybe I could have a root beer.
I don't like to drink soda anymore.
I try not to.
I also don't drink beer anymore because it will make me fucking fart.
Yeah.
I think the last time I tried drinking actual root beer that's not Dr. Pepper, I had a crazy
headache and I didn't even finish it.
Guys, I'm going to open up this second beer.
I could try recreating that.
Yeah, well, because we're going to do movie Mondays after this, so I'm like, you know,
it'll carry over.
This is a Heineken Silver.
So this is similarly 4% alcohol.
Yeah.
24 fluid ounces.
It's stronger than this 3.2%.
Might as well just be fruit juice.
So that's why I got the Imperial, or the Voodoo Ranger, I got the Voodoo Ranger IPA, and I
said, "Man, that's so strong.
I'm gonna be ready to cry after I finish that.
And I kind of am.
I was very strong.
And now I will have this amazing Heineken.
And then, you know, I'm looking at a 9.45,
9.50 bedtime tonight.
- Yeah, so in one hour.
- I'm gonna eat just the very end of the corner
of a 15 milligram edible gummy, right?
And I'm gonna do that in 30 minutes.
And so what I'm gonna do is we're gonna go on stream,
We're gonna start watching movie Mondays.
And I think the movie we picked out
is about an hour, 25, hour 30.
We're gonna get one hour in,
that's how long it takes for the gummy to kick in.
And I'm gonna say, "Guys, Phil has to go out.
"I have to go right now, bye."
And then I'll click into call.
So I got basically my entire night put out.
- Well, you do know that you don't need to do any excuses.
Like, you're free to go at any point.
- Yeah, but I was talking to somebody about this last night.
Anytime I get way too high, I'm way too proud to say,
I'm too high right now.
I've never, ever uttered those words.
Never, not even like to, not even,
not to my closest friend would I ever say,
I'm way too high right now, I need to go to bed,
I need help.
So I will just make it happen and then be like,
guys, (groans)
it's 3 p.m. (groans)
- And I'll leave.
- Yeah, I took a nap.
- Yeah.
- Oh great.
- I need to get back on my nap.
- I took a nap.
- I love naps.
- 2.30 to 3.30.
Perfect nap.
- That is perfect.
Although they say that that's the worst possible
duration of a nap.
- An hour?
- It needs to be either more than an hour and a half
or less than 30 minutes.
Something about, because I think when you do an hour,
you slip into the in-between stage of sleep
where you're not really resting
and you're not getting like deep sleep, you know?
So there's not anything going on for you.
You're basically only napping enough to get a dream
and then you come back out.
So you're just all confused.
- Yeah, I didn't have a dream.
- I really have a dream.
I really don't have dreams.
- I didn't say my creativity fails.
- Yeah, that you would have had a dream.
I woke up this morning and I didn't have a dream,
but I did wake up thinking, dude, she keeps,
all around the house, she keeps hanging up t-shirts
and stuff to dry and forgetting about it.
And then we go to sleep and I wake up
in the middle of the night and I'm sure,
I'm so sure it's a specter.
I'm so sure it's a poltergeist.
And so I sit there and I have the most scared
I've ever been in my life,
like sitting in a trench in World War II.
that level of like physical fear,
adrenaline rushing through my body.
- Yeah, you've been up to your ears.
- And then I realize, yeah, and then I realize
it's my South of the Border t-shirt
that is sitting there.
- Don't look now, but if you see on your webcam
over your shoulder, there's a shark specter
jumping off from the ground.
- I looked, okay.
- What's your favorite t-shirt?
- My favorite t-shirt?
- Yeah.
Hmm
Probably my t-shirt that says it's a t-shirt
That I bought for $40 when it was like I spent my my only $40 I owned on it
It was like when I was really really broke and it's a guy playing pool and it says
Yeah, yeah that same shirt it says why work when you can run the tables amazing
And I almost never wear it because it's a white t-shirt, so I get really scared. It's gonna get stained
Mm-hmm and some guy at a show one time offered to buy it for me for $200
He was like that was the coolest shirt. I've ever seen. Will you can you sell it to me and I said buddy
Wait ten years and add two zeros, right?
Yeah. Well, you know what my favorite my favorite shirt is the one that you gave me Caleb from South the border
It's a black shirt and it says what?
something about being a crazy tamale or some shit
I'm such an amazing friend.
You are.
I found the other South of the Border shirt
that I meant to give to Rex at the office yesterday,
or two days ago.
Or not two days ago, a week ago.
But I found it and I was like,
okay, because I forgot to give it to Rex
and it's been almost, it's been over six months,
this is just my shirt now, I'll get him something else.
No, that's fine, I have one of your shirts
that I've just stolen and appropriated.
What is it?
It's the one with an alien that says
take me to your dealer.
Oh yeah, thank God.
I definitely lost so many clothes on the tour
and I was about to be so sad
if it was one of my favorite shirts.
Yeah, no, it's not.
No, that's fine, you can have that one.
For me, favorite, Monster Energy logo on the front.
If you can read this, it's show off on the back.
I love that shirt.
I would buy that shirt from you.
That is an amazing shirt.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't remember where I saw you wear that.
It was recent.
I saw you wear that and I was like,
God damn, that's an incredible one.
I think I definitely wore that in New York.
Remember?
Yeah, last time.
It's gotta come with me everywhere.
I take it.
Of course.
I would hope so.
It's like the nuclear codes.
Yeah.
Never let it out of my sight.
Guys.
That's enough.
That's enough beers we drank, I think.
It certainly is.
Unless, uh...
I mean, do you guys have anything to say to close it out for the people, man?
What, I mean, this has gotta be, by the way,
this has gotta be...
the number one podcast on the Patreon right now.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Every single episode people are going, what?
Wait, they do two episodes a week
and also this bonus episode that is a better version
that has upgrades on two of the hosts
and one of the hosts stays exactly the same?
(laughing)
- Yep. - It's crazy.
- Did they do that? - Amazing.
- It'll take over.
- It's the best value-- - It'll have 15,000 followers
on our Twitter account. - Yeah.
Guys, juice beers we drank.
- Yeah, out of which we drink.
- Rex doesn't get a single dollar of the money.
- No.
- Right, this is free labor, but we need--
- I do it a lot.
- Here's what I want, the dream that I have
is that one day, it's called the Podcast About List,
Patreon, but more people are subscribing
for beers we drank.
They're not even listening to the Pod About List,
they're like, what the fuck are you talking,
Pod About List, I've never even heard of it.
- Yeah.
- Right, wait, Pod About List, isn't that the company
that owns beers we drank?
- Right.
- And then this is the most popular podcast in America,
That's what I hope for.
I think that's, we're on track.
And we're, you know, we're drinking beer at Joe Rogan, we're drinking beer at Bobby Lee.
We're on Tiger Belly.
Right?
Yeah.
We're drinking IPAs called, you know, Dog, Head.
Dog Tits.
Tom's Blood IPA.
Yeah.
I would love to drink one one day.
Alright, bye guys.
Bye.