We are going
I love that drinking sound.
I know.
I love beer.
And drinking.
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that boob out.
the
my god it's beer
yen guys welcome one hundred yet again
to uh...
one hundred to close to one hundred episode of beers we drank only the
closest we've ever been to a bit closest by far the we've ever been
Let's go ahead and crack open these beverages.
It's a strong top.
- Can I lead as the host
and as the probably having the most boring beard?
Which I thought would be fun.
- As probably, as easily the fan's least favorite member,
you are allowed to lead.
You get to go first.
To try to earn some goodwill back from these people
who really, really despise you.
- I went to my local 7-Eleven,
the one closest to my house.
And I was going through the preselection,
They had really generic stuff, really nothing too crazy.
But then I saw that they had this one, and I thought to myself, "This is going to be so
funny."
But then Rex prefaces beer with being so crazy that I think it's kind of the lamest beer
in the world now.
It's an Indian Pale Ale, Evil Dog.
Aero Del Mar.
How is that not crazy?
That's awesome.
That's awesome, man.
Wait, it's Ocean Dog, it's Sea Dog, I thought it was Evil Dog.
I thought it was Mal, not Mar.
Right, not Mar, like the Corona.
I think I am fully dyslexic.
Dude's poppin' Zen.
That's okay, I am poppin' a Zen.
Um, I will go...
Well, first I need to hear... Sorry, I just assumed you were gonna skip the rating.
No, it's okay. I will rate it badly, as I always do.
Mmmhmmm, I'm surprised you sprung for the IPA.
That is so not the flavors that I think you like in anything.
Yeah, well I saw the dog and I saw I saw dog and I thought it was what can be funny
You like a dog
Type beers you're not me and me and
Rex over here. We're getting
Caviar type beers we are getting the kind of an aged cheese
Clams
That kind of thing a chicken nugget pizza pizza beer. Yeah, that's like the kind of you like chicken nugget pizza food
and the chicken nuggets and pizza of beer I'm gonna go next guys this was a fail
turned reverse fail otherwise known as a win I forgot or I did not have time to
get a beer today I was busy all day long non-stop go go go yep and then I was
like oh we have to record I looked in the fridge for mayonnaise didn't find any
man is but I did find a beer that my wife hid from me so that I wouldn't drink it
I found a beer that she hid for me secret and the secret beer and those who have
seen the show before know that sometimes I get my wife go and get me a beer or
she on she gets a beer for me on the way home she always picks the most
disgusting pumpkin worse dog shit coffee really just as a way to prank me it's a
full prank that she does to me.
And this time, I wanna show you guys the difference
between a beer that she gets me
and a beer that she gets herself.
Every beer I get is a bacon washed, disgusting,
- Wasn't the last one, the normal beer,
what was it called, the beer can?
- The regular beer.
- Regular beer.
- Yeah, so this, she just gets a normal, just IPA,
just a craft IPA.
this is a lamplighter brewing company double IPA.
It is disappearing into the forest.
It's an invisible beer.
It is, it has a rabbit on it.
It's so clear that a woman picked out this beer.
Yes.
Because he was smoking my ass beer.
I did not pay attention to the fact that it's almost 9%.
But guys, because I didn't pick out my own beer,
because I didn't pick out my own beer,
I'm taking this to another level.
Because what do I have before me?
But a bottle of Buffalo Trace, guys.
We're doing a beer and a shot tonight.
- Damn.
Wait, I can join you.
- I can also join you.
I still have my skull.
- Let's go, man.
- All right, I'm gonna go get it.
- Hold on, I'm gonna go do the same thing.
(coughing)
(singing)
*sad music*
*laughing*
what's up?
what? WHAT?
I just tried to open this with my mouth as you guys left, and the cork flew off, and
probably two ounces of bourbon went directly into my nose and my eye.
Oh my god, I'm fucking covered.
Ugh.
Okay, man.
That is an amazing sign for things to come.
You know some no passion is coming.
Oh god that was insanely, that feels bad.
What's up?
Oh my, I opened my, you were gone but I opened my bourbon with my mouth and it exploded into
my nose and it was truly one of the most painful things.
Somebody will clip this and you'll be able to see I had a true reaction.
And that's how you know none of this is scripted.
Things like this happen all the time.
up
to beers
we're bodies
musco beers
also okay
or
uh... now the beer guys
this is how i'd be a shot where he chases with the beer
jesus christ
Now beautiful Rex.
So I lied about having a crazy beer.
I have a Heineken.
Oh my god.
Pranks we pulled!
Don't do this to me!
I just, I offhandedly was pranking Caleb and then you fed that information to Juvio and he's like "Oh my beer is so gay it's got a dog on it."
You told me it was crazy.
I mean I was, you know, just running with the bit, the gang.
Since when have we done pranks and lies on this show?
Since never.
Well, starting today.
Okay, give me a Heineken review.
It's perfect.
Heineken is great.
Heineken, okay.
Heineken and Rolling Rock, I call them the green bottle twins.
They are severely underrated beers in a glass bottle.
I don't think I've ever had rolling rock in a glass bottle, but I have had 30 green cans.
The green cans are not as good as the glass.
Something about glass feels harder to me than a can.
Yeah, I would agree with that, yes.
Okay, so yeah, so I'm on the right track.
It also tastes better out of the glass hard bottle.
I think that's true.
There's a, okay, here's, I'd like to posit you guys something, okay?
Right.
Sure.
This is my theory, I've been working on this for many years.
Beer tastes better the harder the glass is, right?
Well, what about a Sapporo?
A Sapporo is a very hard glass and that's one of my favorite beers, the hard can.
I see.
So you're saying glass as...
That's an extremely heavy duty.
So, yeah, container.
The harder the cup is, the drinking thing.
So like a really thick cup?
A thick glass cup is great.
But okay, so the vessel is harder, the beer is better.
But then with water, guys, the inverse is true.
The best water comes from a shitty plastic cup that I stole from the movie theater.
A big, disgusting, BPA-filled plastic cup with ice-cold water.
And then also, those bottles, those eco-bottles, those eco-water bottles that you can crush
and turn into a twisty weapon.
- I drink out of this and this is hard.
- See that doesn't sound good.
That sounds awful to me.
- Have I ever shown you guys my water drinking thing?
- Whoa, it's a Bucky's cup.
- It's a Bucky's cup.
- See that's a perfect looking cup to me.
- It's a really insane cup.
It says, sorry, I can hear you over the sound
of freedom ringing, which I'm not American
nor care about freedom.
- Well, we let freedom ring.
You just said the same thing twice.
- Right. - Yeah.
- But I drink water-- - You're not American.
You don't care about freedom.
What do you care?
What, if you ran for president,
or Presidente of Mexico--
- Dude, this is so fucking easy.
I've been thinking about this for so long.
- Oh, okay, well, let me interrupt you.
Go ahead, you have the floor, my friend.
- What I would say is so,
I wouldn't make any grand promises.
I wouldn't go out there in the streets
kissing dirty babies.
all
Here comes Chris Christie, big, making out with a kid's head.
Ew.
Alright, so no baby kissing, no grand posturing myself as the new star of any which side political
spectrum side.
My one and only thing is I'm going to go out there on the podium on the Republican debate.
So you are, you said no side, but then you said you are a Republican.
I just ended up there. I just ended up there anyways.
Okay. So we'll just go. Uh, I'm sorry, Donald Trump. Uh,
what I promised the people is I want to make groceries $1.
Wow.
Can I ask you about this policy and plus we're building a wall by the way.
Yeah. Go ahead. Lady in the, in the white and the glasses. Go ahead.
Beautiful lady that I'm going to kiss later.
*laughter*
Hey, I have a beard and you are clean-shaven.
I don't wanna hear none of that.
But he has short hair like a boy, and you have long hair like a girl.
He looks like a lesbian.
Point to kill, but he's wearing a ribbon.
Nope.
Thank you.
Like a lesbian.
You're losing the debate right now.
Okay, go ahead.
What's your point?
Anyway.
Is all of the groceries you buy at once $1, or is each individual grocery $1?
I think that would be absurd.
I think it has to be individual groceries. So like every individual item is now this is just becoming the debate
So I just like to jump in here the
Groceries are not $1 as a whole according to mr. Julio's plan. I'll be ridiculous. That would be ridiculous, but I am an agreement on this
Grocery should be individually
$1 in this country. Yep, you come back home
You spend I don't know tops 30 bucks. You're gonna full pantry for it for two weeks
Okay, I like that but
Theoretically all groceries could be $1. They would just get smaller and that's fine
What if you had a smaller pantry? What if that's what we have really offering so but when you say all so you're saying
Like if you bought I don't know again something I eat a lot of you have one
Socialist Marxist into this debate by the way. Yeah, I agree. Well, it's clearly this woman in the white
And I think I recognize you from a Playboy cover issue. Yeah, and I'm okay with you staying
But I do think that yeah, if so, what's an expensive grocery? What's something you buy?
That's like kimchi is something that I buy and every time I get to the register. I'm $9
I can't believe I just paid $10 for this a big thing of a
of ham. A big thing is the groceries that you buy.
You buy spiral ham so often?
Are you insane?
Why would like what would a pound of ham should cost $10?
Yeah. $1. A pound of ham is, is, is not $10.
I don't think it's like the cheapest possible meat.
Well, I just went to the bodega and everything was $10 for a pound.
True. Well, you live in Hollywood.
That's true Hollywood East point, you know, that's what they we did
We had two TV shows that filmed in my hometown of Wilmington when I was a kid really and once people started
Dawson's Creek, yeah and
Another show like that that I don't remember the name of it, but because of these two shows we got the nickname
Hollywood East guys a bunch of stuff in my hometown that says Hollywood East
Well, Asheville is a woke nexus.
Well, I didn't live anywhere near Asheville.
Well, I'm just saying.
Well, you do come from a woke family.
Yeah, my family is anti- until recently, the least woke people of all time.
I was thinking the other day, my grandpa still says, uh, the blacks.
He says that all the time.
But he's not saying the n-word, which for a guy in his 70s might as well be saying people
of color in the most respectful way possible.
That is litera- I think that that- that he has- that's like his limit.
That's like where he can get to like 1930s level of respectfulness towards other races.
If you as like a person in their 20s are like the blacks, you are racist.
If someone who was born in 1940 says the blacks, they are saying black and indigenous people
of color.
Mmm.
But it- I guess you're right.
Just not enunciating the other four words of that.
I guess that's true as fuck.
My family, my mom has become a Wokie recently in the last, because of Trump.
Trump turned my mom completely into a Wokie.
Yes!
Trump turns moms into libs because he grabs women by the pussy and they hate that.
Is that true?
Yeah.
How did this transformation happen in your eyes?
Well, my mom, I think, okay, my mom was not a reality TV person, so she never had the
existing goodwill for Donald Trump, okay?
She didn't already think he was funny.
She didn't watch any movies with him in it?
Like, Home Alone?
Two?
The Home Al-
Can we get over this Home Alone thing?
We get it, he was in the-
He was a celebrity.
Plenty of celebrities are in movies all the fucking time.
Yeah, but not-
Okay?
The Minions are in-
Are in Despicable Me, did you know that?
I didn't know that, yeah.
And they're also yellow.
And they're completely yellow, just like Donald Trump.
Or he's some color.
Will you vote for a Minion?
What?
Real quick.
the
I was just the biggest dork. I forget that we had the same childhood. Yeah. Yeah in a way
We split at some point where you kept getting smarter and I stayed at the same kind of level of intelligence
but I
I had
Basically kind of saw a seeded this entire this libertarian thing with my mom for some time and she was showing I would put Ron
Paul videos on the on the TV on the YouTube app and
I would be like check this out man. He's basically owning
People because they I got her with the weed thing first. I was showing her Ron Paul videos
She was like, yeah, we'd should be legal and
Then she voted for Gary Johnson
Obama won and she held it against me for probably four and a half years treated me very differently
And then it's your fault, yeah, it was my fault and then and then the the fucking the
Debate started happening. She gets plugged back in Donald Trump comes up. She loved
What's the name Nikki Haley from South Carolina? She loved Nikki Haley. She's
this time probably I
Think Donald Trump will probably be the night
I do too I was thinking that which is like it'll be nice to not have to change our intro
Because the only two politicians anyone will care about or Joe Biden and Donald Trump. Yeah, probably but the thing is so
Nikki Haley gets knocked out my mom thinks of Donald Trump as an evil bastard and she thinks what is the next thing to a woman?
running for president a
gay guy
Yeah, and I
Got I got her she voted for Bernie in the primary. I believe
Which was pretty crap, but she said I'll vote for him in the primary because you want me to but I'm not gonna vote for
him for president
Which was awesome, but now she's still a huge Pete Buttigieg fan thinks that he should primary Joe Biden
She thinks Joe Biden is a pedophile. She's still that's a thing. She's like one of the only people who's like like straight-line Democrat and
Also believes that like Hillary Clinton has actually eaten a child
Like she believes all that shit. That's so awesome
Pretty awesome. Should we segue this into talking about what happened in Crown Heights?
What happened in crap? Oh, oh with the tunnel the tunnels
Yeah, I'm gonna let you take this one man. This is probably the funniest
the video of the
Hasidic guy
Crawling out of the tunnel and scurrying away
Uh-huh.
Might be the funniest video that we'll ever make.
Just wanna jump in, just wanna jump in here.
If I told this story, I would not have said scurrying.
But, again, Rex is telling the story, so he can go ahead and say scurrying.
Dude.
Anything like that, go ahead.
He was scurrying, 'cause he got that, he got like, and he started shuffling like this.
Yeah.
Too fucking slow.
Or not yet.
We're, we got...
Well, it's not our fault that fucking Haseeds are crawling out of tunnels in Crown Heights,
being videotaped by, you know, fellows on the street
doing probably the most embarrassing caricature of being a Jewish rodent of all time.
Okay, here...
Alright, again, Rice is fully Jewish, 100% Jewish.
He can say whatever he wants.
Every single person in my family is Jewish.
Okay.
Here's what I want to say about the tunnels.
Yeah, go ahead man.
I...
I... if I knew how to make a tunnel,
then I would make one. That sounds fun.
What's in it?
I don't think they were raping. I don't think they were doing anything crazy down there.
I think they built those tunnels
because they thought it was cool.
And then as soon as someone saw them in the tunnel, they were like, "Come on now."
I agree. I think that there's no malice with these tunnels.
I think they were almost certainly storage facilities
And the thing is if you the thing hot seeds are a whole different
Kind of person that you never see anywhere else. They all drive minivans
They all have barred windows that they go sit on once a year to do some holiday
it's a very bizarre culture and
what and I
Think that
They could definitely I could see them just being like it's cool. Like it's cool to have a tunnel
Yeah, like this is just cool, you know
I'm not gonna go with they own everything. That's not something that I would say personally
Maybe like a chosen people right and that nothing particularly applies to them
I think we should harness this power because they also wasn't it a big thing like when Israel was like claiming that
They were Hamas are like underground bases. It just came on that day that Israelis made the tunnels
Regardless I think we can harness this this power from from this chosen people and
Make more tunnels for for trains is what I say. That's my new platform
Seeds should build the railroad sir. I'm hearing from you. I think that would be a very
My time
Okay
There's no I thought types of Jews and there's there's normal people who just happen to have be
Unlucky enough to born people weren't Jewish. There's Hossein's who love it and then there's Israelis who are the mentally ill
Those are the white lights
Why is it that on this show everything we say we say with no malice and it always is the most anti-semitic thing
Are you on my screen? You're pointing to all my other discourse? That's right. Are you pointing at Rex on the feet?
I'm putting up the right person
Okay. Yeah, I think it really is psychotic that almost every single time it ends up being a
Disgusting display of anti-semitism in a way that we never mean it to be. Yeah, of course
I think except for maybe this guy
Yeah, are you pointing to me cuz that is Julio on my screen? I'm pointing at you Rex. I really am pointing at you
You pointed the other side, please. I'm a little
There you go, there we go, yeah, so enough of the tunnels man
Talk about it all you'd like man. I know you're talking about it behind closed doors. No, you never I have a family
And I have a life that I'd like to continue living
You're looking it up right now. You're watching the video
Not man, it was so funny
I went into that account that really puts like that take talk on Twitter and it was just like fully like a
like a pro sireness just like oh, this is what happening with like sign is in today and
I think that what they got made fun of so hard that they deleted it within like three hours
Which is really funny to me
Again man, it was cool. I know that now they've they've done something which I think this is a hate crime
they
They covered up the hole where the guy popped out of they did
It's a hate crime in the sense that we're not gonna get another video of a Jewish guy
It's a crime to every to man
Right man as a whole has been hate crimed by this disgusting display by the NYPD
Did you see that the Italian guy that interacts with that sect of Chabad so often that he's called the rabbi?
No, but that's awesome. That Italian cop who was like yelling at them. Wait, that's the guy- wait that guy that all the pictures are of?
Yeah, is he- they call him the rabbi? They call him the rabbi. I love that guy. He's awesome. Yeah, it's so funny
There's some post it's like it's all scam. It's all scheme because he's called the rabbi
No, that is the nicest way possible for saying he's the only one with the soft touch enough to interact with those
Wow, wow, do you should I maybe convert I
Would that be has there ever been a Gentile who is converted to not just Judaism, but a acidic Judaism
Yeah, I knew them. Yeah, I mean really I know a Mormon that hot seeds are Orthodox. Well, it was hubbub
So oh really
Has seemed but the thing the thing that's cool about the the whole like Hasidic thing is that they're there in these are the
closest thing that like is in Judaism to like like
Buddhist monks, yeah, like they believe they believe in like that like the
The what's it called the kabbalah kabbalah?
The Kabbalah is so cool, man
Most of them don't believe in the Kabbalah cuz that's like what Madonna is into
What's the kabbalah? Really? The Kabbalah is like this Jewish mysticism thing. And then also there's these there's all these posters. I don't know if this is
Chabad or Hasid, but there's all these posters in New York City that say like the
the
What's this? What do they call them?
The Savior is here or whatever and it's just some random like 95 year old guy on the poster and they're like this has been this
Is the real Jesus?
Yeah, and I think that is cool
Yeah, the Hossein's believe that like their one rabbi is the Messiah
basically
And then they passed that down
Generationally, okay. Yeah, so it's like Dalai Lama. Yeah, it is basically Dalai Lama
Yeah, I mean it's it's awesome if they weren't a completely evil sect of people that
Get away with lots of crimes like rape and things like that, which is I'm not saying that in an anti-semitic way
It's horrific what happens to the I know there's a there's a movie about this. Yeah, it's it's really bad
they don't like interact with the police at all, so they just
Things go on
and solved and...
Right.
They can't read, they don't have phones.
They have to have that really shitty haircut.
With the paisleys, the curls.
Paisleys, yes.
My mom was a kebab goer for about two years.
Yes.
No, but it was segregated so I didn't care.
Oh, you didn't care if she shaved her head or not?
Yeah, I was awesome. It was like, because growing up I would get in trouble every time we had
to go to the temple, right? You know, it's like, you're so annoying that your mom is
like, "I'm going to break your PS2 if you don't stop."
But then she goes to a different church so you don't see her.
Well, she's on the other side and she's not allowed to see you.
Oh, God.
So then you can just be on your phone the whole time and that is awesome.
God damn, that's cool, man.
That actually sounds so- my mom used to-
Isn't that so fucking awesome?
My mom would do full WWE moves on me in the middle of church because I drew a smiley face on the pamphlet.
Almost every single time.
Yeah. Yeah, my mom would fucking destroy me.
My life would be in shambles.
But then my grandma's on the other side of me, giving me gum.
Oh yeah!
Thanks for the gum, Nana!
I think that's an experience that people have been losing over the years.
That kids going, being forced to go to church and just being, rotting there for like two
hours so bored.
It's not TikTok.
They put, send them to church.
I had a much, I had, I would say I had one of the worst church experiences of all time.
Right up, Noah had the number one worst cause his dad was the pastor.
But my mom was the worship leader at our church.
Like every church we went to she would find a way onto the worship team.
And so I would have to get there at 6 in the morning and stay for the rehearsal and then
for both services every single day.
It was hell bro.
And so I would walk around and I would cuss to myself.
Because I thought that this was a cool kind of way to...
I thought God could hear me so I'd walk around and be like "fuck."
Yeah.
Ass.
For four hours?
Yeah, well, she'd only made me go to one service.
Right.
She'd only made me go to one service.
And my, I know I've talked about this before, but my past, sometimes I would really tune
in to what my pastor was saying.
His name was Devin.
Most of the time I'd completely zone out, but then every once in a while I'd lock in
because he would start talking about Obama and every single time he would be hinting
that somebody should be assassinating him.
And it was so fucking awesome.
That is awesome.
Yeah.
The nice thing about Temple Riot is that there's always a game of pickup basketball going on right outside
and kids in Yankees, Yamakas are just draining free throws because their fundamentals are amazing.
Free throws? They're doing fouls? They're calling fouls?
Of course! Everything is a foul.
But they're litigators at heart, so they're always getting into trouble and being like "Hey, that's a foul!"
It's a six hour game of 21.
But they're just sinking buckets from the freezer a lot.
That is so awesome, man.
Yeah, we didn't have anything like that.
My church was all fat guys, like fat people who like all owned all the franchises of all
the like fast food restaurants in our hometown.
And then there was one family, the entire family is like six boys shows up to church every single
a
nice bow tie look like? Crazy patterns that you fucking wouldn't believe. Different
themes depending on what time of year it was. You could tell that it was
autumn. Not even by looking outside you look at his fucking bow tie. He had a bow tie
I'm not I'm not kidding when I said I went to this church for four years never
saw him wear the same bow tie twice. Not once. This guy would wear him he'd turn
him and burn him dude. Give him to his kid every fucking time. He looked amazing.
that is crazy it was pretty it was pretty sick but we don't have in Christianity
we don't have a I'm trying to think if there's anything that's like has like
hot seeds in Christianity I guess Mormonism is kind of like that we're
like a little bit more insular and there's like kind of weird rules yeah I
I mean Mormons are similar. Really the Hasid's are like the Amish.
True, I guess Amish are... what are they? Yeah.
Are Amish... Amish aren't normal style Christian.
No, they're like Christian plus.
But don't they think the Pope is the devil?
Well, most people think the Pope is the devil.
That's true. My entire family thought that all of Catholics were going to hell.
Yeah, it's like a sect, right? You know?
Uh, maybe like Greek Orthodox?
Like, like the true, like, Orthodox, but...
I went to a couple of Greek Orthodox churches 'cause my friend went there.
And that was... I've still never been to a Catholic Mass, that's probably the closest thing I've ever gone to it.
And it was so...
-fucking boring, dude. -Yeah.
I was like, "I'm never complaining about church again."
It was so goddamn boring.
'Cause here's the thing, man.
the orthodox churches where the people wear robes
either greek orthodox or catholic
what do you get on communion
a wafer
yeah okay what do you get at a an evangelical
a hearty piece of sourdough bread
that's what we got and grape juice
that's actually fire
that was our communion
a big ass piece like
straight out of cracker barrel
just cornbread anything
yes any card they had their of a fuckin sweet potato and then you take that with
grape juice
it was amazing jesus has been picking up
over the years
yeah and i was reflected uh... in his in his uh... church
we had some big ones
jesus a little diabetic
was a little sweet
and as well as a little people probably every year we probably lost
in a two hundred fifty person congregation
probably lost three people to heart attacks every year
yeah but i think that's just living and it's not like you live in the south but
that just living near itself
i live in it
kind of fucking bullshit did you just say to me it's not like i lived in the
south that's pretty
that's crazy shit
that's what i think that's what i think that's the thing that's out
not carolina's not the south it has north in the name
Are you- I'm sorry, have you lost your mind?
Wait, hang on, I think-
Have you lost your- is North Korea the North Pole?
No!
It's Asia!
It's the North Pole of Korea!
Okay, then it's the North Pole of the Carolinas, but it is the South!
It's below the Mason Dixie line!
It's a- it is the South!
The Mason Dixie line is...
You're showing your hand here.
What?
It's Mason Dixon!
I said it and then I was like please nobody notice that I said Mason Dixie
line listen here's how Southern North Carolina is my hometown had the only
coup d'etat successful coup d'etat in American history because it was a that
town had a black guy running the newspaper and it got raided by the Klan
and they destroyed the entire town burned everything down and then it sucked
for a hundred years because of how racist people were.
Okay.
Being from a place that's racist doesn't mean you're from the South.
LA is in the southern part of the United States, it's below the Mason-Dixon line.
Sorry, Los Angeles didn't exist when the Mason-Dixon line was drawn, okay?
So I see a flaw instantly.
It's not part of the South, I'm sorry man.
North Carolina is part of the South.
What do you think the South is?
Do you think fucking Arizona is the South?
It's not the South.
No.
That's the Southwest, obviously.
It's very different.
North Carolina is easily the South.
You've spent no time there.
I'm not going to listen to you.
You're stupid.
It's...
No, I'm sorry.
You do not get to claim the South in this way.
Can we take a trip?
Are you crazy?
Are you out of your fucking mind?
Can we please take a trip to North Carolina?
Do you know nothing about North Carolina?
North Carolina is the South.
I'm not saying a small town isn't racist.
No, no, the entire...
No, I'm sorry. I'm sorry I even said that. The entire state is the south.
The entire state front to back is the south.
Asheville is literally like a woke college area. It's-
Why do you keep bringing up Asheville? Asheville has like, it's like 80,000 people in Asheville.
It's like the seventh biggest city in the- in the fucking state.
What are the big cities in North Carolina?
Charlotte.
Raleigh.
Woke.
Charlotte and Raleigh are not woke.
And what is a wolf this have any
Atlanta's woke
Yeah, Atlanta is lit. Atlanta is the South but well, Georgia is the South but Atlanta is
Not the South
You
Okay, you you are done. You are done. We're not talking about this anymore. We're moving on to sports, right?
This is not a something that you can even this is the I have never been more disgusted with you in my entire fucking life
This is like so disgusting to me that you would bar. Sorry wait, I'm back in barbecue
We have we have one of the big four regional barbecues and you're saying it's not southern. Wait, what is it?
What is one of the four regions? What are the four regions?
Kansas City
So it's Kansas City the self. Nope
Nope.
I think Rick's wins.
I'm starting with that.
Okay, well you don't win, it's the South.
Google it.
I'll Google it right now.
Google what the South?
I hate to do this.
Is North Carolina the South?
He's going to read a whole ass Wikipedia article now about this.
Wait, no, no, it's...
They were part of the Confederacy, but...
That's the South.
The Confederacy is the South.
a
They're saying this is the South, but it's not the real South.
You don't know anything!
They're talking out of your ass!
I'm just saying what I read in one form or post.
I didn't say it's the Deep South.
The Deep South is people start talking in a crazy way.
Yeah.
That's not... I have nothing to do with that.
And I'm glad. I've been to all those states and they're all really, really terrible places.
Someone said it's South-ish, not Southern.
You guys are so fucking stupid.
It's on the line man, I don't know what you want me to say.
It's very up in the back.
It's, it's, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, see, see, see, this is where you get it wrong.
It's not on the line.
It's below the line!
It might as well be the line.
That's fine, I'll take the line.
And you know, but, so, it is the line, because Virginia, not Southern.
I mean some people like- But Virginia is, I would consider Virginia
and North Carolina to be basically the same thing.
the
Rex and we're going North Carolina and South Carolina are effectively the one
big state so this is where you have a real problem and you can't say anything
because you've never been to either of them you have nothing to say about these
two places they are the same state the water they're different because we have
two different kinds of barbecue and by the way there's much worse and nobody's
nobody even knows about it nobody has any North Carolina barbecue is iconic
South Carolina barbecue, nobody gives a fuck about that.
- Is that your North Korea, South Korea argument?
To keep yourself separated, just the barbecue?
- Pretty much, there's a huge barbecue divide
because in the South Carolina, they do the same barbecue
but they add mustard to it.
- That is true, I do know that.
- So it's disgusting.
It really is like revolting, I can't even look at it.
The smell when you walk into a South Carolina barbecue place
of which there are very few because they are so disgusting.
There's more North Carolina barbecue in South Carolina
than there is South Carolina barbecue.
If you walk into one, immediately you're hit
with this disgusting wave of just,
oh God, keep that away from me, it's yellow.
- Right, okay.
I think I've heard enough.
I think I might have taken away.
- Okay, we can go differently.
We can go differently to a different topic.
Okay, wait, we did Jewish stuff, we did Southern stuff.
Julio, it's your turn, what do you have?
- Fuck, I don't know, I was,
Mexico has been crazy recently.
- What's going on with Mexico, man?
- I actually don't have a single idea
of what's going on in Mexico. - I think that you
are more informed about what's going on in America
than Mexico by a long mile.
- I think that's what people in America think
of anyone in the world.
- Well, it's true.
- It's not true because I don't know anything
that's happening in either country
because I have fully turned into a suburban white mom
who just hates talking to people
and I never leave the house
unless I'm going to the supermarket.
- That's, I'm sorry man.
- It's actually kind of cute.
- Yeah.
- It's actually really chill.
I'm eating food today.
And I'm thinking I'm about to become a chef.
- Yum. - How so?
- I think I'm about to just cook every single one of my meals
for the first time in my life.
- What have you been doing?
You've been ordering food?
No.
Thank God, this is one of the worst things you can do for your wallet.
Oh, I lost my wallet today and then had it returned.
I already talked about that on the premium episode.
Yeah, let's talk about that.
Oh, someone stole my debit card that I never take out of my room.
And they used it, I noticed, to charge for Turkcell,
which, take a guess, Turkish cell phone.
How did somebody steal your debit card?
I don't know, but I saw like an $8 charge for Turkcell
and then a three cent like withdraw from an ATM.
- Okay, so wait, wait, wait, wait.
- This is a confused thing that you have.
This is probably, if you go to any smoke shop or deli,
they always have a very different name
on your bank statement.
So you'll go to-- - No, Turkcell is real.
- Turkcell is real?
- Turkcell is real.
- And so did you get RFID scanned or something, you think?
- I love that 'cause I never use that card.
I haven't taken that card to a deli.
Mmmmm.
The 3 cent ATM is making me think that this is not possible.
So they did a 3 cent ATM withdrawal and then a 3 cent deposit.
It's insane.
That just can't be true.
Do you want me to share?
No, no, no. I mean it has to be some issue that is going on with your bank or something.
There's no ATM in the world can you take three cents out of.
I mean a Turkish lira is three cents.
Do you think if you call them and you go like, "Hey, there's like something crazy going on
with my account.
Yeah, nine bucks are like being crazy right now."
No, they flagged my account for fraud.
And a Turkish lira is literally three cents.
Oh, so you think that it might be in Turkey somebody is taking out one dollar.
Yeah, they were testing it to see if it was number one.
a
You use one of those? You use one of those wrist rests?
Oh god, holy oh no.
That is a disgusting thing to use. It's a Christmas
gift. Throw it away. Give it to somebody else.
That's like an old person, that's like a mouse with a ball.
Yeah. Wait, no, the ball mouses are fire.
I know you like the ball mouse. I do. Unfortunately, the ball cracked
during travel. You're kidding me.
I used a cue ball for a bit, but it just wasn't the right fit.
Wait, you can swap the ball out?
Of course.
Oh my.
It comes right out.
Whoa!
Can you play with it?
Yeah.
No, you probably can't.
You can?!
Of course.
Oh my god.
Have you fully given up on this ball mouse thing?
It was $100 and I broke the ball.
So yes, I gave up on it.
I did not feel like getting a new ball.
Just get a replacement ball.
How much is just the ball?
Like 30 bucks.
Can you just get like a golf ball?
By the way, I've seen you lose $600 in four minutes.
That is for fun, and it's different.
Okay, yeah.
Money that I have to take from my bank account
and give to a company is real.
Money that becomes a one or a zero on the screen
doesn't count.
Right. Okay.
It hurts to lose 50, if you lost,
I will say it does hurt way more to lose $50 in
like cash you if yeah that you like
Either you misplace the cash or you like send it to the wrong person on Zelle or something that stings way worse
Than losing three hundred dollars gambling. Yeah, and it's not even close really
It's completely different. I don't even know the amount that you have to lose gambling
I'm telling you I'm talking about this shit. They were showing us last night. Oh
Oh, the slot league?
Okay, yeah, we should talk about the slot league.
Guys, for those of you who like having fun, there is a guy on kick, an Australian guy,
who does a fantasy slots tournament that you can join the league and bet on which slots
are gonna win what amount of games or whatever.
next season I am having a team we're called we're called the monsters and we
are going to destroy we are going to destroy what's your line just so you
know my line here's my line yeah dude not to show you a while what no not what I
know no no no no no no no are you doing the trick the ones that and that pay
every once in a while. His name is Systems, Heather. You go for the slots that pay a little
bit almost half the time. So you go for a sweet bonanza. You go for a juicy fruit, or
not juicy fruit, you go for a fruit party. Yes, sweet bonanza did one. But that's not
so interesting to people who don't like gambling.
Yeah, you go for a Teo. You go for a-
You go for Teo. Teo would be an amazing choice. Teo would be an amazing choice. You go for
for
made any progress on building your slot machine, Rex?
No.
It's a side project that is getting... it will continue to be on the side.
I want to do it so bad, dude.
I think that... I think you have to do it.
Do you know anybody who's into, like, game dev stuff?
No.
That's really the problem.
I want to, like, contact No Limit City and, like, build out a system to turn their slots
into something else.
What does that mean?
Just like, without getting into technical,
like a way to turn their slots into a Ponzi scheme.
I think they would love that.
I like scamming stuff.
Yeah, I think that would be cool.
Money type of things.
Right.
Yeah.
Tech is so funny.
You know like CES is happening right now?
Yeah.
I was uh, I was watching like this big thing. I watch a WAN show man. Come don't ya know me
Did you see the rabbit the like a on a like saw that?
The pitch that the guy was doing is so funny and I'm gonna try really hard not to do an accent when I imitate
It was like, you know how everyone hates their phone because they're always tapping too much and there's too many apps on it
That was like the pitch for it
That problem cuz my phone screen is broken dude
But my phone screen broke and then I got a new screen on it and it works even worse than the broken one does
So now I hate tapping it's infuriating to me to tap. Well, that is a problem with your phone
That's not a problem with the design of the phone. I love looking at my phone. I don't know the difference
Okay, I just buy this shit. All right, I buy this shit. I put it on moist critical videos and then I just let it autoplay
Like
How can that possibly be your pitch, okay people hate their phone would you replace
With a fully AI little little gadget that you only hold one button and you talk to it and it does something
You know what I looked into for a while?
This phone that has a complete it has like the same screen as the Kindle the like paper screen
Yeah, because guys I'm I if you know one thing about me, I love candy
Okay, and I love flashing colors
and I was interested in getting a phone that did not have the candy and the flashing colors, but then I
Looked at it and it was $600. So I said no to this phone
Also, you would you would lose your favorite activity to want to do on the phone
Which is which is I I got to I got to notice this on first person
I saw this happening Caleb if he ever gets on a train that's longer than a couple minutes
He'll just sit on his phone. He put on the phone in his ear buds and I'll just watch slot videos for the entire time
That's true. I have a I have a I have a serious YouTube addiction
My youtube addiction has gotten out of control to the point where I think that I need to like maybe go to rehab for YouTube
That's no way
I do
Yeah, I already watched it man don't even worry about it it came out two hours ago and it's an hour long
How is that possible? I watched the premiere man
How I watch the premiere while I was at the dog park how many do you think you watch a day
in terms of hours or videos
Let's go videos and then let's actually let's do ours. Fuck it.
Ours? Yeah. Is there a way that I could see on my... there is right? I could pull up
the... You could probably just like look up like... Wait hold on. Yeah hold on one second.
I don't know where I look at my screen time bro. That's gonna be embarrassing.
I'll put... I'll do it. What do you what do you think it's gonna be on YouTube?
for a week or a day?
We'll go a day.
Yeah, sure.
Probably three hours a day.
On the phone? No. I don't watch YouTube on the phone much.
Rex, you are very close.
What is it?
Today, two hours and 36 minutes.
Yeah.
Of YouTube.
But, I'm also listening to YouTube things.
Right.
I would say that's 90, not 90, that's 70% of it.
percent of it is I'm listening to YouTube, because I'll put on something that is mostly
an audio type thing and just listen to it while I walk around.
But I'm trying to do that, I'm trying to get away from listening to other people talk and
get back into music, because music heals your soul in a crazy way.
I fuck everything with music, that's what I use YouTube most for, is music.
This is my top ten.
You have YouTube Premium?
Yeah, I do.
YouTube Premium is low. If you do anything that's not YouTube Premium plus the music, you're wasting your money.
You have YouTube Premium, you don't use the music?
Or you do use the music? You do, okay.
Because I know some people who have YouTube Premium, they don't use YouTube Music, they still use Spotify.
Because they think that it is embarrassing to use YouTube Music.
And guys, let me tell you, this is by far the best music streaming service there is.
It is the best.
the best.
Okay, well one thing is that you're kind of late behind on the times.
They split them up recently, like two months ago, maybe four months ago.
I got grandfathered into the package deal.
Yeah, but it's more expensive.
It's package board, it's more expensive.
I don't give a f- I don't even know.
I don't know.
I could not tell you how much YouTube cost.
They didn't grandfather you into anything.
It's just the same deal, but it's more expensive.
- You're talking like this is an ISP or some like--
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
- Oh, let's get a valid customer.
- You don't understand.
- You did not get grandfathered in.
The server's changed.
- You don't understand.
- You're getting charged more and you're like,
yeah, I'm special.
Yeah, I'm one of the special ones.
- They're letting me keep the same price.
Whatever that price was, again, I don't remember.
But they're letting me keep it.
I'm pretty sure it was upwards of $50.
- That is simply not true.
- It's true.
It's true.
Also, how many, like, now I think about people who don't have YouTube Premium, it's so sad
to me that they're watching these advertisements.
Because I'm at the point, I'm at the point where I have gotten, I never thought about
ads ever before I got YouTube Premium.
Now I'm at the point with ads where they infuriate me.
If I'm watching a Twitch stream and an ad comes up, I'm done with it.
I'm turning off Twitch.
I'm not watching.
you can get turbo.
You know what has the worst ads?
It's like Hulu.
Yes.
I remember it's actually infuriating.
One of the first stand up jokes I did when I was a kid was about opening up Hulu, because
I was real into tech.
Opening up Hulu and watching a thing and when it says, "Is this ad relevant to you?"
Clicking no on every ad in the hopes that one day they would get the idea that I just
don't like ads that much. That's why it was a kind of a stand-up comedy joke and
I was 16 years old. Right. That's how it should work yeah cuz some people are
sitting there like oh shit TurboTax oh what a lovely break between the thing I
I was enjoying.
- That's actually quite interesting.
Oh, H&R Block, oh, Pepsi, I like Pepsi.
These are called NPCs, guys, I learned this recently.
And NPCs like ads.
But me, I'm kind of a main character type,
so I don't care for these advertisements.
They're a waste of my time.
- Yeah, I think what got to me was not the ads
on like when I'm on YouTube on my computer.
On the phone and on the TV,
it is, they can get so annoying.
And also something I noticed recently with Twitch ads
is that they are also, there's no consistency
on like the volume of the ads.
So I'll be watching like a Twitch stream
that's like, he doesn't really get that loud, the streamer.
And then I'll just like run an ad
and it's just like blasting loud music
and just showing me gum.
I'm like, yo, this is, this should be banned.
My third platform, I'm banning loud ads.
Only quiet ads from now on.
- Something has changed with these advertisements, man.
Because I have recently gone and watched
one of these YouTube compilations.
Big surprise, I'm watching a YouTube video.
But the YouTube compilations that are,
it's like all the ads from your childhood.
And something about these, I was like,
I remember every single one of these.
I remember not hating them when they were on.
And they are so different now.
I hate these ads.
I would never remember these.
No kid in 20 years is gonna be like,
oh shit, that progressive commercial really,
I'd like to see that again.
That is nostalgic to me.
- You know what I think-- - What changed?
- I'm gonna think back on,
what's his name for the insurance company?
The one, the guy on the red shirt?
- Nobody-- - That's gonna--
- Jake from State Farm, you're not gonna notice that.
- Damn, remember Jake?
The head no way died in that accident
He will not you will never die. No, he's gonna explode. They will replace it. They replaced him once they're gonna replace him again
I don't think so. Yeah, there's a white replacement. Jake is a
forever type of
Immortal type of thing. Yeah, but then I get nolly llama favorite Jake's
Well, that's true. That's like like a Steve from Blue's Clues thing. People will grow up with different Jake's something about that
That is beautiful to me.
What?
Blue's Clues?
Well, Blue's Clues is of course beautiful to me, but also growing up with a different Jake
from State Farm.
I grew up with the original one, and then I saw these kids growing up with the new Jake,
and I said, "You know what, man?
Knock yourself out, kids.
That's an amazing, amazing privilege to live in the same time as a Jake."
Yeah.
That is true.
We live in a beautiful time.
There's no doubt about it. We live in one of the most beautiful eras ever.
It's 90 degrees in January. This is a perfect time to be alive.
Yeah.
I really don't like June.
And the future will probably only be better.
What do you think is the year... what year is it that like, you have the perfect balance
of like, global warming is not so much destroying the earth so badly, but then also you get maybe
a cool video game. Because obviously the best one, like the coolest video games are going
to come out in 20 years, but things are going to be underwater. So there's some kind of,
there's some equilibrium to be found there. Some GameCube game maybe? I'm not a global
warming expert guy, but like 50 years from now, things will not be underwater in 20 years.
in
Yeah, that is true.
I think that's more it's sinking.
You know what I want to see from the future is getting to like the years 50, 60, 70 and having Madden 73.
Madden 73, nobody knows what, people think Madden means football.
Right.
Yeah.
That's what I want to see.
We're going to go to the Madden game.
That will be an amazing thing.
They're doing a live Madden game down at the theater.
the
of
on like ESPN2, like ESPN3.
- See, that's, but people never,
I guess nobody thought of the fact that there,
it's like the NFL,
if there was 50 different kinds of football
that everybody liked.
- Right.
And you couldn't, it was completely inscrutable
if you liked one kind of football.
- Yeah, and it's only for people who are under 30.
- Yeah.
- Like, of course you're not gonna make any money on it.
- Except for us. - Esports is so funny.
- We will make some money with Esports very soon.
- Yeah.
okay i have to go i have to leave right now
really you disappear
i'd like to just hear it so it's it's and i'm having fun and i'd like to say but
i do have to go
that's when i'm gonna finish my lamplighter brewing company rather rabbit
guys
and now that i had the whole thing i would not recommend drinking this
this really slowed me down and now i have to go do something
so this is a bad decision do not drink a double i_p_a_
which i never understood what that means sorry
c again i like you podcast about
it's just natural for you it's in your blood
that's true as fuck man
do you think i ever
stop asking me a major question
i have to leave man
okay as the host of the show i'm i'm saying goodbye to our guests
uh... kelo pit
the bible leo the by rex are to yesterday
Thank you so much for coming.
This has been beers we drank and I'm leaving the call to put an end on this.
Julio you better not talk when I leave.
Bye.
He sucks dude.
He's so bald.
He is so bald.
I was just thinking about how bald he is lately.
I think this combo, I don't know why we followed his lead.
I think it killed me.
I spent stretches.
I spent stretches of the show just thinking too much about what I was doing.
And it really took me out of the experience.
I drank this today as well. I'm just gonna show this.
A Gyat?
-Gyatweed? -It's called Gymweed.
Okay.
And it's an energy drink that has ashwagandha in it.
And it was fire.
Didn't they start banning that shit because it gave people cancer in the balls?
Wait.
Are you sure?
I don't know, I have no idea.
I don't think that's true.
I think they did something to it.
I'm pretty sure that's false.
I'm pretty sure that's real.
As the host of the show, we're saying goodbye.
Thank you for watching Bish We Drink.
Caleb is not the host, and I'm the host.
Goodbye.
I'll say bye now.