[Sipping]
[Burp]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer broadcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[Burp]
This is a journey into sea,
into intergalactic,
planet,
- I'm a fool, rip it!
- Beers we drank, motherfucker,
with Juvio, Caleb, and Rex.
(record scratching)
- We're back.
- We're back with Caleb.
- Oh!
Oh no, fuck me, man.
- What just happened?
- Ah!
- 10 seconds in and you already made a damn mess.
- Not even 10, in the first second,
I opened my beer and it had such a splashing effect
because it's so well carbonated.
shout out to the good people at Athletic Brewing Company,
that it popped open the water or the beer
onto my keyboard.
- Really?
- No, I'm lying.
Yes, really, yeah, yeah.
I have beer all over my keyboard.
- All right, 'cause--
- And I have enough problems with my keyboard as is,
by the way, so.
- You need a new keyboard.
- This is forcing you to get a new keyboard, it's good.
- You need a new one. - I do need a new keyboard.
I need one bad. - It's literally a good thing.
- My keyboard, anytime I type with eyes,
it takes me about five minutes to log into my computer
in the morning because it just double types keys
like every single time.
So when I try to put in my password, it's all fucked up.
- If you have like isopropyl alcohol and some Q-tips,
you can take your key caps off and get in there with it.
- I ain't never doing that.
I will buy a new keyboard.
- So just buy a new keyboard.
Well don't stop being a pussy.
- But I don't have extra money for it.
- Oh my, it's like $20 for a keyboard.
- I'm not buying a 20, I will buy a three or $400 keyboard.
Not a $20 keyboard.
- All right.
a $300 keyboard. Well you're looking in the wrong place. Your camera's actually a
little lower. Yep. Pretty embarrassing. Actually it's looking much much cleaner
in your room. I think that's because the angle is aimed so that most of the frame is the
ceiling. Yes. Wait, am I right? Can you see around it now? Can you see? Whoa dude, mid move. I can see that basket. Yeah. Is the
Excitement is setting in, huh?
Yeah, I just, uh...
I had to give a, like, virtual walkthrough to some guy earlier
-to tell me how much it was... -Of your furriflies?
Yeah, so he could tell me how much it was gonna cost to move.
And, uh, it was, like, so nasty that I was just like,
"I'm sorry! I'm sorry!" and just, like, bleeding, bleeding shit.
Alright, tell us how much it was.
Depends on... It's on the line.
So I'm using one of those containers. So if I use one container, it's 4500 if I use two containers
It's gonna be like 6200 god. It's so expensive to move across country. Yeah at what point is it cheaper to just buy all new stuff? I
Think if it was like I got one quote for
Like an entire like moving truck and it was like 13,000. Oh
You know, yeah, that's this is like the budget one
Yeah, I did have that thought which is like I could get rid of my mattress. I could pack up my hard drives and send them
my new computer
But I think it's just worth it. Did you sell your car? Not yet? You're going to yeah
I'm planning on it
Planning on in the next six days. Yes
We talked about this last week and he's going to one of those kind of scam so my cars you're gonna smell somebody yeah
Six days is a scam usually take a little more preparation than that I think that maybe you might end up being scammed.
I just need to get rid of it like a bunch of paperwork to sell a car.
I mean I'll just take a day.
Okay.
I don't want to know what are you drinking I am drinking the beast unleashed 6%
Wait, most of those years they do a hard monster white maze white hay
Okay, give us a give us a out of ten and then also give us a basketball player height
Someone it tastes like someone took like a white monster and then you know, they're really shitty vodka
You buy when you're in college
It's like $10 for a handle or or maybe like 99 bananas like the unflavored 99 cent vodka
Yeah, that's what it tastes like. It tastes like someone took a white monster,
poured a little bit out, put that shitty vodka in there, and didn't mix it. So you
just get the taste of the vodka first and then a little bit of the flavor. Yeah, it's horrible.
I would say a very solid 3 out of 10. Okay, and now a height? 5 foot 7. Oh, okay,
- Isaiah Thomas.
- Yeah.
- All right.
Jubio, what do you got?
- I got actually quite a colorful beard today.
- You look so happy today.
Can I just say this?
You look pregnant.
You look like glowing.
- He's glowing, yeah.
- Well, he's happy you're back.
- You got really good news or sex today?
- Nope.
- You had sex, didn't you?
- No.
- You had fucking sex.
- No, you know what I did today?
I went out to eat wings today
at this really shit place
where they put gummies in your drink.
And the whole vibe is so insane.
- I don't know what's shitty about what you just said.
- No, I'm with you.
Why do they do, what is up with this?
I've seen so many videos the past couple weeks
of people being like, here's a McDonald's hack.
And they get a Sprite from McDonald's
and they put four packs of Starburst in it
and a pack of Fun Dip.
- Basically that is like a drink
that they would sell at this place.
And the vibes were completely awful.
- I blame Mexico for that.
Yeah, the vibes were completely awful.
And then as we're like paying and like leaving,
they have like this, like, you know, like the Mexican candles.
So they come in like this, like glass, like huge.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The Catholic ones.
Yeah.
They have like custom, like funny ones on each table.
And when I when I got up, I bumped the table and I dropped it and it broke.
And I just like we had just paid as well.
So I just like I was like, oh, yo, check it out.
That this broke and we just stepped.
I didn't even care.
I like it. It's so awesome that at restaurants
you can break glasses and shit and they just what are they going to?
They're not going to.
Yeah, they thank you.
They're like, oh, thank you.
Well, you gave me some work.
Yeah.
Anyways, I'm not happy about that.
I'm happy about my colorful beer,
which I guess is named Playa Car.
It's got like some sort of monkey on top of it.
It's like a monkey beer of some sort.
Playa means beach, right?
Yeah. So and car means room, room vehicle.
Car, yeah.
Yeah. So this is not a really great name for a beer.
Yeah.
It's not a great beer, honestly.
Number?
Give us a number.
I'm going to go four.
Now a height?
I don't know. I don't know basketball players.
I don't know a single one.
You know, you also just a height and you can do you can do metric if you need to.
Sure. We'll do.
I don't know. One seventy five.
175 meters.
That's quite tall. It's a giant.
Well, guys, the day has come.
The reckoning has arrived.
I was out of town visiting my family
on a trip where basically the entire thing is me
and my cousins and my uncles and aunts get just like
fucked up beyond belief for like a week and a half.
But I decided that coming back from this,
on the back end of this trip, I decided I'm going to do a month with no drinking alcohol.
So I have today...
Grogless August.
I'm doing Grogless Augless.
Grogless Augless is a really good... Yeah, I'm doing Grogless Augless.
And I'm not sure what Augless is, Jubio, but sure.
This is the Athletic Brewing Company Upside Dawn Golden Ale.
And I've already had one of these today because it doesn't matter.
I mean it's a fucking, it's water.
So I'm gonna take a sip.
Is it just like hop water or something?
No, it's a brewed beer and they take the alcohol out.
Interesting.
Honestly, man, this is pretty good.
This would be, if this had alcohol in it, I would say that this is like a 7, or maybe
6.8 out of 10. And in terms of height, I'm going to go like 6'3", like Derrick Rose.
That's what I'm going to say for this. It's pretty good. The problem with these is they
still have calories in them, like a beer. This thing's like 90 calories, but I'll drink
10 of them tonight.
Right. It's like sparkling water.
Yeah, so I might as well just be doing sparkling water, but for the purposes of this podcast
I did get a beer and I will be finding this is for all of our sober gophers that listen to the beer podcast
I know there are many many many of you
This month is for you guys
This one goes out to all the groggless oglesses who can't drink beer because they used to have a serious fucking problem
Threw their lives killed somebody touched a woman any of that kind of stuff
You couldn't pay me, but this is just the beginning
of what I think is gonna be an amazing month.
We're happy for you, man.
We're here for you.
Thank you.
I almost, let's see, I started yesterday, the 1st.
Started at midnight,
didn't have anything after midnight,
and I made it, I almost gave up at about 4.30 p.m. yesterday
but I powered through and now I've made it to day two.
'Cause it's fucking, I love beer.
Yeah.
'Cause I was doing, the thing is, okay,
here's the problem with beer.
It's so amazing that yesterday I was doing nothing.
I didn't do anything yesterday.
I was at home alone most of the day.
And when you're doing nothing at home,
you're like, fuck man, I want a beer, right?
But then also if you go out and do something,
if you go to some kind of show
or somebody's house or some shit,
we go watch a game, you're like, "Goddamn, I want a beer."
So if you do nothing, you want beer,
and if you do something, you want beer.
And those are both your excuses for wanting beer.
- I think this is something very uniquely to you.
- Wanting a beer?
- Just doing nothing and just wanting beer?
I don't--
- I don't think that's uniquely.
- No, dude, that's like the number one thing to do.
- I don't ever just sit home and just hanging out by myself
and I go, "I want a beer."
- But we've established that you are some kind
of cyborg freak that doesn't like fun, you know?
Me, I'm one of the most fun-loving people
in the world, maybe.
- You hate fun.
- I love fun.
- You love staying inside.
- That's fun sometimes.
- Yeah, okay.
Rex, I think you're more like me in this scenario, right?
You're just saying--
- Yeah, I don't need to drink a beer,
But I understand fully what Caleb is saying.
It's nice, man.
Yeah, sometimes you just want to drink a beer.
Oh, there's nothing.
Sometimes you're so at a restaurant
and you're having a beautiful meal and you're thinking, wow, you know,
it would perfectly round out this delicious, wonderful time.
I'm having going home drinking a beer.
Oh, yeah.
No, a beer there and then going home and drinking more beer.
Yes.
Because that's the other.
Here's the other thing about beers, man.
You can't just have just one, right?
Cause you have one and you're like, you have to drink.
If you're going to drink,
you have to drink and drink and drink until you get so drunk that you fall asleep.
That's the only way to do it. You know, I, I have never had a beer at six o'clock.
That's why I hate day drinking because I know that I have to drink probably 20 to
25 drinks from like, I've never gotten a,
a a bloody Marriott brunch, you know, because that's the end of my day then.
I'm just going to be so fucked up the rest of the day.
I think Groggly's August is going to do huge things for you.
I think you're going to be a new person.
You're going to feel amazing after Groggly's August.
I do this probably twice a year for like one month,
and I always feel so amazing at the end of the month.
And then I immediately I'm like, yeah, but I mean, I'm going to drink again.
It's way too good. Yeah.
Oh, I don't like being the bummer.
I know so many sober people man and they like to think that they're high on life and having so much fun but they're not these are broken people the sober people are the true broken people of our world.
You just dedicated this cargo store the silver sandy's the world shit julio i feel bad for them.
Yeah, I'd like to dedicate this to single mothers too while we're at it.
People who have really hard lives.
Okay, it is it is hard as fuck to be sober.
It's not worth it.
I think it's easy and I think and you can have fun by not drinking.
You can't have fun without drinking man.
Yeah, that is sober isn't fun.
Being sober is not fun.
And if you don't drink, you got to do drugs.
Yeah, you have to do drugs.
California sober. If you do not drink and do not do drugs,
something is actually fucking wrong with you.
Or you have some kind of,
um, maybe some kind of like disability,
mental disability, you don't even know what beer and drugs are.
Those are like kind of the only
I don't think that's... acceptable. I'm basically sober.
I just drink like two times a week,
and I vape constantly, and I'm addicted to energy drinks.
Yeah. Oh, another thing is,
Every fucking sober straight edge guy I know drinks about 800 milligrams of caffeine a day
Yeah, and they are so in denial about it, but I've never I don't drugs
caffeine is so fucked I
Did like two days last week of not drinking coffee and I my day was over like 2 p.m. I was so sleepy
Withdrawals, it's so fucked and they last for weeks by the way if you've ever quit caffeine for like a long time
You have like two full weeks of feeling so shit you have to take a two-hour nap in the middle of the day
It's an impossible life to live
I have to take a nap the moment the monster wears off for the day. Yeah, exactly
Last night I drank two monsters, and I just had a pain in my chest and arm kind of went down my arm
And I was like oh, that's probably normal
Everyone I get pains in my arm all the fucking time
Yeah, also, I wish that nobody ever I wish I didn't know I was talking to somebody about this. I wish I had no
Idea with the symptoms of a heart attack stroke or cuz there's not nothing I can fucking do
Right if I'm gonna have a heart attack, then I I'm gonna feel it
I don't need to sit there thinking I'm having one two or three times a day
So I think you can just ignore them
This is what I just norma right here. Perfect. What's that? Tiger bomb?
You just rub that shit wherever you start feeling heart attack type pain and it
Numbs it so it just goes away in ten minutes. What are you talking you use a numbing cream to?
Sedate yourself through heart attack symptoms
You numb your body
Yeah, I just like, you know, just shooting pains through your.
Oh yeah.
And then I'll just take it and I'll just rub it like this.
I almost want a demonstration, but I don't know there's any way for you to show
this this thing's effects.
It's like, oh, it hurts.
And then I'll just dip my fingers in.
It's so painful that you're grabbing and saying, ah, it hurts.
Yeah.
And I just rub like on here.
He's on the floor saying, I heard.
It's not I'm on the floor.
I'm like, give me my tiger bomb.
It's on my desk at all times.
What is it? It's a numbing cream.
Yeah, it's like a muscle relaxer.
Does it work on your thing?
For your nuts?
I haven't tried it.
It probably is.
I would love to make it feel like I had no nuts or thing for one day.
Just to see what it was like.
Just kind of rub it in, like just around it.
So just isolated it.
That would be amazing if I get to if if I had the option to go one day
without a dick and balls.
Not even, I don't even have to have a vagina.
Just one day without any genitals.
- Just a nub.
- Just to see what it's like.
Not even a nub, just like a full kin,
like kinda, you know.
- Would numbing it-- - How would you pee?
- Yeah, would numbing it--
- I would need to pee.
- Suppress the feel of, that you need to pee, do you think?
- Maybe.
- Everyone needs to, even if you get your dick
like blown off or whatever, like you have no genitals
whatsoever, you still have like a little straw
like a catheter or whatever.
Yeah, but you don't know that.
Well, I saw it in a movie in 2008.
What movie were you watching that had a P2?
I don't remember.
This was not a movie.
No, it's a movie.
It's one of those like movies.
You think videos are movies?
No, no, no.
It's a movie that came out in like 2008.
It was a comedy movie.
It's security camera footage and it's black and white.
And he's like, oh, it's a classic.
You know, like, like Sex Drive or like whatever those shitties,
Forgetting Sir Marshall, one of those types of movies.
And the big reveal was that I think it was
it was one of the I think it was like one of the fat black dudes
that was always in those movies.
I forget what his name is.
Anthony Anderson. Could be.
And he pulls his pants down at the end and he's just got a nub with a tube in it.
And then I had to look it up to see if that's really what would happen.
And I don't know what movie it is.
I know for sure it happened.
It's real.
And if you don't have a dick, you still have to either.
Of course, you still have to pee.
There's the pee has to go somewhere.
Yeah, we have the gift of science.
I think for the sake of science, you should know your thing
and see if you pee yourself in the next science right now.
Yes, it's let me translate.
Sometimes he said science, not science.
I heard science, too, and it took me.
But I'm smart enough to use context clues.
Yeah, anyways, you got another thing
and you got to see if you pay yourself.
Here's a funny one.
Elkay 99 made in Korea.
What's that L and K stand for?
Elkay last names of the scientists from Korea
who made it Elkay 90, I don't know what Elkay 99 is.
Yeah, I don't know what you're talking about.
Yeah, just think of think of two last names from Korea.
Little.
Uh-huh.
And Chris?
Yeah.
You're 100% right.
What is LK99?
You don't follow science at all.
Just tell me, is this an element?
What is this?
It's a metal, but it's not the point.
I just thought it was funny.
Well, it needed some kind of, you were just saying, I thought maybe this was a band?
No, okay.
That would have made sense that they have.
It's like a big thing.
It's like the superconduction.
It's all over Twitter right now.
He's on r/science.
Rex is looking up some nerd shit on Twitter everyday.
But I just think it's funny that they're like,
"Dude, this is all over Twitter."
The two best scientists in Korea,
their last names are Lee and Kim.
Ten minutes before recording.
Twitter search bar "science".
See what comes up.
Alright, you guys are
so not smart, so cool,
because you don't know anything.
Yeah, we are cool.
We are cool 'cause we don't know anything.
Yup, uh-huh.
And you're lame because you know stuff, yeah.
Yeah. This is how the world works.
I'm not fucking gay, I look, I know.
Whoa! Bullshit.
We did not say G-A-Y.
You brought the gay thing into it,
but now that you say it,
yeah, you could be gay for that, I don't know.
(laughs)
I don't know what gay, I mean, you know,
you know what I was thinking?
They should change, instead of, you know,
you say you're queer, I'm LGBT, I'm this, I'm that, right?
They should just change it to just weird.
- Well, that's what queer means.
- Yeah, I feel like that's what queer is supposed to mean.
- Yeah, but I grew up in the early 1990s, late '80s,
or 1980s, where that meant a whole different thing.
I wanted to just be like, oh, excuse me,
I'm actually weird, like that kind of thing.
- You know, gay means happy.
What kind of scenario?
What?
What kind of scenario are you going, "Oh, excuse me, I'm weird"?
Excuse me, are you sexually weird?
Yeah.
Like this is a place for weird guys to hang out.
Is this a weird friendly bar?
You know, like I like that more because also it's a little more inclusive.
It might even include...
How about friendly?
I think that's a great word for gay people.
Friendly is an amazing...
Yeah.
I don't feel...
You know, friendly.
Friendly. Yes, this is good.
Yeah. Weird is a little bit.
You're right. Weird is already is still got a little bit of a negative connotation.
Friendly. Ain't nothing wrong with some some guy who's so friendly that'll,
you know, tug on your puberty.
Too happy. We just use chipper.
Chipper does sound like you're calling somebody
like then people would say, like, oh, he's a chipper, you know?
You don't want to say that.
Yeah, those damn chips.
Yeah, I don't want that to be. Yeah.
What are you controlling there, Juvia?
I think half of my power just went out.
Well, it was the correct half then.
Yeah. You're still with us.
I'm still here, thankfully.
But not to get really hot in here.
That's OK. For me, it's fine.
Yeah. You're wearing a hoodie in August, man.
Because I feel sick and I have a kind of a girlish urge
to wear hoodies when I feel bad.
Right, hang on. We're gonna...
I do like to sweat out illness.
We're gonna step all the way back.
Caleb is finally back from his two-month hiatus.
Yeah.
He's been off Twitter, off online, off everything.
And he's finally back and he...
You became a complete musician and you look like one now.
Yeah.
I did become a musician.
He's an MC.
We're already over this on the other podcasts that I do.
We don't have to bring up...
I don't listen to that bullshit.
- Bullshit.
- Talented on every fucking thing.
Oh my God, you're so talented.
Why don't you talk about it on this show?
Didn't talk about it on this show.
Dude, leave me the fuck alone.
I need some time to come up with music.
- All right. - I did go golfing.
- What are you doing with your last three days alive?
- What?
- That is some epic shit.
- I forgot about that.
- I literally, I regret every single thing I have ever,
literally my life is so bad, man.
My life is so fucking bad.
the
I thought that's the thing.
That's the bullet is.
Yeah, the bullet gets into his apartment from outside from outside.
And you have to leave the apartment.
You have to go on.
All day.
I remember posting that tweet and literally thinking like, I'll be dead by then.
Even if there's no, you know, I was like, oh, this would be funny.
But oh, wait, 2023, I'll be dead.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's so soon after you posted the tweet.
When did you make that?
like two years ago to 2020 I think three years ago.
Yeah.
It feels like every time you post something a month after,
you're like, I completely hate that.
Well, yeah, that's what it means to be good at using Twitter.
I mean, that's what I think any that's what it is with anything I do.
By the way, I love it.
I love that it's called X.
I'm fully on board with X.
This is cool.
Yes.
Do Twitter is such a stupid name and tweeting.
I'm every every name. I feel like anytime a new
App comes out that gets really popular. I'm like amazed at how bad the name is
You know like I like tick red has like the worst name and branding
but it's the biggest thing and I I feel like
But I it's just come not used to them. I guess like I was thinking about YouTube yesterday
I was like that is such a terrible name for a website. Yeah
YouTube.
Well, it was because it was, it used to be like a, like an old like tube TV, right?
The app icon.
It's all about that.
You were in the TV.
You think they came up with the icon before the name?
I think they did.
No, I don't think that.
You think they saw the, someone made them an icon and they created an entire app and
website around it?
No, I'm just saying that's what we really do.
It's a TV.
You're in TV.
It's your TV.
- If we did this podcast in 2008,
do you think we would be on the front page of YouTube?
- Yeah.
Well, first of all, we would have invented podcasts,
so we would have gotten a Nobel Prize.
- Do you think we could have,
do you think that us three could have,
in an alternate, do you think there is an alternate reality
where us three are maybe a decade older
and we become the Vlogbrothers?
- Ah, yes, I do think so.
I think that is really dangerously close to happening.
I think with Rex--
Us three becoming vlog brothers?
Yeah, I think with Rex coming up there,
you guys are gonna start getting an actual crew together
and you will become-- And then what, vlogging?
Semi-vlog, yeah, you're gonna start vlogging as well.
We need to get-- What would I vlog?
What is there even to vlog anymore?
Yeah, nobody does anything anymore.
People love it when you vlog doing nothing.
It's not like Casey Neistat
is flying drones for Manhattan.
- Is that what he's saying?
- I don't know, he's too ugly for me to watch.
He always has, when he was getting big and giant.
Casey Neistat, are you kidding me, man?
He makes all, he's just like a guy
who makes videos about him biking around.
- South African guy who--
- He's not South African.
- He's South African and he served in the IDF.
- This is not true.
He's just a very, very ugly guy.
- No, that would make sense,
South African serving in the IDF?
- That's what he did.
- Really?
- He did, yeah.
- I didn't know he's South African.
He has a completely American accent.
- He has lived here for a while.
- Cool American, Americans are so cool, man.
But he looks like a tiki mask.
He looks so fucked up.
His cheeks are in the wrong position always.
- That's why he's always wearing sunglasses.
- Do you guys remember,
did you guys ever have a Ripley's Believe It or Not book?
Growing up?
Uh-huh.
Do you remember the guy who could put his bottom lip
over his nose?
Yep. I do remember that, yeah.
He looks like that guy.
But his lip is underneath his lip.
Mm.
So it's like, what's your deal, bro?
What kind of world record are you breaking?
Wait, what are you talking about?
His lip is under his lip.
World's most famous ugly guy.
I had a, that guy, that guy actually used to really scare me
when I was a kid, the guy who could put his lip,
I remember that was probably the first time I was ever like actually terrified as a child,
like really, really terrified.
And then I told my mom that and she said, don't worry, he's not real.
And then my older brother told me he was like, like whispered in my ear.
He was like, he's real.
And it made me so fucking scared.
I was so scared of the lip over the nose guy.
Well, isn't the point of Ripley's Believe It or Not is that you're supposed to believe
it.
Did you think it was going to get you?
you? Or you was going to break into your house and get you?
Honestly, I think now, because I've seen it now in color and it's really not
that scary, but in the book it was in black and white.
Right.
And that made it way scarier.
First thing that ever frightened me, Courage the Cowardly Dog.
Oh my God.
This guy.
Yeah.
Whatever his name is.
Fred.
Yeah.
Yep.
Wait, what guy?
Did he?
It's just a smiling guy.
Yeah.
That guy.
I don't know what really you know what really scary knows what's good the movie signs.
It's really shitty science.
Science okay yes i know yeah when he walks in the alien walks in the background of the birthday party yeah that was a scary fucking movie.
Yeah that's a scary movie to watch when you're like 10 years old.
Yeah, I remember I was so scared of even the idea of this one movie called Darkness Falls.
You ever heard of this movie?
No.
It's a movie about an evil tooth fairy.
And I was so scared of the cover that my brother brought it home from Blockbuster.
And I was so scared of the cover being like out on the living room table that I hid the DVD somewhere so that like nobody could find it and use it.
And my brother ended up having to probably pay $25 for that DVD because I hit it.
Did you ever see that movie? It's like, it's called like Cabin in the Woods or something.
And it's like, it's like a worm. It's like a bloody movie.
Do you know what I'm talking about? Cabin in the Woods is a, is a Joss Whedon movie, I think.
Okay, well, we're talking about in like 2012. No, this would have been before that.
So you're talking about a movie where there's a calvin in the woods.
There's like a maybe it's a snake some sort of eel like creature with teeth.
Anaconda.
Not anaconda.
Tremors.
I honestly have, I don't know anything.
I, I, movies elude me.
Movies is to us what science is to you.
We love movies and we look up movie facts all day every day.
We love that shit.
Movie check right now movie check movie corner. What's the last movie you watched? I watched talk to me
Are you again already talked about it on the other podcast, but it was a great movie
I recommend anybody go see this in the a 24 style a
24 movie in theaters. It's about a scary Australian
Demon-esque kind of life that some people live Rex
That like movie with Jennifer Lawrence that came out recently you saw
Don't come for me or whatever. It's called. What's it called?
No, it's called fuck it's called like it's called like I'm miss Lawrence I missed the G
It's like a double entendre. I guess that wouldn't be a double entendre, but it's called something
Don't come in me don't come it's I think it might actually be called don't come
No, no, it's literally called like get hard on me or I'm gonna make you hard
I looked it up, but it's only in Spanish in my on my Google. What's it called? It's called as a male forward in Spanish
Come for me, please
Sorry, yeah, do whatever
It no, it's guys we have to get this no hard feelings. That's what it is
No hard feelings. That's and do you understand the joke that they're making?
I didn't. Not really.
Like, this little kid
that she's trying to fuck
he does not have any
hard feelings for this
human. He numbed his thing
He numbed his thing with Tiger Balm.
He comes in the movie. There's no
hard feelings. What? But not until
the second part of the movie.
Wait, you also watch this?
Or are you making this up?
I think you're making this up.
Did she suck him
him off? No, no, he tries to fuck her and he just fucks her leg and then like nuts on her.
Yo! That's a beast. Does she fall in love with him? Yeah. Really? That is so sweet. Is this
just like a remake of that one movie where they make a girl like fall in love with like
some like fail song guy? Basically, yeah. Oh, okay. Remember that movie? Failure to Lunch?
- Oh, failure to lunch?
- To lunch.
- Failure to lunch. - Failure to lunch.
- Is that McConaughey?
- No, it's Hugh Grant.
- Oh, dude, who's gonna fuck Hugh Grant?
- That's not Hugh Grant.
- I think that is McConaughey. - That's crazy.
It's McConaughey.
- How is McConaughey a failure to lunch?
- He's just in with the parents.
- He's, go be a movie star.
That's why that movie Pursuit of Happiness sucks so much ass.
- Yeah, you're Will Smith.
You're a millionaire.
- Rap, dance, act, do it all.
You're, oh, oh, I'm so poor
because I'm such a triple threat.
- Dude, Men in Black-- - Suck my dick.
- It's so good still.
It's so, so, so good. - Men in Black is fucking good.
- It's so funny. - Men in Black is good.
- Wild Wild West.
- Wild, I was just about to say, Wild Wild West is good
because, okay, Whitey doesn't know what boobs feel like.
You know that scene?
Whitey doesn't know what boobs feel like, but holy crap,
as Will Smith felt lots of lots of breasts
in this Wild Wild West.
- I haven't seen the movie in a long ass time.
I think I'm gonna watch it again.
- It's amazing, there's a spider at the end.
- Yeah, I do remember the spider.
The last movie I watched was Barbie.
- I saw Barbie as well. - I went to the theaters
and I saw Barbie, what do you think?
- Thought it was fun, man.
I thought it was fun.
- I refuse to see it because it's against the patriarchy.
- It is definitely against the patriarchy.
But there was a scene where the mom--
- Half of the movie is pro-patriarchy actually.
You just gotta pay attention to half of the movie
and then start suing everything out.
- I guess you're right, it depends on how you take
all the canned parts. - Yeah, it's your POV.
- But for most guys it'll be like,
well, this is sick as fuck. - I'm doing a meninist critique.
- It is a little bit like they leave the men behind
at the end, which is sadly very true
to what's happening these days in American country.
But I, fuck, what was my point about this movie?
Oh, I didn't have a point, but the part where the mom
is kind of monologuing about how hard it is to be a woman,
I honestly was like, that sounds fucking hard.
That sounds really hard.
I had never really thought about it.
And they have to be women on top of it.
It's really hard.
Yeah, I mean, okay, so you have to be a mom.
But she says like, you have to make them happy,
but you also have to not be like a whore.
You have to be like career driven,
but not be like too much like a man, you know?
And so you have to do all this stuff.
You gotta be soft, but you gotta be hard as well.
Yeah, meanwhile--
Meanwhile, you're a fucking pussy.
Yeah, but also-- It bleeds.
You're doing all, yeah, so you have this horrible affliction,
you have your period and all this shit.
You have to do all this shit, this and that and that.
It's all so hard.
And then on top of that, you're stupid.
- Yeah. - True.
- So it's like, you can't win, you know?
Like that stuff would be hard for a man.
How hard is it for a woman?
- How do you feel about the ending?
The last little montage they did.
I don't remember any movie that I've seen.
If it didn't scare me, I don't remember it.
- Okay, nevermind then.
- Oh, that was my only point about "Talk to Me".
Too much blood.
I don't need to see blood.
I would like for there to be bloodless options
for gory movies. - I think you shouldn't watch,
I think they should ban watching horror movies
during summer.
I think summer is no horror movie.
- It's too hot.
- There's no place for it.
- But that's like when you're like,
Oh, it's a summer night and I have a cute girl that I'm--
- Yeah, we're gonna go watch Oppenheimer
and watch a guy drop a bomb.
- I almost don't even wanna see Oppenheimer
'cause I know I'll become so obsessed with it
and pattern my life around it.
My dog just walked in, it's not allowed.
That's what scares me about watching that movie.
- That movie is too long to watch in a movie theater.
- I also thought that.
I think two hours is my maximum.
- Yeah.
I'm pulling my phone out, I'm watching TikToks, I'm pausing the movie 11 times.
You think Oppenheimer is complete shit?
No, I think the movie theater experience is complete shit.
I did have some pretty god awful nachos over watching Barbie in Atascadero.
The seat fucking is so uncomfortable and I was sitting next to a guy that was just,
he was just like, the movie hadn't even started and he was just like
all what he have through his popcorn, he was making so much noise.
noise that's what I do I have my snacks
but I'm not sure previews are over right
I'm getting a 92 ounce diet coke I'm
getting the largest popcorn yeah okay
okay Julio when was the last time that
it took you two hours to eat 20 skittles
I don't I don't it's only in a movie
I don't get skittles what the fuck what
do you get in that it takes all my
hours to eat it yeah it's getting 11
mangoes covered in tahini yeah don't
Tell me that you cut one of these people who sits there and you eat one
you eat one fucking crunch cluster every 10 minutes and you like time it out
so that you'd have one at the end of the movie.
No, I don't do that.
Just eat the fucking food!
I don't do that.
It's meant to give you just enough energy to get through the movie without needing dinner.
Yeah, I'll eat an 18 ounce steak in 10 minutes.
I'm not gonna fucking save my...
A nerd's rope I'm gonna go through way faster than that, man.
Yeah, I went to when I when I saw the Jennifer Lawrence,
no hard feelings.
I stood in line for 30 minutes.
OK, I got the largest like the tub of popcorn.
Yeah, I got the 60 ounce Diet Coke.
And I got into that movie, drink the whole Diet Coke,
immediately had to go pee.
It'll do that, man. Yeah,
it will fucking do that.
Drinking a ton of liquid will make you piss.
I was having shit attacks during every movie that I saw
where I think when I was watching Talk to Me, maybe I was too scared.
But I shit my I shit myself.
I shit yourself.
I know I shit the toilet three times.
And every time I came back, my brother was like,
you missed the only scary part of the whole movie.
Your body, I guess.
I was hitting the eject button.
Yeah, as soon as I as soon as that music started,
Either the music starts creeping up or it or it get.
Oh man, I don't want to go too far into it,
but I have been shitting like the the like Fritos
honey barbecue twists is what like all of my shits have been like recently.
But I don't want to get too far into it.
Moving through your hot dog with me shit so bad, let's be for it.
Yeah, I'm not.
I'm not fucking getting a hot dog anywhere,
but a baseball stadium is like, yeah, insane to me.
Or Five Guys.
I disagree.
I like the Five Guys hot dog.
I disagree with this.
Hot dogs are not so good for you.
I know, but I disagree.
They're on the lower end of healthy foods.
There's a...
[laughter]
There's a place in my apartment that's just like a guy just making hot dogs.
There's like a little cabin near these like other places and they're so good.
There's not...
It's kind of funny because right near my house,
There's a guy that makes tacos and burritos and shit like that.
So it's kind of like a weird guy.
That'd be funny.
That would be funny if Julio has an American guy who makes hot dogs right outside
his apartment, like a little cart.
You know, there's actually a little car.
It's like a Ferrari that he's making it out of.
Yeah. Yeah.
Meanwhile, right on my street corner, there's a guy with a bunch of fruit.
It's tahini.
And then a guy with making birria outside.
I wish that guy was inside my apartment.
I do think Mexican food is probably 25% better if you eat it outside.
Yeah. Well, it's made to be eaten while you're outside.
Yeah, you should be.
You're supposed to eat it with your hands and standing.
You're supposed to be standing up.
There's supposed to be a bunch of like cars just
like just putting up a bunch of like dust on your on your shit.
Yeah, I get really dirty.
Yeah, that sounds amazing.
That's a good ass taco right there.
Yeah, yeah, it's a hot.
The dust taco.
The dust taco does not sound that good to me.
If I'm going to be honest, I do not think I would eat the dust
taco.
I would probably get an al pastor if it was on the menu.
I think I'm going to stop eating pork to it starting to kind
of disgust me.
Really?
Why how much pork are you eating?
Not much.
I've never eaten much, but I think I might completely cut it
out.
Okay, but it's just so it's weird, right?
Am I wrong about that?
I think pork is one of those things that I eat so little,
or like not so often that I don't care about it at all.
I feel like pork, I would almost put in the same vein as like lamb and veal,
where there's like, it's like the act of,
of like making pork happen just makes me kind of bummed.
I'm not sure I can eat it. And also it's like the,
I do think that like the, like, um,
What do they call that?
Halal is on to some things.
Like pork is nasty.
They eat shit. They eat their own shit.
They don't sweat.
Yeah, but it's so cheap.
I used to eat a lot of pork when it was really cheap.
When I was really cheap.
I would get some pork every two or three weeks.
- Pork is very yummy, but I definitely would not eat it
that often.
- I think the only time I would be like,
mm, yummy pork, is when I'm getting chicharron.
- I also don't like their skin.
I do love, that's the thing,
I recently got into chicharron and pork rides.
- Bro, I'm gonna change your life.
- Goddamn that, that is good.
- I'm gonna change your life.
As soon as you get your damn passport
and you get your ass down here,
I'm gonna change your fucking life.
- What are you gonna do to me?
- I'm gonna turn you into a complete Mexican.
You're gonna be a complete gringo walking around like,
"Yo, can I get a kilo of tortillas, please,
"at the Bodega?"
You're gonna change. - A kilo?
- Yeah, that's what you're gonna say.
- Whoa.
- You're gonna turn completely upside down.
- Do you think I could be a loco gringo?
- Yes, 100%.
I think you would love it.
- I think I could be too.
My brother's a loco gringo.
My older brother. - But he's in LA.
- What, you want him to fucking move to Mexico, man?
- It's fucking shit there.
- No, you can be a loco gringo in LA.
- Whoa, that is--
- I'm pretty sure you can.
- You could definitely be a loco gringo.
He's marrying into the, he's getting married in Mexico.
- Is he?
- Yeah, what is more loco gringo than that?
- Can I come?
- Yes, dude.
- Okay.
- It's a fucking Mexican wedding.
There's gonna be 50,000 people there.
- All right, he's a loco gringo actually.
- Dude, he's a complete loco gringo.
- I think you have to upstage him.
I think you have to move to like Mexico City.
Oh, dude.
What did we decide it's called?
What?
It's not El Jefe.
Oh.
I forgot, I forgot what it was.
But it's got another nickname.
Yeah.
It's got a different nickname.
I would move there, man.
It's cheap and everyone there is like just white guys now.
Yeah, pretty much.
There's so many YouTube videos that are like,
I moved into a six-bedroom apartment in Mexico City
that used to belong to a family for 200 years
and I only pay 300 bucks a month for it.
Yeah.
And it's just, I do love those videos
where people move to a country
that is not an English-speaking country
and they just walk around there like,
"Look how cheap everything is.
"Oh my God, I'm gonna buy all of it."
I think I saw a video yesterday
talking about how Mexico has the most
digital nomads type of people.
And I think Mexico City specifically.
They have like so many of their like higher end
like living type of like places.
They're just completely full of like gringos.
- I feel like if you do that,
you're just setting yourself up
to eventually be taken hostage.
- I think that's true.
- That's why you get an air tag implanted in you
or just one.
- And also that's why you still move to Mexico City
and you move to my city.
- Your city-- - Where you just get
a big ass house.
- Dude, I don't want a big ass house, bro.
I want--
- You don't want a Rancho, man?
- I wanna wake up every single day
and see the fucking Empire State Building.
You don't understand how powerful that is
for somebody who's 17 and a half percent Italian.
- I don't-- - That is like--
- I don't think your, I think your apartment
is like half windows, and I don't think the view,
I don't think you have a view.
You have big ass windows-- - Oh, okay.
Have you ever been on a submarine?
- No.
Do you know of submarines?
Are you familiar with their anatomy?
I am, yeah.
So you might be familiar with a little invention
called a looker that they put in submarines
that comes out and it can look in any angle.
Wait, you have a look in your apartment?
No, but I'm saving up for one.
Yeah, I think you have a complete crap view.
I have a nice view.
I look at my, let's see, if you look out of my windows,
You see a parking lot to another apartment.
Yeah.
And you see there's a flight line for people flying into LaGuardia.
So I can see some planes.
I think I can show you my view.
I want to see.
Don't tell me you see a mountain.
Rex, talk about your view.
Rex has a kind of nice view, but it's just water.
That's usually as good as views get.
Okay.
No, as good as views get is water contextualized.
It might as well be an aquarium that I'm looking into when I look out of your window.
I want to see some beach.
That's true, you can't see the beach, but you do see boats, which are cool.
You could tape that to a window.
That could be not real for all I know.
Alright, show me your view.
Holy shit!
That's my view.
That is an amazing view.
I said fucking out.
What the hell, you live in paradise.
I had no idea.
Yeah, and he pays $17 a month for that apartment.
How much do you pay for rent?
I think like, I think it comes to like less than $200.
Oh my God, man.
And you get to look at mountains and a building?
Yeah.
God, we need to move this whole operation to Mexico.
That'd be funny if as soon as Rex moves to New York, everybody here moves to Mexico.
I'd be pissed. Yeah. I'd be pissed. I'd have to fucking live in Mexico. That'd suck.
We'll all go together. We'll get a literal castle. I think Cal has the most,
has the life that can be just upended the easiest. Because you own like two
things. Yeah but imagine. You live in a shoebox and you own two things. But what if I was doing, like
trying to do stand up in Mexico?
Uh, we could do that.
Do you think I would crush?
Yeah, I could be like a guy who doesn't know any people in here.
English type comedian.
Completely love pretending that they're like from Texas.
Like they're just like, Oh, that's so me, the U S so they just like, they just eat
any, anything up that's from the U S or like, yeah, people, Popeye's is about to
come back.
If you love eating chicharrones, you might be a local gringo.
You are a complete local gringo.
You're your Loco Gringo in the making.
Yeah.
Maybe that could even be my stage name.
Loco Gringo.
Do you guys have a Mexico's Got Talent?
Uh...
Or Mexican Idol?
I don't...
No.
Or a Mexican Ninja Warrior?
I'd watch that.
Uh, I don't think so,
but I think you can make it through the ranks.
I think I could do it.
I think I could go and start over in Mexico.
See what's working for me.
Listen.
You don't have to do anything rash,
Especially with Rex moving there.
He just barely, he hasn't even moved
and you're already leaving him behind.
- Yeah, I don't think, even if,
I think it would be pretty much a 0% chance
I could convince my wife to move to Mexico.
I don't think that's happening.
- I think it's, I think it could happen.
- No, I don't think so, man.
I'm gonna be real with you.
I think she'd be a prime beheading kind of person.
She's got a really small neck.
I think it'd be, she'd pretty much get, you know,
done like a goose.
- There's no one getting beheaded anywhere in the country.
- They'd split her head between two kidnappers
like a wishbone.
- Y'all, I'd like to give out three Pinocchios
to Mr. Julio who just said,
"There's nobody getting beheaded in Mexico!"
(laughing)
(blows raspberry)
Yep, three Pinocchios for you.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
That's complete bullshit.
That's completely fake news.
People find heads on the it's like finding a dollar.
It's kind of rare, but it happens.
People, there's more people getting shot and beheaded in New York.
Every single, nobody gets beheaded in New York.
They get shot.
They get, they get, they get shot.
Yeah.
Anything you can imagine, but nobody's going as far as beheading.
Listen, all I know is that Americans completely have their, their
priorities, completely upside down.
There's people shitting and doing drugs in the streets.
Meanwhile, everyone's complaining about a little sign
on top of the Twitter building.
- Science.
Okay, let's ask her right now.
Would you move to Mexico?
She looks disgusted.
She's using her finger to make a gagging motion.
Oh God, what are you doing with your eyes?
Stop.
It's not even the right country.
No, I'm kidding.
- You're not kidding.
But she did say no.
That's fine.
We'll just deal with her later.
That sounds like you're going to
behead her.
Me and my primos.
You're going to deal with her later?
You're going to fucking behead her.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
we're not making it, bro.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's not going to happen. It's not in the cards.
No, it's fine. It's completely fine.
I don't want to see any beheadings.
And just knowing my luck.
I just can't, if I was a luckier guy, I'd move to Mexico.
(laughing)
- Do you think as soon as you hop off the plane,
we're gonna be driving into the city
and you're gonna just look outside the car
and just see someone get beheaded?
- I think they're gonna have a razor wire limbo
sitting at customs that I walk into
'cause I'm so excited to be in a new country.
- And you, yeah, you would just go right under it.
- Maybe I see a chupacabra and I run, right?
And I'm running full speed and then I cut my own head off.
And now nobody's even going to jail.
Not that you guys have prison there,
but I'm just, there's no recourse.
- Yeah. - Right.
Okay, that's fine.
That's okay.
- Is weed legal in Mexico?
- I think so.
I'm not, I don't know.
- Interesting.
- Whoa.
It's kinda cool he doesn't know.
- I completely don't know.
- He doesn't even care if it's a crime or not.
He's still gonna--
- Are you allowed to have guns in Mexico?
- I think so.
You don't know anything.
How do you know?
You can only get like hunting.
That's a picture on your fucking window.
Hunting gear.
Yeah.
What does that mean?
I don't think you can just, can you go to Los Walmart?
Wait, I think we looked this up the first time I was in New York.
We're looking up a bunch of like gun guns for some reason, uh, kills apartment.
Um, and I think the only way you can buy guns in Mexico, if you like buy them
off, like the, the army specifically.
Oh yeah, I remember that. Yeah.
That's actually cool.
It is kind of cool.
The only way for you to get like killing people guns.
You have to go.
Any gun can kill people if you try hard enough.
Those like little rifles.
A water gun?
Yeah.
It could drown you.
That's not true.
Cool bro.
You could not drown me.
You think you could drown me with a water gun?
I could try.
I mean, you can't.
I mean.
But then it's like, can we do that?
Can we try that?
As soon as Rex moves to New York,
he tries to drown me with a wad.
This is, how is this fun for me?
- I think if I shot you in the back of the throat
with a super soaker, like 11 times in a row.
- I just drink it, asshole.
- It would hurt.
And then you'd cough.
- It might hurt, I would drink it.
- Yeah, you would cough and then--
- Okay, here's my pressure.
Okay, go ahead, say shoot and it'll be like you shot.
- Shoot.
(imitates gunshot)
Shoot.
Shoot, shoot, shoot.
- Boop, boop, boop, boop, boop.
- No, this is, no, you guys are so compulsive.
- No, that's not what would happen.
- That is not what happens.
You know what you need?
You need one of those electric water guns,
the one that are all fucked up
and they shoot at it at the same pressure.
- Oh yeah, the ones that shoot like a buck shot.
- Yeah.
- Wait, Phil, do you have something to say?
He tried to eat the microphone.
(Phil laughs)
Get out, get out, man.
Go! - Thanks, Phil.
- Go!
What are you doing?
Get out of the room!
- I think you could completely drown him
with a super soaker.
- Yeah.
- That's the other thing, dude.
I put him in my backyard, right?
What if he gets beheaded?
- I think dogs rarely get beheaded.
I think dogs kind of rule the world down here.
- What if I get scared of him
because I think that he's some,
he's La Llorona or La Chupacabra,
and I behead him.
Now I'm part of the problem.
- Listen, this is, you know what this is?
This is all a bunch of white guilt, white prejudice.
- Oh, you're right.
- That will completely-- - I hate white prejudice.
- Just dissipate-- - I'm being white guilty.
- It'll completely dissipate
as soon as you visit the country.
I think you should stop dwelling on it.
I think--
- That's the other problem, bro.
What if I go there
and people start worshiping me like a king, right?
And then I basically take over the entire country
and do colonialism all over again.
That'd be annoying.
And now everybody's speaking Esperanto
because that's what I choose to be,
our national language. - You cannot be a king.
You can't be a king. I couldn't be a king. I couldn't be a king my ass.
Shut up. Perfect head for a crown. He did it. He shut up.
When I said shut up, he was about to say something.
He went, oh, and then stopped. I was about to say something.
Very kingly of me to make commands that are followed.
What would be your first command to your people?
To get your bitch ass out of this country. That's what I would say.
I'd say Julio has to go. He's exiled.
I'd send you to that island that they put Napoleon on.
But I actually, I would make it,
I would put you on the island next to that one because Napoleon was such a great
man that you don't deserve to walk on the same sand that he did.
Is he good or bad?
- Napoleon?
- Is he supposed to be good or is he supposed to be bad?
- I think there's no such thing as good and bad.
- I think they only paid him in a bad light
because he was short.
- I agree.
I fucking agree.
If he was six foot two,
they would not have called him
all this nasty, disgusting stuff.
- What bad sister are they calling Napoleon?
- People only look up to Marx and the other guy from Cuba
because they were over six feet tall.
- Agree.
- My new theory.
That's an amazing theory.
Tall men have it so easy in this world.
Yeah.
They have it so fucking easy.
I mean, that's actually, that's not true.
No, I haven't really--
You have it so easy.
You have it so--
You just told us you pay $300 a month for rent, man.
I think that's--
You think your landlord would have given me that price?
No fucking way.
I think she wouldn't.
I think she wouldn't rent to you.
I think she would hate you.
She sounds like a fucking bitch.
But she is a bitch.
So what if I said $310?
Listen, you've never seen money like this lately.
$310.
You can easily take it.
Yeah.
I'm gonna get, actually, when's your lease up?
December.
Bidding war.
Do you not, no, that's not.
Bidding war on the way.
I am going to bid on your apartment.
What, 400 bucks a month, dude?
That's what it's gonna cost me so that you're homeless?
You guys don't--
Worth.
Worth, I'm not even, I'll never go there.
You don't know where I live.
I won't even set up an Airbnb for it.
I don't want, 400, it's not worth my time, right?
400 bucks, I make that in, you know, three weeks.
Guys, can I sublet the apartment?
No.
Yeah, for $4.50.
But I will put it up on Airbnb for $15 a day.
You could be a live-in maid for the Airbnb
we end up running.
Yep.
I don't think I want you guys to visit me anymore.
I think I've changed my mind.
And guess what, we're putting an aquarium
in the living room with a shark.
- I would actually really love that.
You can order the bomb.
- We're ordering a bomb to your house like a pizza.
- You can do that.
- 30 minutes or less.
- Yep, and you're gonna make a video
where you suck the bomb delivery guy's dick.
- Okay, guys, this is not what Mexico is like at all.
- Explodes the bomb.
(laughing)
- Thank you, the bomb explodes in your hands.
- This is not what Mexico is like at all.
I think you guys have just a wrong idea
of what a beautiful country this is.
you guys just painted it in the wrong way,
such as people paint Napoleon because he's short.
Only because we speak a different language.
- Nobody, I mean, honestly,
you asked if Napoleon was good or bad.
I don't know the first fucking thing about Napoleon.
- I don't know what he did.
- He's French.
- That's the problem.
That's the problem.
He could have been a worse than Hitler style guy, right?
But I wouldn't fucking know because he was short.
So nobody says anything except he was short.
- I think people start worrying about him.
- Another thing about it,
people used to talk about Napoleon all the time
when I was a kid, and now no one talks about him anymore.
- They're making a movie.
They're gonna talk about it again.
- Yeah, now, yeah, this year, next year.
- Okay, so. - They already made a movie.
- But for the past 10 years, Napoleon has--
- No one talks about fucking Oppenheimer,
and now it's all you can hear about.
- I used to talk about Oppenheimer all the time, actually.
- You don't even know who that is.
- You're right, it's Albert Einstein's op, their ops.
Were they ops? - Yeah.
- I think so, I haven't seen the movie, I think they're ops.
- I haven't seen the movie either,
but I know the history. - I know Albert Einstein
is in it.
- You said Albert.
- Albert.
- Albert Einstein.
That's how he would say his own name.
- Can you please numb your thing and see if you pee yourself?
- Can we please just see you numb it once, man?
- Just numb it.
- Just, come on.
- He says, "I can't do it."
- He's gonna do it, he's a good man.
- No, I'm just a little part of it.
- He's pretending, he's pretending.
- No, he's hitting his leg right now.
There's no way that hand--
- He's pretending, it is completely pretending.
- Yeah. - That's his knee.
Okay, you're a bastard. - He's numbed your knee.
- You're a complete lying bastard.
- What do you mean I'm numbing my knee?
My knee is right here.
- Wait, do you have no pants on?
How'd you get your hand in your pants?
- I reached up, wearing--
- Completely no pants. - No cool shorts.
- No pants Friday.
- You, oh, I kind of believe this.
That's kind of a convoluted enough way to touch your penis
that I do a little bit believe that he numbed it.
Okay, then give us a trip report.
Just trip report, one second, and what's going on?
Are you feeling?
It tingles, whoa, he's starting to like it.
He might be addicted.
How much was this tiger bomb?
It's like $11.
Oh, okay.
It's not that much.
Yeah, just have a heart attack?
It's saving you a lot of money.
No, it's probably 30 heart attacks.
30 of those is more than Jubio's rent.
30 tiger bombs. That is true.
This world is crazy. I'm moving to another country.
Okay. What are you guys getting into this weekend? Huh? Let's close her out.
I got beers. I got fake beers to drink.
I'm packing.
He's packing. He's potentially, what are you leaving?
I think the eighth now. Okay. I got a,
I got a new quote from a different company.
So we got one other piece of drink.
Well, actually, you might not have another piece of drink in this in this house for
Rex. Yeah, this is my last one.
Next one, he might just be in New York completely.
Say goodbye, drinkers.
And I have to probably do it in the office because I'm not going to have one of me.
You guys might even have to do it together as best friends.
We don't have to.
But if if if we need to, we're if we'll see what you want to do or if Brexit thing is,
I'm not going to go all the way over there to record or to unlock the door and then fucking not stay and record.
So wait, can we do an official send off of this house?
Can you run to your front door and do the doorbell?
Oh, yes, please.
Thank you.
That's what I did.
I love it.
I love that.
The fact that this is going to be recorded.
Oh, my God.
Have we heard it before on the podcast?
I don't think so.
I think it's in one of my videos on YouTube.
Shh, shh, shh.
Wait.
I'm getting worried.
So every time something gets delivered,
every time someone is at the door,
he has to listen to that for the last like year or so.
Maybe almost two years.
Last two years, two years.
But he's finally free.
He's going to have just a normal, just "Blaaah!"
Wow.
That was fucking amazing.
That was awesome.
Alright.
See you in New York.
Bye.