*sips tea*
*slurps tea*
*burps*
*gibberish*
*music*
beer
beers we drank mother fucker
with dubio, caleb and rex
beer
welcome back to another episode of
beers we drank
guys we have guests in the building
today with funny backgrounds
you guys
everybody hold up a beer
one by one
hold up a beer rex i'd like you to start because you're my friend
i haven't talked to you in some days
and this is looking like an invisible type of beer
type of beer. All right, hold on. Let me turn off the green screen.
Okay. I have a Lord Hobo.
Oh, this girl does not like when I do that. Every single time I pay you,
it takes me hours to work up the courage to hit that submit button on the direct
deposit.
I made an awesome discovery.
When what, what is that?
If you press end recording, it ends the recording?
Is that what you discovered?
Whenever I change my background on Discord, it goes crazy and it breaks.
So I'm not going to do it anymore.
That is super awesome.
Okay, are you still recording or do we need to restart completely?
Yeah, you can keep going.
Okay, Rex, talk about your Juice world.
So it's a Huel Melon, Galaxy Meridian, and Azaca.
And these are fake words that they made up
to describe this beer.
- Yummy.
- Sound like they could be real.
They did not give me a bag, so I put it in my hoodie,
so it's a little shaken.
- Okay, now give me a sip and a rating, my friend.
- Yeah, it's beer.
It's like a solid six and a half out of 10.
- Okay.
All right, I'd like to go next
because mine is a bit of a disappointment.
- Yes, do your beer.
- So I got one beer and then we played some video games
and while we were playing video games, I was like,
I'll just have this beer and I'll go get another one later.
And that was this, the Zuber.
And I was gonna do really something very funny
where I was gonna have my phone pretend to ring and say,
oh, my Zuber is here.
And you guys, I don't know if you've,
have you ever taken a car service?
They have, they're called Ubers.
I was gonna do that.
But guys I drank the whole damn thing.
I drank the whole thing and it was not very good.
It tasted like toothpaste.
So I cracked into my, what we call the Pitshouse Reserve Selection, okay?
And I went deep, deep into the archives and I got this guys.
A Heineken 0.0 alcohol free beer.
This is an amazing beer guys.
I'm gonna take a sip.
Okay, it tastes exactly like a normal Heineken.
This is the supreme zero alcohol beer.
- Is this a-- - Does it really?
- It really does.
It gives you diarrhea just like a normal Heineken.
This is an amazing no alcohol beer.
- I think that might just be you, man.
- The wife reserves?
Can we get an update on how that situation developed?
Oh, the beers that she was hiding in the fridge?
Well, here's how it developed guys. She got mad at me. That's the end of the story
She got she I drank her beer and she got really mad at me
And she called me two or three times the next day just to complain about how I took her beer
So if you're wondering how the marriage is going not so good
I'm gonna give this on the NA scale. I'm gonna give this a
8.3 and again, this is portnoy. This is an amazing score
Okay, this is an 8.3. I like this beer a lot, okay
Yeah, I'll go next I got a I know how you guys have been doing a mixed drinks these past couple weeks
so I went ahead and I got myself a a
mango beer Oh
Mango mixed with beer so it is still it is it's beer with chamoy and mango
Yummy, but it only has a mango picture on it. So I think it's gonna be completely mango juice
The mango has Chamoy on it in the picture
But it's true. It's got redness on it
Who's the real Mexican here that is it's me good
listen
Mango cart is a an amazing beer, which it was more common on the East Coast. I love mango cart. What's mango?
I like all
You're
Sorry, I burped
And guys I'm gonna have to switch to my microphone or to my headset microphone because I just heard that my headset is dying
So give me one second
Can someone tell me what my
Mango cart is just a mango beer and it's yummy. Yes. Well, I don't think it's supposed to be just like a mango
I think this is like mango juice mixed with a normal Victoria beer which you can see. Well bros. How do I sound?
- You sound amazing, man.
- Thank you, thank you.
It feels good to have a Britney Spears microphone set up.
- This pretty much is a thing that a girl would buy
at the store when you ask for a beer, I would say.
- Yeah.
- But I like it because of that.
- Okay, all right, so our two esteemed guests,
I waited to introduce them until they have their beers.
Let's start with Alex.
Alex, what do you have for us today?
Alex, both of them have been on the podcast before,
you're very familiar.
I have a Spark Ominous Wushing IPA.
I have IPAs.
It's not bad though.
Did you buy this beer?
No, I took it from my roommate.
Oh, we like that!
We endorse this.
The beer is good, man.
It's alright.
I'm gonna give it like a 5.
5.
Okay, this is it.
Alex picked it up immediately.
It's the Portnoy Scale.
This is the 10 is unachievable and the zero has never happened.
Right.
The five five that's right there.
That's an average beer.
Yeah.
I don't think I'd ever go out and buy this.
But you would steal it.
Yeah.
I would steal it.
What do you usually get at the beer store?
I usually get probably Heineken or Stella.
Like Cronus too.
Whoa.
Okay.
What's the Canadian like?
I'm like a Molson. Molson Canadian.
Is that like the PBR of Canada?
What's like the shitty common beer?
Oh we have PBR.
A lot of people drink PBR.
Well what's the one that you guys have there?
I don't know dude.
I'm probably Molson Canadian.
We do the same thing.
He's never drank beer before.
This is what I was about to say.
I always forget that Alex is 15.
I am 17.
in the chat said old-fashioned pilsner have you seen have you come across this
I'll play I remember I remember man I go I just go to what I usually go you go to
the fridge you see what the roommate bought and you steal it yeah and I steal it I say
all right I like that I do our next guest is Brian who has I'm sure an amazing
beer he has a he always has a crazy selection of beer sitting in the house
us
and
I mean you can but...
It gets tough.
I've had fun with it though.
Interesting.
And I don't I think it's be I think my brain thinks that this has more than 0.0 in it, but it truly is zero
Well getting drunk is all in your head. Anyway, it's why you know
Yeah, some people can drink and drive and some people can't it's why some people can make good decisions while drunk and some can't
You know, yeah
Force yourself out of it. Yeah, and you could force yourself into it. Oh
- Oh, easily.
- Yeah. - I've never done that.
- You've never, well you, I think you've never been drunk.
- I think so too.
- I would, I really want this,
maybe at Cam's wedding you'll wild out.
That's what I wanna see.
- Well I think-- - We're gonna make him
eat the worm.
- I think the two closest I've been were both in New York,
and one of them was when Rex tried to poison me,
which we've went over this multiple times.
And the second one-- - With that margarita.
- Yeah, and the second one was at your wedding
where Noah tried to poison every single guest.
(laughing)
- That's why we paid him.
- So I think next time I will die.
- Well, you know what they say, good times to charm.
It takes time to get drunk.
- I think that very soon,
you've never had a night where you've been very drunk
and taken your clothes off or done something
like a feat of superhuman strength,
lifted a car off of somebody, that type of thing?
Nope, I've been to a friend's birthday party, drank some beers and just drove home.
And that's it.
Were you drinking when you got hit in the head?
That's awesome dude.
What's up?
When you got hit in the head by a piece of the ceiling?
It wasn't the ceiling, that was a construction site, it was a metal beam.
I was on the way back from buying some tortillas, so I was not drinking now.
It was like 10am.
Wait, I don't understand.
I don't understand. You were buying tortillas and it was 10 a.m. I'm supposed to think you weren't drinking?
You hadn't had a morning Modelo man, be honest. Yeah, come on man.
Guys, Mexico is completely different to how you perceive it in all those racist TV shows like The Simpsons and Harry Potter.
I assure you it's completely different. I don't think there are Mexicans in Harry Potter. Is there a Mexican Hogwarts in Harry Potter?
No. No.
Let's make a better is on robot chicken. I'm gonna look that up. I'm sure that she's made a character called like Juan taco
Yeah
He's from Spain, yeah
Juan taco guacamole, please
Anyways, yeah, this is all just to say that you know
I always talk about my experiences as a foreigner which none of you are
Except maybe one of you and I just wanna I just want to bring you guys into my home
I just want to invite you guys to a different country and
I
Google mapped your Google Street food viewed your apartment and it looks like there is nothing to do for
Miles and maybe even years in any direction. So I'm not all that interested in visiting my I don't live in an apartment anymore
I've moved out of there or in your house. I'm sorry
Yeah, I moved out into even further away from anything which is pretty cool. It looks like like Las Vegas suburbs
It does not look all that fun to visit but I'll come I'll go anywhere man
Okay, the wife is bugging me about going to France. I don't want to go to France go to France. It sucks. I
Really don't want to go to France you have France in Canada. Yeah, go back
Place that fuck that man. These people are rude, right?
Yeah, French people are mean men and they simply mean yeah, they're stinky
They're racist and
There's Neanderthals
Yeah, they're not even human. I really don't care for the French at all. I'm gonna say it
I like you liked it. You liked it when you went but that's because you look French
Bro
There was no the only person that was kind of rude was the person at the TSA whatever
But she I was completely fine. I didn't even speak the language
Yeah, I think
that you're a Spaniard.
But you don't speak any language.
You're from Mexico.
Yeah.
So, even, like, you didn't have the, I think there's an immediate bad will that is put
upon Americans when they visit as soon as they start speaking English.
Or apparently it's even worse if you start, if you try to speak French.
They really do not care for that at all.
Well, I think I'd better.
I think that's fair.
I hate when Julio speaks English.
It pisses me off because he's, it really is a bastardization of the language.
Yeah.
It really, really gets me.
You should see his text messages.
They are awful.
What's wrong with my text messages?
It's like a dog jumping on a keyboard.
It is not English that you text us.
Not even close to English.
I texted you guys something so beautiful today.
I'll say that it's really cute.
I'll write down question marks.
You didn't text me today.
Oh, I haven't texted all of my friends.
But I texted this to my guy friends.
I texted this to my guy friends.
to my guy friends.
Uh-huh.
My straight guy friends.
Alex just got so excluded.
In text meme ad.
I said, I said this, not me missing you all so much that I got
New York bagels and it's a bagel brand that's called New York bagels.
And no one even cared about that.
I literally didn't even notice that you said that.
I've never seen that text message.
I don't think that sent.
I think it was too gay to go over the network.
Well, he sent it to not really any of you, but just Caleb and Cameron and Patrick.
That's awesome, man. I mean, we all live in New York.
So, that's me, man.
Well, it wouldn't make sense for me to send it to Alex because he's...
No, I'm a New Yorker.
He went to New York. He's from New York.
You're not a New Yorker.
He's a native born and raised.
I have a picture of Margaritaville right here.
right there it's right here look you can see the city behind him look at that
beautiful city oh that is so fun that's sitting right above your full Homer
Simpson just like yeah I just taped it up there sweet man you better hope you
never have a girl in this room ever I don't think you have to worry about that
too much? No. Oh,
geez. Alex, how's the love life going, man?
I had a date today. Wow. How'd it go?
Uh, she was French. Oh, you're kidding. I'm not kidding, man.
She's actually French or Quebec.
Uh, no. Well, not even Quebec.
She just lives on the border. So like they speak French.
And did she smell badly?
He's kind of fat.
Nice.
He did it y'all.
I know man.
I went I was like, whoa.
Yeah, I did the first time.
Oh the first time it was like last year around this time.
Maybe it's just this time of the year.
I guess the year the winter ever dating.
Yeah, so the heating more.
Last year
It was like my friend's girlfriend's friend and then the show business. Oh, yeah, I pull up and then she was fat
Just the forehead pictures. That's what they were showing you. No, man. It was just like she really knew how to use those angles
It might be on me maybe I just love fat woman
Oh clearly not but I think you can't tell the difference in a picture. Yes
Some people don't see color Alex just doesn't see size. I don't see wait
Might be pretty large. I want you to be smothered like Norbert
Norbit
Said Norbert
Man I think okay, so I was I was
Going this week
I've been like
Really trying to eat well and stuff because there's a thing coming up that I might need to be like in really good shape for
But tonight I found out that I think I wouldn't actually be doing it until like neck or this
October or November so now I'm thinking I have like three months where I could get pretty fat
Before I really need to worry about anything
Should I get like a like pretty bigly fat for a little bit? Yeah. Yeah, I think yeah, it should be like to like 220
It needs to be an amount of weight that I could gain and then lose well
also, like you know really a
Like percent in this like the way you've been telling us like in private which is you're like I need to be insanely ripped
For this one thing so I think going getting instantly rip is very different to just being kind of fit
How you're saying it? What do you need to get insanely fit for?
first of all, I
Can't say all the details, but it is some kind of some NDA
It's a work thing and I got yeah cash for playgirl guys, okay
and
I'm not familiar, but please tell me.
So me and all my straight guys were just in a discord call sharing our screens,
scrolling through celebrity penis at about 11.30 p.m.
Right before all of our girlfriends and wives got home.
And guys, these celebrities are not packing like I thought they were going to be.
I thought that every celebrity had a giantly large penis.
It turns out they're medium to small, most of them.
No print?
very little prints I was seeing very little prints it's it's very 50/50
because there's some celebrities who have massive huge wieners of course but a
lot of the biggest cocks that were on the subreddit were celebrate not even
celebrities there were guys who were in a movie in the 60s for like five minutes
yeah you sort by controversial that's a cool I didn't do that even once
the
that
Lion Justin Bieber doesn't have much downstairs. It doesn't look like no way Mark Wahlberg. The hell is this guy?
Mmm, not so much Scott Disick big bouncing free ball bulge
That's a broken gift
Henry Cavill, oh, I see why these are controversial. These are not nude
Hmm. I see
Wait, oh, these are not
these
Don't even fit the paradigm
You guys were looking at I'm Cox the other day
the
I think you should get five chances a year and get to see anyone in the world's dick.
You know?
Even just a regular guy on the street.
So you have an ability to just point at someone and kill them?
Yeah, look at how they're working.
Do you have like, um, are you, is it, say somebody wants to see your cock.
Are they interrupting you in whatever you're doing?
No.
Like your son is being confirmed and they're like, "Someone needs to see your cock right now."
And they pull you out?
No, it's, you know, like...
'Cause every single person is either taking a picture of their cock, they've been naked at some point in their lives.
The cocks are definitely, you know, have been seen by some sort of camera device.
Never once.
CCTV, yeah.
And the government should allow you five times a year to just see
They get freedom of information request. Yes. Oh, okay
Ken klippenstein sending out the foia
Request for to see a cock right and it could be anyone. This is like a you know, government portal
Will you just say that your computer? Yes. Yes, it would be your first five, right?
Oh, yeah for year one year one of the program
year one of the program
the
Looked up your who's your first five then? Okay. Well, I haven't thought about it that far. I don't really have any
Is a good one, yeah Papa John
under there I
Don't see Alec Baldwin. We do Trump Alec Baldwin is good
No, somebody else would do it for me. Oh Barack Obama's a great one and and Trump honestly, give me a both side by side
Can you look similar can you screen peek
You mean can I can can be like pull it together?
I get if I have ten friends who already use their five on January 1st because they couldn't help themselves
And then I have an idea because I have some restraint to look up a cock
Can I invite all my friends over Super Bowl party?
Okay, here comes Seth Rogen's cock guys
Three two one. Yeah, but I think it would be fun to do to your friends
On to your friends you you want to anonymously look at your friends cock, that's what you're saying. Yeah, of course
Imagine settling it argued it that way and being like
Do you as the person so this is all self-reporting right
the
It would be funny. It would be a funny and
This would be funny. I don't know if everybody would love it
Well, that's the thing I guess it is five for one like yes, I give up the the right to my privacy and my cock
but I
Also get to look at well, I mean there's four guys here
Yeah
and this would certainly be my first four just because you guys were just because also we've been lobbying for years to get this
Introduce
No, that's for oh true. God. Damn it. Yes a man you enter America. You got it. That's how you get a green card
Maybe yeah look photo of your cock with unlimited views any any
You can look at their penis as many times as you'd like
Yeah, who's the 12th president the 15th president and you got to give us a picture you did
Actually, no, I mean are you willing to give up to be an American?
Yeah
Sure your cock who cares to be I'm fine over here
Okay, then we're gonna bring it down there
No, yeah
I will become the Mexican president. It's definitely not very hard and I will
enact this law
This would be like a new deal if you made an app where if you submitted a picture of your cock
You could see five random cocks. That's a gay guy app and like a bad one
But if you make it tied to the identity of the person that's a straight guy app
This website the only man the only people who will use it are men yeah
No
They'll all be looking over the same celebrities. Nobody's gonna look up a man. They knows cock. They
Think they're disgusting. They could see it if they wanted to see it. Exactly
I'm a question about the infrastructure of this the system
Back in I know. Yeah, I know it has the view counter. It doesn't tell you who should viewed it
But how many people viewed it?
Do you have to look up yourself to look at that number or do you get like emailed?
I'll like do you have to look log into the government portal be like, oh, oh, by the way, you get a Google alert
Yeah, you get a Google alert. Okay. Yeah, it's
Notification on your phone it's next to your battery. Okay, it's built into Apple
Well used to be an app and then Apple put it in the new iOS. All right follow-up question. Would you?
rather have a
10 or under view count or an over a thousand of you count
over a thousand
18 to use the website Leo boo the very least
And if it's if there is react emojis tenor under if there is not react emojis
Give me the wrong numbers because if I had to like see that I had a thousand views of my car and like there's 500
thumbs down
It should be like the be real reactions though
Pain real we should do this
You're saying every day I have to upload a picture my cock at a random
Time to prepare
Shaved in a wild god. Yeah, no grooming. No manicure. Yeah, there's no raw dick
You do a full-body picture by accident. Yep with the poop sitting in the toilet behind
Well, I almost turned be real in the peen real so I don't think it's that much
Yeah, half the time you get a be real you're taking a shit anyway because we all spend three hours a day on the toilet
No question. Yeah. No, so
the
I can think of millions of movies.
Except for pornography.
I can think of zero movies.
And the second one was,
would I take one of these roles
where you have to show your penis?
And this was a tough question for me.
I thought about it for some time.
Do you think there's any movies
where a woman has to show her breasts?
Yeah, any movie that I want to watch.
Right.
Well, women,
53% of the population,
90% of the people who watch movies I
feel like
They need to show more cocks than movies
But we like cocks women like boobs more than cocks you anti-nudity in movies
Yes, I'm anti-nudity and I'm anti-gore. I've said this before I don't like either of these things in movies
I'm the gore you can't
Like ox dude, because they've watched that like naked date make it attraction like it's fucking catnip
they love that stuff. We've talked about this before. That is a, just like the peen, peen reel is an app for men.
That is a show for men. No.
Yeah. Wait, what is that show? Naked Attraction, oh this again. Naked Attraction is a dating show where you look at people's naked
disgusting
penises that are hairy and you say I like that guy and then they zoom up and the guy
has, is one of the ugliest people of all time, burn, scars all over his face. Wait, you like guys?
I'm not on the show. I'm a watcher.
How about this? Would you go on naked attraction?
When I go on naked attraction, I'm married.
If universe where Janna doesn't exist...
Yeah, she died. She died. She never...
Quantum died, never existed. You're never married.
Well, I do a lot of things.
the
a huge TV I would get the thing is you know I'm 50 inch TV you don't have to
fuck the people no you don't have to they don't they both the time don't fuck
they actually hate each other yeah maybe 70% of the time yeah of course okay so
this show I would go on I would go on right yeah I'd go on right now wait do I
get to be the picker or do I have to be one of the people in the queue what are
the people oh god I don't I'm not just a piece of meat
Isn't the picker also naked?
The picker becomes naked at the end.
At the end.
They level the play field.
And then there's two people and they go
"What do you think of his cork?"
"I really hate it!"
"Quite nice cork, eh?"
We've talked about this before in the podcast.
It's called a cheeky little bum, doesn't it?
We had the idea of doing a
Moving Monday style
series, but on kick.com
we just watched that show and we just
the naked guys go on there.
Which is a great pic.
One of my favorite things is when they're bisexual and they put one trans person on.
Yeah, you're talking about this.
Yeah, then I won't get into it.
I think that if we did that series and we did a kick.com stream of Naked Attraction,
the problem is the show's 45 minutes and the stream would be 4 and a half hours
hours because of how many times we would pause and zoom in and give our opinions.
It's a British show?
Yeah.
It is British.
That's disgusting.
This is perverted and wrong.
Yeah.
I think the number one thing against it would not be the nakedness but maybe the copyright
and watching the entire show.
So there needs to be a fully Wild West.
I could even on kick I don't think you can show a disgusting British cock
Would actually have to go to a campsite I think I feel like if we just wait six more months
We'll be able to do it on twitch
Which is twitch is gonna be out of out of money. Yeah
Well, it's just gonna be fully chatter bait in six twitch
Well, you have my other beer which walk back the naked update. Oh, I finished mine and it was it was great
Well, I saw I was on Twitter on the for you tab
And I saw a video of the Dan dangler shaking her rear end in the shower, and she looked pretty naked to me
And I was like this is what they're doing on twitch. Let me show my penis
Well, I think I think I was maybe during that update, but they did walk away. It was today. This is a girl
But I think in March or April
They're discontinuing like twitch prime it's going away
So maybe something fucked up is gonna happen to the site
What they just well, they just they just fired a bunch of people. I think
Like 200 people. Yeah. Yeah, but a bunch of people are firing people
Wait, that's not a problem. I'm stuff. It's just not gonna I think it's going away. Yeah Wow
That's how much shaft can you show before it's illegal that's an amazing point because I've definitely seen shaft in
a
PG-13 movie I've seen shaft
40%
A lot
It's 40%
you smell
depending on the
On light you could just be sure you're showing like what if you have a stick and you show two inches
the
I'll bring my tiny dick into this.
With a Michelob Ultra, that is a classic go.
Classic second beer.
No one can get mad at it because it's a second one.
That's true, even though it is a repeat many, many times.
Oh, what the hell?
That is shit.
This one tastes like shit.
You're not a golfer, man. Y'all are not golfers.
I got fully a water one.
I'm a golfer, bro.
This is crazy.
I know Alex is. Me and Alex would love a Michelob Ultra on the links.
The back nine you have you have one mickle of ultra per hole
Can you please California and go to El Segundo Tom golf
Yes, great. I love I'd love to do that when I'm not in a meeting at the same time. Yeah
I was so executive that day. It was crazy. You did
We went to the top golf in El Segundo and they had a part they had a
a
The something at El Segundo.
Yeah.
It was sick.
It was very sick.
And then the last...
They have actual holes in the top golf out there?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
They have a little...
What the fuck?
...nine hole course next to it.
It was really hard.
That's crazy.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
It was like my first time golfing ever and it was really fun.
And then the last hole they have a camera where you can watch your shot.
And they do like the tracker on it and stuff like on the tour.
And that was the very end of our live show tour.
And that is when that was the day that I realized that I had gotten really fat on the entire
Because I looked at the
At the thing where they like show everybody's videos back-to-back and I was like, oh who's this fucking fat?
And guys it was me and my shot did not look very good either
We were so bad, but it was very fun. Yeah. Yeah, it was pretty bad
That was when I was much worse at golf now, I'm basically an expert I've played executive courses
So I had an executive day Julio drove be true. I was his Mexican slave
He gave me his headphones and then I was in ways canceling headphones
Bagels for breakfast and then we hit the links. Yeah
That's the life man. I cannot
Wait to be I think I'll be one of these people. I mean, I'll never retire. This is an impossible
Right goals for me, but if I were to retire, I think I would be one of these people, you know
A lot of people retire and they're like, oh, yeah, I retired and I realized I was bored and they get another job
That would never be me. I
Would retire I would play golf every day. I would watch
TV shows rewatch TV shows I would have an amazing fucking time
Yeah, here's the thing. So my my dad right now
Is like persona non grata at his job. He's getting Japanese style fired where they just give you less and less responsibility
But he doesn't have a Japanese man's shame. So he just golfs
every day
That's what you're supposed to do I like that
Until you literally
That you can't move what happened my grandpa man
He was good. He golfed every day for like 10 years and then his rotator cuff exploded. Yeah
He hurt his back like because I was I was in Arizona for like nine days
He went golfing seven times and hurt his back
four days
Yeah, hey we need to go golfing up here bro
All the ones that are like close to New York City suck dick, but we go to like
Jersey for this park golf course right near me has
Pretty good. They've like I think three courses. It's like a big-ass
Thing and they're pretty nice. They have one like nine hole par three and like two
executive courses
There should be like what vertical golf courses
Do you know I mean like no I no idea what you mean, man. What does that mean? You mean top goal?
That's what you're not you mean every level is a
Hole, yes, but then that would be boring because they all be that a standard kind of size. No, no, they could be huge
But then this within the building would be unmanageably large. Yes
Well, here's the thing right you're saying the building would be unmanageably large a
Golf course is just that but just spread out
That's true Rex's what I just mean vertical farming right now. That's I just mean in New York
I don't think there's anywhere where you could fit a building that wide
Except maybe pretty tall on a park. Yeah, it's at least 18 floors not to mention the clubhouse the pro shop
Well, I'm all
In the air, you know true they would be yeah, it would be very very tall wait, and then you just have levitating
That's what the Burj Khalifa girls yeah
They will try to do like in like Dubai and they would it would be like the talk of the town for like a whole year
And then I'd be like, yep after 18 billion dollars nothing happened
like the line
12,000 Burmese men
A single floor
Are we gonna
Foundation in 25 years. Are we gonna make a trip to the line in Saudi Arabia?
You don't know the line the line city, oh, yeah
They say it's happening man
It's their new those those project
This insane like architecture videos where they talk about insane new high-tech buildings. You're like, wow
That's crazy. And then you forget about them did the next day
Yeah, cuz none of those have ever come true every single like I would what you watch those ten years ago
and they say they're gonna be done in ten years and
Then you check in on it now and whoever started it is in jail every single time
Yeah, the coolest ones are like yeah, these are just this one just started. It's gonna be it's gonna be a lot of housing
It's gonna be like a big mob because we a hotel is gonna be great and they'll be done and approximately
62 years so I don't care
The only people I trust to do this is is the UAE because they did
Huh and a con of course, but you a they did the big building and then they also did the globe the world islands
Where they have every country as as an island lives on those hates those or they're completely empty
Everyone who lives anywhere hates them
But they look cool. Yeah, I want to be one of the workers that build these things
You have a you have a good shot you want to volunteer you don't want to get paid
I want to become a statistic as one of the workers that died. Yes
15 workers that yeah
Send your family $8,000 when you die
Loves being in harm's way
You know tell me your new new work
Adventures my line of work. Yeah, I did a stop a kid from stabbing his dog. That's pretty awesome
I was walking to the kitchen. I see him hunched over like doing this
I'm like, what the fuck are you doing? And then so the dog is a chihuahua and then what he had was like
Like this needle like like that trying to status. It wasn't like a knife, but it's a chihuahua. That's basically a knife
You don't need a knife for a chihuahua. It's over and then I was like, what the fuck bro. What are you doing?
And I go over there to like stop him then he turns it on me
But little did he know, MMA black belt, Brazilian Jiu Jitsu, Disarm, Headlock, Armbar
And then I give it to like, um, his mom or something and then all they said was Jeepers.
I was like, "Try to kill your dog." I was like, "Okay."
Your mom said Jeepers?
Yeah.
Come on, bro.
She said Jeepers.
Try to kill your fucking dog.
This would be so much worse if it wasn't a chihuahua
Yeah, like if it was like a golden retriever or something, you would probably feel worse
It's like I died. I see those doctors up
Like a disposable dog
Like it's me. It is. Yeah, I
Agree they're loud. They don't live. They live a long time actually do the ballet 18 months
In your house they do and in this kid's house. I think I think it's your wall is I
Like every dog maybe except it's you all I think I think that's the only one
I'm not so much a fan of Chad had chihuahuas when we were growing up and they were
Disgusting they would just sit there. They would shit one would shit into the other ones directly into their mouth
It was just they were the worst dogs ever
They were disgusting dude, then one dog would be taking a shit the other would come a lick his asshole and
They were like brother and sister
Nasty man, yeah had a friend who they thought they were adopting like some kind of like terrier or something
There's a chihuahua pit bull mix man, which is just that's a
Yeah, that thing would just get so mean so aggressive every single time you walk into the house just immediately try to attack
like they're doing anything about it, but
Who's having that with like attack or a needle, you know, then that's fine. Not saying I would step in that fast, but I
am I
Used to babysit these kids who had a they had a lizard
They had a I don't know what kind of lizard was a bearded dragon. That's what they had
Have you ever seen a bearded dragon?
It's a disgusting, loveless pet to have.
They cost an insane amount of money and then you have to feed them live roaches.
So I take the job and then like first day they're like, "Yeah, this kid, he's going to
practice fencing.
The other one's going to practice violin."
You pretty much just sit there and you give them cheese that's when they want them.
I was like, "Okay."
And then day two I show up and they're like, "Oh, also you have to take live roaches with
Tweezers out of this cup and feed them to this disgusting
animal and
it was
It was terrifying. I hate bugs. Yeah, of course I had to
Well, it was 17 bucks an hour man. I did it for like six months. That's crazy
Yeah, it was not so good escape and attack you happen all the time not attack me
but they would fall I would be so disgusted I would hold the cup like way far in front of me and
Sometimes close my eyes and I also would never use the tweezers that I was supposed to use
I would just dump them eyeball it out of the cup. And yeah, they probably have a crazy
African roach infestation because I was just dumping roaches all over the floor all the time
I would just throw it which is like a couple like this and just like go like this
I just hopes it hope it falls near the
The lizard so I should have done
That was disgusting man, I do not miss babysitting at all as a job
Yeah, I don't blame you. Yeah
The cheeses were for the kid and I say cheese it's they weren't even cheese it they everything they had was healthy
I used to steal food from them
I used to bring a Tupperware in my backpack and steal like three quarters of a gallon of milk from them
Because they had a really expensive nice milk and I couldn't afford groceries
is
I'd take my bag and throw it in my bag and then I'd get home and just so drunk after a show
come home and drink milk and eat cheese.
Just sitting all night.
Yeah it was really, actually I kind of liked babysitting now that I think about it.
It was kind of fun as fuck.
Why'd you stop?
Well, because of a little virus called COVID-19, man.
That's right.
I had to stop all my jobs and I had to move home.
And I had to meet you.
Rex, are you vaccinated?
Vaccinated in what way?
That means no.
That fully means no.
Against COVID?
I took one Johnson & Johnson shot.
Is that the one and done one?
Yes.
That gave people crazy bodies or something?
Okay.
How many are you supposed to have is my actual honest question.
Are you supposed to have 100?
I think 100.
100 or 150 they want people to have now.
Yeah.
Okay.
I stopped at, I had one and then I had one booster.
But not, no, sorry, I had one and then-
You were supposed to get two or three?
You're supposed to get two shots or three shots and I whatever I didn't finish the last shot
whatever it was.
Yeah.
I didn't do it because I was like I'm probably good enough.
Got COVID three times.
The thing is you don't even get COVID anymore.
You just get the flu now all the time.
That means you have a long COVID mate.
No dude everyone is sick right now.
With COVID?
Everyone in the world is sick right now.
the
and
version of COVID that just murders mice. Yeah, I'm pretty excited for this one too.
Which nothing's ever escaped one of these labs so that's at least a little bit of a
nice relief. But yeah that's pretty that's pretty awesome. I mean it's gonna
happen again pretty soon I think. Yeah it's just gonna happen forever. It would
be so sick if it happened again. I'd love it. You'd love it? I had such a
good time. We played games all day every single day. That is true. We became
- Did they give you guys checks?
- Oh yeah, oh you, I don't know.
Did they give you checks?
Did you get COVID stimulus?
- Me?
- Yeah.
- Oh no, I didn't get anything.
- Nothing?
Oh my God, I got like five grand.
- I got like, I think when COVID happened,
I was at my old job and I was already getting paid like shit
and then they sent us all home, we were working from home
and then they were like, yeah, we're also gonna dock your pay
to like half or like less than half.
So I was pretty much making no money
And that's why I started streaming
and I'm playing more something every day.
And yeah, it was really bad money-wise,
but I was living with my dad,
so I didn't really feel it much.
- That's the thing, you'd be moving back in with your dad
if it happened again.
Because the podcast would be over.
It's over.
If anything bad happens in the world,
we're always teetering right on the edge of quitting.
So, this podcast would probably survive.
We'd be doing this forever and ever.
We're getting more and more guests.
More and more guests eventually, 100% podcast.
Yeah.
Everybody having the same Discord background repeating
because there's only like six of them.
Of course.
Yeah, this...
You gotta start doing the custom ones with GIFs and funny images.
I usually do, but guys, my Discord Nitro has run out.
I hate to say it.
My discord nitro is gone.
Five dollars a month, it is one beer a month.
I'm not paying five bucks a month.
Yeah, you know what I'd rather have, man?
The beer!
Everybody always says that.
Oh, it's the same as a beer, same as a coffee.
I love beer, I love coffee.
You could go a month minus one coffee.
No, I couldn't.
Everything in my life would fall apart.
That would be a domino effect.
Many people's lives would be over
if I skipped one coffee a month, one beer a month.
I agree with Caleb on this one.
This is like the people playing for Twitter blooping,
like you can just pay,
are you not gonna pay for the app to use the most?
Which I think is ridiculous.
- Well, that's like a reasonable thing.
- It's like eight bucks.
- Not for me, I don't care about that.
- Hi, Chad. - Okay.
- They have a, you think, are people still doing that?
People are still like, oh, I don't wanna support Twitter
'cause Elon Musk is--
- Yes, dude.
people fucking call him a nazi every day
oh my god who can
you get it
you guys are not the mix the coolest cars in the world
yeah they don't even work
he makes the most amazing cars ever
i think i used to be a tesla hater too but then i had an uber where i was in
one
and i it took me about fifteen minutes to open the door
and i was like you know what this is what a car should be
you know well you know what's worse than that a kia or a honda
where they open too good and people steal them.
Exactly.
And also, people say, oh, the cars explode.
You know what other cars explode?
Every car.
Most people die in car accidents, giant explosions
where their heads fall off.
OK?
This is not a point against these cars.
These are amazing cars.
Everybody should buy one of these cars.
And they look badass, man.
The Cybertrunk, this is the coolest car ever.
I love that Cybertrunk.
The Cybertrunk, it looks amazing!
Why are people hating on these fucking cars?
Yeah, I'm with you man.
Somebody had to do something, cars are getting out of hand
in the way that they've looked the same for 20 years.
Yeah, well I personally
I thank him for his latest invention,
the app that spawns
naked women
under every single tweet reply.
He made everything better!
He made everything better, everything I need is in one app.
Oh, I'm looking at a recipe.
Oh, there's a woman's asshole.
That is it's one single one-stop shop for everything. Oh, this is what I did today though. Yeah, you can do me today
And it's just them
Thank you, ma'am
I do really like how bold they're getting with the the porn Twitter replies where someone will be like
So my guys my grandpa passed away and then the first response I'm alive in my pussy has not been eaten in four minutes
Here's a picture
I sucked his cock
Did I said one today where it's just like I think it was just like a picture of a guy
I mean it may have been a streamer, you know, it was like, you know a kind of viral tweet. So if of course you have like
Porn bots or whatever but one of them was just a woman asking like am I supposed to know this is and you can clearly tell
That it's the profile of like an OnlyFans woman. That's like, okay
Who's gonna click on your tweet being like, oh is that but it just works
This is the biggest industry in the world
Well, maybe not but it's up there I
Mean as far as I know it the ads are getting awesome. The ads on Twitter have gotten so amazingly good
It'll just be like on X. I'm sorry. It'll be a picture of a 60 year old guy
Who's got he's like covered in honey and he paid $5 to make sure that a hundred people saw it
Now it's getting to the point people I
Will be scrolling. I'm not gonna say who but I've been scrolling on Twitter or Instagram and I've seen ads
from people that I know
who paid to have their
their posts promoted
but they're not
They're not like oh here I'm doing a show at this time. It's just like a picture of them. Yeah, isn't that crazy?
Who would do that? Okay. Well, I mean I did that but that was just you know, I'm not gonna say who Wow, you know
I won't say who so you hate me. I look good in this pic, you know, just
And sometimes it's people that I follow and it's like I would have seen the photo anyway
Yeah, I think it's a even better than that
I like how you can't ever tell what when you go into replies you can't tell what's an actual reply and what's like an like an ad
Like Rex linked me like some fucked up video like this this week
And I was like it was really it was a shocking video
I was like, ah damn and I was scrolling the replies and like one of the first ones were just a guy
Quoting himself promoting his own post about like a tank
You know, it's like oh, it's just an ad. I just click it. It's just a reply
is like look at my post about a tank under someone's video.
That's kind of badass though. I'd like to see photos of tanks more.
It is so funny how like you go like every viral post has a million sub viral posts under it now.
It's like meant for like your brain to just turn off and forget that you're
in the replies to a different post. It's like a new timeline under every viral post.
It's smart man, it gets me every fucking time.
It does.
I look at all these photos.
I get, I've been fooled, we've talked about this before, I've shown you the proof.
I've been fooled by every fucking Instagram message I've ever gotten, man.
I mean I'm responding to all of these women and it turns out that they're all fake.
And I'm not even looking for sex.
I just want friendship.
friendship and I mean if you go to my hidden requests on Instagram I mean all
these group chats man and I I'm like oh group chats are cool my phone isn't
working but then I talked to these women a little bit they're trying to sell me
stuff and make me go on different websites yeah and that's something like
looking through stories and you see an ad for a hundred dollar piece of meat
and you're going oh let me get that I guess here in a week can I have that
it
and then they'll say pick me up baby and shake my pussy
which is not... and I go I
don't think I'm so interested in that
I'm single and available for
any activity so I say okay would you like to go have some lunch on Thursday
and then they say watch me naked
rude
little forward a little rude that's a thing
What happened to manners, right?
What I do to be nice?
Why not directly contact me right now?
I like a man with a big penis and sturdiness.
Man, you're in the wrong place, baby.
Yep, I'm sorry, I can't provide either.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I have neither.
I'd like a gentleman to talk to.
Now that, that one I haven't responded to, but if you need a gentleman, I'm here.
And that's my message to every single one of these women
You're a gentleman. I'm a gentleman, right? So I'm not if you're gonna say
watch my watch my big ass and
And shake my pussy. Well, look at my bubbles. Like I get I get these messages every day. Look at my bubbles. I have three
I'm not gonna look at your bubbles, but we can talk about philosophy and literature
It's more the wave I'm on
Okay, I have to go join one of these video chats actually
Thank you so much to all my guests for joining me today, I'm the host thank you to my guests
I'm the host my for it's been an amazing time on beers. We drank
Tomorrow today tomorrow
Tomorrow in Tampa, Florida and Saturday in Tampa, Florida
Where my Tampa heads out where my Bush garden family out at?
Come out to these shows guys. They're gonna be so awful man
perhaps
GWA after this
Previously
Appointment with someone else you have an engagement never an engagement prior and I don't
Well, not for a little bit.
You got some money to burn, man.
Let's do it.
All right.
Bye, y'all.