[Sipping]
[Burp]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer podcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[Burp]
This is a journey into sea,
into the middle land,
Bud Light.
Ha!
Food ribbon!
Beers we drank, motherfucker, with Juvio, Caleb, and Rex.
Yo.
Hold on.
Wait.
Are we starting?
Yeah.
Oh.
That was a sick one.
OK.
Wait.
[INAUDIBLE]
He says, are we starting?
Then he pulled out scissors.
- What are you doing? - You're gonna cut your hand off.
What the fuck is this? Oh, he's using a bottle opener?
I guess Rex has been in New York for such little time
that he can't even have a bottle opener in his entire apartment.
I thought we had one and we don't.
Okay, I was gonna break the bottle there.
- I'm gonna fuck up my own. - I kinda fucked up my own.
You almost got it, man.
You're really, really close to getting it.
- I don't think I will. - Don't use your fingers, bro.
Before I finish this, I'll introduce my beer.
Go ahead.
Today I got a Brewdog, Brewed in Elon.
It's an Elvis juice.
Whoa.
I'm paying respect to my favorite musician.
I don't know if you like him that much.
That looks pretty good.
That has to give me a taste.
It has the complete American flag on it.
It's not the complete thing.
I don't see all 50 stars.
Oh, it tastes like fucking shit.
It tastes like shit?
- Tastes like shit.
- This is a complete under five foot basketball player.
- Under five?
There's never been a basketball player under five feet tall.
This is a terrible, terrible review.
- Yeah.
- You clearly never played basketball in Mexico.
- Oh, true.
- Yeah, it's just like a--
- They're Michael Jordan.
- Like a WNBA star.
- Dude, oh my God, you got it off.
Okay.
(laughing)
- Grapefruit, if you use IDH, don't ever buy this.
If you're using--
- Well timed.
You're brown bagging it?
- Why are you brown bagging it?
- Because I get to do an epic reveal.
- Did you do a, you did a 40?
- No, I just did a 22.
I have a giant Heineken.
- Nice, dude.
Wow, you really are New York City vibes.
- I went to three different delis.
And yeah, this was, first of all,
I went to three delis and two of them
didn't have beer at all.
- What?
- I know.
One of them had a child working the register.
- A lot of them, oh yeah. - Just a straight up boy.
- Yeah, a lot of them. - Well, that makes sense
why that one wouldn't have beer, I guess.
- Were they full halal places?
- No, shitty delis.
And that one I went to-- - There's one in New Orleans
all halal, no beer at all.
- No.
So I went to another one and they had six packs of stuff.
They had a sour monkey, which I almost got.
They had the Sapporo Reserve, which you got the other time
and I made fun of you for it.
So I thought, what beer do they have
that we've never done before?
And there are two options.
Hard Arizona Iced Tea or Heineken.
You made the right choice.
I went for the Heineken.
Yeah.
All right, tell us how the Heineken tastes.
Give me a Heine review right now.
Out of the ground bag.
You fuck Heineken?
I like Heineken.
So, six five, dude.
Six foot five player.
Really?
- Yeah, all right, now get now out of 10.
- Like a solid 6.5.
- Whoa, 6.5 on both, that means a 10 for you
is a 10 foot tall player.
- No.
- That's what you mean.
- That's what I meant.
- 10 foot tall basketball player.
- A 10 is like a seven foot six player,
just like a Yao Ming with extensions.
- So you think that six five is the exact intersect,
where they both do the exact same point?
- Yeah, just an above average.
- I can see that, that makes sense.
I have the Flying Dog Deep Fake Non-Alcoholic IPA, y'all.
Deep Fake Non-Alcoholic IPA, y'all.
And here comes my review, y'all.
- Here comes my taste, y'all.
- Y'all, my taste is, this is a light
and refreshing little number.
I'm gonna give this on the non-alcoholic review scale.
Guys, we're breaking eight.
We're gonna go with an 8.1,
aka a six foot 11 basketball player.
This is a great beer.
I recommend all of you sober gophers try one of these,
grab one of these off the shelf.
You won't be disappointed.
It has notes of citrus, less than 0.5% alcohol by volume.
Wouldn't say it really tastes anything like an IPA,
but it looks like a beer, it feels like a beer.
- Can I ask you a question about this,
about your brand new non-alcoholic meter?
- Yeah.
- Do any non-alcoholic beverages enter this category?
- Well, it's really funny that you should say that.
- Like, can you put water and soda in there?
- It's really, it's honestly so fucking funny
that you would say that.
- And milk?
- Because.
- Can you drink some milk?
because I do have another beverage here.
And it is non-alcoholic.
And I would like for you guys to guess what it is.
- Is it milk?
- It's not that crazy, but it's crazy
that you brought up other, I was gonna drink this after,
but I'm gonna review these back to back, okay?
- Okay.
- You each have one guess what this is.
- I guess milk.
- Milk. - Milk.
- Banana milk.
- Ugh, if I can get it open.
- You need some scissors.
- Oh my God, this is so hard, what the fuck?
You need to handle some scissors. Oh, what is what are Logan Paul and ksi doing with these lids? Oh
It's a complete it's an American prime it won't fucking open though. Holy shit. Oh
All right. All right. I got it open y'all
I got open the ice pop prime 20 calories 10% coconut water
Let's give this thing a taste.
Caleb had such a difficulty opening this that it completely crashed the entirety of the SinkGaster site.
I did. I dropped my phone or my microphone, which is my phone in a way.
I dropped it onto my computer.
My apostrophe phone.
Yeah. And this, guys, this is, hmm.
That's good, man.
A lot of people say it's too sweet.
I like it.
Do you think all the primes are going to get sued and banned soon?
Yes, I have. And seeing that the FDA is doing an investigation into Prime has made me drop my intake of Prime down to maybe one every two weeks, where at one point I was drinking them at least every other day for quite some time.
I thought that you'd be a well, actually, I guess that'd be more like a Rex move, where if you heard rumblings of them, like banning something,
You would buy a bunch of them.
You would buy like a hundred boxes of them and just drink them over the next 10 years.
I really want to avoid getting any kind of cancer,
especially bone cancer.
That really scares me because it makes your bones spiky.
And brain cancer as well, because then I can never,
I feel like people will always think I'm a little stupider
after I successfully recover from brain cancer.
We did, I had an employee that was in an accident,
and he was in a motorcycle accident.
He had a brain injury and he was an actual,
he moved down from like a normal productive guy
to a literal like,
retarded guy.
(laughing)
- Is this a recent,
you've only had employees for like two years,
this can only be like 10 guys, man.
- Yeah, he is like one guy,
he worked for like three months.
He kind of looked like Bobby Moynihan.
He was like in his 40s.
- Okay.
The first time I ever talked to him,
we were like going over some stuff,
and just in the middle of like talking,
just pulls out a joint and starts smoking it,
like on camera.
- Whoa.
- And I was like, I'm fine with that,
but also, shouldn't you like say something?
- I would say that that is probably more damaging
to his brain than any 80 mile an hour
head on collision could possibly be.
- Also, wait, what do you want me to say?
You want to be like, sir, permission to talk, sir.
- Permission to do drugs right in front of you
right now.
Permission to join.
You want to do it?
Why?
Like, hey, is it cool if I smoke?
Would you care if you're
just that you're going to be
addicted? You're not smelling it.
Who gives a fuck?
Yeah, but I want to hit I want to
smoke and I have to be the good
smart guy.
You work in the most bullshit
field that exists.
You work in the most bullshit.
No, I don't.
Broadcasting has been around for
100 years before we started
Chuck E. Cheese Monopoly money.
Fake job accusations and they end up splashing me.
Let's go over the meat of today's episode.
Guys, Rex has completely moved to New York.
He has.
I'm sitting in my crevice.
Is that crevice behind me?
Is this your office?
Well no, this is my bedroom. This is my door.
And this is where my closet is.
This is the full length of my closet.
I still haven't been over.
Let's see the entire room.
It'll be really quick.
So here's the closet.
Okay, with the green there, a green cape, you're a superhero.
Got my AC there.
Got my air mattress there with my single unclothed pillow.
Blackout curtains.
Yeah, I'm going to be in the closet.
I'm going to be in the closet.
Blackout curtains.
And then we're going to the last wall.
Mm-hmm.
And that's it.
You're missing a wall, buddy.
There it is.
That's nice.
There's the door and the wall.
The whole room.
So that's everything.
That's the whole room.
That's a tiny room.
It is very small.
That's OK.
You're not a big guy.
You don't need a bunch of space.
You also don't make a whole mess.
You also don't live--
Yeah, the smaller your room is, the less messy it'll be,
'cause there's not enough room to put a bunch of bullshit.
But also, how excited are you to not be living
in a in-between space that is not really a bedroom,
that people just walk through all day?
That is very nice.
It's nice having a door.
And I can see it has a lock on it.
Yes, and I have a second bedroom that is mine,
which is where I'll put my desk and office stuff.
Whoa.
So I won't be in here the whole time.
This is just a sleeping room.
Right.
But because I don't have a desk, I am just, I just have a chair and a bed and a laptop.
And this is the bigger of the two rooms?
No, but this is the one with more natural light that I put blackout curtains in front of.
Speaking of natural light, can you tell the story that you told me the first day you got
to New York when you took your nap?
Yeah, I just was like waking up and staring at, making direct eye contact with
pedestrians because my room is like on the street.
And then, uh, when I was putting the curtains up, I got one of those like
tension rods that you like twist.
Yeah.
And I was kind of standing on like the sill of the window and like holding it up.
Like, you know, like this, my arms were behind me.
So my dick was like the furthest out point.
And as I was doing that, I hear like the sound of like talking and I look down
and there's a dad and his daughter directly in front of my crotch.
- Just with your dick and balls right between their faces.
- Yeah, basically, yes.
Just like against the window.
- Were they taking pictures with it,
like it was some kind of landmark?
- They were tourists.
- They were like up against the,
they were like, "Oh!"
Taking it with a selfie stick?
- I think I was,
dad like made eye contact with me,
and was like.
- He shook his head too?
- He was approving, "It's your room!"
- Yeah, bro.
- It's not your fault that you're completely naked
with your dick out and your balls out?
I wasn't naked, I was fully clothed, but it was just, you know.
- You're gonna have to get used to this, man.
New York City, you see naked people
through windows all the time, man.
- Yeah.
- The only thing is, you need to make sure
if you see a naked person, or if you're naked,
and you see somebody sees you naked,
it's fine as long as you never, ever see them on the street.
- Yeah, he lived in my building.
- The dad does?
- Yes.
- Oh, that was your first impression
with your new neighbor?
- Yeah.
- Is that you showed your dick to his daughter?
- Again, everything was covered.
- I don't think, wait.
- Covered in jizz and piss.
- I completely don't think this matters at all.
I don't think building neighbors are real neighbors.
- I agree.
There's a fat guy that lives across the street
that I, I think I've said this before.
I have, he doesn't have a blind on one of his windows
and it's the window that is directly in front of the fridge.
So I always just see him butt ass naked,
walk up to the fridge and eat food in the middle of the night.
Yeah, like drink out of a gallon of milk.
But I've never seen him.
I've never once seen him anywhere outside of his house.
And I walk around all day.
Do you think he's these pawns where you leave your apartment?
I think he kind of does.
I mean, it might be a it might be a screen.
It might not even be a window.
Somebody might have a TV up against one of these windows.
That'd be kind of funny.
Yeah.
That's someone's face.
By helping you.
Yeah. I mean, that'd be that's about
the funniest thing you can put in a
fake window, probably.
I mean, it would only work for one.
My favorite memory of looking through
someone's window.
Well, I got two, I guess.
The second one is when I was walking
through Amsterdam, you can just like
look into people's houses and like
just look at their living rooms and
how they're living in their lives,
which I didn't really I don't really
know how Europeans live at that point.
So that was I learned a lot
from just looking into people's houses.
And my first, my top number one window peeping into memory
is when we're on that train stop
with that looks over into someone's bedroom
and he's always playing Overwatch.
- Yeah, that guy's always playing Overwatch.
- That guy is--
- What, damn, what stop is that?
- Is it Myrtle?
I forget what it is.
- No, no, it's the,
Maybe it is the Myrtle Avenue M.
Yeah, it's a complete M stop.
There's a guy who's always playing Overwatch at his computer.
And he's always playing it every single night.
And we want to be friends with him, but I don't think there's any possible way
where we can link up with him, although I wish we could so far.
Have you watched the John Wilson episode where the guy
He's talking about like having the train in his backyard.
He just like opens the door and he's got the train there.
I don't think so.
I was wondering if that was the same guy.
I think it's the second episode of the new season.
No.
You think it's, you think it's like the Overwatch guy?
Yeah.
Cause he's like a young guy and it's like the correct angle to
be like looking up into the train.
Does he have a sick computer?
It doesn't really show it.
It shows like him talking in his room and then it pans to like
looking out the window and it zooms in on a guy standing at the train station.
It honestly could be.
It could be because John Wilson lives in this neighborhood.
A lot of that show is this neighborhood.
So maybe he was sitting there one day and he said, I'm
going to go talk to that guy.
That's what I was thinking.
Could be man.
He beat us to it.
We could have made a TV show out of that.
Yeah.
I mean, safe to say if I was.
I would not be talking to John Wilson.
If I was making that TV show, it would be, there'd be a lot,
but I mean, I'd probably get distracted by stuff pretty easily.
I probably wouldn't find anything interesting. It would probably just be,
it would be just like,
my mistake is that I'd start filming one time when I was like really hungry and I
would just film like into restaurant windows, people eating, people making food.
I want to do like puppy eyes. Yeah. Or I would do, I would just get,
I'm pretty obsessed with the idea of like a, like a Christmas, Christmas Eve.
and you look into everybody's windows
and everybody has, it's all kids opening presents
and then hugging their parents
and you get really like upset about it,
you know that thing?
- Yeah. - People doing movies?
- Yeah, like you're alone and you're cold
and you're walking around like this.
- You're the ghost of Christmas past?
- You could do a John Wilson thing
from the ghost of Christmas past perspective
pretty easily I think.
You have icicles forming on the end of your nose
'cause it's so cold.
They have a warm hearth in their house.
- Yeah.
- I think if you were ever to appear in John Wilson,
I think you would be just walking down the street
with your shorts that show your balls.
(laughing)
- Which shorts?
Because I, okay, so I have two pairs of pants right now.
Well, I think I got rid of the shorts that show my balls.
I have two pairs of pants right now
that have big rips in the crotch
and they've only gotten bigger.
And then I have another pair of pants where the fly is broken
and it's just permanently down.
And I just keep trying to zip it up and it just comes down.
And the other day, I like,
somebody was borrowing something from the office
and he brought his girlfriend to the office.
And I was like, "Hey, nice to meet you,"
you know, introduce myself.
And she was like, "Just so you know, your fly is down."
And instead of saying like, "Oh, thank you."
I just like a psycho, I said, "I know."
(laughing)
I know.
Oh, I don't know.
And then you already know.
And then she left.
And I was like, yeah, it's weird.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah, I walk around my fly down all the time.
Just kind of thing I do.
It's my style.
I think I'm bringing you back.
Yeah.
No, you they're bringing it's called dance fashion.
They're going to take you down.
Yeah.
Fly down shoes on the wrong feet.
Opposite feet, shoes.
Yep, just a big potato sack.
Have you ever thought of just changing your entire wardrobe
into just wearing a bunch of wooden barrels?
Yeah, it would fit, I think, with my whole apartment's kind of aesthetic.
Yeah.
Actually, I think completely, yeah.
It's so aesthetic when you're wearing your wooden barrel.
Barrels are expensive. They're like $300.
They are expensive because they're hard to make, man.
They're hard to make and they're durable.
You try to bend wood like that.
It's tough.
I can.
Oh, it's very, very tough.
I wouldn't be able to.
So, day three of New York City.
Day two.
Day two of New York City.
How are you feeling?
What are you thinking so far?
What are the things you find are different living here?
What's going on, man?
So, today I had a chill day.
I worked.
I ate some Indian food, tried an Indian place down the street.
It's really good.
Okay.
I passed out for two hours after eating the Indian food, because it was so heavy.
I woke up, I did some more work and now I'm podcasting.
So I've had a really short day, all things considered.
This is a classic New York City, New Yorker day.
You're working, you're eating takeout and you're falling asleep and then you're
podcasting at the end of the day.
Yeah.
I mean, this is just about...
Yeah, just about as New York as it gets.
Do you think that your sleeping schedule is better suited for the East Coast?
Yes, because when I wake up at 1 in the afternoon, it's like if I woke up at 10 back in California.
So no one gets mad at me when I sleep in.
They're like, "Wow, you're up so early today."
Yeah, I do.
Well, also...
Whenever I'm in New York, I feel like I'm ahead of everyone in the world.
It's a weird feeling.
It is.
Also, the fact that, again, your house or your bedroom is not a place where people have to
walk through all day means that less people will be mad at you for sleeping in.
Yes.
And just like no one is waking me up.
So it is nice.
Yesterday, we went to get those chicken katsus, and I looked up the best way to get home,
and it was like taking a bus.
So I walked to the bus station and I missed it by like one minute and the next bus didn't
come for like 20 minutes.
So I just walked the rest of the way home.
Had a nice walk, walked into a babe store just like on the way.
Just kind of like having a nice time seeing all the people.
Only like three guys stopped me and asked me for money.
And I said to each of them like, "Hey man, I'm not bullshitting.
I really did forget my wallet."
I'm like, "No, we take Apple Pay."
And I'm like, "I'm still uploading in class."
You know, like...
But this is a nice time.
It's like a nice hour, like 30-minute walk.
Nice.
I'm happy for you.
I'm really happy for you, actually.
Yeah, I've walked more in the last like three days
than I did probably in the last like two weeks when I was living here.
Yeah, you walk a lot, man.
You get a...
And it feels fine.
The first two weeks i first moved here i had my legs hurt so fucking bad all the time those just walking so much but you get used to it.
Yeah the shin splints in the.
The good the girl and nothing beats sitting in traffic for a for a whole hour just to go for like twenty kilometers or about about ten miles i guess.
Is that what you do?
It's awesome.
I know.
Well, guess who would never guess who would not know that feeling right now?
Boo.
This guy, my fucking ass, because my car,
since I last talked about this, my car had been booted, right?
My car got booted.
It has now been impounded by the city.
And I've had my they have taken the tags,
the license plate off of my car and destroyed it.
What? Because my registration was out
and I owed so much money that they destroyed my license plate.
Oh, I thought they destroyed the car.
No, they did not. They did not.
I wish I wish I fucking wish that they took my car
and turned it into those cubes.
I want that cube so bad.
It's worth so much more to me than this fucking Ford Focus.
They want me to pay $2,400 to get my car back.
Is the car even worth that much?
Yeah, dude, it has like it has like 98000 miles on it.
It's a 2009 Ford Focus.
I looked up like $3000.
I mean, it's probably worth $5000.
And I looked up I was but I had the same thought.
I was like, I wonder what I can get for like a similar price.
The only car that I could find that was like available for like cash
purchase was like a 2004 Toyota with 220,000 miles on it.
That's probably a nicer than your Ford.
Toyota's are still good.
Toyota's are go forever, probably.
Toyota's 100 should completely go forever.
I don't know. Ford Focus dies at 110.
All right.
Well, the problem is, guys, I already fucking paid the money, OK?
I have no money at all.
Me and my wife are broke.
We ate hot dogs for dinner because we're trying to not spend money on food.
I'm so sorry, man.
This is the lowest point of my entire life.
My car is in God knows where in Flushing.
It's probably rats jumping all over it, homeless people touching it.
It's peeing inside of it, peeing into the engine.
I'm going to pee all in every single part of my car.
There's going to be a rat's nest in it.
It's going to look like they took it out of the water.
Except the water was yellow.
And to top it all off,
When I finally pay this shit and I only paid like 75% of it,
I've got to pay the other 25 at some point.
But after I've everything paid tomorrow, I get the car towed.
I can't even get it towed to there.
They won't even let me just pick it up because it doesn't have a license plate on.
I have to get it towed to my friend's driveway
and then tell him that it's my house and then they'll let me take it somewhere
or they'll at least just leave it.
Once I get all this shit done, the fucking car still has a spare tire on it because I've had to replace the tire for a week.
So then I'm going to finish all this shit with the car and then still have to fix the fucking car.
Yeah, it is just I I'm at a loss for words.
I I need this prime so, so badly tonight.
Hmm. That's good.
I'm taking a load off.
You know what we need?
We need several angel investors just to fund our lives.
I agree. I agree.
I will do anything I will do.
Again, anything I mean, I will do anything.
I just want money.
I don't have any money.
My life is over.
Everything's falling apart.
I just had to
I had to talk to a garbage man today for an hour and a half.
Oh, it's just been a bad week, y'all.
I'm sorry to say. Yeah.
Well, that sounds really bad.
It's like a real bummer.
But I'm sorry to say, actually, that I've had actually a worse week
because two of my best friends just this week alone
when completely viral
and I have not even gone a little bit of barrel at all
this week.
That is tough.
I'm sorry, man.
Listen, I hate when my friends leave
me behind.
My friends,
Rex, did
some sort of like
crime against the world.
Caleb died
and everyone's like talking about
him. But what about me?
I am the one that cares the most
about going viral and no one even
wants to talk about me and my
achievements.
OK, so maybe let's cook up a
viral fucking post for you,
bro.
OK, what's how does a post go viral?
You need.
OK, so let's break down what was Rex's viral post, these vapes.
Yeah. So, yeah, well, there was a picture.
So maybe I need a picture.
It definitely needs a picture.
You need pictures. You're not a good enough writer.
Only Caleb can go text viral.
You can't. Yeah, you can't do that.
You need you need a funny fucking photo.
OK, so you could do
maybe you could get attacked like mauled by a like it's some kind of animal and
and then take a selfie and be like.
- There's already a viral post like that right now.
- Oh fuck.
- Really?
- Yeah, there's a hawk that dropped a snake on a woman
and then they both attacked her.
(laughing)
- What?
I haven't heard this story.
(laughing)
I thought I had a bad fucking week.
- That's how Mexico started.
That's how Mexico was funded.
- That is true.
(laughing)
- It's completely true.
She, her arm is completely destroyed.
They destroyed her arm?
They teamed up on the same body part even?
- Yeah.
- Okay, how about this? - It's horrible.
- Wait, how about this?
How about I crash my car and I take a picture of it
and I post it and I caption it,
no more driving much?
Ah, fuck.
Yeah, maybe some grocery stuff.
Grocery stuff always goes viral.
- Grocery stuff would be good.
If you could find a thing inside of a thing
where it's not supposed to be,
if you could get a box of Lucky Charms and find something,
if you could find a rat in a tin of Heinz beans,
that could go mega, super duper viral.
I mean, yeah, we're kind of running out of options here.
If you're not willing to get really badly hurt,
I just don't know what we can do for you, I guess.
- Well, do you guys think I have it in me?
- To go viral?
- I think you can do it.
- Do you think I could go viral?
- I think that, I don't know, you might,
I mean, I feel like if it was gonna happen,
it would have happened by now.
- Yeah.
You might need to screenshot something.
- You could screenshot a text from me.
- You're like, I'm always thinking about this.
- A Tinder message.
- A Tinder message is so, so, so funny to me.
- A Tinder message and it's a girl being like--
- A Reddit post.
- True.
- We could make a fake Reddit post
and then you could screenshot it.
- Yes. - This is what we have to do.
We manufacture this. - Yeah.
- Okay. - Because they're all fake anyway.
So what's the subreddit? - So it should be,
I completely got this.
It's am I the asshole?
It's always am I the asshole?
- Am I the asshole?
There we go.
So what we need to do is we need to do
the ultimate asshole post, okay?
- So it would start with,
I'm, am I, what the fuck?
Am I the asshole?
- I'm the asshole?
- For being a Karen.
- Yeah, am I the asshole?
And then my age is 19 and I'm a girl, 19F.
- Oh, here's what you could say.
Am I the asshole?
I'm 20, my girlfriend is 13.
Am I being an asshole?
- Okay.
- Her parents think I'm a total asshole.
Uh-huh.
Me, male 24, girlfriend F12, on her parents' couch.
And they're mad at me.
Am I the asshole?
Okay.
This is great.
This is going to go mega viral.
People are going to believe this 100%.
Of course they will.
The most important part about going viral is that everyone does not know that.
The most important part about going viral is that everyone does not think at all about
what they read on Twitter, so you need to lie.
You need to come up with a funny lie.
Okay, so here's my follow-up question in Virality Online, say.
So at what point should I sell ads on my replies?
Immediately.
One line.
Because that's how you get the most views.
You get the rose for men, the sucker rose, the thing that sucks on you.
The clit sucker.
I think...
The turbo, gawk gawk, pussy.
You also have to write an update as well because people love the updates on the Reddit post.
I saw people believe truly anything that is posted there.
I saw one a couple days ago that was like, it was like an updated one where it was like
me and my wife are in an argument about this and this and this. I went to my parents' house
and took our kid. Am I the asshole? It was one of those. And then the update was like,
"Guys, my..." And there was a lot of drama involved in it that was already kind of not
believable.
Yeah.
Then the update was like, "Guys, I hate to say this. My wife was so distraught that she
drove the car into a tree and died shortly after I made this post." I was like, "Is that
Really what you think guys whose wives die are doing
is immediately updating their Reddit post to keep people--
- So yes, that is not a typical human reaction,
but a Redditor, a Redditor with a wife,
they're not human, they don't have human instincts.
- Yeah, I think it's completely human to be like,
being like some drama, like something happened in your life
and you're first, or you're like,
one of the first things of yours to be like,
I need to make a, I need to know
whether I'm the asshole or not on Reddit.
Like that is, I don't think there's a single person
who thinks that way in the world.
- Yeah, I don't believe any of those posts.
I don't believe any, am I the asshole?
I don't believe any, today I fucked up.
Those are always like the craziest thing ever.
Those are always like, today I fucked up.
I was doing the dishes and I slipped on dish soap
and my cock went into my sister's mouth.
I fucked up so bad, y'all.
But isn't this some funny shit?
- I like the ones where it's like a,
it's like this like some family drama
and it has like a,
like it's like a really positive ending
and it's like just like a bad movie.
- That's always my, if you're gonna make it up,
why are you making up a good ending?
- Yeah.
- Those might be the only ones I believe, I guess.
Update I kill myself.
- Yeah, that is not, that one's always fake.
If anyone dies, nobody dies at the end of most stories.
- Yeah.
- Especially nobody's lucky enough
to have the ending be a death
after they've already had an interesting enough story
that they posted it on Reddit.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Nobody's dying at the end of these, man.
This is all, it's all fake.
- I feel like if you took a Seinfeld episode
and turn it into an "Am I the Asshole" post.
- Yeah, top of the line. - You could go viral.
- I'm the asshole, I live with my parents,
and I sold my-- - I sold my dad's clothes.
- My dad's clothes. - I lied and said he was dead,
I sold his clothes, and then my friend
wore the clothes from the thrift store
to my parents' house, and they got in a fight.
- I think that would hit on Reddit.
- That would definitely, that is believable.
- That is believable on Reddit.
- Well, it's funny you say that no one believes in it.
Nothing is true on Twitter anymore.
That post that someone made with Rex's picture
made it all the way to Mexico.
And like, some of my girlfriend's friends
were like discussing it in their private DM.
- What was the post?
- No way. - I didn't see it.
- So I posted a picture of like all the vapes
I found in my room.
- Yeah.
And there was, you know, like 10 pounds of them in a plastic bag.
And someone took it and said, like, "My friend is a school teacher, an elementary school
teacher in Southern California, and this is what they've confiscated this month from elementary
schoolers."
People were like legitimately like tagging senators.
Yeah, this definitely made it to some representative's desk for certain.
Yeah.
People in Mexico were discussing about it like, "No way!"
First of all, it's August.
School has not been in for a month.
No one knows when school starts.
Yeah.
I don't even know it was August.
Wow.
Yeah.
And then believing that elementary schoolers vape.
Like, but there's more than one elementary schooler that fakes.
Yeah, elementary school is kind of stretching it, I guess.
Right, middle school, believable.
Elementary school, fiction, obviously.
I feel like the whole post was very obviously fake.
I was getting so many posts that were like, "Yo, most evil man, this dude is using your
posts for misinformation."
And I was like, "It's not his fault that you're all retarded."
I think my favorite part about that post was when someone came into your replies being
like, "At least you should dispose of them correctly."
And you were so petty enough to do a funny reply to them.
And then even out, like way, so many hours after that, you went ahead and you did the
funny reply in real life.
So what happened was this person was like being like, "Oh, you should dispose of them
correctly.
The batteries are going to be a disaster for the environment."
which is like, "I'm just gonna throw him in the ocean." And she was like, "No, you shouldn't do
that." Whatever. I would do the right thing. And then hours passed. I think it was literally the
next day. He posted a picture like, "All right, I'm gonna throw him in the ocean."
Yeah, I walked down to the beach. I went to right where the water meets the sand,
and I just put the bag down. Took a nice beautiful photo.
You should have made a video of you actually dumping them in. It's worth it. I mean,
It's not that big of an environmental impact for that.
It's more funny than it is bad for the environment.
In Long Beach, bro?
I was, but there was people everywhere on the beach.
They're there to do the same thing.
It's fucking Long Beach.
No, they were kids.
I felt horrible.
I was like, I can't dump 200 vapes next to an eight-year-old.
You should have offered them some vapes.
That would have been a funnier video
if you walked around handing them out to the little kid.
- Or like, yeah, put 'em in a candy bowl
and be like, "I'm all set for Halloween."
- Yeah.
(laughing)
That, see, that's the mind of a viral poster.
- Exactly.
- The only question left for me, I guess,
is actually a question from some Mexican representatives
who wanted to know, did you actually finish all those vapes?
Or did you only hit 'em like once and forget about 'em?
- What do you think?
- Did you-- - I think it's a mix.
due diligence and go through every single one to see if they were good.
Every single one.
Yeah.
I found two. You sat there with two piles.
Two of them were still good.
Yeah. Those are the ones that you had yesterday.
Yeah.
Yep.
Yep. There's one right there.
And where did you find that one? Do you remember?
This was in a backpack.
OK. See, that makes sense.
What was the worst?
What was the most surprising place you found a vape in your cleanup duties?
One was beneath the sheets of my bed.
I believe that.
Like between the mattress and the sheet?
Yes.
I completely believe that.
There was one that was tucked inside underwear where I had done laundry.
It was in a drawer.
There was two behind my computer.
The tower itself?
Yes, the tower in between the wall and the tower.
I completely believe all these locations.
Let's see.
There was a bag that I found in a drawer that I had like clearly
started to collect the dead ones in.
So there was like 10 in there and I like kept doing that and I would find
bags with like three to five each.
Like I've got like five different bags where I've been like, I shouldn't, you
know, like keep these all together.
It's like, God, everywhere.
Um, There was like, I cleaned off both of my nightstands and
found seven.
Would you put yourself in the
top one percent most prolific
vapors in the United States?
A hundred percent.
Yeah.
I think it's literally
everywhere.
Yeah. There is no place I will not
vape. A plane.
A bar.
Inside anywhere.
I never stop.
I miss vaping on a plane.
That was always so fun because it's
just so obvious that the people next
you hit you so fucking much.
Yeah.
I waited till the person that was next to me on the plane to fall asleep before I
went.
Hmm.
They had a cherry limeade dream.
Into their mouth completely.
So they also.
The smoke's got to go somewhere.
Yeah.
They got to get off an alarm.
Well, the thing is, is on a plane, you take a little tiny hit, you hold it till
it becomes invisible.
And then you slowly exhale through your nose.
Because getting caught on a plane is a $200 fine.
-Really? -Oh.
-Yes. It's a very big deal. -I didn't know that.
They fucking care.
I was about to say, "What are they going to do? Kick you out?"
Literally, yes.
-They will ban the flying ones. -I think they did.
I think they banned Wardell from JetBlue or some shit
because he posted a video or a picture of him vaping in a bathroom.
I think I think that JetBlue just like banned him for a year or some shit.
Yeah, they take it really seriously.
No, I have a city out faking
vaping on a plane bathroom and produce Photoshop
like a Lufthansa or something like airline they're never going to take in your life.
Yeah, so you get a lot of that and it goes completely viral.
This is actually a pretty good idea.
Yeah. Yeah.
I also think that to make you viral,
We we need to broaden our horizons here a little bit,
broaden our view.
It can it doesn't just need to be on Twitter.
We can think of a Facebook post.
We could think of a tick tock Instagram YouTube short.
I think Facebook is bullshit.
I think tick tock is where I'm going to go viral.
OK, what's your idea for tick tock?
Because that has to be a video or a selection of photos. Right.
I don't know.
I can't think in video.
You could, but also here's the thing with that is that it's tough is that it has to be PG.
You can't have cussing and stuff in those, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, you can.
What are you talking about?
You can cuss in TikToks?
Yeah.
I've seen so much bad shit on TikTok.
It's crazy.
I thought that they like are super heavy moderating it or something.
Like if you cuss in one, then it won't show up on people's pages.
Nope, not at all.
- Man. - You have to use euphemisms
in text.
Say like-- - Oh, right, yeah.
When you use text on the video,
you can't just be typing like,
I'm fucking a pussy with my cock.
- Oh, okay. - Yeah.
- You gotta be like, I'm fucking a--
- Which is very crass, by the way.
- PU55Y for my COCCO. - What's the whole thing
where they, you can't say killed or suicide,
you have to say unalived? - Yeah.
- That is so fucking
freaky to me. - I think that's TikTok.
I think it's really stupid when people assume that any social media is like that.
And they're like typing in like lead language to be like kill yourself.
It's like just type it normal.
Yeah, just be a man.
Yeah, don't be a pussy.
Just be a man and type it normal.
But I get it man.
I used to try to say every word under the sun and get it through the RuneScape sensors.
But those Gowers brothers know what they're doing man.
They would pretty much catch it every time.
Well if someone knows anything about this, this is Mr. Blank over here.
Fanned 17 times on Twitter.
Official world record.
That is a lot of times.
It's a lot of times. It's definitely not a world record.
It's definitely not.
I also made that up. I don't know how many times you've been fanned.
It's like 14.
Oh, that's close.
I'm on gear 3, dude. I'm a good boy now.
You fixed it.
The key is to just never post anything.
Yeah.
Well, the key is not to reply.
Replying is the best.
Because a lot of the times that I would get banned was like,
you'd see someone say some stupid shit
and then have that need,
that deep need to tell them they're being stupid.
Yeah.
You gotta,
[laughs]
you gotta fact check them on Twitter.
Yeah, I need you to literally die for what you just said.
I think the only time I ever got a temp ban on Twitter,
I got a 24-hour ban because I told Patrick, I said, like, shut up, idiot.
I did like I did like a kindergarten
like reply.
I think the first time I ever got banned, I said I was going to karate chop
random guy like I just told karate.
Well, that that means that they consider you're going to be the weapons, man.
Yeah. Wait, can we see?
Can we see one of the chops?
Show us a chop.
Show us your chops.
It's too lethal.
I'll show you a chop.
Hi-yah!
Oh, get that thing away from me!
Don't point that at me!
You just broke my screen!
You spiderwebbed it.
I'm sorry, man.
I didn't mean to.
I can't hold back.
It's too powerful.
You know what we could do, man?
You know what I think is coming back?
What?
I think that in the next two years,
and you guys, this is Caleb's Lock of the Week.
In the next two years,
we're going to see a big resurgence
of a little game that I used to play in the bathroom
called Bloody Mary.
Kids don't remember Bloody Mary.
So if you, you don't know about Bloody Mary?
I'm from a different country, I don't know what that means.
I don't know what that is.
- Hey, dude.
Okay, when we're done recording,
I want you to take a video of yourself.
- Okay.
- Go into the bathroom,
turn off the lights in your bathroom.
- Oh, okay.
- And say, "Bloody Mary, bloody Mary, bloody Mary."
Say it three times, she'll appear in the mirror
and she will kill you.
- I don't think she's gonna do that.
- You never know till you try.
My mom, I told my mom about it when I was a kid
and she did it in our bathroom
And then she locked herself in there
to prove to me that it was fake.
But then she pranked me and said,
"Bloody Mary, Bloody Mary, Bloody Mary."
Turned off the lights and then said nothing.
And I banged on the door
'cause I thought that my mom was dead.
And then she came out laughing.
And me and her, not that great of a relationship these days.
Don't talk all that much.
- Why did that start?
Was it like a movie thing?
- Well, it started when Bloody Mary
attacked somebody in the bathroom
after they said her name three times.
- I don't think that's true.
as far as I know.
- If they are gonna play it now,
they would say Five Night Freddy.
- Five Night Freddy, Five Night Freddy, Five Night Freddy.
- That's his fucking name.
- Freddy Fazbear, Freddy Fazbear.
I think kids are even too young
for Five Nights at Freddy's now.
That's like a 10 year old game.
- Yeah, that's cringe now.
Yeah, but that's cringe now.
- Now they say Baldi's Basics, Baldi's Basics,
Baldi's Basics.
- Not even that, nope.
Now they say Skibbity Toilet.
Skibbity toilet. I think that's fake. I've decided that no it's fake. It's a skibbity toilet.
It's got 10 million, every fucking thing he does has 10 million views.
That's not that much. In like two days 10 million views? What are you talking about? He looks like
Mr. Beast numbers bro. Gangnam style fucking had a billion views okay. That was the biggest video
in the world. Yeah. Skibbity toilet. Oh look I've looked up, here's the two things I've looked up
on my YouTube, Skibbity Toilet and Skibbity Toilet Lore. Skibbity Toilet, season one, all
episodes, 89 million views. That's a lot of views. I wish I could see a graph because I
would like to know how much of that is people our age being like, "What's the deal with
these kids?" 19 hours ago, Skibbity Toilet upload 5.4 million views. Yesterday, Skibbity
toilet upload 21 million views in one day for skibbity toilet 56.
Ok I guess kids are fucking into skibbity toilets.
You went vile one day and now you think you can move over skibbity toilet?
I don't think I'm bigger than skibbity toilet.
Move over skibbity toilet here comes the vape guy.
The vape guy, I'm going to keep posting these with one extra vape every day.
He's going to get more views every single time.
I did get another date.
We need to be doing more Skibbity Toilet content.
Reacting to it, talking about it.
We need the Skibbity Toilet podcast.
Discussing it, yeah.
We can make a Skibbity Toilet, yeah, Skibbity Toilet kind of lore podcast.
The Skibbity Toycast, yeah.
Every time a Skibbity Toilet episode comes out, we do an hour long kind of like talking
dead episode about it.
We have celebrities on, we have Chris Pratt on.
I think people actually do that.
People do that?
- Skibbity Toilet recaps?
- Yeah, they like talk about lore and like--
- Well yeah, the lore, trust me, I've seen the lore video.
He says that basically-- - Why are you looking up lore?
- The Skibbity Toilets have infested the city
and the cameramen are basically fighting
the Skibbity Toilets.
- That's the entire lore? - That's fucking good.
- Yeah, it's not that, I think the guy who made it,
when he first made it, he was like,
"Oh, it'd be funny if there was a head inside of a toilet."
And then all these people started making videos like,
"What does it mean, what does Skibbity Toilet mean?"
and then he decided to make it a whole series.
- I think the thing I hate the most about that
is that I really hate that song.
The "Skibbity Toilet" song.
I don't fuck with it.
- You don't like,
♪ If you see us in the club ♪
♪ You'll be acting real nice ♪
It's a good song.
- Well, that part is like okay,
but then it goes into the funny TikTok remix
and it's really bad.
- Yeah, I don't, whatever language that is,
I do not care.
I don't think it's a real language.
Well, he's just he's just saying, I think it's Turkish.
It's definitely not Turkish.
I think it's literally racist.
No, it's I.
Well, I first heard that song in a Turkish tick tock.
It's like the Turkish guy with a big belly who like
he gets invited to restaurants and he just like starts shaking his belly
because he likes he likes the food so much.
That's not what I'm talking about.
Wait, y'all.
So I completely think this is Turkish.
Sorry, I'm watching Skibbity Toilet 56.
Basically the Skibbity toilets are dropping what looks to be nuclear bombs on the city
and they have a giant Skibbity toilet that has just, well, it obliterated the cameraman.
So this is going to be a really hard fought battle.
A lot of casualties on both sides.
And at this point, you know, it's one of those things where you always think the winners write
history right so we don't know who the good guys are right now in this in this
battle because for all we know in a year from now we'll be saying those skibbity
toilets they those were the good guys the whole time yeah yeah they're the
noble cause you know what I was thinking what they should make Oppenheimer a
playable character in Call of Duty I think he was like a hundred pounds yeah
I think he would get rolled over.
I don't think he was a soldier.
He wasn't.
I don't think he's a killer.
He could spend the whole fucking thing doing calculations.
Do you think?
He could spend the whole game in the back
and then maybe if he calculates...
And then you get 25 kills and then he drops
the atomic bomb.
But you already can get a nuke
from playing the fucking...
No, wait, wait, I kinda get this now.
It would be funny if you bought his skin
like Warzone and he went to do like the special animation on his like backstab
and he's just like he's just making a calculations and he's just like
eventually builds a bomb and drops it on the guy who he backstabbed. I think that's a good idea.
I don't think that this is a very good idea y'all. I think that's a good idea.
I haven't played Warzone in a long time. Me and Rex have been playing Warzone every day for the past two months.
You have not been playing Warzone. Ask me how many Warzone games I've won.
How many victory royales have you had in the last two months on Warzone?
Probably 20.
That's not, you don't even know what the map is on Warzone anymore.
It's...
Oh, good press.
Boards, map.
Boards.
I do wish that I could go back to enjoying that game.
When that game first came out, I loved that game.
I was so terrible at it, but we played it so fucking much.
It was very fun.
That's the reason we're here now.
We owe it all to Warzone.
Warzone is what created this three-headed beast.
Yeah.
That's very true.
What a beautiful three-headed beast it is.
It used to be fun, man.
We used to just drink wine and play Warzone every single night.
Now I'm drinking-
Just the worst period of our lives.
Now I'm drinking Bomb Pop Primes.
My car is somewhere, is in some kind of prison.
My car is in Rikers Island all locked up.
I mean, things have taken a turn for the worst.
I think we should all get into Baldur's Gate 3. I think that that game looks
too hard. How so? It looks too much too hard too much hard. Looks a little too
hard for me. I like easy games where you do the same thing every single time.
There's too many options. I was talking to Cam about this yesterday. Games where you
get in and they don't tell you exactly what to do I hate that shit right
tell me what to do I want to I like it to be on rails I like roller are you
curious at all about the world about the real world yeah I'm not curious about a
pretend world. Okay. I want to be in and out 20 hours. If you want to tell me something about the world, then just tell me. Don't make me find it out on my own.
Exactly. Exactly how I feel. I played that game The Outer Wilds. I liked it for
about three hours until it was like, "There's no dialogue. You have to piece
the story together." I'm not Columbo, buddy. I'm not gonna walk around. If I'm doing
detective work I'm getting paid for it okay I already do enough of that in my
real fucking life I think it'd be funny to like put you like lock you in a room
and make you like stream like one of those like weird like puzzle games like
the overden where it's just like it's like super you like that game yeah the
overden no is that is that not do you have to like look up a solution well
There's a mystery.
There's enough of it.
It's interesting.
Yeah, it at least keeps me,
something like even Skyrim.
Once you, if I'm far enough away
from the main quest line in Skyrim
that it's gonna take me 15 minutes to walk back to it,
I'm turning the game off.
Okay.
I don't wanna do that.
I do not want random encounters.
I do not want to have people run up to me and say,
"Halt, hero.
"I need you to find my watch."
I'll go, "Suck my dick, dude.
"Get the fuck out of my face."
I want Halo 3.
Halo 3 is a good game.
Any of the RPGs are so fucking stupid, man.
These side quests, I never wanna see,
games need to, when games are like,
like with Baldur's Gate, they're like,
There's 180 hours of cinematics.
There's there's you can spend a thousand hours just on the side quest.
I don't want to do that shit, dude.
I want to get to the end.
I want there to be a big red boss.
I want to beat the boss or give up on it because it's too hard
and never play the game again.
Can I can I erase you a counterpoint? Yeah.
There's completely nakedly women in the game.
I'll buy the I'll buy it if if I if it's
Under $200 I'll buy the game
but I'm and if
I can I can Google these naked women and find out what they look like not true and lose
I'll look right now Baldur's Gate all nudity
Baldur's Gate 3 all
Nudity, I bet there's already a porn hub video
Baldur's Gate nudity porn hub
You're gonna get a virus
Balder s gate 3 porn gamer girlfriend plays Baldur's Gate 3 while getting fucked
I don't want wait no old and
Companions cute what the fuck is that video?
Baldur's Gate Dark Alliance extreme mode 1 he's just watching porn
Claire nude full gameplay part one.
I ruined the school's club room forever with a tennis racket.
Did you see a did you see
you see that clip where there was like some some like she fired a tournament
and they didn't turn off the the naked chili mod?
Yeah, I did. I actually just saw that today.
That is so fucking funny.
The Tia just had a naked Chun-Li
mod installed and they like start the game and the guy start the guy
the announcer dude, the match starts and the players know that something's wrong
so they just start walking into each other and the announcer goes like,
"Very interesting, we get the Kimberly pick on the other side."
He's still trying to do announcing for the fucking match.
Just trying to ignore it.
Yeah, and it takes a full 20 seconds before he's like,
"Oh wait, hold on." And then the screen goes black.
Hold the phone!
(laughing)
- It's a really good video.
- I think that's so crazy to be just playing,
fighting, I said this on stream, I was like,
I don't understand at all the appeal of just fucking,
like sucking at a street fighter,
but just like while looking at a naked woman.
- Yeah.
- I'd be so pissed.
I would turn gay.
- Do you know that guy Jason Unruh?
He's like a, he's like a leftist YouTube guy.
It's got like a Mohawk.
Yeah.
So there's a video of him.
He was playing fallout on like stream talking about whatever, you know, lame
politics shit he's on about.
And, uh, he like walks up to one of the NPCs and it just immediately starts to go
to like suck his dick.
He's like, Oh, Oh, no.
and it just like cuts out.
(laughing)
- This is a great Steam community post
by somebody under Baldur's Gate 3.
Sex scenes not explicit enough.
Can we get a mod or something?
(laughing)
- Yeah, let me see some fucking pussy.
- Yeah, well that's the thing.
It used to be, years ago,
it was shunned to show sex and pussy and tits.
And now it's the biggest game of the world.
And everyone is appreciating, is there a crying mouse?
- No, that's a dog with a chew toy.
- Oh, I see.
- He's moving away from the door
so you can continue with your point.
- I forgot what I was saying.
- You were saying it used to be a--
- Years ago.
- Yeah, 10 years ago, we used to have--
(laughing)
- Yeah, there was no tits, no ass, and no balls.
- Yeah.
- Now we have Steve ass, John tits, and Fred balls.
- A viral post.
That's a good way.
Okay, yeah, wait.
Wait.
That's, we nailed it.
Post that right now.
10 years ago, we used to have no tits,
no ass, and no balls.
Now we have Steve ass, Joe dick,
and two hairy balls.
Yeah.
You know?
Post that right now.
Okay, I'm gonna post it right now.
You have to post this.
Okay.
This is such an easy, this is a layup, dude.
- Yeah, slam dunk. - See, one hour,
and that's the kind of thing we can come up with.
- How did this start?
10 years ago, we used to have--
- 10 years ago, you used to have no tits,
no ass, and no balls.
Now we have Steve Tits,
Joe Dick,
(laughing)
- And Harold Balls.
- Steve Tits,
Joe Dick,
- And Harold Balls.
(laughing)
- Okay, this is going, I'm retweeting this shit right now.
This is going so mega viral, you won't even believe this.
- I really wanna be the first post on X to go viral.
- This is going viral as fuck.
This is going to be, this is going to be a...
- Yup.
- This is going to be amazing.
- Your phone's gonna go crazy.
- Yeah, get ready to turn your notifications off.
- Ah, I'm putting it in silent mode, I can't deal with it.
- You can't be bothered with this shit, man.
- I'm gonna be honest.
- What? - I hate the fame.
I hate being the center of attention.
- You just said you want to be addicted to my posts
more than anything. - But I didn't know
what I had when I had it, you know?
I had all this peace in my life.
I had peace and quiet. - It's been destructive.
- My only notifications were my friends texting me,
I love you and I appreciate you all every day.
And now all I get is fucking--
- Like good morning, I appreciate you doing this.
- Oh, Felix Peterman, which is your tweet.
Text you see, send you a DM and call you gay.
Like I don't care about any of this anymore.
- It would be really funny if I started texting you like
XQC.
Like your house is on my wrist.
Well, he's like, he was messaging that guy,
Ethan Klein from like Page 3 shit.
And he's like, your house is on my wrist.
And I think it would be really funny to text Juvio, like your,
your house is on my wrist, but just like an Apple watch.
Well, my, yeah, my rent is just like 300, 300, I think.
So it wouldn't take much.
Yeah, that's not, that's a, you know, it's basically a beginner watch.
I wear your year's rent every day.
It's a T-shirt.
That would be so fucked up.
Rex for the longest time just thought I'd live in like a mud hut.
And whenever he saw me, he's like--
- That's not true.
- I thought you did too, honestly.
- That is not true.
- And whenever I saw him, he would be like,
he would just feel so bad about me.
He's like, man, I'm just, I'm so sorry about your situation.
I'm like, what are you talking about?
- I thought you lived in an upper class teepee for years.
- I didn't think you lived in a mud hut.
I thought you made 11 cents an hour doing slave labor.
- He kinda did.
- I kinda did.
- And that's why I was like,
I'm so sorry about your situation.
- You used to work a full-time job
- And make like 500 bucks a month.
- Yeah. - Yeah, basically, yeah.
- Which is pretty fail.
- And now I'm the richest guy in Mexico.
- Yep, and now you have generational wealth.
- Yeah, I'm gonna buy a car.
- I'm sorry for feeling empathy for my friend.
I actually don't give a fuck about your situation.
- You don't even wear watches.
That would be such a stupid flex for me.
- It bothers me. - You don't wear watches.
Show me your wrists.
- They bother, I hate wearing stuff on my hands.
- Do your watches bother you?
- Yeah, it's uncomfortable.
It bothers me.
- That's an interesting kind of autistic OCD thing to have.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
It is, I mean, that's definitely what it is,
but it does bother me.
- Do you guys wanna be Apple Watch, Apple Fitness buddies?
- I have a really old Apple Watch
that I got from Cameron's fiance.
She sold it to me for $20,
but it doesn't really work very well.
It's like the first one they have.
It basically just tracks your heart rate.
I don't think I can add friends on it.
- Well, that's so sad.
- Yeah.
I'm not rich like you, Jubio.
Where you can buy an Apple Watch every day.
- I don't buy an Apple Watch every day.
- And now you have one of the most viral posts in the world
and you're already getting ad revenue for it.
- Oh my God.
- I mean, this already has 35 likes and six reposts, man.
- I don't even.
- I love that they renamed it to reposts, by the way.
- I love reposts.
What even is a tweet?
They should call it a Musk.
So true.
Call it a Musk right now.
Yeah.
I think-
It has six Musks, six Elans, 36 Elans, and 42 Teslas.
You know?
Three stoplights.
Dude, I see Teslas all the time down here.
You see Teslas down there?
Yeah, I think Elon Musk is on the come up.
My gym is right near a whole lot of Rivians.
You know those cars?
Mmm, yeah.
And they, uh, I don't think they've sold a single one.
It's full every single fucking day.
Well, I think they're expensive as fuck.
Yeah.
There's a secret behind that.
They're really expensive, but if you buy one, you get like $36,000 from the government.
Really?
Yes.
So they're like an electric car.
So you make money just ripping them off.
Yeah, they're like, any electric car.
So they're like $70,000, but then you get like $36,000
back on your taxes.
- That's interesting, 'cause there's a Hyundai, I think,
that is one of the cheaper electric cars
that is like, I think only 50K.
- Yeah.
Yeah, there's like a bunch of like--
- Yeah, the Ioniq.
- Different tiers of like tax rebates you can get.
- Uh-huh.
- I think you should-- - It's like--
- Rex's complete word for this,
I think you should completely look it up.
- 2023 Ioniq 6 sedan, $52,000.
I'm gonna buy it if I'm gonna get a $36,000 rebate.
- Yeah.
- Why don't we just get like a--
Why don't we just get like a--
- They want you to get an electric car?
- Let's get like a team, like a van for a gang, for a team.
- I want one of those new Amazon vans.
Those look cool as fuck.
- Those would look kinda cool.
- They look fucking cool, man.
- I watched a review of it for some reason
And I was like, I'm never gonna be in one of these
or even gonna see them.
We don't get any of this shit down in Mexico,
but it look fucking, it look pretty sick.
- It's fucking badass.
- One of those Waymo Chrysler minivans.
And I wanna sit in the back seat for 20 hours a day
and just get driven around to different places.
- Yeah, so people can touch you.
Yeah. - Yes.
Yeah. - Oh yeah.
- Get paid $20 an hour to watch the car,
Make sure nothing happens.
My whole time my hands
are aren't on the wheel.
It's getting into accidents.
Yes, I remember when my car was total.
They did.
Waymo was like in my area.
They just started to like
Waymo trial and I took it like
everywhere 'cause it was cheaper
than like an Uber 'cause it was like
trial and it was so funny 'cause
it would get like stuck trying to make
like a U-turn or like turn on a red light.
It would be like the.
It'd be like really tented.
Wait, you actually rode in that shit?
Yeah, I rode it because my car was total and I had to like go to like physical
therapy and shit and like all these different places.
Whoa.
Damn.
So they operated in the city I was in and it was like $9 versus like $15.
So you get in, there's like a guy that's sitting there that's like, "Hey, what's up?"
And then you close the door and it just starts and it shows you like-
They still have to have a guy in it?
Yeah, because they can't have a guy that doesn't like, there has to be a guy in the driver's
seat pretending to drive.
He's got his hands on the wheel, his feet are on the pedal, he's got to be ready to
like slam on the gas or turn in case it goes haywire.
I think it's really funny that the thing that Americans have been tackling for the past
like five or six years is how to make like fully like automated driving a thing.
Well, the problem is, so this is when I was living in Arizona,
so I was living in Chandler, but Tempe, which is one city above Uber,
self driving was going on at the same time and it's straight up like mowed down
a pedestrian. Like someone like,
it was like an old woman at 4am jaywalking and it just fucking just cringed her.
And so they were like, "Okay, no more."
Well, don't get nasty with it.
But it turned her into a red goo.
You said that an elderly woman, 90-year-old woman,
you're saying that she got creamed by a car and you're...
Oh, come on, man.
This is fucking...
This is an awful story.
Anyway, it completely murdered her.
I said, "Free fast-free into the mirror at 3 a.m.
and I got creamed."
That's disgusting.
So they stopped allowing all the self-driving car trials down there?
Yeah, I think that's probably a good idea.
I have to go pee, so we're going to end.
Okay, goodbye.
Bye.