There it is. Wait, hold on.
And there it is.
Wait, I had an... Here, I have to do this.
Can you tell me if you guys can hear this?
Uh-huh.
I heard that.
Can you hear this?
Oh my god.
Oh my god, this beer is stinky. I got a stinky one.
Well, boys, cheers.
Cheers.
Alright.
Welcome to beers we drank.
we drank. Let's go around real quick and go through what we have in our right hands. Gbio
is already enjoying it so so much. I'm drinking a stout. What's the brand on that? Minerva.
It's a Mexican brand. It has 6% alcohol. You were supposed to get beer and you got cerveza.
Yeah, that's fucked up dude. You're already ruining the show. Alright, it is cerveza. Well
- Well it stands for beer in Spanish I believe.
- That's what it stands for?
- I'm not entirely sure, yeah.
- Questionable choice.
- It's completely stinky.
- It's stinky?
- What's stinky about it?
- It tastes, the smell.
It's really stinky.
- No, I know stinky beers.
I've had stinky beers before.
I would say--
- Yeah, name one.
- Well Guinness is another stout that I would say
every once in a while you get a Guinness
it smells like an armpit.
- Yeah.
it's not that good of a thing to put in your body I think. I've never had Guinness in my entire life.
Is it true that Guinness is like, they filter it through a fish? Is that real?
I'm gonna say it's 100% true. I think probably without a doubt that's true. Yeah, that it goes
through a fish's body. Well I remember it was like a thing, it was like if you were vegan you
you couldn't drink Guinness.
This can is no way.
That's true.
I know that they, I mean they do weird shit though.
They put a ping pong ball in the can over at the Guinness factory.
They put a ping pong ball in the can.
Yeah, well that's so you can like play with your friends when you're done with the beer.
Yeah, good luck fucking opening a can buddy.
Yeah, there's a ping pong ball in the way.
There's a tool for that.
Fucking asshole.
I guess that's right.
Alright, what do you guys have?
Alright, I'll go.
What does Rex have?
I have a slushy machine 9 XXL that has...
Now that's a beer!
Has pictures of the Scooby-Doo van all over it.
Now that's a real man's beer.
This is for adults.
That's a milkshake.
I mean, the point of this show is to put... it's for a working class audience, you know?
The union members who get home from their electrician job, they just saw their best
friend die on site. And they get home and they get to crack open a super slushy surprise
right along with us. Kick their feet up and watch Girls.
My favorite show.
Take a sip and tell me. What are the notes on that?
Fruit. Just some sort of fruit flavor.
Kind of like a cartoon fruit, right?
Yeah.
One of the melons from Super Mario Sunshine.
Yeah, exactly.
Whoa, you have a...
Some sort of growth in the cap of this beer.
Oh, maybe you'll die.
Maybe that's why it's stinky, dude.
Maybe first beer of the entire show,
maybe you got a spoiled, poisonous
sludge beer.
Now he's gagging when he smells it.
How can you tell when a
beer goes bad? Does it taste like
shit? It tastes bad
and it stinks.
[laughter]
Your first beer might be a bad, you might have gotten a bad beer, man.
I don't think, I don't think beers go bad.
Well is it a milk stout?
Don't milk, do they have milk in them?
Can the milk in the milk stout go bad?
Um, no it says I can't drink this if I'm pregnant or have a car.
So it's one of those two things.
Yeah.
It's gone bad because it knows you have a car or you're pregnant.
I'm drinking.
I'm drinking a Zajvek, which is, I live in a Polish neighborhood and I see homeless guys
drink this all the time.
And I've had it one other time before and it's actually, it's so fucking good.
It's like the cheapest beer you can buy in a bottle.
I think this is a dollar fifty-nine, this big beer.
We kind of have the two spectrums of beer between you and I, which is I have the stupid, expensive
beer for fat guys and you have the homeless guy swill.
I have another beer, I don't know if I should reveal it now.
Or if we should.
You have multiple beers.
Yeah, I got two just in case.
I heard, Rex said that he was getting a couple of beers and I was like, you know what, I
think I have two as well.
I only grabbed one, but if we get to that point I'll run really fast.
Well, I'll just show you what this other beer was.
You're not going to run to the store and pull a recording apart?
No, run to the fridge.
Are you fucking stupid?
- Oh, I thought you were gonna run to the store.
- This other beer I got-- - You need to run to the store.
- Come on, man.
This other beer I got is a Melnik Izbachanka.
- Tour the world, dude.
- Yeah, which is from Russia.
It's from Russia.
- Yeah. - So--
- It's from Russia.
- I'm excited to tear into that bad boy later.
It looks a little lighter, a little on the lighter side.
Zyvec, you know, this is a, I mean, as you can see on here,
Makes people want to dance, it's pretty high alcohol content.
- You know what they call it when you mix two beers together?
They call it a super beer.
- Really?
I mean, these would be great candidates, I think.
- For a super beer?
- Yeah, I mean, I've had, you know,
it's a great drink that me and Noah drink
every once in a while.
You take a Miller High Life,
and you put about an ounce and a half of Aperol in it,
and then you put some lemon juice in it.
And that's the only beer cocktail I've ever had,
but it's damn good, man.
It's really fucking good.
- Never had like a Boilermaker?
- What are you on about?
- That's the name of a beer cocktail.
- Well, explain it or just shut up.
- Okay, I'll shut up. - What is it?
- Don't worry about it. - No, now you have to tell me.
- What is it?
- Well, only people who know should know about it.
- That's some bullshit, man.
- That's, I'm gonna look it up.
You're fucking stupid.
- So-- - Boilermaker beer.
Guys, let's go through the history of alcohol use
in our families really quickly.
So, Juvio, you can start.
What's the, are your parents big drinkers?
Has anybody been kind of like super dependent
on alcohol through their entire lives?
- My dad used to drink and smoke at the same time
all the time, and now he has heart issues,
so he stopped drinking.
- But he's still smoking, right?
Still keeping the faith?
- Right.
- No, he quit smoking before I was born, I believe.
- That makes sense.
- But he kept on drinking and then he stopped drinking
because he got in a car accident.
- That removed his mouth
so that he couldn't put any more beer in it.
- Yeah.
- Oh wow.
- So now he got in a car accident
and now he has heart problems.
So he can't drink either beer or coffee, I believe.
- Were the heart problems from the accident?
Or from drinking?
- No.
From coffee.
- But they say, dude, they say that heart problems are,
the later into history we get,
The more we find out that heart problems are caused by fucking holding DVDs and like touching
like industrial byproducts.
It's not the smoking and the drinking, man.
That's good for you.
It's the oils that they put on everything and it's Febreze is what's destroying your
heart and giving you cancer.
How could beer fucking hurt anybody?
I know.
I don't think anyone's ever died from a beer overdose.
That's what I'm saying.
No, they actually, here's the strongest case possible for drinking is that drinking is
is one of the only addictions where if you stop cold turkey,
you will die.
- Yeah.
- Because your body recognizes that it's a natural thing
that should be inside of your body, is alcohol.
You have a gland in your brain, and I don't,
the name eludes me, but it produces pure alcohol.
- The beer gland.
- And I think, right, yeah, I think it might be
the beer gland, and supposedly, right before you die,
it releases a huge hit of beer, and so you end up dying,
and you have some kind of like,
kind of psychedelically drunk episode.
- Yeah, I think that's true.
I've seen a couple of YouTube videos about that.
They say it's really crazy.
- It helps you kind of drift away.
Yeah, no, people who have near death experiences,
they have, they say,
well, I was,
I was watching a movie and I was kind of,
like in my head,
and I was kind of forgetting the plot
over and over and over again.
And that's what it was like to die.
- Yeah, and I really had to pee.
- It's really incredible. - So bad.
I had to pee every 10 minutes. I could feel somewhere a woman was mad at me, somewhere
on earth. It was definitely amazing.
You know, just classic being on beer stuff.
Yeah, dude.
Listen, speaking of beer stuff, what are you guys' favorite activities to do while on beer?
While on the beers.
Sorry, one more thing. You said beer stuff and that just made me think of a stuffed beer
and that is probably just a good idea.
So yeah, maybe if you put a pickle sitting in a beer.
It'd be funny to do a land back type deal against your girlfriend when she starts putting stuffed
animals on the bed.
You just put more stuffed beers on the bed.
These are mine.
I grew up with these.
I've had these since I was two years old.
My favorite activities to do while on beer. I love falling asleep during sex. I fucking
love that. That's always, everybody feels good about that. I like bombing at stand up
comedy because I add too much to drink. Going up and just completely forgetting my lines
and then just going into Fallout 3 vats and finding the ugliest person in the room and
making fun of them instead of doing my material. That's good. And I like puking.
Yeah, that was mine. I love throwing up white foam.
You love puking. Puking doesn't... it's good. It feels good. It feels way
better than when you're about to puke. Yeah, and I don't know about you, I
throw up, it's miserable. I'm like crying. I'm like, there's tears coming out of my
- Yeah, facial abuse, my mascara's running.
- You're throwing up like a girl.
- Yeah.
- You eat a sandwich, you immediately go throw it up.
- You do have the hair too.
- I know, I gotta hold it back, I gotta put.
- I've lost my ability to, I used to be really good
in college about if I drank too much,
I could pull the trigger and I could just vomit
and suddenly I could just shove my finger in my throat.
But I think that I, by osmosis,
because of the people that I hang around,
my gag reflex has just like gone away.
And now when I get too drunk and I try to,
I try to fucking pull the trigger, it just doesn't work.
And it's like the saddest thing ever.
Because like, there's one thing to go into a public
restroom at a bar and make yourself vomit,
but it's so much worse to go in there
and just fucking finger your mouth for like two minutes.
And just somebody, somebody next to you in the stall
just hears you just like gagging on something,
but they never hear anything at the toilet bowl.
That's a bad feeling, dude.
- Yeah, I usually wait 'til I get home.
That's usually like a right before bed activity for me.
- Really, it kinda calms you down?
- Well, I get to spin so bad.
So, it's like it's gonna happen eventually.
Might as well on my own terms.
- Dude, I honestly just, you know,
I hate to say it on Beers We Drink,
but I just don't drink that much anymore.
So I'm trying to even remember the last time
that I had that much fun.
- I don't think I've thrown up in years.
Yeah, it's probably been, I do remember the last time I threw up.
I was hanging out with Patrick and Racine, and then Racine left really, really early.
And there was just me and Patrick were just at the bar still, and we were like, "You want
to just keep drinking?"
And we were like, "Yeah, sure."
And then we just stayed until the bar closed.
It wasn't even like a celebration.
I just stayed at a bar too long and then vomited out of the Uber window halfway through the
ride home.
And I was like, "I mean, that's a bad..."
That does not...
The tension between somebody who has to vomit and an Uber driver, they have a sixth sense.
They're like a predator natural.
They know exactly, as soon as you get in the car, the fact that you couldn't finish their
name because you gulped in the middle of it.
They know that you're going to vomit.
And so being on the receiving end of that is pretty terrifying.
The last time I threw up was when we were in New York.
Not last time, but the time before.
Yeah, me and Rex shared this moment.
Yeah, and I, we had gone to the booby bar and we kept drinking like the really cheap
like margaritas.
And then you went home early and I went with Patrick.
And then like, there was a cool guy at the door.
I'm not gonna say anything else again, you know, about him, but you know.
Oh no, I know that guy.
Yeah, I know.
The guy, he looks, he's like Black Sebulba.
Yeah.
He's got like, he's got like fingerless gloves on and goggles and shit.
Yeah, and he was like, "Hey, you wanna hit this?"
And I was like, I mean, for me, of course.
You know, and then drank more beer, and then we got in the Uber and I was like, "Alright,
focus.
Get home first before this happens.
got like 10 minutes in the super you can hold it and I was just like like just
like gripping my my thighs for dear life, looking at me you know and then we get
into the thing and I'm just like my whole body is just like limp I like
can't even hold myself up over the toilet yeah so I'm like throwing up
throwing up and then I like can't even hold myself over the toilet so I just
roll into the shower and just start throwing up on my side.
(laughing)
- Oh my God.
- The worst part was then I like woke up
and I was like, all right, got to pull myself up.
And without thinking, just like grabbed
the toilet paper holder and just ripped it
straight out of the wall.
- At your Airbnb.
- At the Airbnb.
And then just like looked at it.
- There was a dungeon Airbnb,
so it was already a really bad experience.
And then I woke up the next morning
and I just see like bits of like red throw up
all over the bathroom.
I'm like, "Oh, something happened here last night."
- That's amazing.
- And then I bought like super glue tape
and just glued it to the wall
and then just like put a little bit of paint to try.
They didn't charge, yeah, they didn't charge us.
- They didn't charge you?
That is amazing.
- Yep.
- J.B.O., what's the last time that you threw up
from having too many beers?
- I don't think I've ever done,
I don't think I've ever done that.
What?
Excuse me?
I've never thrown up from having too many beers.
Okay, so we're basically--
I've never really even been drunk.
The most drunk that I've been was that exact night,
because you guys kept force-feeding me those margaritas.
Yeah.
And then I got saved by a strange woman
who just took my margarita from me,
and she just drank it.
Whoa, dude, she was hoping
that you were gonna take her home.
She was hitting on you.
- I don't think that's true.
- It is true, man.
- That's not even true.
- It is 100% true.
Have you guys ever been roofied?
- No, but a friend of mine has,
and then he fought the police
and got just like completely fucked.
Just his face was like all just bruised
and destroyed the next day.
- Yeah, it happened to a friend of mine
who is my brother that you know.
(laughing)
- That would happen to him, yeah.
- Yeah, like five or six years ago at New Year's Eve.
And this guy loved beer, for the longest time he loved it.
And then, it was New Year's Eve, he was like 10 minutes,
he was at some bar for like 10 minutes and got roofied.
(laughing)
And then he woke up and yeah, he was like trying to fight
a fucking 40 people on the street
and woke up in some bathroom somewhere.
I don't think that's a good, yeah I'd like to avoid that at all costs I think.
I don't think you have anything to worry about.
How does a man get roofied?
What does that mean?
I don't have anything to worry about.
Hmm.
What could you mean by that?
I think you're a beautiful male presenting individual.
I think we should start a new challenge.
No one would be confused about what you're about.
Well I think.
We should start a new challenge for male friendships to like go to bars and try to roofie each
other as a prank.
That would be so good.
Yeah.
But it's kind of, you're a little bit playing roulette there.
Because, you know, if you're looking at the bar,
your buddy goes to the bathroom, you look at the bar,
everybody got a vodka soda.
There's fucking 15 vodka sodas there.
Yeah.
Right?
You're like, ah, uh-oh.
Then all of a sudden you roofied some old lady
and now she's having sex with her too.
(laughing)
that's not good right?
no yeah that would be bad
I think a fun game would be to like roofie
like you had two beers
you roofie one of them and you gotta try and convince the other
person to take the roofie beer
I feel like you don't
*laughter*
like that British game show
with the balls
yeah
that's a funny game
the thing is dude I would take some roofie
one time if I was on my own
if I, you know, had a day off and I was just sitting at the crib.
Yeah, you know, just for like a chill, relaxing day.
Yeah, you know, I just see what it's like, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I wake up and my dog is fucking me.
[Laughter]
You just wake up and your laptop is
Arrowid and you're looking up like Roofie Trip Reports.
[Laughter]
Yeah, I uh...
You need a trip setter.
That's true.
Yeah, you need someone to trip set you.
I'm gonna go get a frat guy to trip set me.
You know, you remember when Rick Ross got in trouble because he said he had that line
where he said he put Molly in a woman's drink?
Yeah.
And everybody was like, "What?"
She ain't even know it.
Doesn't Molly make you like go fucking crazy and want to watch Fantasia?
No.
Okay, I've never done it.
Actually, I did do it one time.
That's what it made me do.
I was like, "Let's watch SpongeBob."
It was mostly meth when I took it, and it made me smoke a pack of cigarettes just back
to back.
It sounds amazing, dude.
It was great.
Just clenching my jaw, biting the filter.
That's the best.
When you want to smoke into the filter because you want a cigarette so bad, you're like,
There's some more in there for some reason yeah, yeah
Man
Now I've never taken a substance I know soda we made you smoke weed one time and watch Mac and Devin go to high school
And I didn't freak out at all you got completely freaked out and weirded out. No. Yeah, that's not true. You did basically
Introducing people to weed is such like a fun
Thing it sucks. You don't get to do it once you turn 20
Yeah, well I got to when I was 23.
It's very rare after that point, you know what I mean?
You need to meet some Amish Mexican guy who's always on the computer and you need to kind
of pluck him out of that and bring him to your crazy life in New York City where you
smoke weed once a month and you need to show him that amazing healing drug.
Where you sprinkle the innards of a weed pen onto your dinner until you go insane.
- Yep, yeah, where you eventually get diagnosed
with marijuana-induced psychosis by a psychiatrist.
That's what we need.
- Did that happen to you? - We need more of that.
- Eh.
(laughing)
- We don't have to get into it, really.
It's kind of personal.
- I'm sorry for asking.
I should've--
- Yeah, well, let's talk about beer.
- Back to your privacy.
- We need to get back to beers.
- Can we get back to beer, please?
- Yep. - Yeah.
- Can we please get back to beer?
- So, I just got big news.
- What's up?
- Today, I received my brand new fridge.
I recently moved into this apartment and I got a brand new fridge.
And the first thing I did, filled it to the brim with beers.
How many does it hold?
Because that's like horsepower with a car when you see a fridge.
What's the beer holding?
What's the beer cap?
I think approximately like a hundred beers.
No way!
My ass is a hundred beers.
Well ninety beers in the fridge and ten in the freezer.
Yeah good luck drinking a frozen beer.
You're acting like a fucking dick.
Beer in the freezer?
I'm just going to thaw them.
I'm thawing the beer.
I guess you're right.
You're not going to drink.
Like if you drink 10 of the 90, you're not going to go through the other fucking 80 by
the time, by the time you go through the other 80, the 10 from the freezer will be thawed.
That's how you're pretty smart.
You're pretty smart.
I'm not done with my first beer, but it's kind of starting to disgust me.
[laughter]
So, I'm gonna move on to...
I mean, I'd like to... it's in Cyrillic on the front, so I'd like to try to read this.
"Kamapi blui mehi buki."
[laughter]
"Nibu yoka."
Why are you doing an accent?
Russian accent. You don't know anything about Russia.
You sound like a Sim.
I sound like a surf, that's what I sound like. I'm gonna open this.
Okay.
What's your candy beer taste like?
It's great.
I can tell that there's literally a thousand calories in this beer.
Yeah, that is so incredible.
They do taste so good though, but they might as well just be canned smoothies.
Like the ones that have like fucking marshmallow and shit in them.
This has like a list of like seven different fruit it's supposed to taste like.
When I'm drinking beer, the only marshmallow I want involved is going to be on the radio
and I'm dancing in my car, right?
- Yeah, that's right.
- While I drink the beer.
- That's what's up.
- You're dancing in your car?
- While I drink.
I'm gonna take one sip of this Russia beer.
- Yeah, just take a five second sip.
- Oh!
(laughing)
- That's a ghost.
- Oh God, man.
- It looks entirely like piss.
- It's been 24 minutes and you are now
disgusted by two beers. You know what, I'm gonna go back to the first one. That one is
just not... you know I like this... the thing has been beer is really so bad after it's
been sitting for 20 minutes. That's why beer is so fun to drink a hundred of very fast.
Yeah, you gotta just keep it going. You're gonna have to speed up on drinking spoiled
beer. Look at me man, I got... I've been working my way through this bad boy. I'm like here,
halfway through. Yeah, we should be about halfway through at this point. 25 minutes in. I think
this beer is completely poisoned. And now it's incredibly dark. You could go get another beer.
Tell me about this mango cart, or melon cart that you just got. And also, well I guess
you won't want to pop it open yet, but I'm going to want to hear your thoughts on it.
I'll get there, I'll have to really power through this sour. The thing is, dude, those
Sours and the thing those are the only beers that if you put them in the fridge. They're exactly the same tomorrow
Yeah, you know so you don't feel pressure to finish the
15,000 calorie sour beer at any given point I
Kind of like it. I kind of like the feeling that I'm like pregnant at the moment with a beautiful. Yeah
What uh what's the first beer that you ever motherfucking had Bud Light
What was yours I
I think mine was probably a PBR.
How old were you?
Man, I was probably 14.
Yeah.
I was 14 or 15, something like that.
I was definitely like 11, 12, drinking my dad's Bud Light.
Yeah, my dad didn't, my dad was a gin drinker.
So he never had beer in the house and gin was too scary to me.
But I, but my first time, you know, I would have beer every once in a while
when I was like 14 or whatever. But my first time really drinking probably I was probably 16
and I poured I like raided my mom's liquor cabinet one night with my buddy and my mom
real classy lady she had uh Hennessy and uh Svedka vodka and I poured a so I'd never had
hard liquor before and I poured a solo cup with half Hennessy, half vodka with no mixer
and I held my nose and I chugged the entire thing. I was like, "That's what you're
supposed to do?" Yup. Yup. I mean, I probably had fucking my first time ever really drinking.
It was the equivalent of like 12 shots of fucking everything in 90 seconds. Yeah. And
I just completely it tasted so I remember it it put me off a liquor for a long time
it tasted so so bad and I was completely I blacked out almost instantly yeah I'm
ever blacked out and I woke up when I woke up I when I like came to I was
running down the road and it was like pouring rain on me and that and then it
just kind of back and forth. And then I just remember like that being the first
time I was ever hungover. And having to like, when you're 16, having to
explain to your mom why you feel like the the hangover of a grown man who just
had like the craziest night of his entire life. Yeah. Like I would never, I've
never had 12 shots of anything since then. Yeah. It was pretty hard. I, so my dad,
classy man that he is only had two types of liquor in his house crown royal
fuck yes and Jägermeister. I thought you were going to say crown royal and crown apple.
He's a crown maple man now. Damn. Crown royal is good. And I remember one time
there's some maybe was like a funeral or something we came home and it's for one
of his friends and he gave us all these shots of Jägermeister and he poured like a ghost
shot right and I shit you not the shot like just started to move on its own.
It's like a very vivid memory of a shot glass moving to the edge of the counter and then
just like stopping.
So your dad did a magic trick to you and freaked you out for life.
Yeah.
Do you guys believe in ghosts?
Yes.
Jimmy is Mexican so he definitely believes in ghosts.
Oh 100%.
- He puts the egg to his forehead before he goes to bed.
- I put the egg to my forehead and sometimes when-
- All Mexicans believe in ghosts, right?
- Sometimes when it gets, yes,
sometimes when it gets cold, I hear like a, like a,
ooh. - Ooh.
(laughing)
- And some may think that that's just the wind blowing,
but I think it's a ghost.
(laughing)
- Let me in, it's cold outside.
- Running through the air into my apartment.
- Ooh, I need a hoodie.
- Yeah.
- He's whispering that he's cold
- There's a crack in the window.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, Ghost Google doesn't have the weather yet.
- I mean, that happened today to me.
- You had a ghost? - In broad daylight.
I had a ghost sighting in broad daylight.
I was walking around my apartment
and I heard him speak to me.
- What'd he say?
- He said, "Ooh."
'Cause I don't know, that's not the only thing
he says to me.
- Yeah.
- And what did you record? - Kind of food, actually.
I just said, "I'm pretty busy right now, buddy."
- Hey, I have a podcast to record.
Can you wait like an hour?
Yeah, take it up to somebody else. I'm filling my new fridge with beers that I can't plug
in yet because it just moves. The beers are getting hot in the hot fridge.
Oh yeah, your beer is in the middle of the living room or your fridge is in the middle
of the living room.
We don't have to go into where it is.
It's in the middle of the living room. I was explaining, I tried to explain to him over
text like he was like, "Oh yeah, I have to leave it there until it settles or something,"
which made no sense to me.
It doesn't make sense.
It doesn't make sense. What do you mean it settles? Yeah, have you guys never moved a fridge before?
No, I'm not a millionaire
Billionaire who buys for ages willy-nilly. Yeah, I've never bought a fridge in my life
The compressor has like oil in it
So you have to let it sit for a little bit for as long as it's that's in movie. You have to let it sit
But it can't sit at the place that it's supposed to go as to sit. Yeah the room. Yeah, I can't be one again
Well, I have to watch it. You have to watch it for what is it gonna?
leak the ghosts might
Yeah, they might leak or the ghost might take it. The ghost probably tried to drink your beer and that's why it tastes stinky
You have a cursed beer yeah that
Reminds me of the the pirates of the Caribbean where he drinks the beer that said he like has to crack open the top
Cuz it's got barnacles all over it. Yeah
Yeah, that reminds me of that. You know, you have the ghost death beer
Yeah, yes, I don't think I want to finish this beer. I think I'm gonna make you one you're one sip in man
Yeah, this podcast is supposed to be we're supposed to be fucked up by the end of this show. I know and you're
truceps
Yes, dude, look at me with my Polish beer, bro. I'm ready to watch soccer. Yeah
Fan of a soccer team
Yeah, I think that you know I'm getting you your shit kicked in if you went to a footy game with your
with your little beard filled with skittles.
Yeah, I would look exactly like that guy that got hit in the head at the hockey game.
I would love to die at a sporting event as a man.
That would be like, I think...
I could take you guys to a footy match.
We could go to the Lucha Libre in Mexico City.
That's the...
That's wrestling, right?
That's wrestling.
Yeah.
That's WWE for, you know, you guys.
No, it's called Lucha Libre.
Do they hit each other for real or is it fake?
I mean...
Uh, yeah, they kill each other in the ring.
Oh, okay, well that's cool.
Do you think that they would have any room for some kind of white hero?
[laughs]
Uh, I said, like a...
Like a white hero character that just comes into the show?
Maybe like an unplanned...
Do you think that... How would they respond to an unplanned white hero who walked in and just sort of...
Just actually kicking the shit out of every single one of those fucking fuckers?
Because what, the biggest wrestler in the Mexican WWE is like fucking 5'5", right?
I walk in and I just start just pounding the shit out of him.
Yeah, for a guy that's your same height.
Yeah.
Sorry, the audio keeps cutting in and out.
I'm not really hearing you very well.
It kind of sucks that, you know, because Mexicans are pretty short, but we're talking to literally
a guy that's like four inches taller than both of us.
Yeah, I would say it's probably one of the worst things in my life.
Is that Jubio is so much taller than me.
Yeah, it like genuinely is a little frustrating.
Yeah, dude, I always wanted him to be so small, you know?
Yeah.
But he's such a giant, he's a gentle giant.
People think I have small guy energy.
I wouldn't say that.
I think that you have, I think that it's the complete opposite.
I think that you have a, you're kind of cool, calm, and collected in a way that only a very
tall man can be.
Yeah, I would agree with that.
That's really nice of you guys.
Anyways, I keep digging into this thing and it's releasing a smell that's too bad to bear.
So explain what you're digging into.
I don't think we really, there's a goo coming off of the underside of the beer cap.
Yeah, the beer cap, I'm scratching it and it's releasing a terrible smell that's
That's almost ghastly in nature. Oh my god
You can't drink that you're gonna get sick. Yeah, don't drink that beer
I don't think I'm gonna keep drinking that beer anymore your first thing
That is so sad that your first beer for the only time when the beer that you drink really means anything. Yeah
It's your first one. It was a
Catastrophic dud. Yeah, that's really unfortunate
I feel so fucked up.
That's like telling someone to break a leg, you know, for a play.
Drink a bad beer before your podcast.
GBA, you ever do, you ever do, uh...
Hey, drink a bad beer before your beer podcast.
Yeah, I hope your beer sucks.
Yeah, yeah, drink a bad beer.
That's like, that's like Google saying.
I think I've heard it before.
We have to start, we're gonna start seeing each other before we record.
Yeah drink a bad beer.
Yeah I hope your beer sucks and it's been infected by ghosts.
Yeah I hope you have infected fucking ghastly ecto beer.
I think you might be a beer genius Rex.
I need to start believing in ghosts pretty soon.
I think I'm getting to the age where.
You don't believe in ghosts?
It's crazy to me that you don't.
your experiences and family. No, I believe that there's people that, every
once in a while I will believe there's people living in my house and I look for them. But
I don't believe in ghosts though. I always think that.
You live in the city that's most likely to have ghosts.
But if I hear like a weird creaking or something, my instinct is not there's a ghastly spirit.
My instinct is there is a crackhead maniac living in my closet.
that to me even though it probably makes less sense than a ghost that's what I
jumped to mm-hmm do you ever get afraid to like look into a mirror or like look
into a like a glass look through some glass like a window perhaps no no here
you're a dog.
Yeah. What do you mean? What if there's a ghost behind you? What
if there's a ghost?
Okay, you're expecting a fully like the James Wan movie that
there's gonna you're gonna close the vanity and there will be a
Civil War generals.
When it's like 3am and you're like, there's 3am and I and I
called the blue Grinch, you expect him right behind you.
- Absolutely.
- Herobrine is gonna be sitting behind you in a mirror.
- He came out of Minecraft.
- Yeah, well, you know, the secret is to like,
not have any mirrors in your house at all.
- But then people who come over to your house
will just assume you're ugly.
- Yeah, which they already know in your case.
I'm just kidding, I'm sorry, that was.
- Well, or at least they won't,
Maybe they haven't noticed, right?
But then they go over to your house
and then they're like, "That's weird.
"This guy doesn't have any mirrors in his entire home."
- What if you're trying to save them?
- Oh my God, he's as ugly as shit.
- What if, no, I think that would be,
that makes no sense.
They would call it a thing.
- That's actually a better point.
- That I'm a vampire.
- If you went over to somebody's house
and you noticed that there was like a dust outline
where a bunch of different mirrors had been
that they clearly took off before you got there.
- You'd be like, "Hey, what's up?"
- I would assume, I'd be like,
Oh, they don't like they can barely handle one of me like they don't I'm so ugly right? Yeah
They don't want me to someone says my teeth if I want to work someone's house and they have no mirror
So what if some they're a vampire?
You also believe in
This is what we're looking for dude.
Dude, I am so fucked up and I've never felt closer to two people in my entire life.
I know.
I'm so fucked up.
I'm about to fall.
I've had one full Polish beer and I'm about an eighth through my Russian beer and I'm about to fall over.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
And I can't see straight.
Well, what do you go?
Go take a load off in that bed of yours.
My microphone won't fit.
Yeah.
See?
It won't reach. My microphone won't fit in my bed. Guys, we're seriously drunk AF, dude.
Oh my God. You realize how excited people have been for this podcast? I've had so many
incredibly high up people in the radio broadcasting world reach out to me and tell me, "When
is 'Beers We Drank' going to come out? When is it going to come out? You've been teasing
it for a year and we're finally doing it." How amazing does that feel to accomplish something
like that. It feels amazing. I never thought I would return to the microphone.
Did you used to pick up the fucking stick? I did, I did back in
five years ago, man. What was your podcast about? I was a
recurring guest on a podcast called Girls Chat, which don't think too much
about that. Wait, Girls Chat? Hmm. So this is a podcast with guys on it and it's a
joke I'm guessing. Sure, let's say that. Okay. That's the only way that I'm gonna let you
slide on that one. Exactly. I'm not too convinced, but we can go ahead with the story. Yeah. There's
no story. There's nothing to talk about there. Nothing interesting happened. Your recurring
guess, would you say that you occupied sort of a whack pack sort of spot on the... Yeah. I was
kind of like the Kramer. I'd be in there for the sea plots. Ah, but you're also the funniest one.
Well, right only guy on the show. Come on. Exactly. Yeah, it's that simple me and rex were talking about last day and night who
We are in the unlike the time for characters and we I think we decided that he might be seinfeld
No, no for that one
Not for that reason
Well, I do I I do like to complain and I think I sound a bit
like him while I'm complaining. That's what you just, that's what I just said. I know, I know.
I know I'm trying to make it so it's not anti-semitic when you say it.
No, you don't have to do that for me. I'm fine with it. Okay. I've made my peace, yeah. I have
my thing which is that every person is like some amalgamation of every Seinfeld character.
you know you're like 40 percent George 20 percent Seinfeld in Jubio's case he's 100 percent Elaine
Elaine with a with a lane with a uh Lola Bunny t-shirt
no that's not true that's cool that's not even really true i like this theory i like that you've
just like rediscovered the like Joseph Campbell like myth thing just with like
Seinfeld I don't know the Joseph Campbell myth thing just that like every story
has like fucking five people in it yeah that's true yeah yeah I think that's
good I think every good group of people is every people like like oh you are
high on beer. Your beer gland is working overtime. Whoa, I'm so fucking drunk, man. I'm seeing
a purple elephant in my room. Fuck, I'm tripping off beer.
Right, let him finish. Let him finish. Go ahead. Finish your thought.
Like a truly good story about multiple characters. They make up the fundamental archetypes of
every kind of person. Yeah, so like I understand comparing yourself and your
friends to Seinfeld because that's basically an astrology kind of thing.
Sure. But what what is another what's another uh story that has exactly all
the Seinfeld characters in it? Yeah, probably Curb Your Enthusiasm.
Yeah, you might be right. It's all just Seinfeld. South Park. You know, I've maybe seen
Okay, South Park, who's Jerry?
Uh, that's uh, Jerry is Stan.
Uh, Kramer is Cartman.
No, I think Cartman is George.
No, Kyle is George.
But Cartman always has the problem going on.
That would be my argument.
Okay, I can see that.
Wouldn't Kenny be Kramer?
Kenny is a lame.
Hmm.
He matters the least.
Yeah, he's a bitch.
No, I guess Kenny maybe is Kramer.
Kenny is Kramer.
Can we just pause to appreciate how advanced this shit is?
I know, we're on another level.
This is not something that we could ever talk about on the main podcast, right?
But I come out here and we're getting crazy.
Episode 1.
Seinfeld and South Park are the same show.
You know, this is some game-changing shit.
What's this yellow beer about?
What are you talking about?
Yellow beer?
Are you stupid?
It's green.
Listen for the yellow.
This guy had, this guy was drinking pure penicillin and now he's having a, uh, being attacked
by some kind of biotic.
He's gonna go blind by the time this episode ends.
Yeah, you're done dude.
Like I saw that shit that you drank.
That was fucked.
I have an announcement to make.
I'm quitting beer.
Alright, well, podcast is completely, you, you, you, you whiffed it then.
You know, I've only seen maybe two episodes of Seinfeld though.
I need to go.
It's on Netflix now.
I need to watch it.
It's great.
Yeah, but every time that I think about watching Seinfeld, I'm just like, "Man, Curb is so
funny and I go and watch Curb."
Because Seinfeld, there is something we said for a TV show being able to use the F word.
Yeah.
It's going to be a little funnier.
Okay, so I will say, speaking of the F word, and maybe not the same F word you're thinking
of. When's the last time you watched Glenn Gary Glenn Ross? I've only seen it once
and I was maybe 15 and I decided this is exactly how I will live my life.
Alec Baldwin calls them all F words in his famous coffee is for closers speech
and it like just a little bit reintroduced it into my vocabulary for
like a day. Yeah, probably the past 24 hours means a bit. Just a little bit. Yeah, I would
say that you should never watch Django then, because that would be pretty catastrophic for
you. Or the boondocks, my god. My god. It took years to unlearn the damage that the boondocks
Dude, I found out some fucked up shit about Pulp Fiction.
You know that in Pulp Fiction, Quentin Tarantino didn't write the entire thing?
Really?
Who wrote it?
Yeah, the lat- there's some other guy named like Roger Avery or some shit and he wrote
the whole Bruce Willis storyline.
And he like, his agent like sued Quentin Tarantino or something because they wrote it together.
They like wrote the movie as like three different like individual stories.
that Quentin Tarantino wanted so badly to have at the beginning of the movie, a film by Quentin
Tarantino written and directed by Quentin Tarantino, that he had to pay this guy a huge
cash settlement basically.
But the guy also got the Oscar for best screenplay.
They shared it.
Interesting.
Yeah.
That's crazy.
That's astrid.
Quentin Tarantino, I've been watching all of his movies again.
They, dude it's kind of crazy how good they are.
They're so good, man.
They're so good.
What is the obsession with people like kind of shitting on these great movies?
Because it's...
I feel like it's like they think it's like entry-level like filmography, like getting into like movies, right?
Yeah, but that's stupid.
The best music ever made is fucking Halsey, you know?
It's the exact same concept.
Yeah.
You ever listen to the Chainsmokers?
That's the best shit.
It's fucking unreal, dude.
Yeah.
What the fuck it's amazing. Yeah. Mm-hmm and Pulp Fiction
I feel like or Quentin Tarantino as a whole gets a bad rap. Yeah, it's like how people shit on Fight Club
It's like cuz when you're 14 you first learn about stuff
That's not just on TV or not on the radio
And then everyone loves it too much and they have to like walk it back because you don't want to be seen as like a perpetual
15 year old
So then you have to pretend to like shit like Skeena Mareink or whatever fucking stupid
You don't like Fight Club. It gives me a stomachache. It's too much violence in it. Yeah
Okay, I'm not kidding. I can't watch movies with that much violence in them because I get a stomachache
I've never seen it. You've been watching Quentin Tarantino movies. They're hella violent.
Yeah, but those are, you know, those are like funny violent. Yeah, they're silly
Yeah, fight club is like, you know, I think you know what it is man. It's that pure just a
I hate I just hate that that miss misanthropic
Nihilistic BS and fight club, right it's lame. Yeah, you know, I watched Tarantino movies and I say
Okay, so it's awesome to be fucking to like the coolest thing in the world to me when I was a kid
It's like what if a black guy knew karate, you know, and that's purely all Wu-Tang and Quentin Tarantino
Right. Got it. Yeah
Wu-Tang was definitely the coolest guys to probably ever
Exist. They're number one dude. For sure
They're so good. I've been I've been listening to a bunch of like
Old rap recently and I can't believe that I ever kind of stopped. It's just the best. It's the funniest stuff ever made
Do you remember the first time you heard the RZA's verse on the Kanye West so appalled or is it so appalled?
I forget which one it is. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, and he's just screaming. He's just like
It's like the entire day. It's like he's coughing the entire time
And you're like what happened to this guy this guy used to be sit used to sit in a flooded basement and make the greatest songs
At all time and now he's coughing through a chorus on a Kanye track. Yeah, and it's awesome. It's still cool
It's really it's really good
Yeah, and they made to he made to kung fu movies that are pretty good
Yeah, man with the iron fist wanted to pretty cool. What do you guys think about the Kanye's?
reputation with the mainstream media nowadays.
You know what, I'm going to leave this one to Rex.
I think he's still good.
Well, you heard it.
We fully support him.
It would be very hypocritical of me to abandon someone for saying
they love Hitler because I would just have to
unfollow everyone on Twitter.
It is so funny
how many people he
reached out to
to like in the last year, like how many comedians that he reached out to saying like, "Hey man,
you should come work for me."
Really?
That is so funny.
Yeah, yeah.
He like, he reached out to Shane.
He like texted Shane and was like, "Yo, you should come write for me."
And a couple other people too.
Everybody has to say no, I think for pretty obvious reasons.
Of course.
But I, and I would say no too, but a little bit,
I was like, come on, shoot me a text.
- Right, it hurts not to even be asked.
- Yeah, right?
- Right for what?
- Maybe you're too PC, maybe he doesn't--
- I think I am too PC.
I think I need to buck my,
I need to become a, I need to get into whatever thing
that Steven Crowder does.
'Cause the fact that he was offered $50 million,
I've been thinking about it for like a full month.
- Yeah.
- It's like the craziest thing I've ever heard.
And he sucks.
More than Rogan.
Yeah.
That's so awesome.
Where does that money come from?
Well, I do give a lot of money to Daily Wire.
And I gotta stuff.
Me too.
I wouldn't say I give 50 million, but I give a 50th of that.
And I need to stuff.
Yeah.
A millionth of that.
A millionth.
Yeah.
Rogan makes sense, you know?
People everywhere, stupid guys everywhere listen to Rogan.
And smart.
And smart guys.
Smart, very smart guys. Sorry, I should have prefaced that. But, you know, at least that
makes sense how much money he gets. He deserves it even, I would say. Yeah, I mean
he's the hardest working man in Austin. They've been saying that for some time
now. I think it should be our first guest. I would love to talk to him. I would do
anything yeah to have him held hostage in a saw situation I would do fucking
anything did you could do even custom traps just for him yeah right yeah like
cuz you know he's not flexible so it'd be just simple stuff like touch your
toes you know yeah do a hundred push-ups yeah just like to like fear factor shit
to
- Yeah.
- Do you think you and him share a special bond?
- Because of bald?
Or his baldness and mine, and my upcoming baldness?
I'm not bald yet.
- I was thinking more like you're both are.
- You think of me as a Rogan type?
- Yeah.
Like a Red Ranger type of deal, you know?
Like a leader of industry.
- Oh, that's funny.
I think of you as like, you remember Jeff Dunham had a Jose the Jalapeño on a stick.
You're like kind of a miniature version, like a lesser version of Jose the Jalapeño on
a stick.
Yeah, we need to get you a hat.
That type of thing.
We do.
Not just any hat.
A sombrero.
For my wedding, for my wedding, will you walk around with a sombrero with guac in the middle
and chips around the room.
[laughter]
Um...
Please.
Okay.
Yeah, everyone would be so confused when you're part of it.
Exactly, especially because you're taller than every single person there, so nobody
will even see the guac and chips.
[laughter]
You'll just be walking around with the guac that will fully just turn brown on the top
of your head.
[laughter]
I mean, I'll do it.
That's beautiful.
I'll completely do it.
That's crazy.
Will you do the same with a bunch of money on your hand?
I'm going to give you the money, Yamaka.
I'm going to put it on you ceremonially.
That'd be amazing.
You know I converted to Judaism for some time.
Really?
Have I ever told you that?
No.
I converted to Judaism for about six months.
What happened?
This fucking Jewish bitch I was with broke up with me.
What a hoe, I hate that, I'm sorry.
No she was a nice lady.
But I got into, I started going to temple with her and I was like, okay, I was like
15, I was like okay Judaism is fucking amazing, they're blowing us so far, it's like way
more fun than like church.
She had a dope ass temple too, people like jumping around and dancing and shit, it was
sick.
Then I went home to my mom and I was like, "Mom, I'm a Jew."
And she was like, "I don't think that you're Jewish."
And then I started delusionally thinking that my family, that I was actually Jewish, genetically
Jewish, where I would grill my grandma.
I'd be like, "So, Grandpa's Italian, but a lot of the times people would lie about that
kind of stuff when they come to the US, right?"
She was like, "No, he's Italian."
and I'd be like, "But some people would lie."
She'd be like, "Yeah, but I don't think..."
And I'd be like, "But some people would lie, right?"
And eventually she'd be like,
"Yeah, I guess some people would lie."
And then I'd go around and be like,
"Guys, I'm an eighth Jewish.
I'm completely Jewish, but I'm not at all."
But I really did want to be,
and I enjoyed my time in the Jewish faith.
But the reality is, man, the book is too big.
- It is too big.
Do you want to break a glass at your wedding?
The weddings are also Christmas.
I can't miss out on Christmas, man.
The actual reality is that Hanukkah is a piece of shit holiday.
It's so bad.
We have completely stopped celebrating Hanukkah in my family.
Yeah, there's no reason.
It's just Christmas now.
Do you get more gifts because it's like a thousand days?
Here's what I would like to do.
It's Jewish, so the gifts are like socks for one of the days.
Now hold on, what do you mean by that?
- Well, okay, so--
- Yeah, what do you mean by that?
- When you're a kid and you do Hanukkah,
your parents are Jewish.
So they-- - Right.
- The gifts-- - So what, fucking
incredibly high IQ and creative,
they dominate the creative field?
- Right, and the financial one.
And they do so by giving-- - Whoa, wait, listen!
(laughing)
That's crazy, okay?
I'll admit that they have an amazing record for producing artists, successful artists.
But I'll stop there.
Okay?
That's very wise of you.
Yes.
You're treading on thin ice.
But you know what would help?
Maybe some socks for Hanukkah that would keep you warm while you're treading on thin ice.
That's a good point.
The thing is, dude, I get socks every Christmas and I love it.
Yeah.
Because I'm a grateful Christian.
Right. I'm not saying that socks aren't a great gift. It sucked when I stopped getting them.
When was the last time you bought socks? You just wait until the holidays every year and then you
get them. I buy them every month now because I just lose them. What the fuck is- no. That is not
true. You don't do your laundry. I know that kind of guy. The only reason to buy socks every month
is because you'll wear them three times and they'll be completely black and you'll throw
them away.
Alright, a little guilty of sharts there.
But I did laundry and I have only like four complete pairs left.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, you got some kind of fucking borrower situation.
Yeah.
I just wear whatever.
Or hear me out, it's the ghost sock.
The sock ghost.
It's a ghost that steals your socks.
I think I'm just bad at taking things out of the dryer.
I think that's just something I'm not very good at.
You're forgetting them, you're not checking the crust.
Right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm in a rush.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess I pretty much lose something every- I always lose.
My wife always tells me the one thing where she's like,
when you do laundry, make sure that this delicate piece
of whatever, this shirt or this sweater,
make sure that you take this out halfway through
and you take good care of it.
It's a prized possession of mine.
And every single time I do laundry,
- Forget.
- I just, I don't even forget it, I lose it.
Whatever it is, not only do I not take care of it
the way that she wanted me to,
I always just completely lose it.
And then she's across the street asking people
who speak no English to go through their laundry
to see if a shirt that she likes is in there.
I'm terrible at laundry.
- Yeah.
I just got a hoodie that I bought on Grailed
and it came from, let's say, a very Chinese part of Canada.
- Let me guess, OVO hoodie.
- No.
- Okay.
and it smells so much like a grape swisher
that I can't wear it.
- That's amazing.
Why would you not want to wear it, man?
That's a pheromone.
You're gonna be picking up some of the hottest women on earth
smelling like a grape swisher.
- I know.
- Is this the hoodie that you bought on accident?
- Yeah, yeah, I didn't mean to buy it.
I just asked him if he would ship to me
and then he sent me an offer immediately.
And I was like, wow, this would be rude to--
- What's the hoodie?
- It's just a--
- Put it on.
- Put it on right now.
- No.
- Put it on right, what does it say?
- Put it on right now.
- It doesn't say anything.
It's just a black hoodie and gray.
- It says the N word.
- Why would it be the N word?
Why would I own an N word hoodie?
That would be insane.
- I could see you owning something like that.
- No.
- 'Cause of how crazy you are.
- Like that six, nine outfit from like 20 years ago.
(laughing)
- What is the F word?
- Pussy.
- Just walk around like that.
- Yeah, 69 on that thing.
Dude, the fake off-white jersey.
Yeah.
That was sick.
Dude, you guys know that Noah used to wear like off-white, like fake off-white in high
school?
That makes perfect sense.
He used to have like those exact shorts and he would wear those and he looked so sick,
man.
Pyrex?
Yeah.
You look so sleepy.
Me?
Yeah.
I am very sleepy, dude.
I've had two beers in some fucking time.
And these aren't just any beers, man.
These are fucking straight from the war zone beer.
Yeah.
And they're tearing me up.
You're so pink and silly.
That's because you're not, once you've found out that you're 100% Irish, you're not allowed
to have any of the Eastern European beer.
Okay, I'm actually 50% Irish.
And I actually learned that I have a sensitivity to alcohol and caffeine as well, once I looked
through the rest of my DNA.
So I'm sure that you were very interested to hear about that.
Yeah, I was very interested.
I wanted to see what your face looked like.
You're so pink.
That's because I have night shift on, on my computer.
Here, I'll turn it off and you'll see what I really look like.
I'm just stark white.
You got actual asian glow dude.
You took one beer and you're ashamed.
Yeah, you literally look like an anime character.
Drawn on a white piece of paper.
Alright, I'm turning it back on.
I need to do, I need to, we should go through as bonus content the rest of my, all my traits
that I have on my 23andMe thing.
Because some of them are very, very wrong, man.
I'll tell you that much.
There's one in particular that I was like, yeah, this is--
Is there a way for you to contact them?
Just be like, I think this is wrong.
I think you're wrong.
I'm actually--
Excuse me.
I think that I am West African.
Can you please--
Can you recheck?
I think you got me mixed.
I think you got my DNA mixed up.
I think you got me mixed up with a white guy.
Because this is not me.
99.98% white guy.
It's fine because if I did that it would just come out like 99.8 Ashkenazi Jew.
Which would be just as embarrassing. Nobody broke the mold. Okay, get this one guys.
Caleb, your genetics predict 82% chance that you do not have a bald spot.
Whoa. 18% chance that you do have a bald spot. I would be so mad.
Not me dude, I'm buying lottery tickets.
You're one in a million.
59% chance you will not experience hair loss or thinning before age 40.
41% chance that you will.
Get this one dude.
3% chance of greenish blue eyes.
3% chance of blue eyes.
There you have.
Oh my god, my beautiful blue eyes.
Yeah.
Jimmy, what color are your eyes?
Oh, they're like poop.
They're not like poop.
Somebody told...
Beautiful.
They look like poop.
I heard somebody say to somebody else the other day that they had beautiful eyes and I had
never noticed this guy's eyes and I looked into them and they actually looked like they
had the texture and color of pieces of poop.
I told him, I was like, just so you know, that girl just wants to fuck you.
You do not have pretty eyes.
She's just trying to come up with anything she can come up with.
I mean he's a good looking guy but she should have said like, "I want to suck your dick."
But instead she was like, "You have beautiful eyes."
And they were, like I said, not beautiful.
Yeah.
What color are your eyes, Rex?
They're greenish gray.
Greenish gray.
Yeah.
And they change.
They're probably really gray right now.
They do change.
They change.
And they change.
And I have a power that makes them change.
Well, they change depending on my mood dude, no way no seriously and if I get drunk they get grayer
Mmm, and if you said you think it's a yellow
And if he's in love they're pink no, that's fucking stupid. Yeah, you're right if right if it's angry
Okay, I'm not a fucking animate your abilities is filling free
Yeah, yeah and blue if they're calm
Well guys, tell me how, let's do a quick, here at the end, seems like we're about wrapping
up, let's talk real quickly about, let's give a numerical score to the beers that we drank
tonight.
Sure.
Because that's kind of the point of the show, right?
The beers we drank.
We drank them.
Right.
Right?
Oh wait, actually I need to see, you have to take one sip of your melon cart.
Are we reviewing the beers?
Yeah dude, we're doing it.
And by the way, this is a comedy club rule, there's a two drink minimum, Jubio.
So for next time, keep that in mind.
Okay.
Oh, whoa.
That's good, right?
The melon cart?
That's crazy.
I like the melon cart.
Tastes like someone dissolved a piece of a watermelon Jolly Rancher into water.
Yeah, it's good.
All right.
So Zyvec, Z-Y-W-I-E-C.
I'm gonna give this beer, like I said, I've had it before, I like it all right.
I'm going to give this a 7.1.
Okay?
It's a pretty decent beer.
For the price especially.
Now this other fucking Russian piece of shit, this thing is a 5.6.
If that.
It might even be lower.
This is a terrible beer.
Do not recommend, let me see, Melnix Izbochanka.
This is not a good beer.
Do not pick that up.
So yeah, that's about it.
I think I would rate my Coast Beer a 666 because it's going to haunt me forever I feel.
That's an incredibly high number for a...
And I'm going to die.
For an entirely fungal beer.
It's plant based.
This is a 450 North Brewing Slushy Machine 9 XXL.
Wow.
That is named exactly like a gas station sex pill.
Yeah, honestly, like a solid eight, eight and a half.
For a sour.
For the price, like a two out of 10.
It's 10 bucks?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's pretty crazy.
Sheesh.
Yeah.
Melon cart, very highly rated, seven and a half out of 10.
There we go.
I don't know what it costs 'cause I stole it.
For that, that's a 10 out of 10.
I don't think they're that expensive.
I think it might be $14.99 for a six pack or something like that.
Two and a half bucks each, something like that.
Well it was zero for me and that makes it the best beer in the world.
Amen brother.
That's right.
Amen.
Alright here it will play us out, Rage Against the Machine.
That is the official beers we drink.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
[Outro Music]