[Sipping]
[Burp]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer podcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[Burp]
This is a journey into sea,
into the land,
planet,
- I'm a food ribbon!
- Beers we drank, motherfucker,
with Juvio, Caleb, and Rex.
(funky music)
- Beer.
- Oh, shit.
- Well, mine was a bottle.
- Oh my God, mine exploded, holy fuck.
- I think it's very clear what mine is.
- All right, then you start.
- Okay.
So I-- - And let me just say,
amazing taste.
Amazing taste, amazing beer.
One of the best. - Thank you.
- Sorry, I'm just, I'm fawning.
I have a Bud Light Lime Tallboy.
- Christ, this is an amazing beer.
- Someone just drank, literally just drank this.
- So? - I know.
But here's the thing. - It's called a recommendation.
- Okay. - I went to a party
on Saturday and I walked to a corner store
and I bought this Bud Light on a Saturday.
- On Saturday. - I see.
- And then I went back to the party
and realized I actually didn't really want to be out much longer.
Nice.
I took it home with me in an Uber.
And then when we unexpectedly recorded a day early, I thought, wait,
there's already a beautiful beer in the fridge.
That's sometimes God just lines everything up for you, huh?
Serendipitous.
Exactly.
That is amazing.
So now I have a Bud Light Lime.
Okay.
Now you will review the Bud Light Lime.
So,
mm.
Crisp, refreshing, delicious.
- 100%.
- This is like a seven foot one beer.
- It's a great beer.
It's a great beer.
Now, numerical value, please.
- I would honestly say this is like a 7.5, eight out of 10.
- I feel you on that.
I think I gave it an 8.1.
- Yeah.
This is like a power forward you can build a team around.
Definitely, definitely.
This is a Luka Doncic kind of like, this is an early all-star, young all-star.
Exactly.
He's in his first two seasons, but he's so good.
The raw talent is just there.
Yep.
You can definitely, this is pure raw talent.
That is what the Bud Light Lime is.
This is an amazing beer, you guys.
I would like to follow up Rex's beer with mine because I have something that I noticed when
I was just at the store just now.
Okay.
That I was looking through the beers and I, the most of like the kind of unique
looking beers or whatever, they just come with like this, like, what's this?
Like 12 ounce, like tiny ass can white, white cloth type shit, like small
white type shit.
Uh huh.
And I was wondering like, why does the U S have a monopoly on tall, tall boys?
Because we drink on the street.
We are street drinkers.
It's a street drinking culture.
You brown bag it.
Right.
OK.
Well, we have a living room culture
where you take-- you bring this into your living room
and you drink it, I guess.
This is a-- I think it's--
Norteña?
A Norteña.
Norteña.
Deluxe, it says.
Which means from the north.
That's a deluxe.
That's really, it goes down really easy.
Tastes like beer.
I don't hate it.
- That's a big win for you.
- That is an instant, seven feet tall,
8.9 type beer for me.
- Wow, okay, that's a ringing endorsement.
Of the beer hater.
- I don't hate beer.
- You do, you hate beer.
- The beer hater himself.
- Guys, it's episode 100.
- It's not.
We've been doing this show for two years.
And to ring in the 100th episode,
I thought what better than the first beer
I ever brought on this show, a Zwiewek.
That's right guys, this is a Polish beer
from another country.
And we are celebrating 100 episodes today,
right here, right now.
Here comes my sip and furthermore, my review.
- Rex, I don't know about you,
but I think Caleb might be fashionably early
to this celebration.
- Wow.
I mean, it tastes just as good as it did
a hundred episodes ago.
- He didn't review it under our paradigm.
- Oh, true.
- Because it was so early, so long ago
that he drank a drink.
- True, we were just babies.
- Yeah, so this actually needs a real review.
- Right.
- Guys, what is it to say?
This is, if you mixed a Guinness with a Bud Light,
that is like the exact flavor of this beer.
It has a funny, two funny people from another country
who think they're doing something cool by dancing.
They don't realize that that is in our country,
very embarrassing. - Been gay, yeah.
- So guys, this is a seven three.
- Okay. - A seven three
on the numerical scale. - Wow.
- And I would say that this is a six 10 or so
on the basketball player scale.
- Nothing but hitters tonight.
a really good bench player coming off playing 12 minutes.
- Yeah, yeah, you know, this is like a PJ Tucker.
This is a defense beer.
- Right. - This is, you know,
this is like 12 points, 15 rebounds, and three blocks.
Like this is like a good-- - Very reliable off the bench.
Not a starter.
- Yeah. - No star power.
- But every once in a while, gonna pop off
and have like a crazy offensive game.
- Yep. - So, yeah.
I mean, Zywek, guys, this is the king of Polish beer
and kind of dominates my neighborhood for a reason, I think.
This is a good beer, y'all.
- Yeah.
- Do you think you're becoming Polish slowly?
- I definitely look more Polish than I did
when I started living in this neighborhood.
- Yeah, you kind of look really Polish to me right now.
- Yeah, when I shave my head--
- Is it because his camera is displaying it 140 by 140?
- It is a little blurry, but he looks like a Polish man.
Like, I think I would see you getting, like,
killed in some sort of like road rage accident, like a.
Cause I'm driving on the wrong side of the road.
I moved to New York city and I don't,
I think I still drive on the wrong side. So I just start doing it.
Which by the way, that's what it's not in Poland.
You don't drive on the left side of the road.
You're the rule is you drive on the wrong side of the road.
That is actually the rule. Okay.
So I would move to New York and I'd keep doing that.
And I'd probably hurt a lot of, a lot of young people with a lot of talent.
That's why they have such trouble screwing in light bulbs.
It's like, you know,
they each one has to go the wrong direction before they put it in correctly.
They call them wrong bulbs.
Everything goes in the wrong way there.
Exactly.
That's why we have all these jokes here.
The first person puts it in.
He can't do it.
He's too stupid.
The second guy puts it in the wrong way because he thinks it's the right way.
The third guy does what the first guy does, but all together, they create one
brain capable of doing things properly the wrong way.
- Yeah, I would really like to experiment with these people,
put them in cardboard mazes,
and put scratch off lottery tickets at the end,
and see if they're like those fungus
that can find a cookie or whatever.
That would be pretty cool.
- Guys, I have the best idea.
We should do a live show in Poland.
We should go to...
- I'm down.
- Where?
- Warsaw. - In the city in Poland.
Okay.
- Warsaw, Poland. - Warzone, yep.
- I'm down to go to a Warzone.
You guys wanna go to a Rebirth Island?
We should do a show on Rebirth Island.
A live show on Rebirth Island.
- We should do a show in the Fortnite Island.
- That's a pretty good idea.
So tell me, what is it like being in the middle
of a Twitch.tv subathon, guys?
These are one of the biggest, hottest things
in the world right now.
And you know, among us, one of the very stars of it.
You know, when I when I came back from my road trip, I was like,
this is this trip has drained me economically so much
that I definitely need to put a lot of hours into the streaming this month.
I was like, oh, what did I just lean into that joke about doing a jubileo timber?
And I actually do it.
But in such a way where I can actually, like, you know, step away
from the computer and actually do my job on a computer without my
computer blowing up. So what I did is we have like the Paul
radio stuff. So whenever I'm not actually streaming or like
playing something on on on the stream, it's just going with
like old Paul episodes. And I thought that my life would be
perfect, but it's completely not. It is so tiring. And I
wanted to go lay down for like two hours just to watch stick
- Here's the thing, man, not every time you stream,
you don't, stop streaming yourself weightlifting.
Why have you had it in your head
that every single time you go live,
you have to be lifting heavy, heavy weights?
This doesn't, of course you're tired.
- That's my content, that's what I'm known for.
I can't break out.
- You should try variety streaming.
You should do an Among Us playthrough.
- So, funny you say that, but variety streamers
are usually the most popular ones in the industry,
but it's the hardest to become popular at
if you become a variety streamer.
The best way to get known is to be like
a specific one thing streamer.
- That's why everybody who streams now
is from like World of Warcraft or RuneScape
or shit like that, right? - Yeah, it's WoW, RuneScape,
I think a couple from League, I guess.
- Overwatch.
- What game did Hasan Piker play?
He was a professional, what? - Yeah, OnlyFans.
- He played Warzone, I think.
He played a little bit of Warzone, I think.
- And now he talks about Warzones, that is interesting.
- That's true.
- That is actually quite interesting.
- He's turning our youth's brains into Warzones.
- That's right.
A lot of our youth's homes are Warzones,
'cause they have two dads and they start,
that just doesn't work, man, straight up.
- No.
- It's okay, I think having a husband works,
but dads are so mean.
I can't believe that some of these people live with two dads.
That's going to be so fucking hard.
So have you ever met a mean gay guy?
Are you fucking joking?
Is that a joke?
I would never say a joke like that.
Yes, I have been gay guys.
I've been watching in the mirror family guy on Hulu.
And I have, you know, Hulu has ads
And I have got maybe 200 ads in the last three days for
prep and getting HIV tested.
That's you know, hey, you guys, everybody knows a story
about the lady who got the ads from Target about pregnancy stuff
and then found out she was pregnant.
Guys, I hate to say it.
We're going to be losing Rex to one of the most dangerous diseases
known to mankind,
which is HIV AIDS.
- Okay, I thought we were gonna go with someone else.
- Well actually no, this means that you are,
wait is prep, you take it to avoid AIDS
or it's when you have it?
- It's to avoid it.
- Okay, so this just means that it's in your future.
You still have time.
- Right, it means that I'm having a ton of
mind-blowing gay sex and then I--
- Well not even gay, maybe with a woman who has something--
- Gay woman.
- Yeah, it could be with a gay woman.
(whimpering)
- I mean, I think Magic Johnson got this disease
from having sex with many women.
I don't think he ever has had sex with a man.
- Phones could read our future, like magic balls.
Magic phones.
- There's a new tarot cards.
- Yeah.
- They're kind of the new everything.
- They're kind of like shaped like a tarot card, actually,
if you think about it.
- Wait, and your background looks like a tarot card.
- Oh my God, the 730 of AIDS.
- Holy shit.
What the fuck is that?
Is that some Junji Ito bullshit?
- I don't know, I forget what I got that image from.
- Well, it looks scary and I'd like to not see it anymore,
so put that damn device away.
- Infernal device.
- I think, you know, when all this AI stuff
started popping off a couple months ago,
I was thinking the entire time,
Don't we already have AI Akinator?
(laughing)
Couldn't we do Akinator for every question?
No, 'cause you gotta pay for it.
Well, once you pay for it though,
if the Akinator, guess what the cure to cancer is?
He's gonna get it, he's never wrong.
I think he only does people though.
I think that's all he knows.
But I'm saying--
- Maybe you can ask him, wait,
maybe you can ask him, Akinator,
who's the person who knows how to cure cancer?
- There we go.
- Now.
- That makes way more sense than what I was saying.
Yeah, just get people, just the people who we need,
we can find them with Akinator.
This is a good idea.
- Do you think people would be a lot less resistant to AI
if there was just a little genie
that hovered on the right of your screen and used it?
No fucking question.
If they brought back Clippy and put that on AI, people would be typing in their social
security numbers in a fucking instant.
Didn't people hate Clippy?
Wasn't that the thing?
They certainly did.
Not my generation's Z-ass.
I thought it was ironically funny.
They hated him and now they think that they thought it was lovely when he was gone and
dead.
He's been dead for so long.
What was the one with the kangaroo?
What's up?
Oh, Banzai Buddy?
Bonsai buddy?
Maybe Bonsai buddy.
That's a monkey. That's a monkey.
Oh yeah. Monkey. The purple monkey. Yeah.
Yeah. The purple monkey.
You know, here's what I miss you guys.
Here's the character, the, the off,
oft forgotten character that I really, uh, miss.
Jeeves.
Oh yes.
Instead of something stupid like chat GPT, it should be ask
- Jeeves. - Chad Jeeves.
- Jeeve, Chad Jeeves.
(laughing)
Chad Jeeves would be amazing, dude.
- Yeah. - Jeeves.
And that even sounds better coming off the tongue.
Jeeves, write my essay for me.
Right away, sir.
- You don't talk to Chad, you do your write to it.
- Well, it's like having a butler.
And you know, what is AI if not a slave?
- That was always the confusing thing
about the branding of Ask Jeeves,
is that you would never ask your butler
what the weather is.
He's mostly there to bring you ice cream.
- Yeah, but he would bring you the newspaper.
And the newspaper would have the weather.
- Well, maybe the newspaper.
- And yeah, it'd be his job to stay abreast
of current events.
- I thought that he was purely, basically,
an ice cream machine.
- No, you're living in Home Alone 2.
- No, listen, I live in a castle.
I'm at the top story of the castle.
It's like three miles for me to leave the place.
Okay.
And I need to find out what's going on around.
I'm not doing that myself.
I have paperwork.
I have castle.
I gotta like read books in my expensive chair.
Someone's coming up with your boat today.
Yeah.
Right.
And I go, Jeeves, what's that sound out there?
Jeeves.
He goes, I'm on it.
Jeeves comes back.
I'm on it.
Yeah.
I just asked Jeeves to bring a little bag
to take care of that little problem of yours.
Oh yeah, hey Jeeves, how about you bring a bag over?
Yeah. Yeah.
Bring a bag over and throw all these cans on my desk.
Oh, I was thinking that maybe he was gonna bring drugs.
Oh my God, dude!
(laughing)
It's gotten, how have you let this happen?
Man.
I knew it.
How is this fucking possible to?
I know we did this last week
And I think it would be lame if we just keep bringing it over and over again.
But yesterday I was talking to Rex and Annie,
we were playing a game and we were just like silently just playing,
and suddenly I just hear like this loud crashing.
I was like, "Dude, what is your problem?"
He's like, "Sorry, I jumped. There's so many cans in my desk."
So it's going to the point where there's so many cans on his desk
that he can't even just like operate without knocking a few or several of them over.
four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14,
15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26.
- Got that one. - 27.
- Yep.
- That is so fucking insane, man.
- We need to send you to hoarders.
- Just throw it away, bro.
- We're sending you to hoarders.
- This is hoarding behavior.
This is not normal.
You're passing this off as a normal male behavior.
This is not normal male behavior, guys.
I'm sorry, that's wrong.
That is normal male behavior, I'm sorry.
No, to have 27, no, maybe three.
I disagree.
Maybe three.
27?
Sound off in the comments.
Nobody does this, dude.
No. This is not normal.
I've done this since I was a mere boy.
That doesn't surprise me.
That's because you've been wrong your entire life.
Because you've always been weird.
This is something, this is a,
you need to see a psychoanalyst about this.
I used to have tens of Arizona iced tea cans on my desk
before I drank Monster.
- So it is a collecting thing then?
It's not out of pure laziness.
- It's not a collector, it's completely out of laziness.
- No, it's not completely, you like it, you like it.
- I don't hate it, I'll say that much.
- Can we-- - You think it's a little fun.
- Can we just, you know--
- I think it's funny.
- Let's just break it even, you know,
let's not go to our side where you do the right thing
and you clean your fucking desk,
Or let's not be on your side,
we just have all the shit on your desk.
Let's build a wall right behind you.
Some decorations, something creative.
Put 'em all up and see how long it takes for you to make
to completely cover that wall behind you.
- I guess if I got a little bit of some glue
and did that, put a little inner ring.
- That is hoarding.
If you're gluing cans to your wall, you are a hoarder.
- Well no, I'm making art, which is completely different.
This is not art. This is like when my dad got divorced and he convinced himself that it was
artistic for him to
Modge podge every wine label that he drank onto a piece of canvas
It's just this is not art man. My dad gave these out for Christmas
People were like, oh, okay. Thank you, man. And he's like, yeah, what if I really heard of that? I drank all that wine
But hear me out
what if I
I gathered them all together in a big bag,
and I gave it to the homeless guy
who nods out on the stairs in front of my apartment,
and then he used it to buy one cigarette
with the five cent refund.
- Whoa.
- Yeah, I mean, that's definitely a better option
than letting them just sit on your desk,
to the point where now you have almost no real estate.
If you wanna use your desk for something,
you're gonna have to start stacking them.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- And I'd hate to say what kind of thing
you come up with in terms of stacking.
- I would love to see a stacking situation.
- There's plenty of room over here.
- If you put it over there, it blocks your fucking computer.
It blocks your monitor.
- No it doesn't.
- I would love, I would love for it to just--
- That's where I use my mouse, I don't understand.
There's so much mouse space.
- Yeah, that's where you use your mouse.
- We're gonna be playing Valorant
and she's gonna be like knocking shit over.
Like just like turning around.
- Do you not have a mouse pad?
- Wait.
- I knew it. - Dude, that's not that crazy.
- I knew it. - Wait, wait, wait.
- I knew you didn't have a mouse pad.
I was wondering why you got so much worse at Valorant
since you've been in New York.
You don't have a mouse pad. - I haven't had a mouse pad
in months.
No, it's because my ping is fucking 15 versus 70.
- I said you got worse.
- I know.
- No, it's the no mouse pad.
That is fucking crazy.
That's crazy. - It's not that crazy.
No, that's not crazy.
- That is so crazy.
- All right, let's address these claims separately.
- Okay.
- The mouse pad thing, I can hear you,
but they get dirty and I throw them away.
- That's fine, just do that then.
- Just clean them.
- They cost $10, you get clean them easy.
- I know, I just need to get a new one.
- You clean the bathtub.
- I just need a new one, that's all.
- Months.
- The second, and it has been many months
since I've had one.
- Okay, that makes perfect sense.
Everything is lining up in my brain.
As for the claim that I have become worse at Valorant,
it's true.
However, it is absolutely related to the fact
that I have adapted completely to playing with AD ping.
- I've noticed it looks like you're playing
with like a mouse that shakes around.
It's because the sensor is on wood instead of cloth
like it's supposed to be,
and it's bouncing all around and getting fucked up.
- All right, you know what?
I will get a mouse pad and we will put this claim
the test. We will put this to the test. You're going to be amazing at video games once you get a mouse pad.
That's not the issue. I'm just bad at video games.
I haven't seen you in two weeks. That's not true. We talked literally yesterday.
I haven't seen you in three weeks. And I saw Caleb on Monday.
He's been around. He's been around. He's been, "Hey, okay, yeah, fuck me. I'll kill myself."
I'm not talking about Caleb. You say one mean thing about me, I will kill myself.
No, I was trying to do that.
I'm just not gaming.
I'm on...
I'm like on Pacific time,
but I'm in Eastern time.
So I wake up at noon,
but it's like I'm waking up at 9am
in California. So it's like the perfect...
Man, you used to be cool.
Now you're just like walking around talking about
being part of a
podcast and
meeting
creators.
even call us anymore he has been really busy meeting leftist creators he hung
out with Vouch the other day and Rex said why doughnuts he said uh well I'm
humongously fat actually you must know did you see that plane that had to turn
around because there was shit all in the house.
Saw it, I lived it.
You didn't live it.
No, I wasn't on the plane.
But did you see it?
I saw the thing, the thing, what do you call that?
The news story. What is the details of this news story?
There is, I think it was a baby, or like a kid,
had like explosive diarrhea on a plane,
and shit his pants, and just completely like
liquid shit just like ran down the aisle like ten rows of seats on a plane and so
they were like it was so disgusting it smelled so horrible it was such a
hazard that they just turned the plane around. You know what, before they even
turned around so it was a plane coming from like Atlanta it was going to
Barcelona it's a long intercontinental flight. That's a very long flight.
And he had just left the airport, I guess.
And I guess this person just felt like, first thing I'm going to do in this plane is stand
up and shit all over the plane.
So that happens.
And they said that they were spraying like vanilla, like, I don't know, like odor or
whatever.
So like the smell would at least like stop.
But people were saying that it just smelled like vanilla poop.
So they were like, no, we're going to turn this shit around.
So they turn around and they land in Atlanta again, and they have to rip out the carpet.
Someone told me recently that they got on a flight and there was a guy who was really,
really late to the boarding process, got to the gate right before the gate closed, and
his bag was too heavy to get on.
He's covered in sweat, drenched in sweat, because he'd ran the whole way.
And his bag was too heavy to take on the plane as a carry-on or whatever.
And so he took like seven pairs of pants and seven shirts out of the bag and put them on.
And it was like, okay, put all of these layers on.
It was like, okay, now can you take it?
And they're like, yeah, I guess so, whatever.
And he got on the plane.
That doesn't make sense.
The plane smelled, yeah, it makes no sense, but the plane smelled like so bad because
this guy was covered in sweat already and then put on seven layers to get on the plane.
I think it was, maybe it was a different flight,
but I think it was this same flight
that he was telling me about
where they smelled something awful
while they were in the air
and they thought that it was him,
but it turned, and so they started like
spraying air freshener everywhere,
and it turns out it was like an electronic
that was melting in the plane,
and so they had to land in Buffalo.
- Oh my God. - This little guy.
- This guy, if they had not realized this,
this plane would have gone down
'cause this guy wanted to be disgustingly stinky.
- That's crazy.
- Yeah, planes are scary, man.
- Imagine dying because someone else smelled bad.
- Yeah, at least make it me.
- Someone else smelled so bad.
- At least kill me on one of my stinkiest days.
- They're not that scary.
They're a little uncomfortable.
- I'm pretty scared.
Every single time I get on a plane,
I come fully to terms with my own death.
- When's the last time an American died on a plane crash?
- Probably like last week, two weeks ago.
Dude, on like a truly commercial,
yeah, a commercial plane.
I don't know, it's been a long time.
You know, in the other parts of the world,
they're fucking dying all the time.
Their planes suck, man.
Yeah, they're dying like roadrunner-ass acne deaths.
All the time.
Yeah, you know, they're fucking driving the plane
into a mountain, they're crashing into a tree
because they saw a woman's ass on the sidewalk
from 7,000 feet away.
They're always doing that in like, you know,
Mexico, Malaysia.
- You do that, doesn't happen.
- These planes just go.
- So there's-- - I don't know what that is about.
Do we just get the best planes in America?
'Cause now our planes seem to not go down that often.
- I think so, I just Googled it
and there's conflicting information.
Some are saying like last time was 2009, 2013.
But there's this Wikipedia article that's called,
List of Fatal Accidents and Incidents
involving commercial aircraft in the in the US. And there's been
one incident this year. And it's had one fatality. And the
incident is called the 2023 San Antonio ground crew suicide
incident.
Okay, I don't know if that counts. But I guess I guess if
we could if we're not counting that that was like it was like
last year,
can you fucking click on the article and tell me how he died?
He suicided.
I think I don't care about, I don't care about, uh,
Did he hang himself from the wing?
I mean, there's so many options.
Probably did jump in the turbine.
I feel like that's a pretty, that's a decent way to go.
Oh wait, nevermind.
A ground crewman was ingested into an engine of the aircraft
operating Delta, Delta airlines.
So it wasn't even, and it wasn't even on the air.
So I don't think it counts.
I don't think it counts either.
Yeah, he was simply ingested.
That's an interesting way to put that.
I don't think I care about beautiful birds in the sky.
Ate him.
I'm pretty scared of planes.
I don't care about planes being like the like cancer to the
environment anymore.
When I was I don't want to drive to a destination ever again.
I just want to fly there.
I had this math teacher when I was in high school was just a
fucking bitch.
She just like sucked everyone hated her and then everyone
figured out that the reason she was a bitch was that her
husband got sucked into like a engine turbine and liquidated
like in front of her.
And so everyone, everyone's like, yeah, she fucking deserves that.
Am I right?
She kept teaching.
It was like years before.
Oh, God, I would.
But yeah, she had she had a very bad disposition,
which I guess, you know, makes sense considering that's like a horrific thing
to go through.
Yeah, that's pretty tough.
Don't take it out on me.
Yeah, leave that shit at home.
People always go one or two ways if something really bad happens in their lives.
They either become very good people or so fucking annoying.
And at first when somebody's like really annoying because their entire family was wiped out in a massacre,
you go, "Oh, I understand."
Until you meet somebody else whose family is wiped out, who's a complete Mother Teresa,
and you go, "Oh, fuck this other bitch. What the fuck is that?"
Yeah, what the fuck is your problem?
- Yeah, smile more, sweet cheeks.
What's the big, what's the deal?
- Fucking dumb, fat bitch.
- Yeah, I don't, I don't even say fat.
But yeah, what is the issue?
You know, just put a, you know, smile through the pain.
It's not that hard.
- Yeah, I say that--
- I didn't kill your family.
That you, I mean, at least I never proved it.
You know?
- There's a Polish bald guy who did it.
- Yeah.
- Some guy that looks like he was made of PS1 graphics.
- Okay, so you've been noticing I've been going to the gym.
Thank you.
His entire face is eight triangles.
This is sounding like a compliment to me, personally.
Guys, to change the subject abruptly,
I'm kind of bummed that we had to record tonight.
And it's not because I don't miss you guys
and love talking to you both.
Yeah.
And love talking to our non-sober gophers that listen.
It is that tonight I was supposed to watch the new episode of Tucker Carlson on X.com
where he talks to the man who smoked crack and had sex with President Barack Hussein
Obama.
Guys, this is going to blow this whole case wide open.
It's exactly, listen, my grandpa called it the first time he saw him on TV.
He looked at Barack Obama and said, "That guy smokes crack.
I swear to God he said that."
And then he started talking and he said,
and you know what, I think he might be gay also.
Guys, Pete DeVita cracked the case, okay?
Why aren't they having him on Tucker?
That's all I'm saying.
But I need to listen to this.
I need to listen to this episode.
I need to watch this.
This is important information.
- I'm shocked that it's happening.
- It's finally happening.
Where was this guy years ago?
Why couldn't he have stopped this guy
from turning our country into a communist wasteland
before he got in front of the nuclear codes.
- It's a shame. - Power codes.
- Power codes.
- He had to wait until Obama killed his gay lover,
chef, to come out.
He could have saved that man.
- He easily could have saved that man.
- Why does it matter at this point, is my question.
- That's a little bit the problem, is like,
you know, that's the only thing,
and it is the only thing, the one and only thing
that makes me maybe not think this guy
is all that creditable.
It's because he is doing this at a time
when it doesn't matter.
What's he gonna do?
If Netflix finds out Obama's gay,
they're gonna give him 10 more shows.
- Yeah.
Spotify's gonna give him 11 more podcasts.
- Exactly, so I don't understand what he's trying to--
- You know what the--
- This is cancel culture, I'll say it.
This is cancel culture.
- Yeah.
- They're trying to cancel him
'cause he smoked crack and was gay for many, many years.
He smoked crack for over 50 years.
That's not a big deal anymore.
- How old is he?
- He's probably in his 50s.
- I think Tucker Carlson should kill that guy
and just blame it on Obama and see what happens.
- He could get away with it.
He could easily get away with it.
- You think so?
- Yeah.
No jury in America would convict him.
- I think it would be really cool to come out
and be like, you know, Bill Clinton raped me
when I was 12 years old,
and then come up with one of those
like Rube Goldberg style suicides
where you like hang yourself and shoot yourself
in the head like 15 times.
- Uh-huh.
(laughing)
Even better, rig it to Bill Clinton's.
And even better idea is you rig this to Bill Clinton's stove or something.
So he goes to turn on the stove.
Wait, what's that?
Is that a marble?
I don't remember putting that there.
Falls out the window, falls down 50 different tracks, goes about 25 miles,
presses onto a bazooka that you have positioned, a boardroom that you have
positioned in your mouth, you have your mouth wrapped around it like Riley Reed.
And then it just blows your head off.
Yeah.
I think someone should do that.
- It's a good idea. - Yeah, Clinton like trips on a banana peel
and he like kicks it into a little lever that tips the ball over.
Yeah.
Or just straight up, an anvil falls on your head and then yeah, he's in jail forever.
You did your thing.
I think, I do think that this might have been this guy, I was thinking about like, if you
were in your 60s and you were like, "Okay, it's finally time to come out to my family."
Like I've been holding in this secret about myself, my sexuality for so long, and holding
it in has been slowly killing me, eating away at me.
I need to tell my family."
And you sit them down and you say, "Guys, I'm gay."
And then maybe you panic and you say, "And I had sex with Barack Obama."
"And we were smoking crack."
"And we were smoking crack, guys.
Or at least I thought I was gay.
It turns out it was the crack I was smoking with Barack Obama that was making me just
I think I was gay.
Yeah. And he did it.
It would be funny.
Do you have ever seen those like news stories?
That's like, uh, it's like an old couple.
They're like in their eighties and they'll be like, uh, my, uh, TV ordered $400 in
gay porn pay-per-view.
Uh, I think it would be funny to do that, but it's like, you know, you like cheat on
your wife with like someone at work or something.
And she's like, Oh, where were you?
and you were like, "I was smoking crack with Obama."
The president?
- Smoking crack with, just big up talk.
Smoking crack with Obama?
- Obama?
Like you're like--
- With Barack Obama?
- You're looking around your house
and you've got the TV on, you see a crack in your walls
'cause you're-- - Oh, smoking crack with--
- Broke, and then you like turn to your left
and there's a TV and Obama's on it,
and you're like, "With Obama?"
- With Barack Obama, the TV has Tiger Woods on it.
With Barack Obama.
(laughing)
Smoking crack with Barack Obama, that's what I was doing.
Sorry.
And we were having gay sex.
I did see one clip from the interview, his teaser trailer if you will, where he says
the guy's like, "Yes, we were smoking crack and we were having gay oral sex and I could
tell it wasn't his first time and I'd be willing to bet it wasn't his last."
So he was saying not only did he look like he knew what he was doing, he seemed so insatiable
and desperate for more that he's certain that he continued to have sex with men after this episode.
I just want to know how they found this guy.
Probably at a bus stop.
In that teaser he was like, "Oh, the media doesn't care about the truth. They never hit me up."
I guess. But how do you find him?
Yeah, where were you saying this?
Yeah. We need to look into his records.
Maybe Tucker Carlson's hanging out at crack-smoking gay clubs.
Yeah.
And he just took a hit of the pookie and he's saying, "So what's new?" You know?
And the guy said, "Oh, well, I had sex with Barack Obama and we were smoking crack."
And he spit out his... he did a spit take with the crack smoke that he had just inhaled.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, what?
Yeah. Said, "Oh, wait, okay. That's actually pretty cool. Do you want to come on TV?"
Well, not TV. Do you want to come on a website?
He just does like a Twitter podcast, which is so weird.
Now that we're finished with him, do you think we could link up?
Tucker, if you would like to come on the podcast about Liz's Patreon, if you want to become
part of the podcast about Liz's family, all you had to do was ask.
You didn't have to stage this whole Barack Obama crack smoking thing.
Yeah, we think that's funny.
It definitely got our attention, but we would have just done it, man.
would be your lie to get famous?
Like in 40 years, what are you, what are you lying about?
I feel like an easy one is just say anything about North Korea.
People just believe it.
That's true.
So say I went to North Korea and I, I, uh,
Oh, like I escaped and they made me eat.
Should I start going on Joe Rogan and saying I escaped North Korea?
Yeah, they made me completely bald because I wouldn't get the North Korean hairstyle.
They whited me.
They opened my eyes.
Because they want everybody to fit in there.
Yeah, they completely whited me.
They taught me perfect English and I couldn't communicate with my North Korean peers.
They made me drink beer since I was three years old.
Yep, kind of awesome, a little bit awesome.
They run me over 1 million times every single Thursday
for no reason. - I don't know,
I feel like that is good.
The guy, have you guys seen this guy
who's like a YouTuber who made a video
that was called like, "My Plane Crashed?"
And he pretended that his plane crashed,
but he just jumped out of his plane.
You haven't seen this?
He's in jail now. - No.
- So he crashed the plane by like doing an ejection?
- But it said that it was like failing.
But he just is like, but the video is just him like flying the plane and
there's being like, oh crap, it's going down and it's nothing is happening.
And then he just, he already has a fucking jet pack on or whatever it's called
parachute. And he just jumps out of the plane and just takes like an awesome
GoPro video of him jumping out on a parachute.
And then the plane just like crashed into a mountain, but it could have hit
somebody. Yeah. I mean you're not allowed to do that with a car, let alone a plane.
Hang on, I think we should advocate for the freedom of this guy. I just saw Mr.
Beast shoot three tanks over and over again and just blow up basically like a
nuke in just some yard. But I'm sure that he asked the police. Yeah you have to get
permission to do stunts like that. Like this guy could have done it if he didn't
just do it with it for you'll see didn't do a very good job faking it they found
the plane it was basically in one piece and they were like nothing is wrong with
this plane.
Yeah so black box there's that's the whole point they can always figure out
if something went wrong with the plane.
Yeah but no one died nothing happened Mr. Beast is arming a militia.
Yeah but if you crash a plane that's an insurance thing they're gonna check that.
No I don't know if he got into insurance I don't know if he tried to do insurance
If he was smart he would have, but I'm not sure that he did.
That's what I would have done.
- Yeah.
- That seems like a no brainer to me.
- I think it looked good.
- I mean, there's no way like 2 million views on YouTube
is gonna be enough to pay for a new plane.
- I don't know, YouTube pays pretty well, man.
(laughing)
- Yeah, yes sir.
- I mean, do you know how much a plane costs?
- This was like a crappy plane.
- I did think that you were talking about
like a commercial plane, I was like,
"Whoa, that's crazy." - No, no, it wasn't a plane,
it wasn't a jet, it wasn't like a commercial anything.
It was probably a $15,000 plane, if I had to guess.
- It's not a bicycle, it's a plane.
They're like hundreds of thousands of dollars.
- Not like a little plane, they're not that expensive.
Look up cheapest plane.
- Cheapest plane. - I think you can get
a cheap plane for like a couple thousand bucks.
- Cheaper than Caleb's car at this time.
- Definitely, definitely.
Like a single person plane
with like a little propeller at the front.
- Yeah.
- They're not that expensive.
- It's made out of paper and it doesn't fly.
- They're not like a million dollars.
- It's also small.
- Yeah, you can't fit anybody but you in that thing.
He's doing research, he's researching us.
The cheapest plane that I can find is 45,000.
Yeah.
But think about, but what about used?
No, that is used.
No, but I could find a cheaper plane.
More harshly used.
I could find one.
Yeah.
One that you're willing to crash.
It's nothing to you.
Check marketplace.
These are 1970 Cessnas, the just shittiest plane you can buy that still flies.
Nah, those are Cessnas last forever.
How many miles does it have on it?
Does that matter?
You think?
How many air miles does it have on it?
Uh, let's see.
Time.
405 Smough.
That's a lot of Smough.
That's hella Smough.
I don't know what that means.
That's a lot.
How would you guys do it?
How would you guys become famous fraudulently?
I think something really easy is just like faking like a, like a interaction with a famous person that already died.
Oh yeah.
Cause they can't deny it.
Who would you fake it about?
Elvis raped me when I was one year old.
Well, I should have died long before you were alive.
You can prove that. How old am I?
You're 27.
You can't. No, that's not my age.
You're 28.
You're thinking?
Well, you didn't even know, so it doesn't even matter.
Converting it to metric?
Yeah, it is. 28.
You're 28? You were born in 1994?
Or '95?
Yeah. So, uh, yeah, Elvis probably died in the late 80s if I had to guess,
but I don't actually know, I guess.
Michael Jackson killed my dad.
That one makes a little more sense. That one makes some sense.
You could say that your dad tried to touch his monkey
and Michael Jackson killed him.
Yeah. I think I can get away with that.
Your father is alive as far as I know.
He completely is. Yeah.
So that makes it a little tougher, I guess.
Listen, he said 40 years in the future.
I think when you're old, you can just say anything and maybe like
some insane person from Fox's will hear it and it'll make you famous.
That is true.
This guy did seem a little old.
I felt like Barack Obama, this guy was like maybe 20 years
older than Barack Obama.
And maybe he wouldn't go for that.
Do you think he'd go for you?
An old gay guy?
Yeah, of course an old gay guy would go for me.
- No, Barack Obama.
- Barack Obama, yeah, an old gay guy.
Yeah, he would definitely, I'm their type.
- You're their type?
- Yeah.
- What are you?
What type do you fall in?
- A super, a super top, an ultra top.
- Mega top.
- Yeah, a mega top as some might say.
A giga top.
- Right, you have the biggest head-shaped penis.
- I'm a human walking penis.
- Penis-shaped head, yeah.
- Yeah, they give me a little temporary tattoo
on the top of my head.
And I get-- - If you had a bowl cut,
you would just look straight up.
- Jump into people's butts.
- I think that's any bowl cut, no?
- I had a bowl cut when I was a kid.
My mom called it a surfer cut.
And I said, "This is a bowl cut."
She said, "Nope, it's a surfer cut."
(laughing)
- What's a surfer cut?
It doesn't exist, I'll tell you that, Julio.
It does not exist, but my mom told me that I had one.
- The kids at school did not think that it was real.
- No, if it did exist,
the kids at school did not know what it was.
They had never heard of the surfer cut, apparently.
- You think I should get a surfer cut myself?
- I think that you would look amazing with a surfer cut.
- I have long hair right now.
- You would look like, okay,
you would actually look like an Edward.
- Yeah.
- What's an Edward?
- Or an Edgar.
- Oh, I see.
- Yeah.
- You would look like a Fred.
- Yeah, you would look like a complete Edgar.
which I still never really got an answer
as to what an Edgar is.
- This is like a stereotypical like South Texas,
South California and Mexican essay type of guy.
- Who they have bowl cuts?
- Hey fool, you like Rick Owens?
- That's Edgar, yeah.
- I saw a video, I sent it to you earlier.
- You like wearing hood by air pants?
- You sent me a video?
- Yeah, I sent a video earlier.
You should play it into the microphone.
I sent it into the work group chat.
It's a guy who--
The Chilaquiles Burrito?
Yeah, it's a guy who I've been following for a long time
and I thought that it was a Mexican guy.
I was born Mexican.
For the first 10 years of my life,
I was raised by a Mexican lady.
This is a white guy.
The other day, how Kevin--
Whoa!
Chilaquiles Burrito and it instantly reminded me of her.
We were extremely poor and my mom had to work long hours
and that's why I barely got to see her.
Why is he talking like that?
And he needs to make us these burritos
anytime he wants. That's his voice,
that's what I'm saying.
That's his voice. That's crazy.
And he makes videos-- Wait, hang on, hang on.
Where he doesn't show his face
And he makes videos where he's like,
today we're going to be making a Tapatio burrito.
- This is what it looks like.
It looks like a complete white guy.
It looks like he's--
- Yeah, he's white.
- He's just like a white guy
who had a Mexican nanny growing up
and he just started talking like that.
Isn't that awesome?
- That is awesome.
He's also making something that looks really delicious.
- He's making a Chilaquiles burrito.
Too many carbs for me, but I--
- I love Chilaquiles, bro.
- I feel like Kayla's burrito,
that's just like three burritos.
That's just-- - You know what?
- It's just tia.
- In Mexico City, they love doing that shit.
I don't wanna speak up too loud
because my girlfriend loves Mexico City,
but they just do that shit.
They put tamales in bread and just show a tamale torta,
and that's what they eat during the winter.
- Are they as fat as balloons?
- Some of them.
I don't know, I've never been.
(laughing)
- Well you have to remember, they're three feet tall.
So walking to the street corner for them is like--
- They're burning off calories, yeah.
- Yeah. - That's a good point.
- They do have much better public transport
so they actually walk around the train stations, I guess,
jumping into it and whatnot.
- Yeah, jumping like beans.
- Yeah.
- Whoa.
- What?
That's not racist.
- Did you guys ever have jumping beans when you were a kid?
- No.
I don't even know what that means.
- Well, it's these beans that they put
in this little plastic container and they jump around.
- Oh yeah, I think I saw a tiktok about this.
Don't they have like worms inside?
- Yeah, they have bugs in them.
That's why they jump.
How sad is this?
There's no such thing as a magical jumping bean, you guys.
I'm sorry to break that fiction.
This is like a Wendigoon video.
Guys, this is an animal that has been trapped in a bean.
Not that cool.
- I think that's pretty cool.
- Not that cool.
Not as cool as a magical jump.
Well, if you start at magic,
there's almost nowhere to go but down.
So an animal stuck in a bean,
I just don't care all that much.
- What about a boy stuck in a peach?
They wrote a book about that.
- A boy stuck in a peach, a boy stuck in a balloon.
These are more interesting stories to me
because they involve humans.
- But a bug stuck in a bean?
- A bug is so stupid, of course it gets stuck in a--
- That's a boy for someone.
That's a boy for another species.
And I have no interest in becoming a citizen of these species.
What if it was Earthworm Jim?
Earthworm Jim?
He started, he watched one TikTok, listened to one TikTok about a guy who's a white dude who talks Mexican.
He's like, "What if it was Earthworm Jim?"
What the fuck is wrong with you, man?
Come on, bro. You're being fucking racist.
If it was Earthworm Jim, maybe.
That'd be your lie to become famous in 40 years.
I had an answer to this and I completely forgot it because I was looking at airplanes on eBay.
Yeah, you seemed pretty invested for a sec.
Did you find one?
Yeah, they get pretty cheap, but what's more fun is you can buy those little carts.
We were right.
He didn't tell us out loud, but we were definitely right.
You can find those little carts that they drive around the airport on.
Really?
Oh, shit.
Yeah, and they're like $2,000.
That'd be really fun, I think.
I think they'll be awesome.
I think. I've always thought that that would be a good job for me. That would be fun until the cops
just like shoot you because that's not street legal. Yeah, but let me tell you, I took a cab
the other day and I saw this dude on a quad like maneuvering between pedestrians on the sidewalk.
Yeah, people just do that in like Bushwick and Bed-Stuy. Yeah, so imagine if you had
like a pallet of beer on the back of it.
And then you're just going around.
Nobody's going to complain.
Yeah.
If you just hit someone, you give them a beer.
Fuck it.
I've never told you guys.
Uber eats guy.
A cab.
I did ever tell you guys about the time that I was eating outside at Zatar in
Bushwick, which maybe you guys have been to, I don't know, but there was a, there's
two guys on a moped riding down the street and a car just t-boned both of them.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And they just flew over the fucking car and they looked completely dead and then they got up and
they just walked over the guy and they just like hung out with him for like 30 minutes and then
left. That's so awesome.
It was amazing.
They hung out?
They hung out with the guy who hit them with their car, with his car.
This isn't really my story to tell, but I was like,
Pat was like saying that he got like hit, like talking about what happened after he got hit by
and I was like, Oh yeah, I remember like last year you got hit by a car. He's like, No, no,
it happened again, like two weeks ago.
It's I mean,
He's just a constant magnet for it.
He's got a kind of wide figure. He's got the wide broad shoulders.
I don't think the shoulders of the figure matter at all. I think he just loves riding a bike
and like closing his eyes to see what happens.
I, he's been talking about riding his bike more and I can imagine that he's
probably on his phone 90% of the time when he's riding a bike.
Well, that's normal.
What are you going to do?
Pay attention to the road?
I don't think you're supposed to use your telephone as you're riding your bike.
No, like Uber Eats drivers do it all the time.
They, they're looking at, you know, the map and like whatever.
He can use it to bounce the duck.
They know that their lives don't matter that much.
That is like a guy, a creative like Patrick.
You can't be looking at your phone as you.
That's like 100 Uber Eats drivers.
Yeah, exactly. It's not even it's not even comparable.
Yeah, it's going to be awesome when there's only two jobs,
which is a podcaster and Uber Eats driver.
We're almost there.
Yeah, I mean, that's already the New York City
economy is podcasters who don't live, leave their apartments,
giving money to Uber Eats drivers who run their errands for them.
It is crazy how many people, you know what's even worse than, actually maybe it's better,
I was going to say, you know what's worse than like somebody who has like one of these stupid
creative jobs, like a, I mean creative, like jobs like a Twitch streamer or a podcaster at
like a low level, is people who are like trying really hard to do that and just failing man.
That is true. That just kills me, man.
But I actually think it's probably braver.
Yeah, there's a lot of respect for me
when people do the like go fund me to buy a gaming PC
and then stream for three months, realize they are just
a black hole of charisma and wit and run off with a new computer.
That is admirable to me.
Yeah, that is that is kind of cool, actually.
- Does that shit happen still in GoFundMe?
- I don't know about GoFundMe,
but that definitely still happens.
- I feel like there was a bunch of GoFundMe scans
for a little while, and then they were like,
"We're gonna crack down on this shit.
"You need to actually be the person,
"you need to have a real thing."
But every day we get an email from this fake joke
GoFundMe that Patrick made months ago,
And it's got like $12 on it.
And GoFundMe is like, you need to get your money.
You need to get, you need to set up withdrawals
and get this money for you.
- Yeah, I did a GoFundMe a couple years ago
that was like, it was like,
help pay for Peter Griffin's weight loss surgery.
And it got, I think it got like $30.
- Really? - Yeah.
- Yeah. - Did you cash it out?
- No, I think I was just like, who,
I posted it somewhere as a joke
And then I think it was $30 of people giving to it.
And it wasn't even weight loss surgery.
Actually, it was like, he had already had weight loss and this was to pay for the
like skin to be tightened.
And I wrote this whole thing about how this was the scenario and people
decided to give money to it.
Like when you were a creative.
Yeah, exactly.
Now I feel like now you're more of an executive head rather than a creative.
Definitely trying to slide into more of a CEO role.
I do see you more like a corporate person rather than a,
"I want to make a video about sucking penis on Twitter."
Yeah, that's childish. I would like to basically have 100 or 200 or 300 people who work under me
who really respect me. But in some kind of... I don't even know what the business would be,
maybe like a private army or so, something like that. Like an actual business.
Can I make a question about your CEO experiences or aspirations?
Yes. See, this is a good test of my CEO-ship.
I'll say this. I'll say, "Shoot!"
Do you still have those plastic eyes sitting on your desk?
Yeah. Yeah, they're right here. Yeah, bad guys.
Guys, the video with these is coming very soon.
(laughing)
Very, very soon, another two or three years
and this will be famous.
- What about the other thing that's much more expensive
than these guys?
- The other thing is still being created,
but that will be debuted.
And you know what?
Maybe I'll use the googly eyes with the other new thing.
- Do you have it already?
- No, it's being fabricated.
- Man.
- Really fucking sad.
I really hate talking about that thing because I do want people to see what it is.
They will see by this time next month.
They will never see.
My friend Julio, what is your job position?
What is your job title?
Mine?
Yeah, what would you call yourself?
Maybe editor/producer?
Okay, yeah, so that's a hat you wear I would say.
That's not your position.
Oh, what does that mean?
How much do you spend doing that on a weekly basis in terms of most of his job is video game friend?
That's 60% of it.
Surely, so you're saying keep saying I'm so happy that I have a guy I pay.
To play video games with so it takes you 16 hours a week to edit the podcast.
I said 60% of my role, my position.
Well, you're making a mistake, Rex, of him working a 40-hour work week.
He does not.
Right.
Listen, I've been live for days now.
I think about 60 hours.
I don't know how much five days is.
That is a lot.
And how much Uber Eats have you ordered in that time period?
once. Yeah, once. What are you doing for food otherwise? Well, he's still at his house. I'm
at my house. It's not that hard to just pop into the kitchen. He doesn't live in a mansion like
you. Yeah, I make breakfast. Dinner is... He makes Mike breakfast. He just said he wakes up,
he makes Mike breakfast. That's his roommate. Dinner is just whatever I can scrounge,
- I'm gonna go ahead and get started.
- Okay.
- So, I'm gonna start with the sandwich.
- I'm reeling up the case.
- Are you learning how to cook?
- A little bit, yeah.
I made some burgers the other day.
- Ooh.
- Yep, and they looked weird.
- That's good.
- So we're still learning.
- They're not, they weren't circular.
- They weren't completely circular, yeah.
- Well, that doesn't seem,
I guess that's even more weird, you're right.
If they're perfect circles.
- So no, I'm completely, you can come at me.
I will dodge your bullets.
I will dodge your knives.
I got nothing to hide.
- I will say, how is this current position
gonna go on a resume when you move on to your next thing?
Because you're not gonna be 50 years old
doing this podcast.
- We'll see.
(laughing)
That remains to be seen.
- He's got you and Pat just chained up somewhere.
I am currently living in a really high status in Mexico
and I really don't want to think about the future.
I think--
- That's smart.
- I think life is great. - That is great.
- Life is great.
You have one of the greatest positions on earth.
Many, many people messaged us before you were picked
to be this position and said,
"Hey, I'm 15 years old and I really am so bored
"and I need credit for my world history class,
my AP World History, can I be the intern?
And we said, no.
- No, we're outsourcing.
- We're going to outsource this job to another country
because it is so grueling that no American
could possibly stand to do this job.
And here we are, man.
- And that's true.
- Here we are.
A year and some change in, and this guy's crushing it.
All right, I finished my ZVEC.
I'm gonna go sleep.
- All right.
This was good.
Bye bye French.
Bye goodbye beer forever.