All right, now Rex do us a little clap. Perfect. I couldn't hear that.
That's okay. That's good.
Stop, that's not how it works.
It's okay, keep clapping as much as you want.
All right, okay. Enough. Okay, to start off the episode, I want to show you guys something.
I need to hear this.
Over the weekend, Pat made this, which is going to be our new theme song.
It's a potential theme song by the way
because I've heard Pat's music and I
Suffice it to say I'm not a fan
So okay, I want to hear this before I give the okay kiss stamp of approval right okay?
Okay, I like it so far
*sips*
*burps*
You're listening to beers we drank, America's number one beer broadcast.
Okay.
*music*
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
*burps*
This is a journey into...
*garbled*
Bud Light.
beers we drank motherfucker with Juvio, Caleb and Rex.
(upbeat music)
- Beer.
- Oh, wow. - Wow, okay, all right.
- That's actually really dope.
- It was a lot better than I thought it was gonna be.
You know, I would say that it's tied.
It's tied.
- It's tied?
- It's tied for the number one spot.
- Okay. - 'Cause I was thinking
that it would just be,
(imitates guitar)
but I guess we can maybe swap them back and forth.
The thing you said we should have done was "Bulls on Parade" and I did it once and I thought that was stupid.
So I stopped doing it.
Why? It's cool.
Yeah, it is cool.
It is cool.
Have you ever listened to the Avalanches?
No.
Do you ever listen?
It's a music thing. That's what it reminded me of.
Yeah.
I don't listen to music. Anyways.
Alright.
I also wanted to start off by showing you guys that I know that Rex is usually the one that
buys this crazy weird beer.
That is true.
But today I went to the grocery store, I went to the Walmart Express, that's what it's called,
and I bought a little thing called Duff Beer.
A censored beer.
Whoa!
From the Simpsons.
What the fuck?
Is that real?
It's a real beer that you can buy in Mexico.
Oh my god!
Why is it trying to blur it out, dude?
Because it's copyrighted.
Holy shit!
No copyright infringement intended.
It's also like a really big can.
Yeah.
That is amazing, dude.
That is so sick.
Well, pop it open.
It says, "Lager Beer Hell."
I don't know what that means.
I also got a weird beer.
I got a beer so weird that it's a soda
with no beer in it at all.
And I would like to explain myself, okay?
- Sure.
- The last three nights, I've had buddies
who have had daddies who are in town, right?
Buddies with daddies have been in town, okay?
And so I've had to go out to bars,
I've had to meet my buddies' daddies.
I've had to meet my buds' dads.
And I have been just having too much to drink
and it's been making me have diarrhea.
So classic bus that's have that but uh...
did that dad buds
that but
dad buds
that but so maybe i don't know
you'd have to ask those that if he has
if he likes weed
uh... i think he's a republican
but i have decided that
and we'll be a very record yesterday the day before
so and i would find a beer then but
on this monday man beginning of the work week
I'm going to have to go with a Spreeker Low Cal Cream Soda Fire Brewed Craft Soda.
It's made with honey.
And I know that that's disappointing to a lot of people out there.
And I really would just like to...
This will never happen again.
I promise you that.
Even if I become an insatiable alcoholic, a dangerous alcoholic, the kind who rolls over
their kid's head in the parking lot because they are so drunk, right?
and I have to quit alcohol forever, court mandated,
I will drink two beers a week,
every single week, until the day I die.
- God bless you.
- Yeah, so, cheers.
- Cheers.
- Well, I guess I'll introduce mine,
as it is also a Monday,
in the work week,
and I, the only one on this podcast
that has even something remotely close to a job.
We'll have to continue to work after this.
- Whoa, calm down, buddy.
- First of all, you have a boss, but you don't have a job.
- True.
- The only real people with jobs in this world
are business owners.
So in that regards, it's really just me.
I'm ahead of the rest.
I have to think about everything.
- All right, I'll accept that.
I stream on Twitch every day.
So, back to what I was saying.
Yeah.
I will be drinking a unique beer called a Strawberry Lemonade Rehab Monster.
That looks good, actually.
I've never heard of a rehab monster. That sounds a little crazy.
- This is an incredible soda.
If anybody lives near a soda store,
this is a smart pickup.
Let's see, this has to have Splenda in it
or something, right?
It's got honey, and I can taste the honey, guys.
It has glucose syrup and saccharin.
- What do you guys feel about--
- That's what's in mine, yeah.
- But honey, I'm not a big fan of honey.
I eat at least one tablespoon of honey every single day.
Do you want me to read the paragraph of ingredients in the monster?
No, we get it.
It's beer.
Yeah, which we have, so it's gotta be good.
Uh oh, my mic, my Audacity just stopped recording.
It's gonna be one of these guys.
You're recording on OBS, it's fine.
Alright, so I'm just gonna start it again.
And I'm sure you got all your audio inputs in OBS working correctly.
There's basically no doubt.
Yep.
- Yup.
- But I just started recording.
- I tested my audio for two seconds.
- I just started recording here,
so you can figure it out if you need to.
I'm not gonna worry about it,
because I'm too busy relaxing with my friends.
Guys, can we--
- Yeah, exactly.
It's the first time I'm ever recording a podcast.
- Shut the hell up.
Shut up.
Guys, can we admit that this has been an awful week?
Just a long one, dude.
And we earned these beers.
- We did.
I had mine on credit a little bit,
'cause I had 'em the last three days and none today.
But boy am I sitting here thinking about those beers
and just smiling.
- Yeah. - Yep.
I'm enjoying my death.
- I mean the news, the news is out of control.
Everyone is getting fucking cancer.
- Oh that damn news.
- Everyone's getting fucking cancer.
Guys, let's pull up the news right now,
just to double check that it's still as crazy
as I remember it being.
CNN.com front page news.
Much of the US could see a huge shift in temperature.
- Oh my God. - Really?
- Yeah. - Yeah, well,
it's coming from winter to spring, I would assume so.
Come on, you're reading fake news.
- Man tries to open plane door,
stab flight attendant on LA Boston flight.
The world's gone mad.
- You can stab people on flights now?
- Apparently, I don't even know how he was able
to get a stabable implement onto a plane.
- I know exactly the news story
that we should talk about.
It's a little something, it's called the opinion column.
And here's the opinion.
CNN.com opinion column.
Chris Rock showed why you never slap a comedian.
(laughing)
That'll show you guys who are thinking
of slapping a comedian that hey, guess what buddy,
18 months later, they're gonna put out a five minute clip
where they call you gay.
So you need to chill.
- Is that what he did?
I didn't actually watch the bit.
What was the bit that he did?
- He just goes like,
Will Smith, every single person in the world
was fucking his wife.
His wife's getting fucked by fucking every human.
She moved on to animals.
She fucked every animal.
She moved on to fucking plants and bugs.
And everybody was shitting on him for this.
Everybody's saying, "You're a bitch,
"you're a bitch, you're a bitch."
And then he slaps me.
That's what he says.
He says he slaps me, the only guy who can't beat him up, he's a bitch.
Wow.
Yeah, it's pretty powerful stuff.
I kind of got a free saw on when he said it.
Here's something funny.
She's fucking bugs.
I didn't realize you met her on tour.
How about that?
Oh, with Adam?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh yeah.
(laughing)
I really took me a second to think about what that meant.
- Yup.
- I was like, I thought for a second,
like, does he think I have bugs around?
I keep a bug in my, does he think I'm a bug or something?
- No, you're not a bug.
- I honestly thought you were calling him a bug.
- Yeah, me too.
- Which I thought was really funny.
- Yeah, but then you--
- Well, there's only one epic guy to call a bug.
One guy that's so funny to call a bug.
Regardless, you've already created drama in the show now.
So you have to go ahead and submit an apology.
- I just got a text on my Apple Watch.
He dropped me from the tour.
I'm gone.
- That's fine, you're already on the show.
- I'm gone.
- And you didn't even talk about beers we drank.
I mean, I didn't watch it,
but I just assume you didn't talk about beers we drank.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I didn't.
I don't, I'm really bad at plugging.
- Good friend, you are.
- Anytime I go on anything, I'm so bad at plugging.
I'm too good at being in the moment,
being an amazing guest on every single show that I do,
to the point where when people say,
and when they say, "What do you have to plug?"
I go, "Ah!"
- Ah, fuck it.
- Don't even worry about it, I don't give a fuck.
Just don't give a-- - It doesn't matter.
- Just Google my name.
See what I'm up to.
- Yeah, there's, yeah, Google my name
and you'll find a drummer and then a drummer
and then a couple of high school basketball players,
but underneath all those guys,
you'll find me and the stuff that I'm doing.
So go check that out.
- When Beers We Drink becomes the number one beer podcast,
you'll be above all those guys.
- I will say-- - One day.
- There is two high school basketball players
that I am really, really hoping never make it to the NBA.
I'm like praying on their downfall.
I hope that they, and they're pretty good.
They're pretty good, they have my exact name.
And if they even become like benchwarmers,
like fucking into the bench, I'm fucked, dude.
I literally should be like setting up like saw traps
to like tear their ACLs and stuff
because these kids are dangerous to me.
They are pretty talented.
- Well, right now as it stands,
if you Google Caleb Pitts,
first one that comes up is @braingetter on Twitter.
Then a lot of pictures,
good looking pictures of yourself and two other guys.
- Oh my God, good looking, whoa.
- Caleb Pitts White on Instagram, which is not you.
And then the third hit is Caleb Pitt's epic SMP wiki fandom.
(laughing)
Then the videos, and then your IMDb.
And then your pod chaser has a really funny
profile picture of you.
- Probably not me, if it's funny.
- Completely awesome.
- I look really, really good looking usually.
(laughing)
- Yeah, you do, yeah.
But yeah, I think as of today, you shouldn't really worry.
But maybe if they do become--
- But that's what I'm saying, dude.
if these kids step it up a little bit.
If these kids had, you know what, here's what's nice.
These kids don't have enough heart to make it to the league.
You know, luckily they just don't have it in them.
So, I think--
- Luckily they're not football players because,
you know, then you'd have a real problem.
'Cause there's so many more players
that make the team football and basketball.
- But maybe they have less of a,
most of them probably have less of an SEO impact
because there are so many of them.
There's definitely football players that like,
nobody gives a fuck about.
- Yeah, for sure.
- Definitely NFL players, like kickers.
Who gives a shit about, nobody's like,
getting a kicker jersey,
they probably don't even print their jerseys.
- Yeah, name one kicker.
Oh, I got one.
That guy, his name is Young Ho.
- Charlie Brown, that's all I got.
- Yep.
- That's literally the only one.
- And he missed.
- And he's not, he's gotta be
one of the worst kickers who ever lived.
But I gotta say who's even worse at their job is Lucy.
- Yeah.
- Lucy is, is that her name?
Or is Lucy the other girl?
- No, women are the same to me.
- Lucy Peanuts.
Let me see, yep, I was right.
Lucy Van Pelt.
- Yeah, and that's another peanut head ass Peckerwood.
- Almost the entire show is Peckerwood crackers.
- Yeah.
I hate to say that.
It's really unfortunate.
It is true. Charles Schultz, not the uh...
wouldn't fly today, basically.
I'll say that much.
Yeah, they could make peanuts today.
You couldn't.
What's the last cartoon you watched?
The last tune I watched?
What do you mean by that?
Like all the way through?
Like I watched every episode?
Yeah, what could you possibly mean by that?
Possibly me by that attribute.
That really is professional podcasting, always having something to talk about, always having a nice kind of hypothetical question or like a personal question to spur some conversation.
Like what's the last cartoon you watched?
Yeah, what's the last cartoon you watched?
I watched Spongebob the other day on, what's that, Tubi? No, the other one. The free one.
You watched Bob Esponja?
Yeah.
How was it?
Bob Esponja.
It was good. It was in Spanish. It was the episode where they were making fun of
Sandy Cheeks for being Texan.
And the response was like, "Everyone from Texas is retarded."
Oh, yeah.
And it was like, "That's true!"
Did they localize that? They're like, "Everyone from Guadalajara is a fucking moron."
[laughter]
No, they still make fun of Texas, which is funny.
And I never really understood it.
And people in Mexico know what Texas is, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, some of us.
And no they all know
Tell me we all know you guys know about Texas. You don't know anything about the south
I'm from the south of Mexico
What is even in the south of Mexico named one place in the south of Mexico better countries like Peru and Brazil?
Are there?
Yeah
No, yeah, what I was okay. This is completely stupid and irrelevant
You guys didn't bring the beers. This is technically turning to beer we drank
The the show is completely broken. There's drama abound
Rex still has an apology for calling you a bug
Well, you're a really bad weekend and I want to ask me about it. Okay
Well, I just in a second, but I would like to say here's what I'm discovering
I'm sober Rex is sober and you are drunk and you are rage you are
Like I hope to God that you don't have children in your house that you've never told me about because
You feel like you're giving like a kind of a belt dad kind of energy off in this call right now
Looks like you may snap a belt on a child's neck. I have a feeling after drinking that beer. He's gonna be
Grabbing them by the throat
Yeah, and say things like you little yeah, yeah, why I oughta that kind of thing no
You're getting completely homer-fied by your duff beard. I'd just like for you to admit it out loud, please.
I'm not homer-fied at all.
You are. I can see you're turning yellow. You look jaundiced.
That's not even true. I've never said "doe" in my entire life.
You've just said it now.
Is that what you said?
No, I said I've never said "doe" in my entire life.
You said "doe" maybe a hundred times.
You also do, you go, you have your version of "doe" which is "what?"
[laughter]
all the time. So you are home. Oh my God. He's Homer. Wait,
how is it taking me years to realize that he's Homer? It had
it. How am I even Homer? He's 100% of Homer and I didn't
realize till he held up a Duff beer in front of my face and
said, look at this beer I bought. Look at that. Now, I'm
like, oh yeah, he was over the entire time. Yeah. It's
honestly not that yummy. I wish I had a juice. I wish I had an
and
as some sort of artificial sweetener.
- So you're the, I guess you're monster specialist, right?
Which is the best one, do you think?
- This one.
I just bought a new-- - I agree.
The rehab ones are the better ones.
- The rehab strawberry lemonade, it's sweet.
It has no carbonation, so it just goes down.
'Cause the thing about a monster,
your body fights you as you try and drink a monster.
The carbonation makes you fight back
from like drinking-- - That's 100% true.
- This one's not carbonated.
It's gone before you even know it.
- Yeah, it's like not a canned monster.
- Where does the Mangoloco one land in the tier list,
do you think?
- Everyone loves the Mangoloco, I'm not a fan.
It's good, but it's not a top tier.
- Which one is that?
- It's just like juice.
It's like with the juice line, actually.
- It's got juice in it?
- Yes, mango juice, and it's pretty yummy.
- Yeah, it's good.
- It's the one I've had that I liked
enough to buy a couple of those.
I would put Monster Energy, and this is going to hurt some people's feelings, at the very,
very, very bottom of my energy drink rankings.
Okay, but so what's above it?
I think that there is nothing worse than a Monster Energy.
I would drink a Bang before I drink a Monster Energy.
I would drink a Ghost before I drink a Monster Energy.
Okay.
I would drink a C4.
I would drink a Red Bull.
I would drink a True North.
I would drink a caffeinated Spindrift.
I would drink an uptime, right?
- I don't even think I've heard of uptime.
- You gotta try uptime.
What's uptime, by the way?
Nothing much.
What's uptime with you?
- Nope.
- The, I would drink a--
- 7 p.m.
- Shut up. - Nope.
- I would drink a--
- Shut up time.
- Wait, what is another one that I like?
I already said True North, right?
- Well, down time.
- Yeah, you guys continue while I think about this.
(laughing)
- There's no caffeine in it, it makes you sleepy.
I would drink a Starbucks refresher,
one of those fucking ones, before I drink a Monster.
- Get out of town.
- Excuse me.
I would drink a Yerba Mate,
well before I would drink a fucking Monster.
Monster is terrible.
- You're being facetious now.
- I, no, fuck no.
I fucking hate, Monster's terrible, man.
- No.
- It has the wrong amount of caffeine.
I either want less or I want more.
- Okay, I can see that.
- It's way too sweetly tasting.
And it doesn't have the right vitamins for your skin.
- I see, so you're an Alani Nu fan.
- What's that?
Oh, I drink pussy before I drink Monster.
- Okay, yeah.
- And I fucking hate pussy.
- Me too.
- I would drink pussy well before I drink Monster.
I would drink any, I'm usually always a zero-cal energy drink guy.
I would drink a full-cal energy drink before I drink any monster.
- Interesting. - That's crazy.
So you're a certified monster hater.
I hate it. It's terrible. I can't believe it's caught on like it has.
Remember when I got everyone into Pussy?
Yeah. That is an amazing drink.
- That was amazing. - Yeah.
And then you brought it to Brandon Wardell's house,
were like wow pussy yeah that's crazy that's so funny and then Jack ordered a
plate a pallet of it and then yeah a picture a couple months ago of him just
like like the fucking big case of 24 case yeah I'm taking out of it yeah yeah
man you know it's not that good it's your like live sugar yeah yeah I was
- I was going through those, I was drinking like four a day.
- They're good.
- They are good.
- I recently cut way back on caffeine though.
I've been one or maybe even a half a cup of coffee
at about 11 o'clock.
- This is my second one of these.
- Since when?
- Today.
- How long you been up?
- Got up at like eight-ish, got out of bed at nine.
- Oh, nice.
- Yeah.
- That's a somewhat normal sleep schedule.
- Yeah, of course.
- You didn't have a nap, right?
I did have a nap.
Yeah.
I've also been taking my caffeine pills,
although I recently discovered the logic pills,
violent diarrhea every time.
Some ingredient in them just sends me straight
to the bathroom.
Does it make you want to make awesome music?
No.
Well, that's what-- it's the wrong kind of logic.
You think that you're doing this.
Instead, you're using your asshole like a doll.
Just making amazing, yeah,
groggy man drum loops.
Just beatboxing with your butt directly into the toilet.
- Not to be grotesque, but it's so wet and watery,
I can feel shit dripping down
kind of to the lowest point of my ass cheek.
You know what I mean?
- Did you start that sentence with not to be gross?
(laughing)
- Not to be grotesque, he said.
- Not to be grotesque, but it's just disgusting,
watery shit coming out of my hole.
- Not to be grotesque, but.
Wow.
That is nasty.
But, you know, there's no women will listen to this, right?
- Yeah, exactly.
- No, this is a guy doing a podcast.
And if they do, they are making a serious mistake.
This is programming them, you know?
- Right.
- But also, I bet, dude,
- Oh, I just realized something so annoying, bro.
- What?
- Women, women are gonna listen to this,
and they're gonna fall in love with us.
- Oh, for sure.
- They're gonna fall in love with us
'cause it's three insane alpha males
of all different races, creeds, religions, right?
- Yep, yep.
- Catholic, Jewish, Christian science.
Right?
All different IQ scores, you know?
We're not gonna get into that part, right?
Yeah.
But, we have one thing in common and that's we like drinking beer.
Yup.
We like doing, um...
Outdoorsman activities.
We all shop, but we basically buy everything from REI.
I think you should crash again.
I think I should what?
My shit crash again?
My computer's gonna plug for a sec.
It's very possible.
- Well, Rex, I think that girls are gonna feel the,
they're gonna feel represented with your experience.
- See this is why--
- Women are constantly having diarrhea.
- Here's another perfect example, by the way,
of why they're gonna like this,
'cause I'm not one of these fuckin' new age pussies
who knows how to use a microphone on a computer, right?
(laughing)
Women are actually, you wanna talk about,
you wanna talk about cream soda,
go to any one of our female listeners,
look in their shorts, 'cause it's gonna be bubbling
- And they should go to the hospital.
'Cause that is, you're not supposed to bubble.
- Yeah, and beer, what's that made with?
Yeast. - Bubbles.
- And where does yeast come from?
Fucking women's-- - That's where it comes from.
That's where it comes from.
That's how you get yeast.
Those little pellets, the active dry yeast
you get in the store to make pizza dough.
That's how you get 'em in. - Active dry yeast.
That's what women leave behind on the lifting bench.
- That's right, yeah.
That's the thing about sharing a gym
with women to
and also a quarter of the times
it's mostly beers on just how getting distracted
right up to
i'm kinda uh...
s psyche myself out making myself think i'm drunk rakes of couples like a
personal beer
now uh... and also they got the snail trails is leaving everywhere because
since it's a take my shirt off
you know yeah
as i do that uh... is the by the way this is my gym outfit
this is my gym shirt
I do. How many gym harassment videos have you been on since you started going to that gym
with women? I try to harass about every day but leg days because I'm so exhausted on leg
days. It's hard to fucking chase and hit. And stare and scream. Yeah. But you know, every
Every once in a while I'll even look at a guy.
Check a guy out? That's mighty brave of you to admit.
I kind of like harassing and making people feel unsafe more than I even care about my own sexuality.
It's really not sexual at all. I only want to make every single person around me feel so on edge and so afraid for their lives
that it doesn't matter who they are.
- Yeah, no, I agree.
I was actually thinking today,
have you ever heard of Roko's Basilisk?
It's about like AI shit.
- No.
- Okay, so it's like,
if you ever do anything to stop AI in the future,
AI is gonna exist and it's gonna put you in hell prison
for stopping it from coming about.
- How would it, so if we do anything now,
it's gonna remember is what you're saying?
- It's gonna remember.
It's gonna look back in history
it's gonna be like you didn't contribute to me existing,
therefore you get put into infinite hell prison forever.
- Interesting.
- And I like to think that every woman on earth
will be put into the hell prison because they--
- Because they didn't help.
- Yeah, right, they didn't help.
Well, not that they didn't help,
but you know, they're like,
"Ugh, stop using my face in pornography."
(laughing)
They don't understand that these are stepping stones.
They're living pads.
Right?
See us, we're good worker bees.
We're drone ants.
Right?
Yeah.
We're sitting every day.
I'm typing just as much information into ChatGPT
as I possibly can.
Right?
I'm teaching them about everything I know about.
I'm writing entire essays about Opie and Anthony
and sending it to ChatGPT just to fill that blank space
that it might have.
Right?
Yeah.
I'm writing about my friends.
I'm writing about movies that I like.
And these girls--
- I'm entering my genetic sequence.
- These girls are saying, "Oh, but what if somebody,
"what if somebody asked ChadGPT what my address is?"
Well, bitch, put it in!
- Let 'em know.
- Yeah.
- Think about hell prison.
Is that better?
- I'm doing it for your own good, right?
I'm doing an entire 3D scan of your full body
on the bus for your own good.
Because when you turn fucking 400
and you finally decide to upload your brain,
you're gonna be in hell, basically.
You're gonna be in complete hell.
- The seventh circle for women.
- Your consciousness is gonna be tortured for all eternity
because of Roku, is what I learned from Rex recently.
- The Roku Corporation.
- Yeah, they're making Roku City a real thing.
They're trapping women in there.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, and here comes AI, and AI's doing rampage, right?
Crashing the windows, punching stuff.
- I love that game.
- Dude, I used to, that was probably the first thing
that ever made me horny, was when you punch open the window
and the lady's taking a shower, and she goes, "Ah!"
And you say, "Come here, bitch!"
And you pick her up and you eat her.
- That's dope.
- Yeah.
- Normal.
- Do you ever play Rampage, Rex?
- No, never.
I don't even know what that is.
- Any arcade games?
- No. - Wow.
You truly are a girl of the podcast.
- You didn't play any arcade games,
but you're the one that has a DDR booth in his house?
- Yeah.
- But you never went to fucking Jungle Rapids?
- No.
- That's in my hometown, you never went there?
- I'm sorry, man, I never went to Jungle Rapids.
Where'd you grow up again?
- Wilmington, North Carolina.
And what's your address?
My address now or back then?
Back then.
1422 Whisper Park Drive.
All right.
Note that down, chat GPT.
Go back in time, put him in the hell prison.
No, I really didn't play much arcade games
because my mom is insane.
All right, let's get into it.
Yeah, Jewish.
All right, we got into it and it's over.
We figured it out, got to the bottom of it pretty fast.
No, I'm kidding.
- No, one word answer.
- Jewish moms usually are amazingly beautiful to me.
- We don't have to talk about how beautiful my mom is
for the third consecutive episode.
- How beautiful she is.
I wish I could meet her.
- My mom looks like me if I was a girl.
So you can think about that.
- You mean the thing that we talk about all the time?
- Yep, yep.
thing we talk about every single day.
Man, Rex, I just wish you not as a gay thing.
I wish you were a girl and you were one that you were like,
super into just like letting all your friends use your body.
If I was a girl, I would be dealing with that for sure.
No, you wouldn't. Just cause I'm so nice.
That's the funniest, like, like middle school boy hypothetical is like, dude,
if I was a girl, like I would just like guys fuck me all the time.
I would, I wouldn't even care.
I'll just offer it up.
- Yeah.
- No, you would be a complete hoe.
- You would not be a hoe.
Yeah, you would not be a hoe.
- You think I'd be a prude?
- You'd be-- - You'd be a spick and spank
old prude? - You'd be a femcel, I think.
- Okay. - Femcel.
- I can buy that.
- I thought that was just a girl.
- It's a female incel, basically.
- Oh, okay.
I'd be a hoe, dude.
I'd be sitting, I'd be like in a frat house.
Dick in my pussy, dick in my ass, dick in my mouth, watching the office, people fucking
my armpits, people fingering my ears and shit, fingering my eyeballs just like this, just
like, acting like I can't get anything out of that.
Yeah.
Just, just a mass of hands reaching towards you.
Yeah, I'd basically be like plugged into the Matrix.
Like I would have, all of my senses would be muted by foreskin.
and there would be nothing left for me to experience.
And I would just sit there until probably I died.
I would die with a big smile on my face.
And then my dad--
- You'd be like, who's the guy in Star Wars
that's like ensconced in ice?
- Yeah, exactly.
I would die and then the coroners off it,
at the coroners, I'd be on that metal table, right?
In a zipped up bag.
They'd unzip the bag to show my dad
and it would literally just be a mountain of cum,
can't see me at all and my dad would say,
"Yep, that's my daughter."
(laughing)
Yep, that's her.
- Yep.
- Yep, zipper back up.
And then they literally just toss me into a river
and just, "Bye bye."
- They don't even need a coffin.
It's like perfectly shaped in like a rectangle of cum.
- Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, they would probably like, let it dry.
They'd put me in a dehydrator
and then they'd have somebody come chisel out
like a beautiful, amazing, like good woman.
Like not like I was yeah, yeah, decent woman with clothes on.
Yeah, they
chisel out a long dress.
Exactly.
Go down to your ankle.
They would do that.
I would have when I get my life when I got my license so that I
could go like fuck random guys across the city.
I would get my donor card, right?
And then the next time that I would get like I would say that
I was an organ donor and then I would die and my organs would
all get shipped to the hospital and then all of a sudden some
some fucking poor kid has a heart in him
that's waterlogged with cum.
There's literally like jizz in the heart
pumping through this fucking kid with cancer's body
and he just dies, he just has to die
because they get it and it's just like,
it's a brick that you can like break a wall with it.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause it's so fucking filled to the brim, saturated.
- Yep.
- I think that's just for us though.
- Yeah, just kidneys and 100% cum.
- Exactly.
I'd be a sponge. I'd be a complete fucking jizz sponge.
And I would...
I would literally eat... If I was a girl, I'd be such a slut, I would eat...
I would eat jizz off the street. Like, on the floor.
I would eat jizz.
Are you gonna finish that?
Yeah, and I would just lick it up.
I would scrape it. I would just scrape it...
into my mouth.
Yeah.
I would staple my lips to the side of the curb and just scrape everything just into my mouth.
And just see if there's jizz in it.
Every sock I see on the ground.
- You're just putting dollars in your mouth
and kind of just letting them sit in there.
- I would literally lick doorknobs
because it would make me so horny thinking about the fact
that guys had jacked off and then forgot to wash their hands
and then touch the doorknobs.
- Which who does?
- Nobody washes.
No, it's always, you're hanging out or you jack off,
you completely forget and then your dad's like,
"Hey, you wanna meet 25 of my friends
"and shake all their hands right now?"
(laughing)
Yes sir, Dave, Mike, nice to meet all of you.
And then at the 25th guy, you finish it and you go,
oh, guys I have to go to the bathroom.
And then you go in there, and you think at first
you're gonna wash your hands, but it made you so horny
that all those guys touched your disgusting hand,
you have to jerk off again.
- Yeah, with all 25 of their male sweat on your hand,
that's like a 25 guy jack off.
And then you walk back out and say,
"Ah, guys, I hear you met my twin brother.
"Well, let me meet you guys."
David, Mike, do it all back down again.
- Yeah.
That's beautiful, man.
That's a beautiful story.
And I can't believe that happened to you
every single day when you were growing up.
- No, I'm just kidding.
I'm a pretty normal guy.
I just think it's funny to be just pretty nasty,
you know, just a little bit nasty sometimes, but not too.
I mean, if anybody doesn't like
that kind of humor like that's not that big of a deal.
You just don't have to listen.
Maybe somebody will like it though.
- Yeah, somebody might, who knows?
- Yeah.
- I don't know what kind of grotesque person
would think that's funny.
- I don't know.
- You know what I was thinking about?
It's just like, it's SpongeBob, right?
That's a guy with a lot of holes.
- Yeah.
- Can you make a good, can you make a good hoe?
Yeah, you know like--
- Can you make a good hoe?
Oh yeah.
Yeah, you know like talk about frat house situation whole for everybody. Oh, yeah, it's easy
If he was in my life, he's soft if he was in my life
He would be I would accidentally rip him in two while I was fucking him
And then there just be even more holes. It's true. It's a good point
He is only is it a sponge is more holes than it is fucking sponge material. No, you know
And that's how I feel about women.
- I kinda, okay, that's a little too far.
How I kinda, what I kinda wanna get is,
you know how loofah is a,
both a, what you call like one of those scrubbers,
but a loo, it's based on an actual plant called a loofah.
And you like cut it, and it's a,
it's some plant that you wash your body with,
and I really think that it could get,
it could finally clean my ass.
I've been waiting on something that is strong enough
for my ass for a very long time.
- Have you considered just becoming a bidet guy?
Like, you know, just-- - Well, when I was younger,
When I was a younger man, I used to shave my ass.
I would shave my ass right down to the hole.
And then I would walk around and it felt like
I was a dolphin with a human ass.
'Cause it felt so bad.
It was just like perfect, smooth skin,
rubbing against each other.
But then I got such an awful razor burn there one time
that any time I farted, it hurt.
It was like the most excruciating pain
I've ever been in in my entire life.
I would fart and go, "Ah!"
So I had to stop shaving my asshole.
Yeah man, for sure.
You were supposed to put maybe some baby oil in there or...
I didn't know about any...
I didn't learn, it was self-taught.
I was a self-taught asshole shaver.
Why were you doing that?
Because I thought having ass hair, I thought girls would like it.
But I was 15 or 16...
How many girls were seeing your asshole?
Nobody.
and see my asshole for probably three more years but you know just in case
yeah I was just a little bit I was like any given night I just got done laying
the most amazing dick of her entire life right yeah I beat it up no I'm fucking
I'm fucking milk so fucking my friends mommy's I beat it up right and then she
I'm like, do you want a glass of water?
My turn.
No, she doesn't say my turn.
Oh, I need to turn.
[LAUGHTER]
I said, do you want a glass of water?
I turn around, and I'm still trying to be sexy because it's my first time.
So I kind of crawl like a cheetah to the end of the bed.
And then she sees my asshole perfectly, right?
Yeah.
That's beautiful, man.
So does that answer your question?
Yeah, you're on all fours crawling to the end of the bed.
Yeah.
the
You are a fool.
Why not?
I don't, that feels, it feels just like, dude I'll say it, it feels kinda sus.
You're fuckin, you're stupid. You are dumb.
Thank you for pulling the punch. We really need some sponsorships on this show.
Thank you for not saying the R word.
Yeah, we only get, it's like PG-13, we get one.
Yeah, you said one earlier. I'll be normal.
I would never say that word anyway.
Anyway, anyways, yeah, you're fucking stupid. Why don't you get a bidet? It just it cleans your ass for free
Okay, it's not free
First of all number two
My hand cleans my ass right and every time I get into the bathtub of the shower
My hand is the bidet and I basically do a karate chop my asshole over and over to do that
Do so put your hand and they go
Yeah, exactly I'm doing a perfect karate chop right and maybe even a credit card swipe a couple of times
Yeah, right. Yeah, not that I like that. It doesn't feel good to me, but I do it on your hands
Yeah, I soap it up and I lube it up with soap not lube. I soap it up
Just fucking you know you swipe it you're going in you're going in I used to put my finger in my
shower
Cuz I was like I was like so
Disgusted by the idea that like the the first inch of my asshole was not clean and there was like maybe some nasty poop in
there so I would so put my finger and pop it in just like to the end to the
fingernail you know and go like yeah right when I came out yeah yeah you
- That's great, man.
- You gotta be fucking it all day.
- My parents were divorced.
Nobody taught me how to shower, guys.
I had to learn myself.
I had to learn, I listened to podcasts
to learn everything, how to do everything in my life.
- That is the thing, is your dad never,
like I feel like, you know, growing up
I expected my dad to teach me how to shave
or do literally anything.
- No.
- And it just never happened.
- No, my dad didn't teach, look at,
I cut myself, I cut the shit out of my head today shaving.
I've been doing this for years, dude.
I put like a fucking hole in my head.
- I think no one's dad's teach him
how to like shave their head.
- I'm not gonna teach my, you know what my dad taught me?
How to avoid my mom.
That's exactly what my mom taught me.
- Which is a really good skill.
- That's the only thing my dad ever taught me.
- My dad taught me how to lie to my mom.
- Yeah dude, some good skills.
Stuff that actually comes in handy.
Shaving?
I can learn it.
I'll look up a fucking YouTube video, man.
first time after my parents my parents were some six how weirs
my parents who they were there yet something that i will you when you when
they divorced i was twenty
uh... i was i was a little bit
that's uh... first-time
and that picks me up
goes to the golf store
by some golf clubs
because
don't tell your mom
sick
students you know
say we went to fucking this
I was like, perfect.
I got it.
And then, you know, I didn't stop lying to my mom
until I was, I never stopped.
- Were the clubs for you?
- Yeah, all the time.
What?
- Were the clubs supposed to be for you?
- No, I'm six.
What the fuck am I doing on a golf course?
- And he wasn't good.
Like, you know, Tiger Woods kid played golf at six,
but Rex can't do that, too.
- I can't, I still can't play golf.
- I thought it was gonna be like one of those classics
like your parents trying to bribe you to love them more.
- Oh no!
- Took you to look at him buying stuff for himself.
- Yeah.
- And you were like,
"I'm being naughty by not saying anything about this."
We're getting nothing out of it.
- So, it's called protecting the bro code.
It's fucking bitch ass mom.
(laughing)
- What's the bro code?
- Yeah, wait, can we establish exactly
what is in the bro code right now?
- Number one.
I mean the premier bros of the world I would say.
- Yeah, always lie to women.
What they don't know, won't hurt them.
- Every chance, by the way, take,
that is a no single excuse every single time
you lie to a woman.
A woman says, if you have a female waitress, right?
"Hi, can I get something started for you?"
No. - No.
I'm not even hungry.
- No, I'm not even hungry.
I came in here on accident.
Actually, I'm blind.
I'm blind and I thought this was my car.
(laughing)
And try to drive away.
And she'll probably, I mean she'll probably fuck you.
Just pure confidence of that move.
She'll probably go, this guy is a true alpha dog.
And I need to be involved with him romantically.
- Yeah, I'm blind.
- I'm blind.
And my car has two horns right here.
(laughing)
- 'Cause then you'd honk.
- Yep.
- I thought I was driving my boat.
(honking)
- All right, number two.
Bros before hoes.
- Yeah.
- Never, you know, let your friend down.
- Bros before hoes, by the way, that's the,
if you ever wanted an answer to the trolley problem,
That's what it is right there.
Yeah.
'Cause that's what people leave that line out,
but it's either one, you can save one guy,
or you could kill four girls.
- Or one bro. - There you go.
- Right? - Or a hose.
- And before the fucking ghosts of Christmas pass,
or whoever the fuck gives me that opportunity,
before they even finish explaining the scenario, right?
Not only am I directing the train,
I'm up ahead, I ran in front of the train,
I'm cutting all their heads off.
You know? - Yeah.
Fucking sawing their heads off. I'm putting long ways on the tracks
Bring the train all the way to the slowest possible
So they just very just kind of maybe it takes like two hours for it to be fully crushed. Yeah
Yeah, good. That's what I say good rose before hose always lie to women
What else?
Get get pussy
Get pussy help help your friends get get pussy. There we go. That's like that's it
Cuz you're not and it's not right to
to lie
Or right in a way in a way that you can like manipulate somebody to having sex with you
But it's completely okay for you to how to try to get your friend to have sex right so you can so here's what you
Do you bring your friend?
And a girl you that you guys both approach the girl at once right and she says hey, what's your deal?
And you say he doesn't speak English. I'll do all the talking for the rest
he's a millionaire and
He needs $10,000 right now deposited into his banking account, but he'll send you a hundred thousand back
Yeah, he's a prince of a different country you don't know yeah, yeah for you and surgeon yeah
- Yeah, exactly.
- Yeah.
You're wearing scrubs, and I'm just saying,
yeah, he's just so tired from all the surgery he did.
Open heart, kids.
- He's wearing scrubs,
the perfect outfit to attract a woman.
He's wearing a suit with scrubs underneath
'cause he didn't have time to change, right?
- Yeah.
- He's wearing both a stethoscope
and a giant gold chain with a clock on the end.
(laughing)
He has an LSAT study book in one hand,
and in the other hand he has one super long finger.
(laughing)
- Yep, perfect man.
- And girls are--
- They're just all over him.
- They're trying to suck his dick the entire night.
- Dude, imagine if you had one finger
that was like double the length.
- Dude, girls would know what the fuck is up.
- You would get pussy all the time.
- That's the thing, girls would say,
"What's up with your big finger?"
You say you know this thing come here single big finger
They say get that pussy over here. My dick is four inches
How it sucked dude if your dick was smaller than your finger
Yeah, I'll look at it
Wait whose hand whose hand is bigger. Oh wait. We're the thousands of miles apart from each other
to
- My fingers are not that long.
- Me?
- You have long fingers.
- I don't think my fingers are that long actually.
- I have stubby, fatty fingers.
I always have them.
- All the better to
pop women.
(laughs)
Yeah, your asshole would be a lot cleaner than mine.
- Definitely.
(laughs)
I think that's why I didn't like it.
'Cause I was, you know,
everybody had a point in high school where they were like,
you know i don't think i'm gay but i gotta do my due diligence on this whole thing
right i can't just i can't just you know it's just right at all it's because then
if you don't write if you did you completely write it off
you're thirty five you have two kids
all the sudden
uh...
there are not amazon delivery
you catch the guy's eyes the wrong way the sun's in them in the wrong way and
you're ruining your life is fuckin he's he's got his braces around your penis
Like that's not good.
I want to avoid that as much as possible.
So that's why I--
- You're bent over the couch your wife picked out.
You fucking hate it.
He's fucking pulling out, getting shit and cum all over it.
- Your first time or two, he's spraying your poop everywhere.
Nothing is right, right?
- Yeah.
- You decided to, you were like, last night,
you were like, "Hmm, I haven't had tikka masala in a while."
Right?
Next day, you lose your ass virginity
and there's poop everywhere.
'Cause you were a rookie, right?
So I didn't want that.
I was like, "I'm going to finger my butt
with a sh-- with some shampoo on it as a lubricant.
Just to see--
Shampoo?
[LAUGHTER]
Or whatever.
Whatever you say.
Shampoo.
Or whatever was a slippery--
at the time in my life, any slippery thing.
Uncomfortable.
And I was like, maybe I--
maybe I will like it.
And I did it.
You know.
And you liked it.
Maybe six or seven times.
Not-- didn't go--
Six or 700 times.
Didn't go all the way in and never did anything else with it.
I didn't like jack off and figure my but I just put just a little bit of just guys just just a little tiny fingernail
In there and then I said no not for me and I retired and my butt has been it's decommissioned, right?
It's decommit. It's like it's like a small rain
It's like an old train sitting on a train track a couple miles out of the city. It's collecting dust
Yeah, but I will say
Unlike those old trains. It's perfectly preserved
Perfectly preserved.
Perfectly, perfectly preserved.
No dust in it?
No erosion.
When's the last time you shaved your entire ass down to the hole?
The what?
Oh man, it's been a long time.
It's been...
It's been at least
5 or 6 years.
I was in my teen years when I was doing that.
I was a nubile young teen.
Shaved my ass.
I know, I know. It's because we're not drunk enough.
You brought it up. We didn't even talk about it.
Yeah, I'm so fucked up dude. There must be something.
You know what it is? It's honey. It's an aphrodisiac.
It is honey.
It's homosexual.
Yeah.
Nothing wrong with that.
You kind of did have an entire, a complete sexual energy this entire episode with your, with your open shirt.
That's what it is. Holy fuck, it's my shirt.
I gotta close this.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- I gotta close this.
We started talking about the news, right?
And then I was like, "Oh, this is fucking whack."
- That's crazy.
We tried to talk about the news.
- We tried to talk about the news,
and then now it's just been basically
a deep dive into my sexual life.
- Yeah, here's some news.
They need to ban that app, TikTok.
How about that?
Women are doing disgusting things on there.
- You saw the one that Noah sent the other night?
That honestly, like, that disturbed me.
(laughing)
For people, for the people listening, Noah sent us a video
that was on TikTok of a woman.
She's in a sheer dress and she has, she's like backlit
and she's like doing a dance and you,
she has nothing on underneath the dress.
You can see because of the light,
you could see the actual outline of her labia, right?
And I was like, okay, I like joking all day
about eating diarrhea and shoving it
into a woman's butthole, whatever.
But actually, maybe a female bodies make me want to vomit.
so badly. So this should not be on TikTok.
- Yeah.
There was a, I saw this guy today who was like,
yeah, I'm a games journalist.
And he's like, I'm trying to get set up to do like
live TikTok gaming.
And he can't even do it.
But then he's like, and this is what shows up on my feed.
And it's just a woman pouring like milk on herself.
It's like.
- That's the thing, dude.
It's a combination of like,
they're using the same tactics that they use to like
get kids to like counting and math,
but for fucking like porn.
That's what those videos are on TikTok where it's like,
oh, you learn the ABCs while you watch somebody cut foam.
Right, but they're doing that with like,
yeah, a woman is like putting,
which fruit fits in my asshole right, you know?
- Yeah, well that's what you feel.
- That's the future of gooning is like game footage,
family guy and then pornography like one corner.
Yeah. Well, I mean, that's like what feeds look like when they have like no,
no like user input. Like the pod, the podcast feed,
like when whenever I like peek into it, when I log into it,
it's always like 80% it's just like something extremely pornographic.
Like I think the other day I saw just a woman just breastfeeding on tech talk.
Well, that's not pornographic. That's completely natural.
You can think that's pornographic. You fucking scumbag.
What the fuck dude, that's natural.
She pulled out her whole thing.
On TikTok.
How else is she gonna put it in a baby's mouth?
There's skits on there, I don't think.
And then, yeah, they're kids.
They don't understand what's wrong, they were just doing that themselves
like 2, 3, 12 years ago.
Exactly.
I just think it doesn't have to be documented.
It's a beautiful, natural thing.
You're putting cameramen out of jobs.
Good men, who used to work at National Geographic
National Geographic and now their job is to film a woman with an iPhone 14 breastfeed a baby.
And you want those people, you hate those people.
I do, yeah.
Because they're union workers. You hate them.
Yep. They unionize.
It's true.
Despicable. I hate you.
Honestly, being sober has made me realize that Juvio is a monster.
I'm not a monster. He is a monster. He's so he's like probably the worst person. I know I know it's not true
Wait, no one name one despicable like they've done in the past month. You were late to the meeting this morning. I
Was not even late you were monster behavior
He's 30 minutes. He's fucked up the recording last time. He's 30 minutes late. He fucked up. That's not true time
You plug in your PS5 controller.
There's something called, have you ever heard of a term, you may not have this in Mexico, conscientiousness.
You have low conscientiousness and high neuroticism.
Okay?
That's not even true.
I'm gonna send you some Jordan Peterson videos.
You are a complete Mufasa from the Lion King.
That's you.
Low conscientiousness, highly neurotic.
You're Mufasa.
Me?
I'm not Mufasa.
Me? I'm the parrot.
What's his name?
George.
Rolfo.
Or Rulo. What's his fucking name?
Jubio, get on that.
I'm looking for something else.
Oh, sorry.
Just because we're on a different show, you think your job has changed?
Look it up!
Yeah.
I was looking for this.
Don't show them!
You can't see the book,
but I'm holding the
It's over a little bit.
And a good kid, Matt City.
Can you imagine?
Look at his feet.
And he's got Crocs on, and he's completely bowlegged.
And his Crocs are 40 sizes too big.
That's just how big my feet are.
Whoa.
What size shoes do you wear?
Big ass feet.
11, 12.
Did you say women's 12?
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah, same size shoes as me.
Women's.
That's not true.
That's not true, dude.
What?
Sure, you do not have.
Yeah, you do not have.
I wear a 12.
Really?
Yeah.
That's a lie.
A children's 12 years old?
What?
No.
No, actually an awesome 12 plus is what I would say.
Put your feet on camera right now.
Lean back.
No, that is not going to happen.
You do not want to see my feet.
Do you have socks on?
I do not have socks on. In my own house?
Why?
Fuck no. Because I have nice wood floors.
Look at that!
Oh yeah!
Guys, I don't like this.
The way, the direction that you guys have taken this.
Your creative direction is really poor.
Are you calling me poor?
Yes, I am.
Prove me wrong by sending me money.
Yeah.
Maybe on a special day.
Ooh.
Christmas.
I'll give you a gift.
Whoa.
- Guys, I am really, really excited for St. Patrick's Day.
He's gonna give me a pot of gold.
- What would you do if he sent you a really nice bidet?
Would you use it?
- A bidet?
Yeah, I would use a bidet.
But that's the kind of thing
that I gotta clear with the boss.
Anything that comes into my house has to be wooden, pretty much.
So, I just bought a bathroom scale,
and I bought one that is so terrible.
And so useless.
No, no, no, no, no.
I bought it without asking her.
And I bought one that's this big.
And it's, but it's glass.
So I have to, and I hide it.
I hide it every day.
So if you could send me a wooden bidet,
maybe, like,
the aesthetic of my house is, you ever see those
roller coasters that hurt your back?
The really old ones?
It's too expensive.
Yeah, like they should just tear it down and put one of those ships that goes back and forth, but instead...
It's happened like five times. I'll send you all the time codes.
Next week, it's going to be so incredible, I'm going to get a new USB-C cable.
And the people are going to really appreciate that. I think I have a strong feeling that people are going to really appreciate that.
We are now taking bets on whether or not you forget to buy the USB C cable
I'll take the I'll take the forget line
Yeah, what's that - 500?
Yeah, that sounds about right. Yeah, I don't know how it's work
- means it's more likely
It makes sense to me yeah, well fuck you how about that yeah, I like that
- Yeah.
- I think, you know what I'm gonna do guys?
Instead, because I did not have a beer tonight.
- Uh-huh.
- As soon as we're done recording,
which will be in the next minute or so,
I'm gonna walk over into my kitchen
and I'm gonna smoke so much weed that I have to, I get,
like, I like smoking weed and then it's like
a ticking time bomb before I actually go crazy.
So I just, I will have to go to sleep in the next 30 minutes
and that's gonna be such a freeing feeling.
- I'm happy for you, man.
- What are you gonna do, Rex?
because you didn't have a beer,
so you need to hurt your body in some way.
- We'll be going back to work until late at night.
- Workers high.
- Yeah.
- Cheerio.
- Yes sir.
I drank a buff, what do you mean?
What do you mean?
- He drank a buff. - He drank a buff.
- He's drunk.
He's drunk.
- We're done.
- He said I drank a buff.
- I drank a buff.
- Till next time guys, bye.
Bye.
[BLANK_AUDIO]