(sipping)
(burping)
- You're listening to Beers We Drink,
America's number one beer podcast.
(record scratching)
(upbeat music)
- What's up all my chuggers?
Trying to get that burp out.
(burping)
- This is a journey into sea.
- Into the middle of.
- Plain and clean.
- Bud Light.
- Ooh, rip it!
- Beers we drank, motherfucker,
with Juvio, Caleb, and Rex.
- Hold on.
- Are we cracking?
- Oh, okay.
I gotta introduce my beer.
So I'll wait until this bullshit is done.
- Well, if you're so slap happy to introduce your beer,
then I think you can go first this time.
- Okay, so I don't wanna get,
I don't wanna get accused of same-beering
the podcast. Yeah, but it is it is a Modelo Negra, but it's a
different type of container that it comes in. If you could see
it's a bottle.
And can you say what the name of this podcast is?
Brews we drink?
Yep, that's right. That's right. So this is a beer that you
drank already.
Nobody it's different in a way.
The one I had last week, I think was in a can and this one has
foil on top of it, like a Ferrero Rocher almost.
- I really hate that foil on there.
'Cause I feel like they're probably charging me extra for it.
'Cause of its gold, 'cause of its color is golden.
- I'm assuming this is like an extra $20 in New York City.
- It's pretty expensive.
No, it's not expensive at all.
It's like the cheapest beer there is.
How is it? Is it better or worse out of the bottle versus the can?
I'm opening it still.
OK, well, then we'll just completely move on then.
Yeah. Yeah. So can I can I do my because I really want to try it.
This is a fucking mess. So I have two beers today.
OK. Oh.
I'm very excited about them.
Mm hmm. This is.
Computer Karen, yo, a SpongeBob
based beer paired with a
SpongeBob based flying slush man.
He is. Oh my God.
By four or both by four or five north in their new SpongeBob line of beers.
Wow. So you're excited.
Yes, I have Plankton's wife.
There was like computer like Krabby Patty.
There's there's like seven different SpongeBob beers.
Yeah, but I'm very excited for computer.
Why don't we think about a company making beers based off of a children's TV show?
I feel like that's some sort of breach of morality.
Every single person who watched that show as a child is of legal drinking age.
Yeah, but they're still running it. They're still making that show today.
And there's children today watching it today.
You do this. There might be little kids out there trying to buy that beer.
Yeah. There's kids watching this podcast.
Is it really good? Did you take a bite?
It's really good.
He took a bite.
Computer, Karen is raspberry, guava, grapefruit, and mango.
Grapefruit? I've never heard of that.
But that sounds really delicious.
Shut up!
I got delightful news. It tastes the same. It's the same beer.
You're kidding.
So you started with Karen. I'm very excited to hear about the Flying Slushman. That's
going to be coming up. Stick with us here at Beers We Drink. I'm going to introduce
my beer right now. Guys, I went classic this week with a Sapporo. Wait, but not just any
Sapporo, a Reserve Sapporo. Classic. Which I think I probably had this when I thought
I was having a normal Sapporo and I did not know. So I'm going to take a little sip. What
does it mean to be reserved? Oh my God, that's the best beer in the world. This is probably
for can, this is probably the best, if you can only have one, this is an amazing one
beer to have.
Agreed.
This is a perfect beer.
And I like that there's a great aspect to a Sapporo where the can is too heavy, it's
made with Japanese Damascus steel, which they make knives out of.
100 times folded beer can.
It's been folded 100 times in every can.
It's been brewed 100 times as well.
It has a hundred times brew.
It's very, very old, but for whatever reason, the can design, they put like an inch of just
pure metal at the bottom, so it always feels like there's an extra sip in here when you
finish the can, so it's like almost a prank beer.
That's awesome.
So I like it.
Definitely.
So I have a thing about Japanese beer, which is that I think sake bombs are like a healing
elixir.
Do you?
sick, like you have like a stomach issue, you've got you've got a cold coming on,
you go get a bunch of Saki balls, knock that shit right out. I would agree that
it probably helps with your mental health, but I'm not sure about your
physical health. I have healed physical ailments with Saki balls. I think if anyone knows about
potions and and breweries, it's gonna be him and not any of us. Why is that? Because he
he eats funny pills to like heal his brain.
- I do.
- I do too. - He's a genius.
- Well, we do eat funny pills.
That's just part of being a man.
- Not at his rate.
- That's just part of being a man
who thinks that his brain is the number one
most important thing on earth.
- Right. - Yeah, but if we put it
in a graph, I think Rex's pill and,
you know, pill consumption is much bigger than yours.
reach there's at least 15 different pill type object like let's get an overview
helicopter cam go yeah the webcam not not not don't pull them in move the way
okay starting on one end of the rainbow please tell me that you're gonna go all
the way around well of course I got golden book tea pills I got central tea
pills. I got all the different, you know, I got fucking
healthy brain pills.
I got immune plus gummies.
I got all my, you know, I got logic.
I got. Yeah. Oh, yeah.
I remember these.
I remember this.
I got extra strength migraine relief for when you take too many pills
and your brain feels a little fatigued.
You got to hit that balance.
Mm-hmm
I've got another thing of immune plus gummies, which I'm hitting on
What's this I love the would you just vase I just these are babes, okay, so you're basically
Blast fate that's awful
That's fair. You're doing very well mentally and physically is what I'm kind of gathering. I think that if I
Had one more week like the last four weeks had been I would be in the hospital
Yeah, well we have a grizzled you look very grizzled I'm glad you're free yes listen guys
so I've been thinking about this podcast a lot because
people have been
Over the moon I might say
about the quality the quantity
The
the sound mixing.
Yep.
And basically this is, we're rapidly becoming a top 100, top 50 podcast and people are begging us to put it on a
its own stream, its own feed. They want its own RSS feed. I want to list to it on iTunes.
Yeah.
No, motherfucker, it's actually a premium experience, right?
True.
That's kind of the whole point of the podcast, I might say. It's almost a speak easy
to be on brand.
But, I
Did notice that this becoming a little bit of one of these hanging out podcasts right and we don't want that
We don't need another hanging out podcast. No
Get the microphones away from white men
We hate crackers at beers we drink
So basically what I want to do is I kind of want to change the format to you guys know that show around the horn on
ESPN I love that show so around the horn is the greatest show ever made
My problem is I watch that shit and I go what the fuck are you talking about?
I don't know what the fuck like who the fuck any of these people are
I don't know what you're talking about
But I do like that you're in squares and that there's some different graphics and you're talking about individual stuff. But when they go
Greg
Masterson he
Destroyed his knee on the on the fucking field. I don't care who that is. I don't know what that is
I don't know what field they're talking about. Exactly. That's my problem. So I
So I am thinking that maybe we should go,
we should do topics one by one and just get,
at least for this episode, we try it out.
We should get everybody's view
on a different topic one by one.
I would love that.
There's nothing I would love more than to share my views.
It's funny that you say that because all week
I've been thinking about a specific topic
that I wanted to bring up and talk about.
Okay, well not before I get to my two topics
that I actually brought.
Okay, that's more topics than what I brought actually.
I brought two. So, no, number one is I had a new idea for a new show description that
we could put on iTunes if we, or not iTunes, but on the, like if, if there was a page somewhere
that said beers we drank, it would be, so you guys remember these old jokes? Yeah?
Yeah, I remember jokes.
Okay, you guys remember old, or wait, so I did it in the wrong order.
I remember every joke.
Okay, so basically it would be a Jewish guy, a Mexican guy, and a normal guy walk into
a bar. In a ball? No, no, not a normal guy.
And that would be like, because this is, this is the, it captures perfectly the point of
the show, the conceit of the show, which is that the whole show is just about what if
these three were at a bar and, but they didn't like hanging out and they like doing, they
like pretending they were doing around the horn at the bar. Because you don't hang out
on the show. It's not a hangout show anymore.
Not a hangout show.
No, it's not.
It's just in a round the horn style.
What if three guys went to a bar?
They were all different races and levels of normalcy
and had different kind of hair.
And then they pretended they were on ESPN for an hour and four minutes.
We do run the gamut of hair.
Yeah, that's right.
Normal.
Yep.
Interesting.
Oh, OK. Double interesting.
I was trying to get a boring.
I got an answer hint haircut kind of.
- No.
- You have a Hitler--
- That is quite literally the least interesting haircut
for 10 years running. - No, I didn't get
a Hitler haircut.
- You did.
- No, I got like a little mullet sort of.
- You got the fucking Edgar, but you're not cool enough to--
- That's not true.
I'm not an Edgar, don't say that about me.
That's actually racist.
- You're a fucking Edgar.
- What's his Edgar?
- First, racist incidents.
Don't worry about it.
Number one racist incident in "Breeze with Rank."
- I think you look good.
I think you look like you're in Peaky Blinders.
(laughing)
- No, that's not true.
Which that would be a much funnier show if it was in Mexico.
Peaky Blinders.
What's that show about?
I've actually, I know nothing about it.
It's Killian Murphy.
Some blokes in England drinking some fucking beer.
So it's basically the show's about this.
It's about a guy will say something like,
"I don't want to pay that."
Or like, "You better get out of here."
To the guy from 28 Days Later.
But then he comes up and he has a full Hitler haircut.
And he walks over and he says,
"Actually, bloody fuck you."
And then that alpha male song from TikTok starts playing
and there's like a bunch of different videos of him.
Yeah.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
And he starts walking around in slow motion.
So that's so it's like the episodes are only about.
Yeah, but the episodes are 40 seconds long.
It's like Fight Club in England.
I think very mixed.
Fight Club in England?
Yep.
(laughing)
- You can't say that and then like get out of it
by taking a sip and now you're pretending to cough.
Okay, next topic I have here.
Guys, there's, I mean we've heard all about it,
but this AI stuff is getting frankly out of hand.
AI stands for artificial technology
And it is a growing, it's a growing technology.
It is growing.
And I hate to say that.
So what is y'all's opinion on that?
Around the Horn style show.
Around the Horn.
Where we kind of give our own opinions
on the different topics.
One thing I will say about Around the Horn,
completely ripped off At Midnight.
I agree, points.
(laughing)
- Actually, okay.
I'm rethinking the whole thing.
(laughing)
I'm rethinking the format of the show
for no reason right now.
Okay, so if AI was in a room with you,
what would you say to them?
- Hey, how's it going?
- Points.
- No, that's--
- Points for politeness.
I would say, "Hey Siri, turn off."
- Negative points to Jubio, negative points to you.
We'll take all your points away.
- Siri's actually, no, fuck off.
- You said, "Oh, and now he's cussing on TV."
Yep, you're done, you're never invited ever again
to @midnight.
- But it's @midnight, you can say--
- Or @945.
- You can say, "Was it actually at midnight?"
- It was at midnight.
- The TV show?
Oh yeah, dude.
I one time watched it with my dad and he said,
he was like, "This is filthy.
"You cannot watch this in my house."
And he made me turn it off.
- It was pretty disgusting.
And it turned out the guy who ran it
was no clean whistle himself.
- He had the old, I would say he had the--
- Justin Orland.
- Basically the same guy.
He had the number one Me Too story.
- So funny.
- Where he was--
- Easily the funniest.
- His girlfriend had like full vagina reconstruction
or some shit like that.
Or no, it wasn't that.
like she had like a life threatening thing in her,
like she had a life threatening vagina.
I don't even know that it was her vagina.
She had some kind of surgery where she had to have it.
And if she didn't have it, she would die.
It was a really, really bad recovery.
Bomb extraction surgery.
Yeah, she had a bomb in her body.
(laughing)
She's in the, the only two people who are in the like
recovery room are the girl's mom and Chris Hardwick,
her boyfriend.
And her mom is like, when can she like go back to work?
Like when can she go home or whatever?
And Chris Hardwick just goes, when could she have sex again?
Yeah.
When did you fucking suck my stupid dick?
The doctor.
Points to me.
When he asked the doctor, the only thing he said is when can she fuck again in front
of this girl's mom after she had like her stomach ripped out of her body.
Yeah.
That's it.
So you got canceled for that?
Speaking of canceled.
No, and then also I think that he raped also.
Well, yeah, whatever.
Speaking of points to him, did you see the stuff about
Emily Radage?
You know, her husband and the Saftey brothers.
Oh, no. What happened?
So he he used to work for the Saftey brothers on like Good Time
and Uncut Gems, who's like a casting director.
So it leads off with the story about like a 17 year old girl.
They were like, we're going to bring you on to do a scene with Robert Pattinson,
your favorite actor.
You love what a dumb bitch. Wow. That's right.
And then they were like, just kidding.
It's just some ex con we hired.
And then he's like, can I fuck you?
Can I put my penis inside you?
To Emily Rzaczkowski?
No, to some 17 year old. Oh.
And then he
so then it like moves on from that story.
And it talks about a different girl during Uncut Jams,
because I was during good time.
So then during Uncut Gems, he found another 17 year old on Instagram
that he was like, I'm going to make you famous and then like brought her
back to the apartment where he and Emily were like staying.
He's like, Can I put my penis in you without a condom?
Just kidding. I'm not going to ask.
And then just like kind of did it. Never mind. And then
no points to him.
You know, I was talking to him and then that's it.
- If I had been there, by the way, I would have said--
- Points.
- No points, no, I would have said no points.
No points at all.
- Too much.
- Way too much, dude.
- And then I would go--
- No points at all.
- I would do my thing, I would hit my button,
I would go, "Rapey McRapeface,"
and then you go, "Points."
- Yeah.
- And then I go, "Okay, points to me for Rapey McRapeface."
No points to you for having sex with a 10-year-old.
Yeah, so he hit up a 15 year old on Instagram
and then she like was like, Yo, why are you DMing this 15 year old?
And he's like, Why are you a retarded kike?
Which you can say, because Rex is both.
I can say both.
I can say both those things.
And he's like, What?
It's a fucking it's a joke, bitch.
Get a sense of humor.
And wow.
So that's his cancellation.
This was Emily Radzikowski's husband.
Yeah.
Friend married.
Wow.
So how does I mean, obviously, that's terrible.
That guy's bad. Yeah, it's not funny.
But the real story is, how does it reflect on her
that she would even be married to such a monster?
So I'm kind of and she's famous and he's not.
So I'm a lot more interested in blaming her in this situation.
If you guys join me in that.
It is entirely her fault.
I do see that she enticed him to do this.
If she had been sucking his dick enough, this would never have happened.
Or she should have, she should have
maybe
immobilized him, should have broken his kneecaps
or something. Yeah. She should have killed him.
Should have gone through his phone more. More women should be going through their men's
phones. Agreed.
We need to do more background checks on everyone for everything.
If I had a fucking
boyfriend,
I'd be going through his phone all the fucking time
dude. Yeah?
Oh my god yes. If I had like a
hot, successful boyfriend.
- Yeah.
- There's no fucking way I'm not touching that phone.
- I wasn't successful, but my ex used to have
a fucking GPS tracker on me.
- Did you see that?
Like she shot like a dart gun that went into your neck
and put a chip in you.
She just had the location sharing on your phone.
- Yeah, but she made me install an app to do it.
- Okay, that's a little crazy.
Yeah, that might as well be a blow dart.
- Yeah.
I wasn't even doing anything.
I didn't leave my house.
I still don't leave my house.
- That's even-- - Was that when you
were working at a distro, Cream?
- I would get even more suspicious.
If you were just in the house all the time,
I would assume that you would--
You just got a second phone.
See, you see how good I would be at being a girlfriend?
A crazy girlfriend?
- You would be really good.
Which is crazy because Julio was in this call,
and as a Latina, he should be the crazy girlfriend.
- Exactly.
- What's the one app that you guys would go through
on your boyfriend's phone?
I would go instantly on Instagram to see his feed and then check.
Yeah. We'll check the feed first and then I'll find all the hot girls that he
follows. And then I'll go to, to his, uh,
messages and see that he sees messaging, uh,
LeBron James or something like that. And go like, who the fuck is this?
Yeah. How, how,
how awful would that be if you thought that your boyfriend was cheating on you
and you go into, uh, you go into his like Instagram DMs.
And instead of like him DMing like hot girls all day,
he's literally like just responding to like,
reacting to Russell Westbrook stories
with like praying hands emojis and shit.
That would be worse, right?
If he's like reacting to J. Cole stories,
like, yo, this is lit.
Like I would--
- I'll do you one better.
He's just reacting to his favorite podcasters stories.
- That'd be way worse, yeah.
- Yeah, he's reacting to Patrick and getting it.
(laughing)
Yeah, you find out that he's he's responding to Brandon Wardell
open Q and A's on Instagram stories.
You got. Yeah, I'm leaving this guy.
But if I had a boy's phone and he was my boyfriend,
I would probably go through the settings and probably change his
change the language to French or Chinese or something. Yeah.
Something that's really hard to speak.
Yeah, exactly.
And then let him, you know, go do his thing.
That will teach him to have a phone.
What do you even need a phone for?
Not much these days, but that's back to my point about artificial
and technology technologies,
which is that guys, this is getting crazy these days.
Basically, I don't I saw this.
Sorry, am I speaking?
Let him finish.
Thank you.
Muted.
Basically, I saw that OpenGPT can now draw a smiley face
with no-- if you just ask me.
[LAUGHTER]
That's the other way.
That's fucking crazy, dude.
So it's worrying me--
It's going to take all the jobs.
I-- that's-- yeah, you're fucking telling me.
I have a job as a smiley face drawer.
[LAUGHTER]
I get paid $400,000 a year to draw
smiley faces.
I'm going to be in
my livelihood is in danger.
Eli Ezra Yudkowsky's
fucking militia army of
minimum wage workers
who bomb Amazon Web Service servers
because they host a chat GPT thing.
That's what I'm looking to do.
That would be very, very fun.
What do you think AI is going to take over
creative jobs like podcasts and shit?
I think, actually, I think like 18 months.
Yeah, yeah, I think it's going to be real.
I think we're pretty much done.
This is like I would say beers we drank might even be seen
as historically as the last great podcast, right?
By humans.
Yeah. Once I starts doing their own version of wait, wait,
don't tell me and stuff, you're just going to it's over.
Car talk, right?
They can bring car talk back with the dead guy.
Right, exactly. That's the thing.
You could have a new episode of the Joe Rogan podcast
three times a week.
It's three hours long.
They have famous guests with a lot of voices,
and you get to hear your favorite podcaster, Joe Rogan,
talk to famous people multiple times a week for free.
Wow.
Don't even need to include Joe Rogan in the whole thing.
You're saying AI is going to make this dream a reality?
Oh, I was talking about Spotify.
Oh, OK.
Oh, never mind then.
We're talking about artificial technology right now.
Talk about AI, not Spotify.
Why don't we talk about...
Wait, that just gave me like an awesome idea.
Oh, yeah, that is true.
Just like having an app where you can just like make your own
pod, like your own dream podcast.
It's just like Joe Rogan speaking to my friend.
Well, oh my God, what would be your dream Rogan episode?
Um, yeah, actually you.
- Shut up.
(laughing)
- I wouldn't want to go on.
- It would be so funny because you would be
so intimidated by him.
- You would.
- Me? Joe Rogan?
- You're the same kind of guy.
- He's a pipsqueak.
He's a pipsqueak, I would take him out.
What, bald?
Is that what you, bald with tattoos
and basically shredded, ripping muscles.
- You would be so shy, you'd be like,
"Oh my God, my king talking to me right now."
- I do love him so, so much.
- Yeah, you would be stunned.
Anytime I hear, I've heard a couple of stories of him acting, even just,
just slightly, just a little bit Hollywood and a little bit snobby.
And it literally, it's, it causes psychic damage to me.
Yeah.
He is my, he is my every man.
I thought he was better than that.
Yeah.
But then he's been, you know, then you realize he was on TV when he was like 21.
It's kind of amazing that he's as, see, now I'm just going to gush about him
for five or five or 10 minutes.
It's amazing that he's so he's built.
Um.
Are you crying?
No, it's sorry.
He's built a basically a entire Empire
with just him and his little brother or whatever.
Jamie.
I don't know what Jamie is.
But him and his little brother basically done.
They changed the entire world.
So now there's more and more people are starting to believe
in Atlantis.
and I would say that's directly his doing.
So I think he's a very good man.
- Yours goes a lot to Joe Rogan, I would say.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- I would say we're brother podcasts.
- Yeah, yeah, no doubt.
- We're a brother podcast.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Either that or impulsive. - A projector style podcast.
Yeah.
- I would say we're part impulsive.
- I think we're both, we're half and half.
- We're like the best parts of Rogan
and the best parts of impulsive put together.
I'm Big Mike, Jubio is George,
and obviously Rex is Jake or Logan Paul.
Right. George.
George is there like a comedian friend
like started stand up like six months ago.
And Bobby Lee made fun of him because he's a Christian
and he like walked out of the episode.
That's awesome.
You got so bad comedian who walks out on a podcast.
Yeah, because Bobby Lee is like,
"Oh, Christian, yeah, what do I suck Jesus's cock?"
And he was like, "I can't even fucking do this."
And he left the room.
That's not cool, man.
I don't play with that.
You watch impulsive clips, shorts?
No, no, no, no.
No, it's even worse than that.
I watch podcast drama channels
that when something crazy happens on Impulsive,
they will cover it.
Now that is what's up.
Now that is the lowest of the low.
I think whenever I think of Caleb using his phone,
I feel like half of the day he's just,
he's just browsing YouTube shorts.
And the other half of the day, he's playing a game on his phone
and he's never looking at either discord or text messages or slack.
He's always, I almost always have do not disturb on.
There's a single button that is just an electrical pulse that zaps him.
And I like about it for
- 30 minutes.
(laughing)
- If I could set my phone up to do that, I probably would.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- If I could put a thin layer of electricity
that just like zaps up and down on the top.
But no, worse than my phone--
- Before Julio was the group Twitch streamer,
my dream idea was that I would be a Twitch streamer
and I would have like a shot caller
that would be like a love sense,
but for like Twitch streaming.
And so people would--
- You can totally do that now.
- No, I think that's against TOS.
- It's against TOS.
- Well, it's against TOS on Twitch,
but there's Skick and Rumble going around.
- Oh, shit.
Yeah, we should go on Kick
and we should start beheading animals.
- We should start gambling and shocking you
whenever you lose money.
- I do think I would get shocked for five--
- Hey, that is so smart.
We shock him when the bonus pot loses money.
(laughing)
- Use the shock of electricity?
Okay, we are doing that, that is so funny.
- That is such a good idea.
- I know, that's what I'm saying.
When I found out that you couldn't do it,
it was like devastating.
- Yeah.
- That was my dream.
- Today's a new day, so we're ordering
a shock holler tonight.
- I'm looking at my screen time,
and my number one by a lot is YouTube.
And then my number two is New York Times Games,
because I'm a bit of a crossword/spelling bee fan.
- You're spending eight hours a day looking for Wartle.
(laughing)
- She's like, F-U-D-G-E.
- No. - No.
C-R-E-A-M, no.
- What is your guys' top one favorite
Wartle word to ask to submit?
- Dozer.
- Okay. - Or bozer, I mean.
Bozer.
- That's not funny.
- Do you mean like my opening gambit or my--
- I don't do WURTLE anymore.
WURTLE is for babies.
- WURTLE's fun.
- It's for children.
- I do love when I can use a silly word like penis.
- You know which one's my favorite one?
My favorite one is KITTLE.
- Okay, and hey, I got another question for you.
What is your favorite shape to put into that block
that only accepts a single shape?
What's your favorite one?
Since we're just going with just baby fucking loser games.
Circle?
- Okay.
- Cool, and what's your favorite domino to stack?
Which one, the one with the three dots and one dot?
- I'm gonna take over here as the host
and I'm gonna give you negative points
for being rude to me.
- Okay, that's been Beers We Drank.
Thanks for joining us.
We're never, it's basically completely over
because there's been a mutiny.
We'll be back next week with a hot girl instead of a Jubio.
- Oh, yeah, that'd be great.
- That's the idea.
- We're never gonna hear our first guest.
We need guests now.
- I don't need guests, dude.
- We need to do one of those podcasts
that has so many guests that no one gets to speak
a full sentence the entire show.
- Right. - For like three hours.
- What are you even talking about?
- I wanna just sit there and drink my beer quietly
for an hour.
- Yeah, I just wanna see something else.
- Just listen. - Talk.
(laughing)
I fucking hate talking.
- We should choose one podcast that already exists
that has a lot of guests on it,
and we should just take all of the guests that they do
just the week after every single time.
- I think that's a good idea,
but also I don't know any podcasts.
- We could check out Impulsive, you could check that out.
- I guess, I mean, the only way that I discover new podcasts
is when I go on Google Podcasts
and I search the word spaghetti.
And I look at all the spaghetti podcasts.
- What are you talking about?
- I've done it before. - He does do this.
- You have a spaghetti method to find podcasts?
- I don't find them, I just think it's funny
that you can go on a like a podcast tab.
You can do it right now, listener.
You go on a podcast tab, you search a silly word like spaghetti,
which who's going to call their podcast spaghetti or the spaghetti podcast?
Probably is going to be dozens of results of people being like this.
And you listen to this.
No, I just look at him.
Yeah, you I take that back.
Caleb has a normal time on his phone.
You are the monkey.
- Yeah, you have a crazy time.
- I'm gonna look at my screen time.
- Oh, I wish I was playing Crazy Time right now.
- Oh, wow, we haven't played Crazy Time in a long time.
- I know. - I would love,
do you remember the first time
after discovering online gambling,
the first time that you went to a real casino?
And you were like, this is trash.
- It's bad. - This is literally
so fucking bad, bro.
Where is the Crazy Time?
Where is, like, I was hoping that it was gonna be
basically just different stages like SNL.
And I'm just going to walk up to them and be like,
Hello, I'd like to lose $100.
Wow. Twitter number one for old Jubio.
Yeah. And then Firefox number three.
That's crazy. This guy loves jacking off.
Yeah. No, that's not true.
I'm looking up stuff.
So you hate jacking off?
I hate jacking off.
No, it's not true.
That's not true. I just look up stuff.
I'm going to go look at my tabs now.
When I went to a real casino,
I've only gone to a real casino once after I started online gambling.
I lost $300.
Was that an AC with us?
OK, twice. Yeah.
AC was fun because we were all together,
but I went to one with my parents, with my dad, and
I remember going to all the slots and being like, where are the bonus buys?
Why are all these slots so bad?
And then I lost $300 and I was walking towards
the ATM to take out more money.
And I happened.
My dad happened to be coming from the other side of the casino, saw me.
It came up. It was like, Oh, how are you doing?
Yeah, you still up?
I was like, Of course. Yeah, no, I'm just
actually I'm going to go cash out.
And he's like, Yeah, you know, I'm up like 400 bucks.
Like, I think I think I think we're good.
They get out of here.
And I was like, Oh, yeah, that's probably a really good idea.
Let's get out.
Wow. So your dad still thinks you made money.
Yeah, I completely lied to him about it.
That's so embarrassing.
My dad losing $300 in an hour and a half.
Yeah, that is a lot of money.
You know what happened?
What I started doing dollar 50 spins on a slot going,
I can't lose all my money doing this.
You can you lose.
I've never I've been to a casino.
I've had probably 15 days at casinos at this point,
And I've never came like I've never won.
The slots are eaters.
They do every single time.
Yeah, you really have to like go.
You have to be like you have to want to play like backer
rot or some shit like that.
But like the last thing I want, the one time that I went and did that shit,
I went and played roulette
and it was like real late at night.
And there was this like fat southern guy who was like
just he was putting so much money down.
And so everybody loved him.
Everybody was just like loving it because he was betting like a thousand dollars
on like numbers and shit.
Like he's obviously a rich dude.
But he was like
yelling about he was he was screaming quotes from like Talladega Nights.
Like he thought, yeah, so he was like, he's like throwing down
a thousand dollars on the thing, like tipping the lady 500 bucks.
And she's like, oh, thank you so much.
And he's like, oh, sweet baby Jesus.
Oh, sweet baby Jesus, little baby Jesus in a manger.
And everybody's like, yeah, yeah, this guy's the man.
And he got to live, he thought for like a while, like he's doing.
He thought that he was like
the the king of the world for a minute.
He was he was doing Will Ferrell lines.
And he's saying, if you're if you a first, you're last.
And he's just like and everybody's for some reason just loving it
because he's like just a drunk, ugly guy screaming.
And I was like, that is the you have to be like that kind of guy
if you're going to make any money in one of those games.
Yeah, you have to be like a Porky the Pig dude
who's dishing out office quotes.
And then people will say for whatever reason,
God will bless you and you will make a lot of money.
God blesses all his retarded children.
Yeah, exactly.
Totally.
And it's just a movie that I like only the half of it.
I don't like the first half of the movie.
Did a rewatch recently.
Not really.
None of his shit really holds up.
OK.
Yeah, Elf does completely hold up.
If anybody...
Yeah, you think Elf holds up to me in particular?
You are an elf, canonically in the Bible, Jews are Elves.
So next question.
I like Elf.
I like the other guys.
The other guys.
You never seen that?
Oh, you're saying the movie, the other movie, the other guy.
Yeah, I'm naming Will Ferrell movies.
I thought you were talking about the other guys.
Creatures. You are a moron.
No, I like Elf. I like the other guys.
I like what's another welfare.
I like Anchorman.
Anchorman's great.
Yeah, that movie came out today.
We called Dankerman.
He would.
Smoke one.
No, because anchor it.
No, no points taken away.
- No, it would be called Anchor Woman or Anchor,
like do that.
- Anchor them.
Anchor them, that's perfect.
It would be called, or you could even add--
- Say points right now.
- Okay, points.
But not points to you, you said Danker Man,
which made no sense.
- Anchor them, I said anchor them also.
- No you didn't.
- What do you wait on at midnight?
Do they win money?
- No, oh my God, oh my God.
- You foolish man.
- Where do the points go?
(laughing)
- That's literally a conversation I've had with like,
my grandma walking in the middle of the night
and I'm watching at her.
Wait, where do the points go?
- I live in a different country.
- Wait, they just,
the points just go away at the end of the show?
- Yes, you moron.
Haven't you ever seen "Whose Line Is It Anyway?"
Where the points basically don't matter as far as I know.
- But they do,
because the winner gets to be the host at the end.
- Wait, he has seen "Whose Line Is It Anyway?"
- I mean, whose line is it anyway?
- Whose line, the points matter.
- Okay, so the points actually--
- They say they don't matter, but they do matter.
- Okay, so that's actually the trick of At Midnight.
They say that the points matter.
- But they don't matter. - But the points do not matter.
- I think you're trying to lie to me.
- No, I'm not.
I'm really not.
'Cause when the workaholics boys get up there on At Midnight,
they're not fighting each other,
trying to climb to the top over each other's broken bodies.
It's not competitive like that. They're working together to make somebody laugh and his name starts with a J and
It ends with a bunch of I don't know how to spell your name
But it ends with a bunch of probably accents over every single word and maybe a backwards L somewhere
With Ron funches is saying puns in his sweet voice. Yeah, his sweet is honey voice
He sounds so pretty he has a beautiful. He's like if Danny Brown was jovial
He's one of those guys that should have stayed really fat. I
Hate wait hold on wait. He lost weight. You don't even look it up. You're gonna be so upset
They're both
I'm gonna punch his weight loss. Oh
My goodness he lost weight isn't that awful look at him. He's like
Jonah Hill
Yeah, it's so bad and he used to be basically as fat as a balloon and now he's
He used to be a big old black balloon. And now he's basically just a normal guy. He lost
140 pounds that's too much man
You're supposed if you're a fat guy who's who has ever had a picture taken of him of you
You need to realize that somebody somewhere is sitting looking at that picture
You're going
(laughs)
Laughing at it.
Yeah.
So it is on you to not tear away that person's joy
by losing weight.
You can't do it.
You're supposed to go out.
If you're comically fat, you need to completely be a,
what's his name?
Ralphie May.
You need to die.
You have to die.
You have to just exponentially get bigger and bigger
and bigger until, I think he popped one day.
I think he was in the middle of traffic in Los Angeles and he popped and he exploded.
Yeah.
And people thought that maybe some kind of fish market truck, uh, uh,
flipped over, but it was just Ralphie Mays kind of in trails and we're
finding whole, whole pieces of sushi.
Just splattered across the, uh, the four or five leather tarp of meat.
Yeah, exactly.
Can you imagine what that is?
(laughing)
I mean like, you can't put him in a normal coffin.
You literally, you have to put him in a round coffin.
They have to, right?
They make fat guy everything.
Damn, coffin for fat.
A reinforced fat guy coffin.
Coffin for a fat person.
Oh my God.
A company called Goliath Casket makes them
as big as 52 inches wide.
- That's so sick, dude.
- Goliath casket. - Imagine that doesn't
fit you enough, but you're like,
you know, you're on the line,
so they're like kinda squishing you in,
they're like. (laughs)
- Dude, this is like a queen-size bed.
- Yeah. - Wow.
- Yeah, and it still might not be big enough
for someone like Ralphie Mae.
- Wow.
- I think it'd be funny if they were like,
no, we can't put him in a coffin,
and they're like, they burn your body,
and then there's too much ash to put in an urn,
So they have to put you in like a big jar.
Yeah, they have to put you in a rain bucket,
like a 50-gallon drum that you would keep a chemical in.
And people have to be like, "Yeah, that was my dad."
Yeah, they put him in a Home Depot paint bucket.
He's in that big blue, Breaking Bad, 55-gallon drum
right over there.
And when we go to spread his ashes,
we have to roll it down the beach.
We have to roll it up and down the dunes.
Yeah, God bless those big fat people for being a giant burden even in their death.
That is so amazing.
It is really dope.
Yeah.
Do you think there was fat cavemen?
No.
I, last night, or a couple nights ago, I smoked way too much weed and I asked Chad GPT if
there's any evidence that cavemen ever experienced any kind of depression.
(laughing)
- Like a cave painting, with like a frowny face.
- I was like, was there like an Elliot Smith caveman,
who was like, yes, exactly, frowny face.
- You asked Chad to be T this?
- Yeah.
- What did he say?
- I think that's just how you do anything now,
because I'm into artificial technology.
Yeah, you'd go on there and you say, what is it?
Dude, honestly, the thing that I saw
that scared me the most this week,
was the somebody showed that you can take a picture
with the new one, take a picture of your fridge
and it will tell you what to make
with the like ingredients in your fridge.
- What?
- Yeah, and I-- - What?
- Is that scary?
That scares me.
- See, that's what I'm saying.
- How is that scary?
- Artificial technology-- - We have to do terror,
we have to terrorize this shit.
We have to-- - It gives you,
it gives you access to a dumb friend at all hours.
- Yeah, exactly.
Young friend with unique skills.
It's amazing.
Who might one day become a ghost,
literally a ghost or a god or a demon
if you give it enough time.
Have you seen the post where people are asking
to do ASCII art of like a word
and it just spits out a completely
different word that's completely wrong?
No, I haven't seen that.
I think you should ask it to do that.
I think it really grounded it for me.
Like it's just, oh, this thing doesn't do anything.
It doesn't know anything.
you're wrong you're wrong dude no it's over anything but it knows a lot you
have to understand it's it's a dumb guy with access to every book okay Rex I
think it's now it's time for you to break out with the thing that you showed
me earlier today what did you show him earlier did he showed me wrist GPT oh
yeah Riz GPT what's Riz GPT it's a new thing some guys made so it uses augmented
reality glasses, uh huh, whisper, whisper API, which is the
uh, chat to beauty plugin that transcribes audio on the fly.
Yeah.
And then, uh, what it does is while you're talking to someone,
it will in front of your eyes display a generated response to
what they're saying.
So you don't even have to use your brain to think of what to
say in a conversation.
It's marketed to like end awkwardness in first dates and job interviews.
But the best part about the job, the like the technical that it did was like this person
is like asking you a question and he, you, the AI comes up with like the most generic
answers that don't really answer the question.
Which is perfect.
It also takes, it takes so long to process that.
Yeah it also takes like five seconds.
So you're just sitting and smiling.
So the setup is this.
By the way, you said job interviews.
So you're in an interview for like a marketing position.
Could I just look this up?
You sit there and the guy says,
"So what's your biggest weakness?"
And you just kind of look right at him.
For like a minute.
For a minute, and then you go.
While it's like processing.
Hey, I just realized that if we were both emojis,
we'd be the perfect pair.
Want to find out which one?
Yeah.
Something like that.
It's just like something super generic
that wouldn't really convince anyone to hire you.
- I think that you would get hired if you said,
"Hey there, sorry, I know we're in the middle
of a job interview.
Are you Pluto?
'Cause you may not be a planet,
but you still look out of this world."
They're gonna be like, "Wait, this guy actually has
extreme charm.
I think he would be an amazing member of the geek squad."
the two options were first dates and job interviews
because those are like two very different,
you know, type of scenarios.
- Those are things where people get awkward, you know.
- Yeah, but those are like two very different scenarios.
- Can we use this right now?
- There's two different energies.
- Is this out yet?
- I don't think you can really use it.
I think you just use it like open AI.
- It says it's coming soon, guys.
Riz GPT, oh wait, hmm.
Hmm, I might've been wrong.
It might actually be out.
But I was thinking after, like with that context earlier,
how cool would it be,
ChachiPT as a co-host to the podcast?
- That would be probably the,
honestly, probably by the time this podcast is posted,
there will be 500 podcasts that have some variation
of that idea incorporated in them.
- Yeah, but I was thinking beer.
- Yeah, but we should ask him what he thinks about beer.
- I was, when I was walking to the beer store today,
I was on my phone typing the chat,
CBT, can you give me some,
some other titles for my podcast?
Here is some past titles like, uh, you know,
like red Mustang. Yeah. You know, I,
I forgot what the, what I called it last time, but that one,
I am become a drunk destroyer of beers or whatever,
right? Drinker of beers. What does it say?
I said here, have a beer, gives beer. It says as an AI language model I don't have a
physical body to consume beer but I appreciate the gesture.
I like that it only took us like a month to get to the level where we're like what if we just read shit in the chat sheet.
It is fun dude.
Wait, wait, I have to get his opinion on your topics. AI and the other thing. I forgot what the other thing was.
Oh, no, that's, I don't want to do this.
I just wanted to give it a beer,
but I thought that maybe it would be like,
okay, grabs beer, gulp, but it didn't.
So I give up.
And now I will open my second beer, by the way,
which is a little bit of a curve ball, guys.
I'm ready.
You know me.
I never go the same beer twice.
This is a June Shineheart Kombucha.
Oh, okay.
P.O.G. flavor.
So you might not--
Person of color.
Player of the game.
of player of games. I actually don't know what what is a passion fruit orange guava.
Mmm Wow. Penis of Grinjer. Penis of Grinjer? I didn't say that. You did say that. Let's
see how this one is. That's um pretty good. I can't lie. I like hard. Okay I want to
I get to my topic now.
Oh yeah, to your topic, yeah.
My topic that I've been thinking about this entire week.
Yeah.
I want to talk about animal beefs.
The fuck are you talking about?
Like meats?
No.
Animal beefs?
Like between animals?
No, between you and an animal.
Oh.
So, it's been well documented that Caleb has been fighting different mice in New York.
That's true.
So we don't really have to go into his beefs.
Unless he has an update on those.
I would rather ask Rex on whether or not he has an animal beef that he's ever been in
- I'm gonna go in one, because I myself
have been embroiled in a tight beef this past week or so.
- I don't know why you're dragging me into your story.
I don't have problems with animals.
- I'm just, I just wanna, okay.
I'm just opening the floor to see
if you had a story about this.
- So you're opening the floor so that you don't feel
bad about telling your story?
- No, I don't.
- Why are you getting so defensive, Rex?
You're acting like it's so crazy
that you might beef with an animal.
- Why would I beef with an animal?
- Because you broke, but you stopped being vegetarian,
for one, and I'm sure, by the way,
when I stopped being vegetarian, animals started noticing.
- Did they?
- Animals started treating me differently.
I will say that.
I was vegan until I was 17 years old,
as soon as I stopped, animals started treating me worse.
Strangers, stranger animals, strange animals,
different animals, really weird animals.
You were a predator.
Pigeons stopped looking at me, started shitting on my face.
Dogs, any time that I would go to another person's house when I was vegan, dogs were attracted
to me like I was made out of fucking beef jerky, right?
Which might have had something to do with my sweat condition.
But they loved me.
And I knew that it was because they didn't eat me.
Cows, when I would drive down the road in a cow, in like a farmland area, cows would
look right at me, make direct eye contact.
And then when I stopped being vegan, it all went away.
So I think you're probably experiencing a similar thing.
So the beef that I've been embroiled with, it's been with, funny you say pigeons because
it's been with pigeons.
You guys have pigeons in Mexico?
My entire adulthood I've been having a really tense relationship with pigeons because in
my old house, where I used to park my car, there was like, you
know, there's like, there were just shit on my car all the time.
Yeah, because they sit on top of it shit in it. And I was like,
pretty pissed was like, Oh, I'm like parking on the street.
Something nothing much I can do. But ever since I moved into this
apartment, I noticed that the past people who lived here, the
left a grill with like a cover on it. And as soon as I took the
cover of, there was like a nest inside of it and there was a
pigeon there. So I was like, all right, I want to just take just
throw the shit away.
Whoa,
the pigeon will know the pigeon will know this is not a this is
not welcoming space for my kind.
Leave a note.
Wait, that is not how by the way, that is not what you're
supposed to do with a bird's nest. You're supposed to not
touch it because it's temporary. And they're gonna forget that
they made it or something. I don't remember why you're not
supposed to do that.
I'm pretty sure that's wrong. Anyways, I threw it away. I was
like, you know what, he they'll get the message they'll get that
I'm racist against them and they will never come back. And I left
it at that for a couple for a month or so. And I, I kind of
noticed that they were like kind of flying in and out. And I was
like, shoo him away if I ever saw him. If I ever caught him, I
was like in the living room. But this past week, we noticed that
there's in my balcony, there's like two like AC condensers,
like just sitting by a corner, and behind one of them, that
we're nesting again. And one night there were just a pigeon just hanging out on
top of like the like just hanging out on the wall. I'm like, "Oh that's weird." And we
saw the nest, we're like, "Oh that sucks." So that same day I bought my best
friend Santiago. Santiago the owl. Some of you may know him. We don't like, I don't
like Santiago. We already talked about this on the podcast. Yeah, we won't go into too much
depth in it. So we could like just scare them so that they wouldn't hang out in
here anymore. Um, and I put him
down, and I thought he was doing
his job. But I come in the next
day, and there's a pigeon just
sitting on the nest. And I'm
trying to shoot away, but it
just won't go away. I'm like,
Joe, get out of here. Fuck,
fuck off. And it's not gonna
wait. And I'm like, All right,
I'm gonna get the broom, and I'm
gonna kill you. So I get the
broom. And I try to like, like,
just nudge it. So just flies
away. And the fucking thing
starts batting at it. It bats at
the broom. And it was so violent
towards me. And I'm like, you
know what this this pigeon must be sitting on an egg and they're really
defensive but I really don't want them to be here laying eggs in my fucking
balcony so I googled and apparently they're they really hate pepper so I
just like threw a bunch of pepper in the balcony and the thing left and sure
enough there's a fucking there's a tiny little pigeon egg on the nest behind my
AC unit.
So I'm like, okay, this is that egg.
You're a killer.
With I am going to listen in the past.
Every every episode, one of us has to wear the evil crown.
Caleb was the evil guy when he when he shoved a finger up his ass.
Rex was the evil guy.
I mean, that was that was a little.
Right. So you guys were judging.
It was like taking the logic pill on the podcast.
I'll be the evil guy this week.
I threw away.
- Don't pretend like those are comparable, man.
You're in the life. - I'll be the evil guy.
- You're literally a murderer.
- I threw away the nest and the egg.
- Oh my God. - And I was like,
you guys need to get out of here.
- You didn't even give it a chance.
You didn't even, okay, here's what I'd do.
If I'm in your situation.
- They're gonna come grab it and take it away.
They don't have any hands.
- Hey, asshole, here's what you do.
You pop it on your favorite chair
and you hatch that puppy.
- No.
You sit on that. You should be sitting on it right now.
And you warm it up.
This is a strictly no pigeon household.
I'm popping that egg and speaking of my ass,
it's going directly in my ass and I'm making the most beautiful baby pigeon
you've ever seen in your life. I cannot believe you.
You did not go out and buy a $30,000 incubator.
I did not even think about that. I thought about, I've been putting pepper,
I've been putting pepper all over my balcony every single day.
So they sniff it and they go away.
-You should have put pepper on the end. -The amount of time you've spent doing this,
you could have found a rehoming place that could take care of it.
Absolutely.
-Absolutely. -I am...
-There's no such thing. -Genuinely...
Genuinely, you're a bad person.
-I don't care. -I have never...
This is the first thing you've ever told me, and I'm like,
"Is he a bad person?"
I'm starting... It's not an evil crown.
-Yeah. -It's a...
You have an actual evil...
And you're smiling as you tell us a story.
-You're a soul-sucking pet. -You look crazy right now
with the knowledge that you've killed a living thing.
Not just killed it, you ripped its mother away from it
and then you threw it in the trash,
which is the most insulting way to kill it.
- I warned them several times.
- They don't speak Spanish.
- I didn't say they didn't speak Spanish.
- They speak English and you should too.
(laughing)
- My actions speak for me.
- You were a cold, this is why--
- I'm in disbelief.
By the way, child of divorce.
This is what that does to you.
- It is.
- If you are thinking about divorcing, look at this.
Look at this fucking evil.
You will end up with an evil Mexican fucking goblin.
- Edgar-ass son.
- Yeah.
- Stop calling me Edgar.
I don't have an Edgar Hecker.
It's a moat.
- I don't know who Edgar is.
- It's a racist epithet.
- A racist epithet?
Edgar?
- It is.
some West Coast shit that I'm not privy to? It's like a Southern thing.
It's some West Coast shit! It's kind of like a Southern thing.
Because every Mexican guy in the South looks the same. Yeah. And they're named Edgar?
Pretty much, yeah. Edgar is like a... I don't know if I can say that word. A white
type of guy for like a Mexican type of guy. You know what I'm saying? No. I don't know.
- A white guy who wants to be a black guy,
the Mexican version of that is an Edgar.
- Is an Edgar, oh, okay.
- I'm kind of oversimplifying it.
- Juvia's definitely an Edgar then.
- I don't think I know what,
I think we're thinking of two different things.
- No, I'm thinking of the same thing,
I'm just explaining it bad.
- So like my brother is an Edgar?
- If he was Mexican, yeah.
- My older brother, oh, okay.
- But you said it's about white guys
who are pretending they're Mexican.
- Yeah, you're doing the worst job of explaining this.
- Oh, it's Mexican guys who pretend to be white.
- I also don't think you know what this,
I used to think that you knew what this meant, Rex,
I don't think you know what it means anymore.
- I know what it means.
- No, you don't.
And I'm not looking it up right now
to make sure I'm right before saying it.
- No, you're stupid.
- If you looked that up on my Google,
you'd probably just get some Edgar Allen Poe shit
'cause it would be basically tailored
to my more poetic interests,
because I don't really sit around
doing racial stuff all day.
- Here is the urban dictionary definition of an Edgar.
- Okay.
- And you will see that I am right.
- A middle high school Latina boy
who typically wears Jordans, sags his pants,
has a bowl cut or mushroom cut,
and often says the N word.
- Oh, a mushroom cut.
- Yeah.
- Is that what they call that?
Yeah.
Why are they doing that?
That thing looks terrible, man.
Uh, it just, they, they love it.
They do love it.
Why?
I don't know.
There's something about that belt of like the Southern US and like all the way
Northern Mexico, that's just like that.
Everyone up there is like that.
Yeah.
So you have, there's Mexicans in Mexico who are doing that?
What I'm trying to say is I'm one of the good ones.
Wow.
Hard to disagree with that.
You're the only one I know.
And I'm saying that is a Mexican version of the white guy
who wants to be black.
There's a word for it.
- Oh, okay.
- I don't know if you can say it.
- You should say it.
- I really don't think I should.
- I think I don't know what you mean,
and you should say it right now.
- I should say it?
- Oh, fuck.
- Damn, yo, he got you.
You soundboarded his diss.
Yo.
- Oh.
(laughing)
He said, "Shay it," and you went, "Badoom."
- I really wish we had like a drumming, just build up.
But yeah, you should say it right now.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Yeah, I really would rather not.
- No, that's okay.
I didn't learn that you weren't allowed to say that
until probably six weeks ago,
so there's plenty of recorded times of me saying it.
- Wait, you can't say it?
It's illegal to say it?
- You can't say it anymore.
- You definitely can't say it.
- Yeah, you can't say it anymore.
Who says who?
The board.
I don't know. Who's in charge of that?
The committee.
Basically, basically 14 year olds are in charge of that.
So whatever.
That is kind of how the world works out.
If a 14 year old says that you're not allowed to say it,
you just can't say it anymore.
Because one day they're going to be your boss.
So just, it's better to just not touch it.
Yeah. It's for the best.
Yeah.
Okay. Well.
Do you have any topics, Rex?
Or any animal beefs?
Nope.
My life has been quite boring.
Yeah.
And way to go.
It's funny that for you, man.
To, in the last 10 minutes of the show, just bring up that you did animal cruelty.
I think that was smart.
That was smart.
That really kept the energy going.
And I'm not an Edgar.
Yeah.
So we're going to leave it at that.
Welcome guys.
Beers we drank another episode in the bag.
How exciting is that?
We'll catch you next week where hopefully.
I got points for my topic.
By the way, Jubio, I would like to say really quickly that torturing animals is early signs of psychopathy and serial killing tendencies.
I didn't torture it.
You put it in the trash.
You put peppers around it because you found out I hated it.
Then let me put you in the trash if that's not torturing.
You turned your balcony into Guantanamo Bay.
Yeah.
That's not how it works.
You made a torture chamber. You pepper sprayed them. I heard you say that.
No. I don't say pepper spray.
You sprayed pepper all around my balcony.
(laughing)
- And then you put them in the trash.
- It's a natural pigeon repellent.
- No.
- It repels them.
- Yeah, you propelled it into the trash can.
So I'm gonna stop recording right now
because you're such a piece of shit.
- Okay.
(dog barking)