[Sipping]
[Burp]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer broadcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[Burp]
This is a journey into sea,
into intergalactic,
planet,
And we're back.
We had to take a week off.
We took a week off.
Our excuse is that Caleb, he just left the country and we haven't been able to find him.
So instead of missing a second week, because he's still missing and we still don't know
where he is. We decided to bring on three of our closest friends.
Noah, who's been on before, Brian, who we have talked about before on here,
and Mike, who is a complete journalist.
So he turned his face off so no one can see him.
He's in danger. He is in danger.
Someone just cracked open a beer.
Usually how this goes is we crack open our beers at the top.
At the start. I'm sorry.
No, it seems to be halfway through his beer, but I guess you can just talk about your beer.
I guess it's talk about my beer.
Yeah, I got a penis modelo at the deli.
It's lukewarm because for the podcast, I completely yeah, I have a lukewarm penis modelo.
It still tastes pretty good.
I was swimming Pikmin and he just like joins is like, Yo, what's up?
I'm like, What the fuck are you?
I'll see you in an hour. I thought you were
You're waiting for everyone. I take the time. I was like, oh wait, it's completely 5 p.m. And I got it wrong
Brian what are you drinking?
Classy Colorado Kool-Aid. That's right
Yeah
Rex you got a completely green drink. I have a
have a
Ex-brewery Baja boy
So you're actually drinking?
I thought you weren't drinking. You have a very important business meeting.
I was going to drink a little bit.
So I was talking to Rex about recording today and he was like, "Yeah, that's fine. I'm just going to have to miss Premiere and also I can't drink because I need to do an important business thing."
I was like, "Okay, that's fine." And he was like, "But you can just record one modello. It'll be fine."
fun. He's like, no man, it's like a public thing. I can't show bust.
And first thing he does is sure enough, he cracks open another crazy,
insane beer.
Well, I know that if I didn't, you know, crack open the beer, you'd be like,
Oh, why don't you crack open the beer?
Three other people here so they can crack beers and drink them and talk about
them.
I'm going to drink this really fast and then I will drink the monster right
after as my second beer.
It might even look like a normal beer, but you're so big, it's actually a 40 ounce can.
It's a 20 ounce can.
No, that's 40 ounces.
I've seen no business meetings are the best time to be.
Not a business meeting.
It's like a presentation.
It's like a yeah, it's a presentation.
Even more of the reason that was my presentation cheat code.
Two shots, half a bar is annex.
Well, you're you're an insane person.
You're completely crazy.
Mike, are you drinking?
And he could.
I am.
Whoa.
Yeah.
So I have, I completely have COVID.
Um, and I'm never going to have an edit.
I had it before and I was surprised.
I like, didn't believe my girlfriend.
She, I did the nose swabs and she took it in the other room.
And like the second she put it into the sample machine, it was
just like you have COVID.
Like completely red. And I didn't believe her and she had to
take a photo and show me.
Not to sound offensive or anything. Do you feel like a
complete idiot for getting COVID so so so late?
Yeah.
I feel like I've been like I've been playing the you know, the
Google Browser T-Rex jumping game and I've kept it going for
four years somehow. Yeah, I feel great.
But you also not bad.
I feel bad right now.
However many years COVID has existed, I felt really good.
I thought they turned it off like four months ago.
But they just know what they turned it off with the switchback.
Yeah. Were you you got in Miami, right?
I must have. Yeah.
Either on the bus to New York or on the plane from New York to Miami.
I'm a worst case scenario doing
Barbenheimer in Miami.
I got it.
Barbenheimer will definitely give it
to you.
I feel like you get it pretty like
when I got it, it was like two days
after I
not even to like a day and a half
after I came in contact
with it. I got it.
What do you get it?
I got it like two years ago
on my birthday
from my girlfriend.
I was so on my own last night that I during COVID during the height of COVID, I was the
brave person that kept traveling and moving across countries during COVID.
And never once did I get any sick.
But one like New Year's party, my dad just went and he came back and he just was completely
sick. And he stayed like he quarantined himself in his room
for a single day. And then after that, he was just like hanging
out in the house. I was like, Oh, I guess I just go kill
myself. And I just completely had got COVID in my own home,
instead of all the airports that I've been in.
Yeah, you were flying a lot.
I was kind of pissed. I was I was flying. But my excuse was
that I got one of my shots in Chicago.
Yeah.
And it doesn't it doesn't matter that you're flying.
I flew a plane.
It doesn't matter.
It's going to be funny when Mike can't do his job.
Hello, especially all.
Let's go.
Got a long coding.
That's right. That's right.
Bottoms up.
I have the American version of Modelo, which is the court.
The court banquet, baby.
Now I'm going to get one COVID.
Yeah, I hope so.
I have immunocompromised, but I, yeah, I hope I don't get it.
Are you going to feel bad?
Are you immunocompromised?
What does that mean?
Uh, dude, if I knew, uh, I honestly,
You have an autoimmune disease, right?
Yeah.
Um, this is not a fun topic for beers we drink, but yeah, when I was a kid, my
parents like took me to a bunch of doctors and they were like, you're like too tall
at this age.
You're like way too big.
You have more fans and then they ruled that out.
This is so boring.
All of you guys are like looking at other stuff.
No, I mean, I'm cleaning my beard.
I'm not going to have a sticky beard.
I'm not going to lie.
I was about to ask if that's the reason why you were so tall,
because you your body just didn't know when to stop growing.
And I think that is I think that is no, it's not true.
I got this all by myself.
I put in the work I put in the hours.
There was a kid I went to school with who did have Marfan's and that's the point of what
your body is just like we're going to keep going for as long as we can until you die.
Yeah, can you get like Marfan syndrome of the penis?
Yeah, I have that.
Yeah, no, it would suck to be like, you know, 68 or whatever, like, and then no fucking dick
is like normal size.
What is normal size then?
Yeah, that would be...
Is it a five inch?
Yeah, like two, three inches.
Two, three?
Poor guy.
That's really bad.
Yeah, but it's like one or two.
Look like the little tiny button they put on like the bottom of a shirt.
Yeah, that's normal for serial killers, man.
That's not normal for anybody else.
There's got to be a basketball player who has that problem.
- Yes, it's your man. - A pro in the history
of all professional basketball,
one of them has had a very small penis.
- Ton of them have had small penises.
- It's been exceedingly many.
All right, you went next.
- I feel like that's why they have that whole world
of lawyers who just keep every single woman
that they sleep with completely hush hush,
so that info never gets out.
- Do you remember that post,
that was like an Instagram post about Drake
putting Frank's Red Hot in a condom?
Oh yeah, burning his cone.
That's crazy.
When I first read that, I didn't get the context.
I thought it was before he used it.
If you want to get fucking hot sauce in your dick, there's probably a better way.
He's getting in there with a hot cock.
Didn't she find out because she used it?
Yeah, she was trying to lock him up and get herself pregnant with Drake's
Drake's a sploosh, but he, I guess he just carries hot sauce somewhere in like in his
ass.
I don't know.
I don't know how he got hot sauce.
He keeps it in his purse.
What do you mean?
Does he have a purse?
Yes, he has a purse.
I'm going to Google Drake purse right now and if he doesn't have a purse, you owe me
$20.
Sure, Drake has a purse.
Drake should have every item in the world.
He should have like a brand.
Oh, yeah, like a Donald Trump style brand
He's buying Birkin bags for his future wife. Okay, he's got a
Forum there's at least like a guy who works for him who carries his purse
You'll never see a picture of Drake. Of course. He's a guy whose job title is like carrier
With Khalifa weed roller job
Carrier
He's just waiting that's how the room like a dog. Yeah, he's in the room
The entirety of Drake
20 guys standing around your bed new scenario. What do you mean?
Ten thousand dollars or watching Drake fuck
$10,000
I wouldn't watch anyone.
Well, hold on, hold on.
Can I film it?
Yes.
Okay.
Because then you can make more than $10,000.
To be totally honest, to take the kind of outsider's perspective on this, I might just
take the second option.
I might just watch because there are not that many people on earth who can say that they've
seen Drake fuck.
And $10,000 is like, in the grand scheme of things, not that much money.
It's like two months of a paid-
Rich guy, rich guy.
Come on, come on.
My house in the context of like
a paycheck, you get like two or three paychecks and that's $10,000.
Yeah. So you're you're a complete landlord, right?
And you yeah, you really understand.
You hate poor people.
Yeah. Most of the listeners of beers we drink, I think, live in favelas.
Yeah. $10,000.
What's that like one week of work?
Yeah. Yeah.
Couple hours working a construction job.
Yeah, it's a single day that I collect on all my rent.
I work in the...
I don't think I would want to tell people that I saw Drake Fuck.
What if he had a fucking...
I feel like there would be too many questions to answer.
Then you'd have to say like, "Oh, I turned down 10k."
You would want to talk.
So I can fucking bang somebody.
You would want to tell people though.
That's the whole thing.
You get to...
I would not.
I really wouldn't.
Why would you see Drake Fuck?
I kind of understand this because $10,000 is not enough money to materially change your life if you're not like...
Me?
You know, broke.
That's a much safer way of phrasing it.
Um, because like, I've been trying to sell my car, and it's like the shittiest car in the world, and it's like $11,000.
And I'm like, okay, so $10,000 is like literally nothing now.
I've never had an $11,000 car in my life for sure.
Only the cheapest cars.
I paid $6,000 for it.
Straight beaters, right?
Oh, shit.
God damn. I do think that you you you asking $11,000 for that car is a complete scam
I think that car should go for like 200 bucks
11k I
Looked it up online. That's what you what you haven't talked about your car. I love I love this about Rex
His car is so insane. It has nothing in it. It barely has wheels
It doesn't have a cruise control. You know, I think it has a radio and that's it
It has air conditioning it does it is it bad does it suck?
It's a shitty. Yeah, is it a midsuit? It's a Kia Kia
Kia-ria drive a Kia so I'm gonna oh, it's a fucking
Car yeah, it's literally the shitty whose cars are
$15,000 brand-new. I know why is it? Why are you selling it for $11,000? I'm not that's what it's like the KBB is
So I was like so like a good job sell it for five grand and ball out. I don't know do a Vegas trip or something crazy
But I have to move any instance
Do you think if you drove it to New York from LA that it would it would even make it I
Think it would I was thinking about driving it back to Arizona and even that I was like I need to
think definitely like blows up and just
melts
So there's a point in between Arizona and California where you're like going up a mountain and it's like a hundred and twenty degrees and it's
Where everyone's car brings you?
Yeah, I drove a fucking
Honda Odyssey like the mom minivan through that and about like ten minutes in our AC went out. Yeah
Yeah, you got it. Turn your AC off and it's 120 degrees and I was thinking about it was like, you know
I'm just not gonna do that. I was just gonna sell it
When I drove to LA, I thankfully, like you just go down it if you're going into California,
right, from Arizona. Which is perfect, it's so perfect. Because that car actually like
exploded like six months later, the engine did, on the highway. I do not think I would
have made it. That car had no AC, the windows didn't roll down, the radio didn't work, I
I don't know that car was a piece of shit.
It was constantly leaking oil.
Yeah.
What brand?
It was a Ford Focus piece of shit.
Complete piece of shit.
Like horrible, horrible.
I had a, I had a car I paid two grand for and uh, it fucking the engine block
cracked, so I would just carry around in like the back seat, like 10 quarts of oil,
just like any one quart of oil.
And anytime I had to drive, I would just put in a quart of oil and it would be gone the next time I had to drive.
Mm-hmm.
So I would just fucking leak oil like 30 miles.
You were playing the long drive in real life.
Yeah.
You have like the little jalopy that you're like putting together with your hands.
I just had like a fucking funnel and oil in my backseat.
I just did not give a fuck.
Can you tell a story about the pig that your dad put in the truck of your car?
What?
You told me this story about someone like just leaving like meat in the back of your car.
Oh, I don't know what you're talking about.
But I did leave a giant gummy bear in the back of my car, my first car.
And it got all melted.
Yeah, like one of those like five pound gummy bears.
And I fucking left it in the trunk of the car in the middle of the summer when I was at work.
And it fucking melted and turned into just got puddle of like hardened gum worm and like laminated the inside of the truck.
Was it in a wrapper or was it you just had it?
So it was in a wrapper, but I opened it.
So it was in the box in the wrapper and then I like put it in the trunk of my car.
Because I used to like, I worked at Krispy Kreme at the time and I worked the drive-thru
window and I used to fuck with people a lot because like you couldn't get fired there.
So I would just have it sitting on the counter near the window and just like go over and
like gnaw on it like a dog.
And they were like, you have to stop doing this.
So I was like, okay, okay.
But it was in the middle of the summer so I put it in the trunk of my car.
It was 115 degrees out.
And I was like, well, it's fine.
It's in the trunk.
It's like dark in there.
It's not going to get fired.
I can get out and then I got out.
No, I opened it up.
It was just a puddle of like like this big, you know,
of gummy bear just leaking out of the box and everything.
And it's like, no, no, no.
And I like went inside and got like a scraper, like a dough scraper.
And I started just like doing that really fast and like pouring soap on it.
And it just made it worse.
And I was like,
my hands are cold.
The car when you sold the car was it still there? Oh, yeah
He didn't get it you didn't think to go get a
Good question, how far do you get in into the the gummy bear by knowing it and the
Krispy Kreme I think
Yeah, like we started the ear yeah, you start to hear that's a very impactful like not to do right
No hands no hands
on it just yeah just mouth just like this other half hanging out doing doing the
lady in the tramp just fucking just I think it's really kind of them to let
you get 20% into the bear before they're like okay you have to stop yeah they
let me do anything at that job I and then I would just I remember like the
last thing I did was I sent like a bunch of money and an apology for stealing and
but then like because these managers were trying to get me fired but I wanted to
quit so I just wrote a letter saying that they told me to steal this money
and they devised a scheme and I returned it and said I felt bad and then I quit
and they all got fired. Damn, that is crazy. That's incredible. You're an actual supervillain, you're insane.
No, I'm a regular villain.
Yeah, true.
See, I had the same thing happen to me, but I actually did steal the money and then didn't pay back.
I didn't actually return as much as I saw.
I returned like 200 bucks and I took like...
Oh, you actually did?
Oh, okay.
I thought you just made it up and then gave them money to get them fired.
No, no, I did that.
I came up with the scheme.
They were all too stupid.
Oh, nice.
I was 17 and they were like, you know, mid-20s, 30s.
No, I got got fired for my first job at a grocery store because I found out they had a store coupon button, which just meant that you could hit that button and then type in an amount and it would take that off of the bill.
Yeah.
So I started fucking just abusing the hell out of that. Okay, now this guy gets $20 off. Like, Oh, this guy looks sure he gets $30 off like whatever.
Random people.
Yeah, literally anybody like how I got fucking caught was this bitch ass fat mom on wick who was like a
Super couponer came in and fucking gave her $20 off. She's using fucking wick
That's like a women and children like food stamp shit. Yeah, and
then
Like I noticed her like because she's so hyper focused on how much all this shit cost
Checks the receipt afterwards and then takes it right to fucking customer service like goes and tells people that like I
Gave her $20 off
Do you give her less?
She knew I I act like I've seen you did a nice shit. I did a fucking nice
Dollars off and then she boom went and read it on me
Fuck what I would do is I remember
Like they didn't have like a key card system
There's really no authentication for like a manager code except for a password
So I would just watch them enter their code one time memorize it and then use that
So anytime someone paid with cash
I would just void their ticket and put on the cheapest item and then take the cash
Whenever someone came through after we close the register
I would just be like yeah, just give me like five bucks or give me ten bucks and just like still sell them shit
it. So, and then I would split, you know, tip out everyone at the end of the
show. And I did that for like four or five months.
Made fucking 50 bucks a day.
Basically.
I think you were, you were a complete Robin Hood figure for this Krispy
Cream.
They paid fucking $8. So it's like, fuck you.
If you know, if you're working a job that pays less than like $13 an hour,
if you're not stealing, you're, you're fucking up. Like you should be actively
stealing from any like retail job, anything.
You should just steal everywhere you go.
You should just try to steal as much as you can.
And then I fucking would get yelled at by people around me because they'd be like,
can you just stop stealing everything?
That's the best part about being a bartender is you're just expected to steal.
Like you just,
it's actually an industry standard that you steal the alcohol and you drink it and
you give it to people for free.
Well,
You get into almost every...
But I mean like, you go to Walgreens and you fucking, you're checking out, you just reach
down real quick and put a candy bar in your pocket, you know, like...
Yeah.
Fucking just any, any little thing you should just be stealing.
Yeah, anything.
Anything you can fit in your pocket.
Yeah, that's what, that's what self-checkout is there for.
So you always like just forget...
They don't fuck with self-checkout anymore.
People abused it too much.
So I...
Who is they?
I actually...
Like Walmart and shit?
Oh, okay.
'Cause self-checkout still exists.
Yeah.
in like like the big places they don't fuck around with that shit anymore.
They actually got I got arrested in L.A. for my girlfriend made me steal like
twenty dollars worth of mochi ice cream balls.
And I went to L.A.
County Jail for it.
But is that like a gay as crime?
It's like so it's so stupid.
I actually think the cops were right in that situation.
Yeah.
Maybe they arrest you for stealing, but they arrest you for how gay the crime was.
My girlfriend wanted mochi ice cream balls.
It wasn't like we hadn't already been stealing from the store, like stealing a ton of shit
from them already.
But that particular day, it was mochi ice cream balls out of like a little...
It was like a cooler.
How did they get you?
What do you mean?
Just like three guards are standing by the front of the door, like waiting for you to
leave.
They got three guards in a fucking...
It was huge.
It was huge. It wasn't a Walgreens.
No, this was like a big grocery
store. Yes.
And you didn't put on like
you didn't put on the big eyes and go
like, oh, I must have forgot to scan
these.
You didn't try to wiggle out of it
somehow.
He had like a definitely did.
But this big of their shut down
his pants.
They were like, we've seen you steal
here before.
That was the thing.
We've been stealing from them.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
And you know, it was nothing though.
I just spent like a night in jail and because I'm white,
I didn't have to do anything. I didn't, nothing else happened.
Yep. I'm white. I'm really, really, really white.
Get over the fact that you're not Chinese.
Have y'all seen those ID picture? No. Can we see it?
It's I saw it the other day. I don't understand how it's one,
the same person as Noah and two that he's not Chinese.
I think you always look crazy like in IDs and like driving license pictures.
I look pretty much the same as I do right now.
You can look crazy, but you normally don't look Chinese.
I'm really excited for this now. Mike, have you, have you stole anything before?
Uh, I used to, when I was a kid,
I would steal cheese sandwiches from the cafeteria. Um,
that's cool. It's not, it's not,
I would go in after everyone had gotten lunch and the like,
this was in middle school or something like that.
And there are lines where you go and get stuff and there would just be like Kaiser
rolls with four slices of American cheese on them.
And I would take those and I would like pocket them and I would eat them on the
bus going home.
Two pieces of red with a bunch of cheese in it.
Yeah. Honestly, it should have been free.
Yeah. I think those are supposed to go into the trash.
I don't think we're supposed to eat those.
Those are just scraps. I thought they were great.
Those sound like the free lunch that they give you whenever you don't have enough money in your account.
I don't think it was that kind of school district where they had a free lunch.
The last thing I stole was 50 monsters.
50 monsters?
Yeah, like 2 of the 24 packs.
Just had them in the bottom of the cart.
So 48 monsters actually.
Bottom of the cart? I've stolen thousands of dollars worth of stuff from bottom of the cart.
- Bottom of the cart is a fucking, that's a cheat code.
- You just scan everything top of the cart,
you have all the nice shit on the bottom of the cart,
and then you just go out.
- I didn't even do it on purpose.
I was just, you know, I walked to the car,
I started putting things around,
I was like, oh, I definitely did not pay for this.
- You never do it on purpose.
- Oh, that was an accident, I'm sorry.
- I legitimately, no, I'm being, I'm serious.
This one was actually an accident.
It was so practiced that I didn't feel.
- I've never done anything that frigging,
Like I've done stuff like that where I buy like a couple of stuff and I just like don't pay for like a like a jar of like jelly or some shit.
I'm like, oh man, whatever.
I guess I just told this, but 48 monsters is insane.
Yeah, that's Rex drinks that in a week, so it's that's nothing to him.
It is true.
I drink.
I go through a 15 pack in like a week and a half.
That's good.
All right, let's see.
Let's see.
Yeah.
I have to tell
I don't live like anywhere. That's your legal name in your ID. Okay
Tell me he doesn't look like fucking yeah me in a prime, dude
That's me
18 years old. Oh, man
Yeah, I honestly do see it. Yeah, that's fucking me
I guess it's a wrecked Rex's uber profile picture. I didn't even know you drove uber or is this just like yeah
Oh for writing. No, I have yeah
Yeah
What do you mean it's gone now, you know have pictures of you a short hair outside of your profile picture though no
That's it can't be true
Can be possible. What about when you're a little kid? No, but no family pictures. No, I didn't take pictures
There's just like gaps of like years where there's like no picture you've let you sort of this is the excerpt not him
Really not Rex
That was me when I was a freshman in college. It's in my dorm room
Like you got to run it back you need to get you need to have short hair again no
I'm actually about to cut my hair
Well, I'm the other guy with long hair here like we can connect oh, yeah, we can
Yeah, we can bond over this
I
Knew I was eventually going to cut it
Like even when I started growing it out. I just don't like dealing with it. I
Most of the time I want to put it up
I'm not I wouldn't say I'm bored of it like
Just what I'm working it can really be in the way and when I'm eating it's in the way when I'm walking on the street
It's in the way so you know what the answer is
Figured out you just give yourself. Thanks
I will shave my head bald before I give myself bangs.
Just listen, when you're cutting your hair, you're gonna cut your hair, give yourself bangs, do it like the Hitler mustache when you're shorter, you know?
Like really really short, like turf bangs?
No no no, just do it like right to here, but you know, just to see what it would be like, and then you know, you can finish it off.
Oh, I understand, I understand.
Yeah, like before shaving, you know, you give yourself a Hitler mustache.
I was gonna I was gonna go to like a Puerto Rican barbershop and get it done
So now I'll cut my bangs at my house and then I'll go to the Puerto Rican bar
We're the bangs a guy with bangs. I'd be like, can you cut my hair?
They're gonna get out of me for being you do that. Can I pay you to get like the like Korean like Bob cut?
With like the
Classic like you know Korean kpop fucking
my first ball cut
Cut before you should rock that for like a day for like a week even a bowl cut. Yeah, I mean I have to work I
Have to like interact with people at work not dude. It's all being avant-garde
Okay, I'll get a little dangly earring yeah
We can go together. We can hold hands and get dangly earrings dangly earrings and bowl cuts
You're also about to become neighbors.
Yeah.
I'll wear a mesh shirt.
I'll wear a mesh shirt to work and
bartend in a mesh shirt with my
nipples protruding.
The place you work is like pretty
nice, right? It's like, yeah, you
know, they wouldn't let me wear that.
The owner constantly like talk shit
on what I'm wearing.
Do I wear this hat like every day?
And he's like, I don't know, he's
just he thinks I'm a hick or
something like that for sure.
Well that is a hick ass thing to do.
Yeah it is a hick.
But like it's not like Realtree isn't something you can wear.
Like it's a cool thing to wear kind of.
I'm wearing it because I'm a hick.
But he needs to understand that you can wear it not as a hick.
And you know if I had never told him I was from North Carolina he wouldn't know.
Yeah he'd probably, you have a California vibe.
Yeah.
Except for the fact I say y'all all the time.
That's really all.
California vibe. Yeah, I guess he is. Actually, you know, you could be more of like an Austin, Texas annoying guy.
No, no way. I get more of like a Guangzhou province. That's right.
Two-tier city in China. Yeah, Shenzhen. I'm from Shenzhen.
This is actually perfect because I've been wanting to have Noah on for a couple of weeks.
Because I want him to tell the weird stories that he gets when he goes.
From people at work. Yeah, yeah, he gets so many insane outside his job that I wanted to keep it in recording
I'll start it with a deaf guy. I feel like that's a good place to start that one's like pretty short-winded
But there's this guy who terrorizes the neighborhood that I work in
Which is just all of Greenpoint. He terrorizes it all his father is like the
Lone shark for the neighborhood. So he has like this insane level of protection where like if you
Like if he gets fucked up like his father's gonna like get everyone else to fuck you up
So all you can really do is call the cops on him and get him arrested
Which even then like he's been arrested like 50 times. It's like ridiculous. He's always in and out but and he's down and he's deaf
he's deaf, but
he
Just goes around and like just knocks people out like constantly
He just knocks people out on the street all the time. I'll go game. Are you work?
He I did not get knocked out games. All right, I'm getting there
I'm getting that the guy that not gonna came that girl or Caleb song
No, that was in the middle of Manhattan, so this guy's only ever in Greenpoint he never leaves
Yeah, he never ever leaves like I'm being serious he never leaves I see him every day
Like the lady next door to us is like she owns a laundromat and
She's known him since he was like a little kid
So like if we ever have like really bad problems with him
She we can like grab her and she can talk to him because she knows ASL and she'll talk to him
but one day he like came into the
restaurant during brunch and
I was like helping a table up by the front of the door and I like knew who he was
but I just found out who he was like two days prior is probably like four months ago and
He's like trying to like tell me something without signing though.
And but he's really just also like yelling.
He's like, "Ugh, ugh, ugh, ugh!" at me.
And also he's like kind of jacked, tatted, shirt off,
always drunk, always really like strung out.
And I was like, "Nah man, you have to like go. You have to go. You have to leave."
And I'm like trying, I like come out from behind and I'm like moving him out.
I'm like, "You have to leave."
And as I'm like walking towards him, he just pulls his pants down and wags his cock at me and then runs out of the restaurant.
What the fuck? I think he might like you, too. I think he likes you.
Yeah, I think he might like me.
Was it normal size or was it...
And I didn't really get a good look at it. I was looking at his face.
I really... and it happened so quickly, you know, I was just astonished that he wagged his cock at me in the first place.
But it's definitely like the not the worst thing that's happened to someone should wink at him got like a knife
He like pulled a knife on him and like tried to stab him Jesus. Yeah
and then the next
Time like something really weird happened. I had this huge monster of a guy. He was like 6 10 probably and he had like tons of
bags of
Takeout like you could tell that it was just from other restaurants
He had like four or five bags of takeout all with like receipts and different bags. So he's been to different places
and he just immediately sits down at like the dirtiest table in the restaurant.
Like people had just left. It was a bunch of people.
They had a lot to eat and drink and I go over and I'm like, Hey,
let me clean this up for you. I clean it up for him.
He immediately hands me a $20 bill and starts ordering like wine and all this
other stuff. Like he orders like a wine and an oyster. So I clean it up.
I go wait on like whatever actual normal tables I have cause I can tell this
guys a freak and then bring him his wine and I got the oysters coming.
I bring the oysters out and he's like, talk, he wants to like talk to me,
wants to have a conversation. But he's saying the weirdest shit. He's like,
I live in a cube.
Like that's the first thing he says to me. He's like, I live in a cube.
Yeah, I live in a cube and um, like I can't really even remember what else.
He was like, I've got a beautiful girl for you. Do you like Polish women?
I was like I can set you up with her like and then I tell him I have a girlfriend and all this stuff like
specifically Polish women
Only Polish women like actually dude you hit it
Final a sampler of fine wares. Yeah
Fucking has a specific taste like that. Yeah, like it's specifically Polish women
Yeah, I actually get mistaken for Polish as well because it's a Polish neighborhood like all the time. Yeah
Yeah, all the time people are like do you speak Polish and I do not speak Polish
They constantly they're seeing you trying to screw in a light bulb
So I
I like finish up this conversation with this guy,
especially after he's like,
let me get you this Polish woman.
And then he orders like a chocolate mousse
and he hasn't touched his oysters.
It's been like 30 minutes and he hasn't eaten a single one.
And I like, I'm trying to figure out a way
to get him out of there.
He's been there for like an hour and somehow,
I can't remember what, but he was like,
can I get this all to go?
Like, can I get my oysters that have been sitting here
like 45 minutes to go. Can I get the chocolate mousse that's coming to go?
And I'll pay you. I was like, okay. So I box up his oysters
and I, we like box up his chocolate mousse and,
um, then I bring him the check and he pulls out like one of the fattest wads
I've seen anyone pull out in the restaurant. Also,
he's dressed completely normally. He's like white t-shirt covered in stains.
like cargo shorts and flip flops.
Normal in the sense of like what a normal person wears.
Yeah, like he's not homeless is what I'm saying.
I don't know why it was under the impression.
I think, I don't know if it was because you said it's,
you told the story already to me,
but I thought that this guy showed up in a suit.
No, no, he did not have a suit on.
And that's also what I'm trying to say,
like why he has so much money as well as why that suit.
I thought he was the deaf guy from the last story.
No, that guy's tiny actually.
That guy's like 5'7".
A box of his oysters and then again, whip his cock out.
Yeah.
Okay, thank you sir.
But this guy, he pulls all this money out and he keeps counting.
He counts out like $200 or $300 and he's like, "No, that's not right."
It's like $40.
And he's like, "No, that's not right.
That's not right.
Do you guys...
I don't think I have enough.
I really don't think I have enough."
He keeps saying that to me.
"I don't think I have enough.
That's not enough."
And he's counted out like $400.
out like $400 like that's not enough money.
And then he looks at me like do you guys take EBT?
No we don't take EBT.
It's like OK that's fine then.
And then he gives me $200 and then walks out with once again another new takeout bag.
He now has another one added to his collection.
I presume to go to the next restaurant down the street and do the same shit which is like the craziest thing about that story to me is he probably did that exact same thing to four
restaurants previous to like four different guys in the neighborhood.
So he just doesn't know how to count?
He might not know how to count.
It's not like a not like a funny way, but like like he's
he actually doesn't know how to count at all. Yeah. Yeah.
What do you think he does for a living, though, if he can't count
and has carries around $5,000 in cash?
I think he tries to fuck bartenders.
I think he maybe maybe he's a pimp.
Yeah, I think I think he might be a pimp.
I think you're going to be showing up in a in one of those like prank
shows and in a little bit, you got to be praying for a TV show.
This bartender was the nicest guy I've ever interacted with.
Yeah, because I just talked to him like 30 minutes like, No, man, you're cool.
You're cool.
In the new piece, it's all like, no, I see village Polish girls.
Yeah, that's where some of them would sit.
They're like, "No, I don't!"
"No, I don't like Polish girls, man."
Yeah.
Yeah, and then just like a bunch of
stinky people. I had a really stinky girl
come in the other day and get milk.
And she just got a glass of milk.
I hate stinky people.
Yeah, she was like,
dressed very nicely.
Like, $3,000 bag,
all designer, but she was
the stinkiest woman I've ever had in the restaurant.
on
New York is the stinkiest place on earth.
Yeah, but you get used to it really, really quickly.
Like, you don't think it's the stinkiest place on earth?
No.
Well, what about in America?
And America?
I think it's also probably not.
I think it's top five stinkiest places.
Well, Texas, where they do like paper manufacturing and shit like that.
And that's their cash.
These are fucking dollars.
You live in fucking Dallas.
He wasn't.
I did not live in Dallas.
I've been to Dallas tons of times.
My mother's family's from Dallas.
I spent tons of time in Dallas.
Six months in Dallas just straight six months of six months in Dallas when I would do that a long story really where in Dallas
I
Spent like probably two months in Arlington and that's a shit hole. Yeah
And then the other rest of the other four months were in Fort Worth
Yeah
I was going all over the place in Dallas
There's nice parts of Dallas but Dallas as a whole is a shithole. Yeah
The walking that that's like what for this yeah, I did get the skateboard a lot which was sick
I was really heavy in the skateboarding. Yeah
Downtown Fort Worth is nicer
Now I'll rep for work I like San Antonio's my favorite place in Texas
The river
Houston is tied with San Antonio
Austin sucks awesome sucks
awesome awesome
Dope if you're gay and you cuff your pants
I don't cover my pants.
What do you mean?
Which is what you do.
I don't cover my pants.
The fuck are you talking about?
Let's look at him.
Notice those pant legs right now.
Pull those pants up.
Alright.
Oh, you're wearing Pyrex shorts, bro.
Yeah, I'm wearing Pyrex shorts.
You cannot call anything gay.
You cannot call anything gay while wearing Pyrex shorts.
I'm wearing fake Pyrex shorts from China, thank you.
Which is stinkier than New York.
Oh, your brain goes over to the home line?
Shouts out.
Boom.
Where's stinkier than New York?
the
That also doesn't sound that bad.
Where smells the best?
I think we're asking the wrong questioner.
Antarctica.
Fresh wind.
You think it's...
I think...
You can only really go bad, so you need the most neutral place, which is either of the
poles.
I think Washington.
Yeah, I was gonna say Washington.
It probably smells like fresh rain.
D.C.?
No, no.
No, like the Pacific Northwest.
Like, DC probably smells like fucking shit.
No, it smells mostly.
Yeah.
Like Snohomish County, Washington.
Like wherever all these people live probably smells decent.
And I think some gorgeous woods.
Mm-hmm.
Gorgeous woods.
The Amazon.
The beautiful forest.
It's pretty good.
Yeah.
I think the most beautiful flower garden.
What about a city?
A big city.
Maybe like Dubai?
Dubai probably smells of it.
No, Dubai.
You know, I really doesn't smell like anything.
It smells like hot dust.
They got no pipes in Dubai.
They have to carry the shit out of the city with trucks.
You know that?
I didn't know that.
They carry the shit out of the city?
Yeah.
They wipe their ass with their hands.
They have no sewers and no, no pipes.
What's it, what's a nice smelling city then?
Japan.
I don't know.
Japan?
Japan.
No.
Japan the city.
Because of all the flowers, the cherry blossoms.
Wait, Rex, why do you fuck with Austin so much?
Why do you live in Austin so much?
Oh, I just had a cousin who lived there for a couple years.
When it was like the big hipster city.
Yeah, it's not that anymore though.
That's not what it is.
That doesn't mean there's not nice things to do in Austin though.
There's nothing to do in Austin.
Yeah, there's... you can...
I mean, literally, except for New York City,
NLA,
San Francisco,
Chicago.
No, fuck Chicago.
No, I literally like anything besides New York City and L.A.
is like, I've heard Philly, Chicago are pretty nice.
And then Detroit, Pittsburgh.
I like to talk about Austin's a tier two city.
Yeah.
We need tears like the Chinese do.
You need to fucking get them fucking actually right.
We need.
They got tears.
Yeah.
Do the Chinese actually have tears?
Like, yeah, it's like their credit is official, official system.
Like they've got tier one cities, tier two cities, two, three cities and shit.
I don't know how fucking far it goes, but the Chinese love to rank things.
That is like in their blood.
They love rankings.
They look to list Starcraft came out.
They were like, Oh shit, we can fucking rank.
They love ranking things.
Like you go back thousands of years and they're like top five
beautiful women in this city.
That's the type of shit they've been on for years.
I think I could make it big.
That is the craziest stereotype.
I feel like that's a thing a dad would say.
I don't know, my dad was once talking to me about a friend of mine and he was like, "Oh,
the Bulgarians, they're loyal."
I was like, "Oh yeah, I guess."
They're loyal?
The Chinese like to rank things?
That's crazy, man.
Chinese like to rank things? That's crazy man.
No dude, it's fucking true dude.
I think I could make it big in a tier 2 Chinese city.
No you couldn't dude.
You don't think I could make it in a tier 2?
You do not have the qualities that would make it.
What do you think you would bring? What are the traits you would bring?
You would be in prison after spending 5 days in a gaming cafe.
No, no, they let you die in there. They let you completely just be there for a day.
Not if you fucking suck at League, which you do.
That's not true.
You think you could make it like playing League? That's what you mean? Or just in general?
No, just make it in life, in general.
No, dude, you'd fucking log on to a Chinese server in literally any video game and you'd get demolished.
Yeah, definitely.
You'd feel so small. You'd feel like an ant.
I think I would not like gaming if I was in China.
In person, to be like what, 6'3"?
That's a crazy thing. I would need to pick up a new hobby.
You would be the tallest guy in all of China if you moved there.
But you would have to learn Chinese.
Yeah. That's the hardest part.
No.
No?
I would say he speaks a lot of Spanish.
I think I can get by just fine.
I think I got enough charisma in me that I can make it.
I think they will love me.
Do you think you would fit in eating all the food that is in China?
Like all the weird...
Like eating a monitor lizard and stuff like that?
Do you think you could do that?
Do you think you could fit through the door eating all the Chinese food?
Honestly, do you think he could handle the spice of Chinese food?
Of real Chinese food?
Maybe not actually.
I do remember seeing this one TikTok of a guy just like,
having, just killing a crocodile,
just like, just like skinning it and like cooking it.
And I was like, "That's just too much."
- No, that's a monitor lizard.
- That's nothing, dude.
I saw them fucking crack open like a fucking anthropod.
It looked like a giant roly-poly bug, dude.
They cracked that bitch open
and fucking ate the legs out of it, man.
This is insane.
It doesn't look like a natural creature.
Can't eat that.
It's gotta have like fur or wings or something.
I think a lot of fish are too weird to look at.
Yeah, tons of fish are gross.
They like to eat tons of like weird looking fish and I don't know.
Like the blob fish?
In Korea they like eating weird fish as well.
I think South Korea is fucked.
There's like a long history of Chinese famines and that's why they'll fucking eat anything.
they fucking don't have the hang ups like Chrissy and Americans eat the ground.
Eww, no, that's not food.
They'll fucking eat the ground.
Yeah, I'm 25 years old
and I only still eat chicken nuggets and cheese pizza.
I'm 25.
Yeah. Yeah.
Americans are like, oh, I have autism from GMOs.
Can I have chicken nuggets?
Yeah.
Like, let me eat.
Let me eat the first thing I see that's crawling.
Yeah, Chinese people are like, Oh, I'm gonna I'm hungry.
Let me eat some delicious.
OK, so this is solely Rex's opinion, and we're going to come after him.
You are you have complete free reign.
You can kill him if you want.
Yeah, Rex is in big trouble.
You just have to live stream it.
If you we won't press charges if you kill Rex and you live stream.
I'm saying this truly out of respect.
No, I 100 percent.
I do respect that.
- Fucking eat dirt.
- Out of...
(laughing)
I think out of all of us,
I think Rex is the one that could make it
in the tier one Chinese city.
Any tier actually.
- I don't think that's true.
- I think he would.
I think he's learned enough about the culture
that he would completely fit in.
- It's called Chow Chi.
- They'd be like, "Wow, look at that guy, he's eating mud."
(laughing)
- Chow Chi province, and it's dough pieces covered in soil.
- That sounds good.
- The soil's pretty good.
Sounds good season it it's pretty good. Yeah, I've never heard of rock salt
Okay, all right, you're right we do eat rocks
Yeah
candy
Indecent thoughts
You'll be a thought leader actually in China. Yeah, you think he could rise to the top of the CCP. Yeah
There is a long history of like China file Jewish leaders in the CCP.
It's like one of the first non-Chinese people in like Mao's like cadre.
I would watch a two hour long like CCTV or not CCTV but um what's the news channel?
Just like a news channel.
CNN.
No not CNN.
BBC.
Um, no, not BBC.
It's like a live, it's just like live streams of shit happening.
Oh, you're talking about like the people's, Oh, Oh, C-SPAN.
C-SPAN.
Yeah.
Just like Chinese C-SPAN of Rex giving a two hour long, like meeting just in,
in very, why would you want to watch that?
Passion Chinese?
That would be awesome.
I would love to wear that in a suit in front of like hundreds of people.
I would watch that for two, three hours.
If I don't even understand what you're saying.
If I could take a really painful injection that taught me Chinese, I would move there immediately.
One hundred percent.
If I had to be tortured for a year to learn perfect Chinese.
Yeah, you could just do that in a year.
You could lock me up and starve me and shock my nipples with electricity.
And then at the end I can learn Chinese.
It takes so long to learn like good Chinese.
Oh, you mean like as if you grew up?
Yeah, that's what I mean.
If I could go through like hellish pain for like six straight months.
Six to eight, now you're moving goalposts.
Yeah, you're completely stupid.
If I could just fucking get hurt for one second to learn Chinese.
I would take the most pain I've ever experienced in my life for a full day to speak fluent Chinese.
That's it.
Yeah.
Like if I was like completely immobilized, laying in bed, couldn't move, couldn't think,
couldn't drink, couldn't eat.
Yeah, like just shitting on myself and pissing myself.
Yeah, just fucking miserable.
Vomiting.
But at the end of it I get to speak perfect Chinese.
No, but you would think, you would think I already know Chinese.
You would think.
Lightening round, lightening round.
What's the worst pain you've ever experienced?
Dude, that's a difficult...
I
Don't know my little brother kicked me in the balls really hard one time. I
Can't remember why I think I kill him too many times on Halo. I think I
Sprained something in my leg once and it's really painful. I never broken anything
Yeah, I've never broken anything either I could put a factory new I
Broke a pinky toe, but I was like too drunk to really feel the pain. I just like slammed it into a wall
The next morning it hurt like kind of bad, but it definitely wasn't the worst
Was the worst thing? I don't know. I'm trying to think I got ghost pepper in my eye one time like ghost pepper
When I say something else
Probably
Yeah, the pain of capitalism crushing my spirit
Michael, you have to know something.
One second, UPS guy at the...
You have to know something.
Yeah, I know some things about pain.
No, I think it's either when my lung collapsed or...
I have this thing where sometimes when I'm flying,
and I'm in a plane and the plane is descending,
they depressurize the cabin poorly,
and I, from like an earlier filling in my tooth,
my tooth have like a little pocket,
a microscopic pocket of air in my tooth.
And for some reason, the way like the pressure, the deep,
the pressure change interacts with that,
it like makes it feel like my head is about to explode.
Damn.
Fucking awful.
It's not very good.
So you just like,
I was mostly asking the question as a joke because Noah was like for a day of the
worst pain I would love to know Chinese.
Yeah, but whenever we bring it around to you, you're like, yeah, my life
completely sucks. I was born with no legs and no arms and no eyes.
And pretty much I just suffered my entire my entire life.
But I'm completely rich now, so it doesn't fucking matter.
Yeah, I didn't even catch whatever.
I'm going to assume I'm going to assume Mikhail said, like, I shut the door on my
thumb one time. I got killed.
He got killed.
So do you like avoid as much as you can?
in half by a samurai.
That's not true.
I guess like I don't remember the worst pain I've ever actually
felt because like I chopped my thumb off when I was a little
kid.
What I had to like surgically reattach it.
Were you on the ghost ship from the movie ghost ship?
Yeah, do you have a scar?
No.
Yeah, I do.
So
you really can't see because it happened when I was 18 months
old, but like you can definitely do it.
Yeah, like right here.
- You were 18 months old?
So your mom chopped your thumb off.
- What?
- How did you chop it off at 18 months old?
- I put it in a...
- Blender, blender.
- What was it?
I can't really remember.
- In a machine.
- I mean, of course I don't remember.
I was fucking 18 months old.
So it was like a knotted pipe strainer or something
or like pipe cleaner.
And I like stuck my thumb in it and it like sliced my,
I like pulled it.
I pulled my thumb.
- Oh, like razor wire.
Yeah, yeah.
Do you think you could be an assassin?
Yeah, definitely.
Like in a different life?
In a different life.
Yeah.
I really wanted to join the special forces really bad.
I mean, that was never going to happen, but you know, I definitely could have like been
an infantry guy and then gone and just killed people for money.
I think Noah could.
I don't think Brian is stealthy enough.
Souldy enough?
Stealthy.
I don't think he's stealth.
I'm probably the most stealthiest guy that you've ever met.
- You got caught doing your crime recently.
- No, I didn't.
- Yeah, you did.
- I've never gotten caught doing any crime
other than the one I said earlier.
- You totally, you told me,
I'm gonna tell the story, I'm gonna put you on blast.
Brian completely stole so much shit from his old job.
- I didn't get caught.
- And he got caught by a coworker.
- No.
- That's not being caught,
they knew he was gonna do it and they set his ass up.
- No, I did not get.
Okay, first of all, I've never stolen anything from any job that I've ever worked in heaven.
Second of all, I did not get caught doing anything that is completely untrue.
Okay, so you just alerted the sentries that were waiting there for you and you decided that it wasn't...
I completely avoided alerting all of the sentries.
You alerted the guards and they came to your position.
It's just, it's not true. I walked on tippy toes.
I'm the most stealthy, silent individual in the world.
How did he get caught if I'm sitting in his Herman Miller right here?
You're up.
Hey, let's flex on him real quick. No, let's flex on him real quick.
But this is so stupid.
What are you sitting on?
I asked Brian very nicely, can I have one?
Can I pay you for shipping and have one? He's like, nah, I got two.
And I can't.
I said, what are you going to ship it?
It's not feasible, bro.
You can't ship a whole chair to Mexico.
Put it in a box.
That's going to be more than it's worth.
It's going to be like seventy dollars to
ship it. I'm not even kidding.
It's going to be more than seventy
dollars.
Yeah, it's going to be like two hundred
Yeah.
That's so cheaper than buying the fucking
chair.
Have you checked on Craigslist?
It's still used.
You can you can go to office supply
or office surpluses and get them for like
fifty six dollars.
in Mexico.
Live in Mexico.
You probably can't do that.
Yeah.
Come to America.
Mexico, an entire building costs
$10,000.
Bring it as your carry on.
[Laughter]
Come take one of the ones from the office and bring it as a carry on.
It'll be cheaper than shipping.
Yeah, just rolling it down the aisle of a plane.
It's just fucking bumping.
I'm trying to shove it into the...
I'm trying to shove it into the upper compartment.
[Laughter]
I need to have all of you come to my domain and you will understand everything in my life.
I'm going to be coming in your domain for sure, bro.
Yup.
I don't know about all that.
Uh-huh, you do.
Alright.
I do want to go to Monterrey.
I need to paint myself like a Tigres fan.
Badly.
When are you coming down?
I don't know.
I need to get a new passport first.
Bro, no one has any fucking passports.
I have one.
I just need a new one.
We're American.
We don't need one.
You fucking idiot.
Yes, but only because I got it like two months ago.
Oh, where are you going?
To Bermuda.
Whoa.
Whoa, he's going to the triangle.
He's going to go.
I'm going there to explore the triangle.
If he disappears, you're going to fly right in the middle of it.
Good luck, Brian.
You will never see him again.
I'll leave it in the world.
You should come down and visit me, man.
Yeah, definitely.
Pee for trip?
I will house you.
But only you, you cannot bring.
Oh, don't say the name.
Come on, man.
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
All right, we're going to go.
(laughing)
- Bye. - Bye.