Recording, and I'm playing the song.
Sorry about my fan. I'll turn it off.
Jesus!
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
We can't hear it though, but you're fine.
I'm fuckin' here.
Not my problem.
Beer's we drank, motherfucker.
With Juvio, Caleb, and Rex.
Beer.
Somebody is moving a bowling setup.
A homemade bowling alley.
I have two questions for you right now.
Do you think that that could possibly be a ghost?
And two, how do you respond to the allegations lobbied at your person by a certain person
in our friend group that you live in a fully empty abandoned building.
Who lobbied that at me?
I can't, I cannot.
Okay.
Noah said this?
Yeah.
Um, okay.
So.
We should give the context for that because.
Okay, let's do, let's do beers first.
This is too much.
Let's do beers first.
Alright, let's do beers first.
It's been, we took a week off.
We forgot how to do a show.
Horrible family tragedy and here we are.
I have a twisted tea, half and half guys.
I did the original flavor last time, this time I did the half and half, hard iced tea and
lemonade.
Guys, I love the original twisted tea.
Love it to death, one of my favorite things.
This tastes completely identical and I did not know there was no lemonade in the original
twisted tea before I had ever had this.
This tastes insane.
Is it like sugar?
Half tea, half lemonade.
Oh, okay.
It's sweetened tea.
It's like Arizona tea.
I see.
This, this, this Twisted Tea thing has been going on for a while.
It was going on with you guys before I, when I was in town and I didn't even get to try
it.
And I was so curious.
It's amazing.
Do they not have that in Mexico?
No, we don't.
This is a magnificent, magnificent drink.
I'm going to give this, I'm going high on this guys.
I'm going to give this an 8-1.
Wow.
You love the sisters.
Now rate it in basketball terms.
In basketball terms, this is Ant.
Anthony Edwards, is that his name?
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, this is him.
This is a high upside, doing some insane things, punching way above where he should be for
how old he is.
your
the
I do not understand why people are drinking white claws and stuff.
If you don't want a beer, this is the beverage to go for.
This is like, I mean I'm like a quarter of the way through this already.
This is a giant can.
It's so delicious and it has caffeine in it.
Which is extra good.
Which I like caffeine quite much.
Okay, who's next?
I'm going next.
I have a beer Julio might be familiar with.
I have a tomato gelato.
A gelato!
A cendilla picante!
Whoa!
I have a cendilla picante modela gelato.
Ok, I've seen this often, but I think that gelatos are basically disgusters.
So tell me why, but I've only had the tomato ones.
Ok so that's just tomato juice?
And the mango one is way too sweet.
Yeah, tomato juice is awful.
And only like old men who are weird drink it.
I would pause it.
This is a spicy watermelon flavor.
Yeah.
Whoa.
What you think, white boy?
This tastes really good.
You look so Mexican today.
It's crazy.
Me?
No, not no, never you.
Me.
Never me?
What does that mean?
It's because I have my pointy shoes on.
You can't see.
every you dude. My shoes are so long and pointy they're curling under my desk. What if I bring
my beanie down like this? Rex has so many looks, has so many looks over the years that have
known him. You've always looked like a ball. I'm sorry but if I- A ball! Well you've had
You've had two looks. You've had guy with hair and then most of the time you've had a ball.
Ball is the other one I get.
No, that's fine. That's a fine thing to say to somebody that you love.
You look like a ball.
I'm sorry.
You're a famous ball. Like a cue ball, a beach ball, a volleyball.
You are probably the most famous ball around.
Yeah.
I can't take a word famous, Paul.
Rate the beer.
Rate it.
Say any number and we'll just continue.
This is like a 7.5.
Maybe an 8.
Very light 8.
You know?
You do Anthony Fantano.
On the score.
Me, Portnoy.
You, the Needle Drop.
I guess that's true.
watched Anthony Fantano but I guess saying like something is his...
I think it's just something that you can just like pick up like without watching it
how does it what's that called like you don't have to watch it but just like
pick it up by like context clues I forgot what the term was yeah anyway this is
delicious it tastes like water with sweet and spicy it sounds good you know what
is it something that the Spanish world is hiding from us
agua fresca this is the best drink ever I've noticed women the sweet there is
water hand agua fresca that is starting to come up in in vending machines really
see it more often. I think Minute Maid makes an agua fresca. Obviously not Bluey Autentico.
Yeah, Autentico agua fresca is basically the best drink on planet earth. Like a melon flavoured
water. Oh my god it's so damn good. I love that shit. This has been around for a while.
I thought you were talking about... It's probably been around anciently. Yeah. I would assume.
One of the most famous TV shows in Mexico, it was like one of the gags on there was like
agua fresca that tasted and looked incredibly weird.
So that's like a 50s show.
Pretty much like the dirty rag agua fresca that looks like shit but it tastes like mango.
Dishwater agua fresca?
Yeah, yeah, basically.
That sounds pretty good actually.
It was a funny thing 50 years ago.
Show me your fucking beer you piece of garbage.
Finally I know what everyone has been thinking over
Over every single episode. Oh, what's to be you're gonna bring in is you're being some bullshit. I was meaning like
Take out the roja. It's gonna be something stupid
Something that everybody's ever like already seen you have a heater this week. You're claiming today
Yeah, oh shit. I'm clean
Claiming it's more interesting than my usual beer
You fucking bitch a couple weeks ago
I discovered that we have quite a beer collection on my supermarket and
They have a nation section. So I went ahead and pay myself up a original Thai beer called singer
Oh sing ha this is a good beer. Yeah, you think so? I've had this one. I
think
I had some kind of fucking Asian beer. That's good. I like it
It's a premium lager from Bangkok
Okay score that muh, this is a 7 I like it
Little anticlimactic but under rate underwhelming
Score, I just think it's a it's a good like you ever like that's not even true
You don't like beer I don't know why you're arguing with that I I don't like
Dark beers. This is this is pretty late. This is really not even going for a decimal point. You think seven point zero seven point one
It's a little it's a little better
Also, I also saw the hello
Things house and there that I want to I wanted to buy all of them. I like those. Yeah
Character I realized recently shut up
That when you showed me the singha I was thinking of that beer and that I've never had the beer that you just tried
No, that one that's crazy. That one's so completely green, but it has sing in the name. That's true
I think you won this time. It's
Different sting
Another debate that I've won. Yeah, it's really funny
The like the Asian part of like the because it's got like all over the world
the
in
was watching
i really can't
madagascar
yeah
yeah that's africa bro
that's the asian part of africa
really i'm learning a lot from you too
basically
have you watched like early curb
curb your enthusiasm?
you know the episode with the uh...
the basspec ratio is somehow smaller than four by three
it looks like it was filmed on a phone
You know the episode with the uh...
the carp
not the carp actor, the acupuncturist
I don't know, it's been many years
well it's got this guy that does like
he's the asian voice
for like twenty years
but you never like see him actually he just does it in like cartoons
is it the guy who plays the dad duck in kung fu panda?
I believe so. Whoa I love that guy he's isn't he in he used to be like an actor
in the eighties
Yeah.
Yeah, and he's-
And he passed away, I believe.
No, I think he's still alive.
Uh...
He passed on.
Okay.
Alright, well he's dead.
*laughs*
But the point is...
Uh, I had never seen what he looked like before.
I just assumed that there was, like, multiple guys doing that voice.
No, it's one guy who invented the Asian voice everyone does.
Yep.
And he's from Hawaii.
Really?!
Yes.
That is funny.
Well, good for him!
the
Israel Kaliwa'uwi
Israel
They can't claim him anymore
They invented Israel
Well he, what do you mean he passed on?
Good
What do you mean good?
He aided himself to death
He had children
So?
What the fuck is your problem today?
Think about the children in Gaza
I care for these children too
Why are you so hostile?
It's just a fat guy who passed on to the next line
to
He deleted the video today.
It was a couple days ago.
Guys if you're not, if you don't know what's going on right now, first of all I'm praying
for you because you do not have a lot upstairs.
Because you should be plugged into this.
If you like this show you should be plugged into this kind of stuff.
Tap into this shit.
Me and Rex's favorite gambling streamer Mr. AZ who is either 24 years old or 21 years
old.
He said both ages.
So
he had met levied an accusation against rosh dine who's the number one biggest
really streams of the drake
does the good that streams of the drake where they promote state dot com
levy an accusation of russian that he was attacking him
with uh... all this like fake information and then also that russian
does not use real money guys this
is huge fucking news
so that was already come down
uh... of course it was known
but it proved it
but he proved it he brought rossi would have to have lost
to
billion dollars
which is just not gonna happen without being
you would never catch me losing two billion dollars not even on my worst day
i would cry
two billion are you kidding me
when my in on mosk
even for him it would hurt
somewhat
probably no
but i was a fifty five billion which is
honestly very funny
well twitter
uh... now
on what
he'd be still on the get his uh... stock
is bested stock plan for
turned has learned to look at it
policy scheme
or really i don't know anything about the story what happened with that
uh... the judge in delaware is not letting him get his like twenty eight
imagine you've got you you're
an african child a starving african child i was
you you call your way out of some fucking lithium mine
or blood diamond uh... mine
uh... a whole in africa and are coming
uh... dark night rises whole
you finally make it to the united states
and he said him have a great idea
ebay
not the day
people are just
was a bit yeah i think it was a bit off
the
and i think it would be a bit of a little bit
PayPal which was bought by eBay. So basically he created eBay. Yeah, you invent PayPal so that people can buy drugs
now
That sells and you say hmm. What else I want to use my giant African brain on
Hmm, maybe a car that runs on batteries you do it
Everybody's saying you can never do that cars run on gas. You can't have a car that runs on a battery
You fucking do it you make some of the greatest coolest looking cars of all time that are the best possible
Ubers they're literally made for uber. They're perfect
The handles don't open that makes no sense. The handles are I like that. It's a it's a security measure
Yeah, the one time we took we took that Tesla over. I felt like I was sliding around on the seats
Exactly. Yeah, they don't have seat belts. You have to hunt for the seat belt. The entire thing smells like a matchbook and then you make
Trillions right? Yeah, or you think you did and then some fucking fat guy in Delaware handles parking tickets all day
Yeah, no, no, no, no, no, you can't do this. Yeah, that is some bullshit
He was
Like
Billions of dollars in stock under the condition he could make Tesla like a trillion dollar company
And everyone's like, "You'll never be able to do that. That is retarded."
-Mm-hmm. -Uh, in 2018.
-And he did it. -Well, you could say it.
-Yeah, back in 2018. -Yeah.
Yeah. In 2018, you could definitely say that.
Well, actually, no. 2018, you definitely could not say that. You could say it now.
-But 2018, you cannot. But the point is... -Right.
...he's not getting his money. Which is very funny.
That's why he's been complaining about the state of Delaware on Twitter.
Which is very it's a very funny beef to have with like a state. I like that shit. I
don't like
Kansas
Yeah, but you can't fight the state of Kansas. What do you like?
Watch me watch me. I'm more powerful than you will ever know man, and that's what
That's that that's the host of the show I would like to congratulate Caleb on his big breakthrough
It is officially gonna be the year of the Caleb. Guys, we all saw it. He's starting off in LA.
He's going all over. He hates not-Kansas though.
He's gonna be a big-time celebrity and we're here to just interview him pretty much.
Is this because the Chargers posted my video y'all?
And then deleted it like cowards because they found out that
it was a racist video.
It's not a racist video! I never understood this!
How do people say that this is a racist is it the least racist video ever you were calling him a pussy and
some other
What kept being a gay guy is that's a lot of you down on our gay Kenyan president
Hawaii I say he's from Hawaii in the video completely true. It's all facts. Oh, why?
No, I don't think you don't think it's a state does what you said
I say Hawaii. Yeah, you said that. Yeah, you know what?
Never watch the video. I've got
Just sent that shit out did not watch that shit man. I need to make a video
I need to think of a video idea man. What should I've been? I've been telling you
I've been telling killer for you two years now make another video and he goes like no that's stupid and then
The Chargers come in and they're like, "We're Caleb's biggest fans" and we'll post this video without even doing an inch of research
You know who this guy is. We just saw this video
I don't know like on TikTok or some shit and then they were so
Amazed that you replied "What's up?" to their tweet that they fucking deleted it.
That they deleted it man, these fucking cowards. I thought I was about to get tickets
My dad likes, not the Chargers, but he likes the Rams which used to play in LA. Close enough.
and or they do now they do now again yeah okay so they played in LA when he was a
kid and then the Chargers came in so he hates the Chargers actually but I was
gonna surprise him with April Fool's tickets where when the NFL is on in
April and that's not gonna work out I guess I guess my entire thing is yeah in
my head it was it was two scenarios as we won which is the the the utopia they
found out who you are they're like oh my god we're such fans of your video from
five to ten years ago let's collab let's make you the face of the Chargers
social media Twitter account yes and they fly you out they take you to the
games and you're running around doing your thing the second scenario is that
what is my thing do you just run around and do your thing I run around you run
around you post tweets I'm the charger stadium I hate Obama which is what I
said and I'm also a racist which is what you said I didn't say that in the video
and second second scenario they delude the post and they block you which is
halfway there honestly they did I don't know if they blocked me I didn't check
but either way it's only content exactly dude people I mean what you posted they
probably have posted other videos that were had unsavory people and I'm not
Not that I'm unsavory, I'm very very, I have a lot of mainstream appeal.
You guys would be shocked if you looked through my emails, all the different mainstream type
stuff that comes into my, onto my desk.
But I'm sure they've uploaded a picture of, probably nothing about, probably no Hitler
photo has ever made it to sports.
Sports thing.
see what's the charges considerable
one of the best
no no i'm not saying it's like a hitler
thing
woah don't raise your hand like that bro chill
i can't win in this
in this game of life
i just get shit on all day everyday by everything
i get fucking destroyed
i get destroyed all the time
you're gonna be the biggest celebrity of the world
basically
i get des- i can't because i get destroyed
They're gonna put you in a movie with Ryan Reynolds.
I, I, no. No, no, no.
I was walking around, have you guys ever played that Vampire the Masquerade game?
Yeah. You know there's the ugly character where you walk around and people just are
like "Ew, fuck you, you're fucking ugly."
That is what my life is like. I walk around and people fucking give me the worst
looks, people pull their
kids and dogs and cats away from me as I walk by. Isn't that weird because you have a dog that
what's the kill everything it sees?
I...
um... yeah
he's not the best dog
I was thinking on the way home today
I was like walking him and I was like
god damn I wish I didn't get this fucking dog
how fucking dumb am I that I got a dog
I was thinking about
how much better my life was with no dog
god damn
don't get a dog if you're watching this do not get one
cause you have to you're tied to them for
you know how long does a dog live
like
you're like sitting at the house like the reason why we got him in the first place
was I was like oh I'm at the house all the time it'd be nice to have something
to hang out with and then you realize that nothing is better than just sitting
at the house alone and you watch your you watch TV and you make one of the
worst meals of all time and you eat cold rice you get sick from the rice that is
a much better life than having a dog in your house yes having a pet is something
women do to feel less alone. Men have the computer, we're fine.
That is true. Yeah, exactly. I'm gonna open my door cuz it's getting...
Sometimes I forget that I...
I, uh...
My old roommate keeps asking me when I'm going to give him my address so he can send me the ashes of a dog that I
had for two years and left the ashes at his house.
Feed him, go to, feed him to a bird on a bench.
-Throw it away! -It's like, dog's ashes? Yeah.
What the fuck?
Why did you even have those ashes in the first place? That's my question to you.
They give them to you. They're like, "You have to take these ashes."
So just leave them at the vet. Do they put them in a giant urn? Is it in a bag?
They were sitting in a shoebox, and I left the shoebox in the closet.
The whole point of keeping ashes is a sign of respect, and you're putting them in a shoebox deep in a closet?
Yeah.
It's more respectful to throw them away at that point.
Listen, this dog was blind.
He pissed himself constantly.
The fact I even moved him across state lines is a blessing.
Well, it does, I mean, it seems like the op, it seems like a curse that you had to move
this fucking terrible dog.
Well, I was cursed by having his ashes, if that's what you're saying.
Yeah.
Do you feel like...
Okay, I want to talk about my apartment being haunted. What did Noah tell you about my apartment?
So Noah did the thing...
I don't know. I think you've talked about this before right? The Patrick thing when he locked himself out of your apartment?
Yeah, so it was the it was...
to set the scene I
went back home for a funeral and it was a very very sad kind of thing and
it was like the last night that we were... I was in North Carolina. Mm-hmm, and it was
was
I
just catch my reaction as I looked at my phone just like eyebrows throwing so
crazy and then just without saying anything I just got up off the couch
like this and just the worst posture ever hunched over just walked into the other
room because I had to keep my phone plugged in so because it was also about
to die and so he fucking sends Phil to his girlfriend's house and I guess he
destroys that house too and then calls... wait did he tell you this? He called three
different locksmiths and they all get there at the same time the locksmiths are in
front of my apartment and he has them argue about who will do it for cheaper
this is it's three locksmiths and I'm getting a live vlog of this entire thing
happening he's like yeah I have three Polish guys in front of your apartment
arguing about who's gonna give me the lower price to get into this fucking building.
Okay. So one guy finally breaks and is like, I'll do it for a hundred bucks. And he's like, okay,
I will go with this. So my, my POV of the situation is I sit at my computer and I see that Mike
is playing Valorant with a certain Caleb on discord. And I go, oh, that's crazy. I thought
Caleb was a very important thing. And then I joined the call and, and, uh, Mike goes like,
"Oh no, this is... no, he's at Caleb's."
I was like, "Oh, okay."
So then he starts sending the messages on Discord,
like, "Oh, I got myself knocked out."
And he's doing all this thing.
And I think it must have been like an hour or so
when I can finally hear him talk.
He finally made his way inside.
And he comes in like,
"Oh, dude, Jesus Christ, that was so fucking stupid."
And he tells us that he was out there in the cold with Phil
for about 30 to 40 minutes,
just laying on the doorbell of like every single apartment in your building and no one even
looked at the door.
And so he said...
There are four people in my building, man.
There's what?
It's four people.
It was like a Saturday night.
I'm sure they were all gone.
And now he's accusing me of living in an abandoned building.
So okay.
So proof number two, there's a ghost haunting you right now, making noises.
So I think the ghost building theory is picking up steam.
It's really not.
Another thing was I got back, I do not have, I was just kidding.
I wasn't even sure, I didn't even hear anything.
I got back here and I sat at my desk and literally the entire desk was covered in black ash because
he was clearly smoking a joint at my desk in my room which has no windows and just stinking
it up with disgusting smoker's weed.
Did it smell?
No but I'm gonna tell him it did to make him feel worse.
Just ash everywhere.
Oh god I have a white mouse pad there was a giant black streak on the mouse pad that I
had to go clean off.
He sucks man.
I'm done with him.
I'm opening another beer guys.
This is a Bitburger.
Bit Burger.
That's what I like to do now.
This is, yeah I'd like to bit on a burger.
This is a Prieb Pils, original German Pilsner.
This is a, it was on special, it was $3.50.
Let's see how this one is.
I wish I'd bit a burger.
A burger beer is crazy.
Wow.
Burger.
*sips beer*
Guys this is not what I was expecting from this beer whatsoever based on the look of the can hold on what?
There's a deal with a name. I
Believe it means something in German
Wow, this is really good. This is a pilsner that is not I think of a pilsner as a very light kind of boring beer
This has complexity man
This has different layers to it in terms of beer
It's like beer
It has a almost I would say I would say it's bordering on like an IPA type of like drying out your mouth
type of thing I see I
See some transiting from German to English and apparently bit burger in German in English. It stands for bit burger. Oh
That's pretty simple then yeah, that makes sense
What it what did I have to drink while I was home that's I know that's your question I'll answer that I had
I had a new kind of wine that I've never had before
Which is a Sarah?
Wine and guys, I think I have a sir. I think I have a Sarah addiction. I had three glasses
This is the best wine I've ever had in my life. I
Don't know what that is. I don't know either. I got it from Trader Joe's
The platinum reserve sirah from Trader Joe's I love this one good for wine
Feel like it's good for one. It's bad for beer good for one
It's grapes. I have wine. It's great. We bought a wine bottle
it must have been like almost a month ago now and we don't have a
The court thing to take the cork out. So that was sitting my stupid fridge
We came across this problem because we bought the wine and then realized that my wife's parents are very
Religious and have never drank anything and they did not have a wine bottle opener. One is the religious beer
Basically, they don't do and and then
My wife's dad was like hovering around the wine. It was like I
Wish I could have a glass of wine man
He's like nope, I swore to God 40 years ago that I would never have a single drop of alcohol ever again
That is crazy
He's like 60 something so what are you so
Let's it's so funny to be a sober guy at like 23, you know, yeah
I'm done. Yeah, one year of going crazy. Yeah, and then I went hung out with my dad
1130 p.m. lunch
Margarita halfway finished when I walk in the door of the restaurant and I was saying yes
This is more my kind of thing. That's what that should be like. Yes, dad should be red
Right dad should be a full red. They should be like shrimps. They should be over
Completely pink. Yep
Just floating around
That's the fucking truth of the matter. Yeah
Really small hurry definitely smaller than you because you know what you don't want a dad that's bigger than you that sucks
I remember him being bigger than me when I was growing up, but now I'm larger than him. Yeah, that's weird
Dad's shrink because they get old and old people and boys grow. Yes
Here's a problem that I had when I was home in
My my younger brother my youngest my youngest is
He just turned 13 years old he's six foot one
Dude it was making
Mad dude
He's six foot and not six foot one like he's like he's like, um, he's like a huge man
Yeah, he was like we were like wrestling
Like he came up to me and like kind of wrestled me when he saw me and I felt like I in danger
I was like, I need to take an MMA class to defend myself from my my child brother who started
a yellow exclamation point above his head. It's not red yet because he's not
Yeah, it is bad dude, and he's like sitting there at one point dude. He did something that pissed me off so bad man
We're sitting there talking to my mom and he fucking put his arm and rested it on
Dude, I just had to sit there and take it this kid will kill me
Kiddies huge Jesus Christ, man. He owns you. I used to wipe poop off his balls when he was a baby
And he'll put you in the toilet and now he'll he'll kill me. Yeah
Dude, it was crushing. It was completely crushing. That's horrible. Are you gonna try to lure him into joining the NBA soon? I
I have told him that he needs to join sports, but my mom won't let him because she's, you know,
he's the youngest. She's afraid of him getting concussed and adding to any sort of brain damage
that he probably already has. Yeah, right. But he has a lot of potential. People are saying
questions. Okay, he was the reason I wiped poop off his balls is because he was a baby
when he was born and I was 14 or 15 and so of course I had to change his diaper and he would
have poop all over his disgusting balls and yes I had to wipe that up. Now given this experience and
just extrapolating from the memory of that time do you think he is also you know bigger than you?
Do you think his member is larger?
That's what I'm asking.
Because he's taller.
Do I think that my...
Yeah, Rex, I'm not going to answer that man.
That is an odd question.
My 13 year old brother, you're asking if he has a larger member than me.
I think it's a valid question.
It's just a thought.
This interview sucks, dude.
Yeah, you're not really...
Can you move on to the next question?
I don't really speak to that.
career or some shit but his next moves
what's next for Caleb?
what's next for Caleb Piz?
what's next for me?
well, persona 3 just released today, the reloaded version so now I'm entering back into Japan
in a major way and uh
I feel like they've released 20 versions of the same game over the last like 5 years.
That one got, it was like originally a PSP exclusive or something and then they like
released it somewhere else, I don't know.
So FES is the PSP exclusive and in that one you play as a girl.
Or you have the option to.
Yes.
Yeah.
Yeah, so this is not, this was just the normal one I guess.
But um.
We're going back to the regular one where you play as a boy.
Yeah, so it's better.
Right.
I don't want to play the Persona 3 P P 3 P or whatever
I wanted to wait for the boy one the fully a boy no option to be a girl
Awesome rap in that game when you go into the dorms
It's like yo, I'm persona I got
Guns and I it's like that. It's awesome. It is you know, so in all the other games they they call their ghosts
I call them ghosts
for by saying
Persona yeah, and in this one they have to put a gun to their head and pull the trigger
Whoa for some and I when I heard about this I was like, that's badass
But then I played that I've been playing the game and it really is kind of I don't really like it very much
I think it's a little too much for me. What is that?
Because every single time I'm starting to love these characters and they're putting a gun to their head and every time I think that it's gonna
Come out the other side red instead of blue
It hasn't yet
but I think one of these times one of these things you're gonna put a gun to their head and pull the trigger and
It will be a full bullet that destroys their brain
This is crazy, I don't know I don't like I don't like violence
very much and
That kind of thing. I like cartoonish violence. I do not like dismemberment. I do not like
suicide, squidward suicide is still scary to me as an adult
right
and
i just don't like, i don't like the image of it
but i'm gonna keep playing
i'm gonna keep playing, don't you worry
because i need to develop relationships with every single girl in the game
and hopefully a teacher too
mr. robot
yeah this boy went completely robot
dr. robot's
did i rob- did i robot?
yeah
i think you're fine now
i understood what you were saying though
you said you needed to fuck
you needed to get your fuck on
I don't want to have sex. I just I want to
bashfully hold hands
Well, that's what Japanese sex is apparently. Yeah, so I like that kind of thing. Yeah
You know what? I've been thinking about recently these past couple days
What's that? I need to drop back in into Metal Gear Solid
So this is a game. I have to go back. I want to play this game so badly
But I don't know PlayStation and I don't really know how to do anything
It's not hard man. No, it's pretty easy, but I don't really know how to do anything. So it's hard for me
It's easy for you guys because you guys are nerds
I'm a jock so stuff for you hard for me
I need a persona over the past two months and you talk about it constantly
That is you also yeah, you've gone to the point where you
You try to repress it so hard during when we're recording the the regular
Podcast the the other one and then you come in here you go like, alright guys
I need 15 minutes before we even start going live you go guys
I'm gonna need my 15 minutes person in the corner stuck about it for 15 minutes. Nothing really happened
It's just the same shit the same girls running around and I'm talking to them
a
was
And it turns out guys, high school, you're going to different noodle cafes and eating with your friends.
Yep.
And you are, all the girls are wearing very high skirts, the boys are wearing full suits everywhere.
And you have to battle a demon and find out kind of the secret to the world.
And I just had no idea I guess. I thought that it was a lot simpler than that.
So these games are replacing my high school experience.
What's the point of a Persona game?
to beat the game. There's an end to it.
What is the point? Well, okay. Let me tell you about Persona 4.
The point of Persona 4 is that the demons that lay within you
that you are afraid to confront,
the most powerful thing you can do is look them dead in the eyes and say
"I am this. I have this in me.
I fully embrace the dark sides of my personality."
And Persona 5 is about fucking your teacher.
And Persona 3, we don't know yet.
Because I haven't finished it.
But I have a strong feeling that it will have a very meaningful ending.
Right.
I guess I'll just never play these games and I'll just go back to playing all the Yoshala games again.
They're 100 hours long.
They're really long.
They're not very fun, to be honest.
I love 'em, man.
I'm becoming addicted to that game Vampire Survivors.
That's what I've been playing a lot of.
You should, uh, you know what game I think you would really love?
What's that?
Danganronpa.
Danganronpa?
I've heard this name before.
Yeah.
It's another high school style game.
I think that's like the- OH!
Don't get the wrong idea here, fella!
I don't like it!
I would like Persona just as much if it took place at a work event.
Right.
Where you had to go to class and you had teachers and you lived in dorms.
I would like it just as much as the ones that were you're in high school.
It's not the high school thing.
So as someone who's also like really so been outside of this like for years,
I've heard about Persona, Danganronpa,
and I thought that they were the exact same game when I heard about them.
Is this true, Rex?
they're completely different
do you believe the same one is a murder mystery
well it sounds very well
you all you know i've become obsessed with recently to done it films
like uh... i'd like to know if you would love
and i love who done it by just watched uh...
a haunting in venice the new uh... agatha christie
movie
uh... though hercule porro
with uh... kenneth brana
this movie
maybe the best movie i've ever seen
probably not but uh... it is fun it is very fun
i love
the who done it genre
and i think the next time you know what is clue
yeah we watched the uh... the nice out movies
i liked knives out i thought glass onion was essentially cringe
which is uh...
but just as somebody told me that
I actually liked it, but because someone said that, I now think it's cringe.
Oh, dude, yeah.
Death on the Nile is one of those movies that came out recently and it seemed to really suck.
Yeah, so apparently the other two sucked.
I know I watched the Murder on the Orient Express in theaters and thought it was kind
of crappy, but didn't see Death on the Nile, but Haunting in Venice, I really enjoyed it.
I watched it on a plane.
I also realized I watch 90% of the movies that I watch in a year on a plane.
That makes sense, I guess.
Yeah, watching a movie on a plane feels natural.
There's nowhere for you to go.
Yeah.
If I watch a movie at my house, I don't want to watch a movie.
It's the same as watching a season on a TV show.
That's good too.
That's awesome.
That's very good. That's where I watch the rehearsal.
I watch, I think, all of the rehearsal on a plane.
But I watched um
I've watched some of my favorite movies ever on a plane. I watched the player the robert altman movie. I watched chinatown
on a plane
What else have I seen on a plane i've seen so many movies
I I mean, I really think 90 of the movies i've seen in the last like five years have been on a plane
I saw the uh, the cyberpunk anime on a plane
That's that's a good that's a good one to watch on a plane. It's not that long
One one thing that made me laugh really hard was um
I watched a woman with an hour and a half left into a flight start the movie Heat, which
is a three hour movie.
I just get like kind of pissed when it didn't, wasn't even close to ending when we were landing.
Dude, that just happened to me before.
Then you have to try to find the movie later.
Yeah, that's too much, man.
It made me smile so much.
Oh, dude, you know what I've been doing, or what I did last night and now I will do again
tonight?
Guys, this is crazy. You're not gonna believe this. I
Have convinced my wife
To play Halo combat evolved co-op with Wow
That's crazy. We are about two hours in and I finish we finished last night
No, it's like thank you so much for for playing that game with me
I know that you would hate you hate that kind of thing and she was like no, I actually really enjoyed it Wow
Yeah
Isn't that fucking isn't that crazy?
This seems like you're laying the seats to fully moving out into a bigger apartment and having a gaming room. That's what okay
So here's my plan, uh-huh
plan hamebo
I invoke all that involved.
Sorry, the Bitburger got to me, man.
We're playing Halo Combat Evolved, okay?
And we're playing it with the old graphics.
We're playing it in the Master Chief Collection
with the old graphics selected.
So it looks shitty.
Doesn't that like change the click of a single button?
Yes, but she doesn't know that.
She thinks that I had to hack it
to make it look like that.
That is so strange.
When I was playing that shit, I clicked it by accident
and I didn't know how to switch it back.
off putting. The new graphics look like shit. The old ones look amazing. And I um, so we're
playing on the old graphics. And we have this little TV, this baby TV, and you guys know
I bought a new TV. Right? I didn't know this, no. I bought a 55 inch TV from Sam that I'm
keeping at the office as like the office TV. But here's what I'm doing. We're playing this
and then we're gonna play through all what now she likes it quickly to come
about the play a little too that will play a little three
ods t
and then once we get to the new ones
hello for a little infinite
she's gonna notice
that the game is looking a little small because it's built for a bigger t_v_ at
this point
and i will say you know what's crazy
we have a t_v_ at the office
that i can bring here right now
that is giantly huge and we can play in 4k
and then she'll make me some dinner
well
uh... yeah
so this is a true husband of yours
we're talking about a three or four year plan here
that is
yeah
three or four years
uh... at the rate we're going
we'll probably play
an hour and a half every three weeks of these Halo games so it'll take some time
i think but it'll be worth it in the end i think
you have a fifty five inch tv
i tried to get i'd try to she played out of that harry potter game
and she really liked it i was like
i guess is kinda like
dark souls kinda thing you know to some extent
yet is it's a it's a review role
it's got no combat is going to like that
and
eyes i tried to get her to play elder ring but that that gave her a little bit
That is crazy because you haven't even played
You didn't even like Elven Ring
You played 20 minutes of Elven Ring and you were like
Elven Ring was too hard for you
It wasn't too hard
Play it and stream it with me right now
Not right now
I just don't like that kind of game
I do not like those like
I don't like RPGs at all really
It's barely an RPG
It's more just combat and learning the world
It's still like open world stuff
I do not really care
not
and played all the way through that was like a 3D one like that
like a open world RPG
was like Breath of the Wild and I got really bored with that
and that was like 10 years ago now
this is really sad dude
why? cause I don't like your stupid game
no because you won't give love a chance
I played like an hour and a half of Elden Ring dude
no
it's just not my kind of game bro
it's too hard for you
if that's what you need to
to say
then i'll let you say that
you can't gaslight us in the thing that we don't like that kind of game
you watch people i don't like that kind of game i've never liked that kind of game
i like games
open world rpg i do not like this kind of game
it quite literally is i think that it does count as an rpg
it is an rpg
I'm not, I am amazing at pretty much every game.
I got my girlfriend to play Nier.
She really liked that.
The automata one with the butt cheeks out?
No!
The original.
The old one, oh I see.
She liked that one, the automata, didn't really get into.
Which I found fun.
That one's for guys for some reason.
Yeah.
Can't quite place why.
Yeah, cause see, the automata you play a girl with her ass cheeks out, and the original
you play a guy who talks to a girl with her butt cheeks out.
Very different.
It must be hard to be a girl and want to play video games and there's nothing, no kind of
cock stuff.
You don't get to see a lot of cock in video games.
Yeah.
Which is what they want.
Except for Baldur's Gate.
Yeah, girls are addicted to cock.
Cyberpunk 2077 you see cock.
Oh really?
Yeah, you get to customize the cock.
is
I don't like exploring at my own pace. I have a very bad pace.
I see what you're saying, but you also like Persona, which is maybe the worst at that.
Well, but Persona is about... I like the...
High school aspect of things.
No, it's not... I don't only like RPGs that are in high school. I like the atmosphere stuff.
The LSU of high school.
Because if you are like, open world games feel like a job,
Persona is the worst at that.
It's a school thing.
It's pretty open.
It's not an open world like those though where you're like
You're they sit you in the thing and you have to walk for 10 minutes to get to the next thing
Shit when you that's what I quit Elden Ring is when you have to get on a horse and go to another world
Fairly popular in other rings you think you pick the worst argument
No, no, no, cuz I would I do the next thing
I remember when I quit Elden Ring the next thing was to get on a horse and go to a different place and
That place was too far. So I just started fighting a giant because it was closer
And I fought the giant like five times and just died every time and I was like, well, oh what they're making me
Fight this fucking giant because the other things too far away and so I stopped playing
right, so
You are just simply stubborn and we as you know as people who love you
We just have to like keep working at it trying to teach you new things and trying to open your your you know
expand your horizons like how you were so close when I would talk to you about
music and you'd be like you you tell me you listen to kids music you're gay
whatever and then two three years up three years after knowing us he just
texted me out of the blue yo he is fire and then a week later he goes like
Peso Pluma is it. You never told me about Peso Pluma. Did I not? No, no, no, no, no, lie.
I found out Peso Pluma from another Mexican guy. I love Peso Pluma. I got roasted in the
work group chat the other day because I was logged into the eBay, the work Gmail eBay,
and Patrick could see that I was looking at Peso Pluma t-shirts. I'm pulling up this email
That was such a funny email to get.
Just in the middle of the day, just like, eBay, from eBay, like, "Oh, remember this?
Don't miss out.
Pezza Pluma."
Don't miss out on this Pezza Pluma tour shirt.
And I was like, "Dude, what?"
And then Cam sees a screenshot of someone just looking for Pezza Pluma stuff.
Oh, that's what it was, Cam.
Yeah, I'm going to look Pezza Pluma in our email right now.
Yep, there it is.
Listen.
Recently viewed.
Let's make it yours.
Let's make it mine, dude.
Make it yours.
But imagine how cool I would look at that shirt.
I would be like, "Oh, that's so cool.
That's so cool.
Let's make it mine dude.
Let's make it yours.
But imagine how cool I would look at that shirt.
I think you should go for it.
I think I'm gonna get that shit.
Do you like the latest album? Genesis?
I have not listened to a full album yet.
I just listened to his top 5 songs on YouTube Music
that have Spanish names I can't pronounce.
Ok, that's fine.
And they're pretty good man.
and
to do a lot of those and i'm up into it
baltimore's gay you open my heart of all those gay but that i only like that with
friends though
and you've played a single hour of the game with us and it was five size i love
it
but i think i never had such a good a plea for like several hours
okay out there now do it
okay
it's not a big deal to me by the time you that he misses the throes badly we need
a brit will bring the throes back this weekend maybe a
i think i'd be a good move
uh...
Dude, I found out the kid who made Lethal Company,
do you know that he's 21 years old
and that game sold $52 million in copies?
- No, I didn't know that. - That makes sense.
- Is that crazy? - Yeah.
- I knew that he made like Roblox maps
and basically he started Lethal Company
as like a Roblox mod basically.
- He did, I mean, even with like Steam taking a cut,
He made 30 million dollars, 30 something million dollars.
My thing is, if you're this kid, why would you ever make a fucking game again?
You're done.
Yeah, no, I think he's just been updating it.
I think that's what people that find themselves in that scenario do.
Yeah.
Because here's the thing, right?
He could turn into Notch.
He could turn into Minecraft Notch.
He just sticks it out for 10 years.
Yeah what a right wing piece of crap
Yeah
Is he dead?
Did he die?
Notch?
No he got
He got ousted from the company I believe
Yeah well
Yeah well that was like
One of the first
Microsoft bought it for a billion dollars
That was like a
The first or second thing that happened to him
Like
It was
He got a million dollars
A billion trillion dollars
He got bought out by Microsoft
He got ousted
He had his mansion with all the candy walls
That he invited people into
What?
Yeah did you know that?
He had a candy wall?
Yeah
He had a candy wall in his mansion.
Yeah.
What do you mean a candy wall?
Candy dispensers.
Oh.
Just hella candy in his mansion for some reason.
I thought it was like, like Jack Bensinger has a wall, or he used to in his old apartment.
I think the first time I ever FaceTimed him, I don't remember why, I saw that he had like a bunch of different candies that he had eaten.
he had pushpinned the packaging to the wall.
And now I think he doesn't because he has a girlfriend maybe.
But that's what I thought you meant when you said candy wall.
And I was like, that guy, Notch, probably has a much crazier candy wall than Jack Bensinger
because of Notch's giant body.
It's a little crazier because it's the real candy, not just the packaging.
And you can get the candy if you're a guest at his home.
And then he got, now he became like a racist and then he fully disappeared off the face
of the earth.
Dude, that guy Kim.com, it's so funny that he is like a billionaire dude who had this
whole thing, went to jail or whatever, and then now, I don't know if he still is, but
at some point he was just like one of the guys in Trainwreck's stream who like just sits
in the Discord call and goes like, "Oh yeah, give me some grapes, yeah, go do max multi
the
to
gambling website.
- Yeah, he's--
- God bless him.
- He's like six, seven, 400 pounds,
rich, got nothing to do.
- Yep.
- And just, what would you do if that was you?
- That's the thing, the same shit.
- Exactly.
- I would 100% find, if I had a billion dollars,
I would find a way to be friends with TrainwrecksTV,
Aiden Ross, Kyson Att, right now.
- So which of us do you think is the closest
get into that point. Who do you think is the closest to getting into the Discord call?
It's gonna be Rex. Rex is gonna abandon us for a train.
That's what I was thinking.
Any day now. Any day.
I mean, and I, you know I love you guys, but if a bigger content creator came to me and
was like, "Will you be my goon? Will you be my 24 hour a day goon?" who just sits there
and says, "Yeah, grapes!"
Do you understand how badly that would hurt my feelings?
I would still try to find a pre-game.
You guys know more about Train than I do.
I remember tuning into one of his streams like a couple years ago.
And he was just like silently not even doing anything, just looking at the slot go.
And then he had goons in the background and there was a different POV from the slot in
the corner.
Does his goons, do they gamble with him?
Is that what they're doing?
Are they telling him?
Sometimes they do.
Is that what goes down?
Okay, sometimes they do sometimes they'll have somebody else that he will like stream their thing, but he doesn't he hasn't streamed in months
I think yeah, I don't think he streams very much
Yeah, I think he made a bunch off of kick. He's probably has like equity in kick. It was like the fate
Oh, he certainly does dude, dude. I is kick losing like a million dollars a day
Probably I mean they all lose money. It's so expensive, but they use em. They use AWS
Video hosting yeah, which is like I for like a 5,000 people watching the stream costs
$5,000 for every like six hours streamed if they watch in 480 P and 15,000 if they watch in 1080 P
like
They have to be losing a massive amount of money. Yeah
Well, that's that's the thing right? It's like
They're doing the uber model which is all tech is you just take a bunch of money until you can
Get people sucked in and then just flip
Your incentive model so that you start making money again
What is uber gonna do that?
And what how is this possible because isn't uber in like 30 million or 30 billion dollars of debt or some show?
It's like when it started out like years ago. Yeah, I think I think uber makes a profit now
Under net profit, let's see
I don't know man, I think they make money now, but in the early days they just burnt like
ten billion dollars.
We need to have an idea like this.
Do you think it...
That's all tech is dude, you just burn money until you can make a billion dollars.
And then you go to jail.
Yes, too late.
Yes. Yeah, that's kind of the end of the career. It's about a 10 year cycle.
Right. You just have to, you know, get big enough. It's like if you made 10 cents on
everything, but you lost like a billion dollars until you had 10 billion
customers. Well it's just having an OKADA and putting in front of
someone now. Well, I guess you have to put, eventually you run out of money.
There's not like, I do this shit, I do this shit almost, well not every day, but
whenever I get an idea I just email this in to Rex and he goes like, yeah man,
whatever. When are you going to invest in one of Julio's ideas man? When I, when he
has a good enough idea. What was the last idea that you had for him? I'm gonna look
- I haven't sent him one recently.
I think I told, what was it?
I had a Twitter idea.
Like a Twitter, but it's kind of like a--
- Like a private, like your tweets get deleted
after a month.
- After a day. - An idea for a social media app.
- Yeah. - Yeah, that's not a day.
- That's not so good of an idea, I think.
- Here's the thing, social media apps--
- Dude, we talk too much, man.
- You have to, you can't even get funding
for
*Rex talking about dating apps*
I like this one. I like this one. I said this one on the street before it's PC part picker but for groceries. Oh
Wait, you already have what does that mean? It's a grocery list app
Yeah, you know how you build your your computer on PC part picker and it gives you like the like the best prices on the best
sites
You do that shit. Oh
You're gonna go to 40 grocery stores so you can get bananas
the apples
Basically, you're gonna sit in something fucking slave to go and buy one thing at every
It's not fully
Budget and then it builds a grocery list. It's also that's good. It's how it's it's not fully fleshed out
It's more like the idea of like having that information in front of you because sometimes I feel like I'm getting the worst deal
Possible when I go grocery shopping I did it. I did an order from Costco on instacart per Rex's recommendation today
Okay, so in the cart $130 and I'm like that's a good amazing deal right then it's asking me
Do you want no dude? It's saying do you want to get a Costco membership? I say no
It adds the automatic tip to the driver delivery fee service fee
225 dollars
Yes, and did I order it yes, I ordered it what you get pad Thai
That's history chicken. No, I got a bunch of shit. Yeah, this is okay. Yeah, but
Yeah that that really made me mad. So I need to figure out groceries. That's the
Idea is amazing. It's gonna be heartless of me to see don't tip them
Thank you for watching Rex who by the way has Uber Eats a Taco Bell order at 3 in the morning
And we know that he didn't tip
You did that for my phone!
In a hurricane he'll order Uber Eats
Won't fucking tip a single dollar
And goodbye
Thank you for watching and goodbye
I'm your host, goodbye