[Sipping]
[Burp]
You're listening to Beers We Drink, America's #1 beer broadcast.
[Record scratch]
[Music]
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
[Burp]
This is a journey into sea,
into the middle of,
planet,
♪ I'm a fool ribbon ♪
- Beers we drank, motherfucker.
With Juvio, Caleb, and Rex.
- It is nice.
- Beer. - What's up?
- Yo.
- Hey, hi. - Do we start now?
- We're starting now.
- Okay, wait, ready?
- Okay.
- Three, two, one. - Three, two, one.
- All right. - I did it backwards.
- Okay. - I didn't even get
to the side of the mic.
- You know the deal.
We've been here before.
- I'll go first. - How many times
point five times? I got yeah five but welcome to
Beers We Drink number five. My name is Rax.
No. Wait. Hang on. Hold on.
Oh. This is what I got to drink. A white claw. What kind of white claw is that? A Wok 8.
Sandia. It's a watermelon one. Huh? Yeah. Because I wanted a tasty treat.
So I feel like that is pretty weak sauce
in terms of beers we drank, historical picks.
Yeah. I'm gonna be real with you.
Yeah. Yeah.
I think White Claw is kind of a little bit of a...
I feel like an Amstel Ultra is a way weaker peak.
But everybody, like White Claw is so ubiquitous.
Like you're not showing anybody anything new.
You're not dazzling anybody.
Rex comes in every single week with some kind of...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
He comes in with beers that have mushrooms in them.
You can't be throwing this shit at me
after the "Tuff" episode. Legos and shit.
We did a "Tuff" episode where it was only me
with a "Tuff" beer, with an interesting beer.
Well, well, well.
Really interesting beer.
And you guys were just like,
I want to drink some water today.
Listen, I have some good news and some bad news on my end.
I have good news and I have bad news.
Okay.
Okay, the bad news first.
Okay, I'm gonna hit you with the bad news.
I don't have a beer tonight.
- What?
- But here's the good news,
and actually I'll phrase my good news
in the form of a question.
- Okay.
- Are you two interested at all in mixology?
- Of course. - Yes.
- As a science, do you respect it as a science?
- I respect them as a science.
- As an alchemy or science?
- I trust it like a religion.
- Of course, yeah.
That's like, it's our North Star in a lot of ways, right?
- Yeah.
Would you freak out if I told you that I have a bottled Aperol Spritz right before me?
That's amazing.
That I'm about to have one sip of and give you an instant review of?
Two out of ten.
Not very good.
Perfect.
Yeah.
Sounds awesome.
It really tastes exactly like body wash.
Yeah.
You're supposed to put shit in that, no?
Put it in a glass and put like ice.
Man, fuck all that.
I think you're supposed to just drink it out of the can.
Out of the glass can.
- It's getting everywhere. - It's getting everywhere.
- Yeah, no, there's not enough Aperol, way too much.
- And not too much Spritz.
- True. - Wait, hold, wait.
- Isn't the Spritz like a sparkling water?
- Consumption of alcoholic beverages impairs your ability
to drive a car or operate machinery
and may cause health problems.
- That's not true, that's a lie.
Don't listen to that. - That must have been
one of those prank stickers.
- Yeah, some kid put that on the wrong beverage.
Yeah, well, I got owned again.
And that's so that's just my part one.
Trust me, you'll see the part two eventually.
Once I once I chug this, once I decide that I will just chug this.
Yeah. And I think you'd fair in a chugging competition.
Me against Badlands Chugs.
He would lose immediately.
You wanted me to say I was going to say good, and then you were going to say
against Badlands Chugs and just like kind of ruin.
Of course, I would do badly compared to him.
I wouldn't think so.
You know what's not in my name?
Chugs. I'm not going to be...
I can't do... I'm not going to be as good at something as a guy who put the thing in his fucking name.
You can change your stage name to Caleb Chugs.
That's a pretty good idea.
Just a YouTube channel where I drink like half a Nestle water bottle and I'm like,
"Oh, oh, oh, oh, I can't finish it."
But, uh, yo, like and subscribe.
I think we should do that.
Just because you do videos where I'm chugging just like...
Today I'm going to do a small Arctic Cherry Gatorade.
This one's for Amanda. Her husband reached out.
She's struggling with leukemia.
Amanda, stay strong.
And then I drink one Gatorade and I get really, really close to throwing up.
I like come back, I look like Riley Reid.
My mascara's running.
My eyes are watering.
I have boogers in my nose.
yeah yeah I don't know who that is but yeah I don't know who that is.
She's a rapper.
Mmm that makes sense.
I have a mango Tajin Gosa.
Okay.
So I don't know.
Some sort of.
Tell me my our Spaniard doesn't know what a Gosa is.
I don't know what a Gosa is.
It's a goose!
Nope.
That's not true.
Yeah, I don't know either.
Some sort of beer type drink.
By Owl Farm Beer.
But it's mango tahini.
So I think it'd be something that's right up your alley.
Yeah, that does sound yummy.
I don't really put tahini on my mango, even if it's like acidic.
I like mango with more like sweet stuff.
Like a froyo.
Not me, man.
I'm one of those suckers who buys that really, really hard mango
on the side of the street.
Whoa.
Because if you go to a mango--
I never trust those.
If you go to a fruit cart, then they give you the good stuff.
Because if you don't like it, you can throw it in their face.
But if they sell it to you in a bag on the side of the road
while you're in your car, you're way too far away on the highway
to complain.
They're selling you the worst mango of all time.
Wait, first sip review.
When you're first sip review of this salsa.
Oh, it's spicy.
It tastes--
I can tell you're kind of jittering.
You're kind of doing a it's like a one chip challenge type of reaction
that you're having.
You look like you got stung by a bee.
Start throwing up. Yeah.
It's spicy.
It tastes like I can taste the tajin and I can't taste the mango.
Mm. I love tajin and I tell you what this is.
This is poop.
Yeah, it looks awful.
This is complete poop.
You know, guys, can I?
I know this is unorthodox for this show.
I would like to motion for me to be able to skip directly to my second drink and put this
away and never even look at it ever again.
Please.
I would like to confer with Rex before we take a decision.
Yeah, no, take all the time you need.
Rex, I think we should make him chug it before he skips.
We should make him chug it after it gets warm, after he finishes the second drink.
Wait, you're right.
I'd like to say something really quickly.
It's been warm this entire time.
It's probably a big reason why it's not very good.
I didn't put it in the fridge.
Okay, motion to allow Caleb to put it in the fridge and then drink it later.
In front of us.
I I we gotta go to it right now.
I don't put it.
Okay, wait, hold on.
You got it wrong.
Can you do that to him?
Let me just drink a warm drink.
I don't know what he I don't know.
We told him a time.
I don't know why he just pulled it out of his fridge and just like looked at it on his computer.
this entire time. He's so stupid. Yeah guys, by the way,
wireless headphones, completely wireless headphones.
So I can hear every single word you're saying.
No, I can still, and now I'm in front of you and I can still hear everything you're
saying, but it's good to know.
That's how you guys talk about me when I'm not around. Listen, okay. All right.
Here's my second one. Okay. Is it also hot?
That's completely hot. Check this out.
What's that?
Back to the world of mixology.
The Manhattan.
Bottled Manhattan cocktail.
And here I am, I poured over ice.
I have some ice here, but I was saving the ice for this because I like, I knew I was
going to like this because I've already had some of it.
So this is something that I thought was a single serving, but it turns out it's like.
Yeah, that's like a giant, it's basically a little bottle of whiskey.
and I poured a giant glass of it.
So cheers, my friends.
Cheers. Cheers.
Cheers, my friends.
Shall we?
Now that's good.
That's much better.
That's much, much better.
I saw a post on Twitter about a guy that was like,
"I order weird drinks at the bar
"and the bartender gives me free drinks."
'Cause you order the weird ones?
'Cause he orders the weird drinks that are fun to--
What's a weird drink?
Salty dog.
Pee and soda.
Yeah, it's a salty dog.
I don't know if that's actually,
that's like a gin drink with salt on the rim or something.
It's like grapefruit juice, gin, and like salt.
That seems kind of like a double-edged sword.
Like you're getting a free drink,
but it probably just sucks shit.
Wait, I've never had a salty dog.
I was thinking of a rusty nail.
Rusty nail has drambuie in it,
which I think is some kind of sleep aid.
It's when I need to talk to.
I wasn't that alcohol and used to be medicine.
It is. It's still fairly recent.
I'm using it medicinally right now because I'm going to make myself
go to sleep in a normal time.
I'm going to use this like morning drinking for me.
That's what weed is for to me is to knock yourself out.
But you use it in the opposite.
I go insane on weed most nights. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, see, here's the thing, right?
is if I smoke weed, then I'm double dipping
because this is an excuse to drink beer.
If I smoke weed, that's just me doing it because I want to.
This is an obligation.
- I see, I see. - This is a job.
- You're at work right now. - This is your job.
- Right. - Yeah.
Well, we could do like a Rex smokes weed corner
where you just stand up and go over there
and you smoke weed on your band.
- I considered last week when I did not have a beer,
I considered smoking weed, but then I was like,
I know for a fact that we just have to delete the episode because it would be,
I would pretend that I would, I know exactly, I know myself too well.
I know that we would get 20 minutes in. I'd smoke weed five minutes in,
at 20 minutes in, I would start losing my mind.
Your face has just stopped making sense to me. Right.
And then I would pretend that I got a phone call from my mom,
even though I have a black screen on my phone and I would do a really terrible
act out where I say, no, my sister, my sister, I don't have a sister.
And then I would say, guys, I have to leave right now.
And then instead of hanging up,
I would just turn off my computer,
press the button on the tower,
and just hold it until, or I would maybe unplug it.
- Right.
- That's how scared I would get.
And I do that.
Basically, every night is a race that you smoke weed
and then you fall asleep before you get high.
Because otherwise, I'll stay up all night
if I don't have a looming physical and mental threat.
- You do that every night?
Not every night, but...
- Like six out of seven?
- Six out of seven nights a week.
(laughing)
Yeah.
- That's awesome, man.
- I watch YouTube videos to just fall asleep,
and it's really--
- Well, but I also watch YouTube videos.
I also watch a couple of YouTube videos, yeah.
- See, what you're doing is you're having your cake
and you're eating it too.
You want everything in the world.
- And I eat a slice of cake every night
before I go to bed.
(laughing)
I'll admit it.
- Every time I smoke weed now,
I have to watch Rick and Morty.
Otherwise, I lose the last--
- No, you did that with everything in your life.
You take a shower, you're like,
oh, I got some downtime.
I'm gonna watch Rick and Morty.
- Yeah, you just love Rick and Morty.
- No, I haven't watched Rick and Morty
since the allegations dropped.
It's kind of ruined my life that he did those things.
- Really? - Yeah.
- Really? - He's a moral watcher.
- Yeah. - Wow, I didn't know
that about you.
I honestly completely forgot about all that.
It wasn't intentional.
It was like I finished rewatching every episode
like two days before that happened.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
No, I mean, it's not like I actually care.
Come on.
- You care?
- No.
- You're basically a secret SJW
and you care about stuff like throwing women downstairs.
You think that's wrong?
'Cause you're an SJW.
- No, I think it's good.
I think it's good.
Don't say that about me.
- Didn't he hit a woman though?
- Yeah, he would just like.
I don't think he shot her.
Speaking of shooting.
He cut her head off and her friend's head.
No, he would just search.
He would go on Twitter and search.
I'm a 16 year old girl on Twitter, and he would message every girl.
No, no, no. He used to be he was a birthday clown,
and then they found a bunch of bodies under his house.
And but he was like this.
He played this clown character.
And that's why I was so surprised.
No, he went to Paris.
So he went to Paris.
It's like Fashion Week event.
OK, he snuck up all the way to the top floor.
Yeah. And he killed the producer, the main producer.
It's a woman producer.
Oh, he's also bald.
Completely unseen.
Charlie Hebdo, they drew that Mohammed picture and he went in there
and he just started busing shots at every single person in the building.
Yeah. Right. Yeah. Yeah.
And he also did 9/11 or something like that.
Yeah. Anyways. And and he gave
and he created the greatest cartoon of all time.
Yeah. Six seasons.
Can you imagine finding out that he gave Eve the apple, though?
That would fuck me up badly.
Yeah. But you know what?
Not my problem.
That would be crazy.
You ever seen Interdimensional Cable?
True. Yeah, that's what I would say.
That's what they're going to call me to the stand.
And his girl, his girlfriend's going to be there.
And she's so black and blue, she can't open her eyes.
And I'm going to say, objection.
Have you seen ants in your eyes, Johnson?
Are you in the audience?
Yes.
Okay.
But I do a full object.
I'm a character witness.
Yeah.
Because I witness, I tell them about every one of my favorite characters on Rick and Morty.
I witnessed the TV show.
The president is funny as a motherfucker.
Okay.
He even kisses on that show.
And plus Mr. Meeseeks.
Oh my goodness.
And Mr. Poopybutthole.
Where does this guy come up with these crass names?
So that's enough for my character witness.
Yep, and then they would probably it would honestly probably stone
the woman to death for sure, and she would deserve it.
Yeah, exactly. Because they would be so upset that she dare go against.
What's another guy from that show?
Birdman Rick Bird.
Yeah, Birdman.
Birdman.
Isn't Birdman going out with a high schooler?
Yes. No fake high schooler.
OK, we're not going to go.
We're not going to do the talking dead about Rick and Morty right now.
I don't want to do it.
I just want to ask this question.
Who is your ideal casting choice to replace Justin
Roiland as the voice of Ricky Jackson?
Just just to be very great choices.
Yeah, I think they should do Tracy Morgan again.
Tracy Morgan be great way again.
He did that for squid billies when the.
Oh, yeah.
Early was racist on Facebook.
That would be so funny if they got him for Rick and Morty.
And he just doesn't.
He's still doing the Tracy Morgan voice for both characters.
God, no different.
No different.
And then they stopped writing them as different people even.
Yeah, there's just one just basically like twin comedy stand up.
Yeah, it'd be perfect.
Yeah, we got to go to the poop universe.
OK.
You disagree.
They start agreeing about everything.
Perfect.
- That sounds like an awesome show.
- It would be perfect.
- I would love to watch it,
but "Cancel Culture" just ended the show
after seven seasons on air.
- No, it's coming back, dude.
- That kills me. - It got canceled.
- It's back. - No, it didn't.
They're bringing it, they're redoing it, man.
- Yeah, they're gonna redo every episode
with a different guy.
- They're gonna go back and they're gonna dub over him.
- They're gonna make every character a woman
and it's gonna be called...
- What's it gonna be called?
You better stop.
(laughs)
- Mary and Ricky.
- Still Ricky?
- But like R-I-C-K-I.
- Oh, okay, like Ricky Lindholm.
- Yeah.
- Ricky and Mary, that's the new guys.
- Okay.
- But they're girls.
- But they're girls now.
- Yep.
- They have pussies and they're always like,
"Oh, my pussy hurts."
- Oh, come on, why does it have to be about somebody's pussy?
- That's what they have.
How many episodes of Rick and Morty have they gone?
Oh, my fucking cock and balls hurt.
There's literally five.
Yeah, it's like not that many.
There's one. Why would they if they did a gender switch version?
Why would they just rehash the same shit of, oh, my fucking pussy hurts.
I mean, I think it's a good show.
It'd be funny. No, no, no.
They would go to the even says at the end of the episode, you ever watch to the end
the credits, get the little teaser for the next episode,
and they say, "It's a good show."
- The idea of a female teaser is driving me completely loco.
- And do you believe him?
- I'm gonna scratch my head.
- I agree with everything I hear.
- Skin off.
- So if someone tells me it's a good show,
I'm gonna believe them.
- Yes it is.
- Wait, you're right.
- My TV tells me everything I need to know.
- That's true.
I hope they do another child incest episode.
- What's up with that?
I don't think you realize what the fuck you just said,
motherfucker.
Child incest, you just said that.
And you said you like that kind of shit.
- Wait, I hope they don't do that.
That's what I said.
- That's what I like to hear in a better way.
- I hope they don't not do that.
- I honestly just like when they,
I like when people get their heads cut off in the show.
I don't care about any of the jokes.
I really like that there's blood all the time.
And if they could be a full show of blood and farts,
kind of doing a yin yang symbol,
and that guy's funny voice,
or Tracy Morgan's funnier voice,
that would be fine by me.
That'd be completely fine with me.
- It's the perfect sensory overload show,
because it's got all the, you know,
crap you wanna see visually.
It's got lasers, it's got blood.
- It's Cocoa Melon.
It is Cocoa Melon for 29 year olds.
- Right, it's Cocoa Melon for adults who smoke weed.
- Yeah, and I'm fine with that.
- Yeah, that's what I want.
- Do they stop trying to make it like a edgy,
funny kid BoJack Horseman, like the first couple seasons?
- I have not seen anything past, I think,
the first season of BoJack Horseman.
- Well, the thing is, he's just like a sad guy.
- I thought he was a horse.
- Yeah, he's a horse.
- He's a sad guy horse.
- But it's way more that he's a horse
than that he's sad, right?
- Well, that's the funny part, that he's a horse.
That's why they don't write any jokes for him
because he's just a horse.
- Is that show still on or is it off now?
- It's over, they finished it.
- Oh, maybe I'll have to finish every single episode.
- I don't think you should.
- Just to make fun of it.
Maybe I'll have to.
- It's a really good show to do laundry to.
That's how I watched every single season.
- Awesome idea for next episode.
We all watch BoJack Horseman and we discuss
the entire show on the show.
Ain't nobody got time for that.
Remember that?
(laughing)
How many episodes is it, do you know?
10?
I think it's like 400.
It's really long, I think,
'cause they made a bunch of 'em.
No.
Here's my problem, bro.
Paul F. Tompkins, you made bro a dog?
Bro, chill.
Yeah.
Why'd you make him a dog?
There's humans in the show.
Speaking of being a guy, have you heard the Gucci Mane song?
I'm a dog. No, no.
This is a line.
Sing it right now.
No, but there's a line in it where he goes, My girlfriend, 21.
And I know that's kind of young, but I only feed her crumbs.
What did he mean by that?
He's trying to keep her skinny.
Yeah, yeah, because he thinks it's the smaller she if she stays the same size,
then she'll be 21 forever. Yeah.
And he's right.
It's kind of young, but if I don't feed her anything,
she's going to stay 21 for the rest of her life pretty much.
True. Yeah.
How late, how old do you two want to live to be?
3000 years old.
30 years, thousand years old.
Yeah, it sounded OK.
I heard you say 3000.
Julio, it really sounded like you were going to just say 30.
And I think you're 26.
I'm 27, I think.
How old are you?
I'm 27.
So you're less than three years away
from what you think is like...
I don't want to die.
You'll be good, ready to go.
What do you mean you want to die?
I said, how old do you want to live to?
You said 30.
I want to live to a...
Yeah, I want to make it to 30.
I'm sure you'll make, but that's like
the highest...
What is the life expectancy in Mexico?
Probably four, five maybe.
What is it like walking through Mexico
like a 3D platformer, just avoiding machetes
that are just right at neck level.
Oh, that's why you've survived so long,
'cause you're taller, so the machetes just hit you--
- It's right big in the shoulders.
- Right in the shoulder, you go, "Ow, fuck."
But it's not that big of a deal,
because it doesn't just chop your head off,
and the cartel guy goes--
- No, no, no, no. - Oh!
- We can't reach the eye.
- Yeah, and they get on each other's shoulders
and try to cut your head off.
- Listen, I told Rex this, but I think,
As soon as one of you makes it to me and visits me,
you're gonna change your whole tune,
and you're gonna be like, "You know what?
"Mexico's the best country in the world."
- Yeah, I'll change my tune.
Yeah, it's like, (imitates trumpet)
Nah, I'm kidding though.
- My throat will be cut, my voice will change.
- Yeah. - That's not true.
- I'll change my tune 'cause it'll just be,
(gasps)
coming out of an open throat hole.
(laughing)
My exposed trachea.
- Nothing's gonna happen to you.
You guys are gonna eat the most delicious food.
- You know what that sounds like?
A cartel trap.
- It was the opening. - Nothing's gonna happen.
- The cartel killed those guys and then they apologized.
They were like, "Yep, black guys."
- Is that what happened?
- Yeah. - The recent--
- Yeah, they did.
- The four people from Houston who went missing?
- So the funny thing is--
- Who were they looking for?
- Some Haitians or some shit.
- They were looking for me.
I get it.
So that shit happened and then as soon as it happened,
like Cam texted me like,
oh, it's so funny how you keep telling me and Pat
that we should just like some medical tourism,
which is, I still think they should do.
But they just killed these four guys or whatever.
And I was like, I don't,
that's a different part of the country.
I'm like, that's not under my jurisdiction.
I can't save those tourists.
I can save you guys.
- Okay, so if the cartel pulled up AK-47s, bazookas,
just straight up grenades.
You, if they pull up to your house
and try to take away Cam and Pat,
you would stop them.
- Yeah, I would stop them with the power of friendship.
- I don't think that they believe in that shit.
- I would teach them about money laundering.
- Yeah.
- I'd become their court judge.
- I think, yeah, Rex would be a good asset.
- Yeah.
- It's all about being a good asset to the cartel.
- I believe full-heartedly that if I was captured
by the cartel, I could befriend them,
with my knowledge.
- That would be so sick.
That'd be so fucking sick.
- Yeah.
- Do white men can't jump.
- Right, white men can't jump
for helping the cartel launder drug money.
- Yeah, well no, maybe just straight up white men can't jump
and you're just doing moves with a human head
and just like fucking fade away threes into a basket.
- They're like, "Yep, you gotta cut this guy's head off
from all the way across the court."
A half-court decapitation.
You know what, I never watched any of those ISIS beheadings or the cartel beheadings.
Why?
I think that's because I really don't like violence.
I hate violence and I hate death.
Didn't we just talk about how you love seeing people's heads cut off like ten minutes ago?
I like toons getting heads cut off.
I like happy tree friends because I don't think toons should be around whatsoever.
human beings that have,
that could be distantly related to me.
I really hate seeing them suffer.
- So, what ever happened to Happy Tree Friends?
Who made that disgusting show?
- Well, they had, they,
who did, whoever made that was just sick.
- Yeah, they were ahead of their time.
- They were sick.
They were sick, if you ask me.
- Yeah, they were dope.
I agree.
- No, no, no, no, they were wrong.
That used to scare the shit out of me when I was a kid.
That's probably why I don't like gore videos.
It was funny how there was always like the one guy who was just like an army vet,
and it would just like loose it and kill everyone.
And that was like literally like every, if not most episodes.
I think that show blends together in my head with Codenamed Kids Next Door.
That is the craziest shit I've ever heard.
Because Codenamed Kids Next Door was actually about two by four technology.
And Tappetree Friends was about decapitating children squirrels.
Yeah, that is so crazy.
There's not even animals.
That's not true.
I don't know what to do.
I had an era of psychosis as a child
where I fully believed that code name Kids Next Door was real.
And I thought that there was a tree stump in my backyard
that if I stood on it the right way, it would suck me to end into a layer.
No, that's why you became out of it.
But my teacher, I did become number one.
Yeah, exactly.
I became a total number one.
No, you did number one.
I forget.
Juvia's the number four.
Yes, yes, fully number four.
And you are the Asian girl.
You're number three.
OK, with your sleeves or maybe five, I don't remember.
I think I think that is the black girl.
Yeah. Number four is the black girl.
Number five is a black girl.
Get out of town.
Number four is the no force, the blonde kid.
That's like cool.
No, you know, that's completely true.
Google it right now.
It was back to the Australian.
You were right. That is number four.
No. Yeah.
Number four is the cool number.
Number four is the Australian boy of kids next door sector.
He has close friends with Hoagie and he has a crush on his teammate Kuki.
It's Kuki three.
Kuki is three and number two is the fat one who I forgot.
Number three is the one that I was thinking about.
The girl with the green shirt.
Yeah. Green shirt. Long sleeves.
Yeah, I was really much in love with her at the time in my life,
but no longer.
I remember what was like Power Rangers pretty much.
just like was that like Power Rangers?
Yes, it's the same show.
Was that like Power Rangers?
Did they fight monsters?
Yes, motherfucker.
But OK, you remember Power Rangers?
What they fight in Power Rangers?
Robot aliens.
What they're fighting?
Codenames kids next door.
Probably adults.
I don't remember.
Adults ended at 1.6 other children
who were tied together as a six
person twins.
I remember that.
- That was weird.
- Called The Kids,
or I don't remember what they were called.
But they were probably--
(laughing)
Some kind of The Kids thing.
So I bet now you got a little bit
of a TV Tropes education from me.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, you're welcome.
- I came up, nope, I still don't know anything
about the show.
I forgot completely about the show.
Eddie and Eddie, that's basically the Power Rangers too.
- I love that show. - Eddie and Eddie,
that's basically us. - That's not true.
- That is true.
I'm Double D. - Yeah, and we're just--
- And I'm Double D, wait.
You think you're Double D?
- I'm obviously Double D.
You're Eddie.
- I would heavily disagree with you.
- You're Eddie. - You, wait, okay.
We can say this. - You're completely Eddie.
- I'll be Eddie, you be Double D,
Jubio's Plank. - Just go with it.
(laughing)
- Yeah. - No.
You are the piece of wood with kind of an eternal forced smile
right on your face in blue crayon.
You're the Welsh kid that tries to eat goats.
The Welsh? You think he's Welsh?
He's Scottish, isn't he?
Is he? I don't know.
-Wolf? -Wolf?
I watched it in Spanish.
Oh, true.
-So he's eating weird stuff. -I don't think he was Scottish.
I think he was Middle Eastern.
-No. -Yes.
- Go look up a picture of him right now.
Rolf.
Ed, Ed and Eddie, he's definitely Middle Eastern.
- Drinking, just drinking, just mixed drinks.
- He's an immigrant from a far and distant culture
known to us only as the old country.
He's Borat.
That's what he is, he's a hunter.
- He is Borat.
- He's Borat, dude.
- What an awesome show.
- What's another cartoon that we can Google right now?
- Another cartoon?
- You know which one I liked a lot?
I liked Billy and Mandy.
- Billy and Mandy was, did you ever watch,
what was the one before Billy and Mandy
that had the Grim Reaper in it?
You remember what I'm saying?
Grim and Evil? - No.
- Mm, I don't think that was before Billy and Mandy.
- Yeah, it was.
- What is that?
- You don't remember Grim and Evil?
- I have no idea what that is now.
- Well, it basically came out in 2001.
And they were eventually spun off into their own series, Grim Adventures of Billy and Mandy
and Evil Con Carne.
Evil Con Carne, let's be real guys, flop.
Giant flop.
I don't even worry about that.
Yeah, but Billy and Mandy, they had everything.
They were on top of the world at one point.
Billy was basically unstoppable.
Mandy was like a classic bitch.
Yeah, true.
They make Mandy a hundred times a year now.
what Wednesday is. Wednesday is just true. Mandy. Aubrey Plaza ripped her whole
shit from Mandy. Yep, that's true. And some say that that Patrick ripped his whole
shit from Billy. I would never say that about him. Yep. Do you think Patrick and
Cameron listen to these? No, no chance. I think they do. No, I don't think so. I
I think Pat does.
That's cute.
He's listening right now.
Well, that's fine because we...
Well, you banished both of them.
Did I banish them? I don't remember that.
You took an official decree, I think...
I don't know if it was on the stream or on a meeting,
where you said,
"Cam and Pat are never allowed to come on the show."
Oh, yeah, they're never allowed to come on the show.
No doubt.
Yeah, so they're completely banished from the show.
Yeah.
So I don't think Cam would...
I think Cam doesn't care.
He would respect that.
He would respect that also, that boundary that I've set.
that I've said of this is a man, this is a men's space.
Yeah.
But Pat, I think you setting that boundary would make Pat want to listen to it.
Exactly.
He's such a, oh, he's a boundary pusher.
I think if one person on like the Discord on Twitter just messaged him and was like,
"Yo Pat, they talked about you on Bruce Willis," he would listen to all five episodes in a
single day.
That's okay.
Yeah, I mean, what else does he have to do?
Get hit by a car.
He will die by a car.
It only takes like 10, 15 seconds.
It only takes like 10-15 seconds.
You got your whole day ahead of you after that.
Yeah, he's got a personal assistant.
It's like, Patrick, we have a car hitting scheduled for about 10-15.
Can I talk to you guys about my diet that I've been doing that I'm too scared to talk
about on the normal show because I think too many people hear it?
I've been doing a diet.
Okay.
Where I eat only.
I'm sorry.
It was a joke.
I'm sorry, it was a joke.
You're ruining the reveal, dude.
Yeah, by fucking guessing it instantly.
No, I only eat fruit,
veg, as my brothers across the pond might call it.
I call it vegetables, but they may say veg.
And red meat. That's all I've been eating for three days.
That sounds fine.
And how do you feel?
Here's the fucked up part.
That's a stupid diet.
A lot of people do this diet and they start selling pills on Instagram and they have brown
white bodies.
They're white people who have completely brown bodies and they say it's completely because
of the meat that I've been eating.
So the horrible thing about this is that I don't know that I've felt better in my life
in the past three days that I've been eating just meat, fruit and veg.
I can't believe it.
It sounds really healthy.
Healthy diet.
Yeah, I don't know what's...
It sucks.
Yeah.
That's a normal diet.
The only difference is that there's no bread and cheese, which I know as a mouse is like
got to be really hard for you, but...
You're not eating any cheese?
Yo, I would be lying if I didn't say that I had one tablespoon of blue cheese today.
I had one tablespoon of blue cheese in my salad.
Isn't that just keto?
Isn't that what keto is?
I never learned what keto is.
I thought keto paleo carnivore were all the exact same thing.
I thought they were the same thing as vegan.
What's keto?
Me, you know what I've eaten past day?
What?
I'm going to write it down.
Hit me.
Handful of peanut butter pretzels.
Six freezer burned meatballs.
Is that the brand?
No.
Just found them in the back of the freezer.
Okay, Rex's personal brand to I would lowkey believe that monsters.
Two of them.
Okay.
A coffee and a diet Coke.
You ate two whole monsters.
I did.
It wasn't in a single day.
Were they
about the size of this can?
I would barely call it a monster.
Yeah.
More like a critter.
So I got a brown sugar pop tart.
That's gotta be one of that's gotta be the worst diet I've ever
heard anybody say.
And also not that's the kind of diet that I can't believe you
remembered it beat by beat.
Yeah, like it's you really only remember the good diets like
that. You should have said what I've been eating the last few
days, whatever.
I don't remember. Who cares?
You also you live in a place where there's like a million
people who would just come to your house and give you an
influencer.
I'm not rich.
You're rich enough that you can eat like broccoli and grilled chicken every meal.
You can have a slave that delivers you a healthy meal once a day.
No, I can't.
Yes, you can. What do you mean you can't?
I was. You know, I go to the grocery store, I buy a bunch of
brussel sprouts and chicken, things like that, and I eat that.
And then I run out of that, and it just becomes chaos.
Get what you can get.
Kettle corn, boogers off the wall.
Yep.
Just keep going, just eating whatever.
Yeah.
I've been there, man.
Just licking the inside of a beef jerky bag.
See, and if you can get some of those little specks, where you're like, "I don't know if
this is like silica stuff, like gel, or if this is actual beef."
I think that I permanently destroyed my gut microbiome by being the worst version of a
a vegan for until I was 17.
I just ate mustard and bread until I was 17 years old.
Never once in a while I'd have an avocado.
I'd be like, well, that's that was spinach.
Yeah, I have been shitting
so bad my ass.
Let's talk about it.
Your ass burns all the time.
It hurts. It hurts. Yeah.
And because and it's partially because I'm in there
after taking a shit four times a day,
full blast bidet on my hole.
Just the strongest jet of water.
OK, I would like anybody listening to go back, I think two episodes
and hear how these goons laughed at me when I said that I,
every once in a while, would stick my entire finger up my asshole.
And this guy,
this guy, by the way, this guy, his own finger isn't enough.
He needs an element that goes into his asshole.
That's what he needs.
- We already talked about how you need a bidet.
You would actually, after you told us about the finger
and the ass, I think you would really enjoy it.
- If you saw my ass, you would not be saying anything
about a bidet.
You'd say, actually, it needs more shit on it.
That's how clean it is.
- Okay, now walk us through your ass cleaning technique.
- Yeah. - Okay.
I take five baths a day, right?
One after every single shit.
And with my face under the water,
I viciously scrub my ass with steel wool to get all of the poop
particulate away and floating around that pool.
But it's out. It's it's balanced out because I put Epsom salt in it.
So then I'm in there.
And then while I'm in there, I'm training to become the first person
to be able to breathe underwater.
So I'm inhaling every single one of these poop particulates
because I think that it might make me stronger.
And you're right.
OK, you are becoming stronger.
Look at you. I know.
I was a little flexed today.
Buddy, I have a...
I have a...
Actually, you know what? Never mind.
This is how ripped I'm getting.
This is the color of my skin now.
This is just purely my skin.
I don't have anything on. I'm shirtless.
What's that on your chest right there?
That's a new tattoo that I got.
What does it say?
It says, "Port City Tattoo, Port City."
That's in Wilmington, North Carolina.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Because I put "Port City" and I was like,
"Well, I want people to know it's a tattoo."
So I put "tattoo" underneath it.
Okay, is there anything on the back?
On your back?
Yeah, there's a giant eye.
That's dope.
A couple months ago I was in Chicago
doing stand-up and I got off stage
and I was wearing this sweatshirt
and this lady came up to me.
She's the drunkest I've ever seen somebody be at a comedy show.
And she grabbed my ears.
Like grabbed my head like this and went,
"Do you like Tool?"
And I was like, yeah, I like tool. This is how,
if a woman hurts me in public, I won't do, I can't do it. I won't do anything.
And why would you, I really will just sit there and I'll take,
like a woman can abuse me on the train or whatever.
She can yell straight in my face. She can throw things at me.
And it really scares me the idea that I would ever react at all. Yeah.
I just sat there and she screamed in my face. She said, do you like tool?
And I, she's holding my ears and I go, uh, yeah,
"Oh yeah, I like Tool."
And she was like--
With a smile?
Yeah, I was like, "Oh yeah, I actually do like Tool, yeah."
And then she was like, "Good."
And then she kinda like threw my head away from her face.
She was like, "Because your shirt
"reminds me of a Tool album cover."
And that was the shirt?
It was this one that I have on right now.
And it doesn't look anything like a Tool album cover.
But I think it was more that she saw me on stage
She saw my big ears come out of the side of my bald head.
And she said, I need to grab those and try this face like a steering wheel.
And so she did.
That was the first thing that she could think of.
Yeah, she was like, yeah, he probably likes to.
It doesn't matter what she says at all.
Yeah. You'd remember it no matter what.
Mm hmm. She could ask you how your day was. Exactly.
Tools, tools, dope.
I got into tool way too late in life.
I got into Tool three years ago and I was babysitting.
The last one, really?
Fear Inoculum, huh?
Yeah.
It's better than people say it is, I'll say that much, but I don't want to get too controversial.
I like that album a lot.
I got into Tool and I was babysitting these...
I was...
I would, like, nanny these kids who were, like, really rich and they would go to, like...
I'd, like, drive one to fencing all the time.
But I kind of took it on myself to, like...
Because these kids just had the most busted home life.
Like their dad is just, like, the biggest wimp in the world and their mom is, like...
Their mom had a full mustache.
I swear to God, she had, like...
Like the same level of mustache that I have right now.
She was like a crunchy Massachusetts, like a rich hippie.
And I was like, I need to show these kids one cool thing.
And for whatever reason in my brain, I was like, this is perfect.
I'll play tool, like over our conversation, like really loudly over our conversations
when I pick them up from fencing class.
And I tried it three different times and every single time
they told me to put on Happy by Pharrell instead.
(laughing)
'Cause that was their favorite song.
- That's a good song.
- And every single time I was like,
"You know what, I actually wanna listen to Happy."
That's a fucking dope song.
- That is a dope song.
Pharrell, that's a genius.
- Yeah.
Wait, where does he keep that big brain?
- Probably in his big hat.
- No!
- He doesn't wear that anymore, I don't think.
- That's why he hasn't been anything good since Happy.
- He wears it every day at Stapledoo's head.
- That's not true.
- Okay, Mythbusters, shut the fuck up.
- Yeah.
- Wait, I wanna talk about,
no, we're talking about morality earlier.
I wanna talk about how Rex got banned off Twitter.
- Oh, I did, I got banned.
I'm currently serving a seven day ban.
- You're banned for what?
What did you do?
I'm looking right now.
- It's gone already, but--
- Listen, do long story uncensored of what you said.
I'm not gonna say what I know Jordan Peterson is back on Twitter this week
okay you're already in the clear in my eyes yeah you I don't care if you called
him the most despicable racial slur on earth he was posting some shit about
like AI like he's asking like chat GPT to say good things about Donald Trump
and then good things about Joe Biden it used more words to talk about Joe Biden
Oh God making some points about how this is like proof that it's woke AI or some shit.
Yeah, yeah, and then he at Elon Musk and Lex Fridman two smartest men in the world.
He says, you know, like, you know, paging these two.
What's a what's a rational minded person to think about all this?
and I said that you are in r/fslr and Twitter immediately was like are you
sure you want to send this tweet? And he said yes sir I do! I was like a hundred percent I know I'm in trouble for this.
You're right I'm not sure I'm very sure let me click the green button right now.
And like that it was like all right delete now. Wow and they gave you an
- Instantly, within like 10 seconds I was serving a seven day.
- I just remember I woke up, I think it was on a Tuesday or...
- Oh yeah.
- I woke up to four Discord messages from Rex, where his appeal being...
- I appealed it.
- You want to go through your appeal?
- Yeah, I appealed it.
So I sent this to Juby, I'll read it verbatim, give me a sec.
So what I said was, you know, "I was suspended for seven days instantly for calling Jordan
Peterson an r-slur f-slur.
I understand this can be shocking language.
However, Jordan Peterson is an advocate for free speech and I believe he would not like
it if I was suspended.
Just as I advocate for his right to spew things I disagree with, I think context matters."
Completely true.
- That's absolutely true.
- I submitted that, and you'll never believe it,
I was not immediately unsubmitted.
- Context matters.
That is a bold, bold defense, I'll say that much.
- I'm right.
I stand by that I'm right there.
- I think you're right. - I think you are right.
- But the context there is just that you think that,
like, it's just that Jordan Peterson
is exactly what you said he is.
- Yeah.
- Like, the context is like, oh, but if you look at it,
I'm actually completely right about what I said.
I should not have been...
Obviously I get that you can't say that shit on Twitter anymore.
Arsler, Efsler, whatever, you can't say either of those really.
The issue I think was that he had tagged Elon Musk and therefore Elon Musk was tagged in
Arsler.
Oh, everything always, yeah, just gets instantly...
Even though it was not directed at Elon.
I have no, you know, there's no love laws between Elon and I, but not directed at him.
He has a beast.
Yeah, Elon's dope, dude.
Yeah, he would love our style.
I honestly, the one I thought he was so whack until he fired every single person.
Yeah, that shit's dope.
That is so cool.
I think the funniest one of those, one of those firings was the one, the woman that was like,
captures like sleeping on our office, like,
oh, yeah, I got to like put in the time or whatever if we want to steer the ship.
And like two months later, she was fired and she was like, listen,
I know I was fired, but I'm sure it was for a good reason.
I would love to become Elon Musk and have you two as my like handlers
to stop me from being retarded and I wouldn't do shit.
This would be full devil and angel.
This is like I'd be like, yeah, say the guy was gay
because he was in a wheelchair.
And that's why that was the fun.
That was dope.
That was like he was like, by the way, the guy was in a wheelchair.
Yeah, he doesn't even fucking work.
Oh, yeah. Good fucking fire.
Yeah. Literally like won four awards for being the best guy in Iceland.
The best guy in the entire country.
He's like, no, you don't understand.
His legs were not.
They were not good legs. Yeah.
So I like how he's like, oh, he says he can't work,
but he won't stop treating me.
Yeah, I don't know.
Yeah, you can just yell at your phone.
I can tweet while I'm driving.
In fact, I do.
In fact, I do. Yeah, I scream at my phone.
I have awful news about New York City,
New York.
They have stepped up the traffic patrol
to what I would say is a CCP communist China level.
No. OK.
What do you mean?
Somebody the other day, they dropped me off in front of my apartment, right?
And you guys know I live right next to an intersection.
So they drop me off, they pull into the intersection, and I see them instantly get pulled over, like
literally 15 feet away from me, get pulled over by a tiny NYPD traffic car and get a
$140 ticket for texting while driving because they were putting in their home coordinates.
to their home planet on their phone.
- Yeah.
- While they were in the intersection.
- That's so sad.
- And I've heard three more stories like that this week.
So I would like any NYC motorist to know, it's not safe.
We used to think, oh yeah, it's fun.
You go, you have 10, 12 drinks over in New Jersey,
you can drive all the way back to Long Island
and nobody's gonna bother you.
The pigs are out, they smell blood.
- Oh yeah.
Cut the race arms.
It's time. It's time.
You know what it is?
It's time to race them.
Yeah. If the if the cops start following you, floor it.
I'm going to erase them.
I don't think that's right.
Could you run?
I don't think you can outrun the cops in the New York City cops.
You can because they have they have smart cars.
And I have a kick ass 2009 Ford Focus that has the
has the hood zip tied down.
Yeah. So I feel like after a few blocks,
you'll just like end up like hitting,
like there's a woman like spilling out her car
in the weirdest way possible
and you can't move for five minutes.
- Well, that's the inevitable thing.
You could absolutely do like a burnout paradise style.
- That's what I was thinking is just like,
- Jump through a billboard.
- Anything you could say.
- No, you could just fucking just run them off the road.
Just, you know, have them go into like a stoplight.
- Anything you could say,
oh, what if this happens on the road?
Buddy, I'll drift.
- Yeah.
of drifting because I'll just drift.
I just destroy every billboard in the city.
I do like driving like that complete shit.
I love scoring it and just love being a traffic driving like shit,
because it's awesome because you still can think you're a good driver
for the rest of your life.
Yeah, I see it in in women when they drive and they like,
like, dude, oh, my God, when
when when wifey drives, oh, I am a
I am a menace, bro.
I'm saying, Mr.
Turn signal.
Right.
I'm like, don't look at your phone.
Look at the road.
Oh, there's a pedestrian.
The pedestrians, they have the right away.
Dude, when I drive and she's not in there,
man, I literally I'm not kidding.
I've been on the highway and I've said I've said to myself,
I've been like, I wonder how long I can drive with my eyes closed before it scares me.
By the way, eight seconds, eight full seconds.
Mississippi seconds.
Damn. Before I went, Oh, I got to open these again.
I used to be such a menace on the road, dude.
Running red lights just the hell of it.
I would go 100 plus miles an hour all the time.
Cool car. I had a Lincoln LS.
Oh, look like a BMW.
Fastest car ever.
Yeah. What's your dream car?
We keep talking.
I'm going to go get my my Aperol Spritz. Um.
I'm not sure.
Yeah, I don't really have a dream car.
I used to when I was a kid, I really liked like Jaguars
because of like, there would be like some like racing game
and like a PS2 game that my cousin had.
But I got to like, I think I googled it and I think Jaguars
are like notoriously bad to own.
Yeah, when I when I was looking for cars, and I went to like
this used car place, I got to sit in a Jaguar.
It's like Revit and it was pretty cool.
Like the car is like looks awesome or whatever,
but I could tell that it was like it was going to be expensive to buy and like upkeep.
Yeah, so I think just like I don't know like like an 86 maybe I would love to just have like a small sports car that I can just drive on the weekends.
So for me this is this is a story.
So when I was a kid, I was friends with this like there was like one kid in my neighborhood that had a PS2 and I would go to his house.
like every day to play like Crash Bandicoot.
'cause like my mom didn't let me have video games.
They were too mature for my nine year old brain and.
He like his parents opened a sushi restaurant that became
like a huge like thing like they got like really rich from
opening like a sushi chain.
No boo.
It's called raw and whoa.
No, I know it's like local to Arizona.
But I remember he like moved and then he was like neighbors with like like the
pitcher for the Diamondbacks which is like Randy Johnson and then like his dad
bought a Lotus Elise and I would see his dad driving around and to me that was like
that's what making it is is when you can... That's a Lotus? Yeah like a Lotus you know
just like a stupid sports car that only you drive. So that is kind of the dream
right is to get a car that you don't allow anyone inside.
That is sick.
I saw today I saw a Maybach parked on my block
and I had I don't think I've ever seen one in real life before,
but I kind of was it was like parked in front of a Chase bank.
And I was like, it was parallel parked.
Of course, dude, pay for there's a parking lot
like two blocks away. Go pay for a parking.
I'm going to break into your car.
Yeah, I should break into your car. Yeah.
It was like it was like a 2003 Maybach, though.
It's like not that good.
Oh, not impressive at all.
Yeah, it's like probably 100k or something.
I love the I love the parallel parking situation in New York.
But it's not.
It's not good enough that it's impossible to find a spot
that you can't even keep because the street sweeping.
You also have to worry about every week.
You also have to worry about every single driver in the city bumping,
just hitting your car in the bumper.
And so you have to buy special shields for it.
Like for. Yeah.
Oh yeah, the dino bumper and stuff like that.
Yeah, the bumper bulldog.
I think it's awesome, but I just accept it to that part
where you have to buy armor for your car.
I think it's cool, man.
Yeah.
I think it is cool.
I just think it's really funny.
I could buy a 2006 Maybach 57S for $69,000 in Miami, Florida.
Yeah.
Wait.
And you know there's no rust on that.
I have 1,500 bucks in my bank.
That's a down payment.
This is easy.
It is crazy.
And it's got that early GPS.
Yeah.
That has way too many buttons and a really tiny screen.
And it doesn't work anymore.
Yeah, exactly.
It just stays in Miami, Florida for the rest of the car's life.
Yeah, it's got like a red triangle with like a circle around it.
That's so cool.
You know what you should buy, Caleb?
You should buy a Citroen AMI.
I think that's what it's called.
called. It's a micro car that's
essentially just like a scooter.
And I've been seeing so many videos
about these like small cars just like
flipped over.
And like one of them was like in
Monaco, just like drifting it and
like falling over.
And they're like so cheap
and so small. People just like buy
them just like you treated them like
those like scooters that
not sold in the United States.
No, you can only buy it in France.
That's all.
I think I'm going to import one into Mexico and have it explode.
How much does it cost?
I think it's like less than $10,000.
I think I'm going to buy, I really want to buy a Maverick.
What's that?
It's like one of those really, it's a Ford.
It's like a really small pickup truck that like is made for guys who coach soccer teams.
I know what you're talking about.
Like the C10?
Wait, they discontinued it?
No, they didn't.
Well, maybe they did.
But I really want one because they're like pretty cheap,
but they're really shitty.
And you can get them, you get like a new one for like $20,000,
like a brand new one.
That's you know, I found out in electric cars,
they have a little speaker that like makes engine noise.
Yeah, because like, yeah, they're silent.
But like people need to feel when they're like pressing on the gas.
Well, they also you need.
Do they have an external speaker to know?
No, just some of them do. Some of them do. But there's one like
in the in the cabin. And it's funny to imagine some guys just
being like,
well, the funny thing about that is it's not only electric
courses, like a lot of modern cars. I think when I was looking
at cars, I was looking at the what's the the fucking the
Volkswagen one that's like based on the Jetta. Oh, the GTI golf.
Yeah, the the the the July. So you can buy buy one of those
like brand new and it's like a nice looking car, whatever.
But it has like exactly that for like,
even for like a car with an engine that takes gas,
it will pump in like fake engine noise into the cabin.
So you don't think that you're driving like a--
- That's adorable.
That is so adorable.
- Right?
- Yeah.
- That's literally putting a--
- That's a feature for boomers.
- You might as well put a soda can
between the spokes of the car.
- Literally.
like a motorcycle.
That is so fucking cool.
- Yeah.
It's so cool how fucking, that's like a brain parasite.
Dude, I think I have to buy one of these,
one of these Ford Mavericks.
I would look so gangsta in this.
- Yeah.
- It's between for me.
- You should get a skull tattoo.
- I definitely need to buy a new car today.
A skull tattoo?
- Yeah.
- Buddy, I have a skull tattoo.
- This thing is huge. - On your head.
- What the fuck?
- That's dope though.
- What, the Ford Maverick?
The Maverick is, what the hell?
These are biggest fucks.
It's like a tiny version of a,
it's smaller than an F-150.
Oh.
Yeah, that's why I want it.
I might be looking at the wrong one
because these are like double, double cabin.
Maybe you're looking at the XL, XXL,
or XLT or the Lariat.
Yeah, I might be looking at the biggest car of all time.
It's double cabin, it's a cruelly they call that.
Or maybe that's a dually, I don't remember.
No, dually's the double wheels.
Yeah, dually's it.
It's a cruelly, but it has the--
Yeah, dually has two wheels.
Dually, duels.
Okay. Oh, okay.
But it has the,
it has a very short bed,
I think, is where they cut the space.
Because, listen,
I'm going to be real with you.
I'm not going to be walking around moving two by fours, right?
I'm not in Codename Kids next door.
I'm not trying to make a gun that shoots rubber bands.
Yep.
I just want to move,
I want to go and do 500 Uber Eats orders at once.
And make 60 bucks
in 14 hours and then go to sleep.
You know?
That's, you know what, what that is, that's perfect dog space.
I would yeah, exactly. Just put the dog in there. He immediately
jumps.
I, I did see a video earlier today about a guy where he was
like, you may have seen this. It's this like, model dude, this
like really good looking like middle aged black dude who is
like, he was talking about the least money he's ever made in a
year was $100,000. And he was like, I had,
I had four jobs and one of them was, I was like a fitness trainer,
a tutor, a, uh,
restaurant manager on the weekends and an Uber Eats driver in every spare moment
I had. And I did have a moment yesterday where I was like, man,
maybe I need to start just driving Uber Eats right now and just fucking crushing
it, making six bucks an hour. Yeah. I tried,
I did it one time in college, I did Postmates, but I activated it and then I got
one order and I got way too nervous and I just turned off my phone.
I did it for a little bit when I didn't have a job. Yeah. Yeah.
They send you a Postmates credit card and then they send you the bag.
I have the bag sitting in my car. I have the bag sitting in the back of my car.
It was fine. I mean, that's what it is. Everyone in my house did it.
So I was like, well, I'll just do it.
Every once in a while I get one of those like TikToks where it's a guy just like
doing like DoorDash, like some city in Texas for like a full 10 hours.
Yeah.
And be like, "Oh, I made like 500 bucks," or whatever.
And I'm like, "Dude, I need to move to the US illegally and do this right now."
I felt it not even like, there's no reason that I need the money.
I just honestly was like, "Maybe I'm not grinding hard enough right now.
Maybe I need to be doing construction during the day and doing Uber Eats at night."
I mean, you're doing the
show, the equivalent of that,
which is doing two podcasts a week.
It does like I got the fuck of truth.
I'm waiting more than that, actually.
I am hurting.
No, I see.
Now you guys are starting to get it right.
How so?
We're five weeks into this.
How hard is this?
It's hard.
It's fucking hard.
It's hard because I have a full time job to also.
I also have no.
I also have a job.
Sort of.
No, it's not either of those.
It's hard because it's exhausting physically and emotionally and mentally exhausting.
That is true.
You do have to, you have to come into a...
It's basically the hardest job on earth.
Yeah, I do feel like this one's really fresh because we took so long to record it.
I think the next one, I think the one after this one is going to be complete shit.
Nah, it'll be great.
What we should do is we should always delay, it should be an every nine days podcast.
The first of its kind.
Yeah.
Well, it's like getting off of the base 10 system.
Move into a whole new reality.
Yeah, I'm gonna move into Rex's reality.
Into his house.
Can I ask you guys one question before we wrap this up?
How old do you think the earth is?
Probably 10 years, 30 years maybe.
I think seven billion.
Very funny, I'd actually like you to take this seriously
for once in your fucking life, Rex.
Probably 5,486 years.
That's what I like to hear.
I've been getting very into these guys who keep going on Joe Rogan and being like,
yeah, basically the earth is like 50,000 years old.
And from the very first second the earth was made, there was guys who were making
cell phones in Egypt, which is very cool.
And that's true.
I've been pretty obsessed with those.
That's true.
Graham Hancock.
You know that guy?
No.
That's a fake name that you have to get into.
It's not someone you have to get into Graham Hancock.
He's he claims that Joe Rogan immediately dies after they go in there.
Well, I'm really getting scared for this guy who ate woolly mammoth meat.
Is he sick?
You know about that guy?
You told me about him, but is he OK?
What happened to him?
He's completely fine.
But it does worry me that I feel like that's the kind of thing
where like the FBI gets that
that that facts that a man ate woolly mammoth.
And they say that's a flavor
that nobody should ever experience.
And they maybe do an MLK to him.
Right. Well, they're going to bring him back.
You know that.
They're willing to bring back that guy.
They're going to clone him.
Yeah, I don't give a fuck about.
Dude, why are they trying to play?
They're going to drop new woolly mammoth.
Woolly mammoth 2 dropping in 2024.
Do you guys join?
Do you guys join me in hating
when humanity plays God?
Now I love it.
Oh Christ.
I hate that shit.
If somebody ever tried to create a second Earth, I would probably try to stop it.
I would help them.
You're an asshole.
Nope.
And episode done.