Hello Podcast "About List" fans. This is a free sample of the podcast "Beers We Drank",
hosted by Caleb Jubio and their friend Rex. You can listen to this podcast exclusively
on the $5 tier on our Patreon, patreon.com/podcastaboutlist.
[Sip]
[Burp]
- Welcome to the first ever Beers We Drink.
- Wait, we gotta pop the seal.
- Oh my God.
- Yummy.
- Okay, so.
- Cheers.
- Cheers my friends.
- Just start off.
- Oh that's great.
- Today's Beers We Drink is a special one.
We're in person, we got Noah here.
Noah. What's up?
OK, so we got these three
beers at the supermarket.
They're the most weird looking beers
of all time.
But that was over there
and the show.
The show is not going to end until
we everyone drinks their
perspective beer.
This one don't count.
This is maybe we'll get to those.
Yeah. If you finish all three before
somebody's finished their third, you
get to move on to the Miller High
List.
Guys, this is so much better
than the normal podcast.
Oh my God.
It feels really good.
You all are just sitting at your computers.
He loves the beer.
He loves the sour ale.
What the fuck?
It tastes good.
It's sour candy.
This is, we're drinking right now Bronx Brewery City Island Sour India Pale Ale.
This is not the kind of sour, I honestly thought you were about to pull up with the slushies.
Yeah, I didn't see the slushies.
Oh, what the smooch is?
Yeah, the smoothies.
Do people still make those or is that a fad?
Smoothie beer?
I never even had them.
Yeah, you did.
No, I didn't.
The moon, whatever.
Oh a fruited sour.
Those are like the smoothie beers.
These were like $40 and so those would have been like $60.
Yeah they are like the most expensive beers in the world.
Fruited sours are so expensive and they make you really fat.
Yeah. It's dope.
Went to like a liquor store this morning, we were like oh after having like a lunch breakfast type thing.
And we were like oh let's just see if they got beers.
And we just like looked like two little children being like oh I want to buy some alcohol.
saw a bunch of liquor and wines and we're like, okay, no, we're not,
I don't want to fuck with any of this.
And we went to the supermarket and we saw the funniest looking beers of all time.
We're like, Oh yeah, this is my shit.
These are funny beers.
Even if they did think y'all were underage, they would still sell them to you.
This beer is hurting me so badly. I don't know. I think it's, it's just like,
it's very sour. It's like drinking Fanta.
Like I feel fucked up from it.
Yeah. We have to talk more about the beers, the components and the tastes.
I mean, it's very, very sour.
It's really sour.
It really gets into your throat and attacks you.
It gets into your... I feel like I'm rotting my teeth with this one.
It's a lot of green apple.
I'm getting a lot of crisp green apple from this.
Yeah, it tastes like a sour candy.
It's a little too much, I'm going to be honest.
I agree.
But...
Also, it's an IPA.
Let's power through this one.
Yeah.
Just destroy it?
Let's get the fuck through this one.
I'm not going to destroy it. I can't destroy it.
You can't? You can't.
That's a loser mindset.
I know we did. This is our first ever guest. There's a couple of things about this. This
is big for us. Number one, I never want to have a comedian on this show. That's not what
this is about. This is for the working man. This is for the every man. The working man,
the working man, the working man, the working man.
Y'all work the hardest out of everybody here.
No doubt, dude. Also, I do kind of like the idea of we just only have bartenders.
(laughing)
- No, we don't want--
- This is his job.
- Do y'all know anyone else who bartends?
- No, yeah, I know a couple people.
- I mean, I know bartenders.
- Oh, you know Daddy?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Oh, we should get Daddy.
- The Brooklyn bartender.
- Yeah, Daddy.
- Come on, everybody bartender.
- The other Brooklyn bartender, Mommy.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Daddy and Mommy.
- Yeah, Daddy and Mommy at Brooklyn.
They should come through.
Yeah, I don't work at Brooklyn.
- But this is what I want, man.
I wanted to get him a job there when we first moved.
I tried to, I applied, I gave them my resume and everything.
And you weren't good enough for the video game bar.
Yeah, for the video game bar.
I think I did okay.
Yeah, you're doing alright.
I think you'll make it there at some point.
I hope not.
I hope not, dude.
It's going to be a big step.
Okay, so let's talk about this.
Because I think eventually us four, we will be four person owning a bar at some point.
Yeah.
I was talking to Julio about opening a Brooklyn.
Really?
Oh yeah.
Copy?
Wow.
This morning he was like, we were just eating breakfast and he was like,
how do you think like Brooklyn operates?
I'm like, I don't fucking know.
Okay.
So for people who don't know, Brooklyn is a bar.
It's in Brooklyn that is a bar and then it is also like a
lander cafe.
A lander cafe.
Yeah.
Basically where there's computers, you can play video games on them.
And we're there, man, probably three nights a week.
Yeah.
It's so expensive.
A hundred dollars each time.
Yeah, it's so expensive.
It's so expensive.
So what would you do differently there?
So my thing was year pass for the computer.
Whoa.
See, and I think this is a good idea, but I think he's thinking too much like pro-consumer.
Like the thing at Brooklyn is they charge you way too much for a day pass, and if you
just want like five hours, it's like just five dollars less.
And that's all you can get.
So he has to go more anti-consumer.
consumer. He has to be like, you can only get the day pass into a hundred bucks.
And also every beer is a hundred dollars as well.
That's a good theme for a bar.
Yeah. Like a dollar tree.
You just make it like a suicide beer.
You just pour every empty you find that people don't finish into a pot.
And then you have a crazy nasty beer.
I'm sorry to change the topic instantly.
I saw a haunting video today.
What?
of somebody dumpster diving outside of a PetSmart and they found a bunch of
hamsters and fish
that were alive.
The fish were alive? What about that?
They just like put the aquarium in the trash.
Just like a Krispy Kreme, oh these are from yesterday.
Dude, just fucking, just put them in the toilet.
What are you doing at the trash can? Feed them to the snakes.
Yeah, you have a whole food chain. And the snakes will eat them and become...
Make use of the food chain, bro.
Exactly. That's savings.
Yeah, food for the shark.
Yeah.
This is the good business savvy type of mindset that we need for the...
Yeah, money makers podcast.
Actual money makers podcast is this one.
Yeah, no doubt.
The one in the middle of the week was a facade.
I see four grinders right here.
He completely didn't want to speak because he didn't want to share any actual trade tickets,
but he's going to share them right now today.
Yeah.
And he's not going to get disappointed.
He's not...
(laughter)
- I didn't listen, I don't care.
- Here's four ways to make money.
Feed the hamsters to the snake.
- That is a saving on food.
- You can steal other people's pets
to feed to your pet snake as well.
- Yeah.
- Oh yeah, that's true.
- Just a dog.
- Cut 'em up.
- Yeah, you're gonna need to cut it up.
- No, they like 'em alive.
The snake's like, why do they do that?
Why is it, you go to the zoo,
they're all about feeding rabbits and stuff.
Why don't they feed them just food?
- My girlfriend, her snake, he was a live snake
when she got him and she cried every time
she had to feed him a mouse.
Just 'cause it screams, it screams.
- Wait, she was feeding him live mice?
- Yeah, you feed him live mice.
- She tried, she was like, I can't.
- They like the struggle.
- Yeah, yeah, they like the fights.
- Wait, what is she gonna snake for?
- Why do you get the cruelest possible animal
as a pet for a girl?
The girls love snakes, dude. You're gonna need to talk to her more about it.
Oh, I'm feeling like getting a pet. I think I'm gonna get an orca.
She likes snakes. She also likes... You feed it like once a week. It's a very low
mean. It's like a cactus. Well, but think about this.
So you want a succulent as an animal? Exactly. Exactly. But when you feed a...
You have to feed a dog twice a day, but when you feed a dog, you feed it pebbles.
Yeah, yeah. You don't... Nothing screams. It's honestly the one time you don't
have to think about the animal. Yeah, screams and tears are tucked, dude.
They get fake food. Yeah. A dog would fucking murder a cat for food if you let it.
Yeah. Well, they famously have an argument. You know this.
Because they're the famous enemy.
Yeah. They really do not like each other very much.
What do you think that is?
You know, I've thought about this a lot.
Every time you walk your dog, you're like, "What's with the poems, man?"
I do think sometimes about if I brought Phil over to Pat's place,
and just to your place and just let him go wild and...
You think he would kill Moe?
Well, let's see if it happens.
Listen, I've met both Phil and Moe.
Us as like a third party here,
I think we can both agree that Moe is so stupid
that he could get eaten immediately.
Yeah, he would just let Phil put him in his mouth.
Yeah, he would walk in there.
Probably hates his life so much.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, Moe wants to just go outside and kill things
and I guess getting killed by something else is a good alternative.
Dude, it is so hard to be an animal. Oh my God, it's hard.
I wish I knew what that felt like.
I never want to become an animal.
I'm a divine creature.
You don't want to be stuck in a small apartment in New York,
just yelling all the time, crying and being gay.
And shitting and pissing on the ground.
It's a little bit pretty close to my life, I guess.
But the idea of being a wild animal and having a natural predator,
That's a bad lot in life.
What if you're the top though?
You're like the lion.
We are the top.
Even a lion is like, every once in a while
True, a hippo will fuck it up.
Every once in a while some fucking, yeah,
one of the Trump boys comes down and puts a giant cannon
into your face.
I want to be a jellyfish.
A great white?
No, you don't want to be a jellyfish.
We don't hunt great whites, man.
We don't do shit like that. They just get to eat hot babes.
But they pull up and they put an earring on you and they track you for the rest
of your life.
That's it.
That's what happens when you get an earring in real life.
Dude, you know that when you go back to the great wife...
The great wife dude?
The great wife shark.
Yeah.
Sorry, long day.
Hit the gun.
Great wife shark.
That's for you.
If you, if you, if you get tagged and you go back to the great white hive or cave, wherever
they live, yeah, they shun you. I mean, they just got a clown. You know, on this age, only
if you get it on the left ear. Yeah. And this tick tock age, they're fucking with you. Yeah.
You're the coolest around. You're the coolest. No, no, no. You're saying they got a dangly
tag hanging off the fin.
They actually let you pick, they let the shark pick which earring you want.
Listen man, I have no interest in being a shark, but I do have an interest in having
fins.
That would make me go a lot faster underwater.
Dolphin?
Dolphin shit?
Or like Aquaman?
Like popping out, like retractable, kind of suicide door movement coming off of my ankles.
You know who's got it worse in the sea?
It's crabs.
Yeah, crabs eat the poop. They eat fucking poop.
They poop and...
They like poop though.
Every once in a while, you get picked up by some fishing boat and they're like, "Oh yeah,
your arms are just gone." So they just throw you back in.
Well, that's actually cool that they take your arms away and they put you... Because
you're the only of those... You're the only shellfish that is spared. A lot, they'll spare
a lobster. If a lobster is really big, they just throw it back because it's so old and
they're like, "We'll let it run its course." And if you're a crab, they just take your arms
arms off and then you grow them back. It's not a big deal. What do you mean
they just take their arms off?
Blue or what's the, what's, it's a specific kind of crab. Snow crabs. Some
kind of crab, they just take the arms off. There are crabs who, they're just
gone. And then they, and they get boiled alive. That's awful, dude. When they
die, they get all the bacteria and shit, so it's like you have to kill them
while they're alive. Yeah. You gotta, like, that is awful. You have to kill
them while they're alive. Okay. You have to dismember them while they're alive.
Yeah, you did get owned a little bit.
You're fucking stupid.
No, no, don't kill me!
We're giving you, you get the high-pitched voice for five minutes.
My name's Caleb!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
away right now. No, he doesn't have it anymore. That's great. Alright, how is everyone coming
into their talent of the disgusting beer? I'm about done. I'm about 66% into this. I
think I have a third left and I don't like it at all. I'm certainly going to speed run
these beers. Alright, really, Bronx Brewery, you've made a disgusting product and you are
no longer welcome to the show. It's definitely a bottom half sour for me. Yeah, they make
this in the zoo over there in the Bronx. You can taste it. Yeah, it's like this beer tastes
like it should be 8 to 9%. This is the most unpleasant beer of the batch I would say.
Well have you had these other ones? No. So you're just talking out of your ass. It's
a prediction. I'll let y'all know how this one is real soon. Oh my god he's moving on
already. No make it a surprise. Don't ruin the surprise. People can see him. Yeah well
Crack open the second one. What is this one? This is the Grim.
This one is a Grim single negative. Yeah, I think Grim makes the best beers in the entire
world. I kind of agree. They're really fucking great. I've had their double negative. I'm
not a big stout guy. It's pretty heavy. So we'll see how this one goes. I'll keep my
opinions to myself. And keep your mind open also. Yeah. I'm starting to feel psychedelic
because I've needed a beer today, man. I've needed a beer so badly.
What happened?
I had to go do one thing.
It's probably the hardest thing anyone's done.
I had to go hang up lights at a backyard.
That's a dad activity that needs a beer after.
That's akin to working on the railroad.
It was worse than that, dude, because I didn't even get paid, first of all, and I didn't
get to die.
And you didn't get to look at trains.
Yeah, exactly. I didn't get to feel like I was part of a bigger thing, which by the way,
you worked on the railroads of your grandpas did shut out.
I'll shut up to you. Yeah, like you also stop complaining. You should instead of complaining,
how about you take all the accolades that I'm willing to give you of thank you so much
because we have one of the greatest rail systems in the entire world now. So thank you so much.
Kudos to you.
Have you seen that video of like 1000 Chinese people making a railroad in nine hours?
In China? Yeah, in China. I would have thought in China they would have a robot do that. No,
they got people. They haven't figured out the robot shit yet. They just got hella people.
Wow, in nine hours they made a whole railroad? So they took like a hundred crews of a hundred
people and just had them each do a section of railroad. So imagine in China, like this
room would fill with a hundred people. Yeah. Because they got hella people. They got hella
people. Oh, there'd be a hundred person podcast in China.
Yeah, they would all be drinking a hundred beers.
Wow.
They'd be like, "Oh, this sucks."
They do everything by the hundred.
Three hundred beers. Let's get it straight.
Yeah.
Does China do the thing I don't like where all the money is too much?
A little bit.
It's a hundred of something for a dollar.
A little bit. I think a little bit.
It's in between.
What's their Chinese, what's the money in China?
The exchange? You want the exchange rate?
No, no. What's it called?
The yuan.
Yuan is what people say though, right?
- Won is Korean.
- Oh, okay.
- Yu-won.
- That's a really bad one.
- What's the Japanese one?
It's similar.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it's too much.
- Well, the good thing about China is that
their money is just completely,
it's just imaginary at this point
because it's all on the phone.
They never have a single bill.
It's always on WeChat.
- Really?
- It's on the phone for us too.
What are you talking about?
- Mostly, but you still have some bills and some coins.
- They don't really make paper money very often there?
- Yeah, they completely have done away with it.
- Really?
What about, is there still peasants in China?
Yeah.
That's cool that they're like the last place that has peasants.
That's awesome.
They're the last place?
As far as I know, I only hear about Chinese peasants.
I'm not hearing about fucking Canadian peasants.
That is true.
Alex?
Well, yeah, he might be a peasant.
But I mean like Monty Python style, like wearing rags covered in dirt.
You know.
That's the thing is you see them on TikTok and they're all wearing like anime girl outfits
and shit like that now.
Yeah.
And they're cooking a monitor lizard.
A 400 pound one.
The cooking videos are so awesome.
They just chop a cow's head off.
Dude, the lizard ones, honestly, and the thing is, man, if you watch just the second half
of those videos, that looks like the best food you would ever eat in your entire life.
Oh, dude.
With all the chili oil and sea?
If you didn't take some kind of deep sea creature and torture it and poke it a thousand times,
a thousand times, they're like, oh yeah, I got to put poke it with a thousand
holes.
I was going to say with a hundred guns.
Yeah, exactly. Like you would eat that. I would eat that.
Yeah.
It's not that big of a deal.
The more tortured the animal, the better the food.
I think veal tastes so good.
That's why veal is so good.
Yeah.
Lamb, it's a tiny baby.
That's how you get every animal born with game in it, they say.
Yeah.
They're gamey.
I know, I got game.
Well, speaking of meat, I think we have to move on to your official apology,
Caleb, your officially recorded apology.
About what?
For your betrayal.
What betrayal?
The betrayal he did to them yesterday.
Oh, yeah.
To both of us.
Is this what this is?
Is you guys, is that what you were like?
We need to get Noah here.
So you had numbers, you could corner me?
Yeah, I like how he's instigating this.
When he had his meal paid for.
I was also a victim.
How are you a victim?
You got to enjoy it.
I was a victim.
I was a perpetrator.
I was used.
I was just simply used.
All right, let's go.
Let's set the scene.
What was the crime?
Crocodile tears from Julio here.
Instead of the school boys in the morning.
Here's the thing. No, no, no. We're going to go before that. We're going to go to what
you were going to say. We're going to go to about one month ago. Me, Rex, Julio, maybe
you I don't remember. We were talking on Discord and we're making plans for this New York trip.
We're going to do so much fun stuff. This is going to be the best day ever. This will
be the best week of our lives. What are we going to do? Here's what we should do. We
go eat at Fogo de Chao. Who said that? One of us. I don't remember. I think it was you because
I didn't know they were in New York. Okay, so I could have just never even told you.
So we were like, let's go eat at Fogo de Chao. And then they get they've been here a couple
days. Yesterday, me and Julio and Cameron went out to go get some mic stands. And we
went to an elf or something else. But that was the thing. Yeah, we found a ghost, a ghost
But we woke up, it was like 9am, I texted Julio, I was like we're gonna go run some errands,
you wanna come with?
He said yeah, let me wake up Rex.
Tries to wake up Rex.
And here, this part of the story you can tell, what happened?
I knock on his door, he doesn't wake up, I'm assuming he went to sleep, he stayed up late
because we were gambling last night.
I was like, you know what, I'm just gonna text him, I'm gonna tell him we're outside, I left
the keys inside, if you wanna go out, we'll be back later for lunch.
That's all I said.
Okay.
Alright, so we, well, let's take a little pause.
We've moved on to the grim orange beer.
No, no, finish the story.
We can talk about the beer after.
Wait, wait, I gotta take a sip of this.
Yeah, take a sip.
Yeah, take a sip, but let's talk about the beer after the story.
Okay.
Let's not split it up.
So, he doesn't wake up.
I just text him like, "Hey, we're outside."
He lets me know like, "Yeah, I'm not feeling great.
I'm just gonna rest up and go to the pharmacy."
Like, "Okay, that's completely fine."
We go to our errands.
We fail to do one of them in the funniest way possible.
We get our mic stands and then we're heading back.
I can't just say funny as possible.
What happened is we were looking for costumes for a D&D thing and I found a store called
Halloween World and we put it in Google Maps.
We get there.
It's a piano showroom.
Well, first of all, we get there and it's called like Holiday something.
Holiday Himosis.
Holiday...
It was called Holiday...
Yeah, Holiday...
Central...
Yeah, something like that.
we're like, "Oh, okay, maybe it's some like, it's just all holiday stuff." And
then we walk in and it's a fully like grand piano stuff that would make no
sense. The most expensive pianos on the planet. Yes, exactly the kind of store
that it makes no sense to be a transient kind of like Halloween store for three
months of the year because you'd have to move fucking 50 pianos. It's giant. The
guy who like greets you at the front is wearing like a tux. Yeah. He's like, "Do
you have an appointment?" That's the other thing. It was giant. We walk in, we
walk around where we spend probably no one there. There's not a single soul.
It's a completely ghost store called Holiday Central. There's a bunch of pianos.
There's no one there. It was in Flushing. It was in Jamaica. It was so fucking weird.
It was weird, but also it makes complete sense.
So we needed to say that because we already, we're in a weird mood.
We're not acting like ourselves. We're not acting like ourselves.
We got mentally attacked by the world.
And you guys are in a place called Jamaica, but it's in New York?
Exactly. We're being psychically attacked. We have psychic pain.
And then we drive over to another Halloween story. This one also doesn't
exist. And then we start driving back to come maybe get you and meet up for lunch.
But then
I say, where do you guys want to go to lunch? And Cameron says
Fogo de Chau.
It's Cameron's fault. Cameron said it first. That's what I'll say. And I say,
oh yeah, we could put it. I'll see where the Fogo de Chau is. Fogo de Chau,
381 feet away.
Yeah, I want to say, I mean, come on. I want to do a quick aside. I'm completely
hands off on this one because I don't recall who said it first. I'm not all
that upset because I know there's going to be many more Fogo de Chao trips
coming up. I'm planning on making it a weekly thing. Yeah, I'm not. I loved it.
I'm sure it was fantastic. You should go this weekend. What happened was...
A steak house and it's Brazilian? It was 381 feet away. I said,
"We're already here." Yeah. It would be 30 minutes round trip, 45 to
come get you. And at that point, I won't even be hungry. I'll be so
I'm full of my own spit that I'm not hungry anymore. So I just make an
executive decision. I pull I take the exit. We wrap around. We park. We go in
the guy comes up. He says, Have you ever been to Fogo before? I say no. I have it.
What happens here? I full well I've seen hundreds of videos about this place. He
says, Do you want to order food or do you want the full experience? I order the
experience. Triple full experience. We go, we get, we get, we go to the buffet. Now here's
one thing you need to know about Fogo de Chaux if you're ever going to go and if anyone is
who's listening is ever going to go, which you will go, you will go. Yeah, I'm not so
sure. But if you are ever going to go to Fogo de Chaux, they have this buffet, right? And
the buffet is a honey pot because it's full of some good stuff. They have all kinds of
cheeses. They have meats, they have salads. You would be one to know what it looks like.
vegetables, fruits, I would because I went.
They have all, anything that you would want on a normal meal.
There's an entire meal sitting for you in the buffet.
Don't do it.
Don't waste your time.
Do not go to the buffet.
It's all meat. It's all I'm there for.
I'm there for the meat. I'm there for the steak.
I got one piece of pineapple and two slices of papaya.
No. I wouldn't even touch that.
And three beans. I got three beans because the beans look good,
but I didn't want to fill up.
Three beans, he sits down and immediately gets, it's one bean.
Me and Cam are still sitting down and he's like, "Yo, tell me a bean."
So Cam gets one and I get one.
I didn't even want to have two more beans worth of food in my stomach because the specter
of not being able to eat as much meat as possible upset me.
So then, dude, they were coming in, they had the garlic steak, they had the picanha, they
had the filets, they had the rib-eyes, they had the...
Bigger wrap steak.
Y'all got to chill.
They brought over the chicken.
I said, "Get that chicken out of my fucking face."
Fuck that chicken.
I do not want that chicken.
We said no to the chicken.
a week but I rarely eat steak.
Here's the other thing about Fogo, when they come with that chicken, that lamb, that pork,
you say no, no, no, no, no, you turn that card red.
Which is how it works by the way.
You have a card, one side is red, that means no meat, one side is green, that means yes,
as much meat as possible.
It's really funny, that's like the bubblegum system essentially.
The what?
The bubblegum system.
Have you ever been to bubblegum?
I've never been to bubblegum.
system. So they have the thing where you can like if you flip it's I think it says
like run run for his run that will complete they you will be completely
ignored by all service you say stop for stop you flip it over someone will come
in like what do you want so it's not a line from the movie stop for a stop no
they just put it there run for us run as a line yeah that is it probably could
have used another line from the movie forest I have AIDS yeah she never says
AIDS. What does she say? She just says I'm very sick. Yeah, it's assumed she is. It's
like a Darth Vader type of thing. You think he says I'm the father of AIDS, but he doesn't
say that. He does not say that. It's completely useless because the chicken walks up and we
can still say like, oh, it's green, but I don't want it by the way. You can just leave.
And at one point we're headed on red and the guy still walks up like, hey, you want some
of this? Well, this is also a lunch service. I'll say that it was lunch. So it's a little
more casual. As far as I know, the dinner full experience, first of all, it's a little more
expensive. And it was expensive. It was $46.50 a person. So if I bring you two, now all of
a sudden the bill's $200, right? So it just doesn't make sense. It just doesn't make any
sense. A quarter of a thousand dollars that we're going to go spend at a steak place? No,
not going to happen.
Yeah.
For an unforgettable memory?
You think I wouldn't want to pay for myself? You think I'm not a hardworking man?
What? Say it. My name is Caleb. No. No, no, no. Listen, you can't fuck with him. He has
to redeem himself. He's been shy all week. He's been crying. I see, I hear him crying
from his room. He does. He barely sleeps. Julio did tell me this, that he went to Fogo
to Chow. Talk into the mic! Julio did tell me this, that I went, that he went to Fogo
go to chow and I didn't believe him. Oh, wait, yeah, yeah, back to the airbnb.
Dude, as we were leaving, I was like, okay, who's going to break the news? I
was like, you have to do it because you're the leader of this of this
cartel. It's your fault, but I'll just say
and we're like, no, we'll just never say, but if he asks, we'll just tell
him it's whatever. So I come back to the airbnb. I hope not to have this
conversation with him. I wasn't ready to break down the news, but I'm such a
friend I want to know about your day. I first thing you were hanging out. He's
like, what do you guys go do for lunch? Just a casual conversation.
Talk about breaking us apart. I'm looking down. I'm like, I'm gonna have
to tell him. I'm like, you're gonna be upset. You did not say you're gonna be
upset. You just knew he was gonna be a child. You said, for the show. And I
said, that's very funny. That's a really funny. You said, that's funny. Yeah,
He thought it was so absurd.
Well, I was like, of course, why would they go to Fogo de Chão without me?
That would be an awful, horrible thing to do to someone.
And he goes, he tells me, "No, really, where did you go for lunch?"
And I go, "Fogo de Chão."
And you could have heard a needle drop on the ground.
Yeah, it was, the whole day was completely ruined.
We've been chastised for the entire day.
I'm surprised you didn't get kicked out.
I was simply a victim.
But we're getting kicked out anyway.
It's not a problem.
We are getting kicked out for a different reason.
Oh yeah, talk about that so we don't have to talk about Fogo de Ché.
Let's talk about the beer now.
That's like coffee.
Yeah, it's a lot of...
I mean that's how stouts taste a lot of the time.
It's like a coffee gingerbread.
That's what I'm getting from it.
It's okay.
It's a lot lighter than their double negative.
lighter than their double negative which is nice. I don't like a heavy stout. I mean
I don't really like stouts either. This tastes like a non-nitro Guinness to me. Yeah, I knew
you would like it because it's similar to Guinness. Part of why I like Guinness is just
the nitro though. If they have a normal Guinness or whatever, I don't want that. Yeah. Yeah,
this tastes not as bad as this but I somehow enjoy it less. It's a little tough to get
through. But it's also, I can crush that and that's higher percent but you just can't
crush a stout very easily. They feel heavy.
This is quite hard.
They're very full bodied.
So we have four of the top beer aficionados and speakers on the subject in this room right
now. So I feel like we would be remiss to not go around and go favorite beer. Number
one, like undisputed favorite beer.
I can't.
Just name one, dude.
I brought Miller's.
I brought High Life.
That can't be your favorite.
It's not my favorite.
Actually, I have, you guys say yours.
You're backing me into a really difficult corner because there's a different beer for
every occasion.
This is a really loaded question.
Yeah, very loaded.
There's a different beer for every occasion.
And this is like I stopped into the deli to make sure I didn't come empty handed to the
beer, the foremost beer podcast on the planet.
So okay, well here's the scenario because I am a working man, you're all working men,
you get off a long day of work, you get home, it's like the scene in Cat in the Hat where
Alec Baldwin, he undoes his male spanx he has on and he sits there on the couch, big
belly hanging out of the wife beater.
You pop open a can, you bring it to your lips, what's entering?
What is passing through your gums?
End of the day, hard day of work.
Hard day.
Are we going in order?
You're not going to let me answer.
I'll go first, but you're not going to like it.
I'm going to say Michelob Ultra.
Because that's all I drink back home.
I don't drink at all.
That's all you drink is Michelob Ultra?
Yeah, when I have friends over, we just drink like, my beer.
I like Michelob Ultra.
But I'm never reaching for it.
I'm not going to the store and buy Michelob.
but I'll say mine. If you're skipping the rest of the day, okay, I thought you
were saving
mine. Mine's probably Jeevik because Patrick probably has a hundred in the
refrigerator at all times, which he only likes because he thinks it's a funny
name. Yeah, yeah, he's like I
he's like this is foreign and I shouldn't be able to know how to pronounce
it, but I can't. It's fine. It's okay, yeah, but I just drink his beers for
free. That's nice. Yeah, I've been drinking a lot of the Taheen Smirnoff. I
not been drinking beer at home.
Taheen Smirnoff.
Yeah, dude. It's like a Dia de los Muertes, like vodka bottle.
Okay.
And it's got like a sweet, you know, taheen.
Yeah, I love taheen.
So it's that. It's like a spicy vodka and you can just sip it. It's so good. It's like
sweet.
That's the thing. I don't usually spring for beer and I only drink beer on this podcast.
Yeah.
But I used to be a big beer drinker and I always went for Coors Light.
Right.
Cores Light is the best light beer.
Over, over, I gotta be honest.
What?
Bush is spanking Cores Light every day of the week.
Dude, you are a fucking fool.
Bush, spanking.
You are so stupid bro.
Spanking hard.
What do I have for you?
Dictatorship, Dictatorship type 5's right now.
Yeah, yeah for sure.
(laughter)
I like Gansets.
Like when I was back home, I would crush like a six pack of Gansets like every night.
every night. But I mean if I can only have one beer for the rest of my life, it's gonna
be Coors Light. It's gonna be the Grim Hefeweizen. Really? Yeah. What's a Hefeweizen? It's one
of the oldest beers in the world. It's got a lot of banana flavor on it, malted barley,
it's very nice. It's great beer. Best Hefeweizen. Or the Weifensteiner. You need to speak English
The Weifensteiner is a very good beer.
What is that one?
It's another Hefeweizen.
Oh, okay.
It's probably one of the oldest beers in the entire world.
So a Stout is a brown one that tastes like poop.
What does a Hefeweizen mean?
So a Weiss beer is a white beer, so it's going to be very similar to a light beer.
How about an Allagash White? You like that?
you like that alligash white is brewed very similar to a traditional German
white beer or vice beer. So what's that? What's the hefa come from
God?
I could not tell you yeah yeah, hefe that's what I mean. It's big. I couldn't
tell you man. I just I just drank him. I just put it down.
Mexico City El Jefe? No, that is ridiculous.
Los Big Apple. Why does my brother say that?
I don't know, my brother was talking about Mexico City, he called it El Jefe.
I was like, "What are you talking about?"
He was like, "Mexico City, El Jefe."
I was like, "What?"
He for sure is just talking to like a Mexican guy in LA that's like fucking with him, for sure.
That's awesome.
He's easy to fuck with, for sure.
Yeah, he listens.
So, go ahead.
Yeah, you're easy to fuck with, bro.
Oh, he listens?
Can't lie.
He texted me a couple of weeks ago and he said, "Beers we drink, nation."
Damn!
I love you.
I'm going to go to his bar now.
Yeah, yeah, you need to I'm working on it. Yeah, no, it's doing the drinks. Yeah, I'm doing the drinks
When I come absolutely
You will be here when it opens you'll be here. It's like six months away
It's there's so much shit like LA is such a backwards or like
LA County in California in general is just horrible. Yeah, this is officially the last the last time
we ever book an Airbnb because Rex is moving to New York City.
How are you feeling about that move?
I'm excited.
Yeah.
It's so nice here.
Everyone is always doing shit outside.
Yeah.
You know, I was thinking about that today.
No one does anything outside anywhere else.
This is the only city in America where the rich people have to, like the richest people
in the world, have to see a homeless guy every single day.
Yeah.
It's dope.
around like in the richest neighborhoods in New York City, you walk on the street
and there will be a homeless guy. I don't see a homeless guy every day.
Well, you're not rich. You're not rich. You see him in the mirror.
If you live in Manhattan. Yeah, true. That's true. That's true.
If you live in Manhattan, you will. Yeah.
Like Upper West Side, Upper East Side, doesn't matter how rich you are.
You can be at the top of one of those, the Iron Man places, but still.
That's my favorite part about living here is like in LA,
it was a weekly thing getting attacked by a homeless guy.
But here, you don't even see him. Wait, you were getting attacked?
Yeah, several times.
Several times?
What happened?
I mean, on the subway just...
The metro in LA is so much worse.
Yeah.
What did it do to you?
So, a few times on the subway, guys would try and pick fights with me.
People have a weapon.
They walk around in nunchucks and shit.
They're scary.
It's crazy.
I mean, they take over whole subway cars and turn them into like, "This is my house now."
One guy will just pop a squat in a subway car.
I remember one day on the subway, I was getting on the subway and I saw a guy smoking crack
and then on the bus into work I saw a guy jerking off and then when I got off the subway to
get home I was like, "Whew, that was a rough day on the metro."
And I come out of the station and there's a guy, spread eagle, his whole butthole in
view for me, just dropping a deuce right there.
And also homeless guy poop.
Homeless guy poop.
That's very different than the poop that me and you poop.
No fiber in that dye.
No fiber, it's a different color than I've ever seen before.
It's a new color.
Yeah, yeah, Pantone probably went and sampled it and put it on the color wheel.
Yeah, LA is fucking crazy.
I remember me and you over by where I lived.
I lived by the Wiltern off Wilshire and we were like walking somewhere over there.
Guy with one arm.
Yeah, I was in our there's a guy one arm. So his pants were sagging. Yes.
He had no underwear on his pants were sagging right underneath his cock.
So his cock was falling out and he was trying to hold his pants up with his one
arm. By the way, valiant effort. Yeah. If I was him,
I would have just let that thing fly. There's no way I'm like, I'm homeless.
I'm like that. I have one fucking arm. So look at my dick. I don't care.
Horrendously dirty and flailing about.
He had like a little nub and it was like moving.
Like it was doing something, but it wasn't doing anything. Yeah.
LA certainly has some really new types of homeless people coming out every day.
Every day now.
It's like, and every time I go back it's like, any time you pick up a new Pokemon game, where
you're like, I know the original 151, but all this is getting crazy.
It's all original 151 here in New York.
It's very traditional homeless people.
Good people.
Good people that are just like, give me money or I'm going to scream.
And I go, you know what dude, yeah.
In LA they get straight to screaming.
Today a guy came, I was pumping gas, a guy came up and he was like, "Hey man, can I like
wash your window or something?
And I, or can I like help like pump your gas for you?"
And I was like, "Here man, I got some cash."
Gave him like 10 bucks.
And then he walked away.
He immediately just walked away.
And I realized I just paid him to just go away.
I paid money for, to just not talk to him anymore.
Yeah.
Hit me with the rosé.
beer that we have. Noah's moving in first.
Well, it's not as strong. We got plenty of room.
This one is definitely...
No, take your time.
I got 20%.
I want to get into these millers. I want to drink at least two of them.
These are like the last obligatory beers. These are like bonus dessert if you wish it
so.
Oh, Noah did not have a good reaction to that.
I will say I don't like rose.
Okay.
And I think it's a rose cider and I really only like very decadent and delicate rose
- It's been like such a like a backwards experience for you and me.
- That you having, you know like in this one, I'm gonna think that I'm actually gonna like it.
- Noah's getting the high-pitched voice after that.
He said he only likes very decadent and delicate rosé ciders.
- That's fine dude.
- He's had one before.
- I'm comfortable with who I am. I don't mind the voice at all.
- Somebody kill him.
- No, no, I'll own it.
- Nah, I'll do it.
- No, no.
I'm going to be doing a video on the
news.
I'm going to be doing a video on the news.
This is a craziness episode.
It's extra bow down.
An extra bow down?
If you bow to someone that's respectful.
I wish I could.
Do both of them right now.
My name is Caleb.
Start up and do both of them.
The bow down and the cow down.
Oh yeah the demonstration.
He needs to get on the table.
No you can see it there.
Show me a bow.
I've seen him do this in many times.
Cowtow is like you're on your knees.
Oh!
There he goes.
Whoa!
I would say that's praising.
Yeah.
That's like downward dog.
He just did it to me.
That's awesome.
You got that one for free.
Yeah, I know.
You didn't even do anything.
Yeah, I didn't do shit.
I just used the word cowtow and he did it.
Because your vocabulary is so densely huge.
Use a little life hack.
And it's always so wrong.
It was telling me something about the party yesterday and it was all completely wrong,
but I just believed him.
About the what?
- Something about like acid in my cells
and like exploding and having like an epitome.
I don't know, it was Cam, nevermind.
- Yeah, I was gonna say, bro, chill, I'm always right.
- No, that was actually completely Cam.
- I've never, ever been wrong, ever.
- I feel like I'm getting more of that.
I'm getting like, I'm remembering stories
or like things that happened to me.
And I'm like, oh yeah, you were there.
But it was a completely different person.
- I-- - You are--
- And who was there with us when we went
to the knife store in LA?
- My brother.
- Okay, it was Josh.
Yeah, we went to the knife store and they claimed that they had OJ Simpson's knife.
They sold OJ Simpson the knife.
Oh, that's what they said.
They said that OJ Simpson, for whatever reason, to buy the knife, went to downtown Los Angeles
and bought the knife as if it was like so premeditated that he...
Which I don't think it was, right?
Wasn't that the whole thing with him?
He was going...
No, he's in a rage.
Yeah, he was in a complete rage.
He was like, "Oh, you're fucking someone else."
I think he just bought the knife there and then later did the murder with that knife.
Yeah.
And then they had like a nice case that said OG Simpson knife.
With a glove.
That's the story right?
She was fucking somebody else right?
And then he was like I'm gonna kill you bitch.
It's actually interesting because I don't know shit really.
So the uh, they were amicable.
It was an amicable split.
They still were friends.
and then one day that's why some people think he didn't do it. Some people still do.
I don't think he did it. I don't think he did it. But I think he did use that knife.
It was an amicable murder? No, I think he didn't kill her and he used that knife at
that store. They were divorced. They were divorced. It was his ex-wife. She sold the
knife and he committed suicide. The guy that he killed, the other guy, was just her gay
best friend. Oh. Yeah. If a girl dates me and we break up, she's always mine and she
can't fuck ever again or else I'll kill her. That's the damn truth. That's the damn truth.
You know? And I'll only say that if it's behind several paywalls or else I'll incriminate
myself. Oh fuck. God damn it. You guys are going to post it all over the place and I'm
going to prison. So this rose cider, I like this. Yeah. I like this. You're just not into
the decadent and delicate rose cider like I am. I don't like decadent and delicate which
to me are two kind of opposing words when it comes to describing a drink. How so? Decadent
and what? Decadent and delicate. Decadent means like it's definitely, it's of a higher class.
It's a lot more workmanship put into the drink than a mass produced sort of canned beverage.
and beverage. This is fucking mass produced bullshit. And delicate means that it's probably
going to have some florals in it. It's probably going to have some herbs. So you want dirt
and flowers in your fucking drink. Guys, this is our highest ABV one that we've had. What
the fuck? 6.9%. Oh my god, that's a sexy number. Yeah. It makes me think about something naughty.
This is from Graft. This got birth defects. Ew. That's a horrible name for a brewery. Graft.
I do like that they have to put that warning on beer.
Makes me think of ass.
By the way, if you're pregnant, some pregnant lady is going to be halfway through one of
these going, "Wait a minute!
What the fuck!
Hold up!
Wait!
The Surgeon General thinks I shouldn't drink this?"
And then go, "Who's that?
Some Civil War guy?
Finish that."
I'm not fucking with them.
Oh, one more sip can't hurt.
How bad is that?
You can drink it first.
first like the first trimester you can drink. You can't drink drink but you can like you
can have a glass here and there. It's like a drinkable driving type of situation. Yeah
exactly. If you can handle it, it's completely fine. Yeah, yeah but then after that first
trimester you need to slow down. This is medical advice by the way. Yeah, yeah I'm a doctor.
I'm a doctor and I gave it up to be a bartender. I think that my mom definitely had some wine
while I was, while I was at home. I can say without a doubt my mommy didn't touch it at
I think my mom smoked while she was pregnant with me.
That's rude, what he said, by the way.
That was rude.
What he said?
I'm still a little sore from you going to...
Yeah, I know, you're lashing out.
I understand.
My mommy was a good girl.
Yeah, she is.
Yo, why'd you say that?
My mom's a good girl.
Let me redo that.
My mommy is a good girl!
Is that better?
No, that's worse.
That's worse?
I think you'd fit right in.
You guys have been watching MILF Manor?
Dude, I've been done.
I've been done with MILF Manor
for weeks.
I ran it through in two days.
We only watched it because this morning
he told me that he put it on
just in silence and he turned it off.
You want me to spoil? No, no, no.
We went out for breakfast and
Rex was like, "Yeah, I couldn't sleep. It was horrible.
There's demons in my room. We'll get to that."
And he said, "I just put it on MILF Manor
for like half an hour and on the first episode he gets to the part where they're like touching
the boys. Oh the blindfold challenge. Yeah, find your boy and they get all the women and
the women are like oh I want to touch all the boys and they get up there to touch the
boys and he's like you know what this is enough, this is too much for me Rex. Can I really
quickly say what my strategy would be in that? If you touch all their cocks of course your
son is going to be like oh no! I think that's the smart because they all take their shirts
So you're supposed to touch the upper body.
Yeah, you break the rule.
You gotta give a shit.
Also the thing about Milf Manor is there's no prize at the end.
It's not like, yeah, yeah, it's like, no one wins anything except like maybe we like go out for drinks back home.
When I was in Raleigh, me, Adam, and Chad sat and watched like three episodes of Milf Manor
to the one that was devastating, honestly, where they ask, they're like,
what is the nastiest thing you've ever done? The nastiest sex thing.
And you have to try to match it to your, to who, which one is your mom?
Oh my God, dude. Yeah. And, uh, the one,
this one lady, hers, hers was, I don't remember her name,
but hers was, uh, so the blonde Asian lady who has,
So young is shut up.
She's awesome.
So young was my favorite.
So she's she apparently has sex.
She was like, I had sex with my my son's best friend.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, and he gets drunk.
Gets fucked up.
Yeah. Like basically tries to kill himself in the pool.
Yeah. He gets naked.
He talks out and everything.
And he's like, I don't give a fuck about anything anymore.
Like, yeah, you can tell that he suspected this for so long.
Yeah. Yeah. And as soon as he saw that on the board, he was like, I'm fucked, man.
Yeah, but it's hoping it wasn't her the whole time. Yeah, I think honestly I would
I would kill her first. I think I would definitely kill my mom if I went on that
trip. Wait, do they like get like eliminated? What happened? So they did
switch people out. But I think the only purpose of switching people out was like
y'all are not like making this. Yeah, this is the show mom that got switched
The Jersey mom with the stripper son, they get swapped out.
And I think that's the only one that gets swapped out.
There's that one mom that looks like a teddy bear. I like her.
A teddy bear?
Yeah.
She has that kind of like teddy bear like lines on her face.
Oh, no, I hated that mom. The one that looks like a skeleton?
Maybe.
Oh, the older mom with the gay son. There's a couple gay sons on the show.
There's like two or three gay sons.
Yeah, one of them was just completely there to just touch the other boys.
Which is like, how, of course that would be so hard to break the news to your mom when she's like,
"I just got accepted on MILF Manor. I sent them a photo of you."
Yeah.
And just be like, "Oh!"
They have their nails are painted, they're wearing pearl chokers, they're like wearing their mommy's hoodie at night, you know.
We got a complete sidetrack. We were just watching MILF Manor because I told, he brought this up during breakfast,
And I was like, oh, that's funny.
That reminds me of the story that
Patrick told about you
watching Milf Manor in
your place with your girlfriend and
Patrick's girlfriend.
Yeah, it was mostly driven by them,
by the way. I will say
I was very entertained.
This is a judge free zone.
We're talking about decadent and delicate.
I will own it.
Decadent and delicate.
So and you do say
that one of them is Rex
and then Patrick walks in and says,
oh, that guy's Rex.
And you guys all laugh.
It's so funny.
Which guy?
No, y'all are not deep enough into the show to meet him.
He's the one who replaces the Jersey mom and son.
Oh, yeah.
We put it on because me and Cameron, if you both said the same thing, we thought as soon
as we see him, we're going to know it's him.
And we're looking for him, like, this one's gay, this one's black, this one's Asian.
Alright, pull it up on the phone.
Pull it up, yeah, pull it up, pull it up.
And you'll be like, "This is Rex. It is Rex."
And he does a demonstration of how to eat pussy in front of everyone.
It's so awesome.
Do you know what his name is?
I don't know.
Like he's the one who did it to you.
I don't know anyone's name from that show.
That's okay.
Here's how you eat pussy.
I couldn't even show you if I wanted to. I don't know how.
Holding court during dinner.
Be like, "By the way guys, this is how you eat pussy. Hand me that apple."
it
spitting all over the place. Tell me you see him. Oh, I keep going. That
one's that one's a new one. Yeah, it's a gay one. Yeah, also so young son might
be gay. I don't think it's out on him. I don't think I think he's hot Jimmy.
Yeah, Jimmy, he's a he's Jim Jim Jim Jim Jim. I would if I was around
honestly, if I was in the manor and it was a I was like dude imagine,
because they have that they had better of a cleaning crew, because you know
nasty something's going on. If I was in that milf manor, I was a cleaning crow
as a janitor straight up. I would fold on the on the janitor crew. I would fold
if any if any of those mills or or two of those sons approach me, I'm folding
well. That's the problem. They two two sons or one mill to do any of the mills
Or two specific ones of the sons.
Well, that's the thing.
I followed it.
They get the ugliest crew of all time, so the MILFs are not in.
I will say, on the show, there is only one implied instance of sexual contact.
In the entire thing?
In the entire show.
Well, there's one.
Which is like, "What the fuck?"
Like, "Yup."
The blonde girl and the...
Yeah, yeah, and the handsome Spanish guy.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, the Spanish guy.
They fucked.
They fucked in a hotel.
They like go off the property.
They say, "Wait, you can just leave?"
Yeah, they just leave.
What?
No, no, they win it.
And he like gets a pick and they go fuck and I figured the boy. How do you win?
How do you fucking remember dude? I really do not be the most
Seven or six maybe it's like it's kind of deep into the show
Yeah, I'm - what's like a like a like a YouTube like video essay about it - like no
I was expecting just complete fuck like fuck fest the whole time and it was not at all and I was
Disappointed with how gross it is. Oh women. Yeah, I wanted to see 19 year old boys fuck 50 year old woman
That's what I wanted to say.
Honestly, a lot of the MILFs are a little disappointing.
There's maybe one or two MILFs that are pretty hot.
Yeah, yeah.
But I think what is the explanation for that is like how, why on earth would a hot woman
say yes to doing this show?
Exactly, yeah.
And also, it probably strokes your ego to be cast as a MILF on something.
Yeah.
You know.
That is a situation.
I don't know if they necessarily knew the name of the show before they got put on.
But they understood.
On the first episode they were like, "This is just like a dating camp."
No, no, no.
They all knew what was happening going in.
They knew the whole thing.
You can tell they're all bad actors.
And they're like, "Oh, I didn't even know that you guys were going to be here."
It was like, they were weirded out.
But if I saw my mom, I would be like, "Whoa, what the fuck?"
Or I would just be like, "Oh, what?
My mom's here."
"My mom's here?"
"Where the fuck, where's my mom here?"
"Where's my mom here?"
Personally me I'd be playing valor in my room the whole time. That's right
Do you think they give them that option like do you want to take your ps5 if you want like no
No, they want you to mingle. They want you to rub and mingle.
Honestly, the real version of an interview, if you did it with no cameras, would be...
It would actually be...
It would be a ton of guys playing Madden in 2K.
It would be seven guys playing 2K in the living room every single day.
Yeah.
And the mom's cleaning up and cooking.
(laughter)
Yeah, and they're just like talking about their sons.
that are like getting a little bit competitive about who's the best at 2k by the end of the
show. And the moms are who's the best at cooking and who's the best at cleaning. They just
take turns, they have a chore chart going, they're doing their whole thing. Yeah, the
sons don't do any of it, they don't take the trash out. Of course not. No. Fuck no. I'm
not taking the trash out, I'm playing 2k. If I show up in MILF Manor, God forbid, if
I show up in MILF Manor, that is what I'm doing. I'm unionizing the sons instantly. All we're
doing is playing video games. I don't give a fuck about this show at all. The only way
we can win is to not play.
Yeah, I think that's true.
I do think that is the only way you win that show. I mean, the only way you win is to not
join in the first place because it's the most embarrassing thing you can do.
It is crazy that there's winners and losers on it.
No, there's not. There's not winners and losers.
You said it was one-on-one.
No, they won like, they got challenged. They all picked, like he had the most votes for
people that liked him. So he gets to pick like which one of these women does he take
to fuck in a hotel room. And he picked the woman that he was going to have the highest
chance of fucking. And then he went and fucked her. And that's it. And then at the end they
just all hold hands and are like, "Are we going to keep seeing each other?"
And then maybe the guy says like a haiku that he wrote.
We also watched, on that same trip, we watched some Jersey Shore, first season Jersey Shore.
That show is fucking crazy.
That show they are having sex in the first episode.
That's a real ass show.
That's like completely unscripted.
That is an insane show.
It's so good, man.
Yeah, it's really, really good.
I mean, also, I mean, they're still popular.
Like, uh,
Pauly D is still, he's still doing his thing.
He does DJ sets in Atlantic City like
every year. And he had like a Vegas residency
and shit like that.
I love the reveal in that episode of
The Manor Doing Well.
How to where Pauly D is at
spring break.
Yeah.
That's like one of the one of my favorite
moments.
Pauly D is a man.
Yeah. I love Pauly D.
We got to go to the Jersey Shore.
We got to go and and and I've been to AC many times.
There's a Wahlburger that I want to go to.
AC sucks.
No, you guys are stupid.
Me and Caleb will be in a penthouse.
You guys didn't.
Yeah, but we didn't do it right.
I mean, that's definitely true, but
we didn't win.
Y'all were describing your trip to AC and you're like, we all got way too drunk and we were all so hung over and we hated our lives.
And then we went to AC.
We brought your brother.
Yeah, he's a complete downer.
Well, no, he was just talking too much about like blackjack math.
And then y'all being like, "We're all way too drunk and hungover. We have to leave."
And he's like, "I'm just getting high. I just got hung off my table."
Yeah, it's like a three-hour drive. It was nine o'clock.
And he's the only drunk one. He's drunk off rum and coke because he just started drinking two months ago.
And he was like, "If I'd say to that table I would have made $800."
Shut the fuck up.
Do you remember when you and I sat at that one slot?
It was like a Chinese dragon slot with a huge screen.
I love those.
And I hit like seven bonuses like back to back and then just upped the bet and lost everything before we went to lunch.
I don't remember that. No, I have so many memories of just staring at a screen in Atlantic City.
It's hard to parse which ones are which.
Right.
That's the first place I've ever had a martini.
How'd you have it?
I just ordered it on the bottom of the slot.
Oh, just a martini.
Yeah.
And it came in a plastic cup.
Oh!
Vodka or gin.
I felt like James Bond.
I don't think they let you choose.
No, you just order a martini on the button.
I'm not feeling like I'm going to enjoy the drinks in ACA.
The drinks are not good.
It'll be like rum and coke for me.
I bet, okay, so Vegas is of course way better than they say.
- Yeah, Vegas is fantastic.
- You need to go to Vegas.
- Vegas is basically Disney World.
- Yes.
- Yeah, you have every--
- Vegas is manicured, it is engineered
to extract money from you,
to get you drunk and high and ready to lose your money.
- Yep.
- And I'm ready, I'm ready to go back.
- Vegas actually has good food and stuff.
- I didn't drink when I went to Vegas.
- That is horrific.
- I was just like completely high out of my mind
the whole time and I didn't gamble barely at all. I didn't care for gambling.
Speaking of drinking, this is somehow the worst of the three.
Yeah, I agree. I don't really like it.
This is fine. This goes down easy.
Yeah, it goes down easy, but I don't like the taste. It has something weird.
It goes down harsh.
It's got a bit of funk on it and it's not a good funk.
I opened it and I wafted and I smelled it.
Yeah, it's got a bit of a booger type of vibe to it.
It completely exploded Rex's hair.
on the mic and completely explore. Rex is her. You look drunker than you did when
you walked into yeah, surely okay, yeah, you look messed up.
You wouldn't know you crush this struggle. Yeah, do we have a true
something to something to open this with most people. Do I need to go out and
break it on the rock iron fence?
Yeah, yeah, we didn't even talk about that. Should I go? I think we need to
I don't want to show my cock on camera.
My cock is kind of poking out.
It's right in my cockle area.
Those are my nuts right there.
That's not your nuts.
Just know we got here and...
We needed something. He had to jump a gate to get something for my wife.
No, no, no. So Caleb's wife was like, "I want those chairs."
those chairs and I was like, I'm not getting those fucking chairs. And then I see Rex look
at the fence and suss it out like, can I jump over this fence? And he clearly decided no.
And as soon as I saw that, I was like, I can jump this fence right now. And you got, you
paid the price. Well, I had the super hops and I jumped over the fence. You paid the
paper. Vertical, you know, I could have played it in the NBA. Of course. You know, they didn't
get on skate the first time. The first time, yeah fine. Second time, just complete blowout
and my shorts are in tatters. Like my dick is just hanging out of my shorts right now.
It's just your balls, relax. My dick and my balls dude. Everyone knows you have balls
bro. No, stand in the middle. Damn, those are some CCS shorts. Those are like the tightest
shorts. I will say they lasted seven years. So pretty damn good.
And they wouldn't last even longer.
They're small.
I bought them when I was 18.
They're small shorts.
Oh, I just, I just, they're just tall like a piece of metal.
I just tore them again.
They just hit their best buy date, right?
Yeah.
You gonna go buy shorts tomorrow?
Yeah, we're going to Manhattan to buy shorts with Annie.
I have to work a double.
All right, we'll get you some shorts.
A double what?
A double whammy.
A double shift?
Oh, okay.
I'm bartending brunch and then I'm, you know, you all don't care.
What time are you off?
Say what time you're off.
Like 9pm.
Never mind.
9 to 9?
No, go.
No, no, no.
Leave.
Back to the original cast.
No more distractions.
Finally.
Hand him the keys.
Hand him keys so he can pop the bottle.
I one time, when we were on tour I opened, I was really drunk and Pierce handed me a
a bottle to open with keys. And he was like, "Can you open this with keys? I can't do it."
And I opened it and I tore one of my knuckles clean off of my hands.
Oh, I think I remember that.
It was the most disgusting injury I've ever had.
Here, yeah, I can open them with keys if you can.
He says he can open them with keys.
I can not.
No, it's, like I said, I haven't done it since then. Ripped my knuckle off my body.
I'm very methodical with it.
Yeah, I think I remember seeing you with like a fucked up knuckle.
Where are you going?
Okay, nasty. Farting?
Disgusting. Fart in the fucking, there's a bathroom right there.
If you fart in the bathroom, you are a girl.
Or it's Thanksgiving.
Those are the two options.
I think Rex is feeling that by the way.
I just gotta keep going.
It'll be open and the episode will end.
Yeah, pretty much.
I don't know, we still have to finish these and these are completely disgusting.
I mean we gotta finish these, come on guys.
No, we don't have to finish these.
What's our run time?
- I want an hour or two.
- Yeah, let's go for an hour 30.
Come on, let's crush this.
- I think we can go for like an hour 20,
but I don't, these are like terrible.
- Yeah, I didn't like them.
- Yeah, and it'll take an hour 20 more
for him to open all the highlights.
- No, we just need to unlock the door
and bang him on the raw iron.
- No, that's not worth it.
For a high life, dude, I'm not doing that.
- High life is pretty good.
- There you go, it's open.
Oh my God, it's open.
All right, open the rest of them just in case.
- Yeah, open them all, just in case.
- I'm gonna see, I'm gonna see.
No, we don't need that.
That's great. These keys are not going to work anymore.
We got completely kicked out of our Airbnb, sort of.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. We need to talk about that.
Yeah, yeah.
Go ahead and explain.
You want to talk about, first of all, the demons, how they live in the place?
You have a haunted Airbnb?
Yeah. So we're getting attacked by both ghosts, demons and cops.
Yeah, all three.
You can talk about the ghosts and the demons part and I'll talk about the cops if you want.
Okay, so there's like a sewer grate in the basement. Speak into the microphone.
That just makes noise, like bubbling noises. Okay. Like demonic, just like
bloop.
That's demonic? That doesn't strike me as demonic. No, I'm very well versed in
the demonic and that's not demonic at all. That's hardly demonic. Just the
most evil noise, like bloop. You think that's what keeps you up at night,
That's a water level. No, no, no, it's not bad.
That just means the poop sewer is really close to where y'all are staying.
So, first of all, it's directly beneath a nail salon. I feel like people should know that.
Yeah, it smells like acetone.
Yeah, it does.
They're just dumping chemicals into it.
Yeah, we're smoking fumes 24/7.
Yeah. Then there's like a sewer that runs directly under it.
It's a two-story Airbnb where one story is completely blocked off on both sides.
So it's completely illegal to stay down there, which is why the cops have been coming.
Okay, because according to according to the cops, no, according to the guy that runs the Airbnb,
who's been my best friend and calling me the real estate gang.
Yeah, the real estate.
Real estate.
PSN name.
They log in.
Add him on PlayStation.
His PSN name is the real estate gangsta.
The real estate gangsta.
He has Overwatch 2 and Mortal Kombat X and I think Destiny 2.
If you want to play some of those games, you can add them.
Is it an ER, hard R or a soft A?
I think it's a gangsta.
Gangsta.
Yeah.
Alright.
So you keep showing Rex.
There was, there's a, the people who were in there before us had a party,
which is why there's a sign on the door that says,
"No more than seven people. Parties not allowed. $1,000 fine."
I have to be that close to the mic.
You can angle it.
I need to kiss it.
Put your hand on it. Make love to the mic.
Put two hands on it.
Bro, he's going to phone you.
I can't finish this by the way.
good conscience. You don't need a good conscience. You need to finish it.
Come on, big swig. You're a big man. Come on. I'm drinking you under the table and you
weigh twice as much as me. Come on, man. You are an alcoholic and you work at a bar.
That is not even true at all. Also smells like shit. Not even true.
There was a party there and someone who lived above the apartment called 311 and complained.
And that's what's happening. They're persecuting the real estate gangsta for being so dope
and so fly. This is, of course, according to him. Yeah. So the second day we're
there, which is Tuesday, cops show up and they're like, "Julio..." First of all,
Julio's not American, so he doesn't understand the law, which is that, like,
cops are like vampires. You have to invite them inside. They can't just come
in. And somehow, whenever the cops come, only Julio is ready to answer the door.
right twice. Yeah, they love me. I got coppers
copper is yeah, so the cops come ten thirty in the morning on Tuesday.
Julio, of course, invites them in yeah, big asking for sugar. Yeah,
I'll come in their family,
but I'm a stall. I'm a vision. They're like okay, let me take some pictures in
here. This is a ten thirty in the morning,
So they take some pictures and I'm like, "What the fuck?
Why did you let the, you know?"
In my head I'm thinking, "Why did he let these people inside?"
But outside of your head you're like, "Oh, hello, sir."
"Hello, sir."
"Hello."
"Can I shake your hand?
Good officer.
It's so nice to have you in my home."
Anyway, they come in and they take pictures of everything.
They're like checking out the windows in Julio's bedroom.
They're checking out the door to outside of mine.
They go downstairs.
They're like, "Can we go downstairs?"
And I'm like, "You know, fuck it.
They're already here.
Fuck the guy over.
go downstairs. So they go downstairs, they take pictures and they come back over
and they're like, "All right, we'll be in touch." We go and record on
Tuesday, and we get back, there's a sign on the door, it's a summons for the
building owner. And we're like, "Okay." So I send all the info to the
guy on Airbnb and he calls me and he's like, "Yeah, don't let them in if they come
again." And I'm like, "First of all, I'm not your friend. You're fucking ripping me
off room. I'm not going to protect you, you retard. Anyway, so because this is funny,
this is a funny train of events. Because I didn't get to go to Fogo de Chao, I leave
the apartment to go to Kachapisi Mosque. So it's my fucking fault.
Whoa, wait. Kachapisi Mosque.
So I go to Kachapisi Mosque, I go and walk there, and Julio wants some ice cream so I
if I stop and get some ice cream and he it was really yummy. He face times me
immediately after buying the ice cream. I'm like, why are you outside?
Why are you outside? Tell me right now why you're outside and there's no reason
you should be outside. I was dreaming. Why are you outside? I have a surprise
for you when you get home. I am such a surprise, so I get back and they're like
take a look
notice. It just says vacate immediately.
this premises is imminent danger to
human life,
perilous to human life,
perilous to human life.
I just wanted to scare him and he
got scared and he was like what the
fuck and I mean it's home go for his
runs. I don't want I don't want him to
come to real estate gangster right now.
Don't tell him he's being flying.
Yeah, he's probably fucking a bitch
fine fucking a bit hose. Yeah,
so I'm like no, it's just it's just a
joke. It's not that big of a deal. So
on my P of V, I'm in the basement
rex leaves with the keys. I hear him
take the keys. He didn't tell me that
you got the keys. I hear him take the
he's at the jingling. He leaves. I'm playing Zelda. I'm streaming it with Cam. We're having
a fun time. We can't hear the game, which is really annoying. And I hear the doorbell,
the door ring. I was like, "Oh, that's probably, that's maybe Rex, but I don't know why he
would ring it because I hear him take the keys." And me and Cam were joking, like, "What
if it's the cops? Dude, what if it's the cops?" And I just walk up, so like, "Oh, maybe it's
the cops and I opened the door and sure enough, small white guy with a badge. I'm like, ah,
fuck.
Yeah. I do think it's funny. Y'all keep saying it's the cops. These are firefighters. These
are firefighters and you guys are like, they're the cops. Oh no.
Any theory conspiracies in here? The two times the cops showed up, the fire cops showed up
to our house, the tag along the Robin was an Asian guy, which is really weird to me. I'm
looking at it's really weird to do.
Yeah, the fire marshals are almost homeless people when you see them. I've
seen them. They have so much shit on their body. They have weird beads
hanging from them.
They look weird as fuck. They're just like Boy Scouts.
Yeah, they look like Boy Scouts with like, I don't know, like fucking weird
I don't know how to describe it.
The second pair of cops that showed up, the lead, the white guy, the white guy, he
he spoke like a mouse and was small as a mouse.
- Yeah.
- It was really funny.
- They're so weird.
- It was making me laugh.
So I'm like, "Yo, what's up?"
- They're so weird.
- "Yo, what's up?"
He's like, "Yeah, I just need to put the stickers up
"in here and downstairs."
I'm like, "Okay, come on in, my friend, my cop friend."
And I let him in and I'm like, "Oh, fuck, I'm streaming."
And the way I'm streaming is like so fucked up.
This is the one thing where I had to start the stream off.
I had to like show my OBS like on the on the on the big TV to like see the game
because all the fucked up shit the MacBook is terrible.
So you could see like the stream you can see on my funny little like overlays
you can see if someone subscribe you'll be like,
what's this talking now?
Simpson gamer, Simpson gamer and like a funny video and you can see my webcam
on it and I was like, I don't want to cops to walk through me like yo, what
the fuck is going on here?
Because it would be funny but I would have been on
live stream fails. So I just I just thought it was way funnier if I just
went downstairs and I said to camp is the cops and then I go I get really close to
the camera you got swatted I go if it's the cops and I close it I end the
scenario it was really dramatic and really funny to me and they sure they
don't if they come downstairs like yeah this is fucked up basically you cannot
cook you cannot bathe or sleep downstairs and that's it Wow and if we
"If you catch yourself sleeping downstairs, we're going to arrest you."
I was like, "Oh, okay, that's beast."
I was like, "But can I stay here?"
They were like, "Yeah, you can hang out here."
[laughter]
I was like, "Oh, okay."
-Just don't know. -Yeah, I was like,
"Can I just finish my stay and sleep upstairs?"
They were like, "Yeah, that's fine."
"Just complain to Airbnb and they'll give you a refund."
I was like, "Oh, okay, my friend."
-You love them. -Yeah.
And then the second, the Asian guy, the Robin,
he looked at a clearly fake decoration, like, paved in front of the wall.
He was like, "Oh, shit, this thing work?"
They're like, "No." I'm like, "Oh, okay." They just leave.
And they found the no parties fine thing really funny. And I was like,
"Yeah, and the guy who wants this is a DJ. What's the deal?" And they're like,
"That's funny, my friend." He's got cop riz. You do have cop riz. I've got
riz. He's got cop riz. He would be perfect on a ride along. I do think
cop riz is equivalent to L riz, though. It's basically L riz. No, it's L riz.
W is in exactly one situation.
We have the hottest cops in the world.
Y'all support cops?
Couldn't be me.
When you're a foreigner, you have to have cop wrist.
That's true.
That is true.
As a white man, I can have like, I don't talk to police.
Thank you.
I'm like this.
I can't do anything.
You want to get handcuffed instantly.
No, that's not true.
I actually like handcuffs.
I've always wanted to be handcuffed.
You should say that to them.
Actually, can I have you guys--
Can you guys handcuff me as a joke?
It is funny y'all saying this.
Like when I pull up at your Airbnb now with the summons,
I'm like standing there waiting for y'all to open the door for me.
There's nothing for me to do but read the summons. And it's like,
if you enter, you will be arrested.
Yeah. Can I go in? Or is there like a stakeout? Are they going to arrest me?
Like what the fuck?
Our plan is to get Airbnb to give us our money back,
but we're not just we're gonna complete stay there and yeah we're gonna stay
there yeah and then just completely complain real estate gangster gangsta
sorry yeah he is not a patron no you're fine he won't you know no no no but he I
think you would fuck with his body I like his Funko pops I like the fact that
he has a symbol I like that he collects the classity azul yeah you know he has
pretty gay but no like fire it's like a wizard with a huge telescope and then
like a squire I mean the supreme sticker in the bathroom that's fire like last
year like a hellraiser thing in there I think that might maybe his room maybe
there's like a big misfits poster that can't fun cool yeah what's really cool
horror so in Julio's room is the light just flickers and it's funny because
Because last time we were here, we sent Annie to that room.
And she was like, "Yeah, I'm getting psychic damage here
because this light keeps flickering,
and I'm getting really hot in this room,
and it's horrible in here."
- Oh yeah.
- And we're like, "Oh yeah, whatever."
And then we come two years later,
and the light's still flickering,
and the Airbnb is currently in disrepair,
has not been looked at,
and shit's coming off the walls.
And the real estate guy says,
"Yeah man, it's completely fine."
- He's chilling in fucking, he's in Turks and Caicos.
- He's got a New Jersey number.
- Oh my God.
- Damn.
- That's evil.
Oh, Julio's been talking about like demons.
So last night, I couldn't sleep.
It was so hot in the room,
I had to like strip down to my underwear.
And even then I was still like sweating.
And I'm from Arizona,
it takes a lot to like make me sweat like that.
I like couldn't breathe.
I was like having like trouble breathing.
I was sweating.
- Asthmatic.
- Yeah.
There was just like noise all the time, just like constantly scratching,
scratching, scratching.
That's a demonic noise. You open it with bloop.
I hate the scratching. The scratching is fucking my head so much.
He doesn't want to admit it, but there's rats in the walls.
I think it's a dog.
No, it's not a dog.
That's the most Mexican shit I've ever heard in my life.
It sounds like a small dog.
No, it's fucking rats.
You guys have dogs in your walls in Mexico.
We have dogs on our ceilings most days.
Most days.
Okay, let's finish. Yeah, I can't finish it. We're going to end up the podcast.
Thank you for joining us. You have to finish it. Oh, wait, I just finished it.
I just... Wait, let me see how much is left. Hold on. Give me this. No, no, no.
Give me this. Come on. Oh my God, that's a full beer. Holy shit. So bad, dude.
All right. Thank you for joining us. This will happen again, maybe at some
point. Maybe. Thank you for joining us. It was really great. Goodbye. Bye.