Perfect.
Alright, now we can go.
Should we introduce the podcast first or open the beer first?
Man, fuck you!
I'm sorry, I'm just asking questions.
People know who you are.
Open your beer!
Alright, should I show it before I open it?
No, dude, you open it.
Here, open it and I'll try to guess what it is.
That is a can of beer.
No, that is a can of refried beans that you just opened.
I think you have been mixed up for the guy to my right.
Nope on the video Kayla is to your right so you just call him a Mexican honky.
What do you guys mind?
is a malta, goya malta. That's what I'm guessing. You got it completely right. Yep, here it
is. That's, you're not drinking beer. There's no way that's a beer. That's a fucking root
beer dude. How is this not a beer? How is this not a beer? Show me the label. Show the
label. No. Show the label. What are you afraid of? You didn't get a beer. It's a beer. Oh,
I did a double trick. I'm drinking a light beer today that I'll actually be able to
finish. I threw out, I had another one of those stinky beers in the fridge still.
Yeah. And I think I just threw it out. I don't know what happened to it. Did you
check to see if that one also had the the infection, the cordyceps infection
thing that was sitting on the bottle cap? I preferred not to know. So if I have
like have cancer which I might because I'm growing a I'm growing a thing on my
head. What? Let it just happen. Wait what are you growing on your head? A little
little tumor. You have a bump on your head and you're talking about this
publicly? Yeah. Dude what if this is like the fuck what if this is the beginning
what if this is like yeah dude that's bad you definitely have brain cancer. That's
That's fine.
Doctors there?
Yeah.
It's fine.
I'll be fine.
Yeah, I mean it's fine.
I've had a lump on my head for my entire life, so you're probably okay.
I'm living.
Yeah, but you'd be able to see if it was getting worse.
Yeah, is it red and pounding?
Does it look like a weak spot?
Did you see it?
Like if I hit you three times?
I would love to fight Jubio in a boss fight.
You know a target just pops on to his head after two critical hits.
Oh, absolutely. And you know his eyes go like completely X when he dies.
But then he like, his second stage is... Imagine his giant head
as the body of a butterfly, right? And it just has two
huge wings that come out of it, like the uh, like the Star Fox
boss. Yeah, but it's made entirely out of taco shells.
I wanted to ask, who do you think would drop the best loot out of all the boss fights
of the three of us, but I think we know who it'd be.
Rex!
Yeah, obviously.
Rex, are you kidding me dude?
I'm drinking a Foster's dude.
Oh, nice.
Look at this beer.
I'm going to, well I haven't had it yet.
I'm going to take a sip.
I'm going to have one of these in a minute.
It's pretty hard to sip with a broken neck.
Yeah, I was going to say, you've got to like really just do that motion.
- Yeah, so I've been offsetting it by leaning to the side,
but this is how I have to,
I'll sit completely up straight right now, okay?
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh my God.
- This is how I've been for two days.
I've been at about a 10 degree angle.
- Dude. - Uh-huh.
- Because, but I'm just kind of doing this
to make it look a little bit normal.
- Oh yeah, you look normal now.
- Yeah, I know.
- I think you just got over it.
- I think I'm fine, actually.
- I caught a glimpse of Rex's beer.
I'm gonna say grape cake.
- I mean, you're not, you're actually not wrong.
- It is grape cake?
- No.
- It's grape cake.
- So I guess I'll introduce my beer.
I have a 405 North Lizard Blizzard.
- You need to be killed.
I hope the big one hits right now.
slushy super size with blood orange cake mix and lemon drizzle.
Whoa, so it did have cake.
It did have cake, he was right.
Wow.
Man, you really, for somebody who now has one of the number one beer podcasts in the world,
you really hate beer.
You do not want beer, man.
I bought two sours and then I'm going to drink them both and when they're gone I'll drink
a different beer. Oh, okay. Damn, he's gonna get crazy. I can't have more than one sour.
It gives me diarrhea from being completely honest. Well, I bought these two sours last
week, so I drank one, and now I'm drinking this one. And then you have a normal beer.
And then I will have a normal beer. Does someone who doesn't know what sours are, are sours
just like the Taylor Quinn style like ice cream drinks that Rex gets?
Okay yeah yeah it's like a from what I understand because beer you make beer in
a big pot and at that end with the sours at the end you basically you store like
you throw in like all your Halloween candy right at the end that makes
whatever fucking Rex is drinking that cost $12 a can. See Foster's man you know
this is the most popular beer in Australia?
- You're kidding.
- No, I'm serious.
- I thought it was the VV Long Neck.
- I don't know what that is.
- That one video, that's a VV Long Neck?
Have you ever heard of that?
- I'm really having a hard time,
like I got the first two sips
because it was at the top and it was full,
but from now on I don't know how to sip this.
I like can't move my neck backwards.
You have to dig for it with your tongue.
Oh, I didn't tell you how to do it, right?
No.
You need a straw, by the way.
I do need a straw to drink my beer.
You know how dogs drink water?
Where they put their tongue down and then they cup the water?
Oh yeah, I make a little bowl with my tongue.
You have to do that, yeah.
You have to learn how to do that right now.
No, I can't fit my...
I was going to try.
You need some sort of horn.
gonna try. You need some sort of horn. You're gonna cut your tongue if you do that. I need
a bugle. Yeah, yeah. Okay, what happened to your neck? You need a bong. So listen guys,
yesterday I went to the gym, right? That's a man does. And I was doing shoulders, doing
some shoulders, my shoulder day. And I haven't done shoulders in about two weeks. It's the
last day of my week and the last couple weeks I've been going out of town on the weekends.
I haven't been able to do my Friday workout.
So yesterday I was like, "You know what?
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to go hard.
I'm going to train as hard as I possibly can."
So I got there and I started working out and then this friend of mine, a comedian that
I know, who also goes to that gym that I see there pretty often, he walked in near the
end of my workout and I was like, "Hey, what's up?
Good to see you."
And then he posted up at a bench right behind where I was about to do my upright rows, which
is where you take a barbell and you just lift it up to your chin and bring it back down.
So I started, and as soon as I started my first one, I was like, "Oh, this is way, way,
way too heavy.
This is not the right amount of weight that I'm supposed to be doing."
But I just kept going, right?
Because I was like, "I'm not going to try one time and then drop it while this guy I
nose right behind me, right? Because then I got to look to him and be like,
Oh, like make some face.
So instead I just kept going,
but then I felt the worst pain I've ever felt my entire life in my neck because
I was straining too hard and I clearly pulled something.
But then I had the same problem again where I was like, okay,
I'm not going to yelp out in pain in front of this guy. Like it's only worse now.
Right? So instead of stopping, I just kept going.
I was like about to cry. It hurts so bad.
And I just kept going. And then I finished that exercise. I was like,
man, and he's still here. So I just got to keep working out. So then I tried to do two other
things. And then eventually I let, uh, I basically had a full on ego death at the gym. And I,
I gave up and I went into the locker room and I just laid on the ground for like 15 minutes.
And I was like, "That'll probably be fine."
And then I got up and it was way, way, way worse.
And since then I haven't been able to move my neck and I've just been sitting in my bed
and I don't know when I'm going to get better.
And I don't even know what to, I don't even know what kind of doctor you go to when you're
and you've just destroyed your entire body.
'Cause basically everything from my waist up
is if I move it, it's in total pain.
I definitely have destroyed my spine,
all of my vertebrae, and maybe my brain as well.
- Yeah.
- You should probably go to an urgent care.
I would call that a-- - Shut up.
- Urgent situation.
- Yeah, anyways, I have two questions here.
Number one, did he even notice that you were there still?
I'm not going to look at him to check.
He's not my boyfriend.
I'm just fucking, I just know he's there.
He's a friend of mine.
I don't know him that well.
His name's Kristoff.
He's a funny comic.
He was just sitting behind me and I was like, you know what?
I'm not going to do that.
So you were doing the opposite of the TikTok gym girl where you're like actually looking
for someone to look at you and you're trying to impress them.
Oh no, I actually felt exactly like the TikTok gym girl,
where I almost wanted to go up to him,
even though he was not looking,
he was minding his own business doing it.
I almost wanted to go up to him and be like,
can you please just turn around?
Just literally like, I will pick up the bench for you,
you can stay on it.
Just turn and look the other way.
And if I'd done that, I would not be injured right now.
Yeah.
It was at the point yesterday where like,
I couldn't take a full breath
without just being in the most excruciating pain in my life.
(laughing)
- I think you'll be fine.
- Yeah, I think I am gonna be fine.
- Yeah, it'll go naturally.
- Have you Googled any of your symptoms?
- I mean, yeah, I'm pregnant.
(laughing)
As far as symptoms, I did try Googling neck hurts so bad.
I mean, it's just like, yeah, you just gotta wait.
- I mean, I feel like every man has this happen to them
every once in a while, right?
Like the last time it happened is when I was moving in
into my apartment here, I picked up a desk
and I just picked it up wrong and I was immobile
for probably two days.
- Yeah, it also happened to me, I tried moving
like a mini fridge, this mini fridge right here.
I was moving it by myself and I hurt my back
and I was like, oh man, I think I'm gonna die.
- I thought I was just fine, now I have cancer.
- How many days did it-- - But it's like
a different thing.
- Wait, so now I'm gonna get cancer?
- Yeah, in like two years. - Yeah, from a beer.
- Yeah, from a beer.
You're gonna drink a smelly beer,
and you're gonna have cancer in two years,
or three from now.
- Okay, I'm fine with that.
- Yeah, but your retrovirus is gonna be completely fine
soon, I think.
- Yeah, I think that I'm,
I think this might be my worst ever sports injury,
which is pretty sad.
because I go so hard.
I wanna like, I would love to tear my ACL.
You guys ever fantasize about tearing your ACL?
Because then you just get to like sit at your house
for like, nobody can ask you to do shit
for like three months.
You just fucking sit at your fucking house and watch TV.
- I do think I end up on house arrest
and I just play video games for like three years
while I await trial.
I think that's my--
- Dude, house arrest sounds amazing.
I would get arrested and charged for something that I definitely didn't do.
Just like you said, you await trial, you do house arrest, and then when they finally,
when you are in court, it's like so clear that you didn't do it.
Right.
Because you were so normal during house arrest.
Yeah.
Like, and also like, just the, the, like they set up your case and then like, they just
don't see the evidence for three years.
But the entire time you were no, you were in a different state the entire time.
just didn't tell them so that you could get on house arrest yeah play Red Dead
Redemption and then just really dealt right exactly get through all the games
that are in my backlog oh my god we should set up a like a system like uber
but for like grappers to like just have like fall men don't just like yeah I'll
be a house arrest for you I would the house or the thing where where mobsters
would have somebody go and do time for them if you could do that for house
arrest, I would do that in a fucking instant dude.
Oh my god dude.
Imagine making like six grand a month to stay home and do nothing.
Oh my god.
I would do that for young thug right now.
I would do that for young thug.
I would do that for young thug for ten years.
Do you guys think that he's gonna be, you think they're gonna give him...
They're gonna kill him.
Yeah they have to be giving him the death penalty right?
They're gonna kill him man.
That's so sad.
Did you see that video of that guy like admitting like everything?
Just like completely snitching?
No.
Everybody instantly was like, yeah, it was all him.
He was like doing all these songs,
and while he was doing that,
he was killing people and all this shit.
Yeah.
You guys believe it?
I kind of believe it, dude.
Oh, 100%.
Yeah, like he's definitely going to--
He's cool.
Yeah.
Well, you think it's cool to be a thug?
Yeah, definitely.
Here's your first clue, prosecutors.
Check out his name.
Yeah, Young.
- Young Thug, you missed the important part, Thug.
He was telling on himself there from the get go.
- Oh man.
- Is that your closure statement?
- Huh?
- Is that how you say it?
- Oh yeah, my.
(laughing)
Your honor, you must not look at no further
than the boy's name.
T-H-U-G.
- And that's it, I'm done.
- Holding my breath like that really, really,
really hurt me guys. I'm really, really hurt.
What is the thing we could, the thing you could do right now that will make you feel better?
I think if you like get up and get up and down.
I've tried everything. I've tried watching fucking body cam footage all weekend. Didn't
help. I tried eating like all the cheese that was in my fridge. Didn't help.
How about ice? Just ice your entire back.
I haven't done ice, I've been doing the other end of the spectrum in terms of temperature.
Which is to say heat.
And I've been doing heat, but it just makes me sweaty and I have this heating pad that's
got this plastic outside and so I, last night I fell asleep with it on my back and I woke
up and my sweat had just fused it to my back and I had to rip it off like a temporary tattoo.
It was so bad, man.
I'm really excited for episode three of this podcast.
We've become oxys we took.
- Oh, that?
I have been sitting around thinking
how amazing it would be to get,
like 'cause nothing, like Tylenol
doesn't do anything for this.
I looked my wife in the eye yesterday
and genuinely asked her, I was like,
do we have any muscle relaxers?
And she was like, why would we have muscle relaxers
just like sitting in a pantry?
But I figured it was worth a shot.
I might have my mom send me some.
That's what I used to do. I used to steal painkillers from my mom.
Because, you know, old ladies, they just get surgeries or they even just have friends who just kind of
come over and leave their medication in the cabinet or something.
Yeah, and that's five day supply.
Yeah, dude. And then you fucking take those and you play...
What's that game with the...
The one, you play that one game?
(laughing)
- Oh I know what you mean, yeah the one game
with the guys and the controls.
- What was that game that everybody used to play,
or at least I used to play, that was like--
- Minecraft.
- No it's like a rhythm game where you're like a ship
that's like driving--
- Just Dance.
- Back and forth, no it's not Just Dance man.
- A ship that you're driving back and forth?
- This is just gonna drive me crazy man,
there's nothing that I can--
- Yeah you're saying nothing right now.
- What are you talking about?
- You know what I'm talking about.
I legitimately have no clue what you're talking about.
You're acting like a fucking asshole.
I'm not.
I wish I knew.
Audio surf.
My god.
I used to play a lot of audio surf.
That's so old.
I haven't played audio surf since I was like 13.
Yeah I know, I was playing audio surf.
I just put in, you could put your own songs in.
That was amazing.
Yep.
Skrillex.
Didn't that shit used to not transfer that well?
No, no, it worked fine.
It worked okay.
Yeah, it was only like three tracks or whatever.
It's not that hard.
Yeah.
Okay.
Have you ever seen somebody like, you know those Japanese rhythm games that are like crazy?
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
They're like really weird ones that up there.
It's like a bop it that the guy has to play while he's like on a treadmill and he's like
blowing into a straw at an arcade.
Yeah.
I was at an arcade maybe like a year ago
and a guy, I was just playing like Jurassic Park
and shit, it was for a birthday.
And a guy came in and he came in,
said hello to the person working there,
walked up to that machine,
and just immediately started setting world records
instantly, like doing the most incredible things
I've ever seen somebody do.
Like it was athletic what he was doing.
- Yeah.
And then he left and I asked,
and we all just like watched him.
And he was not a good looking guy,
he was like an ugly skinny dork.
And I asked my wife, I was like,
be honest with me, was that a little bit attractive?
She was like, yes, yes it was.
- Yeah, 100%, yeah, totally.
- Yeah, that was pretty attractive.
- Yeah, those guys are like the modern superheroes.
No one knows who they are, but they just like walk in,
They break a bunch of records in your sleeve.
He was there for like 20 minutes, dude.
He was like there between two other things.
Yeah.
Just to like obliterate this game.
I've been thinking, I've been trying to find a machine that's like only available in Japan and Korea.
I'm trying to find where there's one in America.
It's like the new DDR, it's called Dance Crush.
Where it's like, it's a whole mat that's like a 3x6 touch screen that you like stand on.
You just like go hard on it. You just like there's no like you know
Way you have to be on it. You just have to like be in the way of the notes and shit
It's and it like videotapes you and I've watched videos of guys that's pretty bad
And I'm like these are the coolest guys maybe in the whole world
like like cool Korean guys and like flowy clothes and just like
Doing like a like a shuffle and like you know just I hate when a game records you man when we went remember when we went
to that Topgolf with the--
- Oh my God, the last--
- The last thing it videos you.
I literally went home from that trip
and programmed it, I haven't missed a week
in the gym since then 'cause how unathletic
and fat I looked swinging a golf club.
I was like, this is an actual wake up call
that Topgolf just gave me.
- Well, the thing is, they don't ask for your consent,
which is the problematic thing.
- That is fucked up.
- Yeah.
- You know, I'm out here, I'm playing golf
for the first time in my entire life.
- It was so hot too.
- I don't want you to record me, I'm wearing jeans.
My friend's wearing headphones.
- Yeah, Rex had on over ear headphones
to take a conference call while he's on the golf course.
Just, I mean, I've never seen anybody do anything
that cool in my life.
It was unreal.
- We got assaulted.
There was assault that happened to us in Topgolf.
- I agree.
- And we need retribution.
So funny how bad I was with the headphones on and then like taking them off was like
taking off like a weight vest.
I looked like I had a fucking weight vest on in that goddamn video man.
Yeah we looked bad.
That was a bad time.
It was a sweaty, it was the middle of the summer.
I think it was the end of the tour right?
Is that why we were there?
Yeah.
Something like that?
Cause Jubio was there too.
Oh yeah.
I'd just been drinking for 25 days straight.
- Right, drinking and sitting in a car.
- Yeah, that was so bad.
- Yeah.
- But it was fun, man.
I miss playing golf.
I need to find a golf buddy up here.
- I'm gonna head up my local Topgolf more,
but I don't wanna go by myself.
I'm gonna feel stupid. - You guys have a Topgolf?
- Yeah, we got a Topgolf.
- That's amazing. - That's crazy.
- It's funny, it's one of those things
that gets advertised a lot.
like if you look like the airport in mexico city
but there's a big science like
that the dot top of over there
for that just a p top off and that's it
with a level to make this a people fly all the way real just a fuckin
it's very much top of the so much fun and i want to play a rebirth again
there's a top golf in uh...
either jersey or pennsylvania
has like, they have like stand-ups come and perform there.
And that is like a dream gig.
- Oh my God, how do you do that?
- I have no idea what the, I don't know.
I know that Matt McCusker did it a couple years ago.
And I know some other people
who have like gone and done shows there.
And it's like, yeah, so they have like,
I don't even know what the setup is.
I feel like the only way to make that fun
is if you're like in the middle of the thing,
like theater or the round. - Yeah, people just
hit the ball. - So it's like, yeah.
Maybe you get like a dome or something,
but I would do stand up if I had a loud ass microphone,
just sitting there in the middle of the fucking,
in the middle of one of the nets,
like a spider caught me at the top of the call.
One of the circles.
- How comedy, how comedy do you feel like
the public will be there?
How receptive do you think they'd be to your comedy?
- Well, that's how you would know
if you were doing well or not,
'cause you're too far away to hear the laughs.
if they hit you at the ball that they don't like it very much uh...
but if they're sort of hitting around you
if they're hitting around you in the form of a heart
then that's a pretty good indication that they like it
yeah maybe if they're not hitting at all maybe they're laughing too much to hit the ball
oh that's a good point too
oh fucking god damn it
what about you rex have you ever had any awesome injuries
of course
you know i hurt myself all the time trying like
You know, you have that moment where you see yourself
getting fat, looking terrible, and you're like,
okay, this is it.
I'm gonna get my life in order this time.
I'm gonna exercise, I'm gonna eat right.
And then you exercise two times,
and immediately you just get the worst injury known to man.
- Yeah, a life-altering injury.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Just trying to get back into it.
- That's why I'm kind of amazed that I hurt myself now,
is like, I should have hurt myself
right after that Topgolf thing,
when I first started going back to the gym.
But now, I've been like, you know,
working out pretty consistently for like six months
and this is when it decides to strike
is while Kristoff is admiring my amazing Adonis body.
- Right.
- Worst timing.
But you did a good, you did the smart thing
and you got into DDR.
- Yes.
- Which some might call low impact.
- Yeah, funny you say that.
For twice now, I've gotten like ankle injuries from it.
yet is basically just no excuse for that
yeah
you know you know that i was a little after like an hour and a half it is just
like
it's hard to stay on your feet
you know i would do d_d_r_ if they brief if they changed it from
being dancing if they say if i get some a trick myself into thinking that it was
some kind of
boxing footwork game where they like
it's a r_u_d_ you pretend you're fighting fucking a vendor holyfield and
and uh...
music a song plays. What if you were dancing along to Rap God by Eminem?
Specifically the verse where he goes, you know, "Real hard." Say what now? Yeah. What the fuck did you just say?
Okay. I saw a guy on YouTube yesterday just post a like a 30 second 200 note
chart where he was doing the verse from Rap God just doing like you know. And
you're telling me that he you're telling me that he lived to post this video. Yeah
Yeah he looked exhausted. He looked like he just ran a marathon in 20 seconds.
Was he white?
No he's Korean. He's the shirtless Korean man that I watch.
That's awesome.
Completely shirtless.
Completely normally by the way.
Okay. Alright, why does he put on a shirt I guess is my only question that I have for
you.
Because he's so sweaty after.
Yeah I mean, just sweat through your shirt man.
No.
Do you guys sweat a lot?
Me? Yeah. I'm sweating right now.
I took Ashwagandha before this. I'm sweating bullets.
Wow. You took Ashwagandha before...
I don't think that's how Ashwagandha works.
It's in the blend that I took.
The four pills that I took that had Ashwagandha in it.
Dude, I'm so excited that you're getting into nootropics.
I know.
Being a supplement guy just feels right for me, doesn't it?
It really does, man.
You already look so much better than you used to.
- You look amazing. - Something incredible change.
- Yeah. - Thank you.
I've been a-- I've done all sorts of kind of odd supplements.
Ever since I was like 15, like, I've just kind of ordered stuff that I thought was funny.
- Yeah. - And started eating it.
- I took-- - I used to do--
- Colloidal gold. I took colloidal gold. - Really?
- Yeah. Not even silver, gold. - Wow.
- Why gold? - 'Cause it's fun.
- That's just plain good luck. - Yeah, exactly.
eating gold. Blessed by a Reiki master, it was $30 for a droplet bottle and it looks
amazing and smells exactly like cum. It looks like cum. It straight up just looks exactly like cum.
Some guy sold you cum.
Said it was gold and he was like some fucking jew's gonna order this and put it in his mouth.
He's really underselling it because it was like $30 and to fill up a bottle
That big with cum would not be worth it.
That's like not valuing your time though.
I will say, cum, in a weight sense, cum has to be worth more than gold, right?
Right. 100%. Good cum? Reiki master cum?
It would take me a year and a half to fill up, to break the surface tension on the top of a penny with my cum.
That's how little my fucking... that's how little my loads are.
Yeah, this dude's making $30 every six months.
That's a sign of a slob.
It's called passive income.
Yeah.
No, you gotta work for that, dude.
You have to work for that shit.
You know what they say?
Do what you love, you'll never work a day in your life.
That's right.
That's true.
Yeah, I like cumming a single fucking quark once a day.
Dude, me and Noah, when we were in high school,
I ordered something called Zataichi Lucid Dreaming Tea.
Oh my God.
And it was really expensive.
It was like, I think I'd just gotten a job,
I was like 16, I was working as a parking attendant,
and I finally had like a checkings account.
So I was ordering shit online,
and I ordered this shit 'cause I was getting really
into lucid dreaming 'cause of Sinbad, the comedian.
He talked about lucid dreaming and astral projection.
I was like, I'm gonna do all this shit too.
So I ordered it and it came and I was so excited for it.
It was like $80 and I opened up the package.
It was like a silver package.
I opened it up and it was literally just like wood.
It was like mulch.
There's like no herb in it at all.
It's like pieces of twigs and branches and wood and shit.
I was like, ah, fuck it, dude.
The monks probably know better than me.
So Noah came over, and it was I think 4th of July or some shit.
And we brewed this tea, and it was truly to this day the most like despicably disgusting
unpalatable thing I've ever had in my mouth.
And so we like tried drinking it and then we ended up cutting it with lemonade, it didn't
help at all, it made it worse.
Chug the entire thing, we go to sleep, and the next day we woke up and we were like, "Oh
man, did you have any dreams at all?"
And we're like, "Nope, not even a single dream."
So then I gave it to somebody, I don't remember who, but I gave it to somebody because I told
them about it and they were like, "That sounds amazing."
I was like, "I just told you it didn't fucking work."
I kind of want to get back into lucid dreaming, that sounds pretty--
Yeah, have you ever known anyone that's had experiences with that?
I used to know this kid in high school.
- Lucid dreaming?
- Who told me about this very real,
I don't know, detailed experience about him taking a nap
and being like, "Whoa, dude, I was out of my body
"and I was walking around and I saw myself
"and I saw my brother in the other room
"and he was just playing a game."
And I was like, "Wow, this is the most incredible story
"I've ever heard in my entire life."
But I never really have done it myself,
So I just want to know if you guys have any experience.
- I used to lucid, the reason I bought the T
is I used to lucid dream very often.
That was like, yeah, 'cause I was, you know,
I was homeschooled, I had nothing else going on.
So I would just like sit in my room
and try to lucid dream and astral project.
(laughing)
Mostly, I tried to ask for, I tried to ask for, yeah.
I tried to ask for projecting one time
'cause I was like, you know what?
I don't think this is real, but it's worth a shot.
you know, my time isn't worth that much.
And so the whole point,
the whole thing with astral projecting
is that you sit on your bed
and you like put something in front of you.
Like for me, I think it was a pair of socks
that I put in front of me.
And then you close your eyes
and you just kind of like empty your head
until you're like right about to fall asleep.
And then right as you're about to fall asleep,
you're supposed to reach out and try to grab the thing.
And so that is supposed to like, for whatever reason,
you're in that split second where you're about to fall asleep
you're some Casper-like ghost that's sitting in your body
decides it's time to leave.
And so I tried it.
And then I just woke up the next day.
I just slept the entire night.
I tried it at like 7 p.m.
and I just woke up the next day at like 8.
I just slept a bunch.
But I had a fair amount of lucid dreaming experience.
My first one ever, I think I was 14,
and I had a dream that I hooked up
with my cousin's girlfriend.
- Okay.
- Well, not a dream that I did.
I went into the dream and I was like,
I thought she was so hot, and I was like,
we're going on a date in my dream world.
And then I mostly played basically Roblox
with the rest of my time, where I was like building,
I built like a city.
See, lucid dreams never make any sense
when you try to explain them to somebody.
But when you're doing them,
they are pretty much in the top two coolest things
that you can do as a person, I would say.
- Yeah.
You're supposed to have like an object
that reminds you you're dreaming, right?
Like a red ball or some shit like that?
- I never did that shit.
That's some, nah man, fuck that.
I don't give a fuck if I'm dreaming or not.
That's not my business.
- Have you ever heard about like tulpas?
Where you like give yourself schizophrenia?
No.
There's like a, it used to be a big thing among like the, the brony community where you would basically give yourself schizophrenia and then imagine you were talking to like Applejack.
Uh, and then-
How do you do that?
I'm not sure. I never delved too far into it. I don't know the techniques.
But I think-
That's bullshit. There's no way that you can give yourself schizophrenia. I mean you can give yourself schizophrenia for your feed for sure.
No, you can absolutely, no you can give yourself schizophrenia if you try hard enough.
I've done it. I've given myself momentary, like week-long bouts of schizophrenia just by like
intensely focusing on like someone's tweets for too long and trying to
Imagine what their inner mind looks like
So you can make fun of it better
For me if you just if you don't if I don't sleep for a couple days it starts to get pretty bad
Oh, yeah, Toba is a seemingly sentient autonomous mental companion. Okay. Yeah
I used to you know during my Adderall days I'd be up for like you know 48 72 hours
And there'd be like a cutoff point where you'd start to like go a little crazy, and you'd start to hear
Voices and you get really paranoid and then like during that period you would literally like just develop schizophrenia
Yeah, that's just you know yeah, it was awesome
I'd like constantly be like looking out of like a window and shit like being like
Fucking rear window just to my neighbors
my most
Powerful recent kind of mental delusion is that I thought I
Thought there was a guy in my neighborhood those actively trying to kidnap Phil
My dog yeah, yeah, I think I told you about I was like he's seriously
Weird and then one of the reasons why I was like I was like you know you when you're in that kind of
Mode you're being paranoid you like
Kind of make ties that don't really exist. So one of the reasons why I thought he would do this is because
One time he pulled up to a red light. I saw him pull up to a red light in his car and
He finished his bottle of Gatorade and he threw the Gatorade bottle out of the window and in my brain
I was like this guy is clearly an evil person if he would litter so what else would he do, right?
He's capable of anything.
He's capable of great acts of evil, like littering the day before the street sweeper comes.
So it's pretty, I mean it's scary.
Abundantly.
Yeah.
Well thankfully I take these healthy brain pills.
Is that what they're called?
Yep.
They're traditional Chinese medicine.
You take nine of them.
Here's the thing about traditional Chinese medicine man if you empty one of those pills onto a fucking chicken thigh
It's gonna be the greatest
Yeah, it's just season. It's a ball of season. It's literally a
Monterey steak seasoning blend yeah
How do you know what some brides?
Traditional Chinese medicine is but how can you tell from the traditional? How can you tell how to traditional?
Yeah, how do we know that the manufacturers of this this bottle know their traditions?
What do they take? Well, I assume Qingdao Growful Pharmaceutical Co. Limited
Knows what they're doing
What what's in that bad boy? You want me to read the ingredients to you?
Yeah, hit me with the highlights at the very least. All right, so top one jujube seed
Then we got dong quai root
Chinese yam rhizome
Lycium berry, schisandra fruit, amber, red-rooted sage root, oriental ginseng, and oriental arbovitae
seed.
Okay, so ginseng is pretty much the only thing in there, right?
Yeah.
You can't just be like, oh yeah, there's Chinese seeds in this.
There's Chinese carrot seeds in this.
And they're little tiny brown balls and you take literally nine of them three times a
day.
What?
Yeah.
Nine, three times a day?
Yeah, it goes absurdly fast.
It's like...
Tell me, so how long have you been taking these nootropics?
So I started the nootropics like a week and a half ago.
Have you noticed any difference?
How are you feeling?
I've done controls, right?
Because there's caffeine in them.
So I've balanced it.
I've tried just a monster, which has more caffeine.
And what I think it is, is there's L-theanine in the nootropics that just make it better
caffeine.
And none of the other shit works.
So you really just need to be taking L-theanine.
Right.
I'm paying $75 a month for L-theanine.
Yeah, it's a pretty, it might be 15 bucks for 90 capsules of L-Theanine if you just order
that.
Yeah, exactly.
You know, they sell, here I'll show you, so here's one I haven't tried yet.
Here's Logic, like the wrapper.
And it comes...
So I'm curious because the, wait, wow, oh it comes in its own little thing.
Yeah.
Oh wait, I know that company, what are they called?
Thesis.
on Instagram and they caught me at a particularly low moment in my life where I was susceptible
to buying things on Instagram.
I also like that like I know that company has ones that are called like Mood and like
Energy, and you bought Lodge.
No, hold on.
So they, here's the thing, right?
So they send you a survey that you fill out where they're like, you know, what's wrong
with your brain and I'm like, I'm fucking retarded. Give me the best you got. And they're like,
at the, you know, you know how like with your DNA, they were like, 99% of people have less
Neanderthal DNA than you. They were like, 97% of people scored higher on our survey for
getting a more normal brain. So they were like, here's what you need. Because they send
you four blends to start with and then they like, kind of send you a follow up email to
be like which ones worked for you, which ones didn't. So you get energy, you get creativity,
which is what I took for this one. And logic.
That's why you're so creative right now.
You know that it takes, any pill is going to take longer than, you took it one minute
before we pressed record.
Yup, and it's completely working right now. I feel so creative. I'm creating right now.
You seem creative. I'm getting a lot of creative kind of stuff.
What's your most creative idea right now?
Should it?
No because it's my business, dude.
I got a business idea.
I don't want to talk about it.
It's a stress relieving item shaped like a certain body part for people to chew on and
kind of – but it's for relieving stress.
You're making a dildo made of bubble gum?
That's a pretty good idea actually.
I had an idea the other day.
Because I hate movie theaters.
I hate movie theaters.
Every time I go to a movie theater I freak out and I run out at some point and I have
to go to the bathroom and piss into the toilet to collect myself.
I was thinking about a movie theater that is just individual little rooms with just
normal-sized TVs, nothing crazy, but you're this close to them so it might as well be a
big ass thing. You still get the experience, right? And you can have single person rooms,
you can have two person rooms, you can have ten person rooms if you want to bring your
whole family, right? And they're just kind of little stalls right next to each other.
Tell me that this is not the worst idea you've ever heard.
It's really bad.
It's a bad idea.
If we're doing Shark Tank, I got another I came up with the other day.
Isn't that just like the urinals of like the Chili's?
You just stand in front of the urinal, they have like, some of those have like screens
where it would like just show you ads.
There definitely has to be a bathroom there so you don't miss any of the shit.
So yeah, it's a bathroom with a TV.
Or if you need to pump gas, maybe it could be a little screen right there too.
Yeah, they definitely don't have those yet.
Here's my idea, you ready for this?
It's a thing you put on your wall that will make noise, it'll like vibrate the wall in
a perfect way to block the sounds of sex coming through the wall.
So it works both ways, right?
So imagine a hotel, right?
You know you're gonna be, you're fucking, right?
You're getting it on.
And you don't want anyone around you to hear it.
So you turn it on and it just sounds like TV static and like reruns of Seinfeld.
Which the TV that's in the hotel room wouldn't do the job.
Right, of course not.
But, you know, imagine the reverse of that.
Which is, you're in the other-
Is this like a portal thing?
Yes.
And then the reverse of that, which is, you're on the other wall of someone getting their
shit on.
They're being loud, they're being obnoxious, they're banging the bed into the wall, just
being fucking annoying.
if you could hear like you know some sort of music that distracted you from that.
You know? So it's a speaker that you take with you it just like sticks to the wall.
It's a speaker that can only play one song. Yeah. But no no no it uses like like artificial
intelligence to figure out the rhythm that's going on and then like matches it to you.
you. Right? So you kind of like don't figure it out for a minute. Like you can reasonably
decide in your head that you're not actually listening to someone who's not.
Somebody might be hanging a painting.
Exactly.
Yeah, that's actually a pretty good idea.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Yeah. Because, I mean, I don't know. That is...
One of the worst experiences is listening to someone else have sex. It's not enjoyable
for anyone involved. You know, knowing someone is hearing you have sex, that sucks. Hearing
someone is even worse.
Yeah. Luckily I'm never really, I'm not very good at sex, so I'm never like banging the
headboard against the wall or anything. You know, I'm usually falling asleep in the middle
of it. Usually doing it in like the one chair in my house that I can do without hurting my
hips right I don't I don't really have to worry about this on the chair on this
product this problem but some people probably do yeah well you know you put
a plegic so you can't really do it anyways and I live next to a lesbian so
I actually like hearing the sounds mmm yeah yeah what sounds they make yeah
it's mostly like this I mean I count it from the time when they start cooking
each other a meal that's your wall speaker yeah I go again and then I'm
hearing they're watching fucking devil wears Prada they have the bass turned up
all the way on the movie right and then they start getting hot and heavy right
and I hear 500 buttons unbuttoned from a flannel.
It's pretty amazing.
Alright, I'm opening my second beer.
But it's not a beer, guys. I'm going to be real with you.
What is it?
It's a White Claw Ruby Grapefruit.
Amazing. I thought about drinking a wine cooler as my second beer.
That's a great idea.
I haven't had a wine cooler in so long. A Seagram's. Yeah, that's the only brand I know of that
makes wine coolers still. A blue looking Seagram's that I looked at in the fridge and then said
"eh, maybe next time." Yeah, it just wasn't that tempting. I think we should expand the
bird category to anything that has alcohol in it. I think we ought to be more exclusive.
Because honestly, this is the only time I drink beer.
And this is also, this is probably the most alcohol I drink in an average week.
Yeah.
Uh, Brex, who's this guy?
I'm a fucking loser, dude.
Nice.
Um.
[laughter]
He showed his ass.
I
Love that you live in a an actual frat
Yeah, that's the problem that the fact that he's in a hallway
So yeah, if you want to leave the house you have to go through at least when you lived in the dinner
He's doing you had some
Yeah, that's where the idea of the sex oh, yeah, wait, what am I fit of course you can't have sex in that room
I've done it, but if you do you have to like alert everybody in the house
You have to make sure there's nobody in the rooms on the other side right got a lot like schedule thing
Yeah, yeah, it's unpleasant
born of necessity
Yeah, I guess that is amazing. Thank you I
Think I'm going to watch one of the Steve Jobs doc or
Biopics pretty soon because I need to be inspired to be an amazing great man and leader. Yeah
CEO I think you could do a good job of encouraging people. I don't think so. The problem is I'm Johnny Ives
Yeah, I'm no Steve Jobs. I'm Johnny Ives
Yeah, I know what you're talking about. That's the guy the bald British guy in the Apple commercials
we'd be like, "We actually made it completely out of metal this time."
That dude.
You don't remember that guy?
Nope.
I've only known of one Apple commercial and we don't want to recite it right now.
[Laughter]
It's really bad.
That's not appropriate.
It's not even funny.
But Rex is going to recite it right now.
Go ahead.
I'm not going to do that.
Rex, Rex, what do you guys, where do we think we'll be in 10 years, guys?
What do you mean?
Where, what kind of stuff do you think we'll be doing in 10 years from now?
This is a kind of drinking talk that I like engaging in.
Yeah, yeah.
Probably on the phone.
You will definitely be on the phone.
Yeah.
For me, it's like, best case scenario, I'm gaming.
I'm jacking off three times a day.
I'm jacking, I'm reading books that are, you know, for babies.
- Yeah.
- Worst case scenario, I'm doing,
- You're literally reading.
- Worst case scenario, I'm doing the same thing.
- You're doing like a, like a Superman schedule
where you like follow a strict thing,
but it's like first meal chicken nuggets.
And then like the reading thing,
like you're cracking open good night moon yeah like a reading light one of those
curved reading lights you have a kindle copy of good night moon I think the best
and worst case scenarios are exactly the same thing for me it's just yeah one I
have more money than the other the true the middle ground is the one that sucks
where I just have a job yeah we I was talking with wifey about a job there's
and someone I know has that seems pretty miserable,
but it makes them super, super rich.
And I was like, man, should I try to get a job like that?
She was like, fuck no.
- Yeah.
- And I was like, oh, this is the real difference
between men and women, is that I would love
to make a million dollars and hate
every single second of it.
- Yeah.
- And she just wouldn't do that.
- Yeah. - What's the job?
The job is Alaskan crab fisherman.
Mmm.
No.
That would be sick.
You'd be awesome at that, I feel like.
It doesn't matter what the job, any job.
Your head would like get covered in ice.
They'd have to like-
I wanted to do that when I was a kid.
Yeah.
I used to watch Deadliest Catch.
Right.
And I was like, man, that just seems like the perfect job for me.
But then I got to high school age and I didn't know what kind of degree to pursue that would
in with me being shipped up to Alaska. But then I know somebody who ended up
working at a fish cannery in Alaska and they said that it was the most amazing
experience of their life and they got paid less than minimum wage.
But they loved it. But also this person's not particularly smart I would say.
Yeah. The one job that I think of like that where it's like a lot of
effort and I think they pay them a lot is those ones we like to have like
to climb like a big tower to change a single light bulb.
- Oh man.
- This guy has to do this thing for like,
once every two years, but he gets paid $60 million to do it.
And I'm like, I wanna do that.
Can I do that?
- Those are good jobs.
You know what you could pursue is deep sea,
there we go, ooh, a guava cart.
That looks good, I haven't had that one.
- I thought it said wabba cart.
- Deep sea welding is something that you can do.
So you work on like oil rigs and you weld stuff,
but it takes like, the way that you do it
is that you only work like six months
out of every two years, but for that six months
you live in an underwater bubble
and like 10% of everybody who's ever had this job
just dies in the most horrific possible way.
But you make like 500 grand a year.
- Yeah.
It's cool.
water welding is really cool. Yeah. I don't think I could weld. I don't think I would be
good at welding. Yeah. My problem with it is that it doesn't make any sense because it's
fire underwater. That's why it's so hard. Right. That's true. The entire warlocks. Yeah,
exactly. They have to find the only wizards that are still alive after a hundred years.
Yeah, it doesn't really make any sense to me.
Yeah.
Honestly, my dream job is professional gambler.
Oh, for sure.
I mean, that's obviously like, for me, retirement is just like gambling on Twitch all day.
And they took that from me.
That is so fucked up.
Luckily you're going to Kik.
Right, exactly.
We're sending you right over to Kik.
It is funny that you would be such an amazing Terrain Wrecks TV.
I know.
I was like, if you just, 'cause you have that in you.
- I do. - That exact lifestyle
you have in you is so, like.
- If that existed like seven years ago,
you wouldn't even know me.
- If you had just had the idea first, that would be you.
- I know.
I didn't know about gambling at the time.
When I was 19, I didn't know what gambling was.
It took me until I was 25.
And then unlock something in me.
- Did we gamble together for your first time?
For real, yeah.
Yeah, 100%.
Wow.
Amazing.
Yep.
And just like anything else, I immediately got addicted to it.
Yeah.
Pretty much anything that's...
I could see myself getting addicted to everything, you know?
It's so easy.
Yeah.
Everything is so great.
I don't understand how you can be depressed when everything is so awesome.
There's drugs and gambling and everything that's fun to do in the world.
You are right.
Yeah.
You know just to distract yourself with stuff that ruins your life instead. Yeah, who gives a fuck man?
You're not that important. You don't need to like write a book
Yeah, you fuck you need to find the thing that gets you
So addicted that you forget about everything else
Yeah, you need to literally devote your life to going into debt to like I'm the opposite
I don't think I could ever get a bye Toshi. I
Think that that a jubio. I think that you are afraid of just how unbelievably addicted you could get to anything
Yeah, I think that you have set to measured
Such a such an open dopamine loop that anything could sneak in there
Anything dude you could get addicted to fucking frying eggs
Anything no I am I've got a perfectly strong will
And I can never get addicted to anything.
I mean, I do too. That's why I've never been addicted to anything in my entire life.
I just get infinitely close and then back off at the last second.
Literally like unmeasurable the distance between where you are and addiction.
The untrained eye would never be able to tell the difference.
But I can stop anytime I want.
You walk right up to the edge.
You know what we should do?
We should start like Big Brother but for like gambling streamers.
I just have a house with a bunch of cameras and it's just people gambling all day on YouTube.
But that completely removes the drama that makes Big Brother at all an entertaining show
because nobody's going to leave their room.
You think Trainwrecks has ever left the six runescape tile distance that it takes for
him to walk to the kitchen sink and do code?
I used to just brother as like an example of an ongoing thing forever.
You just think we should have CCTV cams that sit in these people's houses?
Yeah.
Alright.
Yeah, I think we will watch that.
I think in general, I would love to watch every single Twitch streamer with more than 10,000
average viewers.
Just see what their inner life is like.
I would-
That's not good.
Yeah, it's not good.
And that's the point.
Yeah. No, I want to see Hasan like head in hands depressed 18 hours a day.
Do you guys... I'm sure he does that on Twitch. I think you guys ever think about how like
most people that you meet like who are even just like a year or two older than
us just have no idea what we're talking about when it comes to like like nobody
knows if they're over 30 who like a Twitch streamer is. Oh yeah. My brother could not
name a single one. Yeah. Yeah. It's for very, it's for people who are addicted to their
phones. Yeah. Whereas your brother, you know, he has much cooler addictions. That's true.
Pool, playing pool. Playing pool. Yep. Pool and golf. That is a pretty amazing combo. Oh
Dude, that's the awesomest, yeah.
He would, your brother would be the most successful
businessman alive 30 years ago.
- There's no doubt, yeah.
If you put him in Glen Gary, Glen Ross, he'd be like--
- Yeah, he's Alec Baldwin.
- Rushing it, dude.
- Yeah.
- He'd be crushing it.
- I feel like there is a,
you know, the connector from the Matrix?
that goes into your neck.
I feel like somebody is
kind of fucking it up every single time they try to plug it in.
And it just keeps hitting the most painful part of my spinal cord
over and over and over again.
Yeah. I think you do need help.
You legitimately should go to a doctor.
Shut your bitch ass up!
You know this!
What? The doctor doesn't do anything for stuff like this.
Maybe you should go to a chiropractor.
That's a bunch of malarkey.
So he breaks your back, you're like, "Alright, here you go, you're done, bud."
You're like, "Oh, thank you." And then like in an hour, you die.
I would rather be fully, permanently paralyzed than whatever in-between state I'm in right now,
where I can't fucking tie my shoes.
You don't have shoes you could just put on?
I do. I just was using that as an example. I can't tie my shoes normally, okay?
I think you're kind of currently that, you know, when you're watching one of those documentaries
with like, yeah, and Gary was just walking around with this pain in his ass for a month.
Little did he know.
Little did he know he had ass cancer and he died one day from the explosion.
You think I had spine cancer that was suddenly on set at the exact time that I was lifting
a hundred pound weight in the worst way possible?
I think, yeah, yes.
- That'd just be plain unlucky, man.
- Yeah, you slip the disc
and it turned the cancer into overdrive.
- I could have a slipped disc,
but I think slipped discs usually happen
at the bottom of your back.
So I'm not gonna worry about it.
- You probably just tweaked your neck and pulled a muscle.
- I'll tell you what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna eat about two and a half milligrams of THC
and I'm gonna play Counter-Strike Surf
for the next two and a half hours just silently.
- Is that your new addiction?
- That is honestly the most addicted I've ever been
to maybe anything right now.
Is I'm addicted to Counter-Strike Surf.
Yeah.
- You should get into TFT with us.
Requires no movement, no fast movements whatsoever.
- But it's completely reading.
- Not really.
- No, it's just, it requires thought.
it's looking at pictures all day
okay i'll put it to you to get this
most most might have a new rex just
just like spends together in the disco called is completely silent for the
alia
but what's really for us on side filled and we just watch that and play it
that's not a little fiend
uh... seinfeld deemed crossword today in new york times and across the world
were at least
or at least jewish there's a lot of there was multiple seinfeld glad you can tell
the difference and i really can't
And I actually now that I think about it, it's only a Jewish themed crossword.
But one of them was, it was a roll on Seinfeld and it was Elaine.
And I was like, huh, oh, it's Seinfeld.
And then it was like, chutzpah and like, Hebrew word for this.
And I was like, it is Seinfeld themed.
Wow.
This is Seinfeld.
This is Curb Your Enthusiasm.
Yeah.
I think you didn't get to make that joke.
That's the only two Jewish shows, right?
What are some other...
Is there other Jewish shows?
Well, right. I mean, all of them are obviously Jewish shows.
But like, you know...
That's like it.
Those are the most, at least.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Is there some sort of like Jewish cartoon?
Young Sheldon.
Is Sheldon Jewish?
I've never watched The Big Bang Theory.
He's annoying, but I don't know if he's Jewish.
No, he's not Jewish.
I know, I'm reading it in your eyes, it's like a teleprompter.
I love all Jewish people so much, man.
I know.
I wish I would do anything to switch my life for yours.
Yeah, sure, why not?
I really just want a Jewish mom so badly because they're so hot.
You really don't, dude.
They're so hot, dude.
talked about how hot your mom is I know she's a fox yeah might be but you would
do when you know when somebody even gets to the point where they say my mom might
be hot okay so by my friend right now I wasn't right now no I wasn't like she
ruined friendships for me as like a kid cuz like this you fucking all your
fucking buddies no but he said yes I said he said yeah hold on no no no you
said yes I first of all as a kid I wanted my mom to like I because I
watched a lot of stand-up comedy and my mom was so annoying and uptight in my
head I like after watching you know enough comedy I was like the problem is
my mom isn't getting laid. She needs to fuck something so she can fucking stop
just bothering me all the time. So like I remember she had this like boyfriend and
he's talking about getting like a like a Hummer like the like the you know the
SUV. Oh yeah. And I was like yeah hey mom this guy needs a Hummer okay you should
give him a Hummer like like I was like trying to like get her laid because I was
She'll stop being so fucking annoying
If she gets a dick yeah, she gets a dick you know and my 12 year old 11 year old brain that made sense
Obviously, I don't think anything
Nothing would have saved her an 11 year old to be thinking about it's like I need to get my mom
I need to get some guy to rail my mom so she shuts up. Yeah
I've always been thinking it's like you you've always been thinking about your mom getting railed
No, no, just admitted that ways to get rid of shut up to get her. Yeah, like a fucking dick in her mouth
So she can't talk
What is wrong with you if you were my son thinking about the specifics?
I would suck your penis if you were my son honestly
All right, I gotta go piss
Okay
(rock music)
I'm sorry
[BLANK_AUDIO]