(sipping)
(burping)
- You're listening to Beers We Drink,
America's number one beer podcast.
(record scratching)
(upbeat music)
- What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that move on.
(gagging)
- This is a journey of interstitial,
- Plain and kind,
- Bud Light,
Food ribbon!
Beers we drank, motherfucker,
with Jubio, Caleb and Rex.
Much better.
Oh, you start. Hold on.
Wait, hold on.
You said you were ready. What the fuck?
Oh, I just it wasn't that ready.
I thought you were going to say, like, are you ready?
Go.
All right. You go first, Jubio.
I've gone first so many times recently.
OK. Today I am paying
my respects to the
the great nation of Japan.
And I got something that's called the lemon dour,
lemon dour, lemon sour, honey, lemon, lemon, dour, lemon, sour.
Come on, sour.
Yeah, I don't I've never had one of these before.
And I saw the can and I saw that it said shit in Japanese.
And I was like, well, that sounds Japan.
Yeah, Japan.
So you did. Yeah.
-Shitty beer America, shitty beer Japan.
-Yes, that's right.
-Basically, today's the meme episode as well.
We're going to be just reciting memes that we thought about for the entire episode.
-You will never-- He will never drink a Japanese beer.
-Goes to the-- Fuck, I was thinking of a bad luck Brian,
but I couldn't think of one.
Goes to Japan, gets a beer.
And it sucks.
And it's not good.
It's a second meme that just has the top of part of it.
It's a two page.
It's a front and back printed side.
Right.
Yeah.
Take a sip to give us a review.
I'll tell you what I have.
It's lemon and sour.
OK, you have lemon and sour.
A high score.
(laughing)
- Okay.
And what are the notes on this one?
- Lemonade, mango, passion fruit, and raspberry.
- Take a sip.
- Do you think he's ever gonna run out of video game beers
before he leaves the country?
- Never, never ever.
- You don't look good.
- Give it a number, give it a number.
We are now going--
- I would not give it a high score.
I'll give it a low score.
- Nice.
Yeah, it's like a five out of ten so far. It's okay.
What's the high score over here?
Yeah, it's a low score.
Probably like Brian.
Or Penguin.
Well, me today, I have a...
This peaked my interest, caught my eye over there at the grocery store.
I have a giant hard tea.
Kiwi strawberry hard yerba mate.
The fucking Alexa timer's going off, goddammit.
Shut up!
Sorry. The Giant Hard Tea Yerba Mate Craft Brewed Sparkling Tea Kiwi Strawberry.
It's only got 4 grams of sugar.
It's called Giant. I thought it was Bakely. Huge.
It's not that huge. I would say it's...
It's probably a small, normal-sized can.
It's a smaller tall boy. It's 19.2.
It looks like a normal can if you put it next to your head.
It's a small boy can.
It should be very small.
You have the big head.
Yeah, you're a tiny you're a tiny guy.
Yeah, you're a small baby.
No, I'm not that small.
I'm going to take my sip.
It does not taste anything like alcohol, I'm going to be honest with you.
That's good.
What is it? Just tea?
It's a hard yerba mate, like kind of hard kombucha, I guess.
Yeah. Isn't yerba mate like a caffeinated beverage?
Yeah, you're gonna be wired, bro.
It's funny that you say that.
It has less than 25 milligrams of naturally occurring caffeine.
So probably around--
Does it have any energy effects of Yerba Mate?
Well, I believe that is just caffeine from Yerba Mate.
My mate?
That is the energizing effect.
How much caffeine is in a regular Coke?
Like 60?
60-something?
Yeah.
65?
Less than a Coke?
So you'll be fine.
It's less than a Coke.
And it also has that downer kind of thing to it.
Yeah.
Yeah. It's not very good. I'll probably never get this again.
I'm a downer when I'm drinking my beer.
Right.
You're having every last drop of these. Okay. Beer report. Wait,
who knew this was coming? Beer report this week.
I went to Evil Twin Brewing Company in Brooklyn,
New York City the other day.
and I had two beers. One of them was a sangria sour, not my kind of thing. It was way too sweet.
I got a 10 ounce. I probably could have drank four ounces of it. Been happy. The second one though
is a beer called, and I remember Noah talked about this when we had him on. It's a beer called a
Hefeweizen. It tasted like, drum roll please. My boat's in shit. That's my bet. No. Tasted like
- I don't quite.
- A banana.
- Yummy.
- Oh, okay.
(laughs)
Banana beer?
- So, it was amazing.
Monkeys take note.
This is the beer for you.
Any monkey who listens, this is your beer.
This is an amazing beer.
- Well, monkeys make wine.
Monkeys are into wine.
- Oh, isn't--
- Explain.
- They make wine?
- Explain this.
- What are you saying?
- I don't understand, what are you saying?
- No, they just love to make, they make booze.
They make wine.
- No, they don't.
You're lying.
- They do, and they drink it.
- Monkeys don't make wine.
and make you drink it.
- It's real.
- You're thinking-- - Believe me.
- You're thinking of humans. - You're thinking of the joke.
- Why don't you believe me?
- Why did I not believe you that you said monkeys make wine?
I don't know.
- 'Cause they make wine, dude.
- And they prepare it over beer as well.
- Well, they don't know how to make beer.
They have wine stuff. - That's true.
- But they know how to make wine?
- Yeah.
They know how to make wine. - You have to explain.
That can't be all you know about this story.
(laughing)
- They have wine stuffing up their stuff.
What are you talking about?
- No, they just, they make wine.
- You just, you keep saying they make wine.
They make wine.
- Okay.
- Can we listen and explain it right now?
You have a really weird article.
- Give us a box explainer about a monkey that makes wine
and maybe I'll believe you, maybe.
'Cause I'm not too trustful of the news.
Also, I'm not sure that would be honest.
- Okay, okay, so here's an article from vinepear.com
And it says monkeys and chimpanzees are making their own wine.
And they extract sap from the raffia palm trees.
They let it ferment, creating a palm wine,
which is similar to how we let grapes ferment to make regular wine.
So they make a wine and then they use a leaf sponge.
A leaf absorbs the sap and then they sip it almost like a cup.
And there's a video
Well, that's very very sweet. We could only show the video work, but what do you watch it and recreate it with stuff in your room?
Scooping what looks like why I guess I could be construed as scooping wine into your mouth
No, I was watching the video and recreating it he's got like
You never I've never really realized how much you look like a monkey
Monkey arms and hands
You're my most ape-like friend. Yeah, you kind of are you see you're kind of a mix
Yeah, monkey and ape of monkey and human. Mm-hmm. Well, thank you. Yeah
I do like to pick things up with my feet
I think it's a play really fucking good at that and if we're gonna have a competition about that next we can do that
I used to be able to control the remote can
Timmy Timmy remote my own kind of remote that I invented that works with your feet
The Alexa's going off again. I think I can control your Alexa with your feet
The last thing I controlled my feet was probably my phone to watch stick dog
I was just scrolling through TikTok with my phone.
- What? - That is insane.
- You can't even see it, it's so far away.
You're a tall guy too.
- Yes, I can.
- Well, if I was like you,
I'd drop it on your face.
- Whoa, okay.
- Wait, how did you imagine this, Rex?
You thought he had it,
you thought he was laying down on the bed?
- Yeah, he's laying down. - Holding his bed,
holding it with one foot,
and then swiping with the other.
- So, Rex still thinks,
he's still thinking about monkeys,
and monkey-like experience. - I think he is.
I think he is thinking about monkey stuff.
The phone is on the floor and I'm just scrolling with my toe.
And it's actually quite easy.
You can do the--
- Okay, so here's my question for you.
- I can take a picture.
- What situation are you in there
where your hands are full,
but you absolutely have to be scrolling TikTok right now?
- Toilet, toilet situation.
- You have both hands full while you take a shit?
What's going on?
- He's wiping with both hands 'cause of his huge hole.
- I believe that.
- He's just rapid firing.
- He's taking a towel and he's just running it through like this.
- You've both been talking all this big game about your feet activities.
I have demonstrable proof that I can take a picture with my foot.
- That's not demonstrable.
We can't see the bottom part of your desk.
There could be a person down there.
You could hire a photographer.
- I am currently winning the monkey competition, by the way.
So, unless one of you in the next 50 or so minutes can...
- How are you winning?
Rex looks exactly like a fucking monkey.
He wins.
Okay, he's trying to do something with his feet now.
This is not good radio.
This is the worst possible radio that you could do.
Okay, do something monkey-like.
Right now.
I can do something maybe for the audio listeners that is monkey-esque.
Okay, go ahead.
Is this supposed to be fucking difficult?
Is this supposed to be fucking difficult to fucking use your toe fingers?
To press buttons made for...
No, you placed it on the floor with your hands. It doesn't count.
No, don't do it again, Rex.
We've got enough of this.
There's plenty of this being done today.
Whoa!
He carried the phone!
This is incredible, Randy. I don't know what you're talking about.
He carried the phone for people listening.
He carried the phone with his foot.
That was really something.
No, he's stuck in two chairs, and now he's stuck and have to call the fire department
great
I think what scares me about that wine story Rex is still going
What scares me about that wine story the most yeah?
It almost seems like the monkeys are evolving right before our very eyes
It does make it seem as though the monkeys have tasted both our beers and our dinner wines
Something disrupt and they have decided to just part and do the they're like empty towels type types
Situation but with monkeys going their own way. Yeah monkeys going there on wine
Okay, you're making that face and all the fucking foot you look crazy
You can't see the foot it doesn't there's no credit on the bottom right foot
New monkey challenge post that on Twitter with all your feet
No, you know we can all jump how about that right you start
No, this is jump in slow motion
the
He has gone insane.
What's going on with you, you motherfucker?
Yeah, what's going on?
How's your week going?
It's good.
I'm just, you know, working, spending time with my girlfriend
who is staying with me.
So that's why I haven't been gaming as much.
We need to eliminate every girlfriend in all of our lives.
I know.
I do hate sharing a bed with my girlfriend.
She's always so restless.
I'm asleep in the bed for about two hours,
and then I wake up to pee and I go sleep on the couch
the rest of the night kind of guy.
- Really?
- Yeah, 'cause I want the symbolism of,
I go to bed, I wanna be going to sleep
in the same bed as my wife,
but she really is a fucking complete monster
who farts and-- - A monster?
- Is, yeah.
The other thing is, man, people are too,
women are too warm when they sleep.
- They are. - Get the fuck away from me.
You warm bitch. - They don't know how to
respect boundaries and they are really annoying at night.
And also, they talk too much.
- True, I agree.
- Nope.
- They talk way too much.
- I'm actually really jealous of your situation.
I can't do that right now.
- Why's that?
- It's so hot down here.
Like, the climate is so fucking hot.
If I thought about sleeping on the couch
for a single night, I would probably just die.
- Why?
- Through how long I'm sitting here.
- Oh, okay.
So your bedroom's the only one with AC?
- Yeah, basically.
- You don't have a fan in your living room?
I do, but the air is just hot.
It's just hot air.
Yeah.
The entire apartment.
You should get a second AC unit.
Yeah.
See, my AC unit, my bedroom has no windows,
completely windowless room.
Yeah.
And it's easily the hottest part of the house.
The couch is cold.
Yeah.
Also, your apartment is, no offense,
the smallest apartment in the entire world.
I've seen much smaller apartments.
I knew a guy who lived in a fucking one by one by one.
Really? He just stood up a cube.
He lived in a microcube.
Yeah, that's interesting.
Yeah, but our living room is like a little it's it's big
and there's an AC unit there, but it's like a really small one.
So it wouldn't it would be dumb to turn it off.
It costs $30 to get a fan and have it blow directly onto you.
It's it's.
But it's blowing hot air.
You're misunderstanding.
It's blowing completely hot.
It's hot, humid air.
If it's grass.
You're from the dry, dry parts of this world.
Me and Julio were raised in the Amazon jungle of sorts.
Me, Wilmington, him, Mexico, where it is humid and it is green
and it is mean.
The first house I lived in.
Was it the jungle?
Didn't have any AC in my room.
It was not in the jungle, but it didn't have any AC.
It got about 95 degrees in there during the day.
I would sit directly in front of the fan in nothing but my underwear.
Yeah. And just stew.
And I could sleep just fine in there.
You do understand how much more comfortable that is other than just staying
in the bedroom with an AC unit
that's blowing nice cold air?
Well, no, I don't know, because I experience AC at all times as a
civilized first world person.
Wow.
I just have a window unit, man.
Do you have you have central air in the house?
That's nice, man.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's all about to change.
So, yeah, that's true.
The place I'm looking at has central air.
We're going to change your life.
I didn't even realize, I'm such a fool.
Growing up in the South, I didn't even realize that places didn't have central air.
Yeah.
I didn't even know when people said central air, I didn't even know what that meant.
Because if you don't have air conditioning in the South, you just die.
Mm-hmm.
It's so, so hot there.
It'll be a hundred degrees with a hundred percent humidity.
And you just feel like you're drowning.
Yeah.
It's not pleasant.
No, it's a bad place to live.
So this is my situation at the moment.
it's it's not pleasant to be outside of the AC rooms now it's not fine
not fine I need rescuing I did white rescuing I would wait for you know I do
we could do it I do sometimes think about adopting you
- A visa?
- Yeah, I have a visa.
- That's your credit.
- I have a traveler's visa.
I have good credit.
- Well, I think that you would need,
I think you'd need an excuse to go to America
for a long time.
So it would need to be something like,
you know what you could do?
You could join the American Army.
- Mm.
- I don't wanna do that.
I wouldn't wanna stay at home and play a game.
That's what I wanna do.
I would wanna stay at home and play a game.
- That's what you do in the military.
But you do it with 40 or 50 friends.
No, then I have to like go out there in like the jungle or some shit and talk about how cool it is that I'm...
The jungle? You think the military goes to the jungle?
Well, they gotta stop these monkeys from inventing nuclear bombs next, dude.
Yeah, they got monkey Oppenheimers.
Yeah, there's gonna be some kind of industrial revolution with the monkeys.
where they're doing 2x4 technology,
shooting bananas with rubber bands at people.
That kind of stuff actually scares me.
- Yeah.
I've become a destroyer of trees.
- No, they don't destroy trees, Mike.
- They live on the trees.
- They will, they will.
They're destroying trees.
- Why would they destroy trees?
- With their monkey bombs.
- For attention?
- No, for a war, purposes of war.
Haven't you listened to the Tool songs?
- Crazy, the big wars. - The Tool Song?
- Which Tool Song? - Monkey fighting monkey
over pieces of the ground?
- Is there monkey racism? - Wow.
- Oh yeah.
- Are you kidding?
- Of course.
- It's like they're awful to each other.
- Yeah, and that's what the Bunky Bombs are for.
- The apes eat the monkeys, so apes will--
Yeah, so apes will--
No, it's true.
There's video of apes running into a monkey sanctuary.
- Do apes eat monkeys?
- They do, and they'll eat their brains
and rip their heads off.
- Yeah.
- They're monkey fighting. - What?
- Yeah, they're like, they're predatory.
- Whoa!
- On monkeys. - That's crazy.
I just saw some crazy pictures.
- Yeah, you don't wanna see these pictures.
- Okay, I believe you.
- No. - They rip up,
they eat children, monkey children,
baby monkey children.
- Monkey children?
- Aye-aye from-- - I hate monkey children.
- Super Monkey Ball.
- Yeah. - They do that thing.
If you put a chimp in Super Monkey Ball,
he's breaking into those balls,
he's ripping their arms off. - Isn't that Gongon?
- Isn't GonGon a chimp?
- He's a gorilla.
- A gorilla?
- Well, if he was a realistic chimp,
then he would be doing that.
You know, gorillas actually aren't even that,
gorillas aren't very aggressive.
They're territorial, but not aggressive.
I would rather be stuck in a neutral place
with a gorilla than a chimpanzee, personally.
- Yeah.
- They have the smallest penis.
- Chimpanzees are the ones that just fucking
rip people's faces off, right?
- Yeah, chimps will just go insane for no reason.
Gorillas will just, yeah, also people don't realize,
a gorilla's like five foot one.
Gorillas are not that big, they're big.
But they're not like--
- Yeah, but they're strong. - Like towering over you.
You, whatever.
- They're like-- - Whatever.
- Yeah, they're like kilo size.
- Haven't you ever seen like a really short guy
at the gym that's just like ripped?
- Yes, actually, the owner of the gym that I go to.
The owner of the gym that I go to
is this like five foot three, 250 pound pure muscle guy.
And the other day he was going to do dumbbell bench press,
like with dumbbells.
And he had 120 pound dumbbell in each hand.
And some random fucking guy was sitting there
and he was like, "Hey you, tell me I can't do this."
And he was like, "What?"
And he's like, "Tell me I don't have this shit."
- Damn.
- And oh my God.
- That's all he needed.
- But yeah, and he was like,
"Okay, you don't have this."
He was like, "Say it louder."
He was like, "You don't have this shit.
You can't get this.
You can't get that."
- You can't even reach the pussy.
- And then he did some of the worst reps
I've ever seen in my life.
He was like moving his arm this much up and down.
- You know what?
- But he's huge.
What am I to say?
What am I to criticize?
- I'm not gonna blame him.
I'm gonna place the blame on the guy
who was such a pussy at intimidating this guy
or like getting him fired up.
- I'm gonna say that that guy has a little penis
and that he wants women to bully him for it.
You want him to, you think he gets his things stepped on?
Yeah.
That is a big red high heel.
Yep.
That is also, how do you figure that out?
How do you figure it out though?
You like that?
What situation are you ever on?
Like you get stepped on your balls and you're like, wait a minute.
I can see that.
I think you just watch some videos related to that topic and you're like, hmm, this
interests me.
No.
- What if you get it, what if you,
no, no, I think you get your dick stuck in a doorframe one day
and it gets slammed in there and you go like, "Ah, wait."
- Hold on.
- Yeah, hold, wait, hold the phone.
I actually kind of enjoy that.
- Yeah, what if something happened,
it's one of those situations where someone growing up,
they got their, someone just kicked their balls.
- Oh yeah.
- And then 20 years later, it's like,
actually, I kind of, I'm into that now.
- I mean, it would be cool if your balls got kicked
and you just nutted instantly.
'Cause that would be much better than the regular.
(laughing)
- I've always said this, dude.
- Your balls get kicked, which is you just go,
"Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow."
- I've said this my entire life.
I remember thinking this the first time
I ever got kicked in the balls.
I wish that made me nut.
- Right.
- It is kind of crazy.
I haven't been hit in the balls in some time.
Probably over a year since I got hit in the balls,
but I feel like growing up,
my balls were massacred day in and day out.
Not just by like friends and brothers,
but by like the environment.
I was hitting corners with my balls.
- You're too tall to hit your balls on the table now.
- Well, that's true.
That's a good point.
- You just hurt your leg now.
- Yeah, but I haven't been hitting the ball.
I feel like it's a good kind of reset though.
Maybe I need that soon.
- I remember Pat hitting you in the balls
and then cowering for a day.
He's such a coward.
For a whole day.
Yeah, after, for the revenge.
I fight with him in the exact way that I fight with my little brother, which is I,
they do something to me and I think about doing, I think about doing so, so, yeah,
something so over the top, over the line, way overreaction to them.
But, you know, I do ASMR a lot of the times and binaural beats and Headspace, the app.
So eventually I'm able to center myself and say, you know, man, it's not worth it.
And I'll say this, that is a more affecting thing than attacking them and
maybe stealing their wallet is if you just say, you turn the other cheek.
Yeah.
I've never had this experience.
If you turn the other cheek to me, I would just do that.
I'd probably touch it.
You just touch my cheek?
Yeah, your other cheek.
In like a before sunrise kind of way?
Yeah, just really tenderly.
Like kind of caress it?
Yeah.
I kind of miss fighting with my brothers.
It's such a nice thing to have a food chain.
Yeah, I think this is where our lived experiences are going to differ a lot
because you have brothers.
Oh, you're Mexican.
I only had sisters.
Rex has an only child.
I do.
- I forget that, you so don't strike me as an only child.
- I know, it's 'cause my parents are retarded, so.
- Well, I feel like that's, I admit that as a compliment.
- No, I know, I'm saying it's like, you know,
like an only child is like usually spoiled
'cause it's like the only child.
- Child.
- Right, you know, they don't have to share anything,
they don't get anything.
My parents, Jewish, so I just, you know,
I was just sharing nothing,
but there was nothing to share anyway.
- You had nothing to share.
Yeah, they didn't have like, you know, they'd be like, "We can't afford that."
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I'm sorry, man.
No, it's okay.
I think it's a good experience to grow up with.
Oh, you didn't get toys.
I'm sorry that you grew up in the slums of Arizona.
I didn't grow up in the slums.
Parents did fine for themselves.
They just didn't give me anything.
And that's...
Well...
You put AC in your room, so you spent every single day...
No, that was after I moved out.
I had when I paid $300 a month for rent.
Yeah, because it's hard to forget that somebody with Jewish parents is also Jewish.
Right.
Yeah.
Well, I was just broke, you know.
I don't think you, you shouldn't really move out of your parents' house and then immediately
have a nice apartment.
You need to struggle for a little bit.
My first apartment after I moved out of my parents' house was, I paid more than I do
here.
It was in Boston.
Really?
Yeah, when I was going to college.
It was $1,000 a month.
We didn't have a living room, so we put a couch in the hallway and we had rats that lived in
the apartment.
Not mice, big ass rats.
Jesus.
It was the worst place.
And I was so broke I paid rent late every single month because I got behind one month.
And so the cycle of money that I had for my job just...
So I actually paid $1,100 a month for this fucking terrible apartment.
35 Brookline Street, Central Square, Cambridge.
But I live near a Target where I could steal all the cheese I wanted to.
Whoa. And then you shared it with the rats who also paid rent.
I do. I think I've told this on something before, but we had the rats
and we're like, Jesus Christ, there's fucking rats everywhere.
This is the worst place ever.
And I lived with Neil at the time.
And one day we see turn on his.
He's the only person with AC who turned on his AC when he was gone
and just open all the doors and try to get the house as cool as possible.
And one day I went in there to turn on his AC and it was like the peak of the rat problem.
And he had like four or five plates sitting around his room with different slices of cheese,
like a Tom and Jerry.
Like they would walk out and be like, "Oh!" and like swim in it and like do backstroke.
That was the cheese smorgasbord that he left for the mice or the rats in his room.
Wait, so he did that on purpose?
No, he just like that fucker just likes cheese, and he would fall asleep eating cheese in his bed.
I see, I wonder why he had a problem then. Do you think they had sort of like a
like a mutant ninja turtle situation where you became kind of like a mouse
living in this apartment? You turned into a radioactive rat?
Yeah, I would say I have significantly cut back on my mice like activities
Okay, I eat a half a block of sharp Dublin cheddar today
Yeah, I did but it was with honey, and I dare you to give a mice honey. I think my sake honey
I think they're like sweet thing. Well. I don't know that much about mice
Well you shouldn't know I shouldn't because I'm not one
Don't say ask your parents. Don't say
- I think you would discover too many truths about yourself
if you learned about mice.
- Got ancestry.com and they were just like,
30% of rat DNA.
- Let's look up mice attributes.
- What do mice like?
- Yep, they have mice.
- No, I think this is stupid.
It's gonna be like, they have a tail.
They have gray fur.
- No, no, no, no, if I'm such a mouse.
- Look at the cartoons.
- It's so funny.
Let's do this, okay?
Mice have a slender body, wait.
- You do have a slender body.
- Kind of like that.
- They're small, like a mouse.
- Scantily haired.
Prominent ears.
(laughing)
Thinly furred tail, no.
It may be about as long, oh, that's the tail.
I mean, so far it is, if I had to say it,
it's pretty similar to me. - Like 30%.
Okay, let's look up mice diet though.
Mice diet.
- Yeah, what do mice actually eat?
- Anything.
- Seeds, grains, and other plant material,
as well as invertebrates, small vertebrates, and carrion.
God, I love carrion.
I don't know what that is.
- That shit's yum.
- That shit is yummers.
- I think that is all of you.
That is exactly you.
You've been describing.
- Ugh, I hate to say it,
They say chocolate is hands-down a mice's a mouse's favorite followed closely that I buy peanut butter
Well, I basically just had a chocolate yogurt. So some cheese
That's actually a myth
Yeah, that's a cartoon misconception. You've you fell for Hollywood's lies. Yeah, what might actually hate cheese
They're allergic to it
Based on a lie their best friends with cats actually also
They just really hate dogs and they don't speak English
Not a lick of it
They can't sing a French song. Yeah, that's that's Tom
Did he speak English in that show? I thought it was just just them chasing each other the French cousin does
They do occasionally speak but it's very French mouse in the show. You don't know about about Jerry's cousin
the French
- He has a sword. - J'ai le French.
(singing in French)
- He sings that song?
- That song sounds familiar.
- Yeah. - Yes, 'cause you remember it
from this cartoon.
Nobody's ever heard that song
outside of that cartoon. - Wait, no,
he's not French, he's a baby.
He's just a small mouse.
- But he speaks in a French accent
and he sings a French song,
so you tell me who's French.
- I think you are-- - J'ai le...
Tom and J'ai le...
- Tom and J'ai le...
(laughing)
J'ai le...
These are my pets, Tom and Jerry.
I might go to France at the end of the year.
I am not excited.
I don't want to see that place.
I don't want to be anywhere near them.
I think France is cool.
France is a double-edged sword, because a lot of people
either hate it, or they think they're going to love it
and hate it, or they have normal experiences like me,
which I thought it was a really cool place.
The only experience I've ever had with a French guy is,
my wife has a French uncle.
And growing up, I mean, like in high school,
when we were first dating, he lived,
they lived in France, but they would come to Christmas
in North Carolina.
And every time I saw him, this fucking, this fuck, dude,
every time I saw him, he would be like,
Caleb, you are looking a little bit more potly
and fat than you were last year.
He would like call me fat.
- Yeah.
- What is that?
What kind of guy is he supposed to be?
- That's why you hate France.
- I hate the French.
- Okay.
- Yeah. - I hate the French.
- I hate that specific French guy.
- You are fat and gay.
He would say this shit to me
like every single time I saw him.
- You look like a mouse.
- He'd be like, "What are you doing?"
And I'd be like, "I'm going to college."
And he'd be like, "No, no, no, no."
I don't even know what that means.
- No?
- Sounds like he was saying no.
- He would say, "No, no, no."
Like I'm supposed to be,
You know what it is, just do this.
France have a caste system.
Maybe he thought that I was like a untouchable,
like I shouldn't.
He just didn't like me specifically.
Well, imagine what that means.
Imagine how hard it is to be fat in France.
He was fucking fat.
That's the worst part.
Really?
Yeah, dude, he was a bowling ball.
Oh my God.
Because he went to America often.
Yeah, true.
He goes once a year for Christmas,
barely the rest of the year.
That is often enough.
I think you maybe like it.
Food is poison.
I do think that it's very, I do see it very possible that you can have one of those experiences where you
either just happen to meet a rude person or just don't enjoy the sights
or just think that Paris is just completely dirty as a city
and you'll just come back and be like, yeah that's just, that's completely bullshit.
You think I might think France is bullshit?
You might think that France is bullshit, yeah.
I like ratatouille. That's an amazing movie. I've seen it probably over a hundred times
Okay
so
Yeah, I think that you're gonna completely like it then yeah, I am more interested in I want to see Italy
I want to go to Milan and Rome and
Couple of other cities that I know in Italy and do what eat food cheese. He's gonna eat
I want to drink all the cheese.
Drink what, wine?
I want to drink everything they have.
A beautiful Amaro's and amazing apertifs
that they have in beautiful Italy.
I want to go to the Milan Camparino.
They have a Campari bar there
that's run by the Campari group,
where they do Campari only cocktails.
Didn't Noah tell you that?
No, I found this out from a YouTube video.
Thank you very much.
(laughing)
'Cause I've seen a lot of YouTube.
- True.
- Would you do one of those like tours
where it's just like you and like 30 other people
just in a bus going to like different cities?
- No, I will probably do something very authentic.
- Which is?
- Just, I'll just see if I can find a job,
kind of work there for a week.
- Yeah.
- That kind of thing.
I want the real experience of Italy.
I wanna work in Venice but live two hours away
and I have to commute in to drive up an old boat.
That's the kind of thing that I wanna do.
- I think you should go to Belgium.
- That would be nice.
- Belgium's a beautiful place.
- Fuck that, man.
- Belgium is lovely.
- I wanna go to the beach.
I wanna be sitting on the beach doing super bass stuff.
I don't wanna be in Belgium.
What do you even do in Belgium?
- You walk around, you eat some Belgian waffles.
You hang out.
- I hate sweets and desserts.
- I see.
- This is not my country.
- Cap.
- That is not cap.
I do not like sweets or desserts.
I like savories.
- Didn't you say that you just ate
a chocolate thing just now?
- Oh, my shobani flip?
My chocolate haze craze?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yes, but this is just because it's a quick way to fill up
and I haven't had dinner yet.
- And it's sweet and it's a treat.
- So next question.
No it's not, it has more protein than it does tens of calories.
So, it fits my macros.
- I think you are just lying to yourself.
- I'm not one for sweets.
If I was, I'd tell you baby.
I will eat, I'm a one bite of cake kind of guy.
- I understand that.
- I will have one bite of cake.
- I went to a Brazilian steakhouse the other night
and I was thinking about--
- Without us?
yes not let's not do this again
sorry come on we did it on several podcasts and I was thinking about how
perfect all food should be three bites at a time
yeah that's like I think that's what it's supposed to be
yeah yeah sliders yeah just like but you know like different bites of things
because you never want more than a couple bites
I've been complaining about Taco Bell because they sell little sweet desserts
in the amount of two or twelve. Oh and you want three? I want yeah I want like four.
Well then just get two orders of two that doesn't seem that difficult. Well
hey what am I gonna do what am I what do I look like? What do you mean what are you gonna do?
Oh yeah let me just order two orders. Are you stupid? You order two tacos? Yeah just
to order two of them.
- Okay, but maybe I want six.
- Why would you choose the, okay, then order three.
Why would you, why are you complaining?
- You only ordered three of something for myself?
- The complaint only, you're the one who wants
to eat six of them, I don't fucking know.
You were complaining.
- Just give me one order of six.
- You also, you had a second chance there.
You could have said an odd number.
That would have made your point make some amount of sense.
But when you keep saying even multiples of two...
Going with the theme of lying to ourselves,
Ragnar is a big seller of this idea that he should always order
much more food than he usually needs.
And now he's coming down here being like,
"No, no, no, we should only have a couple bites."
You can't save something.
Dessert, you don't need more.
You need less dessert. Always.
Then just get two.
This is the most nonsense problem.
- This means that you are at the apex of your life.
You are right there at the top.
You are fully actualized,
and you're complaining about nothing,
like literally nothing.
- I could complain about so much more.
- I know you can.
No, no, I have an idea.
That is crazy.
- What do you have at this Brazilian steakhouse?
- Meat.
Lots of meat.
Let's see.
- Do you have picanha?
Of course, had some picanha, had some pork sausage, had some brisket,
had like eight different types of steak, the lemon pepper steak.
That was very good.
Sounds amazing. Had some chicken.
They came around. It was really funny.
I thought this guy had like an empty skewer, but he showed up at the table.
He's like, Do you want chicken heart?
I was like, Whoa.
And you said, Yeah, of course, when it went to Rome
And it tastes it looked like an olive when you're
Brazilian, they're small, disgusted.
It was there.
They're pretty popular in Mexico, right?
I don't think so.
Or just South America.
I think they're popular somewhere.
And I think they're supposed to be like really yummy.
But I don't know from my head.
I don't think it tasted, you know, it tasted like too much chicken.
Oh, it was kind of a pure chicken one bite.
It was like a chicken bouillon cube.
Yeah. Well, that's where I've eaten.
And it was really tough, really tough to eat.
I see.
Well, that's what I did.
The chicken has come from.
Yeah, it's his heart.
The heart.
It did. It did make me realize how just like kind of evil a place.
Well, not evil, but like,
you know, you're just like, you just have so much dead animal around you.
You're like, fuck it.
You want to fucking skewer of like 15 hearts?
Yeah, that is some crazy apocalypto shit.
Right. Skewer full of hearts.
Did it taste brave?
No, it tasted weak.
Maybe he wasn't really...
The chicken never knew love.
It wasn't loved.
Could you taste which ones had love in them
and which ones didn't?
I mean, maybe. I only had one.
Yeah, he had a loveless one.
You need to spit that one out. That's like a pistachio shell.
You don't eat that.
Yeah. Can I have a...
Can I have a chicken that's been loved?
Yeah, one that had a lot of friends and was appreciated by its community.
I think that I could have a chicken that I love like a dog
Personally, I think that's not very hard to do. I think it's really easy. I think you're pretty loving animals for the most
But just a little nasty and then we murder them and cold blood
You're not down with him
Crusading against me. I I I just dated a Brazilian steakhouse. I mean, it's not like I'm like crusading against me
I think you are. I think you got some evilness to you today.
Well, it's because I ate the chicken heart.
You are Tom this week. And Caleb is Jerry.
And you're the old lady.
Yep. And you're putting a pie out on the windowsill and I'm skewing it.
I am mostly out of the picture. I'm baking pastries.
You could be the bulldog.
I could be the bulldog.
The thing about the bulldog is he doesn't have any allegiances. He's his own guy.
He hates fucking Tom are you crazy? No what?
He's not on Jerry's side, but he's definitely not on Tom's he doesn't even know Jerry exists so small
He has Tom so much that I don't think it's true. It's right scissors. That's the whole show
Yeah, that's that's not the whole show the whole show is rock versus paper
It's basically the whole show the bulldog is but it's not in it that much
He's in it enough to be paper
No
Think about this. Here's rock, right?
Yep.
Here's scissors.
Okay.
Very simple to go between rock and scissor.
And what's paper?
And shilling paper?
Paper is a different thing completely.
That's hard.
That is totally different.
And to go from...
I mean, what am I even doing with my hand?
This, natural...
I don't know what we're talking about.
This, natural. This is insane.
This is basically a Nazi salute.
This is like, I'm gonna shoot you.
If you throw a rock and somebody throws paper, that's your only way out, by the way.
Whoa, what the hell are you doing?
Fucking Nazi crazy racist over here? What are you doing, man?
That's what makes no sense.
He's so mad that he lost that he's doing a Heil Hitler.
Rock goes through paper quite easily.
I think this is nonsense.
- Oh my god, it covers the rock.
- Okay, well what's your proposed alternative?
- Okay, well you're putting me on the spot.
- Yeah, I am putting you on the spot.
By the way, a rock can't break scissors either.
- Yes it can.
- Not my scissors.
- So, you're thinking about a scenario
where you're smashing a scissor with a rock,
but you can't think of a scenario
where you're smashing through paper with a rock.
- Well just, but that's not the point.
the paper covers the rock and--
- Kinds it.
- Yeah. - And that's how
he kills the rock?
- He doesn't kill, there's no killing in it.
I mean, I guess scissors kills paper,
but it's nullifying the rock.
- Yeah, scissors kills paper,
rock kills scissors.
The paper's not killing the rock by smothering it
and letting it not breathe. - Well, it can't breathe.
No, you said it yourself, it can't breathe.
- I think this is ridiculous.
This is worse than the monkey Olympics
that we had earlier today.
- What about like a laser beam?
Like this.
(laughing)
- The point?
- Yeah, that would cut through a rock.
- That's too close to scissors.
You could too easily switch.
- I like this.
I like the beam.
I think this is my idea.
- Yeah, the scissors just cuts the beam in half.
(laughing)
- Okay, I actually do like that.
- I think this is a good idea.
- I actually do like that.
I changed my mind on that pretty fast.
- Okay, have you ever seen like a dead pig for a roast?
- Yes.
- Have you ever been close to a dead pig
that's gonna be roasted and cooked?
- Oh yeah, dude.
Whole hog barbecue in North Carolina.
- It's really fucked up seeing that pig's head
in your kitchen.
- The worst part is people say the best part
of the pig is the head.
The head has got amazing stuff going on.
I really love when the like Chinese cooking videos go around and you just see an entire
dead animal on a stick.
But it always still has the head for some reason.
Yeah, always has the head.
There's one video of like a pig and it's like perfectly bronzed and glazed and cooked and
then they just cut it and it looks like it's like made of paper.
And it looks amazing.
Paper pig.
They cut it with a rock?
No, they cut it with scissors, obviously.
They cut it with a laser.
No, they cut it with scissors obviously. They cut it with a laser cutter.
See
beam
Scissor
Rock. You think it should be beam scissors beam rock or rock beam scissors?
Yeah, he's gone. Beam loses to scissors
it's too
It's too important. Two is greater than one. Oh
Well, that's what it should be one two three, but for some reason then like it makes as much sense for three to beat one as
Any you know might as well be whatever you know look look how about this seven eight nine?
That's also eight beats seven is that great nine beats eight
Seven beats nine because because nines afraid of seven right
Okay, we're sorry
Okay, okay
- Actually, it should be six, seven, nine.
- Nine.
(laughing)
- That's so easy to throw up as well.
- Seven, eight, nine.
(laughing)
- Okay, do it one more time.
- Seven, eight.
- The people at home that are listening,
he's throwing up seven, eight, eight,
- That's not really an eight.
- in a word that says.
- The eight is the only thing I have a problem with.
That's barely an eight.
- That's a horrible, that's an eight.
- Yeah, that's what it looks like to be.
- Looks more like a B.
That's a B. That's a B.
You are splitting it.
Yeah, and this this is fucking scissors.
Yeah, that's what this is.
And this is a rock.
Yes.
And those are all clear paper.
This is paper.
That's stop.
Okay.
You fucker.
I think I don't like honey.
That is crazy.
I love honey.
Yeah, honey's yummy.
I don't know. It has like a flavor to it that I don't like lingering.
Honey is probably, when I was vegan, honey is probably the thing I missed the most
because I didn't have honey. I did blue agave syrup instead.
Yeah. Which sucks.
Why not honey?
Because bees are murdered.
Because a bee makes it.
Yeah.
Yeah, but it's their job to make it.
It's not like they're dying for it.
That is true.
Well, they die.
And that's why it's okay to order from Amazon because it's their job.
Yeah. Oh, and kill people.
Right.
Because who gives a fuck at this point?
Whatever, right?
It's their job.
It's literally their job.
That's what they do.
No, their job is dancing.
Bees don't dance.
We do dance, actually.
Have you guys seen the video?
That's the that's like two wasps versus a thousand bees
and the wasps win.
It's so awesome because the bees aren't coordinated.
The bees just hurt.
The bees just suck.
The bees just throw as much fucking bee
as possible at these wasps.
And the wasps just hold down the forward,
just crush the bees, man.
- Yeah, I always think about that when people are like,
would you rather fight like one horse or a thousand chickens?
And it's like, the chickens aren't gonna gang up.
- No, they don't know, we've talked about this.
You kill every chicken individually.
- Yeah.
With my scissors.
- They don't know what an enemy is.
- And then you eat their hearts.
- Yes.
- Callback.
Two Kovaks in a row?
Do you think if you ate a thousand chicken hearts,
you would gain some sort of ability or power?
Some balking power?
The chicken power?
Yeah.
I don't think I want chicken powers.
I don't think so.
They can't fly.
They don't have anything.
They can fly a little bit.
What's a chicken's job?
Lay eggs.
Eat seeds.
Will you eat eggs?
I love eggs.
No, would you eat eggs if you're vegan?
If you could lay your own eggs.
No, I didn't eat eggs.
No, vegans don't eat eggs.
Yeah, definitely not.
That was the first thing.
And you're supposed to, you're supposed to give the chicken back its egg.
Right. When you're vegan and you have a, that's what you say to do with the egg.
You go to the market, you buy a thing of eggs and you just give it back to the chickens.
Here you go.
The chickens, by the way, they're going to be eating those eggs.
Yeah. They eat eggs and they eat each other, too.
Every animal except humans eats each other.
I think some humans eat other humans.
Well, just barely, though.
What's what's barely?
What does that mean?
Like one in a hundred people has eaten somebody.
It's not that many.
It was fun for a couple of days when people thought the guys
on the submarine were still alive.
It was fun to think about them eating each other down there
or having gay sex.
That everybody said that.
I don't think that's what I would do.
Like, I wouldn't be like,
Oh, I need to fuck my friend's dad.
I don't think I would.
I would be stuck with him.
I think it's fine.
I think I'd be hungry.
I think it'd be very hungry.
But I would be hungry.
Oh, yeah.
And that's why they don't bring any women down there.
Yeah.
That's what my mom said one time.
My mom was like,
listen, I'm all for equal rights,
but I don't think women should be allowed on submarines.
And I was like, what?
And she's like, yeah, I don't think women should be allowed on submarines.
I think the guys down there are going to get bored.
They're going to choose being completely serious.
That's awesome.
She truly, I think, to this day, and she's like she likes
she's like a Pete Buttigieg voter.
Yeah, she's like, I don't think women should be.
Women should be the president, but not on a submarine. Yeah.
Oh, they'll be the president down there.
Yeah. Cock.
Well, we're saying that, I mean, it's
Basically rape that you're making a joke about here, Rex.
I don't think
I don't think there's laws that apply to the sea in terms of.
That's your response to what I just said, is that there's no laws in the deep.
Yeah, I think it's just about survival.
Yeah, you got to you got to survive by having sex with someone.
Yeah, they should give women
like brass knuckles down there.
yeah that might work I thought it was that that submarine the the window was
feel like you could only take a shit like in the front of the submarine the
word were that either we're supposed to look out of the window just taunting an
octopus right there at the front of the submarine well it's funny cuz you know
like what happened to it is it just collapse like this yeah and you know
they talked about it just exploding right but on this side of it there's a bunch
of poop and pee.
So at your last moment, you're being
clouded together with a bunch of words.
And you're down there for like
they were down there for like an hour out of thing.
There was any pee or shit in there.
See, it's no that no, because I'm the kind of guy
where as soon as that door locks, the car, I'm taking a shit.
I'm I'm taking a shit in front of everybody.
I know there's a curtain.
There is a curtain there.
Well, that's very courteous.
But there's a curtain is not going to stop what I'm cooking.
- Yeah, they want to see the view.
They're down here with me, they want to see the view.
Let the, open up the curtain.
- Check it out guys.
- If they're down for one hour also.
If I'm stuck on the toilet for the full hour,
nobody even got to see anything.
- Wait, okay, hang on.
What is it?
What do you think, what's happened?
- So they took a shit and it smelled so bad
that the kid was like, can I open this?
Can I open a fucking window down here?
- It smells horrible.
- I'd rather breathe water than this guy's shit.
And they were like, no, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, I guess that's possible.
That's not even possible.
It is possible.
It's not.
Clearly, they've never taken a shit in that van.
They're completely bolted in.
They can't open it like a car door from inside.
They can.
OK.
You know how I know?
Because I've done it.
I've been on it.
Yep.
I was on it.
And we came back safely.
Isn't it kind of crazy that you could just open up planes emergency exit?
Yeah, I did see that.
Isn't that crazy?
Yeah. Why?
I didn't see that video, but apparently nothing happened.
Like, like, like shit doesn't go flying out.
No, they were low.
OK, I see.
Oh, maybe there's some kind of like pressure sensor on it.
So it knows where you are altitude wise or something.
Yeah, you can't just open it willy-nilly, but I mean that's you know
I'm gonna try one someday
Um, I would not suggest that I'm really
Try you guys wanna go to the beach
Yes, between you guys want to go to Cancun with me. I think I would fit right in in Cancun you would
Well, yeah, it's a it's a completely it's a bullshit city made for like white Americans
I think women are banned from the state.
Yeah, I think women are banned from the state. Yeah, I just heard sorry
I just heard my wife tell our dog you're done
Another time
Yeah, he's talking his talk arguing
Yeah
Imagine arguing with a dog and losing
She lost
I just heard it stop stop
You know yeah, that's what it sounds like to lose an argument the dog
I think if your entire house went down into the submarine Caleb you yeah your wife and your dog
I think your wife would be the first to go with the dog a hundred percent
I think I think maybe even the dog would outlive both of you now that I think about it
Yeah, he has a big head. He would easily kill both of us
He's like one bad bite away. That's a weird thing about like a chihuahua if a chihuahua bites somebody
You don't have to.
It's not a big deal.
It my dog.
Like today we were at the park and we there was a little girl with a scooter
who rode directly at him while we were throwing the ball
and said, Doggie, and like put her arms out.
And I had to stop him from killing her.
Yeah. And if I did not act fast, he would.
I would be in jail right now.
He would have been dead instantly.
Yeah. And it's like, you know, maybe train your
Your daughter a little better straight.
Yeah, I don't think you should be playing for that.
I think we should respect dogs.
But you know, he wants to.
He just wants to kill like let him be.
Like I'm not as king.
Yeah, he's a person.
Who am I to stop a wild animal, which he is, by the way?
Wild. Yeah.
Who am I to stop a wild animal from from capturing prey?
It's really none of my business.
You're not like his dad.
You're more like his own.
This is roommate.
Yeah, I'm imposing my Judeo Christian values on this dog.
He doesn't know what either of those words mean.
He only knows like eight words to begin with.
He knows sit, spin, lay,
surrender, crate and play.
So six. What about stop?
He does not know stop, but that's probably a good idea
if he keeps running at girls.
That's my teach him stop.
Yeah, most people could use that word when they're running at girls.
Yeah. Stop. Stop.
Stop running. Train a lot of these men, human men, that is to stop.
To stop. What the fuck just happened to you?
I actually went straight to my throat.
Why did you I'm convinced you don't know how to drink.
Every time you take a sip of it, it's a straw.
No, that's not true.
It doesn't matter how palatable it is.
You always have a bad reaction.
There's no way what he just drank was bad in any way.
No, it wasn't that bad.
I was like I said, I wasn't really a fan of the
I'm not a big fan of the honey favoring.
I think honey is OK, but I really wouldn't go for it.
Most times you said go for it.
Go for it.
Most times it wasn't too alcoholic.
It was it was kind of like just a hard tea, actually.
now that I think about it.
But it just went straight to my throat
and I almost choked to death live on camera.
That would have been pretty good.
We probably would have been on a live stream fail for that.
Yeah, that is a live stream fail.
Live streamer dies.
OK, guys, it's time to put our foot down
now that we're talking about live streaming.
When are we moving to kick.com?
I will do a gambling stream on kick.com any day.
Whenever you guys are down. I'm willing and able I would love to yeah, I think that'd be really fun
Well, they just added a these added mature audience
categories for content on twitch
the added porn
categories no
Gambling categories is that true? It's that's true. That's completely true. You can look it up right now mature content
Tags, I think it's what they call. Well, I gotta see this. Can I browse and see mature content?
I went fucking everywhere dude
Diablo 4 is that mature?
My official recommendation for the lemon dial lemon sour is it's okay. It's not
My girlfriend said it was gonna be bad, but it was completely okay
My final for the giant hard tea I
Didn't give this a rating earlier. I'm gonna give this a 5/4. This is just okay
Don't you don't jump out of your seat to go grab this at the store. Don't run to the store to get this
this is really nothing special.
Um, but, you know,
if you need a, uh,
if you're looking for something expensive,
this is a good start.
I think this was $7.
Oh man.
I think this was like $10 and it was okay.
That's crazy.
That is crazy. Okay, I have to leave.
Oh, okay. Yeah.
Okay, well, bye. Bye.
We're gonna keep talking. Do your thing.