and theme songs.
Oh yeah.
I like that sound.
Mmhmm.
I love that sound.
I like that shit.
Oh shit.
I love it this--
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that burp out.
This is a Johnny.
Into--
I hope you're keeping tab of what episode we're on.
I am, this is episode 100, welcome to beers we drank.
I'm having myself a Voodoo Ranger, a juicy, hazy IPA.
Guys, this is one of the funny beers that you can have in this white world and I'm succumbing
yet again to one of the coolest cans on earth.
Cheers, my friends.
I know we've talked a lot about making our own beer.
We should start our own bottle making company and it's a bottle that just makes a little
noise when you open it.
Um...
It's in there like a...
Sun Chips.
This is 7.5%?
I don't think I've actually ever had one of these.
That is...
That is insane.
This...
I mean it doesn't even taste like an IPA hardly.
Yeah.
It's really...
What flavor is it?
It's certainly...
Certainly juicy.
Well it's Juicy Hayes IPA, I already said that.
I'm getting notes of...
Hold on.
Beer.
You're getting notes...
Mm-mm.
Wait, remember what we learned last week?
You gotta, you gotta, you know, stroll around and smell it.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
>> I'm gonna say notes of some kind of wood.
I'm not quite, every time I try to do that,
I feel like I'm almost, I almost found a word that could describe one thing.
But I'm not quite there.
My super taster genes are still laying dormant in my tongue.
>> Yeah. >> But this is a good beer, guys.
I'm gonna give this the exact same ABV, and that's a lesson to the good people over at
Voodoo Ranger.
If you make a 10% ABV, I might give you a 10.
This is 7.5.
This is a 6'8.5" small forward who's probably in his third year.
He's out of his sophomore slump and he's rising to kind of, you know, borderline all-star level.
I like this shit, man.
This is a very decent beer.
I understand why people do it, why people do this one in the car.
It's good.
Yeah.
Um, you wanna go next, Rex?
Sure.
So, this is a beer I did not buy.
It was in my fridge already.
Free beer.
And that is a Coors Light.
Oh my god.
Let's give it up one time for the Coors Light.
Oh.
I love this beer.
I could drink this beer.
This is basically water.
That's the best beer in the world.
I mean, put another notch in your belt because this is a beer that you will drink every day
of your life.
Yeah, I could drink this literally all the time.
This is amazing.
Give me the review man, give me the numbers.
I need to hear, you know me man, I'm a numbers guy.
I'm like 538, I need to hear the projections.
This is like a 7.58 out of 10, but because it was free, that's a 10 out of 10.
true
and i would like to say this right now
all free beer is a ten
that's right every free beer is a ten that is a rule on this show
if a beer is free
it gets a three plus
two plus a seven
ten some might call that
but i just like you know i like rhyming
and now you my mousy little friend what do you have for me
I don't look like a mouse, first of all.
Today I...
Why don't you put those big buck teeth back in your mouth and stop talking to me.
Let's pile on.
He's having the worst week of his life.
Sorry.
I'm gonna get back to that later.
Today I am drinking a... I think it's called Tempus?
Uh-huh.
I don't know, it's like some artisanal beer.
It's a cerveza artisanal.
It says that it's a cream stout.
And I read that on the bottle and I was like, "Oh."
the
Let me get Phil, like put it right in the middle.
Okay, a little closer.
Does that not look like the awning to a strip club?
Yes.
Yeah, Tempest does sound like a bad strip club.
Tempest Cream Stout, and with the color and everything.
This actually-
43%?
I feel like I'm walking into one of the most midnights of my life.
It looks like the label on like a chocolate bar.
Yeah.
With the Milka.
It looks a little bit too elegant for this show, I'd go and say that.
I read Cream Stout on the label and I was like, "Oh, that's going to taste like dessert."
I just took a swig of it and it's just a dark beer.
Yeah, I think the Cream Stout is like milk washed or something.
Yeah, so it's on the side of one of the ones that I don't much like because I really don't
like dark beers but it's okay I think it's like light enough so I don't
completely hate it like I have other beers other dark beers so you know what
this one gets to gets a 5.8 okay and in the AVA scale he didn't make the league
Wow okay that bad 5.8 I feel like is that's kind of interesting he's 5.8 out
of 10 didn't make the league. He's 5.8 and he didn't make the league. Oh okay all right gotcha
the
I'm gonna freak out and start knocking things over.
Let's get down to business.
I am a victim.
I am a victim of rudeness.
Everyone here in this room.
What have I ever said about you that is even remotely rude?
Two minutes ago you called me a mouse and you said I had bug teeth.
Which I don't.
Even though that's more of a rat kind of thing.
that
You couldn't stop talking about it, you dressed up for it, you appeared in front of my eyes,
dressed like a gentleman, and then you guys just went while I was stuck in a different
country and I got facetimed by Rex twice.
And Rex said some pretty rude things, did he not?
And he said some rude things, he said "we're enjoying our night so much I wish you killed
yourself."
He did not say that I don't think.
She said something like that. I think that was the second time we called.
The first time we called...
The first time we called it was like, "We're in the Uber, we're on our way there."
It was like, "Okay, well, I'm at home."
No, we were in the Uber on the way-ar.
In the way-there.
On the way-ar.
We were on the way-ar.
We came on the way-ar.
We were on the way...
-ar. -and...
Nella...
Got a bunch of followers, and clearly...
You were shit-talking us...
Well we weren't there to defend ourselves.
Wait, I can explain this and everyone in this chat can actually back me up.
Because I was playing the Long Drive with Cam.
We were playing the game and we were talking about Thanksgiving.
We were talking about "Oh, it would be so much fun if I flew out to New York on Thanksgiving.
It would be so much fun."
And then we started talking about awesome dinners and plates and how full some plates
are during Thanksgiving and our famous plate was not much full.
Not so full that plate.
So we were talking about it and I just like, you know what, I have this fond memory of
looking at this picture and laughing so much because my friends were having such a good
time I want to relive it right now.
And that's why we posted it.
was not talking shit on Noah or either any of you guys but you still not even me
not even Caleb who I think it made all that food and that please yeah I did not
make the plate he made the plate I'd like to clarify that he filled up on strudel
before he came to Thanksgiving he said he ate two strudels he filled up all he
put on his plate was two pieces of ham and a little bit of stuffing yeah but
that's beside the point I want you to get to the second phone call the second
phone call I think it was you guys as you guys were already done with the meal uh-huh and
you called me and you're like we had such an amazing time that that meat was delicious
oh so sorry you missed it you started I recall this you you Rex held out his phone and all
four of you Brian, Noah, Rex and Caleb all pointed at the phone and started laughing
at me. And I was like, "Oh, okay, thanks." So I just hung up. I was like, "What the fuck
am I gonna say?" It's actually, it's worse than that, because
we were laughing at you, like, kinda as like a joke, but I was in such a good mood that
I just couldn't stop laughing. Yeah.
And then we hollered at a passerby to take a photo of all of us while we were on with
on with you and then I looked back at my phone after we took the photo and you were gone.
Yeah we had it, we wanted to get a photo that was the four of us having the best night of
our entire lives and then you on a phone in the middle of it. Oh my god, I will say, yeah
it didn't, there was no mal intent with that phone call dude, that was just the kind of
mood we were in. Yeah, we just wanted to talk to you. We were gaking you, we just wanted,
We were like, you know, this is an amazing night.
What would make this night even better?
What if Julio was here?
Oh, wait, he's on the phone.
Ha!
That was our thought process personally.
- Why don't we, you know, let's just strike back
and talk about this legendary night.
How did it go?
- Well, man, it started like all amazing nights should.
We went to an absinthe bar
and spent about an hour and a half waiting on our drinks.
- Yeah.
- Let me tell you, these were divine.
I had somebody tell me, "You have to get the martini at this place.
You have to get the martini.
It's the best thing there."
I don't like martinis.
I don't even like barely anything, right?
And I say, "Let me have a martini, please."
And they say, "Oh, amazing choice, sir.
It's this kind of place."
"By the way, oh, wait, I got to get this out."
Noah that night said, he had told us all before, he was like, "We're all going to wear suits,
man.
We're all going to wear suits and dress up, and we're going to look amazing."
and i was like it would be kind of funny if we all wear suits just to go eat
barbecue yeah we'll do that
thinking it would be really funny if all four of us wear suits or at least if me and
noah wear suits
i get to brian's i'm dressed in the suit that i got married in
noah is dressed like a
like an old navy mannequin
he had
wait what?
he had blue chinos on
and a blue
shirt that he claimed was a suit jacket
on top of his uh... of a polo that he was wearing. Do you have a picture of him?
There's a picture of him I'm sure.
But this pissed me off to no end and it was made much much worse by the fact that we
got to the Absinthe restaurant and I was dressed, the only one in the entire
building who was sitting at a table
who was dressed exactly like the men working at the restaurant. Yeah.
Like the same fucking suit.
The same banana republic suit we were all wearing. Yeah.
so i'm telling my my coworker
yeah i'll have a martini and he says amazing choice sir
and then he leaves he comes back forty five minutes later
and the manager
so i didn't know that this is what they do but they come to the table with a
tray
one guy just holds the tray and then a lady
makes the martini off of the tray as the guy serves as a human table
in front of me and it took so long it was like the first time she ever made it
at
I mean it just sucked.
My drinking break.
It sucked.
Yeah, we ate one oyster each.
We had one oyster each.
And one drink.
Mmhmm.
And it cost $200.
It was, it was insane.
What?
I didn't pay for a single thing, thank god.
Thank god.
Anyway, so, from there, we realized we're pretty close to a place in Brooklyn called Barcade
of
mug and then you shoot the mug and it explodes.
And it's, you have to see it to believe it.
This is the greatest arcade game of all time.
And we went, we Ubered over to the barcade to play this game for maybe 10 minutes and
then we had to leave to go make our great barbecue reservation.
Yeah.
Because we spent 30 minutes on the bridge.
And then we got there, man, and I honestly don't even know what to say.
Ryan asked me a question, then two days later I saw him, and I was with my wife, he was with
his girlfriend, we were getting dinner, and he pissed me off more than anybody's ever
pissed me off in my entire life.
He said, "I've never eaten anything like that, I probably never will again in my life."
That was like a once- there's a reason I felt okay wearing the suit once I was there, because
I was like, "This is as important as my wedding.
There is no way that I will ever eat anything like this ever again.
This is fucking insane.
It was like a Korean Wagyu place?
It was Wagyu only Korean BBQ all you can eat.
And I sent a picture of the meat if you want to show people.
Yeah, I'll pull it up on my phone.
I believe it's in the discord as "this beef was different".
I butcher in house and they serve you every cut of the meat.
They serve you like 16 different cuts.
I think I found it.
You look completely red.
I didn't say slightly edited photo.
I found it.
Brian asked me two nights after having this meal that was like completely mind-blowing,
two hours of eating this, look at that meat dude.
That's insane.
That's hella meat.
It's hella meat and it's completely white.
Yeah.
He sat, we were sitting down making small talk and he asked me, he's like, "Oh yeah, that
Korean BBQ thing the other night, did you like it?"
And I was like, "What did you just say man?"
He was like, "Yeah, did you like it?
Were you into that?"
And I literally pounded on the table like this.
And I was like, "Don't you ever ask me anything that stupid again as long as I fucking know
you."
Yeah.
That was the best meal of my life and you knew it.
And now you're making fun of me because I'm poor.
Yeah.
So, two things we're leaving out, which is that we get there and then you can just buy
nice soju and like sake, and we got like seven bottles.
What?
We had at least seven bottles.
Our waiter did a shot with us, it was amazing.
And when I tell you that I had one of the worst hangovers of my entire life, I'm not exaggerating.
Having so hungover the next day, I strained my calf just like stretching the next morning.
That's the opposite of what's supposed to happen.
Yeah, it was horrible.
But I wanted to stop drinking at a certain point because we'd done beers we drank, drank absinthe,
went to the barcade, drank seven days.
For those who don't remember, he had already loaded up on samples at the store.
I didn't bow, but everyone did this to me when they drank their-
We looked away in reverence to his age.
And I wanted to skip one, and the waiter was like, "Well, you are the oldest."
So you have to drink.
You got- I mean, you're not up for shut up, man.
If you wanna really be about this Korea shit, you gotta play by the rules, big daddy.
You're not in Korea, you're in fucking New York.
No, this was Korea.
This was- we were put in- it was amazing.
It was fucking amazing.
So yeah, we were- that's why we got outside after this amazing meal, all this liquor,
and then we call our friend and we just can't stop laughing because we're so joyous.
Yeah, it really was- I mean, I was-
I had a giggle fit.
Yeah, basically yeah, had a giggle fit.
And then we went back to my place and we gambled.
And we gambled.
This is the most amazing night of my life.
Most amazing night of my life.
It's basically just like a perfect night.
I got home at 3 in the morning and I honestly felt like I went home early.
Yes.
I got home and I was like, you know what, in another world that could have been a thick
7am type of night.
Yeah.
It was really nice, man.
here
express or something like that. Maybe we could go to a Brazilian steakhouse. That's a great
idea actually. See, ok now Rex has finally gotten his revenge on you, not on me, I got
to be in both. Yeah, that is true. That is my revenge for the Brazilian steakhouse. I
got to do foie de chow with Julio and I got to do life changing Korean BBQ with Rex, which
by the way, love Fogo de Chao, not even,
this was a hug to Fogo de Chao.
This was, Fogo de Chao was nothing compared to this.
So Rex cannot be mad at anyone.
- I'm not gonna rehash this,
but we all know whose fault that night was.
And it was-- - It was Cameron's.
- It was an afternoon. - It was an afternoon.
- And you kept letting the cops into our place
and got us kicked out.
- Dude, I think I stopped Airbnb being able
to operate in New York altogether.
i think that was me
it was it was the last that was the last airbnb rented in the house as soon as
you left there were like you know what no more b_n_b_'s in in all of new york
they're completely banned because we found
the most insane
airbnb in fucking in brooklyn
so no one gets to do that anymore
i walked by it today and it still had the
uh... vacate immediately sign on there yeah i'm sure that guy doesn't even care
he's not going to do anything to it
to get food grants at some point you know who knows also has risen in the world
posters
his team can with this is gonna piece three in there
he doesn't need
forking for three dollars and register system
yeah that is true
you know that he has three came out closer to the n_e_s_ and
yeah i bought a p_s_ three like two thousand seventeen so that i could play
two k
and it was amazing
And then I played Ratchet and Clank.
And I was fully... you could have convinced me it was a brand new system.
I would have believed you. It was so... I mean, that's gotta be... that's probably...
Top five all time.
It's impossible to call the PS3 like a retro system because it looks...
Because graphics stopped improving around there.
Yeah, exactly.
Like I've been playing, I don't know if you guys know this, I've been playing Persona 5.
Is that true?
Which is a PS3 game.
Yeah, which is a PS3 game and it looks like it came out yesterday, dude.
Did they stop making Persona games after 5?
Well, they have, they, they, don't even get me started, but the next one, just basically the leaks are that it's gonna come out in 2026.
Uh, I wouldn't hold your breath on that.
Persona 6?
Yeah, Persona 6.
Dude, listen, we can't talk about Persona, we're not doing Persona talk anymore, man.
Let's get into the nitty gritty.
The NBA preseason has began.
Victor Wimbenyama is dominating these games.
He's a monster on the pick and roll.
He can shoot to three.
His defensive game is something to be amazed by, is it not?
Guys, what are the takes we have on the preseason games thus far?
I think--
I watched them.
Yeah, I--
Watched them.
OK, now Julio, I'm going to need a little more than watched them from you.
I haven't been able to catch up on that because I've been catching up on last season of the
NBA.
I've been binging it.
You've been binging the NBA season?
Every game?
Yeah, last season.
Huh.
Well, what game are you on right now?
What part of the year?
The first one?
March.
The first game.
You're watching an NBA debut, which is probably Warriors at Lakers, something like that?
Yeah, that's what I'm on right now.
You're on that?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, um...
Yeah, we can talk about anything else, you know?
We don't really have to talk about that.
Worlds is starting tonight.
Are we all excited or what?
Worlds what?
League.
Nah, I know.
No, I know, I don't want to talk about that either.
How about we talk about how because we did liquor we enjoyed, guys I have stepped up my
fashion game for this.
I mean I don't know if you can tell but I went through every article of clothing I have
in my entire under my bed because I'm not allowed to have a closet.
Yeah.
I haven't really talked to you guys since we recorded that.
I know, Loki I miss you man.
I did want to ask you guys.
What?
You miss me too?
I did want to ask you guys, so that you know, I've been good. Yeah, I miss you too. I've been doing this
You know the streaming for a whole month type of thing and someone recommended that I that I do a
You know one of those like you laugh you lose type type beats
but
It's if I laugh at something I have to like make myself a drink with my mask out that potato still have
Cuz I'm not when am I ever gonna drink that?
And I wanted to see if any of you if either you would like to come and join me
On what?
A drinking game?
Yeah, just a drinking game with whatever you have.
And what are we watching while we drink?
Just funny videos.
Probably TikToks.
Funny videos, you laugh, you lose? Yeah, I can do that.
I still have about a fair amount of...
I don't even know how...
I have a lot of that proper 12 left
from liquor we enjoyed.
I had one night where I tried drinking it
and it hurt my stomach so bad.
And even though I was drinking like, I would put like half of an ounce in a tall glass,
like 16 ounce glass of water to try to dilute it.
And it just didn't work, man.
How about Coke?
Here's what I don't like about that shit, man.
I think that if you drink rum and Coke or Jack and Coke or anything like that, that's okay
if you're going to drink two drinks.
But if you are like me and you're going into the what some might say mastery kind of level,
the advanced levels of drinking where you're drinking 6 to 10, I'm not gonna drink fucking
120 ounces of soda.
I guess that's true.
Straight up.
That's why you need diet coke.
That's still soda man.
I'm not, that's enough aspartame to, you could sprinkle it.
So I'm not doing that.
I don't know. I've seen pros just drink so much soda.
You know? Professionals.
Pro what?
The answer there is you just need to use coke as a chaser.
There.
I'm also not gonna chase stuff, dude. I don't do that shit.
I don't do chasers. I don't do limes with tequila.
You should.
Why?
It's delicious.
It's supposed to feel... You should have an instant regret every time that you put alcohol in your body.
That's why beer is so amazingly dangerous.
Because you need these- liquor is supposed to taste bad.
If liquor tasted good, that would be- then people would have some kind of drinking- like
some problem with drinking I guess is what I would call it.
Some kind of drinking problem?
Yeah, they would have some kind of problem.
But because it tastes bad, people don't.
You know?
That is true.
I see.
Yeah, I think I see your point.
Yeah, so yeah, I would mix something...
I agree, you can't drink 15 mixed drinks, that's not...
I do remember one of the first times I ever hung out with Brian, this is when I knew that
he was a real one, he ordered a double Jameson and water.
Yeah.
I was like, let me buy a drink, he's like yeah, let me have a double Jameson with water.
I was like, what?
With water?
Yeah.
and he's completely right dude that's the only way to drink whiskey
because otherwise it tastes disgusting
yeah well you're supposed to like water down
no you're not you're supposed to drink it i've been watching this fat guy on
uh... on youtube
his name
don't know his youtube channel name
bruzel
look it up b-r-e-w-z-e-l-e
kind of an application style name
he drinks so much whiskey out of a uh... they call it a glen
clay glen claren a glen caron
or a glen claren one of these two
well basically it's a cup
but it's very expensive
and he goes
like this and he smells it
and then he takes a sip and he'll drink in one video that he records at maybe
eleven a_m_
he'll drink probably
end of these.
Is he like reviewing the whole bottle or is he reviewing the bottle?
He's reviewing, he'll pour one of each bottle and be like, "Let's compare a Crown Apple with
Jack Tennessee Honey."
And then he'll take all of them.
And this guy's completely unfazed.
And this is the level I want to get to.
I want to be, this guy's easily 400 pounds or 500 or maybe 600.
He can barely move.
He looks like he's 70, but he's probably in his early 30s.
And he is drinking so heavily every single day for his job, and this sounds like paradise
to me.
Yeah, well, you know, to talk about drinkers and how you're completely right that people
hate drinking so much, that most of the world, I don't know if you know this, is a sober gopher.
So much so that they'll have complete events where they don't even have an ounce of drink.
What are you talking about?
So a day or two after you guys had the most legendary, most drinking awesome liquor, eating
awesome meat night, my presence was needed at this wedding.
Oh I forgot about this.
Christian wedding between a Christian woman and a normal guy.
A normal guy?
Yeah, he wasn't anything.
So he was also Christian?
No, he was really scared about most of the event, I was told.
They didn't allow anyone to bring their significant other, I was told.
No one was allowed to bring their kid.
And you were not allowed to drink.
And also I found out later that you also are not allowed to dance, which is crazy.
What are they, Mormon?
That's not a wedding, man.
I know. And I got there and first of all-
I'm fighting you in a celebration, that's a punishment.
I was really sad about this because I had rented a suit for this and I didn't know we're doing
suits for Liquors We Enjoyed until two hours beforehand and it was like a day before I got
my suit so I was like, "Fuck, I can't do anything about this so I'm just gonna do a funny joke."
So I got my suit, it fit weird because I don't have any thing in this apartment apparently.
What? It fit weird because you don't have any thing?
I don't have a belt, I don't have a-
Yeah you know the thing.
I don't have fresh shoes, I don't have socks.
Oh okay, oh I see.
I don't have like an undershirt for my-
You just rented the suit?
Yeah, pretty much.
Well I asked for shoes and they were like, "Okay, what's your size?"
I tell him I was like, oh no, we don't and I still have to pay the full amount even though
the I didn't get any shoes.
Which was really sad.
But anyways, like that's beside the point.
I get there.
I'm going to kind of uncomfortable suit.
I'm going to make it a goal next year that I'm going to actually be a grown up and buy
myself a suit that actually fits me.
We get there.
The place is really nice.
It's like a like a in a building that you wouldn't really think that's like an event
venue building.
It's in a complete building, it's at the top of the building, you can see the awesome city.
And we get there, well the ceremony is still going on, so it's a little quiet, a little
hush.
And then it starts and the only thing that happens during the wedding is they opened
like this, like the dessert table, and all the kids that were actually brought to the
wedding, everyone like ignored that, just rushed in and just ate a bunch of candy basically.
TV host type event host type beat showed up and just like quizzed the the the
couple and then we had dinner and that was it.
Oh dude. That was the entire wedding and then a crazy monster came out and
scared me. What? Wait really? It was the monster that I sent you guys. A monster scared you? At the wedding?
He did.
That's awful.
Yeah, so basically, I had just a horrible night.
There's a monster.
Oh wow, it's the mask.
Yeah the monster was coming after me.
Yeah, so the mask came after me and I didn't drink anything.
I just had made dinner and we left.
I was like, wow, that was so much fun.
Thank you for the update.
I had a question.
I did not know that you took that photo.
You sent it to us and I thought it was just a photo you found.
Yeah.
Can you send me that that might be one of the funniest pictures I've ever seen in my entire life
The fact that they that Mexican wedding
They have no drinking but they hired somebody to come dress up like big head Tony Hawk Pro Skater big head version of the mask
Yeah, and they you know, there was there was like no dancing like throughout the night
But then I'm the little like the band and like the show came in and was like, oh, yeah
Let's just start dancing a little bit while this is happening. But this was this like started like midnight
When the Tony Hawk big head guy came out and the wedding was over at 1 a.m
So it was like it was like the last thing
Or one hour that was what they had for fun is for one hour. They had the mask come out. Yeah, did he say anything?
No, he was just dancing
He was the only one allowed to dance no, no everyone's like get up and dance because it was like a band
Okay, so they said no dancing as a prank.
Yeah, I don't know. It was a really weird event.
Alright, which wedding was better, that one or mine?
Definitely yours. Yours was so much fun.
Oh my god, most of my friends were there. Best wedding ever, yeah?
Most of my friends were there. Best wedding ever!
The burgers were delicious. We had burgers on my... Listen, I'm working class.
The celebs as far as the eye could see. There were so many celebs that left after half an hour.
But it's whatever. Yep, they had to go man. They had to go. They can't be seen with people like you.
Yep. Brian almost fought a celeb that actually stayed the entire night.
We're not going to go into detail on who that was. It was Adam Friedland.
He always fought him because over the DJing rights.
The rights to DJ. Ok, I'm actually going to... Because Brian wanted to play real music
and Adam wanted to play Cha-Cha Swing.
(laughing)
- So Caleb test Adam--
- Brandon Widdle was not invited to my wedding.
- So Caleb test Adam Freeland with a playlist
with the DJing of the wedding.
And Brian--
- Which by the way, he called me,
can I just say, he probably called me
in the three days before the wedding 25 times.
- Yeah.
- Because he was like so stressed out about DJing,
about making a playlist for the wedding
and i said man it's ok we already have a playlist you don't have to really even make one
i was just joking he was like no dude
like what kind of music are people gonna wanna listen to what's gonna get people on the dance floor
there was no dancing at your wedding either to be honest
none
there was more of a hangout
it was kind of like a hanging out
chilling type beat
Everyone just got drunk really fast because Noah didn't tell anyone to water down the drinks that he made.
Noah made it. Noah poisoned everybody. He made two drinks. One which was delicious and one that tasted like cough syrup.
And he said water it down at the beginning of the night and then everybody showed up and he forgot to tell them all.
Yeah, I guess he told you and your wife. He never told anyone else.
He would just watch people pour it and you would have your glass with the drink and some
ice in it and he would be like "Yo, what are you doing?"
I'm like "What?
I'm trying to drink the thing."
He's like "You're supposed to water it down."
I'm like "Oh, okay, why am I doing this?"
So we all got poisoned.
This is like the second time.
We all got drunk and then there was a line for burgers.
We were so good.
That was so fire.
Because everyone was so drunk already.
Everyone got drunk in 20 minutes, they were all hungry.
And then there was a big beef over the DJing rights.
Well it was not so much the DJing rights, it was Brian got drunk and he brought a really
shitty Chinese speaker and then everyone was drunk, Adam was drunk, he wanted to DJ on Brian's
speaker he thought he called it a piece of a Chinese piece of shit and he hit it
with his foot and that got Brian so hit it the entire night Brian was so
mad I was like fuck this guy that has a fucking piece of shit and I'm with
Brian and his girlfriend and he's like yeah he called this shit he called my
speaker like a Chinese piece of shit I mean he's right it is but like you can't
say that about my speaker and then Brian just displayed the most insane like
Houston rap that I've ever heard in my entire life. In the Uber on our way to the bar after the wedding.
That's what he does man. But yeah man, I think that's if you're gonna have a wedding man, weddings are people show up to weddings wanting good food and free drinks and
unlimited free drinks so that's really all that you need to a wedding is not for
you. You are not doing a wed... there's no reason to do a wedding for yourself. The
core thing is enough for you. So the wedding is about have making... basically
paying back your friends for all the times that you had to bring your
girlfriend to stuff and they didn't know. And then now it's your wife so they
can't say anything. So you're paying them back for that. Exactly. That's basically
what a wedding is. So you're saying here's a bunch of free food, here's a
a bunch of free alcohol. And if I can bring my wife anywhere I want now. And also please
get me a gift. By the way, Brian, best gift of the night. Fake Rolex. Best gift of the
night man. Well, it's really big and I'm embarrassed to bring it into one of the people to try
to get the size change. And also I don't want to get robbed. I don't want to get killed in
a robbery for a fake Rolex. It really introduced a lot more anxiety into my life than anything
else.
Also during this legendary night that was your wedding, you also walked up to me, the night
was almost done, you walked up to me, I think it was your cam, I can't remember now, I was
so drunk. Someone walks up to me like, "Yo, we voted and you were voted the second worst
per
Yeah, that is really funny.
That is really funny.
He was dressed up like a scarecrow y'all.
That's not true.
He was on some Halloween shit.
I was not.
Who was worse?
What?
Cause he said he was the second worst.
Worse than him? I don't remember.
Probably...
Hmm.
I don't know actually.
Do you remember who was worse?
I just know I wasn't, I was voted top bottom two.
I didn't even remember that Julio was like that badly dressed.
I don't even remember he was there.
I was there.
Yeah, I mean, first time hearing about it, but it sounds fun.
Yeah.
Well, I'm glad I went to your wedding.
That was the best wedding I've ever been to.
But you know, it was also, it's also a horrible memory for me because it brings back so many
When are you gonna get married? When can I come down to Mexico and give a best man speech?
You can go to Mexico whenever you want, basically.
No, I'm only coming for a speech.
You can give a speech whenever you want.
Alright, I would give...
I would give... Oh my...
I would give such an amazing best man speech.
I would give the most amazing best man speech.
Yeah, there you go.
I would say, "This guy...
I'm his best man.
I met him about two years ago.
We used to play video games together and now he's in the ultimate video game marriage.
He's lost the video game of life.
He is completely lost.
Hey, here's what I would say.
I would say, yeah, me and this guy used to play video games.
Hey buddy, it's game over for you.
Boom!
I thought you were married.
Ball and chain.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
That's
I was.
I also didn't give a speech.
And the worst dressed, but the best man.
You're wearing a huge sombrero that you bought on the way there.
I'm wearing a wedding dress. I'm trying to upstage your fiance.
Yeah.
And basically, I mean, if I gave a best man...
Dude, best man speech is the kind of thing that, to me personally, I would knock out of the park.
Yeah. Have you ever done it before?
No. I think I probably will do one at my brother's wedding, and I'm already kind of generating ideas for that.
Mm-hmm.
I'll probably do about 45 minutes at my brother's wedding.
I think it would be really funny to have you guys come out to Mexico and make you mingle
with my real life friends and family.
Yeah, I mean I can learn Spanish.
I honestly think if I tried really hard I could be completely 100% fluent in Spanish in about
three weeks.
So if you give me three weeks notice, I could study really really hard.
I could give you three weeks notice of when I'm getting married?
Yeah.
That's what I did.
seemed to work out fine. That is true. That is pretty much what I did.
You were like yeah I don't fucking know. I didn't know I was getting married man.
It was a fun time I'm glad I came out for that. But I would love to talk to your
abuela. Sure you can do that yeah. Yeah dude she's fine ain't she? Nope she's old and
She's tiny.
She's so small.
Here's how I go.
Hola abuelita.
Tu eres bonita.
Tu eres...
No butthole. You're not fat.
My dad speaks no English.
I think my sister speaks English.
My mom understands English. I think she also speaks it.
My godfather speaks English.
My dad, zero English, just nothing.
I think it would be so lovely to try to watch you talk to him.
- Hola, papacito.
Tu eres guapo.
- No, you don't get to risk
every single person in my family.
- Why not?
- You have to talk to him about normal stuff.
- Like how guapo he is.
That's normal?
- Yeah.
- That's the kind of, it's a love language.
that's a good conversation to have
in a romance language that's what it's called not a love language love language
is gift giving
yeah
I do that too
you know what I'd bring him?
a big ass bottle of Don Julio and Yeho
and I would say listen man let's break down these language barriers right now
you and me
we're finishing this bottle
he doesn't drink
you and me right now he doesn't drink?
That's not my fucking bi- and he will- he will take one look at me and say, "You know what?
Tomorrow, I begin another sober gopher journey."
And he will say this in perfect English, "Tomorrow, my sober gopher journey re-begins."
And he's a very poetic guy.
"Tomorrow, my sober gopher journey re-begins, but tonight, this white boy is about to teach
me the secrets of the universe."
And me and him would sit under the stars, the Don Julio kind of sitting between us, we're
kind of tugging over it because we're so addicted.
Are we at the beach? Am I having a beach party?
Uh, yeah, you probably would. You'd probably go to Cabo. That's in Mexico.
It actually is, really? Yeah, it is.
Wait, I'm actually smart as fuck.
We would go to...
Hmm, Puerto Escondido. That's where we'd go. That's another place I know in Mexico.
Okay.
And me and him would sit there on the beach, and slowly his fingers would start climbing up my thigh.
and
in a major way
and then
you guys would be back at the wedding going
where's Caleb? where's my dad?
what the hell's going on here?
you come back
uh... he's he's kinda like grabbing
i have a wig on by the way to make him like me more
and he's like grabbing my hair and kinda like
he you know i there's no way to say this in a way that's not crass he's face fucking me on the
beach and i'm kinda like gagging
and uh...
Yeah, I mean the wedding would pretty much be over at that point.
I think I'm gonna have a Mexican wedding and a US wedding.
You don't want me hanging out with your daddy?
Not anymore, no.
Why the fuck not?
I don't want you to get yourself involved like that, in that type of way.
You think it would ruin my marriage, you are looking out for me, that is what a best man does.
That is why you're my best man.
Yep.
Thank you my friend, I appreciate you.
what would your American wedding be where would it be would it be a Bucky's yeah
Bucky's that'd be Vegas dude you got to do Vegas if you do yeah I heard really
bad stuff about Vegas Vegas is is falling bad stuff about Vegas Vegas is not
falling nothing bad has happened in Vegas for a lot of decades bad stuff is
happening in Vegas Vegas is no over like what formula one is coming to Vegas and
and they have completely... no wait hang on
they've completely destroyed the strip. It's horrible to walk around it or even hang
out at it
at it at it. A lot of casinos are getting attacked by cyber hackers and getting
destroyed and exploded
That happened to one casino man! There's so many strikes about
working strikes about some shit I don't know
You could probably talk to them in their native tongue and get them to get back to work
the
I like, I don't know why people are hating on that dome dude.
That dome is cool man.
That's one of the coolest things ever made.
Easily, easily and that's something that in 50,000 years when society is completely over
and rebirth, people will be arguing about how we built that.
Like as if we do with the pyramids now.
I'm gonna be so sad when the sphere gets destroyed by a jihad attack in a week.
The what gets destroyed?
Are you being racist on the show?
Are you taking my bit and being racist to end the show?
No, you can do it. You can do it.
I will say I saw one of the craziest headlines of my entire reading career today.
Which was, uh...
It was, "Israel confirms that missile was of Islamic origin."
I was like...
What?
It is crazy that they're like, yeah, this is from some new guy.
It's called Islamic Jihad.
Islamic origin?
They can tell?
They can tell what religion the missile was?
Anyway, I'm sorry.
I don't want to go into all that.
This is an awful tragedy.
Yeah, let's talk about all that.
But it's completely awesome that's going, that war zone is happening in real life.
I will say, man, I picked a bad week to quit the national defense business to start doing
sketch comedy. I said this week, I said to my wife, I said, listen, I said last week,
there's been no wars in so long, this is a bunk ass, boo boo ass industry, I'm getting
out of this shit. I'm moving over to sketch comedy. There's no future in this shit. Wars
are over man, we have AI doing insane stuff. And she said, okay, you can quit your job.
and right as I do man, shit pops off.
I'm sorry man.
I could have been rich man, I could have gone back to the Korean BBQ place but for now I'm
gonna have to settle for...
You know those General Dynamics guys were looking at their phone popping cigars on the golf
course the moment they saw...
They're like looking at that video of like the Hamas guys coming down and they're even
more excited about it than the 17 year old lad on Twitter.
For them it's King Kong vs Godzilla in the reverse sense. Whoever wins we win.
Yeah. Whoever wins we win because it's great cinema.
Yeah, exactly. Because we get a bunch of cool movies out of this basically.
Have you seen the cool dope ass Godzilla or King Kong game?
The new King Kong game?
I saw the one like for everybody about it that there's a at some point in like a cutscene
the
Popped out with the White Claw Surge Blood Orange guys.
Highly recommend this flavor.
Um, yeah, people are saying, guys...
You know I try to stay away from incendiary topics.
Yeah.
If there's one thing you know about me.
That is true.
But, people are saying this King Kong game is the new Gollum.
Yeah, people are saying that.
And apparently Gollum was some other game that looked pretty awful.
Yeah.
a
made a video about who should kill themselves. Dream.
That's true. That's true.
That guy should kill himself.
I do think, honestly, I think that Dunkey is probably one of the ten best culture critics
of the last twenty years.
He's got a certain...
He has a certain funny voice he does.
He's got kind of a funny fat guy voice that is very distinctive.
I love him dude. He's gotta be the only guy that I liked when I was 13 that I still like 10 years later.
Have you seen his videos where his girlfriend or his wife just makes him be in her videos and they're playing like tea?
Tea?
Yeah, they're just playing around with a tea set and he's like "oh whatever" being cute. Have you never seen those?
I've never seen that. I do not want to muddy my image of Dunkey.
After I saw that I was like, you know what?
Dunkey's over for me.
I'm moving over.
I like to imagine he is like fat Yoshi.
He's kind of like that.
He kind of is, yeah.
He's full he is, yeah.
But he's got a soft side that he never lets on
on his sharp critique videos
of like fucking...
He bodies games left and right, man.
Yeah.
If you're thinking of making a bad game,
you better think twice
because Dunkey has you in his crosshairs
And he's a damn good aim.
I've moved past Dunkey. I think he's cringe now. I watch different shit.
Don't you think Dunkey is cringe?
I think Dunkey is cringe. I watch different shit.
What are you watching now, dude? Don't tell me you watch Nakey Jakey, man.
No, I also think he's cringe.
He's kinda, he's cringe, yeah.
I watch Yonskas.
What are you watching now?
He watches Yonskas.
I don't watch Yonskas.
been watching this YouTube channel called Game Ranks which is just some guy, it's one
guy but he pretends it's like a website like IGN and I love when guys are, it's a YouTube
channel with one single dude and then they keep saying like, yeah we over here at Game
Ranks are gonna give this game a 3.
That's awesome dude.
and
I'm watching the lovely channel where he talks about the drama.
What is it called?
Mogul mail man.
I've been thinking about making one of these YouTube channels.
You should.
I love your takes on the news.
Whatever the biggest news story that is not a news story.
That's the thing.
The last couple of days I've been watching opening up my YouTube and oh a hospital gets
completely destroyed 500 people are dead in Gaza and I open YouTube top thing
some ordinary gamers is like this is officially the worst game ever
I love that guy, that guy is so funny
I think there might be something maybe slightly more important that you could make a video on right now
I love how he can go like over like 30 seconds without going like
Ladies and gentlemen, this fucking sucks.
Ladies and gentlemen, this game is just complete shit.
I think that I can make these videos, man.
Give me any topic, I'll make a video on it right now.
Um, the war on Ukraine.
It needs to be the kind of thing that they would handle, though.
It needs to be like, Blueface and Krushan broke up.
That type of shit.
Okay, so the King Kong game looks like shit,
and people are calling for its cancellation.
uh... some what's up youtube it's caleb
pits nineteen ninety seven back here with another video
right after this intro
uh...
i want to say
i want to interrupt
intros are done
intersects now
uh...
is that true
i'm not so sure
this youtube channel called mom reviews movies it's
It's this old woman who...
You would be watching bomb reviews movies.
No, hang on. Wait a second.
She is an old woman who lives in Vegas
who records all her videos through Zoom.
So you can see on the corner of her video,
there's always her full name.
That's sweet.
With horrible audio, horrible like Zoom audio.
She's talking about the sound of freedom.
Be like, "Oh, this movie was so inspiring," or whatever.
And she has an intro that is so loud.
I really want to reach out and be like,
Like you know what, you're doing great, I love your takes, especially on this pedophile movie.
Drop the intro.
I think she stands to gain so much if she just drops the intro.
And we can talk about the zoom and all that shit later.
The intro is cringe now.
Intros are cringe.
Why does everybody, everybody seems to have YouTube algorithms that show them funny videos
of people making disgusting food or people who don't know how to use a computer.
In my- all the videos that I get on YouTube are actually made for 10 year olds.
Like I don't get anything- there is no skibbity- I've seen every skibbity toilet and I'm up
to episode 56.
Well that's probably why.
Every single- everybody I know is like "dude check out this video I found earlier of a
guy who's trying to fuck a watermelon" and I'm like "oh man that's cool, let's check
out my YouTube" and it's like "top 10 times Naruto was out of pocket".
What is wrong with me?
Why is it only my videos that are like this?
It's you.
No, I know it's me, that's what I mean.
It's an awful reflection of the kind of thing that I watch when nobody's around.
When I went back to meet my girlfriend's family,
her brother's best friend got a DUI, college, couldn't get a job,
and so his job now is making those videos.
Really?
He's like very clearly like kind of ashamed about it.
Here's mine dude, here's my YouTube front page right now.
10 games that died trying to expand their audience.
Historic food preservation, potted salmon.
Make tortillas like a Mexican grandma.
The story of America's most corrupt cop.
I went bourbon hunting for old Forrester birthday bourbon.
What is this?
I don't want to say that one.
Say it.
You have to say it now.
Six common pitfalls in healing childhood trauma.
What are you looking up on YouTube man?
Nothing dude.
See, this is more me. Mortal Kombat 1 Official Omni-Man First Look.
That's my kind of thing. I'll click on that. I'll click on that shit.
I've got "Family Guy Season 15 Episode 17"
Okay, so we're on the same page then, you and me.
I had a feeling it would be you and me on the same exact...
Hot potato, thunder kick, new slot, first look.
Yeah, well I skipped a lot of slot stuff, I'm gonna be real.
Yeah, I got a sky bounty was one that I had got a lot of music got some like tft videos wait
Actually now that you brought this up. I remember that you're a big family guy big Rick and Morty type of guy
What is your official review on Rick and Morty season 7 episode 1?
It's actually funny you say that because I did watch the episode really
I
Haven't watched it in so long that I couldn't tell the difference
Really? Wow. You didn't even tell that it wasn't even Justin Roiland and the other guy?
I didn't think about it that hard because I don't care.
I did think it's funny that it says that he did make the show. He's still in the credits.
Because they're like, it's like created by Justin Roiland.
It's like created by Justin Roiland. Yeah, literally.
Separate the art from the artist.
The episode was not very good.
It's just it kind of just seems like they're on the downswing on the show.
Yeah I just I saw through the people were complaining and I saw that it's got a really bad
audience score on Ryan. Well it's just not a very good episode like if I was for me Rick and Morty
means like I smoked weed I got too high and I need something to like pacify me and if I got
to
This is the last motherfucking thing I- you know what I used to do?
I'm not kidding.
For two months in college, I used to rip a vape pen every single night and watch alternating
Borat and Freddy Got Fingered.
Every single night.
Every fucking- every single night for two months.
I watched Borat and then I watched Freddy Got Fingered.
And then I watched Borat and Freddy Got Fingered.
And I would do that- and I would do this thing where I would laugh so hard at a joke in one
or the other that I would miss 30 minutes of the movie because I would fall off of my bed
laughing so hard and then I would get back up and watch. I've seen both of those movies
30 times at least. In my head, I was picturing this, you were just watching like 10 minutes
of Borat and then be like okay, now the other one. Then you watch it like 5 minutes and
then going back. I probably did that 4 or 5 times too. That's awesome. I probably did
I'm
I stopped watching TV in the shower as well.
My whole life is just...
Woah!
What?
I'm not saying "Why'd you stop?"
But what as if you were watching television in the shower?
We've been over this multiple times.
Why did you stop?
I don't remember this.
I just kinda just stopped.
It just doesn't feel right anymore.
Oh man, I'm sorry.
It was such an enjoyable thing.
I think I don't like my shower this much here.
Do you have a bath?
I do.
I highly recommend baths, my friend.
Yeah, I might do that because it's just been...
I...
When you bathe in New York City, and then you get out of the shower...
You feel dirty already.
Man, don't blame the city you live in, please, because you have a disgusting apartment.
Wait, what does that mean?
Is your phone in your fucking room?
No, it's like you go outside...
Because I get out of my bath and I say, "Oh, I've been transported to some kind of 19th century home."
the
you're already dirty.
What's wrong with your bed?
What are you talking about?
You're not sweating in your sleep?
No!
Not in fall, not in October.
Oh, you're just at the perfect temperature all the time, I'm sorry.
No, maybe I'm a little cold, but I'm not sweating.
You want to sleep cold rather than sleeping warm?
Yes, of course I want to sleep cold.
You sleep better when you're cold.
I want to sleep cold.
I love sleeping cold.
Yeah.
Yes, of course I want to sleep cold. You sleep better when you're cold.
I want to sleep cold. I love sleeping cold.
I leave my windows open all winter, man.
Yeah, you're being a little odd, Rex.
You are being odd.
You're saying that the city is so disgusting that you get out of your bath into your bathroom, by the way, which is about three degrees removed from the city, and you feel dirty.
dirty? No, what I mean, first of all, I shower like in the morning or like midday.
Okay. Maybe I shower after I get off work, but it's before going out.
And then I go out and I'm like, you know, I'm all dressed up.
I'm either too cold or I'm sweating.
Do you have like a winding down routine when you're in your day?
like brush your teeth, uh, no, look at the clock for like two hours.
I would never brush my teeth, but I probably would watch a YouTube video called
"The Dark History Behind Skibbity Toilet". It's about four and a half hours long.
Fall asleep to that every night. Yeah, I do...
what I do is I walk into my bedroom, uh, and I say, uh, "Alexa, turn off my light.
Alexa, turn on American Dad." And then I dance to that. I've seen you do that.
Yeah.
I've seen you do that. It's honestly a miracle of modern technology.
It's probably my favorite thing in the world.
Wait, why have you seen him do his wind-down routine?
When I went over there the other night, he said, this was his...
He was like, "You wanna see my room?"
I was like, "Yeah, dude."
We walked in and he immediately said, "Alexa, turn off the light. Alexa, turn on American Dad."
And I was like, "That was too automatic. This is... He does this every single day."
Every single day.
It's the best, dude.
You could say, "Turn the lights at 20%."
It does it for you.
Turn the American Dad at 110.
Yep. Turn the volume up. Turn the lights to green.
Turn the lights to green. Turn the weed on.
Turn that motherfucking American Dad all the way up. Crank that shit.
Yeah, make the TV really bright.
Yeah, well I had to stop. I had to wait on Family Guy. I'm on season 15.
I'm catching up. I gotta get to at least where they replaced Cleveland Brown with a black man.
season 20. They replaced him with the guy who sang the the Cleveland. That's one of
the most amazing come ups of all time. Kudos to that guy. That guy's the GOAT.
I was talking about this the other day which is that like that song is amazing.
Which song? That's just a thing you can make with AI now and it takes 30 minutes.
Yeah I was gonna ask you do you think that Rick and Morty is one of the
shows that can just be written by AI and no one would notice?
It probably already is.
Yeah.
They probably, I feel like
most stories now,
forever,
will, I mean I guess they
did sign that like agreement or whatever
but like anything that's not
under that, like any book
from now on, you're just gonna put
in your little plot points
and then you're just gonna have it
spit out filler and then
you're just gonna edit it and ship it out.
- Yeah, it's that simple.
We should be doing that with this podcast.
- We should. - We should.
- I think we could.
- All right, next episode,
a fully artificial intelligence episode.
We're gonna get a script.
Or maybe at least the beers.
We'll at least have AI pick the beer.
Can we agree to this?
- Okay, yeah.
AI picks the beer and rates the beer.
- Okay, sounds good.
- All right.
Thank you for watching. - Okay, my feathered friends.
I do outros and intros, but very nice try, Jubio.
Oh, okay.
[laughter]
Thank you to all of my drinking friends, all of my sober gophers.
I love you all.
This has truly been one of the greatest experiences of my short life.
I hope all of you have an amazing weekend, and what can I say but keep drinking.
And thank you all for watching, and see you next week.
Nope, nice try.
Thank you all for watching.
We'll see you next week.
And thank you all for watching, and see you next week.
Okay, I'm just gonna thank you for watching.