*sniff*
Oh, it's recording!
*sips*
I need to talk to my DJ.
What's up all my chuggers?
I'm trying to get that boob out.
This is a journey into...
...the internet.
...the planet, Ken.
Bud Light.
...Hot Food Ribbon.
Beer's We Drank, motherfucker.
With Juvio, Caleb, and Rex.
Beer.
Welcome back, you pieces of shit.
Welcome back to Beer's We Drank, man.
Everybody crack open their beers.
Click.
There goes my delicious beer. Mine is scented with a scent, with an odor.
Well, I'll start because I maybe have the most fail beer of
any of us that we've ever had on this show. All right, let's go. Let's go. Let's go on the fail scale.
Let's do at least most fail beer, half fail beer, and fully not fail beer. So you go first Caleb.
Okay.
Here's my fail beer guys. This...
Last night I hosted Leo, my friend from the United Kingdom.
Shout out.
Came over to my house and me and him, we got back to my house after we had been at the bar
for a little bit and we had a little nightcap.
We had, I had two white claws sitting in my fridge.
We popped them open.
I got about two sips into mine and decided that I did not want to drink anymore and I
put it in the fridge and that's what I'm drinking.
I'm finishing this today, because this is the beer that I had.
I'm drinking a beer that I've already had two sips of.
This is one of the biggest fails of my drinking career.
Listen, it's completely flat and I'm going to give you a sip.
This is somehow worse than the Sober Gophers episode.
I almost did Sober Gophers because I didn't really want to drink anything tonight, but
I didn't want to go to Walgreens and they card you for non-alcoholic beer and I have a temporary
ID right now and I didn't want to have to explain.
I hate having to explain that to people because I hand them a piece of paper and they say what
is this?
And I say it's a temporary grey ID and they act like they've never seen it before.
Anyway, guys, I mean this is a one.
This is just about the worst thing you can fucking drink in your life.
It's the natural lime flavor.
It tastes like complete shit, man.
I have that bottle of proper 12.
I've been slowly, I've been ever so slowly...
Here's what I've been doing with that, by the way.
If I, to be economical, because I already spent money on this bottle of proper 12, but
I hate the taste of it so much, I will pour like a half of an ounce of proper 12 in a
giant glass of water so that it just tastes like water.
And I will have that because that's the only way that I can drink it.
And maybe if I finish this, maybe I'll have to show you that.
This will be the two worst drinks ever.
Should I put proper 12 in this right now?
Yeah, actually yeah.
It's going to get worse than what you're currently drinking.
Okay.
We're just making potions now.
All right, well actually that's a really good segue into my beer.
Since Caleb is making a mixture, I bought a pre-mixed beer that I've been informed by a
very close source of mine that is actually complete shit.
This is a soul mix with a mango juice or whatever.
I think it's like mango and some shit.
Mango and chamoy.
Chamoy, yeah.
I was told that the-
Sounds good.
Wait a second. That's all in theory in practice. I was told this is a wait wait wait wait wait wait
This is amazing, yeah, this is amazing. This is good
Really
That is good. That is good. Good. That's like a cocktail explain. That's amazing. Explain what's going on. It tastes it
Hmm. What does it taste like it has some kind of mixed drink kind of stuff going on?
Yeah, I'm tasting almost like a it tastes like almost a gimlet. Have you ever had a gimlet?
Yeah, I got almost like some kind of whiskey gimlet, right?
It's good, man. This is a good drink. I'm gonna give this a
Fah I'm gonna give this a
Six foot two Wow. This is a point guard. This is a star an undersized but starting point guard
This is a 6'2", this is a 5.7 on the numerical scale.
This is not bad, man.
Yeah, the lime I thought would kind of cut the nastiness of the proper 12.
It really does.
That is amazing.
Doesn't have like a nastier aftertaste or anything?
No, it has not.
It almost tastes like neither drinks that it is made out of.
It is more than the sum of its parts.
That's awesome.
I'm really happy with that.
Wow.
I'm going to drink my mango and chamoy soul beer now.
Okay.
That sounds good.
It's alright.
Okay.
I don't hate it.
It does taste like chamoy and a little bit of mango juice I guess.
So as advertised, it tastes like what it is on the can.
I'm going to go with a straight through the middle five.
I don't love it, but I don't completely hate it like I was told I was going to hate it.
Okay.
if you like to have a way
uh... to more
get it for a good treat
i have that giant i've i've bought that giant mega chum boy
at the grocery store
why and i was a person because i put it on pineapple everyone so well
but i looked at the ingredients and it's just about the worst thing you put your
body
yeah pretty much
all its leader plastic
it's high fructose corn syrup in red forty that's the entire does the first
first
first time I've had Chamoy this year and it's in my awesome beer. I'm a fan of
Chamoy. Okay. So I am very excited for this I saw this. I have a Victory Berry
Monkey. Oh wow. So this is still a 9.5% beer. Uh-huh. But it's it's a sour monkey
with a hint of berry. Let's let's.
There's also a 2.5 percent, so this is like water.
You keep coming with these weak ass beers, man.
Yeah, they get weaker.
That's all I get at my 7-Eleven.
You keep coming with these weak beers.
What are you getting?
What kind of things are you getting?
What's the flavor?
It's almost tasteless.
It's really weird.
Hmm. And normally the chips.
Normally both you and I are fans of the sour monkey line of products.
This is a good line of products.
This is a beer with a lot of flavor.
It doesn't taste so much like beer.
It tastes almost like sour candy.
So this is very surprising to me.
It's odd because you know you taste the sour monkey, you get that overwhelming sourness.
You know?
Could this be a byproduct of you having pretty much like stomach cancer over the past like
two weeks?
No.
Because I don't have tongue cancer.
You've been having stomach cancer?
Tell me what's been going on gastrointestinally.
Okay. Obviously I've talked about having food poisoning like last couple...
I just remembered exactly what happened last night.
And then last night, while we were gaming, we played two games of Valorant.
And during the first game I chugged half of a monster that was sitting on my desk for like hours.
And I ate an entire bag of Gardetto's.
What's Gardetto's?
Gardetto's are like Chex Mix with the extra kind of like flavoring to them.
Okay.
They're yummy. But it's like Chex Mix basically.
So like a 12 ounce bag of Chex Mix.
And uh, I did that during the first game because I hadn't eaten all day.
And it was by the way, the greatest I've ever seen Rex play in history.
Yeah.
It was amazing.
Put on a clinic.
Yeah, I really tore that one up. And honestly, I wasn't doing too bad in the second game.
Until...
He stopped moving. He was sitting in the spawn.
Okay, so I started to feel... you know that feeling of weakness you get when you haven't eaten?
And you're like, "I don't even know how I'm going to get the energy to get up and get food."
So I started to get that feeling, and there was a moment where I made a call.
I like lost a gunfight, but I had hit the other person out. They were low and I kind of went like
Cypher blow, you know like that Julio laughed at me
Thinking I was maybe doing a joke. This was a death rattle, right?
As I was getting closer and closer and I was like, okay, we'll just
Make it to the end of the game
You'll figure it out when you get there. You can make a pizza. There's a pizza in the freezer. You can make a freezer pizza
You'd be pretty
But then I started to just feel worse and worse and I started to go like pale white
I could feel the blood drain from my face. Yeah, I was like, oh no and I noticed I had two bags to my right
one was a slightly ripped empty bag of
Goldfish. Yeah, but you know that like silver bag they come in
Yes. Yeah, if you get it from like Costco and beside that was a
plastic bag filled with records and so my thought was take this silver bag and
Kind of breathe into it to like, you know, like you're on an airplane, you know and calm yourself
Sorry the bet the bag that you thought that you were about to throw up and you said I need to breathe in goldfish air
Well, it was empty. It's a goldfish sat in there for weeks and months. Yeah, that's true
So anyway, don't flavor blast all it had been a flavor blasted bag. It was just a regular bag
How awful that be if you put the if you put the bag up to your mouth on an airplane and you tasted nacho cheese
That is such an awful. I wasn't thinking straight. Okay, okay
Thing I didn't want to go that far. But as I leaned over and picked it up I immediately
threw up a little bit
up again and then during the third heave all the contents in my stomach came up
and it was too heavy for the goldfish bag which had been ripped so the bag ripped
in half in my hand as I was doing so I after that happened I looked at the mess
on the ground by my side and said that can wait and I pulled myself closer and I came back to the game
I played out the rest of the round.
And I'm here like...
There was... you were not moving at all
and you hadn't bought a gun.
And we were like, "Rex, you need to buy. Rex, buy, buy, buy."
And you said, "I'm throwing up."
[laughter]
And we immediately were like, "Okay, we lost this game. That's fine."
And so, I, you know,
tried to do something.
Nothing really happened. So I was like, "Okay."
Went to the kitchen, got
a roll of paper towels.
Cleaned up the mess off the ground.
emptied, took the records out of the bag and used that bag to store the throw-up bag and
the throw-up paper towels.
Kind of tied it up a little bit, you know.
And then, I was like, "Okay, so I have my water."
I started drinking my water.
I was starting to feel a little bit better.
And the game went to overtime.
We ended up winning.
We did win.
We did win that game.
Amazing.
We ended up winning, despite me throwing up in the middle of it.
But the issue was, as we got to overtime, the smell of the throw-up bag directly next to
me was kind of like starting to waft over, so I was like, being like, "Ugh."
Because you can't--because just using my nose would have been bad, and I was like, "Okay,
we have to finish this game, because if it goes any longer, the smell's gonna get overpowering,
I'm not gonna be able to focus on, you know, shooting my gun, winning the game, whatever.
And I said, "I'm gonna tap out."
And you know, went in the kitchen, got like a wet paper towel with some soap on it, and
wiped the floor down where I had missed, where some had spilled, and then proceeded to kind
of unload some trash and take it out to the dumpster, the garbage.
and I looked at my girlfriend and I said,
"I'm gonna make a frozen pizza I just threw up while gaming."
And she liked it. She thought this was attractive.
No, she thought...
And she was like, "And then say what game you were playing."
She gave me a hard time because she was like, "You have a weak stomach."
"You're always eating things and then feeling pain directly after."
I was like, "I don't know what you're talking about."
And she's like, because there's we went to a peri-peri chicken place.
Mm-hmm.
And we had walked to the grocery store that was like, you know, a little further down and then like stopped there on the way back.
And it was one of those places that clearly you're not supposed to eat in.
But we ordered eat-in not thinking about it.
Then realized they wouldn't give us like a cup of water.
And then I would try to go back to the grocery store and the guy looked at me and was like,
"We're closed."
And so I ate an entire like chicken wrap and fries with no water.
And it was like really salty and it made my body like immediately need to like shit and
pee because I just was so dehydrated and all the water like pulled out of my cells.
I don't think that you have a great grasp on biology.
Because I don't think that you eat one salty meal without water and it makes you diarrhea
and piss.
A whole meal?
I mean it just triggered my need to shit.
I think it dries you out.
Yeah, it dries you out and it makes your body feel like it needs water and then because
it's not getting any water it's like trying to expel water because you're too watery.
What?
And I hadn't shit all day, because it was the first meal I'd eaten.
Do you have IBS?
Do you have the Jewish IBS?
I think at some point I've developed it, yes.
It's the only explanation I can think of.
Because I've been able to eat shit my entire life and not really have a problem, but now
I'm like, "Oh, he's my asshole."
But I think you just hit a wall.
I think you just hit a wall.
I used to be able to eat double cheeseburgers every day from cookout when I was in freshman
year of college and now I can't imagine eating. That's like a once a year type of
treat for me because of what it will do to my body. And I would say I'm in an
age gap relationship and the age gap I don't think that's really an important thing but we are on
different sides of 25 which is where your body starts to just be completely
dog shit at everything it used to be good at.
- So, we have basically the same--
- She just came out of high school last year, it's fine.
- Yeah, she got her GED, man.
- Yeah.
- Chill.
- So, we, you know, she's like,
"I eat the same thing as you and I feel fine."
And I'm like, "I could eat when I was your age, back then."
- Which, by the way, if you ever are talking
to your significant other and having to say,
"When I was your age,"
That means you're in a dope-ass relationship.
It means that you're having some of the greatest sex of your entire life.
[Laughter]
You're also 28 when I presume you're not supposed to be like
falling to pieces like you apparently are.
No, you do fall... 26 is where just all the things that went right for you...
Yeah, I think I agree.
Yeah, it's like...
is
I don't even know what it is, but apparently garlic is on it, so I'm just not going to
even try doing it because I eat so much garlic.
Yeah.
I mean, I used to be able to eat really spicy food, and now it hurts my butthole.
I used to be able to just, you know, not really like think about what my meals were at all
in terms of timing and just be able to feel fine.
And now it's kind of clear that like, not only is the diet that I used to be like thin
with making me fat now, it's like, it's also making me feel horrible.
So I have to make some sort of change and I think that's just a process of hitting your
mid-20s and hitting that wall.
I um, do you have a turning point in your life where you know this is the first time that
everything started being so bad with my shits and my eating?
Well I've always had trouble with my shits, I've always had a little bit of bleeding and
a little bit of you know, whatever.
I would say in the last like two, three years, it's really been a downhill, like a noticeable
drop in quality of my stomach.
I see.
You know?
Yeah.
There was a point where, it was during COVID, and I got blessed by Donald Trump with, you
know, a fat check.
Yes.
I remember this money.
Shouts out.
Yeah.
The best person in the world.
eating nothing but fried rice and beans and started being able to go to Trader Joe's and eat like a salad and
Like a lentil wrap and like that
Increase in the quality of food like ruined my ability to be a garbage disposal for food. Oh
Once you saw once you lived the better life. Yeah, I see you couldn't go back. You're stopping a
vegetarian recently as well
You're stomach not being accustomed to all these chemicals and meats and flavors.
Which I would point to as also the turning point for me when I was like 17 or 18 and
stopped eating or started eating meat. I would say that's also when I started
getting much worse diarrhea. But also that coincided with I was dosed with
capsaicin extract and I think it destroyed my stomach forever by my
cousin Nick. Yeah, I do think I kind of want to I wish there was a way to figure
out how good your gut flora is because I feel like I'm completely destroyed. My
cousin Nick three years in a row the first the my dad would make chili at our
family get-together and he would make a vegan chili for me and a normal one and
he three years in a row did different tricks to put something very spicy in my
chili. The first year, he put it in the entire batch and just ruined the entire batch of chili,
blended up Carolina Reaper and put it in there. The second year, he put it only in my bowl while
I was in the bathroom. And then the third year, he synthesized pure capsaicin, the chemical that
makes the food spicy, and put it into a dropper and dropped it into my chili. Like a capsaicin oil.
And I completely blame him for everything that's ever happened to me bad in my entire life.
Yeah, no, that's absolutely fair.
This is, it's like, it's an assassination attempt.
This is a poisoning.
This is like how the Joker attacks his targets.
But we were young, I was, you know, I was 17, he was 25.
He didn't know any better.
Right, yeah, he's just a kid.
Yeah, yeah, he's just a kid.
Um...
Yeah, I don't know. I think you guys just got poisoned by different things.
Well, food in general in America, the quality of it is very poor.
So when you eat a lot of American food, you become diseased.
A lot of sides in American food, I've noticed. I've noticed this.
Yeah, there's a lot of fries, a lot of things of that nature.
I was talking about this the other day.
I think home fries are stupid.
I think they're a complete scam.
I agree.
I'm into hash browns, man.
I like them shredded.
I do agree.
I like them like this and then like this.
And like them nice and crispy like Waffle House.
Yeah, but the problem is none of these restaurants or even the delivery apps consider that maybe
an ESL person who's never been to New York before ordering for the first time is going
to see, "Oh, home fries.
probably delicious potatoes.
You think it's fries?
I think it's fries in my house, in my home I guess.
It's not man.
And it's not.
Nah, just to make sure, home fries are the little like potato squares.
They're just like sauteed potatoes, like pan fried.
I don't think those are that bad that you would be like distraught if you got them.
But I would rather have fries or I would rather have hash browns.
I would be so sad.
I was so sad.
What I would have rather had actual fries or hashbrowns.
I'd rather have a fucking, I'd rather have a baked potato.
I'll say that shit.
I'd rather have a baked potato with sour cream and cheese
than a fucking home fries.
Wait, you don't fucking bake potatoes?
I love baked potatoes, but I think it's ridiculous in the context.
It's not ridiculous.
Okay, alright, what's your tier list then?
In potatoes?
Yeah.
Potato food.
Potato tier list.
I mean, context matters.
What context? You're eating it.
Yeah, but what am I eating it with?
Potatoes aren't a main course. Okay, it's breakfast. It's breakfast. I'm not eating a baked potato for breakfast. Are you saying?
No, I'm not. I feel saner than I've ever felt in my life a baked potato for breakfast sounds fucking amazing
No salsa on the potato I gotta say guys the salsa really straight me over I think I'm with Kevin on this one
No, I know I know my audience. I know who I'm talking to right now breakfast burrito eggs
Sausage but a baked potato in that bitch the whole thing
That's the whole burrito. That's ridiculous. Well, you cut it
Not spouting nonsense, this is not nonsense a baked potato has a better texture than a home fry. No, not all this oily
Same
What are you talking about?
That is actually crazy.
It's a potato that's cut.
It's the same internal potato.
No.
You are out of your- The only different texture of potatoes is hashbrowns because they're so
thin that they get crisp.
Hashbrowns are the only good potato.
How about a scalloped potato?
Okay, maybe a scalloped potato.
Thank you.
And I could go on.
Tater tots.
Tater- no.
What?
Yeah.
Yeah!
No way.
This is like people who get up in arms about steak fries being horrible.
I love steak fries.
And yet you don't like a home fry?
Wait, how, how do you not?
A smaller steak fry?
Are you coming out as a homeware apologist right now? Are you, are you kidding me right now?
He likes home fries.
I like all types of potato. I don't think it's necessary to be like...
Okay here's a good question.
If you're at a diner and they have home fries or normal fries with breakfast, what are you
getting?
How do they cook their...
I would need to see...
You don't need to know how they cook...
Your favorite fries in the world.
Then the fries, yeah.
Okay, then it's not weird to eat a baked potato for breakfast.
Because fries are a lunch and dinner food.
And so is a baked potato.
But can it be eaten at breakfast?
Yeah man, it's all the same shit to me.
I think the separation between a home fry and a regular fry is way too indistinct to
make it so clear cut.
Because a good home fry is crisp in the same way a fry is.
I think it's crinkle cut my friend, because I think it's very very clear.
I think I'm seeing defined edges here between a home fry and a normal fry.
And if we're willing to go from home fry to normal fry, let's go opposite, backwards evolutionarily,
and let's have a baked potato for breakfast.
That is a caveman's way of eating a potato.
What?
Oh, caveman, guess what caveman haven't invented yet?
Fire.
Guess how you bake a potato?
In an oven.
Yep.
No, caveman did literally invent fire.
You're done.
You are done.
That's what was in the cave.
That's the whole point of the cave.
No, the cave was to draw.
What is the whole point of the cave?
was
come on the show is a strong because you're starting
uh... i said get astronomy
but nice try but are in the up
speaking of other you know i got a bit of a doubt
debate today yet again
it comes back
i love big potatoes i've had one hundred five years
but i do not know what it's not a year so you're defending it over a home for i
i don't betty i don't eat potatoes almost ever
the
as
shown
on
Okay, let me say that.
I think it's not fair to compare the two because, uh, rice is a blank canvas for
sauce.
Whereas a potato is a canvas for more sweet kind of thicker sauces or butter.
You can't really put the same butter rice.
That's true.
Tree can, and it's great, but you can also put even more sauce on it than that.
You can't put soy sauce on a potato.
Watch me.
You can, but I think the rice is more versatile.
You can add more things to the rice.
It's a much wider canvas to have flavor profiles expressed with than a potato.
Potatoes very narrow.
The potatoes get turned into chips, which are delicious.
My point.
I like chips.
I do like chips.
I have two bags of chips that I've been eating three chips from each bag every single day.
Three jalapeno, three salt and vinegar.
there
Salt and vinegar and jalapeno and I got him for my wife
She doesn't she ate two of them and then now I've been eating
About three or four of each every single day. It's fucked up
The potato chips are the only ones that get like a name like that, you know Howell's
victor's
They're always getting some kind of name like that for their branding. Mmm
So you're saying no, I really don't know what you're saying. Yeah, I'm saying
You're saying that they have brands of potato chips unlike everything else?
Well the brands are a lot more like, think about like popcorn, or...
Orville Redenbacher.
Right. That's like a full name.
Smart pop.
Right, you see what I'm saying? These are all like 1950s ass names.
A fucking potato chip gets an 1800s name.
Like a doctor made it. Those are Hal's potato chips.
Orville Redenbacher is the most doctor name I've ever heard!
There's some Lay's potatoes.
That's a space-age man-scientist.
Lay? You think Lay is a...
Sun Chips.
This is not a good point.
Doritos. This is stupid. This is really stupid.
You are not cooking. This is not...
Doritos are not potato chips. What the fuck are you talking about?
Yes, they are.
They are corn, my friend.
They are corn chips.
Yeah, what are you smoking?
This is the stupidest thing anyone's said on this podcast.
He thinks Doritos are also made up of...
Sun Chips are also made up of...
chips are multi-grain.
Yeah.
They're chips.
Do you not know what the fuck a potato chip is?
He's never had a potato.
He was talking all this shit about...
No you haven't!
I can smell it.
You know what I don't understand?
What the hell is a potato bun?
That is bread.
I think they use potato like in the dough.
Just a little bit?
Yeah.
To flavor it.
Which potato is known for its very strong flavor.
Yeah, potatoes really knock you out with the flavor.
The potato flavor, oh my god, it's so good.
Yeah, that's why you can't really tell the difference between a potato bun and a regular
bun.
I guess you're right.
Yeah.
Well, here's what's going on in my life.
I'm growing my hair out.
I can see that.
It's dark.
Yup, and my wife has bleached her eyebrows, guys.
That's over for you.
It's over.
I started growing my hair out, and then one week later she bleaches her eyebrows.
We're having an ugly contest.
We're seeing who can get more ugly.
That's a week's worth of growth on the hair?
Yeah, just about, from plumb bald to this.
Can you give us the full walk around?
Yeah, I want to show some of my barber.
It's coming in thick in the back.
In the hat parts.
Yeah.
I think if you wore a really...
Like one of those hats that the brim is like on your eyebrows.
Yeah, yeah.
You'd be pulling the... thinking you have hair.
A cowboy hat type of guy?
I have a cowboy hat that I thought was made of snakeskin,
but then I brought it back to my wife and I was like,
"Check out this cool snakeskin hat."
She's like, "This is made of, like, straw paper."
I'm so easily fooled. Somebody took a straw hat and spray painted parts of it black.
And I was like, "This is a snakeskin hat and I'm getting a deal buying this for $40."
Did they sell it to you as that? Or did you just assume?
It was just at an antique store. I just assumed based on how it looked.
Okay, so no one scammed you.
Nobody scammed me.
You scammed yourself.
Whoever made the hat scammed the future people.
No, you skipped yourself.
Go on, Rex.
I saw a haircut and hairline that reminded me a lot of Caleb.
On a young man on a TV show.
22 years old.
And he had like a swoopy kind of hair.
But it swooped really far back from like here.
On the sides to give the impression that he had a hairline.
This is called a comb over.
It was a comb-over, but it wasn't, you know, I mean, yeah, it's a comb-over.
But it was on like a young, hip guy, so it didn't come across in that like wispy, shitty way.
So it was kind of cool.
It was cool, but you could tell it was on a game show, and over time he got more sweaty, and you could start to see where the airline started.
It's all a facade.
Right, and it started to show through at the end, and I think that's why he lost the game show,
was because he was 22 in that ball.
Have you seen these things, they call them hair systems, they're wigs?
Yeah.
That's a funny name for a wig.
Well, it's a system.
Because only a man would be like, "I'm employing a hair system."
It's a system. I'm deploying a system on top of my scalp that resembles hair.
Women wear a wig.
No, I think they also do hair systems.
for women. I think they're two different things.
That's what's in hair systems. Women couldn't possibly understand the system.
Exactly. They're only oppressed by systems. I just can't. I think the hair
system thing, can you imagine? I think the thing about being bald is, it's not about
if you look bald, it's about whether people know that you are bald or not. Yes.
That is the real shame of being bald.
Yeah.
So if I wore a hair system,
the people in my life would still know I was bald.
When I get home, I would still hang up my hair.
Right.
You know?
I guess, you know, being...
I think...
We love you despite the fact that you are bald.
I know it's hard for you.
No, this is...
It's not hard at all.
This is completely wrong.
A stranger though...
By the way.
Needs to know that you have hair.
The hair system is like a half a step into like a transplant
because it gets like put in by a professional and it just stays on your head.
You have to like take it off. It's not like a wig. You like put on and take off.
Really? I thought you just clip it in.
Why do you know so much about this? You're going bald?
You have one in right now, don't you, you bastard?
He's looking it up.
I know about it because of another podcast
where they gave a guy a hair system, a friend of ours.
Is this a podcast?
No, it's a podcast that Kael has been on.
The Yard?
Yeah.
They gave Slime a hair system? Really?
Yeah, pretty much.
Did he look amazing?
He did. He called himself Patrick Star or some shit.
And he looked great, but he hated it.
He hated it? Does it itch?
I don't know. I don't know what it was.
It seems like it might itch.
I'll message him about it later today. I'm sure he'll love my questions.
Think ball people love talking about their baldness and their head. That's why you never bring it up
Yeah, it is. Basically all we have
All you have at some point. Whoa, you took the label off
I did it got very wet and came right off and the broom. I'm checking out the brew masters approval
by Bill and Ron
Which are very brew master names. That's that's two guys. Not one guy billing bill. Um
Bill and Ron it's ill and Ron. Yeah
These are the brew masters guys
Here's what I've had enough of
Ampersand
restaurants
hmm
I'm done with the ampersands y'all if you're if you think your restaurant is not good enough to have just
One word as the name then don't open a fucking restaurant
I'm done with this shit. I get cattle and cork bread and butter
Food and drinks. This is fucking bullshit. This is not what we should be calling our restaurants restaurants should be called
Derek
Bud Rucker's
Chili's
right, this
and King burger
Exact chili and s
What the hell that makes no sense man, but in Rutgers
and
Huddles tea. Thank God and it's Friday
Bullshit man and fillet Panda and Express we could go on forever win and DS pop and ice
Pop and eyes. This is complete bullshit man. I'm done with this
Kentucky fried and chicken we're not doing any more of these
We've done
Up in a way sure. Okay. No, we're done though. We're completely done. I don't want to do this anymore
I really don't I think I agree barrel
Dom and Eno where would it would go to Dom and Eno's pizza?
This is, I'm shit out of fucking...
Papay Jones, and your mic broke by the way.
My, the thing came out!
That's crazy.
That's how bad I was getting.
Papay Jones.
You know the, the, I think it's a Chris Rock joke, it's like, "Guns should be cheap, but bullets should cost a thousand dollars."
Yeah.
"Eonsigned letters should be cheap, but the ampersand should cost a million dollars."
The ampersand, it should be more expensive
to file for a business license.
- Yeah.
- If you have an ampersand in the name.
- I'm done with the ampersand.
Go on the New York list of doing business as names.
Go to the database, sort by all the symbols,
instead of like the ones before the alphabet.
And you're just gonna be completely,
you won't be able to read that much.
take you years to read all these fucking names dude. What would you call a brand new restaurant?
Like a restaurant type name? That's not a guy's name. I would probably do something amazing
and have just like a square or a triangle as the name for my restaurant. Yeah like it's
a witch house album. Triangle? Yes. Not triangle. Let's go to triangle for a slice? No people
wouldn't even say that. They would make, people would say let's go to that pizza place. Yeah
I would not open a pizza place.
Wait, hang on.
What is it called?
I don't remember what it is.
It doesn't have a name actually, but it has a triangle on the front of it.
Yeah, let me put it on Google Maps.
What is it called again?
Circle triangle.
Oh, circle triangle.
If you think that my high-end restaurant- Circle and triangle would be actually a really
good name for a pizza place.
I've decided.
With an ampersand?
No!
Yeah, with an ampersand.
No ampersands!
dark emoji circle and a kind of triangle with a really dark side for the crust.
Oh yeah, just three letters on the side out front.
Wayyyy that's clean as fuck.
That would be really good I think.
No no no.
I actually completely disagree with you now.
I don't like this, these angs.
I like this restaurant.
It sounds hip, it sounds brand new, it sounds Gen Z like me.
the
are
That is the cut, you're literally the cutoff.
That is the cutoff.
And guess who got cut off, bitch? Your ass.
Your old ass.
Oh my god, you're so old.
What's up?
It's fine to admit, you're old.
I don't care about that.
You need to get really into it.
See, me personally, I think the stuff that you like is basically cringe.
What do I like?
Just all that older stuff.
You watched Lost when it came out.
Every single episode you were up watching Lost.
episode you were up watching Lost at 24.
-Kale meanwhile has watched every single episode
of Skibbity Toilet.
-I've seen every Skibbity Toilet.
I've seen every Eddie Burback video.
This is the kind of thing that I'm into because of my nature.
-We used to watch Z-Nanners and Hutch.
-Dude, I don't know who the hell that is, man.
Shut the fuck up.
I like Ninja and Applesauce, OK?
Those are the only two things in this world that I like.
You're talking like a three year old that doesn't know what plurals are.
Which one?
Both.
No, I like ninja and applesauce is what a three year old would say.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
I'm so young.
I like ninja and I like applesauce.
Yeah, that's what I do every day.
Ninja and applesauce.
My brand new restaurant.
Slam C, new restaurant.
It's a dessert place.
for the sir we got apples okay well okay so tell me how how you're gonna serve
ninja you could probably do a hot a high concept version of applesauce something
something very nice this is really simple this is just one of those like
type mr. Beast burger type beat when we're just signing a image rights thing
with ninja and it's not technically his but it's got his name on it so you you
You see it on Uber Eats like, "Oh, Ninja and applesauce. Let me get a gallon of applesauce."
"Searching applesauce on Uber Eats."
You open up your friend's Uber Eats on his phone and you're like, "Oh, there's some tacos or something."
All the searches are different spellings of applesauce with the space in a different place.
Apple and sauce.
Ninja, one of those.
Ninja, apple, space, sauce.
Apple sauce, one word.
Oh man.
You know, here's
a food that I wish I had
more access to.
Poutine.
I like poutine, guys.
I had poutine.
It's based on fries.
It is based on fries.
That's true. I'm not
laughing about this. This is a fact.
The team is based on Fries?
The Fries are based on Fries?
I guess you're, I mean, I have a really hard time disagreeing with that.
But it does not sound so right.
Inspired by Fries.
It's based on fries.
I didn't say anything wrong.
Your brain is a perfect ball.
Why can't you see?
Um.
When I lived in Boston, there was a poutine place.
It was called Sauce.
And here's another thing I don't like, by the way.
And this place is the only thing that had an exception.
But any other restaurant like this,
All my sober gophers, you have a green light. Go ahead, spray it up.
Completely destroy every window.
Okay.
I don't like when they misspell the names of words.
Or the words in the name.
Yeah.
This place was called Sauce. S-A-U-S.
That's horrible.
What the hell's that, man?
Yeah.
What the fuck is that?
Bitch don't grill my cheese.
Bitch don't grill my--
What is that?
I think it's a ghost kitchen.
Oh, I would love to go there.
there's a you have a ghost kitchen near you called bitch don't grill my cheese
famous yeah I've never heard of this yeah look at my cheese did I give you it what
do they sell grilled cheese that's the worst yeah I've ever said they're set
bitch don't grill my cheese but they sell grilled cheese yes after the
Kendrick Kendrick Lamar song I know I know every rational I immediately got a
My eye blockers stopped me from going to this website so I'm not gonna go on that website.
That was nice of them.
Yeah.
But I also don't like when they take the vowels out of the name, out of the words in the name.
That's a thing they did for Gen C.
Chicken C-H-K-N?
Yep.
I don't wanna eat that.
How about a really disgusting name like Eggslut?
Oh, Eggslut, I don't like the dirty names.
I agree, I don't like the name of Eggslut.
Motherfucking burger. I'm not gonna order the motherfucking burger.
I might order an MF burger, but I will not ever say, "Let me get the fucking turd burger."
I don't think that's what they call it.
Or whatever they call it.
Can I get the poop burger, please?
Yeah. Can I please have the diarrhea pizza?
I don't, that doesn't sound appetizing to me, man.
Okay, so what would you call your restaurant then?
I'm telling you, my restaurant would be called something so elegant
It would probably be called like...
Lily Flower
Aww, that's horrible
How's that horrible?
It'd be upscale French food
Lily Flower
Is that a French flower?
I don't know
Food is French, asshat
hat that name is it fucking French it's new American how about that it's new
American what a bag and get I'm not calling it bag and get I might go all
right fine let me give you another restaurant name barrel barrel barrel
burger well hold on barrel and barrel burger totally different yeah no that
Since Barrel doesn't tell you anything about what they're doing.
A Barrel burger is a very specific thing.
The name should not be two ingredients.
That should not be.
A Barrel is not an ingredient in food.
In the Barrel Burger it could be.
We use Kentucky Bourbon Barrel-aged mustard on the burger.
Fuck you man.
I'm coming up with, I'm the one coming up with, you come up with a restaurant name.
and a whole menu bitch barrel aged mustard you never heard of that it's
it's aged in you the Jack Daniels barrels it's mustard it's cask mates mustard
I don't think I would go to Barrel Burger honestly.
I would go to...
I would call it The Office.
And our signature meal would be called the Jim and Pam.
Yeah, that wouldn't fly.
You would not.
You would, it would have to be a fully licensed, you would spend a million dollars before you even started
Build out on the restaurant. That's not true. It's definitely true. Okay, I got a name. I got it
Normal barrel burger is a great idea. Normal burger is a little bit too tongue-in-cheek
I would say it needs to be earnest there needs to be earnest earnesty to the name. Yeah, it needs to be called something like I
Don't know why it's all flowers coming something like sunflower. Yeah, you know
I don't know.
These are vegan restaurants.
I don't know, it's just a good name to me.
What about like Chester's Grill?
A name is also good.
Yeah.
A name is good to me.
Sunflower I think is a better name.
Caleb's is good.
Caleb's?
Caleb is not a good name.
It needs to be like a one, no.
It needs to be a one syllable name.
Joe, Franz, Ruth's.
These are the restaurants that I like.
Yeah.
Well, uh, looking around at things at my desk.
The Rockies.
Rockies is good?
Yep.
Rockies is good.
That would be a burger and bowling place.
Yeah.
Looking at my desk, maybe...
Eyeballs.
Fake eyeballs.
A bottle cap.
Uh, uh...
Cans.
The cans.
the cans
The Cans! That's a great name, that's what I mean.
The Cans is a great name.
The Cans is a bar, you know.
Is it?
Yeah.
Hmm. I guess you're right.
Yeah, do you want to swing by The Cans for a drink?
Can we look at a restaurant bar?
The Con, though. C-A-N-N-E-S, like the film festival.
Mmm.
Mmm. Now you're thinking.
I'm talking about a place.
Yeah, so, a lot of things are places.
Okay.
There's a place in Bushwick called Wild and Catman Do.
That's a good name for a restaurant.
While in Kathmandu.
Because what would you do while you were in Kathmandu?
You would eat.
You would eat and you would enjoy.
I don't know where that is.
It's in Nepal.
Okay, well, why don't we use something more pedestrian?
Why don't we do Manhattan Burger?
Manhattan is a great name.
The bottle opener.
Again, this is a bar.
Yeah, that is a bar.
If you, any of us three, the stuff in our rooms would probably be bar names more than anything.
What in Rome, when it's a Chinese place?
Mirror?
That makes sense.
Mirror would be a good name for a restaurant.
This is what I'm saying, man.
It needs to evoke monitors.
Just monitors?
RTX 2070 Super?
Oh, Computer is a great name for a restaurant.
That's not true.
Computer?
the
This is the new style of food.
It's New American that you order on like a McDonald's kiosk.
No, it doesn't need to have anything...
It doesn't need to be computer themed, Rex.
You're getting caught up in the name, man.
It just needs to be simple, elegant,
to the point. Not really to the point,
because again, there's no computers.
But it needs to be...
Kitchen.
Kitchen is good.
And what kind of New American food are we going to be serving at kitchen?
Barrel-aged mustard and ketchup.
On top of a barrel fry.
barrel fry.
And if you like the salad at a normal restaurant, wait till you try our barrel salad, which has
a barrel olive oil.
They put everything in a--it's in a--it's mixed in a barrel.
They bring out a big barrel of oil, and they dunk the fries in it, or the salad, and the
fries.
It's the same barrel.
It would be awesome to cook fries in a barrel.
I agree.
i think that we uh...
that the really big issue with some someone didn't know that the just drops
the barrel
and also spoke to the rest of the are they sharing a hot barrel are you
going to be in pain
there was a
there is a reason
the big brother of the big brother of the
i didn't
say anything actually
the
and say anything
i do what more dangerous restaurants is a place near here that's a
uh... when you know it has a take a call to bar
guys this is an experience
i don't remember what it's called
but it is called
something like scientific sips or some shit like that
and everything that they they serve they make it in big beakers
and they bring it out and it has dry ice foamy whatever flying off
oh i hate that those places
you've never even been to one of these places? yeah you're a liar right now
i went to this one place that's like
like dia de los muertos type thing like very dark a lot of uh skulls very goth uh and they
bring out every every single one of your like every meal and every drink they they bring
it out with like a dried that ice and also like it just it just has a bunch of shit in
it and it's just horrible the food is not good and it's always so far away from where you
live i i don't like i hate how it's always so far away from where i live i've noticed
I'm
sip no no no no worse dude he lights my drink on fire I tried to stop him I said
no no no no no I want to drink that don't light it on fire and burn away all
the drink and he couldn't be reasoned with he lit it on fire that sounds
awesome so it was terrible then I drank it and it was really hot how are you
supposed to drink that with your lips in your throat yeah well it's on fire that
That seems dangerous.
You're supposed to blow the fire out.
Which I wish somebody had told me that.
And then you're supposed to drink it.
Are you?
No, you're not supposed to drink flaming alcohol.
Well what's it gonna do?
You put it in your mouth.
It's gonna dribble down your face.
You never seen that video?
That guy drinking the flaming drink and it catches his whole face on fire?
Wouldn't happen to me.
Maybe not to you.
personally I'm a spiller. My grandma used to say I had no lower lip.
You have the least to lose in a fire. I have the least what? To lose?
Yeah, you have the least to lose in an alcohol drink.
Okay, say what you're about to say in a way that can never be construed as anti-bald.
Go ahead, I double dare you. You don't have excess hair that could be
the
That's your neck. You just have a really tall neck.
That's my neck?
Where do you think your head starts?
You're just saying nonsense now.
Where does your head start?
Your neck ends where your hair begins. That is the end of your neck.
That's not true. Because then there wouldn't be neck beards.
I don't have neck hair.
I have no neck hair.
I think you do.
I don't. I really don't.
Look up. Look up right now. He doesn't.
I mean he shaved it.
No.
No, I don't have to do that.
I have been thinking recently
it would be very nice to get a laser surgery to take off all of the hair on my entire head except my eyebrows.
Including my facial hair.
It would make my life so much easier.
I think that would burn a lot.
They'd knock you out for it.
They would knock me out for it.
I think it hurts after.
Still.
Well you know what's probably even cheaper than that? Spilling flaming alcohol on yourself.
That is true, burning away all my head. But then you have that awful burn skin.
We do have to get you a flaming drink and see you drink it.
I'm not gonna do well with it man.
Well not you, him. Because he's claiming that he's the king of drinking on fire.
He's thrown down the gauntlet. He's thrown down the gauntlet.
I have done this.
Yes he does.
What?
I like cold drinks.
You like what?
Well you need to break out now.
You know what I hate, man?
I hate a hot toddy.
That is a disgusting drink for sick people.
It is. You're supposed to drink it when you're sick.
That's the whole point.
There's no way that whiskey can be good for you when you're sick.
It is!
This is not true.
No, but it is.
How is it good?
Because it...
Because it makes you feel good?
It always does that.
Well it feels like rubbing alcohol when you drink it.
So it's like, you know, it numbs your throat.
What?
What kind of whiskey are you drinking?
All whiskey.
It feels like rubbing alcohol.
What are you talking about?
Did you know, I found this out recently, you know that, that, uh, coproceptic or whatever
that spray that you spray to numb your throat, the throat numbing stuff?
You know you're not supposed to drink that?
Yeah.
You're supposed to spit it out.
It's fine.
I was taking it to the dome, man. I was doing 40 sprays in a row and drinking it.
Yeah, it's just alcohol. It's bad for you.
It tasted amazing. Why do they make it taste good if you're supposed to spit that shit out?
Because otherwise you'd be fucking spraying nasty chemicals in your mouth and you'd be like "pit, pit, pit."
Yeah, that should make you spit it out. It should have the Nintendo Switch cartridge taste.
Mmm.
Have you ever put one of those in your mouth?
No.
Me neither.
I'd like to see you do- really?
Yeah.
I'd like to see you guys do that. Because that is a true-
the
like
and on the switch i'm not aware
well next time you come to my house i want you to taste every game i have
and let me tell you what i've tasted them and india two k sixteen is the worst
tasting game
on planet earth
really that's right
it's really bad dude it's racist that they made that game taste worse i agree
why did they take a so bad
Make the baby games taste bad. Yeah, that's what I was thinking. They should make like Mario and Luigi and Mario Kart taste the worst
It should make Paw Patrol taste bad
Yeah, that way of the adult game should taste good. Honestly. Yeah
Like which one it should taste like sour like these are
Persona 5 they these games should taste like sour candy. You just couldn't let it go right before the hour you had to say it
He did we we did a whole episode without a persona man
It's the only other game that I have that is not a baby game
The other games I have are fucking Mario maker and crash bandicoot someone in the comments said that we should have a an episode
Where it's the persona hour just so you can get it out of yourself of your system
Well, we have to wait here my you don't want to hear my theories man. My theories would blow your mind
What possible theory could you have? Let's let's say
I'll say it dude. Here's my theory. Okay, and
and
It's made by atlas, it's the same game.
People already stole my fucking idea, they got a hold of my notebook somehow, and they
stole my idea.
But whatever.
It's a PS3 game made by atlas.
I don't care who made it man.
Atlas makes Persona, you're stupid.
I'm supposed to know that?
I thought Marvel made Persona.
That would be awesome.
Or DC.
DC yeah, dude, like you you, you know rip off your persona and your Deadpool underneath. I'll say it's badass
that they
Did the that they named the main character Joker?
Yeah in that game. That's impressive. Yes. That's really impressive. I
Cuz it was your wild
Wow, I didn't even put that together. Yeah
What did you think that they call him Joker?
Because it was a cool name and I had it and I imagine there was some meeting somewhere where they were like
Yeah, we we really want to call him Joker. They were like we there's already a very famous
Joker is more famous than this Joker would ever be I don't think
Also, you don't think Joker was famous in 2010, I don't think Joker was famous in 2010 in Japan
Joker has been famous since
and
as
uh...
This is a podcast.
- Yeah.
- You are stifling conversation.
- I want to lie.
I want to lie.
- I need to fill people's heads with nonsense.
- I think when the hour's up, I get to have fun
and prove a fact wrong.
- All right, well, yeah, we can stop
so you can go Google, man.
- I don't wanna Google anymore.
I actually don't wanna Google anymore.
- No, no, no, no, no, go ahead.
Go Google.
I have to go take a shit.
- Yeah, I have to leave.
- No, you can Google.
Rex is on a time crunch.
So now this is your Google time.
You know what? I have a great idea. Why don't you do right now a Googling stream.
See how far that gets you.
[laughter]
A full...
Fucking idiot.
Just Google things for four hours.
Alright, well...
Okay, and I heard his feelings.
Uh, guys...
What do we have to say?
Except thank you for being here for another amazing episode of Beers We Drank.
There will be a live-action Beers We Drank...
Soon.
there will be a live action beers we drink but surely before that is recorded
november seventeenth i'm doing two shows in los angeles at the yard theater
i will make a real put the ticket link
in this thing
level so you can check that out
and uh... that's a really
i'll forget to send the link straight up at least i can happen
i'm saying this it's not gonna happen
uh... but thank you so much for listening a lot every single one of you
and i think it was a mangana and about a good night and i'm not always and i've
been the host forever