You're listening to Patrick's Podcast.
Patrick.
Alright, so, this is...
Wow.
Ooh.
Bless me.
Bless me to high heaven.
This is a solo episode.
So this is just me by myself.
Cameron is busy right now.
He's moving.
He's moving into a dumpster.
He's gonna be living in a little dumpster.
It's gonna be really hard to record with him
'cause with COVID and everything,
he's gonna have to record inside of McDonald's.
to use their Wi-Fi.
But I think the living part, I don't care about that.
I mean if he's living in the dumpster, that's his choice, it's his decision.
Caleb told me that he ate...
He thought he was eating a burger, but it turned out that it was like...
raw or something.
I think he, I think Caleb ate raw hamburger meat and now he's uh, he's throwing up.
He's been throwing up, I guess like, he threw up exactly before we were supposed to start
recording.
It's 3 o'clock right now on Tuesday.
He threw up and said he needs to take a nap for an hour.
He also told me, you know, he said he ate a bad burger last night.
He told me that he drank three bottles of Aldi wine.
So I don't think it's the burger.
I think maybe this guy drank like three bottles of wine.
How do you drink that and fucking do anything the next day?
If you're drinking three bottles of wine, you're in couch lock for the next 24 hours.
That's like, just the amount of sugar and the alcohol in that.
I'm surprised he's not dead.
That would kill me.
No, that wouldn't kill me.
I'd be fine.
I think I could drink more Aldi wine than Caleb.
I could definitely do that.
The other night I drank like... was it like New Year's Eve?
I've been doing dry January.
That's what I've been doing.
I'm going to see if I can do a whole month not drinking.
Which is... since COVID started I've been like...
I don't think there's been like... the longest I've gone being sober is probably like five
days.
I've had at least one beer every day since COVID started.
And that's not good.
It's not a good thing.
But I think this dry January is gonna reset me.
I think I'm gonna get,
I think I'm gonna get telekinesis.
I think that's finally what's gonna happen.
I think finally I'm gonna be able
to move shit around with my mind.
It's probably, probably gonna happen.
Probably really gonna happen.
I'm probably gonna become like Cable from X-Men.
I'm gonna get the techno-organic virus.
I'm gonna sit there, I'm gonna be battling
a demon in my body, a virus with telekinesis.
I'm gonna be battling a demonic techno-virus in my body
with telekinesis.
Man, if I, telekinesis is like the one
Like, it's definitely the best answer, like the answer to the question, like, "Oh, what's
superpower would you..."
No, 'cause flight...
Well, you could levitate yourself with telekinesis.
But flight is probably better.
'Cause the ability to read people's minds is like...
If that's your pick, that's kind of sociopathic, I think.
'Cause it's not even fun.
Like it wouldn't be fun at all.
You would like find out that like some priest is like touching kids or something or like
you would just hear somebody's just like darkest thought at some point and just be like, "Ah
shit, that guy's gonna kill himself when he goes home, huh?"
You know?
But like flight is like, I mean, you'd have to like look out for like birds and shit.
Imagine you get the power of flight, like you get X-Men powers, you get the power of flight
and you like, get attacked by a hawk mid-air.
That would, that would fucking suck.
I couldn't, I couldn't imagine.
Or like some, there's gotta be a bigger bird than a hawk.
Let me look this up.
Let me look up bigger bird.
biggest bird bigger than a hawk?
The ostrich.
Ok, well, that doesn't fucking help me.
I should have fucking looked at biggest bird of prey.
There we go.
Yeah, condor.
The Andean condor.
Well here's the list I guess.
the 10 largest birds of prey from the website rodentpro.com which is a website... let me
look up more stuff on rodent pro. So this is a website for... I guess this is a... where
is their about section? Company info. Contact us. Company info. Company info. Company info.
info. Founded in 1993 in Evansville, Indiana. *Burp* Jesus Christ, I didn't even drink like
soda or anything before this. I'm like gassy as hell. *Burp* There, see, fuckin burpin again.
All I drank before this was water. I don't know why water is making me burp.
So, Rodent Pro was founded in '93 in Evansville, Indiana. It specializes in the production and
and distribution of premium quality animal foods including frozen foods, live food.
So is this a, ok so this is a reptile breeder.
I think, let me, hold on, yeah.
Crickets, mealworms, frozen foods.
Is this a website that you can buy frozen chickens?
Frozen feeder chicks?
Oh.
What animal do you feed a frozen, like, what animal do you feed a chick?
I guess an alligator?
I don't know.
Man, I can't imagine a whole business of- that's the thing, I could never go vegan, I think
my diet is too impulsive.
I think that I eat what's available to me, but anytime I sit down and I think about,
"Oh, I'm killing an animal to eat it."
I could never be the one to kill it.
I know steak tastes good, but like have you ever seen just like a cow in a field there? They look like
They're so majestic. It's like
It does law. I used to there's like a long. There's a farm next to the community college. I went to
And I'd have to bike from to and from
The school because I don't have a license and there's this farm where they had like a shit-ton of like long-haired cows
and
I would just kind of like sometimes I would just like stop the bike and just
look at the cows it's like they look fucking sick dude they look like they
look cool as shit I can't imagine like it made me reconsider eating meat and I
did I went pescetarian for a year but then like I think one day I just wanted
ribs and then I just went and got ribs I was like close enough to like not even
eating fish too.
But what was I talking about?
Oh yeah if you get power of flight.
Imagine you get the power of flight and like you get chased down by a bird.
That would fucking suck.
That would be like the worst.
That'd be the worst fucking thing ever.
Like some, like you're like, "Oh, I'm gonna fly over the Grand Canyon just to see, just
'cause like I'm the only one who can do this right now.
I'm gonna get like a full view of the Grand Canyon without like having to sit in some
stuffy helicopter and some fucking vulture starts circling you, you know?
Like you're just kinda like sitting there.
You're okay, so you have the power of flight right and you can do like the x-men thing where you just kind of like stand
still in midair and you just kind of like
Like, you know how like rogue would put like it's like the energy field under her feet
She's just kind of like levitating like 60 feet above the ground and you're looking at the Grand Canyon and then out of nowhere
just like
two vultures just start circling you because they think that you're a dead body in midair because you're just kind of like
looking at the Grand Canyon being like "Oh, this is so beautiful. This is one of the best
sights I've ever seen." And you just start, your shit starts getting pecked out by vultures.
That would suck. That would seriously, that would suck. I'm still looking at this Rodent
Pro website. Live foods. See, okay, so as I was saying, like what I was saying before
about like oh like I could never like kill an animal. I kill a bug. I don't I don't feel
bad about killing bugs. I think that's a problem. I think it's just because they're so small
like because it's still a living thing you know. Oh you got crickets you can buy a shit
to
of
I mean I could kill a bug. I could definitely kill a bug.
But that's the other thing.
Buying any animal for the express purpose of feeding it to another animal is weird to me.
I don't want to go to the store and get bugs. That's weird.
It's weird to go to the store and get bugs but it's also like,
I
going to make fun of me for this episode.
Like oh, oh, he's, he's gonna, he can't feed, he can't eat meat.
Anyway what was I talking about?
Largest birds of prey.
See the thing about hosting it with two other guys is it's a lot easier to just kind of
rip take jewel hits in the middle of it without it becoming dead air which is
most of this episode right now is me trying to process my thoughts which I'm
already I'm already not good at. Number 10 the Eurasian Eagle Owl. That thing's
Jesus Christ. I think I've been, I think owls scare me. I don't know. No, they look cool.
Owls look cool, kind of. Like if I saw an owl in person I'd be, no I did see an owl
in person before. I was like six. Maybe that's why I'm a little scared of them. It's because
I saw the owl and I thought it was going to attack me. Hmm. Well anyway, this owl, if I
fucking, if I saw this fucking owl in person and I had a gun, I would at least fire off
a warning shot.
Somebody texted me in the middle of that.
I, see, this is what, you can't do a podcast like the one that we do with one guy.
I'm learning that, this is the, I'm learning this the hard way.
Because I have to have my full attention on the podcast and I can't get distracted by
anything.
Fuck, maybe I should have taken an Adderall before doing this.
I don't have any Adderall.
If I did though, I'd probably be quiet for the whole thing.
Just sitting here reading about this Eurasian Eagle Owl.
It's up to, it's like a nine pound owl with a two, Jesus Christ.
Six and a half foot wingspan.
What the fuck?
That thing's fucking terrifying.
I mean, it's eyes too.
Like if you, like staring an owl in the eyes.
Fuck.
That's terrifying.
I should have called someone.
I should have, I should have, I should have called somebody up and asked them if they
could record this with me.
Number nine, the Marshall Eagle.
Africa's largest eagle with an eight foot wingspan.
I'm
I had a bad dream about a bird when I was like six because of Wind Waker.
I thought that the bird from Wind Waker was going to capture my brother.
And I was always like scared of giant birds after that.
Maybe that happened around the same time that the fucking owls came to school.
This is, this is one of the most insane things they've ever made me do.
I'm sitting, I'm realizing I'm in my room by myself.
I'm talking about a bad dream I had when I was six into a microphone and laughing to myself.
This is going to be the thing that you're going to, next week if I actually do send
this to Cameron and Caleb.
Like in two weeks from now they'll just be like, "Yeah, we, um, you know, Pat's been,
Pat's kind of been going through something right now."
I'm just gonna be in a mental hospital, in a padded room by myself, just like, "I had
a bad dream when I was six.
I had a bad dream when I was six."
*laughs*
Yeah dude, birds are
fucking scary.
*laughs*
Number 8, the
Philippine Eagle.
I'm guessing
this bird is from the Philippines.
Yeah.
This one kind of looks like this one's got like a middle part. I mean it's kind of cool-looking. I
Mean it's got like a
This is the worst fucking episode ever maybe
Maybe I should stop no, I'm gonna keep going you know what they said I couldn't do it
so
I'm getting that message
It's adopt... is it...
This bird of prey has adapted to hunted forested habitats and is incredibly
agile even though it weighs 15 pounds...
Fuck! That's a heavy bird! Jesus Christ!
The raptor is known to feed on... This fucking bird eats monkeys and like lemurs
and... pigs and dogs?
What the fuck? I gotta see a video of this thing. Hold on.
Let me look this thing up. Philippine Eagle video.
Oh, it's endangered.
Soaring Philippine Eagle.
Yeah, because I mean, I'm looking at this thing right now.
And it's like,
If I had the power of flight and I had to like deal with one of these things trying to like
attack me, I'd piss and shit myself right there.
Like I, that's fucked up.
That thing's fucked up.
God.
Philippine Eagle feeding.
Maybe look that up.
Philippine Eagle eating monkey.
Oh no.
Oh dude. Oh my god the claws dude. Look at that. Look at that thing's fucking claws.
That thing's nuts. Oh the monkey's just eaten an apple dude or whatever the fuck that is. He's eaten something.
How okay if you're the wildlife filmer and
You're like you're the guy like filming like wildlife shit you
Wouldn't you want to just like?
Just like have a gun on you just it's like oh this monkey's so cute
But this eagles about to eat it just like fire a warning shot at the eagle, right?
Like cuz if I I would want to print if I saw a monkey about to get attacked by a bird I'd be like
Fuck out of here bird
You piece of shit
You know, I I'm not letting a bird attack a monkey I
Don't care if it's a bird of prey or circle like oh wait, they fucking green screen that yeah
Wait is this not real? Is this video not real?
Oh no, no it
It has the baby monkey in its claws. Oh
You prick you prick bird
You are you are the worst
God I would if I was the wildlife filmer
And I saw that bird
Grab a baby monkey by its claws.
I would keep
Like a I would keep like a 44 Magnum with a scope on it in my pocket
And I would I would fire just just clip its wing. You know, I don't care that it's endangered
You're not eating a baby monkey. Not while I'm there
Not while I'm watching this fucking thing
That baby monkey I look maybe maybe it's an asshole. I don't know I don't know
But that's not right
Carrot about the circle life, I don't care about
Nature
Even though in this hypothetical situation I am a
Wildlife filmer and I'm it's my job to care about nature and know how to not disturb
The animals I'm fucking I'm firing off around at that goddamn bird, you know, you're
You you stupid bird you prick bird
Man a bird that eats monkeys
That's just that's disgusting that's fucked up to me and dogs
I gotta look up. Oh, this isn't even the right bird. This is a harpy eagle
What what's a harpy eagle
South America, oh I watched the wrong. Well, I mean I still saw a bird cat eat a monkey
None of you saw that because this is an audio
This is an audio based pod- I'm watching another video of it.
Oh wow, they put their own watermark before.
What?
The fuck is this?
Okay, this is just somebody giving out information about the Philippine Eagle.
I thought it was gonna be...
a video of a monkey getting eaten by an eagle.
Number seven, Stellar Sea Eagle.
Found in Russia and Japan, the Stellar Sea Eagle is the heaviest eagle in the world,
weighing 19 pounds with a wingspan of 2.5 meters.
This bird primarily feeds on fish, but is known to attack other large birds and baby
seals. Also I didn't know that like birds of prey were called raptors. I thought that
raptors were dinosaurs. But... Well if they're called raptors right then how the fuck did
it take us this long to be like... Yeah actually like dinosaurs looked more like chickens than
they do. Or T-Rexes looked more like chickens than they did like a reptile. Like who... Cameron
Cameron probably knows this. If Cameron was here I could ask him. God, I miss Cameron and Caleb so much.
COVID is doing a number on my mental health.
I'm here talking by myself.
About birds.
Oh boy. Alright, I give up. I can't do this anymore.
[laughs]
I've officially lost my mind.
If you got this far into the episode, what the f- what is fucking wrong with you?
But thank you, please subscribe to our Patreon.
I guess.
Watch us on Twitch, check out our Teespring, check out...
We don't even plug. I'm just I'm looking for things to say we never plug anything really
which is probably a
Shortcoming of ours is that we don't plug anything
Who knows who knows if that's even good or bad, maybe you like that we don't plug our stuff I
Mean I would I I don't like it when people plug anything you know
Anyway
Huh.
Alright.
[laughs]
[LAUGHTER]