(upbeat music)
- All right.
Well, Julio's not here today.
We kind of went at that with different ways.
So yeah, hey everybody.
Mommy's gone, so we're changing it up.
We're doing a little D&D session
with Caleb and Patrick,
and not Juvio at all.
- No, okay, right off the bat,
it's Caleb versus Patrick, is it not?
- Yes, it is, 'cause it's Spy versus Spy.
So-- - Do they have a theme song?
- I don't think-- - Yeah, Spy versus Spy.
- Yeah, there's a theme song. - They're a comic.
They're a comic, then they were--
- Somebody never watched Mad TV.
- I never, I didn't, did they have--
- I watched Mad TV. - I watched Mad TV.
I don't remember Spy versus Spy,
like interstitial cartoons, they have that?
Yep, I guess I didn't watch mad TV that close. Oh, that was like season one though. They got rid of that pretty early
Yeah, I'm lucky you yeah, that's probably why I didn't get to why you saying fuck me cuz it's me versus you man
Oh, yeah, that's true. Fuck. They all they did make a spy verse by video game -
Sounds good was it? Yeah guys on PlayStation 1 right? Is it the guys my station - and dango?
I don't think so. It might have been what it kills that that's
Oh, it's gonna drive me crazy. It's a Tim Schafer, right?
- It's Tim Schafer? - Tim Schafer, yeah.
Yeah. All right.
I'm gonna pull up the first map.
So, the way it's gonna work is I'm gonna give you guys
three random items that you're gonna roll to see what you get.
And then you're gonna try to use those items to kill each other
in each of the areas. And then each time it...
And we're gonna do best out of three
or best out of five, really, depending on
sort of how long it ends up taking for you guys to kill each other.
There's other people involved, there's other little things that can happen.
But we're gonna start...
- over here. - Do they have, like, voices that they do?
No, they're, like, silent. They're completely silent.
Oh, that's actually...
- Thank God. - Salute.
Are you setting up any kind of story?
I mean, did we ever find out through the comic
why the spy and the spy do not care for each other besides...
It's like a race thing, right?
I don't think it's a race thing.
I would hope not.
Should I not say that?
Maybe.
I don't know if we could get sued for that.
I think you're going to get in trouble.
I don't know if we're going to get sued for that.
Maybe we should think of something to call them
Agent vs. Spy.
White vs.
No.
I don't think White vs. Black is going to work.
No, but they're white and black, man. This is tough.
Oh, yeah.
Let's just go... I liked your typo that you made when we were setting this up.
Brown versus black.
You said soy versus spy.
Oh, yeah. I was by accident.
I like soy versus spy.
Okay, cool.
So, who's soy?
I guess that's different enough.
Who's soy?
The white one is soy.
Right. All right. So, Pat's soy and you're spy.
And I'm spy.
Okay, cool.
Okay.
And begin.
So, as far as set up and story,
it's just that you guys are living inside
of a spy versus, a spy versus spy comic.
And the various scenarios that happen,
you're always trying to get at each other.
That's your set up and story.
And we're gonna start with rolling for initiative
to see who goes first.
We're starting in like a medieval, little medieval square.
We're gonna start very D and D E
and then we're gonna veer off from there.
So, both of you guys roll your initiatives.
So I 16th. You've got character sheets and everything. Okay, cool.
Okay, well, I got a 16 and those character sheets are in one. I know
where they are. You know where they are. We were doing this for a
while. Where's the character sheets? Found it. Alright, that's
a point. That's not a no. No, I found it. Well, where are they?
Spies up. Oh, don't give him a hint.
Okay.
Well, no, I got it.
Then we, because then we can't.
He has to give me a hint because yeah, then we can't do anything.
I have to give you a hint. I can't tell you where it is.
Well, I just fired.
Okay.
And I got a three.
Don't fire.
Okay.
Okay. I rolled 11 on initiative.
Okay. So Pat.
Wait, mine says that I'm the black spy.
No, you're the white spy.
No, you can click on white spy.
I don't I don't see it on my screen.
I could be white spy. You want to switch?
I guess we have to switch.
No, no, I don't want to switch because then I'm soy.
Go to the newspaper.
I don't I don't have I don't have white spy on my screen.
Did I give you the wrong one then?
You gave me black spy.
So you're soy Caleb.
That's my bad.
I have both.
Oh, okay.
I will give you black spy Pat.
I mean white spy.
Sorry, I'll fix that.
Sorry, but I'm going to need your kill.
Now I don't want it.
No, you're going to have to have it.
I mean, you have to refresh your browser and everything.
Just not yet. Don't do it yet.
Oh, man.
And Caleb, I'm revoking your...
This is too much trouble.
Your soy spice. No, it's too much trouble for me.
You just have...
Too much trouble.
I think we got to just...
We got to reset.
The whole episode.
No, we already had the whole lore.
We did a whole lore background.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, you guys remember.
All right. Refresh your screen.
Okay, I just found it.
This is the white spy role initiative,
motherfucker.
Okay.
Oh, oh, the first point goes to
Caleb's awesome black spy.
Wait, wait.
I know I rolled and it didn't do anything.
No, no, you rolled a six.
No, no, because it still it says
I'm okay.
Hold on.
Let me fix it.
Now.
The whole world saw this.
He's already trying to cheat.
No, no, hold on.
Hold on.
It's confusing now because it said that I was a black spy, but now I'm a white spy.
You already rolled initiative, man.
All right, you got to say it.
No, because that's under you.
All right, both of you re-roll.
Oh my God.
It made no sense.
I thought that you kept rolling.
I fucked it up.
Caleb, I fucked it up.
I'm sorry.
This is already going amazing.
All right, we have not done roll 20 in a while.
I have not done roll 20 in a while.
I got a 10.
I got a 20.
Caleb and white spy.
Here, let me change it to...
Here, let me change it to Black Spy.
Maybe that should be...
Caleb vs White Spy.
Okay, I'm fine with my guy being named Caleb.
He's gotta be victorious.
Yeah, Caleb vs White Spy.
Okay, cool. White Spy does go first, though.
Okay, so now what I need you to do, White Spy,
is roll that d20 three times.
Okay.
And then I will message you on Discord
What items you received?
I got a 12.
Three times.
Roll it three times.
Oh, you rolled a 2, a 5, and a 5. Okay.
Yeah.
Okay, yeah, no, no, no. That's what I want.
Oh, you got two 2s? Okay.
Two 5s.
Oh, two 5s. Okay.
One 2 and two 5s.
All right.
You said "ooh," so that means it's good.
That means 2 is a good item, which I don't like.
Okay, cool. You're gonna get some cool stuff and then, oh boy.
Please tell me some bomb, bro. It's like the one way these fuckers die is with a bomb.
Yeah.
Where are you sending me? Where are you sending the...
Where am I sending you?
On Discord?
Sending you on Discord, yeah.
Okay.
Check this out, guys. I'm fucking his... I'm fucking him.
Don't fuck me.
We're not even supposed to be near each other right now.
Stop fucking my character.
Don't get inside of me.
I'm out of you.
I'm inside of you.
Okay, I got good stuff.
He got good stuff?
I'm going back to my corner.
Okay.
I'm over here.
I'm next to this guy now.
All right, Caleb, now you roll 3d20s.
Okay, here I go.
A 17, an 8, and a 2.
Oh, looks like we both got a 2.
Okay.
So whatever you got, I got 2.
Alright.
Oh, but now he knows what I have.
Fuck.
Yep.
He's cheating already.
He already cheated once.
Damn, I got bad rolls.
This is not good.
Those are good items.
You're wrong.
Wait, so did Caleb get shit items?
No, he got a good item.
What'd you say?
Was it 18?
Right?
Yeah, there it is.
Okay.
No, he got a good item. What did you say? It was an 18, right? Yeah, there it is. Okay. 17, I mean. Okay.
17, an 8, and a 2. Oh, yeah. I like 17.
All right, and then...
an 8.
Oh, okay. All right. Yeah, I'm gonna win. You might win. You've only got two items.
You also have your rogue your your I put you guys in here as rogue. So you also have just the ability to like
Do basic attacks
Consider any like the rapiers or any of that shit. That's just like
Come on, man. If I have a question if I have a
Equipment item am I just wearing it by default or do I need to use it?
Oh
Yeah, you're wearing it by the fall.
Is it passive?
I know what you're asking about.
Yes.
Anyway, also, this, sorry, I haven't used Zencaster in like five years.
I'm not seeing my fucking audio thing go up and down.
Should I see that on my end?
We hear you.
You're fine.
You guys hear me?
Alright, I'm terrified.
You're fine.
Okay, cool.
Alright, so you're up now, Soy.
Soy versus Caleb.
So you can go, you can see here that you have a 30 feet of movement.
And yeah, Caleb, take off your headphones.
Because we're, I want you to know exactly until you guys are in eyesight of each other.
Until you guys are in eyesight of each other.
So, so, so I, you can see here there's like a stand where people are, there's like a market.
There's a few other places you can go.
What do you want to do?
What are you thinking?
Um, do I know where he is?
Uh, you know vaguely.
Like, am I tracking him down?
Okay.
Yeah, you know vaguely.
Then I'm gonna, I'm gonna go, well what's this turtle here?
Oh, that's a frog.
You see that?
Oh, that's a frog?
Yeah.
I saw a dim, purple.
I guess I have to go and talk to this frog, huh?
You don't have to.
Okay.
All right, well then I'm gonna climb up to this roof.
Okay, which roof?
I put my guy there.
Okay, that's crazy.
So that's, let's count how many feet that is.
Okay, I put it there then.
Okay, so roll an athletics check also.
It might not be bad, oh, he can't hear me,
I just realized.
Yeah.
I just don't want him to freak out.
16.
Okay, that's fine, yeah,
you climbed that roof pretty easily.
Yeah, okay, and you have a full view of everything.
All right, what do you wanna do now?
So I can see him?
If I have a full view?
You can see him.
Okay.
Then I am going to,
do I have a disguise kit?
No, you don't.
Okay.
Then I am gonna jump to this building.
Okay, roll another athletics check or acrobatics check.
Acrobatics?
Either one is fine.
Okay.
18.
Nice, okay, cool.
Are you doing a fucking back flip?
That's kind of your movement.
As you jump over, you do hear a dog bark below you,
by the way, and--
I'm 18.
Yeah, no, you just hear a dog bark below you.
You didn't do it stealth.
All right.
You're fine.
Well, now I'm crouched.
Give me a thumbs up-- Okay, cool.
When I can put my headphones back on.
All right, are we thumbs, are you good?
Are you, what are you gonna do?
You got anything else you wanna do for now, Pat?
Anything you wanna do?
I'm gonna go prone.
Okay, go prone.
All right, cool.
All right, it'll be Caleb's turn then, Caleb.
That is so fucking stressful.
Yeah.
That really stressed me out.
He did some pretty crazy stuff.
What did he do?
You'll find out.
I can't tell you, yeah.
So now what, is it my turn?
Yes, what I will tell you is that you can see
white figure up atop a building across the market. I do see him. But you can't see him
as well as you were before. It looks like you could see him for a moment and then he
kind of like fell a little bit out of sight. Okay. Hmm. Is it my turn? Oh yeah. All right,
Take your headphones off, Pat.
Okay, here's what I'm thinking.
Okay.
I think that I'm going to hold out my giant magnet.
It's one of the items I bought.
Yes.
A powerful magnet that can attract metal objects from a distance.
And I think that I... What's my movement speed?
So, 30. Just typical shit.
Okay, I think I'm going to move...
Just typical shit.
Basically 30 feet in his direction with my stealth shoes on.
Okay, cool.
And to see if maybe I attract something with my beautiful magnet.
Nice, yeah.
I would say that if you want to, because he, he, you don't know, but like, I would say
that like he could probably see you from up there.
And like, so I just wanted to let you know that that's probably true.
So and like you would, you would know that.
So if you're going to move forward, like he'll know that that's happening.
That means he's doing something, he said something you can't do.
Okay, so I have moved 30 feet.
Do I attract anything with my magnet?
Yes, you do.
So this woman in front of you, she's got a jewelry stand and
some of her jewels just start like flying off and onto your
magnet.
And she's like, hey, what are you doing young man?
Young Caleb.
Do I have any money?
I just heard Pat just say, hey.
You have 70 gold pieces.
All right.
How much is it going to cost to buy all this jewelry off of
you?
About 55 gold pieces.
Yeah, here, take 'em. I don't need this shit.
You don't need the shit, the gold?
No, no, no.
Oh, good.
I like bling, bitch.
Is he still moving?
Ugh, okay.
Okay, I'm sorry. I didn't mean... I'm just a negotiating tactic, okay? I didn't mean to say...
I'm not like that.
Okay, she's walking over here. She's going to accept the money. Okay.
Okay.
Cool.
So now I have 15.
Yeah, okay. And you got a bunch of jewelry too. So stuff you can maybe do with that.
She's going to go back.
Yeah.
So that's what you've attracted so far. That's just, you can use that magnet,
like throughout. There are other things you'll be able to attract as you move through.
Okay. Can I hear, oh, here's what I'm going to do. Can I put on all the jewelry and then also
put on the magnet as if it is a piece of jewelry, like around my neck, maybe like a chain.
Sure.
So that it's maybe a little more.
Maybe Patrick doesn't know what's going on when he looks at me.
I like that.
Let's do that with I'm trying to think of what you can do for that.
Let's do that with a
let's do a charisma check on that charisma check.
OK, yeah, it's considered that like it'd be maybe like a.
Yeah, it's a charisma check.
I kind of like that.
And I put my headphones on at 20.
Oh, OK. I like that.
All right.
He will not be able to tell that your magnet is an actual magnet.
that bullshit. Okay. All right. Perfect. All right. Okay, cool.
We'll end your turn. Um, wait, let me see. Sorry. Yeah, there's
nothing really. Oh, can I? Oh, can I hide the explosive canary
figure in this jewelry stand? Ooh, you can do that your next
turn because you I should have said this up front. I'll say
this to Pat, like one item use per turn. Okay. All right. But
okay, that's a bad idea. All right, Pat, you're ready to go.
And he's looking at his phone.
He's looking at his phone.
So he doesn't know.
He can't know.
Alright, cool man.
What happened?
No, he can't tell you.
We're not allowed to tell you, asshole.
Okay.
Piece of shit.
Now what?
You gotta take off your headphones, you goofball.
Oh, okay.
Oh, it's just that?
I just rolled a stealth check and I got a 27.
Yeah, cause you're gonna hide from me, you fucking piece of shit.
Take 'em off.
Alright.
Okay, so he's...
Can I see him?
Yeah, you can.
I'm gonna go to the other side.
it.
Take them off. All right.
Okay. So he's... Can I see him right now?
You can't really see him now, but he's like kind of in the mix of the market. But with
that 27 stealth check, he's not going to really be able to see you. What are you... Are you
hiding behind like a chimney? Like what's your plan?
Well, yeah. I'm prone behind a chimney and you can see my arms and legs out the back.
But because I rolled a 27, all he thinks that is, is like a piece of cloth that flew into
the air or something.
Yeah, I like that as a hide action that you did.
Okay, cool.
So what I'm going to do now is maybe I'm going to crawl across the top of the building.
Oh wait, look right here.
There's these like little...
Little goblins.
These are...
Well, no, no, the string here, that's clothed wire?
Clothing. Yes, that is clothing wire.
That's what is it?
It's not called clothing wire.
What's the word for that?
It's like a laundry thing.
Clothesline. Clothesline.
Yeah.
I'm going to zip line across the clothesline.
OK, before you do that.
With the with my hat.
Before you do that.
With my fedora.
I'm going to I'm going to hide that area.
I'm going to hide the area around you.
So don't be alarmed.
Julio won't be able to see it either.
Okay. What does that mean?
Whoa, you'll see.
And so I'm going to just, I'm going to reveal.
The area here, because you got that 27 on stealth, and so I don't want Caleb to be able to see it.
Whoa.
So Caleb, don't my God.
So, so he's not going to see it.
And so you're, I guess we tell, should we tell him in the chat?
I moved you over to where you wanted to go, by the way.
Okay, we'll tell him in a second.
So you're now hidden over there with that 27 stealth.
There's no way he's going to be able to find you right now.
So that's kind of where I can leave you at.
What did you want to do?
Well, I got to see what the building is.
I was going to go down the chimney and then sneak in and then get a
disguise from whoever's home.
It was for sure.
This home belongs to an adventurer who often will leave town to go
out and fight off goblins. He's right now dealing with them. They followed him back to his home
in the front yard here. But you can climb, you can go into his home right now. Nobody's there.
So, oh, no one's there? Oh, shit. Yeah, then I'm going in there and I'm putting on his tuxedo.
This adventurous tuxedo.
Yeah, I mean, I'm putting on his tuxedo.
I'm glad you mentioned that.
Maybe I just take my no 'cause I need the hat, but I mean, does what he can. Caleb recognize me from
my hat or is it like clothes? Does he not? And if I'm not, if I don't look exactly like white spy,
if you if you roll, let's have you roll a charisma to like putting on this disguise.
I wish I had a we. Yeah, I'll tell you about this later, but yeah,
Just roll charisma. Let's see how you do.
23.
Okay.
Wow, a crit also.
What the fuck?
I don't know what's happening, but my rolls are completely boss.
Yeah, you don't have auto crit on because you got a 13 on animal,
which I don't know why he rolled animal handling, but...
I said I pet an animal on the roof.
I didn't even hear you say that.
Okay, cool.
So you are now...
This is going to be crazy.
You're now perfectly disguised as a...
As a butler.
As a butler adventurer.
- And yeah, are you gonna leave the house?
All right, your movement's kind of up, I think, actually.
- Yeah, I'm gonna leave the house as--
- As a butler.
So we're just gonna have you over here.
Here's what I'm gonna do.
- I'm walking around, what's the word for this thing
with the clamshell on top of it?
- Oh, God.
I don't know what you're talking about.
- Butler's food thing.
- What is that called?
It starts with a C.
I have no idea, but here's what we're gonna do.
I'm going to put in here a different icon
and I will move him for you for now.
And we'll see if Caleb probably won't notice
that it's a different guy.
So just give me one second while I pull out an icon.
- What is that thing called that butlers hold?
- I don't know what a butler clam thing is.
We'll ask, we'll ask Caleb.
He'll get, he'll hopefully he won't use that as a hint.
Um, oh, then, then we won't ask him at all.
Okay, fine.
Sorry.
Roll 20 is taking about three and a half years to load.
Um, I mean, we can chop this up.
Yeah, I got you.
I'm just going to actually just copy and paste a guy and then put them over
there and that'll be the guy.
Okay.
All right.
and put him over here.
And then I'm gonna take out your character for now.
We'll put him back another time.
And you'll be this character who is here once I reveal.
And I'm gonna give Caleb a thumbs up.
- I'm watching a video right now on how to be a butler.
- Okay.
That sounds good.
- Is it a carrying tray?
- Yay!
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.
I'm back guys.
Okay.
Yes you are.
Huh?
I said yes you are.
I am.
Alright.
Okay, hold on.
This should work soon.
Please tell me I'm not about to fucking die, bro.
You're not gonna about to fucking die.
I'm trying to just get the fucking...
Roll 20 is the worst fucking thing in the world.
Where is this white cracker?
Where did you go?
Hold on.
I don't know.
You know, where did you go?
I don't know where I went.
There's a completely black part of the screen.
I leave for one second.
I'm trying to unblack it.
It's actually, no, go back, go back, stop it.
Whatever, bitch.
Don't call me that.
Okay.
I'm a nice guy.
Dad.
That's fine.
There we go.
Cool.
All right.
So, you're up now, Caleb.
I still don't see him.
OK, Pat, I got to take my headphones.
Get the fuck out of here.
In the meantime, I'm going to learn.
So here's what I'll tell you what you saw, at least, Caleb.
You saw that white spy kind of disappear even further away.
And you didn't know where he went.
And now he's kind of gone.
Does he look at my
Does he...
Here's also... Actually, I will have you do those, sorry.
Roll a...
Roll Wisdom Saving Throw. I think that's fair.
Twelve. Okay.
I should have really just had you roll Perception, but it's about the same thing anyway.
Okay, cool.
You notice something is a bit off in the town.
There's like...
It feels like with the spies,
feels like he's not he's gone, but he's not gone.
I can tell you that he's around here somewhere.
Is he made out of metal or does he like birds?
I can't answer the second one.
The first one, I don't think so, though.
OK, I'm going to wait.
Can I is it would you allow me to roll a performance check to see if I could
throw my canary figurine in a way that is convincingly a real bird?
Yeah, of course. Well, yeah, do that. That's going to be,
that's actually more like a sleight of... Is that sleight of hand?
Or what? I mean, let's see. Yes, it's sleight of hand. It is.
Yeah, is it? Okay.
It is.
I'll do that. I'll do that. I think that makes more sense to me. It's like more of a dexterity thing.
Okay. Okay, then I... And should I move now or can I move after?
You can do either. Here, I'm gonna throw this first. 16. Is that convincing enough?
Yeah, it's very nice. It looks very much like it could be a canary.
At least for a short period of time, I would say that that is believably a canary.
Okay, and I'd like to throw it generally in the direction of that frog.
Okay. Okay, and now I'm going to walk again,
magnet on my neck, walk another 30 feet over here.
Okay. Oh, yeah. So, yeah, you start to pull in a couple of pots and pans out of one of a...
more of a general goods tent, and people are a little bit annoyed at you, but nothing else so
far. Okay. I throw him a couple more dollars.
Okay, cool. Yeah, you're fine there.
That's not you using your magnet, I would say.
You kind of used your canary, yeah.
So, okay, so the canary is flying in the general direction of that frog.
Is that what you're saying?
Yeah.
Are you targeting it for the frog or...?
Just kind of...
Honestly, I'm trying to see if I can bait out some kind of utility from him
as he maybe is going to try to shoot this canary and have it explode or something.
Cool.
The frog will with his gun.
Yeah, or at least maybe he'll make some noise while he's shooting something.
All right. That's it for me.
All right, cool.
Pat, you can't hear us, I'm a dummy.
Come on, man. There we go.
His headphones are off.
Mm hmm. Mm hmm.
It's called a cloche.
OK, so now we don't know what him.
So he's over there now.
Yeah. In front of you getting further away from me.
Well, I'm still I'm like outside of this person's house now.
Roll a perception check.
OK.
Oh, I'm not seeing shit.
I got to know.
No, nothing's nothing.
So, OK, I'm you got.
Yeah, you go outside the house.
You hear this adventurer go, stay away, goblins.
Stay away.
And I go, we're going to eat you.
OK, cool. I ignore him.
So I let him I let him die.
Yeah. OK.
So he goes over there to die.
And now what do you want to do?
I guess I'm going to.
Where's my because it used to be able
to see to be able to draw the thing
while he's gone, while he's gone,
while he's going pee pee, got it, got it.
I guess it's tell me where you want to go.
Where I'm going to go talk to Sullivan.
OK, cool.
Have him in the fucking thing.
I see the frog.
OK, cool.
I'm going to go walk over to Sullivan
and see what happens when I interact with him.
I'm going to try to read his lips.
Cool.
I'm bam, bam, bam, bam, bam, bam, bam.
Pat, take off your headphones.
Caleb.
Yes, he just he you just saw him walk over to the frog.
Oh, shit.
Fuck.
Did he see my I guess I don't I can't.
You can't answer if you saw the bird or not.
Mm-mm.
I was letting you know that happened.
He rolled a two on perception.
Well, all right then.
What can I do here?
So it says when activated, it explodes.
So unless you've, I'm gonna say that
the way we're doing this is like it has to be activated
after you put it in bird mode.
Yeah, I didn't know what, if it was,
I didn't know if it was,
Yeah, I mean, I just like...
Like he activates it or if I activate it.
These are not bespoke items created by me,
so we're playing on the fly here a little bit.
Okay, so I can now activate the bird.
That's what I'll say, yes.
I am going to activate my bird now.
Okay, your bird has been activated.
Pat, get Pat to put his headphones on.
Keep yours on, Caleb.
Okay.
Oh, you're done.
You're fucking done.
You walk over to say hi to the frog.
He goes, "Hi, I'm Sullivan."
And then, Pat, a bird explodes in your face that was flying around Sullivan's head.
I am shocked that that happened.
You got baited.
You got baited by Sullivan the frog.
That was a pretty good move.
So you're going to take, because I believe it's 1d8.
Okay, cool.
No!
Take one damage?
Yeah, Sullivan is cooked. He's dead.
Sullivan's dead?
Alright, at least we got that out of the way.
I'll say at least Sullivan's dead.
He said, "Hi, I'm Sullivan the Frog."
At this rate, this is going to be one map.
Yeah, I think so.
So, Sullivan is dead.
When you get burned...
My disguise is gone?
Yeah, yeah, your disguise is gone.
Oh, so you were wearing a disguise.
I was disguised as the adventurer's butler.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Okay. You missed a whole... Wait, what can you tell? You can tell Caleb now too what
it's called.
Um... What was it called? Oh, the thing that... The thing that waiters hold. The dome.
Oh, yes.
On top of the plate. It is called a cloche.
Well...
We wanted to ask you.
Thank you, enemy.
But we couldn't ask you.
You thought I would know that?
Uh, I don't know what... Your wife has like shit like that laying around the house.
You think I have a cloche in my house?
That is...
Tell me that...
There is no way that that is too far off from the shit that you have in your apartment.
Yeah, sorry. That is not too far off, man.
Whatever, man.
Cool. There ain't no fucking way
that you're acting like that's not a thing.
Here's a little news for the fans of Things in My House.
Today we got rid of the...
We finally got rid of the bust of
Michelangelo's David that we had.
You never had that.
Yep. We sold that for $20
market. So you had that. I didn't know that. Yep. So you guys see each other now.
Uh huh. Uh Pat, you got hurt. It is now your turn Caleb. You see him now. He's
on fire next to the alchemist who had a frog that is now dead. He's like my frog.
He's very upset. But hmm. Okay, remember you guys. Take your headphones off. You
You do have straight up violence still.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What, bitch?
What?
Can I do something right now or was that?
Oh, you know what?
That's kind of a good point.
You got hurt, but I guess there's more stuff to do.
Yeah, fuck off. One second, Caleb.
So you got blown up by a bird.
Yeah, so I'm just gonna throw my caltrops on the ground.
Okay, nice.
Six, I'm wanting more.
Y'all seeing this video?
Yeah, it's pretty good.
What's that?
Oh, he was the... it's the... that guy made the video that's like the Eurodance song.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah. And then everyone's mad at him because he changed the women.
Yeah, which I thought was actually a good idea. It's pretty funny. I think it's pretty...
I don't think he was trying to be funny, but I like that. So, yeah, you could throw those
rolls sleight of hand on that to see if you can kind of disperse them in a neat way.
16.
Nice, very nice.
OK, cool.
Not going to be the easiest thing for him to pick up in the world.
So yeah, that's kind of your turn at this point then.
OK.
You've got three of those, you know.
So take those off.
Take off those cans.
And Caleb, you'll put your cans on.
I'm coming back.
Hold on.
He's coming back.
All right.
Had to put down my kombucha.
Yeah.
I watched him like get kind of like burned up and then he kind of flailed around a bit.
That's about it.
Okay, well, he rolled a sleight of hand and he got a 16.
I guess I'm making a whisper roll for those but it's actually almost more fun that you
guys can see but you don't know what it's for.
Yeah, it's kind of a nice clue.
Okay, Pat.
Oh, Pat doesn't have his headphones on.
Okay.
I think...
Hmm.
Can I throw my magnet at him
to see if I could take off any metal that is on his body?
Yeah, of course you can.
OK, I'm going to do that.
OK, that's pretty funny.
So you roll a ranged...
Generally at his face, I guess.
Yeah, roll a ranged attack with the magnet then.
So just D20 plus your dex.
Okay, I'm going to roll a D20.
Yeah, we're not going to add your...
10 and my dexterity is 5, so 15.
Add your proficiency,
because you're going to probably be proficient at throwing stuff.
So nice.
Oh, sorry, my bonus is 3.
My bonus is 3.
Okay, so it's 5 total, still 15.
And then I think, what's his AC?
I think you're both, your ACs are the same.
They're pretty, like 13, I think.
Yeah, I see.
13.
Oh, yeah, because it's just dex.
OK, cool.
All right.
So roll 1d6 now for damage, because you definitely just hurt him.
Oh, yeah.
3.
All right, cool.
All right.
You see the magnet hit him in the face.
Kerplunk.
Yes.
And you notice it kind of react to pulling something,
but you don't know what yet.
Well, but it's super strong.
It should be attached to this thing by now.
It pulled something up and attached to it.
Okay, but I can't see what it was.
You can kind of tell, but it's like little glints of metal, little spiky glints of metal.
I can prompt you to see that.
Okay, I still have my movement, yeah?
Yeah, you do.
Can I move closer to try to get some idea of what it is?
Yeah, for sure.
I'm showing you some of the movement options you have there.
Hold on.
Go for it.
Okay, I'm gonna walk over.
Mm-hmm. Cut through the market.
I'm about five feet away from him.
Alright. Maybe.
And, can I see it now?
Uh, you sure can, but you also...
SHIT!
Pat, put your headphones on.
Caleb, keep yours on.
What happened?
Here's what happened. Caleb, um,
you were just sort of, uh, you dropped your caltrips
caltrops on the ground.
Caleb threw a giant magnet at your head.
And you took three damage from that giant magnet hitting you in the skull and your caltrops
you had remaining on your person got taken up by the magnet, which is now, I guess, just
lying on the ground next to you.
Caleb went over to get a closer look at what happened, though, and he stepped on the caltrops
you already put down.
Well, well, hold the phone there, Patches.
No.
as the magnet is thrown, these caltrops are not made out of metal? They wouldn't be attracted
to the magnet mid-air? No. Oh, it seems I've stuck you with something sticky, my friend.
I don't think so. You're sticky now.
I'm sticky. You made him sticky.
I think, I think... You made him a sticky.
I was clearing a path. I was clearing a path of all metal.
I think... Well, how did you know there was metal?
I did. I was guessing.
Did you did you put your headphones?
No, no, no.
To your feet so that you could hear.
No, I literally threw a magnet.
He is he has been doing stuff with the magnet for the last few turds.
He did not. OK.
He's been trying to figure out what's metal here.
I get what you're saying. I'm open.
That is I am fully being logical and you are aiding and abetting a spy.
I am. I'm eating and betting a soy is what I'm doing.
So yeah, all right.
That's fair.
I guess you're kind of right.
It's a super magnet we establish.
I can just pull shit.
So instead of this is not going to be fun.
So instead, Pat, you're going to take six damage
because that magnet is going to fly in the air, pick up the caltrop
and then whack you in the face with them.
The caltrop to put down.
Yes, dude.
Damn it.
So you're now at six HP.
Caleb rolled up on you, though.
Uh huh.
So, yeah.
Remember, you are still able to.
It is now your turn, Pat.
Well, unless you're going to do something sneaky,
you both can have your headphones on at this point.
You're like right next to each other.
Anything that he's going to do, you know, you're going to do whatever.
You all can see each other.
Well, I have I have shit items, you know. Mm hmm.
Then you should probably just skip your turn.
No, I mean, it's not like I can throw these fucking birds out.
Oh, so he has birds. I have birds. You can throw the birds out. I guess I can. I'm gonna throw the birds at him. Yeah, throw the birds at him. You're gonna put two of them in one hand. You silly fucking idiot.
You're gonna spend them both. How do I roll that? Just roll a ranged attack. I'm gonna throw one. Roll a ranged attack. So just d20. 16. Nice. Oh, that hit him for sure. Deets my AC. Yeah. Yep.
Yep, and you're gonna take 1d8 fire damage, so roll 1d8, Pat.
Is this the same bird I have?
/r and then 1d8, yes it is. Same bird.
Four.
Nice. You take four damage, Caleb.
Not a problem.
Cool. Yeah. It is now...
My turn?
Yeah, it is now your turn.
So you said I have normal, just...
Melee attacks, yeah?
Yeah, there are some fun spy antics up top, but it is now just gonna devolve, I think, pretty quickly.
Yep, I'm just gonna melee him.
Yeah, alright.
Run over and just start beating the shit out of him. Alright, go for it.
Well, actually, you know what I'd like to do?
Maybe? What? What?
Where is the magnet?
The magnet is
at this point, it's on the ground next to him.
You can see it's sort of like
stuttering as it's like trying to pick
up stuff from the ground. I'd like to go pick up the magnet
and then push, like, kind of
the end of the metal part
at the end of the two sides
of the magnet, I'm going to like kind of hit him with that so that it explodes the mines.
What mines?
The things that are stuck that came off of his body.
Oh, they're caltrops.
They're just like spikes.
Whatever that is.
Oh, okay.
They're just spikes, yeah.
I'd like to hit him with the spikes on the end of the mat.
I've kind of created a mace.
Okay, yeah, for sure.
All right, roll a d20 and add your strength.
Not your proficiency.
Christ.
You got a one.
Oh.
Oh, that's real bad.
So you swing this around and of course,
you swing around too far.
Oh, bro.
The magnet is now pulling you up.
Up, up.
Pulling him up?
Pulling me up?
What are you even talking about?
It's 'cause you're swinging around
and it's sort of like a shot put where you over,
not a shot put, you know, whatever the fuck.
You're swinging the thing around.
Okay, so shot put makes sense.
Tell me how much damn damage I take.
You swing up, you hit the
and you end up back at the.
Oh no, you don't go up.
Oh, actually, I know where you go.
You swing it around and you lose a little bit of control
and you knock into this orc over here.
With your magnet attaching to his armor,
you take first of all, you're going to take some damage,
but not too much.
Really bad.
Should have just punched you, man.
Yeah, you're trying to do something cool, though.
Wow. You take six damage, actually.
Oh, what?
Yeah, I'm at three HP, bro.
And this orc looks at you and grunts.
And let me see, I don't remember.
One of you speaks orc and one of you speaks goblin.
But I don't remember which.
I made sure you guys had little other languages you could speak.
Let's see, who speaks?
God, dwarf, not you.
Oh, wait, no, yeah, you speak Gaba, not Orc.
So you just hear this Orc go like,
(mimics Orc)
and take out his sword.
It is hard to be black in this world.
(laughter)
To be the black spy, it is hard.
And it is now your turn.
rolling better than you have. And I wonder if Patches did that on purpose.
He did. You have white advantage, they call it.
I think that's exactly what it is. Yeah.
I think that I have white advantage and I think that maybe we should team up against Patches.
I agree. He's the whitest one, including the white spy, he's the whitest one.
That's not, well, yeah, that's a little true.
I think it's time to meet your maker, Patches.
What are you going to do?
Yep, meet your maker, a white spy and a black spy.
Made you.
Yeah.
You're a gray spy.
Can we see each other now?
Can I keep my headphones on?
Yeah, of course.
All right.
Naturally.
So, yeah, your turn, Pat, unless you're going to, I guess, attack me.
I can make myself a guy in the next one, yeah.
What should I do?
You just heard him bang into somebody who now drew their sword.
So...
Oh, okay.
Then I'm gonna sneak away.
Oh, he's a bitch.
But he's smart.
No, I'm going here.
I'm going back on top of this building.
Oh, you're gonna go up the stairs here and over on this little porch?
Yeah.
Do you not realize I have three health?
Yeah, but I'm gonna do something cool.
Okay, cool.
What are you gonna do?
So I'm going up to the building, right?
I'm on this porch that's overlooking the fight.
And I'm just going to drop the bird.
Oh!
All right.
Yeah, you don't even have to roll for that.
You just drop the bird and roll 1d8.
Fuck, man!
That's it.
Yeah!
The orc turns to face you.
He grumbles.
said was was I'm going to eat you little man and then a bird comes out of the sky.
You hear the Looney Tunes whistle drop the explosion and of comic.
Oh yeah.
OK, does the work at least also die?
Yes, yes, of course.
OK, alright, so one point soy.
Zero points, Caleb.
Nice, let's go nice.
All right.
This was, by the way, this map was Duluth back during Hamward Mound.
Oh, yeah.
I remember that.
So, yeah, you guys stumble upon an interesting scene here.
Make your HP back to full, too.
Back to 13.
We're going to have you both roll initiative again.
OK, 8/11.
Hmm.
All right, Caleb, Caleb, you're going to go first.
You're way uptown by the park.
You don't know where the other spy is.
So headphones, I'm going to get my items, headphones off, Pat.
And then, yeah, we'll give Pat your his items and your you your items.
So roll your three d 20s, 22 and 13.
Oh.
So when he's got to be good to and he's going to be a good item,
I can feel it.
All right.
So you should know what, um, two is at this point.
Um, Tuesday canary figurine.
Oh yeah.
Nice.
Okay.
So you got the one canary.
You already have the description for that.
Okay.
Yeah.
And 13 and then 20.
Okay.
It kind of sucks though, because he's going to...
If he sees a bird, he's just going to know what's going on.
I guess he already did, because he had it last time too.
I don't want...
Alright, sorry, I had to re-write a description.
I thought I wrote that, but I didn't write it yet.
Here you go. It's not a very good one, but I'll explain.
Okay, so I have Canary Figurine.
Caring figurine, you have this.
This is magic paint, which makes a tunnel where there isn't one with magic paint.
That's pretty good.
And then here's the thing with 20, because I had more than 20 items, I have an
awkward number you get to pick between a few of them.
Okay.
So on me.
You can pick wild tiger.
Which releases a wild tiger.
Uh, that won't necessarily do what you want it to do, but it's just out in the
A fly, a fly that buzzes around a target who, failing a wisdom saving throw, can't help
but follow it for up to 15 feet wherever you want it to go.
A hypnotic timepiece.
So a pocket watch, he's following religion, Pat, stop.
A pocket watch that does what?
Sorry, a pocket watch that emits a subtle mesmerizing pattern when activated.
So creatures failing a wisdom saving throw becoming charm.
Okay.
And a truth serum dark gun.
So this dark gun fires a truth serum.
I think I want the fly.
You want the fly?
Yeah, I like the fly too.
That seems like the item that would be most likely to work on real life Patrick.
I think I definitely want the fly.
Cool, yeah.
You'll get advantage because it's real life Patrick.
Yeah.
All right, cool.
So there you go.
So what do you want to do?
How far can I throw the fly from?
It doesn't have a range?
You kind of like let, you kind of release it.
Okay, but it has a target.
I can choose a target.
Yeah, you release it and choose a target when you see the target.
Not yet.
Are you pointing at me?
No, no, thumbs down to that.
But I can only use one item here, yeah?
Yeah, you can only use one item right now.
Unless it's a wearable one.
Hmm.
Hmm. I should have been giving you advantage on stealth checks,
but I guess you weren't making any.
Okay.
Um...
Okay, I think I want to walk over to this...
to... let's see. One, two, three, four, five, six.
I'm going to walk over like here.
And then I think I want to put the magic tunnel
Like right around just like kind of where I am, like maybe up against that tree.
Cool. OK, so if he sees that, we can approach that later. Yeah.
That's going to be similar to the fly, how that works, you know? OK.
OK, cool. Headphones off, Pat headphones on.
What did he do?
I can't tell you, you know that, man.
Did you roll three? No, you just wrote a religion check a bunch of times.
Can you roll 3d 20s?
Well,
I guess.
311 17.
So 17.
Did he also get a 17?
He did last time.
So he'll know what that is.
Maybe.
That's the magnet.
It's the magnet.
It sure is.
This is the only one that I didn't have.
Yep.
So it's the only one you didn't have.
So you're going to have the magnet,
which here's the description for the magnet.
You're going to have, what is that?
Three, okay.
- Three, 11, 17.
- This is a fun one.
Me like it.
It's a doppelganger mask.
- Okay.
- So which will create a duplicate of the wearer.
- So basically the same thing I did last round.
- Well, no, this is a doppelganger.
So it creates a duplicate of yourself, not a disguise.
Oh, okay. Yes.
And then 11 is,
oh, this one's fun.
What fun for you?
So I put the doppelganger mask on a different person.
Sorry, no.
So I can put it on somebody else
and then they will be me?
No, no, no. You can put it on. Sorry, the other thing you got...
And then I become somebody else.
No, you... Hold on. Let me just grab that.
When I put it on, I become a doppelganger of somebody else. Is that...
No, no, no.
That's what it says?
When you put it on, it creates an illusory duplicate of you.
Okay.
So it just makes another one of you.
Then why is it a mask?
I don't know why it's a mask, man.
That makes no sense.
I don't know.
I was gonna do some cool shit where I like...
I generated it.
Put the mask over somebody else and then make him kill like an innocent civilian and then
get him caught by the police.
Well, you could... What if you did put a mask... What if we changed it?
Yeah, what if we...
Who gives a shit?
Can we do it so I could do that?
Yeah. What if you did say you put a mask on somebody else and then they are a doppelganger
of you?
Yeah.
That's way more interesting.
But then it also adds the charisma checks that I gotta do.
Yeah. Yeah. You got to convince a guy to wear the mask. I like that. Yeah. That's way more fun than this bullshit that I got pulled from.
Oh, time delayed explosive pen is sick.
Oh, yeah. You got that too.
Uh huh. So.
All right. OK, so what is this person on the corner?
We know you're waiting.
That that's Paula.
Guys, notice how my turns are so fast.
No, that's not Paula.
Like 10 minutes each.
So is there anybody?
Is there anybody around who has like a clipboard like they wanted me to sign up for something?
Uh, actually, yeah, it's except she's this woman here and she's being on the corner by two gang
members. OK, I'm going to go over and stop that, I guess. Yeah. OK. Yeah. We're the gang members.
Hey, knock it off. Who said that?
I'm over here now.
Now I'm over here.
Wait, where are you going?
I'm throwing my voice.
Okay, roll performance.
Eight.
He's talking really like a small guy.
Just right by them.
And they're like,
and then they come over and now they're mad at you.
Now they want to fight you.
Okay.
I'm going to say
Don't.
It's gay role persuasion.
We're gonna be your ass.
Got a good 20.
Never mind.
We're gonna go bathroom.
They go away and she says thank you for saving me.
You're laughing.
Thank you for saving me.
Like it's at my expense.
What can I do for you?
Take this pen.
Oh, and if you see if you see a black spy, make him sign the
paper.
Oh, I would love to. Would you like to sign it?
This is how I talk.
I'll sign that if you take this pen and make the black spy sign it.
Okay, I will. Thank you, Mr. White Spy.
You're welcome.
Okay, cool. And so you take your headphones off. She's going to start walking in that direction.
All right.
You didn't thumbs up me.
Sorry, that was my bad.
Bitch.
Yeah, that's true, but it's your turn also.
You're not going to make me roll anything?
Oh, no.
Don't make the, oh, no.
I know that he did.
I see he got a 20 on persuasion.
It's not a bad idea because, yeah, you know, we kind of did this last time.
Roll perception.
I think that's fair to do when shit like this happens because it is a little bit weird.
19.
Uh, ooh, that's pretty good.
Mmm, yep.
That's so funny now.
Tell you what, I'll let you know when you get closer to it,
but you're gonna know, you're aware that
that somebody wants you to sign something.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Alright, I can work with that.
Let me take a look at my items again.
Man, I kinda, pfft, fuck.
Um, this is not how you're supposed to do perception checks.
I'm really just fucking around here.
Sorry, I'm not talking into the mic, into the mic.
I'm talking into the mic.
Can I, I'd like to walk over to the front of the Monotoli
and talk to this guy right here.
Which guy?
There's a few guys in there.
I don't know how to ping things.
How do I ping stuff?
Just hold, click and hold.
This guy.
Nice, that's a security guard.
I mean, a cop, as you can see,
there's this one woman and she pushed this other woman
in front of the van.
And she's saying, "So what if I did it?"
And then there's this cop, you're going,
"Yeah, she's crazy."
Then there's this cop over here you're gonna go talk to.
Okay.
I think, I don't know what you're gonna do.
Yeah, I'd like to talk to him.
Well, hey, what happened here with this lady?
Yeah, one lady pushed another lady out in front of a van.
Classic cat fight.
And you're a cop, yeah?
Yeah, I'm sort of just looking around making sure everything's okay.
Okay, and did somebody call you here because of this?
No, I was just standing there with my friend over, you see the other guy?
And he points to the guy over there.
Yeah, we were just hanging out and so I saw this happen, I came over.
You saw it happen.
Well, have you heard about this thing where eyewitness testimony is the least reliable
form of evidence that is permissible in court? You know this?
No, I don't, despite all my years.
It's true, man. Your eyes play tricks on you because let me tell you what I saw. Okay?
Okay.
I saw this guy, white guy, go figure, thinks he runs the world, right? And he was dressed
in all white.
I agree.
And get this, man. Yep. And get this, a cop would agree, you're good people. Get this.
He, I mean, what's more sinister than walking around with a lit stick of dynamite, right?
Nothing more sinister than that, right?
I didn't even think about it that way.
Yeah, and by the way,
this bomb that I have, this is a prop.
Just so you know. Halloween's coming.
Yeah, pretty funny, right?
Pretty funny. Imagine if it really had a bomb, right?
Oh no!
Anyway, what I
saw is that all white fella
was the one who pushed
the lady in front of the car
and as far as I'm concerned, this
psycho menace needs to be taken off the streets as soon
as possible. Alright, real persuasion.
That was very good.
So I pretty much get advantage, yeah?
You're gonna have a much lower DC.
Oh, please, please.
Ten.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
He says, "I don't know, but how do I know if it's your witness, though?
You got eyes.
You're doing your eye witness, too, right?"
Is he frozen?
So what's the truth?
Well, you know what? I'll take a test right now. An intelligence quotient test. Right
now. I would guarantee I'm smarter than you. Go ahead, make me roll intelligence.
Let's do it! And he's gonna roll intelligence against you. You guys are gonna lock eyes.
And do an intelligence test. 20.
Okay, that's gonna be a -10 for him.
Nice.
Perps minus 110, I mean, all right.
That's my bad, yeah.
He lost.
He probably would have, no matter what he would have done,
he probably would have won.
He goes, "All right, you seem real smart.
"I'll go talk to that white guy."
You got the perp, go get him!
All right, so he starts to walk over there.
And take on--
And I still haven't used an item, right?
You haven't, what do you wanna do, yeah?
I think...
Huh? I can see Patrick now, right?
Oh yeah.
OK, you know what I want to do as the cop is sneaking away
or walking away?
Can I place the canary figurine in his belt like on his
utility belt?
Roll sleight of hand.
OK.
Fuck!
That's good.
Come on, man.
Are you fucking kidding me?
That's really bad.
That's good to hear.
You put it on your own belt, obviously.
And you like kind of do the, you slap your hands like good work is done.
Oh, this is so cartoonishly accurate.
Oh my God.
And how much damage do I take?
You only take one D8.
All right.
God, seven?
Yeah.
It's not great.
Yeah. So you're taking...
Six HP, bro.
Oh my God.
All right.
- Yeah, whatever.
- That's fine.
All right.
You know, honestly, good turn up until then.
So let's--
- God, I just always do one thing too much, man.
- Yeah, no, it's, you know, yes.
All right, take off your headphones.
Pat, you're up.
- What happened?
- You saw him walk up to a cock.
I almost said cock.
I almost said cock, yeah.
You know, I'll come to a cop, start talking to him, and then the cop started to walk in
your direction.
And then you saw his pants go on fire.
Like he was a liar.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
So I see him right now.
Okay.
What should I do?
So does he see me?
We actually see some.
Oh, he sees you for sure.
Let me see something here.
And his pants are on fire.
Okay, yeah.
So actually, and this cop comes up to you,
'cause that makes sense.
And we'll resolve hers as well in a second.
So I'll put her here.
This cop comes up to you and he says,
"Hey, I gotta talk to you.
This guy over there says that you pushed that lady
in front of that van.
And he says...
That you're a pedophile.
He didn't say that.
Sir, his pants are clearly on fire.
Wouldn't a liar have pants on fire?
Let me take a look.
Doesn't that make sense?
He's a liar!
That does make sense.
His pants are on fire.
His pants are completely on fire.
That's a really good point.
I bet you don't even fuck kids either.
Alright.
No!
I'm gonna go...
Hey, do you like fashion?
I love fashion.
I'm a fashionista.
You love fashion?
Love it.
I've got this new mask I've been selling.
To people.
To people around the town.
That's my job.
I'm a mask salesman.
Yeah, play Majora's Mask.
Okay.
What do you want to do?
Yeah.
Well, this is the
This is a mask that gets you laid every single time that you wear it.
You're kidding me.
Uh-huh. Do you want to put it on?
More than anything in the world.
All right.
Do I have to roll persuasion or something?
Nah, man. Nah, nah, nah.
Okay.
Nah, nah. He puts on the mask.
All right, so now he's got the mask on.
Oh, you should go talk to that guy again because,
well, one, his pants are on fire.
You don't know what else he's been lying about. And two,
I heard that he was a he's a he had sex with a teacher. Oh,
disgusting. When he was a student. Oh, that's totally his
fault. But he was a grown up at the time. And she was the
student. Oh, no. But no, she was the teacher. I don't really. He
sounds like a pervert. I don't really know. Yeah, I think it's
just that he's a pervert. Go over to him. Sure. Cool. It's a
You walk over as he walks over as you now.
And then I'm just going to go.
I'm going to hide over here.
All right, cool.
Roll stealth.
24 nice.
Okay, you're basically hidden.
Yeah, right.
Cool.
It's now his turn.
Caleb
Get up!
All right, I'm back.
All right, what?
You saw the cop go over and you blinked and you could have missed it, but the cop was
gone and there was now some sort of a, it looks like the white guy, the white spy's coming
towards you now.
gone and meanwhile this lady's walking over to you and she's saying "Hi can you
sign my clipboard for the fund for changing lives and democracy fund?"
Yeah you know what bitch that sounds really fucking convincing yeah I'll
definitely do that okay so I walk over she comes over with the clipboard right?
mm-hmm okay I'd like to grab the pen and I'm gonna stab her right in the her neck
like the guy on that movie Red Eye.
Okay.
It's crazy.
Yeah, I'm fucking crazy.
I'm a spy.
Okay, cool.
You grab the pen, you click it to...
Oh, no, no, I don't click it.
Yeah, you do, you fuck.
Of course you do, you idiot.
Come on, man.
You take eight damage, you're dead.
I'm dead.
I'm about to put on headphones.
Keep your headphones on.
I'm dead.
on. That was great. That was awesome.
What happened?
He went over - so he - this lady came over and she said she wanted him to sign for the
Fund for Democracy and my inability to come up with something made Caleb think it was
her who was tricking him, which is my fault. And so, he goes, yeah, I'm gonna grab the
pen and click it.
Explosive pen.
Click it - I would grab the pen and stab her in the neck.
First trick of the book. Oldest trick rather.
Yeah.
And so he goes and he grabs and clicks it and it blows up in his face and he's dead.
I have once again, I have outsmarted myself.
Yeah, I hurt myself with half of my fucking HP earlier.
Damn. Yeah, he lit his pants on fire with the canary.
He 2-0'd me, dude.
Yeah. And now the folks at home can say if I play favorites here
and they can tell me. You clearly play favorites.
I clearly play favorites.
Whose name is most similar to mine is clearly what I did.
I never knew that you liked Patrick more than you like me until...
No, that's not true.
No, I think that I won based completely on my cunning and my wit.
I'm going to, since I wasn't able to listen to this,
I'm going to listen back and I'm going to be furious
at how simple everything that Patrick does was.
I just know I'm going to be so fucking pissed off.
It's going to be like 2am, you're going to text me and be like,
Like what the fuck was that?
Are you fucking kidding me?
God damn it man.
I had, dude, I had a backup
if that pen thing didn't work too.
I had a tunnel painted onto a tree
that I knew you was gonna fall for.
Did I walk over to the tree?
No, not yet.
Not yet, that was his backup.
He had a really cool item that he didn't get to use
which was the fly.
We do this again, we could do spy versus spy versus spy.
That's not a bad idea.
- Yeah, I think we could do that.
And we could tweak it too
to make it a little bit more interactive
when you guys aren't listening.
We'll figure that out, but I really like this.
- This was awesome.
- Okay. - This is a good one.
- This is awesome. - Well, then I--
- For some reason, I really like this one.
- My Spy, I didn't really like it that much.
My Spy goes back to his country.
And you know what, Patrick?
Honestly, man, he probably gets fucking executed.
He failed as a spy.
- And I go to Denny's.
get a Presidential Medal of Honor in your white country.
Be a fucker.
Alright, bye.
Bye.
*static*
*singing*
Shrek. That's them.
Yeah I know. They did a Shrek soundtrack. It's an amazingly underrated album.
*singing*
Love a little fan-mer?
It's not any of the fucking lyrics.
I was singing it correctly.
It's none of the lyrics.
It was all the lyrics.
I didn't get a single.
I sang all of them.
As a current and future musician, man, you did not get any of the lyrics.
I'm talking to two musicians today.
I got a new friend.
They really like me.
They're obsessed with my vanilla ice cream.
I think it's cool that you can remember the lyrics.
With the chocolate sauce and that pasty.
Because every time I've ever written a song, I don't know what I'm doing.
I'm just like, "Oh, I'm just going to sing it."
I'm like, "Oh, I'm just going to sing it."
Chocolate sauce and a piece of tea.
Cause every time I've ever written a song, I'd never...
I was playing in a band for like two years in high school.
And we'd go on and there were different lyrics to...
Music, same thing, but the words...
The thing is, live music, nobody's hearing a single fucking word you're singing, man.
You're doing like house shows.
Say watermelon, watermelon. Who cares?
Yeah, no one's hearing the lyrics at a house show.
It doesn't matter.
You think they got a proper mixer there? No fucking shot.
Fuck no.
No, but it was funny because I just would hit the same melody, but I'd be like...
*mimics the melody*
That's why I suck at karaoke so bad.
I don't know what it is, I can't remember lyrics to any songs.
Can you not read fast enough?
I think it's fine.
Because that's my problem with karaoke when I do something like Drake or Eminem.
I know the words, but I'm trying to follow them on the screen.
Yeah.
And then I get tripped up.
You get tripped up by specific Drake songs.
you gotta do it and stop saying certain things.
The timing gets screwed up when you can't say that.
Yeah.
Which I honestly I think they should stop saying it so I can rap along.
I'm with you.
[SCREAMING]
*Demonic Laughter*