You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Our family's through the walled list.
Crap monster.
[LOUD EXPLOSION]
[FART]
[LAUGHTER]
[FARTING]
[FART]
[LAUGHTER]
[FARTING]
(farting)
(screaming)
(laughing)
*laughter*
*farting noises*
Wait, what's this one?
That one was real.
Yeah, listen to this one.
Okay.
*whisper* Pahhh.
*laughter*
Oh wait, I got one.
*whistling*
*farting noises*
How about this?
That was an inverted one.
*farting noises*
I
I felt that one.
How about this?
(farting)
(laughing)
I spit.
I spit on my microphone.
(laughing)
I spit coffee.
Should we actually go the full 30 minutes
of just fart sounds?
I don't, you know, yes.
We've already done.
(laughing)
We've already done two minutes and I'm out of breath.
Like I can't.
Yeah, I've also run out of farts that I know how to do.
Oh yeah, I guess we could do.
That doesn't sound like a fart.
Were you ever able to do the...
There was this kid Dylan that I went to school with who he would do this thing when the teacher
was trying to talk to him where he would get on the floor on his back.
Oh, oh, and you take your shirt off and you put your back to the ground.
No, no, no.
This is the beginning of that when the teacher is trying to talk to him and he gets on the
ground on his back.
He would get on the ground on his back and he would always wear basketball shorts and
He would stick his hands and cup them under his knees and then just make like a million
fart sounds in a row.
Like just like, just with his knees by, it was the same concept as the armpit thing.
Yeah, yeah.
But he would do it with his knees so there was a lot more velocity.
He would do it to the teacher while the teacher was trying to talk.
The thing is I went to a charter school so there was like no rules.
You could just do that.
It was the wild, wild west.
Kids were farting everywhere.
I would jack off in the bathroom.
I would leave math and go jack off in the bathroom.
You were a jack off at kid school?
A jack off at kid school?
No, not when you put it like that.
Jack off at school kid?
Yeah, dude.
I had a lot of cum as a child.
The farts made me so lightheaded that I thought I said jack off at school kid.
I genuinely thought I said that regular.
The thing is about jacking off at school when you're a kid in Six Flags, you're in the
You're in the stall and somebody comes up to the urinal next to you and just like pisses
and then just lays down just a beefy fart while you're trying to jack off.
You just lose it, dude.
You just can't finish.
Yeah, because you're at school.
You shouldn't be doing it.
No, it was like an easy way to get out of class because they can't say you can't go
to the bathroom.
Yeah, say to the teacher, "I have to go jack off."
Yeah, "Can I have the jack off key to the jack off room?
Can I have a Jackoff pass?
Remember you only get 15 minutes to Jackoff.
The Jackoff kid at my school told me that he put his dick in a shampoo bottle once.
Damn, dude.
The genius.
He was telling me that he did that and then I was like, "Well, how did you...
First of all, how did you do it?"
Because that hole is very small.
The shampoo bottle, like the hole for like, even if you take the lid off, it's only about
like the size of like...
Of a penis.
The size of, no it's not the size of a penis.
The size of, the perfect size of a penis.
It's the size of a quarter.
No the perfect penis size.
The diluvian man penis size.
He was using special, he was using fat shampoo where they make it fatter.
They make the hole bigger.
Perpetruvian man.
Well, he told me that at lunch.
It was a bunch of guys that fucked that shampoo bottle so the hole got a lot bigger.
It stretched it out.
He told me that at lunch.
His whole family was fucking it.
Yo, you wanna come over to my house later?
We're about to like tear up a bottle of Pert Plus, you and the homies.
We gotta pass it around, bro.
We got this new bottle of Alberto VO5 original, that shit that smells like baby shampoo.
You would fuck something that smells like baby, Patrick.
We're about to steal some sacrament wine from my parents and fuck up a fucking bottle of
head and shoulders, bro.
Let's go.
He told me that he fucked a shampoo bottle and then I ended up telling the whole school.
You were a tattletale, dude.
No, he told me while I was trying to eat, so then I sat there at lunch and I went, "Why
did you fuck a shampoo bottle, Eric?"
You're a tattletale.
That was absolutely tattletale bullying behavior.
That is not tattletale.
No, no, that is even worse than Tattletail.
That's called being an air horn.
Yeah.
No.
Yeah, we called this kid an air horn because we got in trouble because I made a very tasteless
joke about my friend's sister raping him when I was in middle school.
And then I said that to this kid, Noah, and then he-
Noah, your friend Noah?
No, not that Noah, a different Noah from middle school.
And then he just yelled that joke back to me.
He was like, "You think his sister raped him?"
Really loudly.
And then I got kicked out of school for four days.
We all know those kids.
Yeah, you told us about that story.
It's an air horn, dude.
Yeah.
The one who was like, "What's that?
You're planning to smoke cat food and have sex with a bar of soap with all your friends?"
It's like when you're trying to steal something from Target and you have that friend who's
Did you pay for that green tea?
Yeah.
It's that same thing.
It's like, shut the fuck up dude.
It's called being smooth and cool.
Yeah, just go with it.
Yeah.
Well, I was only an air horn that one time.
No.
No, you still are.
No, no.
I'm not an air horn.
You are absolutely an air horn.
You're an air horn, dude.
You're an air horn to the max, dude.
Yeah, you are.
You're one of the world's biggest air horns.
You absolutely are.
I'm not.
I am not an air horn.
You are.
You're an air horn and a tattletail.
I'm not a tattletail.
You're an air tail.
A tattle horn.
I'm not an air tattletale. You're an air bud, you dog face bitch.
I'm not a tattletale. If there's anything I'm not, it's a tattletale.
If there's anything you're not, it's not a tattletale.
That's right. That's a double negative, so I'm not a tattletale.
Oh, and you're a nerd. So you just told on Caleb for using a double negative.
Wow! Yeah.
You're a double negative. You are.
You're... yeah I am. See? You're a double negative.
Patrick's a name caller.
Yeah, and I'm a shot caller.
If anyone's a name caller, it's Cameron. Cameron's the worst name caller of us all.
Shut the fuck up, you fat little bitch.
See?
Whoa, see? He gets creative with it.
I deal with this every day.
What? Off? Off pod? Off pod? Cameron's the meanest one of us all.
That's not true. No, Caleb's meaner than me.
I'm not mean. I'm nice.
Caleb's mean on the microphone. Cameron's mean...
Once I put the mic down I'm a sweetie pie.
That's not true.
What are we talking about to each other or to just in general life?
Caleb's definitely meaner to me to the average person on this planet.
Caleb puts on his wig and licks his lollipop and he does little Lord Fauntleroy stuff.
But you, off the mic, Cameron, you...
Caleb goes through evil phases where he makes girls drop out of school because he makes
fun of them too much.
That's not true.
once. She didn't drop out, she dropped the class, okay? And I was actually under the,
I was under the influence of finasteride hair medicine that was affecting my hormones. It
wasn't an evil phase. Listen, pal, do you know where the myth, where people thought
werewolves existed because guys had too much hair, alright? You were basically turning into
a werewolf. I was a reverse werewolf. Well, you were trying to get more hair with your
hit werewolf medicine. I was trying to get more hair to ruin me. That's literally the definition
of an evil phase y'all. Dude you're the definition of a werewolf. You're a werewolf. No. If one
of us was a werewolf it would be you. Patrick's been a werewolf. You look like you're stuck
in the middle between a guy and a werewolf. Like you've almost brushed out of your skin.
I grow hair under my eyes.
Under your eyes?
If you look close enough you can see like a bunch of hair.
Patrick grows like ten rows of eyelashes all the way up and down his face.
That's true, I do have very long eyelashes.
Every girl that I've known in my life has told me that they're jealous of my eyelashes.
Every girl you've known.
It'd be funny if a werewolf, werewolves are always jacked, it'd be cool if one was just
like a fat piece of shit who ate like trash.
Yeah.
Didn't even try to kill people.
Like a dog?
like all dogs are. Yeah, just like went to a dumpster behind a McDonald's and
someone was just like, "Yeah, I just saw like the biggest dog ever in the dumpster."
It'd be neat. Because werewolves don't really need to eat humans. Because werewolves don't
really exist. Yeah, that's the thing about them. Yeah. Yeah, okay, you continue to
believe that. Yeah. I'm sorry, is that 5G? Uh-huh. Is it? It is. What, 5G? What? Not
Not believing in werewolves?
5G is not believing in werewolves, yeah.
I still haven't upgraded my phone to 5G and I'm not going to.
It keeps asking me to update the settings to include 5G and I keep saying no.
Mine doesn't say that.
I will never include you 5G.
Yeah, mine, I don't even get that option.
I keep getting it because it's propping up on my...
You know why?
Because it targets weak individuals.
No, it targets people who know too much.
No, it targets you.
They're not trying to put 5G on you because you guys don't have any knowledge to be erased.
It targets people that it wants to turn into girls.
Yeah, exactly. They want to and they're not going to. I'm not going to let them.
There's people who want to turn Cameron into a girl because they think that Cameron would be too beautiful as a woman.
There are a lot of people who want that but it won't happen.
Someone on the subreddit said you'd be a beautiful girl.
Someone on the subreddit has said that.
Exactly. But I'm not one and I won't ever be one.
Someone on the subreddit has said Cameron would be a beautiful woman.
You will be very soon.
Me and Patrick are going to hold you down and make a woman out of you.
I don't think so.
Yeah, we are.
No, we're going to make you a girl.
We're going to turn you into a girl ASAP.
We're going to give you a makeover.
Listen, pal.
We're gonna give you your face in extreme home makeover.
If there's anyone getting a makeover, it's you, alright, Patrick?
I'm gonna customize you to my heart's content.
See what I mean?
Cameron's Diminished One.
I'm gonna mix and match your...
This is on mic, so it doesn't count to what you were saying before.
I would like to...
I'm gonna mix and match Patrick's parts and clothing.
Just imagine...
Patrick, I'm gonna play with you like a pretty pimple popper pregnant princess flash game,
okay?
I'm gonna customize your whole body.
See, imagine what he says off mic to everybody in his life.
I'm gonna use a bunch of duct tape and rearrange Patrick's body until he looks like a burlesque
girl.
Just like various, kinda like different corsets on parts of your body.
Just squish everything in the right place.
I'm gonna play with you like Source Filmmaker, pal.
Alright?
Yeah.
Yeah, and I'm clipping through your dress.
Believe that.
Oh, and I'm inflating parts of you.
One of the best things about video games is finding that like that tiny the the
atomic space between the modeled clothes on a woman, modeled clothes on a woman and
the modeled like body underneath when you're in free cam mode where you clip
through the clothes but not into the body. That space between the
clothes and the and the body is called Caleb's Corridor.
They did, they named it after me. Because of how furiously you tried to discover it as a child.
I'm a purveyor of it. Yeah, you're a purveyor, I'll say.
I'll say it. It's so funny how many like, you don't get that like for the
male characters too. Like they never model. No, the male characters are just
clothes. Yeah, the male characters are made out of their clothes. Like their
skeleton is the clothes. Yeah, but the girls are like, we
have to make... Well, we have to put a boob under it. Yeah, it's just
something about the female form you got it like even with zamas they do it they
get less zamas samas did you say zamas yes samas samas
samas I mean Samus? That's not how the announcer says it.
That's how the announcer says it.
Patrick is like oh yeah I'm gonna go play some Super Mario
he says zamas it doesn't does yeah it does it doesn't matter he's Japanese
he's like yelling stuff it doesn't matter what he says zamas his name is
her name is Samus I'm sorry it's Samus Samus Samus dude it's Samus it's not
Japanese guy it's you it's me you we discovered that he's the the Smash
Brothers announcer.
Because that's the only guy who says "SAMUS".
Yeah.
SAMUS!
Oh, SAMUSU!
That's Patrick trying to pronounce words.
I can't believe that.
He said "ZAMUS" first and then backpedaled.
That's how he fucking says it!
He says "ZAMUS".
ZAMUS.
That's how I said it my whole life.
At first I thought you were saying "zombies".
Yeah.
That's how I said it my whole life.
The thing about modeling girls' bodies under the clothes in games is the games just don't
work otherwise.
It's true.
That's where they store all the programming for the game is in the girls body.
Yeah, it's all ones and zeros.
And you know, those zeros are what those are.
Yeah, and the ones freaking go into the zeros.
And it's a penis.
Yeah, you put the ones all on the boy characters,
put the zeros on the girl characters,
and then you just let nature run its course.
Girls and boys having sex in a video game.
And you know what happens when you add a zero to a one?
No. You get one. Ten. You get ten. You get a one. You get a boy. A baby boy. You know what happens when you get, when you add it, when you add an eight and a zero and a zero and an eight and a five to a zero. You get, you get twenty one. And upside down. You get twenty one. You know what happens when you add all those numbers together. Forty three eleven. Whoa. That's some serious hitchhiker's guide to the galaxy bullshit that you just threw at me brother.
me
to keep him within like a foot of me at all times
or else she puts him in the trash.
Never ever get married.
- Have you guys watched Cake Wars?
Have you guys ever seen that show?
- I've watched Cake Farts.
- Yeah, I've watched Cake Farts.
That's an all-time video, dude.
I never knew until that video
that when somebody farts,
their butthole pokes out like a bird's beak.
- Yeah.
- Or like, actually more like Old Faithful, like a geyser.
That's like what it looks like in that video.
And so that was, it's,
I'm glad I saw that when I was 10 years old.
- Yeah, you gotta see it.
- It teaches you about the body.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- But-- - And cake.
- I've been watching-- - I never knew it was
under the frosting and cake either.
I had no idea.
So it was really interesting, it was good.
I got a nice cross section there.
- I've been watching Cake Wars with Anna,
and like the way they do it is every episode
has like a theme that the contestants have to like
make cakes based on that theme and it's so weird because like the first episode is
um the Simpsons is the theme and like just the way that everyone talks on the
show like it's just like so clear that none of them have like they all just like
read a packet about the Simpsons before the show started like they're just all
like oh my gosh I love the Simpsons what's your favorite thing about Homer
and then like one of them was like oh my favorite thing about Homer is he has has
two hairs on top of his head and then there's like there's the IMDB fact yeah
no it's so crazy it feels like a Tim and Eric thing it's like insane it's so it's
so bizarre there's like they have a one judge that's like this is real old
Israeli guy and he's like eating the cakes and he's like I love this cake
it's so sweet this cake feels as if it's something that Homer Simpson himself
would indulge in I really I really recommend the first episode of that show
of
get it in the show. Alright. Yeah. How else would they know that you have to have
something that as a reference I don't know you've clearly never drawn anything
Patrick but basically the way it works is you have to have something in real
life that you use as a reference. Take for example the Mona Lisa. Mona Lisa did not exist.
Leonardo da Vinci used a picture of himself face-apped as a
girl and he made one of the hottest bitches who's ever been put on. One of the
baddest. Ezel. Yeah, one of the baddest hoes ever put to, ever put paint to brush. Honestly,
the Mona Lisa choice, choice fucking cunt there. Absolutely top-notch dude. You gotta, you
gotta wash your mouth out with soap right now. I do need to, I need to hold Listerine
in my mouth for far too long. You, you gotta wash your damn mouth out with soap. Yeah. I'm
telling ya, you, you got a problem. I like that, I do that as a snack for me. Ugh. Here's
Here's a prank.
You disgust me.
Replace the bar of soap in your bathroom with candy soap and then go up to your mom and
say the F word.
Uh huh.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
Guess what buddy?
Guess what mom?
Free candy.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
Oh no mom, you're force feeding me candy.
Oh, oh no!
I hate it.
I hate it so much.
Oh my god.
I hate this crap.
Yeah.
Ugh.
Caleb, wash your mouth out with chocolate.
You said a nice thing.
- Nice.
- That's what I was gonna say.
- You said a compliment. - Damn, if that ain't me
as a parent.
- Yeah, that's what I'm gonna do.
- Damn, if that ain't me.
- If my kid says something very nice to me,
then I'm gonna make him wash his mouth out
with candy toothpaste.
- Yeah.
- Now that you mentioned that scheme about the candy soap,
if I am ever a parent, I'm now making sure
that I have a bunch of spare bars of soap
that I keep in a hidden safe.
And then whenever my kid says a bad word,
they have to use a new bar of soap.
That way they can never replace it with candy.
- Mm, genius.
- Unless they do a heist.
- I don't know, man, that's kinda sus of you
to be thinking like that, honestly.
- You'd be thinking about your kids' soap.
- You'd be thinking about, well,
just you'd be thinking about being a parent
and how to punish a kid. - You'd have to have plans,
you know, 'cause then, 'cause they'll--
- No. - Basically, if I make
that plan, now I know how to counteract it.
- If I'm ever a parent, I'm not gonna tell my kids
that I'm their parents, I'm gonna say I'm their older brother
and also my name is Todd.
And I'm gonna teach them how to have blanket forts
and we're gonna smoke weed as soon as I turn 14.
And it's gonna be-- - And one day--
- One of the greatest-- - One day--
- Plays a long time. - One day you're gonna
reveal that your name is Caleb and you're their dad.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah.
And then they'll look back on a lot of memories.
Isn't there a movie where that happens?
- Yeah, it's called Big.
- What is it?
- It's Big.
- No, that's the freaking movie about the size
of the poops that you're eating every day
for your meals every day.
- Okay, I'm gonna quit.
- Let me think about the name of this movie.
Can everybody be quiet now?
- Yeah.
- For like 10 minutes.
I can't remember the name of the movie.
- Oh, okay.
Yeah, it was Big.
It was Big the whole time.
- It wasn't Big.
- Which is the size of the opposite of your brain.
I've never seen big there's no such thing as the opposite of my brain.
Big can't be opposite.
The opposite of your brain is your ass.
No the opposite of his brain is my brain and the opposite of my ass is or the same thing
as my ass.
It's very clear that the opposite of my brain is your brain right now given how small your
brain is.
Cameron has a brain in my ass.
Cameron gave my ass brain.
It's true.
Yeah it's true.
It's true I saw it.
I did not. Yeah, you didn't see it.
Pat paid to see it in one of those medical amphitheaters.
I didn't pay to see it. I saw it for free.
He did, and I was holding a big bone saw
and I was wearing like a smock
and Cameron was covered in blood.
You were wearing a...
You were wearing a sock on your penis like a chili pepper.
You were.
You were, and it's true that you were.
And you can't deny it.
And if you say no, you mean yes.
Patrick, the point of the mic arm is that you don't have to...
that you don't, that it's at your face.
- That you're not far away.
- That you don't go far away from it.
- There we go, there he is.
My friend, we found a friend.
- Well now I think it's too loud.
I think Patrick just doesn't know how to use a mic.
- I have my mic set up so that I can.
- Well that's how you pick up really annoying,
that's why your chair squeaks all the time.
- No, no it's not.
- Can you guys take this to the bedroom?
- No.
- Patrick's in his bedroom.
- I'm not in my bedroom.
- He's right next to you.
- You're both in your bedroom
guys are right next to each other. Hey, here's a riddle. Cameron is in Cameron's bed. Patrick
is in Patrick's bed. But, they're in the same bed. Are they two gay guys? That's the answer
to the riddle. That's the riddle. That's not a riddle. The answer is yes. The answer is
no. Are they two married guys? A riddle doesn't have a correct answer. Okay, that's the point
of a riddle. Are they two married guys with a son like Modern Family, but one of them
is pretending for acting and one of them is real life gay?
Which one is which?
Yeah Patrick is both.
No.
Yeah.
God.
I knew, I, I, my friend John, we found his dad's penis, I probably shouldn't say who
his dad was.
Okay, pause.
We found his penis, we found, we found like a penis sock thing in one of his drawers and
then we just kept it, we stole it and kept it in his car for like a year and a half and
And then he would just, anytime one of us would annoy the other, we would take it out of the
glove box and then dangle it in front of them.
Yeah, so it seems like we found out who the real gay one is on the podcast.
Yeah, it's you.
No.
No, it's not me.
Yeah, it is.
No.
Not you, then.
I've never kept a penis.
I've never played with a penis sock with my friends.
You've kept a penis.
You've played with a penis.
Yeah, my own.
Oh!
Yeah, that's called a comeback.
He plays with it, though.
Like a GI Joe.
Yeah, dude, it's fun.
He squishes, he folds down the top of it like a sock
and starts puppeting it.
I have a crank on the side like a jack in the box.
You mean like a jack in your mouth?
Yep, 'cause that's where you're putting that bad boy.
That's fun.
Okay.
Ooh, yeah.
You crank it all the way up until it's like one atom thin
and 11 inches high because that's how long it would stretch.
I mean, that's pretty good length.
Dude, how few atoms.
That's a pretty good length.
How's that width though, big guy?
Small, I'm poor. It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
- It does matter to me.
- To you, why does it matter to you?
You care about the width of a penis?
- No reason. - He cares a lot.
- He cares a lot about the penis.
- No reason at all.
- That's what the song "We Care a Lot" was about.
It's about Caleb caring about the size of a penis.
- No, it's about you caring about girl movies.
- No.
- Yeah, you caring about "13 Going on 30,"
your favorite movie.
- I've never even heard of that movie.
- Well, you like the first part
a lot more than the second part.
- I don't know what movie you're talking about.
13 going on 30. It's your favorite movie. I've never heard of that movie and you have a 13 year old that that turns 30 and to
You it's a horror. How do you know that?
Because you told me about it. I didn't yeah, you did I did. I'm reading your letterbox right now says 13 going on 30
I find a letterbox. I've never love you. I love it or watch that movie
I I love the don't even have it on my watch list
But then she ruins it by turning 30.
Caleb's reading it off his own letterbox.
You're reading your notes.
I'm not reading any notes.
Caleb's reading his personal notebook.
You're reading your notes.
Caleb's reading his journal where he writes down
his favorite parts of movies while he watches them.
Not, untrue.
A lie from a guy.
Exactly, from a guy, thank you.
We're done here, we can end the podcast.
I'm a guy now.
God fucking damn it, dude.
You suck, dude.
I'm just gonna play Switch.
Yeah.
you guys handle the list I'm gonna play the Nintendo switch. Do that. Let's do it again.
The farts at the beginning make me very lightheaded. I can't even like I've been zoned out. If doing a
fake fart for a minute and a half makes you lightheaded for half an hour you
need to go to the doctor right now. Yeah. You have AIDS. No. You have HIV/AIDS. I
don't have the HIV virus that causes AIDS. You do have the HIV virus that causes AIDS. I did but I cured it.
You pretended your mouth was a butt.
No.
Yeah, and that's where it comes from.
I cured it.
Any time your mouth does stuff a butt should do, that forms the HIV/AIDS virus.
And you did a fart sound.
No.
How'd you cure it?
What's the cure for AIDS?
It's Pepsi.
Pepsi will not cure AIDS.
The only thing that cures...
Pepsi is the cure.
No, the only thing...
No.
Pepsi is the cure.
The only thing that cures AIDS is Dr. Sebi's herbs.
Dr. Pepper is Dr. Sebi.
Yeah, Dr. Sebi's 36 flavors.
What's taped to your ceiling?
That's just some newspaper I was reading earlier.
I like to sit on the ground and look up and read the newspaper on the ceiling.
It's a little challenge for myself.
For my eyes.
I like to challenge my eyes.
So sometimes I'll like put two flashlights on the front of my glasses and just put them
on strobe and see how long I can last without vomiting.
I like to look into laser pointers just to train my eyes.
What are you doing? I'm doing an eye challenge and I'm close to a world record.
You guys introduced the list. I'm gonna eat a bar.
Okay. Top 10 reasons Cameron's bar is poop flavored.
Number one, he bought it from the poop store.
I gotta stop meowing into the mic.
Number two, he's the guy who made the bar.
Yeah, I meowed into the mic.
He yawned.
You mean yawns?
A male meow.
A male meow is a yawn.
A male meow is a ming.
But you're eating poop, basically, Cameron.
Yeah, sure, just introduce the list.
Basically, Cameron's eating poop right now.
This is the most romantic things to say to her.
And her is Kayla's mom.
And you know who her is, it's Cameron.
Oh wait, this is perfect, we can say all these things to the girl from our podcast, Cameron.
Cameron.
The woman of our dreams.
The woman of my dreams.
I close my eyes at night and I imagine Cameron in a beautiful red bikini that's one inch big.
You guys already said I was the boy this episode. You can't do it this episode, you have to wait till next one.
It's called "Take Backseas" and I take backseas that.
Wow, someone who was yelling at Patrick for being a tattletale and an airhorn now wants to do backseas?
I think you're the real bitch here, pal.
Yeah, I think I was framed.
No, I'm gonna frame you, buddy.
I think I was framed.
No.
Oh yeah, you're gonna take that back too, dude.
You can't commit to anything.
I take it back.
God.
Man, how is this guy the married one on the show?
I know, right?
You are both- Oh, I know, he's married to his freaking mommy
and daddy and he lives in their basement and he does chores and powers the house for them
on an electric bicycle.
Is this seriously my life?
I'd call in here twice a week just to get absolutely fucking lasered by two hot shots?
Caleb- This is my life.
Caleb's a mobility scooter. Is this how Beetlejuice from Howard Stern feels?
Can you just try for once and like start the list? This is how I feel. I'm Beetlejuice.
You guys are Howard Stern and I'm Robin and Beetlejuice. And you're right I'm
gonna make you ride the Sibian. Did they make Beetlejuice ride the Sibian? They did not make Beetlejuice ride the Sibian.
I think that way they would go to jail if they did that. Yeah they would go to jail.
jail instantly yeah like automatic jail time immediately yeah I mean that and
also it would have been filmed when the government saw Beetlejuice on on Howard
Stern they like they put a detector on Beetlejuice's butt and that if it ever
touched the Sibian they instantly would raid the studio and put Howard Stern in jail
yeah Beetlejuice was actually he was a honeypot operation and he's actually
filled with bombs and they sent him in they were like they can't resist putting
this guy on the Sibian. And as soon as the magnets from the Sibian touches his
pussy, he had a pussy by the way, that's how far they went in trying to bait
Howard Stern. Yeah he would have just exploded. Wow, wow that's wild. That's real wild.
Beetlejuice, nice pussy. Wow. Beautiful pussy. Hold on, this is my Howard Stern impression.
ready okay hello it's me I would say it's me I would stand beautiful pussy on
baby juice
how's that no no I'll juice all right number one last night I looked up wait
Cameron let me look at you in the eyes when I say when I tell you this serenade
Last night I looked up into the stars and matched each one with a reason why I love you.
I was doing great, until I ran out of stars.
Cameron's pants are wet now.
Yeah, Cameron's in pain because he's scared.
No, Cameron's stuck to his gamer chair.
I don't have a gamer chair.
Cameron has a gamer chair.
You do. You have a hot leather gamer chair.
Cameron has a big gamer chair.
Yeah. I see what looks like the outline of an avocado in sweat on it.
You tell, explain that to me.
It's not a gamer chair. Do you see it?
I can see the outline of your pussy on it.
It's a kitchen chair.
You've been juicing on that, friend.
Cameron has been juiced up.
Cameron just got juiced in the chair.
Ooh, he, ooh, he juicing.
Someone says, I said this to a girl I'd liked for a really long time,
but she was playing hard to get.
So I said it and we instantly started kissing and we have been dating ever since.
That was last year.
Whoa.
Yeah, it's pretty much just something you learn when you're in the game.
Yeah.
You learn how to have game when you're in the game.
Mm-hmm.
I got game.
I be saying shit like this to my bitch.
To my biatch.
You don't say anything.
Yeah, I do.
I walk in from being outside during the time of the day that she makes me go outside, and
I come inside and I say, "Hey, Star's outside.
You're a star."
(laughing)
- She goes, "Get outside again!
"Leave!
(laughing)
"I'm trying to, I'm doing Pilates with my trainer again!"
- Say, "All right, you're a star, you're a star, baby.
"I love you."
- I love my baby.
- This one's, this comment says,
"Oh my God, my boyfriend told me this last night
"and I never believed he made it up.
"Today I find this.
"Damn, that boy is screwed.
"But I have to admit, it's amazing."
- Wow.
Damn, that boy's screwed.
Damn that boy is screwed.
Damn that boy is screwed!
How many more ways can we say it?
Yeah no he said it because he was trying to get screwed.
Yeah that's right.
Woah.
Hey!
What's up?
What's up with y'all?
Let's see if somebody got laid from this.
Yeah.
Because if so...
All the comments are stories about I told this to my secret crush and now we have been
dating for 200 years.
My girlfriend said she had three good reasons for me.
Sexy, funny, and then she attacked me viciously for sex.
This one works okay, laugh out loud.
My girlfriend attacked me viciously.
My girlfriend, yeah, my girlfriend attacks me for sex.
Bragging.
Yeah, sometimes I get home and I get attacked for sex.
Pretty chill, right?
Down low.
Up top.
Too slow.
Said this to my girl during class.
I spent the rest of the period in principal's office for making out.
I said this to my girl and she was speechless like I speaking in Swahili.
The minute someone speaks to you in Swahili you just stop talking.
LOL I can't believe the cringe says hater.
If my boyfriend told me this I would jump him if you catch my drift.
But no guys actually think about saying this stuff sadly.
I would viciously attack my boyfriend for sex.
Sounds less tacky than having a small set of roses.
Not putting down the roses though.
I told my girlfriend this and she straight up came all over the place.
Sounds like Cameron.
No.
That's Cameron's reaction.
That's what happened to Cameron.
Number two.
I sent an angel to look over you at night.
The angel came back a minute later and I asked why.
It told me angels don't watch other angels.
Wow.
What the fuck?
I'm dating a biblical angel. She's a giant baby head with 15 wings coming out of her neck.
You are dating a baby.
Yeah, you're dating a baby. We got it.
I'm dating a biblically accurate angel, just a bunch of lines that confuse my brain.
You're dating a biblically accurate angel, a cherub.
Cherubs are not biblically accurate. That's the point.
You're dating one of those cherub statues from a Greek restaurant where it's blowing its penis and peeing.
I'm dating an evil angel in knight's armor with a sword.
A man angel.
- No, no, it's a cool soul pal.
- Yeah, you're dating a guy named Gabriel.
- Yeah.
- You're dating Gabriel Iglesias.
- No. - You're dating
Gabriel Iglesias. - And if I was,
I'd be rich, so.
- Really awesome. - Who's the owner?
- I'm a male and can't wait to say this
to my beautiful girlfriend.
- That's nice.
- Yeah.
- Good for him.
- As in every first letter capitalized.
- That I would like to say to a girl.
(laughing)
- My girlfriend burst into tears.
They themselves were like the stars.
And she said that she could never leave my side.
I was "the guy".
I'm a 10 year old girl looking at this list for fun.
I usually rate reviews for worst things about Disney and stuff.
This one is seriously juicy.
Basically, I'm 10 and these are some juicy compliments.
Amazing.
This is a really nice thing to say to a girl or a guy, depending on your sexuality.
True.
yeah I told my girlfriend over the phone at like 3 a.m. and I was awoken with a
king-sized hug yeah my king-sized girlfriend my girl is a real California
king yeah she's fucking she's huge in those hugs
guy or I mean they're king so I said that I said that to my girlfriend and
she kissed me and we went to bed now we have twins a boy and a girl sex was
amazing learning about sex through the Sims really fucks kids up yeah there's
like cuz I remember my older brother asking me if I knew what sex was when I
was a kid and I was like yeah it's when you kiss naked in bed it's when you go
dancing together yeah hello and then he laughed and then you get twins a boy and
a girl and then you get twins a boy and a girl and you and then you get to wear
funny shorts that have hearts on them this comment you honestly don't
understand how to love. The messed up reality is if you are not from China the
world is fake. China makes everything guys. Repost this everywhere if you agree.
Whoa. Alright. I'll repost it. Yeah. That's fine. Yeah I like China. Much respect to China.
Much respect. Number three. Number one. They say a picture tells 1,000 words but when I
I see yours, all I see is three.
I love you.
- Your picture is worth nothing, bitch.
- Yeah, you could have said I love you like 300 times.
- Yeah, just say it 1,000 times.
Write a bot to say it three.
- Write an AI to say it 1,000 times.
- Exactly, write an AI to scan a photo, all right?
And put your girlfriend into facial recognition
so it says I love you when it sees her face.
Put on a hat that says I love you.
- Whoa.
- And then, yeah, so then you don't even have to say it
'cause a hat says a thousand, it says three words.
- Great help, once I said this it spread
and now I have a nice girl.
- It spread.
Once I said this.
- Once I said this it spread.
- Every,
I'm a dude and this could make me cry.
(laughter)
I bet it would.
- Definitely the best one.
My girlfriend cried when I said this,
and then cried for hours.
- And she can't stop crying.
- My girlfriend can't stop crying.
Somebody please help me.
Can somebody get two huge corks so I can plug up her eyes?
- Somebody, seriously, please help my girlfriend stop crying.
- Yeah, I'm taking her to the hospital
because my words made her cry so badly.
- Something happened to her t-shirt.
- Yeah, she's wasting away
because all the water is leaving her body.
- Yeah, she's turning into beef jerky.
- She's going to die.
- She's turning into beef jerky, the perfect girlfriend.
- Mm, beef jerky girlfriend.
- Whoa.
- Oh my God, smoky and delicious.
- MathGuy37 comments, I want to say that to my mom.
Somebody wants to...
It's kinda weird, man.
Come on, math guy.
I wanna say that to my beef jerky girlfriend.
Yeah.
Yeah, Slim Jim girlfriend.
Yeah, Slim Amanda.
That's right.
And you know what the shape of it is, 'cause Slim Jim is a long stick.
And a Slim Amanda is like a...
a woman's vagina, basically.
would be the shape but it would be meat.
Number four, when giving her a dozen roses, 11 real and one fake, say "I will love you
until the last rose dies."
So it's already dead.
Alright, cheapskate.
Yeah, it's not a dozen roses.
It was never alive.
Yeah.
Stupid ass bitch.
It is.
Stupid.
The ultimate show of love, and it also includes logic.
That inclusion demonstrates motivation and forethought, something most people, regardless
of gender, never include in their cards or flowers.
This is my favorite one, but I'm biased since I used it in the past and was pretty glad for
coming up with a variation of this on my own.
This is what Cameron wrote.
That's Patrick's alt account where he doesn't do the dumb guy act for likes.
That's how Patrick's internal monologue sounds, but then he's like, "Oh, I can't get 20,000
followers if I post like this.
I have to say, I have to say Yoda guy at the subway, man.
- No. - Yeah.
- I don't do a dumb guy act. - I'm eating a poop on the boat.
- I don't do a dumb guy act. - From the Lonely Island.
I'm eating a poop on the Lonely Island boat.
- On the boat, I'm on the Lonely Island.
- I'm on his boat.
- Yeah, I'm on that boat.
- I'm taking my boat to the Lonely Island
and my dick is in a box and I'm Jack Sparrow.
- I would not, I would just say I'm on a boat.
You would say, "I just jizzed in my box."
I jizzed in my butt.
Yeah.
[LAUGHTER]
That would be a pretty good one.
I just jizzed in my butt.
[LAUGHTER]
Post it.
Let's see.
No.
Yeah, I just jizzed in my butt.
All right, I'm taking that one then.
Put it on the pod account.
Yeah.
OK, let's go.
Let's post it right now.
Let's see how it does.
That's a special preview.
I just jizzed in my butt.
- All right.
All right.
- I wasn't just saying that guys.
I was, I'm not saying, I didn't do that.
- All right, if you say so.
- I'm just saying.
- If you say so.
- I was just saying that, dude.
- Did it?
- Logic and romance.
- Did you post it?
- Yes.
- Logic and romance, the best combination
for a message to go straight to a girl's heart.
Girls love logic and romance.
- Women, they love, women are famous for loving logic.
I love a combination of logic and romance.
Yeah.
Bernie Mac had all those jokes
about how women love logic too much.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
It's true.
Yeah, it's true.
People laugh 'cause it was true, dude.
I really love my girlfriend and I want to make her happy.
It worked like a charm.
Can't wait to use this on Valentine's Day.
I used some of these on a girl that I really like
and she is quite impressed on how I can variate
from romantic to dirty/sexual.
*laughter*
Girl, I'm variating to dirty/sexual tonight.
Damn, ooh, ooh, you've been variating from dirty to /sexual.
Turns me on, dude.
Mm-hmm.
Until the last rose dies, then you have never started to love her because the rose has never started living.
Think about it.
Oh my god.
So don't say this, unless you like lying.
That's what I just said, I said that.
I love lying.
Dude, I love to lie.
I love the invention of lying.
Yeah, me too.
It's such a good movie, dude.
I love Ricky Gervais.
When Ricky Gervais tricks women into having sex with him.
Yeah, the whole movie.
There's that part where he's like,
if you don't have sex with me,
the world will be destroyed by an asteroid.
And some woman's like, well, let me suck your penis then.
And he's like, nice.
And then it happens.
(laughs)
Yeah, they have the full scene.
Yeah, and then they do nasty on each other.
I'm gonna need I was actually that was a man on the street
That was a man on the street bit and that was just a really stupid woman
That wasn't actually part of the movie originally that was a boy
How women are in the UK? He's like I'm gonna need a full scene a full penetration
And I'm not gonna do my own stunts. I'm gonna be I'm like Tom Cruise and I'm and I'm not lying
He tried he kept trying to do the thing from the movie on the set. Yeah, there's over and over again
again. Oh that Louis CK is in that movie. So yep he's also at my house. Yeah. Yeah. We can't
get him out. This brought tears to my eyes. That's what happens when you move to New York.
Louis CK has to film, he has to do the Louis intro through your apartment. Well he has
to do it through people's apartments now because of COVID. Yeah he's eating a pizza over my
trash can right now.
Yeah.
Get him out of there dude.
He threw, he just took two bites and threw the rest away.
What the F?
Yeah, this guy seriously is a fucked up individual.
Now we have to cancel this guy.
Yeah.
Yeah, fuck this guy for a, he can't even finish a pizza.
That does, that kind of behavior doesn't belong in comedy.
This brought tears to my eyes.
My friend used it on their social network profile and I just had to search it.
I love when I have to search things from social network profile.
Number 5, you deserve the world and I know I can't give that to you.
So I'll give you the next best thing.
My world.
My spore world.
My little spore world.
They're referring to my Minecraft world.
My tiny little world.
My tiny little spore characters that look like you.
It's not much, well actually it is a lot.
They're just like mutant versions of the girl.
I made you a spore.
I made some Samanthians.
And they're beautiful.
And I like to use my cursor to hover over their bodies.
They're actually at war with the Blordos right now.
Just be really careful when you launch the world, okay?
Because they might go extinct.
Right now they're actually colonizing a native species right now.
So just give them a little time before you...
They're very violent.
Also, they have penises.
Every single one of them.
They have gigantic penises.
They have giant dicks.
Listen, I don't know. The modeling really got away from me.
It was supposed to be.
It's more of an impressionist thing.
I was trying to model your legs.
But then it turned out that they only had.
Then I realized your legs look like penises.
And so that's why the character has
three penises for legs.
And he has Arnold Schwarzenegger's face.
Kind of just on accident.
I hit random.
And the whole body is a penis.
body is a penis and I'm sorry yeah and look I'm sorry and I'm gonna be straight
up with you I also made a whole it's just it's more it's a Hulk I made a Hulk
listen I made a Hulk in the game please don't be mad at me listen the he's not
gonna jump out of the computer he's in the penis body is just it's just it's
evolutionarily efficient okay spores a game about evolution and about improving
upon your creations and I just found that's the best I age you up 30 years
This is what you'll look like when we're in you know the big 50 anniversary, you know what I mean?
Cuz I'm gonna cryogenically freeze you
Because I'm gonna surgically turn you into a monster because you're 98 years old and you're my girlfriend
Anyway, baby, happy anniversary happy happy six months anniversary
Number six if you held up 11 roses into a mirror they go with the fucking roses again
Yeah, come up with a new thing guys. Yeah, come up with something else. Yeah, how about that? Let's come up with the new one
Yeah, all right if you okay if you were in a room with
Adolf Hitler and you had a gun with one bullet I
Would buy you a dozen roses
regardless of what you did with the
If we did a DNA test and found out you were a hundred percent monkey, I'd still fuck you.
I just wouldn't tell anyone.
And I wouldn't tell you.
Yeah, if I found out that you were a mutant you could still be my girlfriend, but I would you my family couldn't know about it.
Yeah, if you were a rose and I was a rose
- And we were both roses and you were made out of chocolate
and a kiss.
- I would eat you up.
- And it's Valentine's Day.
- If I gave you a kiss on Valentine's Day,
100 roses, a million chocolate bars, and a heart.
- And we're going to CVS and we're gonna get
a teddy bear from CZ.
We're gonna get Plan B from CVS.
- 'Cause last night I busted inside of you
and you were a rose.
- We went crazy last night.
- And we went-- - Oh, we went crazy last night.
- And we're gonna get plan B.
- One plan B, please.
(laughing)
- To the CVS pharmacist.
- Let me get one plan B, oh!
- You sounded like the count.
- I am the count.
I'm doing the count. - One plan B!
Ah, ah, ah, ah!
(laughing)
- Girl, I could never leave you.
I'm gonna love you for 100 days.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
I wish you were my sister so that I could have grown up with you.
Real shit.
There is a kid.
I wish I was your uncle so I could have seen you grow into the beautiful woman you are today.
Real shit beautiful bitch.
There was a kid in my high school who was in my study that I got a credit for.
And he, it was for kids with like ADD and very dumb kids.
he uh his last name was Upton and someone was like hey are you not much what's up with you
but he uh he said someone was like are you related to Kate Upton he went no but i wish i was
yeah i wish i was one of the i wish i was her peeping cousin i wish i was your cousin hey
"Hey, Cousin Caleb, you wanna come to the Sports Illustrated swimsuit shoot with me today?"
"Yeah, Cousin Kate."
I just remember him saying that, and they had cubbies, like study cubbies, and I was
like in one of them, and I poked my head out of it, and I looked at him, and I went, "You
wish she was your cousin so you could fuck her."
Air horn.
Another evidence of an air horn moment right there.
He goes to the bathroom, he goes to the bathroom, he's like, "Please God, please make me Kate
Upton's cousin."
And then he wakes up the next day and doesn't notice anything different.
And then he like, eats breakfast, walks to school, gets into class, and you're like,
"Dude, nice huge fucking tits."
Nice jumbo naturals, bro.
Yeah.
"Nice huge fucking jiggly tits in your bikini, dude.
You look incredible.
Are you Kate Upton's cousin?"
look exactly like her tits Wow boy oh yeah you're you guys you got to see my
cousin do I think that happened oh yeah you're going boy you know you're here
is buying a number seven God was showing off when he created you yeah God was
like hey check this shit what a fucking show off yeah check this shit out yeah I
I put a PS2 in this bitch.
[Laughs]
Yeah.
I put big ass feet on this bitch.
Let's see what the least amount of brain cells I can put in this thing and still make it
functional.
Yeah.
How small is stupid canality?
Hey, I was like, yeah.
Hey, angels, I had a crazy idea.
What if we gave this person like a club foot and little dinosaur arms?
Yeah.
I can make this person and still capable of being loved
Like that God, why are you still in the workshop one of the angels bet that I couldn't make a bitch with a yellow clit
Put the crayons down God
That's how God does it he puts it's a piece of like paper and it's not like a stick
He does it he does it puts all the things
Basically his hand looks like a person and he doesn't hurt
He does a turkey hand with his hand, but it makes a guy and then he colors it in
Uh-huh. Yeah. Their comment on this one says, one of them says, "Nice! Definitely
gonna say this to my crush. Wish me luck! I love you, Lauren!"
Lovely. It will even work with a Christian girl. Even with a Christian girl. That's the biggest
concern is that they don't... Oh no, this went badly for someone. Most of these have not worked on
Christians yeah but I think this is the only one that would work I'm just
scared to say it but YOLO this comment says it's made her laugh the whole
dinner time oh damn he said that to his mom yeah he did he's making mom he's
making very how to convert your atheist girlfriend into Christianity 101
Uh, my girl is an atheist.
Well, that's a, yeah buddy, that's a loss, dude.
Yeah, that's a no.
Sorry to hear that.
Sorry your girlfriend doesn't have, uh, is not shined down upon by God's light.
Yeah.
Sorry your girlfriend isn't a follower of the powerful and righteous minister Farrakhan.
Yeah, sorry.
Sucks to suck.
Sorry that your girlfriend does not believe in God.
that your girlfriend does not enjoy hell white devil yeah yeah here's a comment
all I'm saying the comment that says what do you say if she's Islamic Jesus Allah
not Muslim Islamic specifically you say what up hey bitch what a bitch what up
bitch so be stupid Muslim bitch what do you think about this pickup line she's
like yeah it's cool I don't know who you are yeah that's right
please please leave me alone I'm trying to work at the bank I'm not Muslim my
name is Katie I am Irish I'm Irish Catholic I'm Irish Catholic I work at
the bank please all the same it's all the same to me it's true you just look
really cool. Yeah, basically every religion is the same to me. Yeah, basically it's the
problem for all of our wars. Basically it's the reason why the world sucks. If there was
no God, everybody would have two TVs. So you're telling me we freaking worship a carpenter
who turned into a zombie on the rabbit's day? I'm sorry, what was Mr. Bible smoking when
when he wrote this stuff.
- Yeah.
- Happy zombie Jesus day.
- Easter, I like to call it, I like to call it zombie.
- A guy completely missing the point.
So what, we're supposed to believe that a bunny
came back to life on Christmas?
(laughing)
- Yeah, okay.
- So a bunny is the son of God.
- Okay.
- Oh, and he's made of chocolate?
- Yeah, likely story.
- Okay.
- So wait.
- That's in the Bible?
- When I bite into God, he's hollow on the inside?
- Wait, what the hay?
What the what? - What the hay?
What the hay is this?
Get this crap out of here.
- A lot of these are God.
Number eight, if I died and God asked me
what I'd like to come back as,
I'd say a tear so I can be born on your eyes,
rolled in your cheek, and die on your lips.
- That's what I say to Pat.
I text Patrick that every morning when I wake up.
- Yeah, we have been getting pretty sexual
in the group texts with Patrick.
- Yeah, you guys--
- There's something about him--
- I'm irresistible to you guys.
- There's something about him that drives me crazy.
It's true.
There's something about you, dude.
I think it's, no, it's not that.
It's something else.
It's just how beautiful you are.
- Yeah, you're gorgeous.
- You have beautiful big lips and a thick--
- And a beautiful mind.
- And you're thick.
And also you have these arms.
Oh God, I just wanna--
- I got arms, for sure.
- I just wanna lick you up like a fruit roll-up.
- I'm not a fruit roll-up.
I just want to turn you into a caramel.
- I'm gonna go out with you for a few years
and then marry you, I'm thinking.
(laughing)
- I'm making a plan.
- Yeah, pretty much I'm gonna do it first.
- I'm writing up a blueprint for our life together.
- Yeah, I think I'm gonna marry Patrick.
- Yeah, I'm thinking I'm gonna wait a few years
and then marry Patrick.
- This is not gonna happen.
- Hold on, let me get my to-do list.
- Yeah. - Marry Patrick.
- One second, let me check my Blackberry real quick.
I think I have something on the calendar for tomorrow.
Oh yeah, I have a meeting with Patrick
where it's called a proposal meeting
where I ask him to freaking marry me sexually.
- Wait, I'm getting a message on my Palm Pilot.
- I'm not gonna get sexually married to you guys.
- It's reminding me to marry Patrick.
- Hold on a second, I have a sticky note on my mirror
and it says, "Today's the big day.
"You're gonna marry Patrick in a sexual way."
- Patrick, listen to me.
I'm gonna offer my wife as a dowry
and you and me are gonna get married.
- Then what?
Then what the hell?
- In America.
- Me and Patrick are gonna go to Wendy's for our honeymoon
and we're gonna do it in the bathroom.
in the bedroom.
- Mine is already arranged, dude.
You really wanna buck tradition like that
and disrespect your elders?
- Why would I do that?
- Because your parents arranged us to get married.
- My parents did not arrange us to get married.
- They did.
They said this is-- - They didn't.
- They said you are one of the most--
- They did not.
- You are the only person who's been worthy
of Patrick's love.
Some girl named Cameron came by
and tried to take our son, but we said no,
and we're saying yes to you.
And so I want you to know, if you marry him,
your father will condone you.
If you marry me, your father will disown you.
He'll eat his head now.
- And that's some bread now.
- Patrick already agreed to marry me
and have a 1,000 year trip around the world as a honeymoon.
- That was on opposite day.
- And to have love every night.
- He said we would have love.
He said we would have love every single night.
- Stop fighting over me.
- No dude, you're too good.
You're too good.
I want to have a honeymoon suite
where I lead you to the bed with salt and vinegar
- Patrick, if you choose me, Patrick, if you choose me,
we're gonna have a mansion with 1000 rooms in it.
What do you say to that?
- If you choose me, I will blow your mind.
My tongue is three feet long.
(laughing)
I will do all sorts of freaky frog fucky shit to you
if you just marry me.
Just sign on the dotted line
and let me invest in you with my body.
I already forged a marriage certificate.
You forged it?
Yeah, so we're technically already married.
No, it's not gonna happen.
I already submitted it.
You know what, I just wanna mold you
like a porn star with a fleshlight.
I just wanna get a signature Patrick Fleshlight.
I don't even wanna get married anymore.
I just wanna put a bunch of mud on your holes
and then just get it, just get accurate.
Listen, all I want, accurate hole, and then I'm out.
I just wanna-- I'll leave you alone.
I'm gonna switch around your different anatomies
and get acquainted with different parts of you.
- I'm gonna make you suck a french fry out my wiener.
- This is disgusting.
This is all disgusting to me.
- No it's not, it's marriage and it's love.
- It's all disgusting to me.
- I'm gonna play the bongos on your zones.
- I don't wanna fucking marry you anymore, dude.
Good, I don't even, I don't even, listen to me.
I don't even want to have a beautiful marriage
with you anymore with a kid that looks like half of me,
half of you, split down the middle, okay?
I don't want that anymore.
Yeah dude, you wanna eat poop instead.
It's good that you don't want that.
You wanna eat poop instead.
Dude, I don't wanna retire with you.
I don't wanna live on a golf course and go outside everyday.
You would not live on a golf course.
And I cook hamburgers for me and I cook a pineapple for you on the grill because you
recently turned vegetarian.
He recently turned Jamaican.
You recently became Jamaican.
You converted to Jamaicanism.
I don't wanna have that life.
Jamaicanism!
You did.
He did.
Our son converted to some kind of fucking Jamaicanism. I don't know. He's at Pratt right now, and he's having a bad time.
Yeah. Hey Patrick, Patrick.
What?
Bob Marley was showing off when he created you.
Yeah, real shit, jaw was, jaw snapped on you.
Patrick, if I died and Chet Hanks asked me what I'd like to come back as, I'd say a tear.
I'd say "Boo-yuck-a-shaw." I'd say "Boo-yuck-a-boo-yuck-a-boo-yuck-a!"
I'd say "Urrrrr." "Urrrrr."
Number nine. I'd say "Tingon Massive."
"Big Up." "Big Up." "Big Up the Tingon Massive."
It is sad that Hank's family lost both parents to COVID and a son to Jamaicanism.
It is really sad.
One of the most violent religions.
Yeah, kind of like the Kennedy's yeah, I just drop in like flies. Yeah, I
Put a tear in the ocean when you find it. I'll stop what is with all these tears
And why love is about women girls girls love to cry. They're addicted to it. Yeah, it's true. Yeah, I love to cry
Yeah, that's what I mean think about sex right the two parts of the body cry on each other
Yeah, that's sure. That's what my that's what my scientist teacher. Wait a great way class
Wait a girl's thing is supposed to cry a girl's thingy be crying
Supposed to have wet on it, huh?
Hold girls thing it girl thing. You're gonna go cry. Oh
Girl thing went crying man. Oh
massive massive dear
Chet Hanks describing
Having sex yeah, yeah
Condom too big Oh
Condom went massive on it. Oh
Jet Hanks would not I don't think he would I'm gonna scroll to the last one on this list
No, he has a really big baggy condom like a rasta hat
Damn there's like so many on this list. I'm trying to find the last one. There's over a hundred
There's so many comments on all of them - damn
We could do a part two on this one
But I don't think we should because I think this apparently is originally created meant a man with two heads four legs
Forearms and two hearts. He thought they would be too powerful
So he split man in two allowing them to spend their lives searching for the other half
I'm so happy that you turned out to be mine. Is that so this one if you like Percy Jackson trust me on this
Someone says screw Zeus. It's all about Poseidon
Someone says you're the pad made of my Darth Vader and try that one on Patrick. Yeah. Hey Patrick
You're the pad made of my Darth Vader
Yeah, that's right. You're the pad made of Darth Vader. You're gonna die and I'm gonna wait you Patrick Patrick
You're my fortune to my cookie
Grow up number 343
Go hey, buddy. Go to school and grow up and why not?
You make me feel like an airplane strong enough to carry 100 people yet light enough to fly with the clouds
Hey Cameron grow up much. Yeah. Yeah, I do actually every day. Hey grow up a lot around here much
Hey, hey Patrick what you're my best friend, sweetheart
And I'm sorry for taking you for granted at times
But I would move heaven and earth to let you know that I love you. I'm empty without you
I trust and love you like I trust the Sun will rise in the morning and set at night
- All right.
I don't accept that.
- My penis craving you like a bear crave meat.
It's as simple as this.
(laughing)
That's just how you gotta pick--
- Does it say that?
- That's how you pick a bitch up.
No, I invented that out of my brain.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
- Hey, Patrick.
- I wanna take a picture of things on you.
- Patrick, I'm gonna get in you like a gorilla
and wiggle in there like a worm, all right?
And we're gonna get--
- All right, you're gonna be an apple
and I'm gonna be a very smart library type worm
here in a minute so you better be sweet to the core Patrick you're Patrick and
I'm a pair of swimming shorts basically your Elmo and I'm the guy who's piloting
Elmo there's no guy piloting Elmo I'm the guy fucking Elmo and your Elmo I'm
the guy fucking Elmo basically your Elmo and in four seconds I'm the guy fucking
Elmo. And then you start counting down. Four, three, two, one, Elmo! I'm at number 600 and I still haven't got to the end of this
list. I'm still scrolling to try to find the last one. Basically you're Rap and
I'm Eminem. So basically it's like that. So basically that's just how it is. So
Basically I've picked you up and you're my boyfriend now.
So if you guys believe that I'm Patrick's boyfriend,
I want you to go online and post #CalebIsPatrick'sBoyfriend.
And if you believe that Cameron is Patrick's boyfriend,
I want you to go online and post #BlueLivesMatter.
So let's see who--
I'm gonna get way more hashtags than you.
No, let's see which--
Yeah, I think that's a whole lot.
And you have to be following the podcast account.
No you don't, no you don't.
- Yeah, you do. - No, you don't.
- Let's see who gets more hashtags.
It's gonna, you know, I mean, it could be close.
Who knows, I don't wanna--
- I already have a huge,
I already have a lot of people on my side.
- No, I think there's-- - Yeah, you kinda,
you kinda fucked that one up.
- No, I-- - Okay, well,
- You just can't bring a really stupid--
- I think you're going to take backseas.
- I knew he would take backseas.
- Yep, this was all, it was all to prove--
- Number 825 is good morning, my love.
That one always works.
I'm still scrolling.
I can't get to the end of this.
I can't get to the end.
You guys keep talking.
We should do a part two or something.
Hey, hey, guys, guys.
No, these aren't very good.
Most of them literally are just like, this one says, "You're the chocolate of the chocolation
by the chocolate rolling in my lips."
All right, we can end on this.
We can end on this.
No, I need to find the last one.
We're not ending on anything yet.
No, you know, this list is never ending like my love for Patrick.
I made it to a thousand, but it just says a hundred.
This list is never ending like my love for Patrick.
And I'm going to love Patrick.
I'm gonna let baby let me love you down Patrick.
Yeah, me too.
That plus one.
I just want to get Patrick on the floor.
I feel like if I could get Patrick on the floor, Justin Timberlake style, and we could
be on the floor together, then maybe I could make him fall in love with me.
I don't know.
That probably won't happen.
What was that?
Did you just pull on the spring of your arm again?
He just pulled it.
I accidentally hit the spring again.
He busted a coil.
So, okay.
That spring in Patrick's body just got loose.
So there's the spring.
There's the spring on the arm, and I've done this in an episode before, but check this out.
We can end on this.
This is- You are my personal bomb.
If I don't see you, my heart will explode.
There's a- okay, so if I ever accidentally do this again, check out for this sound.
I can't find the end of this list.
I'm at 1500.
And it hasn't ended yet.
I'm going to stop recording, and you just keep doing it by yourself.
No.
Alright, bye everybody.
Bye.
I'm going to keep doing it.
I haven't stopped recording it.
Oh, I found the end, but you guys can't comment on it.
The last one is, "When the sky falls apart and the stars disappear, as I take my final
breath the last thing I would think of would be you."
And that's dedicated to Patrick.
Go online and message Patrick and ask him to be my boyfriend.
Bye everybody.