You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts for the heartless.
Crap monster.
My question is, do you guys think that this is a cool look to me?
It looks pretty cool to me.
Yeah.
I think I look cool. I walk down the street, everybody's high-fiving me now.
Yeah. So describe your look. Describe your look to the listeners.
I am wearing a black do-rag and a gray tank top.
Yeah.
Yeah, which is what they hand you when you move to Queens.
And also a Volvo with the Puerto Rican flag wrapped around it.
Yeah, dude, you got a Volvo now.
Yeah, I got a Volvo.
I got a Puerto Rican Volvo installed.
They install it to you when you move to Queens, dude.
They turn you into a queen.
But it's just so hot.
I have to, this is why everyone...
You have to dress like that.
They're dressed like this because it's so hot.
Yeah, it just makes sense.
I mean, and I always, yeah, I mean, this is just what people in New York wear.
And now I finally understand.
The do-rag, I didn't realize a do-rag is just to stop you from sweating.
Yeah.
I don't think that's what it's for.
No, it is.
I think it's for waves.
Waves of sweat that are cascading down your face.
That's why it's called a wave cap because it caps the waves so that they don't hit the
rest of your body.
The wife beater is also for sweat resistance.
It clings so tightly to you that it actually clogs all your pores.
You know in England they call those a jersey.
Better name.
Better name than wife beater for sure.
What do they call it?
They're both based off a guy from Jersey who's a wife beater.
That's true, that's why they call them.
too easy to make fun of, especially now that I'm a New Yorker. It's too easy, dude. I've
never, ever been there, but God, it sucks. They don't even have bodega. I was at my local
bodega yesterday, and it's just so amazing. It's like a French salon. It's just the melding
of the minds. Everybody's there asking for a BEC, you know, and I'm asking what that
is. And I'm wearing this exact outfit. You know, the durag and the gray and white beater
walking into the bodega.
I do want to see you walk outside in that outfit.
I will.
I'll see how that goes.
I'm going to be one of the famous Times Square people, like the Spider-Man.
Yeah, you're the Times Square person, but you're just Jamie Kennedy from Malibu's Most Wanted.
Yeah, I have gone full...
You're like Elmo, but you're out there, you're going like, "Yeah, what's up player?"
I have gone full JKMMW.
This is my look now.
Jedi Knight Malibu's Most Wanted.
It's one of the early 2000s Star Wars games.
No, but I have been looking, just looking like this for a couple days now and we went and
got a locker today for our apartment.
Yeah.
Yeah, I did not, I wasn't wearing the do-rag, but I was wearing the wife beater and I did
not, the guy was not getting good vibes off of me.
Yeah, well, yeah, I mean, fuck it.
Yeah, he was like in Park Slope and he was like, he's definitely, he was gonna call the
police on me.
Yeah.
That's what they do to people like you, dude.
Yeah, that's why it's so hard for people like me in New York City because the police
The police are always harassing us for wearing white beards
And hanging out in bodega's yeah, it's fucking annoying dude my favorite bodega is the empire state building ever been to that one
One of the most powerful bodega's in uh, the united states. Yeah. Another great one is the one in the statue of liberty. Yeah
Yeah. See, because you can get like Cracker Jacks and a little Statue of Liberty there.
Exactly. So what I understand about a bodega is that it is a place where you can get pizza.
Yeah, exactly. So 7-Eleven is a bodega.
Yeah, 7-Eleven is the world's bodega.
Pizza Hut is a bodega. Chuck E. Cheese is a bodega junior.
And that's just, you know, I'm learning and I'm growing as a person every day in this beautiful city.
Yeah.
Yeah. The rule here now is like the subway is for essential workers only.
And I just want to roll on that bitch looking like this so bad.
And then when someone asks, I'm like, "I'm a nurse, obviously. What do you fucking think?"
They really did the subways for essential workers only?
That's what when you well I wrote it yesterday but uh luckily I was wearing a suit but basically
when you walk on like a voiceover thing is like the subway is for essential workers only
please do not travel but I don't think they actually I don't think they actually check
they do yeah yeah they would if I went on it now but yeah I think I'm okay.
You have to show them your essential workers card.
Apparently an essential job is being like a white dude in JNCO jeans walking up and down
the subway cart asking for money.
I didn't know that but apparently that's an essential job.
That's an essential part of the New York ecosystem.
That's true.
You take that out.
Yeah.
At least one of those guys.
He travels between the cars.
That's not something people do in Boston but they do it here where people just walk between
the cars because it's cool.
It's so much cooler, like in every movie I've ever seen.
Where there's a chase?
Yeah, they go through the subway cars.
Yeah, here everybody does that.
Everybody clings to the top of the subway car when they go under a tunnel.
They stand on top and they jump over when they go under a tunnel.
Yeah, exactly, to escape a guy who wasn't quite fast enough ducking so he gets hit by
the tunnel.
Yeah, he gets hit by a traffic sign going by.
But you don't see it because it's a PG-13 movie.
They actually have turnstiles on top of the train,
'cause so many people do jump off of bridges
to land on top of the train.
- Yeah, that's like, they actually have a turnstile
on every bridge, too.
- Yeah.
- Because you could jump off the bridge.
- They wanna make some money off people
committing suicide for once.
- Yeah, exactly.
(laughing)
- That's how they're gonna get--
- Listen, you're allowed to jump off this bridge,
you're allowed to jump off this bridge,
but you have to pay 25 cents first.
It's very cheap.
- Yeah, it's a very cheap--
- It's honestly a pretty good deal.
- Yeah, it's very cheap 'cause if it was too expensive,
people wouldn't kill themselves.
- Yeah, but they're gonna raise that in like two years.
You know, they're gonna fucking--
- Yeah, they keep raising it, dude.
- Ugh, it's the worst.
- Back in my day, it was 10 cents.
- 10 cents to kill yourself off a bridge.
- It used to cost a dime to kill yourself.
Now it's damn near a nickel.
- Yeah, they got you putting all kinds of coins up in there.
- And if you try to jump the turnstile,
there's a cop there who's gonna shoot you in the head.
- Yeah, and now they want you to do this
contactless pay on it with your phone.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, they have an app now.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
Ugh.
Disgusting.
Please.
Yesterday I was, somebody did try to assassinate me on a bridge with a firework.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I was walking over the Manhattan Bridge.
Yesterday me and Jana went on a 10 mile walk.
Wow.
And I wore vans.
Nice.
That's very smart.
Yeah, I got fucked up.
But while we were crossing over into, as soon as we like step foot in Chinatown, giant firework
explodes right next to my head that somebody shot from the ground.
Whoa.
Damn.
And then they ran away like cowards before I could kill them.
So but I was going to and retaliate for them attempting to kill me and my bride.
Yeah I would have teleported to them but that was just me.
Yeah I pretty much thought about that.
I almost spent my throwing knife but then I was like you know I'll never get that back.
Yeah.
You know that'll be in some evidence locker for the next 20 years and that thing was given
to me by a shinobi.
Yeah.
a shinobi who looks exactly like me right now and he lives in uh, Astoria.
What have you guys been up to? I've been up to fucking nothing, been packing.
Packing the shit up. You got, you got way too many boxes I think.
Nah, nah there's so much shit in this apartment. You think you have that many things?
We needed, yeah dude, we couldn't like, when we first moved here we couldn't walk around.
No, you know what it is, is this place is so fucking small
that we need like, we got like a bunch of small boxes
so it doesn't like crowd the place up.
The new place is small?
No, this place is small.
The new place is bigger. Oh, this place is small.
Yeah.
But it's the same amount of stuff,
but you're just, you just think smaller boxes will...
We got small boxes and medium and large.
Okay, you got small, medium and large.
But what is your rationale for getting small boxes instead of large boxes?
Can you admit before that it's going to be the same?
We've been transporting them, we've been just like packing shit up and then putting it in
Dom's parents' garage.
So it's easier to put small boxes in her car and bring them to the garage.
Okay.
We arrived at somewhat of an explanation.
Yeah, that's good enough for me.
See, that's the first time I've made sense.
Yeah, that was incredible.
Yeah.
Congrats, pal.
They must have turned the AC on in Pat's building for this episode.
Yeah.
No, dude, I'm still...
I need to get somewhere with AC to record soon because every fucking episode I've been
chicken brained.
Yeah.
Yeah, people want the chicken brain episode.
You don't want it.
People want it, but they don't want it.
You don't want the chicken brain episode.
I promise.
I promise you, you do not.
It's not good for you.
I'm not sure if I have it or not.
I might have it on a hard drive, but I refuse to check.
I don't want to go back and listen.
It's just not good.
It's imagine--
- We might as well have been all wearing
a KFC bucket on our heads.
- Yeah.
Imagine like the worst episode
that you've heard of this podcast
and then add like 50% more dead air to it.
- Yeah.
- I had to imagine--
- About two pounds of chicken.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Yeah, two pounds of chicken
and then me saying something about the chicken.
- Also, Cameron's like first time having fried chicken,
which is like somebody's first time having a cigarette.
Like they vomit.
Anytime somebody has a KFC for the first time,
like yeah.
- Cameron had to leave.
Cameron like went home for a little bit.
- He ate one piece and to teach him a lesson
we should have made him eat the entire
bag of meatloaf. - I did not eat one,
I think I ate two pieces.
- It is the one year anniversary of the chicken episode.
- Yeah, today.
We did record the chicken brain episode one year ago today.
- I did get an Instagram notification.
- I might have to fuck around with some chicken today.
yet and i were talking about it
yeah i might have to do it in a spot
yeah which is another word for bodyguard
near i've fungal i'd my nasty he has slept on my neck weird and fucked it up
yeah you need to stop sleeping uh... pencil dives
uh... yet
yeah i thought he was diving on your bed and getting stuck at least sleeping
straight up i do a handstand to fall asleep and then sometimes my arms give
out
and i land on my head
- Hey, dude, I could've snapped my neck in my sleep.
- That's why you're so smart,
because the blood has been pooling in your brain for 20 years.
- If I bend my neck right when I'm sleeping,
it restricts the blood from leaving my brain,
so it all stays in there and gets smarter,
and it practices being in my brain,
and it's increasing my insulin.
- You do some brain practice.
- I've been doing brain practices lately.
- Yeah, that's why my grandma, she had a brain bleed,
but for that last hour,
she was like the smartest bitch in my family.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause when that blood gets moving up there,
i'm she's doing math problems and stuff in the hospital bed
and we like we need to get you a job and then she died
yeah
is pretty funny
i've been anyone grandma's die
yet she's i still this way theater from her
yet after she died she she's she's she's white beater do read combo to me and
we'll
yeah those who are here is uh...
is actually her giant bro
you better take that that's what i'm not doing
That's not cool.
- You better take that back about Catherine DeVita.
Thank you.
- I take it back.
- What are your grandparents' names?
- Mine?
- Yeah.
- John and Ruth on my dad's side,
and then Bob and Nancy on my mom's side,
and Everybody But John Is Dead.
- Nice.
- Well, that's such a great young adult novel name.
- Everybody But John Is Dead.
(laughing)
Right?
John is in like blood.
- Yeah.
I've talked about John on here. Is he the one who meowed like a cat? No. Oh yeah, he's the one who ran away.
He's the one who ran away from home and lived in a boxcar. Yeah, he's the one. He packed up a bindle.
Yeah, he packed up a bindle full of kombucha and like, smelled himself. He just poured kombucha into a cloth.
- Put shit into a bag.
- And then wrapped it up in a bandana
and put it on a stick in the middle of winter
and was like, hey, I might be home late.
- I'm off to ride the rails.
I'm off to see the world.
- I'm off to do this kombucha.
- I'm off to do kombucha.
- I'm fucked, dude.
- He's boofing kombucha.
- He's boofing it.
- Where is your microphone?
Do you even have it?
- Yeah, I do.
there
no it's not a lot of time no it sounds fine i think there's so much background
noise dude yourself
my
and
no i'm not
i'm not going to pick up any background well so clearly in the last hour
episodes audio power in this one
so yes i'll never run episodes audio
once in my life is i'm too smart suite of you
and i care about the fans more than you guys
You do not care.
You don't care about anything except yourself, dude.
I don't care.
I don't really care about anything.
You're so selfish.
I've been doing a lot of Squidward Joker lately.
I've been doing, like, "You wanna know how I got this big blue nose?
Well, my father was a squidward."
"You wanna know how I learned this clarinet?
He put the clarinet in my mouth and said, "Why so?"
He sighed up, "Why so, Squidward?"
Oh, fuck.
Yeah, I've been really, really making myself happy with that one.
That's how I've been getting through the days.
I used to know a sponge.
I used to work at a hamburger store.
He put his claws in my mouth and he said, "Squidward, why don't you smile more?"
He put his claws in my mouth and he said, "Where's me first dollar?"
I had a boss, used to curse a lot, said, "Eeeeee!"
Remember that episode?
I remember that episode.
Wait, he didn't say that.
That's what the swear is.
Yeah, he curses with the doll.
He swears.
dot he has a salty man he swears like a dolphin
uh... fucking dolphin
now i know
what does the joker even say
uh...
google gaga
it that's what he says
i love the joker says
squidward says uh... ron jeremy was arrested and charged for sexually
assaulting
that's what squirrel is a thing
on this man
but i don't hear me
ron jeremy has been uh... charged with four counts of sexual assault
wall
all the issues here is a really great here's a really great great week here
ron jeremy was arrested and charged for sexually assaulting twenty one fewer
women than trump
thanks dude
while
while yeah that's pretty good yeah i know that makes it that makes it uh...
I know, no.
I mean, so that's bad.
Yeah, no, no, no.
They're going to use that in court.
I'm with you guys.
We should release Ron Jeremy.
Mm-hmm.
Anybody who has less than 25 counts, I think they should be free.
Hey, if Trump gets away with it.
Because he's the president.
So also, Ron Jeremy should be the president now.
That's also how it should work.
Yeah, no, because it's fewer.
It's fewer.
And when you justify it that way, he should have the lowest.
and we don't justify it that way and he's kind of like it only gets to be one sixth
president because he only did one sixth of it
uh... so actually people have to hit twenty five to become president yeah it's
like a kill streak
that's like the tactical nuke president
uh...
oh yeah pat you have to do your new character on this episode
see oh fuck
pat we promised the fans pat will do
I know, but I texted you this morning. I already told you. What happened?
Patrick has to do it to reveal his new character, Homie Hamburger, that he's been developing.
No, no, I can't. I don't even...
You can. You absolutely have to.
No, I texted you this morning. I lost all my notes on Homie Hamburger.
Did you lose... were they in a Moleskine or something?
Yes.
See, you know, you gotta use an app, dude. You gotta use Evernote.
Yeah.
You can't be using Moleskine for stuff like that.
like that. I like using my micron pens. So how'd you lose them?
Subway. Subway sandwich or subway train? On the way to subway.
On the way to subway? Yeah. Did it fall out of your big pocket with a hole in it?
No, I think I might have left it on the 7-eleven counter on the way to subway.
You were reading, you were testing the new character on the 7-11 cashier?
Yeah.
You left the notebook with the accent.
That's what happened, yeah.
Can I pitch you my new character?
You remember what it sounded like?
Yeah, come on.
Uh, no.
I had a waveform drawn on the notebook.
That you were gonna mimic?
Yeah, that I was gonna mimic and do the voice of.
Well, do your best.
Did the waveform spell out anything cool?
It said homie hamburger.
Alright, well say it.
say it. Well I don't remember. Type out Homie Hamburger and recreate it. Yeah look at that.
It was a special waveform. It was like the Nintendo Labo Piano and I have to... Look
I just want to first of all I want to apologize. Did it sound like this? Homie Hamburger. Did
it sound like that? No. Okay so did it just sound like this? Homie Hamburger. Did it sound
like that? It was closer. Okay so something like Homie Hamburger. Was it like that? Just
Just tell me if I'm getting closer or further away.
Keep going closer.
Okay, so is it like, "Hey, I want a hamburger!"
Is it like that?
A little bit closer.
Getting closer, okay.
Is it like, "Hey, I want a hamburger!"
Is it like that?
I think that might be it.
I think you should...
I think, wait, now...
All right, do it.
Wait, Cameron, now say, "Hey, guys, we're gonna...
Hey, homies, we're gonna go get a hamburger."
"Hey, homies, we're gonna get a hamburger!"
That was it!
That was the way it was.
Now say, "If I don't get a hamburger, I'm gonna go get a hamburger."
That was it.
"Hey homie, we're gonna get a hamburger!"
That was it!
That was the way it was.
Now say if I don't get a hamburger, I'm gonna bust a cap in your ass.
"If I don't get a hamburger, I'm gonna bust a cap in your ass!"
That's exactly it.
Does that sound like Homie Hamburg?
That was Homie Hamburg, wow.
Thank you, thank you Cameron for performing Homie Hamburg for us.
Yeah, I'm actually a sounds detective, so I've been working on stuff like cases like that for years.
Really? That makes sense, despite being the producer.
How did you get that job?
I basically detected a bunch of sounds and then the police contacted me and said we'd like you to work for us
Well, and I accepted immediately so you work for the police. Yeah
Whoa, what?
What you guys didn't know that?
Take one good look at me and tell me that I'm gonna be happy with that
Do I look like I would fucking do a podcast with the police yeah
Yeah.
He looked like an undercover cop.
The worst undercover cop ever.
A white dude walking in in a grey tank top, a grey white beater and a do-rag.
Be like, "Hey, what's up man?
I'm at the bodega.
Are you guys selling drugs here?"
Oh man.
Oh man. Hey man, have you guys seen any guns around?
Just immediately getting your ass beat for that accent.
Yeah, I put mascara on my, like, on the hair on my upper lip to make it look like I have
a thin pencil mustache. God damn.
Yeah. Bad showing. My Blue Lives Matter tattoo showing through my chest.
Punisher logo, with the confederate flag.
Hey man, do you guys sell loose cigarettes?
I just want to put one in my ear.
I'm just gonna put it in the wave cap.
I'm just gonna have it hanging out of the wave cap.
That's all I need it for.
I'm looking at that one photoshop of LeBron wearing the durag with the cigarette in it
and trying to match it exactly.
Yeah, you're looking at your phone up to the bathroom mirror in the bodega and going like,
"Oh, come on, my brothers in the force need this.
Come on, come on, we're so close."
Yeah.
I have like a full-length XLR cable attached to a Zoom on my chest.
wearing like a GoPro on your head yeah yeah and the poor like 70 year old
Mexican lady who just makes sandwiches at the store so confused
she thinks I'm one of her son's friends your XLR cable is like going all the way
like outside to like a huge like it's plugged into a van it's plugged into like a huge like
Marshall stack that's being like pointed at the police station.
[laughter]
So they can hear everything you're saying and so can everyone else.
You're talking into a paper cup on a string and there's a police officer
outside with a cup to his ear. And then I get back to the precinct
and they're like, "Yeah, it turns out today is the day we
defunded the plainclothes officers program in New York."
Fuck, man. I worked so hard on that accent.
Yeah, I took classes in that.
I worked so hard. I listened to the Cheech and Chong Mexican American song for three hours.
Yeah.
I downloaded a Daddy Yankee album.
For nothing.
All right, what's our list today? This list is on ranker.com and it's called the
head the headline of the of the of the article if you look on the in the at the
website itself it says Patrick is a terrible friend of SpongeBob if you just
pay attention but if you look at like that at the top at the tab it is
actually a list it says 14 reasons why Patrick is a terrible friend of
SpongeBob and if I'm not mistaken this is though these 14 reasons are what white
nationalists are referring to when they use that number. I think it is yeah.
There's a there's a tab here on the side that says winners and losers and it
looks like today Barry Pepper moved down. So Barry Pepper sorry sorry man you're
today's uh you're the Ranker.com loser. Oh shit.
day. Faith Walper moved up. Oh good, good for Faith Walper. So did Black Adam. Who's Black
Adam? That's the villain from Shazam. Ah, okay. Yeah. He's Egyptian. I thought it was just
how suburban white teenagers refer to their one black friend. Yeah, that's what they call
Pete Wentz. Yeah. They call him Black Adam for some reason. No, they're actually doing
a new diverse reboot of Adam Ruins Everything.
And they're sending out a casting call for Black Adam.
One of the greatest names, for sure.
Patrick is a terrible friend of SpongeBob if you just pay attention.
SpongeBob SquarePants remains a beloved show with incredibly memorable characters.
One particular personality, though, seems eviler than most people realize.
In fact, he's the absolute worst.
theories about Patrick Star demonstrate he's an awful friend to Spongebob and
might even hurt his supposed pal on purpose. When it comes to Spongebob
Squarepants theories fans believe Patrick is often responsible for the title
characters perils. Patrick frequently shows how little he cares and his
relationship with Spongebob looks toxic at best and abusive at worst. It's easy
to see why many people think the smiling pink starfish is a complete psychopath.
this is awesome dude I first I thought this was gonna be like from a 13 year
old but it is like it's like a like an ex-gawker writer yeah is like well
Patrick is actually an abuser yeah this is from no 2019 it's so it's so funny
how like every stupid fucking like take like oh like the himbo's or pedophile
Dating a himbo makes you a pedophile and stuff.
It always traces back to some form of like media conversation that a person was having.
Yeah, every single time.
Like, literally, the himbos are pedophiles thing, I think, who showed me that?
It was you, because you wrote that.
It was me in the mirror, because I wrote the himbos are pedophiles.
You wrote it on a mirror.
That's how you write things like that.
It was about, so that started because they were talking about Andy from Parks and Recreation.
Yeah, dude.
Total himbo, yeah.
Dude, so fucking stupid.
Just turn the fucking TV, it's literally just people who think like, "Oh, if I criticize
media that makes me smart."
TV is real life, dude.
Yeah, I mean, it's insane that people...
People go and get six year degrees in media criticism.
And then they come away and they're like, "Neo is actually not the good guy.
The good guy was the computers."
It's like, "How fucked can you be?"
You're a messed up person.
Yeah, Patrick is actually the anti-hero.
Yeah, that was Dasani Bottle who sent me that.
Dasani Bottle?
Yeah, @thesunnybottle sent me that.
Yeah, that's my name too, actually.
We're all named... I'm the Sunny Bottle.
No, you're not. Just me and Caleb.
No, I am too.
We're both the Sunny Bottle. You're stupid Patrick.
Actually, I'm, um...
You're one of those little flavor water enhancers
'cause you can't drink plain water.
I'm Mio.
'Cause you can't even fucking handle just a plain water.
You're one of those guys who's like, "This water tastes creamy."
Yeah.
What?
You're one of those guys who thinks Nestle water tastes creamy.
me yeah does that mean yeah you're like I am this water water takes creamy why
can't I say taste who the fuck says Nestle water do you do there's no there's
guys who believe that yeah I know one of them I'm not nice
Nestle water yeah Nestle why can't I say anything right now I said Nestle it
tastes creamy's it tastes creamy there's too many minerals in it and I hate
minerals. Yeah minerals are the worst. Keep minerals out of my food. Yeah. If I wanted
to eat a rock I'd eat a fucking rock. Okay. Exactly. Yeah. Or I'd eat one of those chocolate
rocks that looks like a rock but it's chocolate. Yeah. Yeah I'll eat an orange alright. A dark
chocolate orange that I have to punch to open. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah I'll eat a bunny alright.
a chocolate bunny
so that the punch to open
yeah alley day as i'm talking about reese's peanut butter a
all-star like to
yelling at that there is a big chocolate hamburger chocolate patty and chocolate
ketchup yes sir
yali yam on coming hamburger
yeah i know i'd love to eat on a lot of our dinner tonight i'll make a pasta
yet chocolate pasta
spaghetti noodles and chocolate marinara sauce yeah yeah man yeah i'll eat a bar and a kiss
yeah a chocolate bar and chocolate kiss yeah that's right that's right damn i hate eating a
normal bar me too it's a bar my mom makes me a bar hey kids kids we're having kisses tonight
Hershey's kisses no meat kisses. We're eating a meat and vegetable kiss
Don't get your hopes up
Number one on this on this list is he makes spongebob feel ugly
Wow everyone deals with bad breath at some point
But spongebob's Sunday breath takes the cake in season 2 episode 1 something smells his breath gets so bad everyone runs away from him
Spongebob goes to his best friend for advice, but Patrick tells him people are actually running from his bad
looks. Patrick claims Spongebob needs to scream to the world about his ugliness.
Patrick even accuses Spongebob of passing ugly to him, like a contagion. Way to
crush your friend's self-esteem, Pat. Wow. I can't believe that. That's fucked up,
dude. I mean, yeah, that's something you should never do to a friend, is when their
bad breath makes an entire movie theater full of people have, um, they start
crying from the bad breath and they all run out and there's, and fires start and
stuff and then you say it's because they're ugly that's that's abuser
behavior. If there's one thing I would never do is call anybody I know
especially not my close friends fat or ugly. You would never call your friend fat?
Never no no and so I think that's kind of you know that we're seeing a pattern
emerge here from Patrick and I think this is kind of this is an early episode
this is kind of the beginning of his abusive behavior. Yeah it's true it's
true yeah and also it's intersectional because Spongebob is yellow and he's
actually pink mm-hmm so there's something there too yeah there's
something there and he's also a cartoon that's okay yeah yeah and he's square
he's a shape and he's square and he just can't found out that he's gay yeah oh
yeah yeah sure that is an intersectional on it I don't know what is I heard that
I heard that from the TV. If that is an intersectional then I have no idea what
that word means. Yeah if you're not talking about Spongebob being a shape
and a color, I don't understand. A professor is like, "So you guys
understand the concept of intersectionality?" and I'm like, "Yeah I've
seen Spongebob you stupid bitch you stupid Irish bitch number two he stabs
Spongebob in the back that's true the audience doesn't see Pat's family until
season 2 episode 17 I'm with stupid already problematic in my eyes uh-huh
yeah Patrick's parents know their son is dumb but like a good friend Spongebob
tries to help by feigning idiocy hoping to make Patrick look smarter in
comparison. Instead, Patrick starts treating Spongebob like he is dumb. He and
his family openly laugh at and ridicule Spongebob. Without a second thought,
Patrick takes advantage of Spongebob's kindness and doesn't hesitate to treat
him like garbage. Now what's really deep and profound about this episode is it's
kind of like a meta storyline where we're basically invited to view our own
interactions with the character of Patrick Star through the lens of reality
within the show, you know?
'Cause we sort of, we, whenever Patrick Starr shows up
on the TV, I start screaming at him.
And I start throwing things at my TV and saying,
you fat, shirtless, pink, stupid moron.
And Patrick actually says those exact things
to SpongeBob in this episode.
So it's kind of a dark reflection of our deepest selves.
- It's a dark reflection of Cameron's TV.
- It's a dark reflection of my behavior
toward my television.
- In season two, episode 17, Patrick invites us
into his family's twisted world.
- Yeah.
- You know, it's 22 minutes of pure existential horror
as we are forced to see not only a normal Patrick,
but also a girl Patrick and a boy Patrick.
- Yeah, this is kind of like,
this episode is pretty much the same
as the strange thing about the Johnsons.
- Yeah.
- It is.
It's kind of exactly the same.
- I heard that this episode of SpongeBob
was inspired by this.
And that's also, and that's kind of subtextually,
you can see the way that Patrick looks at his father.
And you can see, well, why is Patrick not wearing a shirt,
but his father is?
It's because his father is afraid
of what'll happen if he takes his shirt off.
Notice that there's no scenes
with Patrick alone with his father.
That's 'cause they got cut out by the censorship board.
- Yeah, that was actually,
that was actually one of the other things.
It was a side thing on Squidward's Suicide.
There was actually that, those scenes.
- It's true, yeah.
Originally, Patrick Star was supposed to be oriented
so that he had one leg and he was shaped like a pentagram
due to his evil nature.
- Yeah.
But they were forced to invert him.
- Well, if Patrick goes--
- But then Eminem came along
and everybody got weird about stuff
and they had to change it.
- Yeah, and Sandy Hook, Bird, Columbine.
Yeah, and then Sandy Hook happened and they and the writers of Spongebob actually knew that and they predicted it Simpsons style
Yeah
So that patchy the pirate is always looking for they have this Andy Hook episode
Where that's actually where Spongebob gets his holes from
Yeah
He gets completely Swiss cheesed yeah, they actually had to change the Patrick star character's name from Patrick Klebold
3. He forces Spongebob to raise a baby scallop by himself. This I don't think is too bad.
This is just a man's purpose.
Parenting can be tough, especially when one parent doesn't do their fair share. Spongebob learns this in Season 3, Episode 9, "Rock-a-Bye Bye-Valve."
by Valve.
Spongebob and Patrick find a baby scallop and decide to raise it.
The scallop behaves a lot like a human baby, needing everything from feedings to diaper
changing.
While Spongebob proves himself a capable parent, Patrick spends his time watching TV, staying
out late with friends, and eating ice cream and donuts.
He promises to come home and help, giving Spongebob a day off, but he never shows.
He's a bad adoptive dad and a selfish partner.
You don't always have to take care of your kid.
Yeah.
Exactly.
What if you want to eat ice cream and donuts and you want to hang out with your friends?
What if your kid kind of sucks?
Yeah.
That's basically my plan.
What if your kid is like, "Oh, Dad, I want to go see Hamilton."
Yeah.
Or something.
Or like, "Oh, Dad, I need $50 to go hang out with my friends."
Yeah, $50 to hang out with your friends.
What are you doing, kid?
Right?
Are you renting your friends?
- Friends?
- Yeah.
- You need $50 to hang out with your friends,
what are you gonna do?
Oh, we're gonna go to the ThinkGeek
and we're gonna buy meme Funkos.
- Yeah, yeah, I need 100 bucks to rent out a WeWork
for an hour so that me and my friends
can brainstorm our next app.
- Exactly.
- Shut up.
- If your son does that, it's perfectly okay
to close him into the pull-out couch
and you sit on it and eat a tub of ice cream
and you watch your TV.
- Yeah, we have a trundle bed.
Our son is attached to the bottom
and we only take him out when we need him.
- Yeah, that's true.
The thing is, if you're a husband
and your wife is at home taking care of the child
and you're out eating ice cream with your friends,
it's perfectly okay to call your wife and say,
"Hey, I'm gonna come home and take care of the baby
"and give you a day off."
And even if you don't do it, that gives your wife hope,
which is a powerful force and can push your wife
to
wearing michael rapaport's home attire yeah michael rapaport walking around his
billion-dollar manhattan apartment in house shoes
number I don't remember what number we're on we are the next number for for
he steals Gary's spongebob's beloved pet that's okay to do if you like anybody
like if you like your friends to hairless cats you're allowed to go to
his house at night and sneak in through the window and take them out and play with them
all night without your friend knowing.
Even if he's not your friend, even if he's just a guy that you follow online.
Yeah.
No.
It's perfectly legal.
It's perfectly legal to triangulate his location based on locations mentioned in previous episodes.
The reason is it's effectively legal because the statute of limitations on stealing pets
is one minute.
Yeah.
So as long as you get...
As long as you can hide for one minute.
He just looked up at me after you said all that.
And now he looks pissed.
What did he say?
He looks pissed.
He doesn't speak English.
Yeah, but he's...
He can't hear us.
You're wearing headphones.
He's emotional.
Do you give your cat headphones to listen to us?
He's not emotional.
Yes.
I have a splitter.
You have a splitter?
He likes to listen to music.
What kind of music does he like?
But it's perfectly okay to steal a pet.
He listens to cat music.
Yeah?
Like what?
I don't know.
Cat Stevens?
Oh, come on.
Come on dude.
Dude, that's a good one.
Come on bro, you serious?
We get paid to do this now.
You can't just throw that out dude.
You can't just say Cat Stevens man.
You get paid.
Like not a little bit.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Like a pretty good amount every month to do this and you say Cat Stevens dude.
Yusuf Islam.
There we go.
Yeah, there we go.
That's better.
Uh huh, that's his new name.
It's been his new name.
In season 2 episode 9, appropriately... what are you saying?
In season 2 episode 9...
Cat Stephen changed his name to Yusuf Islam.
Is that true?
Yeah.
Oh, I thought you were saying your cat's name was Yusuf Islam.
Yeah, I'm changing my cat's name to Yusuf Islam.
Yeah.
Apparently titled "Dumped", Gary ignores... oh, appropriately titled "Dumped".
Gary ignores Punchy Rob.
Apparently...
Apparently this one's called "Dumped".
Hmm, okay, Steven Hillenburg.
Okay, I see what, okay.
Hmm?
Gary ignores Spongebob to play with Patrick.
Spongebob realizes this and feels crushed.
Throughout the episode, Patrick doesn't hesitate to rub this in Spongebob's face.
When Spongebob makes a plea to get the snail back, Patrick calls him pathetic.
This is not the behavior of a true friend.
Luckily, Gary eventually returns to his original owner.
If Gary wants to go hang out with Patrick, then Gary can go hang out with Patrick.
with Patrick. We're erasing the autonomy of this character Gary.
Okay. But you got it, well you have to think, especially now with
Spongebob's coming out, you know, is Gary homophobic for not wanting to hang out
with Spongebob? Yeah and that's okay. Because Gary's a snail. Homophobia. Gary's a snail.
No I'm saying Gary's a snail. That's what Cameron is saying. Cameron said that.
Cameron said Gary is a snail. I didn't say that I would say it, but I didn't say it. Okay, okay
But Gary's a snail. What does that have to do with him? Well, do you okay?
Do you think the experiences of us?
Do you think the experiences of a snail and a sponge are equal in this room in this realm of Bikini Bottom?
Okay, there's a snail suffers a far greater
axis of
oppression many convergences of axes of oppression okay, and in this um in Bikini Bottom
Where's the sponge? A sponge has it made, okay? You can work as a fry cook and you can afford a whole entire pineapple.
Alright? A snail has to live in a little dog house or something. I don't know where Gary lives.
How is Spongebob affording a whole house on a fry cook's salary?
That's right. It's the new girl problem.
Yeah, it's the friend's problem. It's the new girl problem.
Tell me how unemployed little Spongebob with his colorful with his with his colorful patties stand is
Affording that big-ass pineapple. He he's he's a something tells me inherited some money. Yeah, right
Look, they barely work and he can afford a pineapple in bikini bottom
I'm tired of these rich sponge gays pretending that they go through the same struggle as a snail
Exactly, that's what I'm saying.
A lowly snail.
Yeah.
Who kinda, you run into the Pluto problem,
I would say, with Gary.
Because why is he not, like, you know,
why is he not autonomous?
Why does he not have--
Well, there aren't really any other
autonomous snails in the show, so I don't think--
The snails exist as like a low life form.
Well, it's just like a cat in real life.
But you gotta fuck it, you gotta,
you gotta starfish that eats chocolate bars?
No, he's, it's not, there's no, are there,
is there one episode where Gary talks?
There's one where he has,
SpongeBob has a dream that Gary's British.
Oh yeah, okay, that's what I'm thinking, it was a dream.
All right, number the next one is,
is he accuses SpongeBob of lying.
That's very abusive to accuse someone of lying.
That is true.
Everything that happens in season two, episode seven,
Life of Crime is Patrick's fault.
he convinces fun job to steal a balloon than the two of them run away from home
but the problems don't stop
both of the friends of candy bars but patrick eats is and probably forgets
immediately he accuses fun for the stealing is candy
sponge bob ever the trooper
offers pad is candy to make peace but patrick refuses threatening reports
bundled sponge bob for balloon theft
everything turns okay out okay because it's free balloon date but patrick acts
incredibly disloyal
this reminds me a little shake shack debacle
that's been going on in the news lately.
This reminds me of every crime.
This reminds me of crime.
Yeah.
How fucking sick would it be if you commit a crime
and you do a carjacking or something
and then
it turns out it was free car day.
Oh it's free car day actually.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're welcome.
It's free car day, you just take it.
Dude, Jeffrey Epstein missed
free pedophilia ring day by like one day.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, free, just free baby boy, baby boy butt day.
He missed it.
- Yeah, if he had just waited one day to get caught.
- Yeah.
- He would have been home free.
- Yeah, Bill Cosby missed free pussy day
by like a couple years.
- This next one I really like.
This is the one I wanted to get to.
(laughing)
- The fucking thumbnail for this.
this is the next uh... i don't want to list is he hunts bunch bob like pray and
they have like a just a terrifying like like uh... like a hidden frame in the
show
where his eyeballs are upside down
projects as a resident is clinging to the ceiling holding a jellies old man
of these days on the internet ready to get started as i said i was going to
write down what what's going on and they look upside down here
Whoa, if you look at the picture upside down, it looks like he has a mustache from his eyebrows.
Whoa.
During season one episode nine, Nature Pants, SpongeBob decides he wants to live with the jellyfish.
Patrick doesn't take this well though.
Initially, he cries, begging SpongeBob to say, and when that doesn't work, Patrick decides to capture him as a trophy.
Patrick cunts SpongeBob like an animal.
I think he is an animal.
Attacking him and setting traps.
While Patrick eventually gives up the hunt, his actions get SpongeBob stung by all the jellyfish.
I hate- we all know that one guy who hunts you like prey.
We all know that one guy that gets you stung by all the jellyfish.
Yes he hunts me like prey but we've been friends for so long.
Well, I mean he's never hunted me like prey.
You know, he's always been good to me but he has hunted some of my friends like prey.
So I still hang out with him.
He goes after them like an animal.
Yeah.
Attacking them and setting traps.
Yes his eyeballs are upside down and yeah he hunts me with a jellyfish net.
He's a giant starfish.
And in the end, yeah, I got stung.
But that's kind of the cost of friendship.
Is it functional?
No.
But what family is?
Hunting Spongebob, I...
I would like to hunt Spongebob.
I would like to hunt Spongebob like prey.
Yeah, I would too.
I'd like to see...
I'd like to get me and him alone on an island, okay?
I've got an AR-15.
He's got nothing, alright?
He doesn't even have his little fry cook outfit.
He's bare naked.
He's running around the island, okay?
I am using my tracking abilities
and I'm tracking his bean-shaped footsteps.
And I'm going after him, and if I see him,
I'm opening fire and I'm filling those holes.
I'm filling those holes with lead.
- Straight up, if I saw a SpongeBob in real life,
I would immediately open fire.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
Yeah, I'm always open carrying, so I would open fire.
I'm always open carrying a Barrett .50 caliber rifle.
- Exactly. - And it has
thermal variable zoom scope. So what I might do is I, you know, and also guns,
bullets work differently through water. Yeah.
So I'd have to account for like, well yeah,
I would loss of velocity and stuff,
but I would activate my stopping power rounds first. Exactly.
I would definitely put FMJ and a sleight of hand as a couple of my perks.
I would have like a P90 or maybe an MP7 as my, as my sidearm.
I would have an advanced UIV up. Of course.
I'm kind of like a, I'm kind of like a berserker.
I would go in with the riot shield.
- Oh nice.
- Yeah, 'cause berserkers love shields, you fucking idiot.
- Yeah, go talk to your cat again.
- No, I have a knife, I have a knife.
- You're thinking of a tank.
You're thinking of a tank.
- You're thinking of a guy with a shield.
You're thinking of tanking.
- All right, all right.
- No, what I would do is basically--
- I didn't know the terminology, so I'm sorry.
- I would use my DDS plus plus,
my dragon dagger poison plus plus.
- Yeah, your dick does something.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I would run up to him.
I'd hit him with my full special attack three times.
And that's what you would do.
And then basically I would mount his nose on my shower door and then use it like a dildo.
Yeah, how gay are you really now, SpongeBob?
You know, you want me to send this photo to Nickelodeon?
I don't think so.
It's okay, he'll grow back.
That's true.
That's the horrible thing about him, is that if you mounted his head, it would grow into
a new SpongeBob.
Yeah, because Spongebob is all brain or something, or he's all, he's a lizard or
I don't know how it works. He's a lizard. He's actually secretly a yellow lizard and
basically what he would do, basically what he would do is he would he would
grow into a monster off of your wall. If you hung him like a singing fish,
eventually he would he would come back and he would enact his revenge. The only
way to actually permanently destroy him is you have to, you got to hit him with
with the degreaser from Team Fortress 2.
You gotta burn him to a crisp.
And then with the fire axe.
- That's true.
- He's completely unkillable.
- Yeah.
- He's like, every time you think he's dead,
he Michael Myers' out of it.
- Yeah, you can kill him by burning him,
but he lives underwater.
All right?
- Exactly.
- If you think about,
think back to the SpongeBob movie,
they almost killed him by shining light on him.
Dude, is he a vampire?
- Oh, what?
- Yeah, that's a really good point.
He does, he gets dried out easily like a vampire.
Yeah, I mean that's... I'm trying to think of more stuff that's like a vampire but I can't
so I think that might be it. Yeah. He says Nosferatu one time. He does. Oh my god, that's
his cousin. Oh my god, he forgot, that episode he just forgot that he invited his cousin over.
And Nosferatu is an anagram for Spongebob Squarepants. That's true. Yeah, it's true.
They have the same letters.
It's the same, it uses all the same letters.
Uh huh.
The ones from the alphabet.
Exactly.
It uses, it comes from the same letter pool.
It comes from the same letter pool, exactly.
Yeah.
Next one.
He keeps an embarrassing photo of Spongebob.
I don't know, I don't think, I keep an embarrassing photo of both of you.
Yeah.
No.
I have a photo, I have a photo of Patrick riding a mechanical bull but just one of the
horns and then no photo of Cameron wearing a dress upside down no I have my
favorite picture I have a Patrick is the one where he's halfway into a window
climb that is good yeah oh that same that same night that was a when Caleb
was in the is in the dryer oh yeah is there a photo of me in the dryer there's
a video of you coming out of the body in there you got half of your body in there
I don't remember I was so fucked up for that show.
Yeah, me too. It was not good.
Patrick keeps a secret in season 2 episode 15, the secret box.
Yeah, you think?
Huh? You fucking... it's in the name of the episode. Of course he keeps a secret.
That's...
But this author is very stupid.
Yeah.
Wait, let's skip to the next one because I think we can really...
You're sounding like Patrick right now, Cam.
We can really speak on this.
That's true.
He refuses to share a toy with SpongeBob.
okay what the hell is wrong with this i'm i'm i'm flipping on you know i'm i'm
yeah i'm starting to take a sponge i'm taking i'm taking a hard stance here
patrick you're scum okay if you won't share your rescue hero with your friend
you're you're worse than um you're worse than donald trump and i don't say that lightly
exactly you are like yeah hitler never shared his toys either
Yeah.
It's true.
Uh, when Mr. Krabs makes a kids meal toy, he doesn't exactly put in maximum effort.
So it sounds like Mr. Krabs is not...
Yeah, do they even... hold on, hold on.
Do they even give out toys at the Krabby Patty?
Not anymore, not after this one.
Not after season 7, episode 6, "Yours, Mine, and Mine."
When Mr. Krabs shoves straws into a Krabby Patty and calls it a day.
That's the toy they're freaking out over?
And also, what a piss poor excuse for a toy.
- Yeah, come on.
- It's literally food.
- Horrible.
- Yeah, make it something that I can dress up
and then undress.
- Yeah.
- You know what I mean?
Draw a little something for daddy on the hamburger.
- Exactly.
- With ketchup.
- And then give it to me for free.
- Yeah.
- And then don't bother me.
- Sexual things about toys that are only for parents
to understand, the kids won't understand when they see it.
When they take off Ken's pants
and he has a giant 15 inch penis,
The kids don't understand it, but it's put in there,
they put it in there for the parents to look at and play with.
- That's just one of those things for parents
that they sit there and they go hee hee hee.
- Yeah, it even has some jokes for parents.
- Yeah, kids toys even have some jokes for parents
that go hee hee hee.
- Yeah, when I was a kid, I used to wake up every morning
on Christmas, we had Christmas every single day,
I would open up a bionicle and I'd say,
Mom, Father, I gotta go to the bathroom for 30 minutes.
and I would take my bionicle in,
I would experiment with its body,
I would find places to hide things,
I would find places to hide it on me,
and then I would come out
and I'd be ready for Christmas again.
- Yeah.
- Christmas the day, the next day,
'cause you did it pretty much the whole day.
- Yeah, basically if I was a president,
it'd be Christmas every day.
Hanukkah is still just once a year though.
But Christmas every single day.
- Yeah.
- Another joke they put in toys for parents
is in the Jack in the Box,
if you keep winding it after it already pops up,
it actually pops up a little more
and you can see its dick.
(laughing)
- It's true. - But kids will get bored,
they won't wind up the Jack in the Box enough
to see that joke.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- There's actually-- - And with the box,
it has the different shapes that the shapes go in.
On the bottom, there's actually one that's circular,
so you know what that means.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Like one on the bottom and it's a circle.
- What do you think the box refers to in Jack in the Box?
- That's right, yeah.
Yeah, jack in a box?
- Yeah.
- Jacking what into a box?
- Pop goes the weasel?
What do you think that means?
- What do you think the weasel is?
What you're supposed to do is you're supposed to put
the jack in the box and the weasel next to each other
and let the weasel pop into the box.
- Yep.
- Let the weasel jack into the box.
- Exactly. - That's true.
- Here's what you gotta do.
- And basically, yeah, you can organize,
You can mix so many toys together at their various,
where their penises and vaginas should be
until they form sort of like a Power Rangers,
like each one of them is a different piece.
- A sexual zord.
- A sexual zord, exactly.
- Sexual zord.
- Yeah.
It's pretty sick.
- Yeah, and that's just, they do that for the parents.
- Yeah, and that's one of the jokes for the parents.
- Yeah, a sex zord.
yeah
yeah that's what me
man i have my fucking my brains fried
i swear shot up
i can't
stopped or nobody cares
i'm gonna die
i don't care
i'm gonna be in a serious patrick right now
you know that you started our
you're being a patrick star
next on people little sponge bob's job
and kill spectators of the process
I remember this one. Season 2, episode 19, the Fry Cook Games.
SpongeBob gets the honor of competing in the titular games, and Patrick...
Oh, there's a little joke for the... for the adult.
- What? Titular? - Titular, yeah.
- Yeah. - And Patrick, the ranker, actually has jokes for the parents, too.
- That's true. - Yeah.
Patrick isn't exactly supportive. Instead, he argues with his friends,
deriding the competition and the occupation.
SpongeBob defends his job, but Patrick continues to belittle him
and eventually competes for the opposing team.
Patrick's pettiness ends up killing a whole lot of people.
Spongebob competes for the opposing team we just learned during
And nice during the games he throws hot oil on a bunch of fish turning them into fish sticks
So they're sold there then sold as food to other fish Wow you know there's so many things wrong with this
That's probably this is probably like this is by first of all why didn't they lead with this one? Yeah?
I also I like I like that they have that this one is he belittles spongebob's job and kills spectators
right like yeah why even include the belittling spongebob's job in this one
yeah yeah on the way up to suite 135 Stephen Paddock was actually very rude
to a cleaning lady and belittled her job and then he did something I think I
don't know but he turned all those country music fans into fish sticks
yeah yeah do you want the fry cook games that day yeah yeah yeah no that's uh I
guess the most messed up part of this wait a second selling to other people
Steve Steven Paddock Steven Patrick oh my god
even oh my god we have to delete even Hillenburg Patrick his middle name was
was was Hillenburg is what people tell you yeah he actually in his manifesto he
said he based the mass shooting off season 2 episode 19 of Spongebob yeah
fry cook games yeah and he was hoping and he and he was really surprised by
everybody's reaction he thought they would just start selling all the people
he fish sticked yeah he thought the music would go on well I like the music
stop come on I thought that it was gonna be Spongebob playing the the Bikini
Bottom Bowl song but no it was some fucking hillbillies yeah I thought it
was gonna be sweet victory but yeah yeah nope nope not not for me apparently yeah
yeah not for me old Stephen Paddock nothing ever goes right nothing goes
That was great for me.
Yeah.
Just a day in the life.
Just another day as Steven Paddock.
Just everything fucking up.
Oh, great.
I just stubbed my toe.
Awesome.
Yeah.
No, this is awesome.
Oh, no.
I like this.
I actually-- I like this.
Oh, great.
Great.
I just started a Halo Slayer game, and I got disconnected.
Awesome.
No, no.
This is actually good for me.
Yeah, no.
Normal world.
Yeah, normal world.
You know what?
We deserve Donald Trump.
know what I'll say me Steven Paddock I'll say we deserve him yeah it's normal
god this nor this world so normal yeah and I've been in my car and mentally be
great great I clogged the hotel toilet now sorry I'm gonna come back to come up
Nobody can find out about this.
I have to do something.
I have to barricade the door. Oh no, the window was open. Who
saw?
Yeah, he was just he was just jacking off to hotel porn with
the window open and he was like, Oh, fuck everybody saw.
Yeah, good thing I brought those Hillary Duff photos of her blowing her fiance.
Yeah.
I have to erase all evidence of this.
Good thing I brought all these weapons I was holding for my friend Hillary Clinton.
Yeah.
Yeah, good thing I have these 15 CIA agents in the room with me.
Who are, yeah.
Next one.
He refuses to take an ill SpongeBob to the hospital.
I would too.
Slow to admit when he feels unwell, knows he needs to visit the doctor when he realizes he has the suds.
Spongebob predicted the future, dude.
Yeah, we all have the suds.
Season 1, episode 15, "Suds."
The bloated Sponge tries to get medical care before encountering Patrick.
Of course, things go terribly wrong.
First, Patrick scares Spongebob into not going into the hospital at all.
Then he plays doctor, subjecting his pal to unhelpful and harmful treatments.
When Sandy tries to correct Patrick, he lashes out and decides to run.
SpongeBob receives treatment eventually, but Patrick cares more about his pride than his friend's health.
Suds is, um, Sudden Unfint Death Syndrome.
[laughter]
It is a little close to SIDS.
Yeah. I think this one was supposed to be an allegory.
This episode was supposed to be like a social commentary.
Yeah. On the suds?
On the, on, on suds.
Yeah, and Patrick represents vaccines.
Yeah in this version. Yeah and each point of his prickly form is a kind of needle.
Exactly. Locked and loaded with small amounts of things like the H1N1 virus or polio
which are expected to cure your child but instead give them a new kind of AIDS called SIDS.
Yeah that's true. SIDS is super super immunodeficiency syndrome. It's the upgraded
Instead of average immunodeficiency. Yeah, a little. Which is what AIDS is. A little. A little bit.
Yeah. This is also how they, this is also coincidentally how they cure AIDS is they
just plug all your holes with cork. That's what they do. Yeah. They're like, "Just don't,
just don't, you know, you'll be fine." Yeah, that's what, that's Bubble Boy is about.
Yeah.
He got the suds.
Uh, next one.
He becomes a vicious tyrant.
He does.
He just looks like a king to me.
Yeah.
In season 4, episode 17, "Rule of Dumb,"
Patrick lucks his way into becoming king of Bikini Bottom,
and it's pretty much a nightmare.
[laughs]
Yeah.
Yeah, it's pretty much a hell world.
SpongeBob becomes his servant and gets treated more like a doormat than any kind of friend.
In fact, the Mad King torments all of Bikini Bottom,
forcing them to give up worldly possessions and demanding free stuff for everyone, or from everyone.
It's kind of an animal farm type allegory.
When Squidward refuses to play along, Patrick compels SpongeBob to make the squid yield.
SpongeBob genuinely fears his BFF. Some creatures go mad with power.
Some creatures go mad with power. That's a fact.
Stars go mad with power.
Patrick is straight up a creature.
Yeah. Oh, Patrick is an allegory for the stars of the world, the Hollywood elite.
gain power and then are mean to their sponge friends.
yeah yeah he lives underneath a rock much like oh my god much like Jeffrey
Epstein did on his island and Spongebob lives in a fruit oh my god Squidward
lives in his head. So Squidward is a representative of a guy who's he's of a
kind of a tortured millennial man who's mean because of his social anxiety, i.e.
he lives in his head.
Mm-hmm.
Whoa!
Do you get it?
Yeah, and SpongeBob is kind of an allegory for being a gay guy because he lives in a fruit.
And he's gay.
Which is kind of a, yeah, which is kind of a school school yard insult for a gay person.
Yeah.
And then Patrick rocks at being a star.
He's a rock star.
star he's a rock star sort of a Kevin Rudolph type and so when Patrick comes
alive he brings his fire and this next picture he's using a flamethrower uh-huh
because he brings the fire and then yes snail word is a is a Gary due to his due
to his because he's afraid of coming out of his shell yeah and then
Krusty Krab is red and he's actually he he represents a spicy pepper
which would be red and mean to you and then Sandy is actually women are the
squirrel of the world is basically what the show is trying to communicate yeah
and they belong and and and women belong in a dome are we starting to kind of see
I think I'm starting to understand. Women belong in a dome and they fear the bull
worm. Yes. That's true. You know? Women fear a bull worm. Women fear a bull worm. And then the whale,
the whale, the pearl is actually, pearl rhymes with girl and then most girls are
actually whales to me. Yeah. You know because it's something. Absolutely. Yeah.
Because they have. You messed up for that one. Larry, Larry the lobster. You messed up for that one.
a lobster because he actually and he actually represents my uncle Michael
very red skin cancer yeah all kind of what I'm basically saying and what most
people who do media criticism are saying is that TV is about my life uh-huh you
know lost is about the time I got lost Brooklyn nine nine is about the time I
sung 99 bottles of beer on the wall with my 40 cop friends yeah and basically 24
is about how old I'm gonna be next year and I think we need to come to a sort of
serious as as spongebob turns 20 yeah I think is coming up we need to come to a
we need to come to a very have a serious examination a retrospective of a
spongebob and how he relates to my exact life exactly see cuz that's I am I'm a
I'm a fry cook.
Okay.
Did you just unplug your mic or something, Pat?
No, I did not.
Oh, your audio just got worse.
Oh.
Well, that's your fault.
Yeah, it's my fault.
Yeah, turns out that, by the way, this entire episode, me and Caleb have been secretly talking about Patrick.
When we said we were talking about Patrick Star, we were referring to Patrick every single time.
What?
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Then I'm leaving.
Yeah, we did it.
We're done um go ahead fuck you
subscribe to the patreon subscribe
We're gonna keep posting
Spongebob stuff yeah pretty much we're basically migrating yeah to a spongebob podcast yeah
Years we're gonna do spongebob media criticism every episode
Yeah, we're changing the name of the podcast a podcast about Spongebob
Yeah, that's one of the biggest changes. We're gonna make we're changing Patrick into a starfish. I
Not even that hard I
Could just do this
Plankton basically represents the children of the world
Yeah
angry at the parents exactly allowing them to cook and you know what they say and that it in the in the land of the
Blind a one-eyed man is king. Okay, and
And that refers to how plankton kind of pulls the strings on all of Bikini Bottom.
It's true. Like people don't talk about that enough.
Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy represent the onset of grooming in today's society.
That's true because there's an old guy and a guy who's a little bit younger.
Exactly. And they're into barnacles and mermaids. And you know what that means.
Yeah, which is a big part of grooming.
Yeah.
Yeah. You're putting each other's barnacles on your friend until they become a mermaid.
Yeah, I put my barnacle on your mermaid because I'm grooning you.
Whatever, back in my day grooming is what we called when you got married to your beautiful husband.
All right.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
All right.
Thanks, thanks for listening.
Thank you for listening.
Bye.