You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts with a hot list.
[music]
Crap monster.
[explosion]
I'm recording. I'll send you the list. Just give me a second here.
Send me my list!
Shut up.
Oh you, oh you shut up.
Oh hush.
Oh hush you.
You're being such a drama queen.
You're such a drama queen, seriously.
Shut up.
[burp]
Seriously.
Seriously being mean.
I sent the list in the chat.
Okay.
Let's be honest.
Welcome to another episode of the show.
Patrick ate too many candy bars and he's having a sugar rush like a nine year old child.
I am hyper as hell right now.
I'm going to say it.
Have you guys ever heard of Bionicles?
Have you guys ever heard of Legos?
There's this game called Lego Bionicles and it's so much fun right now.
I would never speak that fast.
He's bouncing off the walls.
Oh, I'm going up and down in a chair.
He's bouncing up and down in a chair.
You're speaking fast. You're like the...
I'm going son of the mask baby. I'm jumping around.
He's balancing on one chair leg and falling over and then just doing it again over and over again.
You're the squirrel photographer from Hoodwinked right now.
The squirrel photographer?
Yeah.
Do you mean Scrat from Ice Age?
No.
No. He means the squirrel photographer.
He's a buck... He's like a... What is he?
He's a dog.
Scritch is a dog.
Scrat is a prehistoric...
Scritch! Who the fuck is Scritch?
That's a dog that I have.
Yeah, it's a dog I'm familiar with.
Scritch from um, um, Saved by the Bell.
Yeah. Yeah, he got all those women
scritched. He made those women scritched. Remember that?
Remember, did you know he used like a stunt double for all the
sex scenes? Really? Yeah, he did.
I gotta look that up, but Screech, yeah, Screech used a stunt
stunt double. You mean Scrat? I think Scrat was the one that did that. Yeah, Scrat. Yeah,
Scrat sex tape. He used a stunt double. Screeched full movie X videos. Nice. It is, um, user
reviews, 8 out of 10. That's pretty good. Funny, maybe. Witty, no. The thing is though,
porn video has like a 90% thumbs up rating yeah every really heinously bad
yeah okay so these are unless it's a misleading title it's like you're
peach and it's not actually Mario fucking peach you know remove this video
at once this is disgusting yeah it's like Allison Brie fucks Donald Trump and
it's just like it's like a like a sad middle-aged like Latina lady fucking an
old guy yeah this is death this is not Allison Brie Allison Brie has a freckle
on her left leg honestly I'm disgusted you would host a video like this on your
platform there's a whole connection on the page on IMDB for screeched and it
says references so these are the references that screech makes in the
end of like an academic paper no no but so the first reference is to Zorro the
TV series from 1957 and it says in quotes "like Zorro". The second one... so there's
also a section called spoofs so you this is kind of like the Wikipedia thing where
you go and you click like the numbers and then it brings you to a different
page so it says spoofs Dustin hums the Jaws theme as he sticks his penis out of
the water in the tub. So in references it says girl mentions the title after
Dustin's Jaws parody. Is it Balls? Oh no but if I don't think he thought of that
but I think retroactively you could tell. Balls B-A-W-L-S. We need to message
Dustin Diamond and tell him hey man really loved your movie from 2006. Well
the cover of Balls would be like a just a pair of balls. It would just be a pair of
No, not even that it would just be like a like a medical photo of balls
Yeah, just red font balls and also there's still a woman in a flame
Yeah on a floaty hyper detailed
Here the last like to write one of them says like ref the title is a reference to dusted diamonds characters screech blah blah blah
And then it says 24 it ref the movie references 24 and the only reference
IMDB has is it says, "I want to watch the rest of 24."
And then the last one...
No, it referenced 24.
It took place in real time.
Yeah, it took place in 24 hours.
And then this one here, it says there is a reference to Girls Gone Wild on Campus 2.
That's naughty.
And it says that the...
Every porn references that.
reference is TV star gone wild I thought it was gonna be like yeah there's a
there's a scene with a topless woman yeah clearly a reference to any any movie
that has I'm gonna go on to IMDB and do that now like go into like some every
like some art some French New Wave movie where it shows like some French ladies
boobs and it's like do brown here is a reference yeah brown bunny this is a
This is a clear reference to the Kim K sex tape.
This is a reference to Girls Gone Wild, clearly.
Mm-hmm.
Dustin Diamond, is that his real name?
That is probably a stage name.
Unless it's not.
No, I don't think so.
I think it's real.
Yeah, Diamond is such an awesome stage name to pick in the early 90s.
His name is Dustin Neil Diamond.
No way, dude.
No fucking way.
That's his name. Oh my god. His name is Dustin Neil Diamond. God, dude.
Alright, we know who we're casting for the Jazz Singer Remake remake.
Yeah. Dustin. Oh yeah, did they remake the Jazz Singer?
They remade the Jazz Singer with Neil Diamond in like the 80's. Really? Yes, dude.
That's so fucking weird. So crazy. Yeah, I think it's his only role.
Really? Yeah I don't even know if he... yep he goes full blackface. What? Yeah dude he
went the whole nine yards for that one. Jazz singer Neil Diamond. Let's take a
look at this. Oh my god he does! He went right into it. He went hard.
Dude he fucking... I will say I have the soundtrack, amazing soundtrack.
Yeah, yeah, he killed it with the soundtrack dude. He did he did like a full like Greg Louganis dive into that shit
Yeah, dude. Yeah
Yeah, he nailed it. Yeah
That's the only diver I know are there any other diet because
My grandfather he broke his ear diving. Okay. Yeah, he don't apparently he dove with such force
and he had so much gravity behind him that he broke the the surface tension of the
water destroyed his inside of his ear he was trying to listen to what the water
sounded like before he landed just to make sure he'd do it still oh you know
he said you can hear the ocean yeah if you can hear the ocean from the top of
this diving board yeah and then he ear flopped yeah he actually is obliterated
he broke his ear cuz the whole pool went into his ear just circles his brain
all day. Yeah. It actually makes them smarter. That's so, that is so funny that
they fucking, they add, he referred to the guy who fucked the women for him in
Screeched as a stunt double. Like what kind of... Sex is a stunt dude. What kind of evil
kenevil shit were you doing in Screeched? Every time, every time I have sex, yeah I put on a, I put on a
flame decal helmet. Yeah. And a full leather suit with a cutout, you know where.
And I'm on a journey, I just...
I'm gonna run across the room
I have a big rubber band that I've put into the doorway
And I'm gonna run into the hallway of this motel
And I'm gonna shhht, I'm gonna have the rubber band launch me straight into your pussy
I'm gonna jump your vagina with a tech deck like it's the Grand Canyon
*laughter*
Just go one leg down, hop it, and hit the other one
Let me, hold on, hold on, let me get...
But my guy, my, the stunt man fell off in the middle
I'm gonna sit in the corner with my helmet on so when they cut when they edit it
together it'll be there for continuity. Can I fill your your pussy with
electric eels and piranhas so I can jump over it? I set up a dunk a dunk tank I
filled up my wife's pussy with lava and people have to throw a baseball across
the Grand Canyon. Yeah I'm getting... They have to hit through a hole in the Eiffel Tower and
then go all the way around the world. They're putting me in a coffin and
they're wrapping me in thousands of chains and then they're lowering me into
my wife's pussy and I have to try to escape. I was buried alive in my wife's vagina.
Do you guys remember Dustin Diamond got arrested in 2015 for stabbing someone?
Yes yeah that's what I... I completely forgot about that. I couldn't remember if he was a rapist or a murderer.
yeah he's just a stabber I mean Jesus Christ today I almost had to stab
somebody to save a local business yeah I I woke up at one o'clock cuz you call it
a call that a New York minute yeah and then I walked outside went to 7-eleven
came back some guy riding on his bike was like some lady was trying to make a
a three-point turn turnaround he was like move you're being fucking slow and she
like kind of cut him off and he was like oh no you bitch you're not my
grandmother and then he knocked over two plants in front of this like Italian
restaurant next to my apartment and everybody just everybody's like what
don't fuck you fucking idiot he started singing a song and riding away and then
and the owner of the pizza place just booked it at him.
(laughing)
And then I just went in my apartment.
But I got pretty close to kinda stepping in there
and going Batman.
- You almost did it, you almost threw a ninja star.
- Yeah, I almost, yeah.
But you know, I don't know what it is about this city
that just like, if you're from here,
you're just a complete psychopath.
- Yeah, oh absolutely.
- Like just every, I think it's because you--
- It's the water, it's what makes the bagels so good.
- Exactly.
I think it's because you are raised in a place
where you walk outside and you always have an audience.
- That's true.
- There's always people watching you.
- Right.
- And so this guy, and that's the worst part about this,
what happened with this guy knocking over the plants.
It just ruined these very expensive plants.
It's a tragedy.
And he definitely wasn't gonna do it
until he looked at me, made eye contact with me,
and I was smiling because I thought it was funny.
He was yelling at this lady.
I could see in his head, he was like,
"I'm gonna turn this up.
"I'm gonna knock this shit.
I'm gonna break something. It's like a little kid. You enabled him. He definitely wasn't old. He was probably like...
You poked the bear. You poked the bear by doing that.
It's like when like a little kid like walks up to their parent and like kicks them in the shin and the other parent like
Laughs a little bit, so then the kid just like starts attacking. You know what I mean?
Yeah, it's exactly like what kids do. Like if you if you laugh or smile at one thing a kid does they
They just keep doing it. They'll do it like times a hundred. Oh, yeah
I'm gonna hit you with the car next.
He had a Cristiano Ronaldo jersey on.
Dude, I think that might have been Cristiano Ronaldo.
Dude, I think it was Ronaldo.
It might have been, and that's the worst thing that guy ever did.
Is he the one... wait, what did he do?
He played soccer.
Oh, no, really?
Yeah, one of the...
I don't want to say greatest of all time, but...
He was also really into soccer.
He's a legend in two games.
Like Pee-wee Kirkland.
Pee-wee Kirkland?
Yeah.
Who's the, who's the fuckin', who's the soccer player that used to just like shave
like all of his head except for like one patch of hair right here?
Like he would have like, it was like his hairline and he would just shave like everything but
like a triangle?
I don't know.
I don't know anything about soccer.
All I know is that Cristiano Ronaldo.
I only know about that haircut.
I remember there was a soccer player who was biting people.
That's the extent of all I know about soccer.
In Brazil, they cut a ref into pieces or something, or they beheaded him.
Really?
Yeah.
Yeah, dude.
I think there's video of it.
I think it was an early LiveLeague video in the 2000s.
It wasn't a high-level soccer game.
That makes it even better.
It wasn't even...
game and oh oh this is why they beheaded him I'm remembering this now he got this
ref the I wish American sports were like this this ref got into an argument with
one of the players and then the ref stabbed the player oh and then the
player got the player got evac taken to a hospital and then somebody called and
person, somebody called like the announcer for the game and the guy on the
announcer on the the like intercom thing said that he was like hey that
guy that the ref stabbed he just died at the hospital and so then just
everybody in the stands just like picked up the ref and beheaded him and cut him
in a piece of fuck that's what football should be yeah yeah like stop putting
stop like trying to add a pillow on top yeah well you know you know why they
don't admitted to that and you're willing to make to risk your life to
make a hundred million dollars a year or whatever the refs should be evil
everyone should be carrying weapons you should have an evil ref there should be
no guns allowed but if you can get medieval weapons and known yeah a mace
yeah have a place should every each team on the like in a gel should have a
trebuchet where they can once a game you can launch one like a player yeah no they
can launch him into the end zone it's like playing paper football with your
with your thumbs yeah yeah and they they should let you're allowed you can players
do HGH but I realized that they wouldn't let them do that because of how big your
fucking head gets when you do HGH yeah you get a bit yeah what they're they do
not have the materials nor the money to make helmets that big but also actually I
think you having a bigger head it might protect you more from CTE yeah it might
be a good idea to create like a super soldier Funko pop like species of
football players who don't even need pads and they just hit each other with their
heads like the fucking like they're giraffes yeah
Pachycephalosaurus yeah we got some Pachycephalosaurus DNA
That's what the Packers are named after.
The Pachycephalosaurus.
That's why they're called the Packers.
I think yeah if you added like if if if you added if football in America was like was
like the Mario soccer games.
Yeah.
And like you could use a special ability and there was like a guy running around, there
was like a dinosaur.
And you could have Bowser.
An evil dinosaur.
Yeah.
Yeah, an evil turtle, dinosaur guy, and also an old, old man with a mushroom for a head.
I think it'd be better.
Yeah, we should make it so that the football is a bomb.
Also once a game, again, you should just get special abilities that you charge up.
Each team gets a sniper.
uh-huh each team gets a sniper that sits on their side of the field.
Yeah some guy with a Barrett .50 cal, they're already there.
They already have snipers on them.
A Barrett .50 cal, if you do some modifications, you could put a football on that thing.
I agree.
You could put a football on that thing and launch it across the field.
Yeah, if Tom Brady deflated it enough.
Oh, man.
Hey, you talking about my fucking boy dude.
Hey, what the fuck?
He moved to, he's playing for the...
He's still number one in my fucking heart.
(laughing)
Okay, Thumper, he's still number one in my fucking heart.
- I wish you were a real Boston guy.
I wish you were into the Red Sox and shit.
- I wish, my brother is.
I wish I fucking understood.
- You're a poser, dude.
You're not a Boston guy.
- I am a Boston boy.
I'm Boston Irish, bitch.
- No, you're not.
Cam likes hockey, at least.
- Yeah, I like hockey.
- I like hockey 'cause they fight,
but I couldn't get into hockey in high school
because of my brothers.
- Yeah, you're not a real Boston boy.
That's what I'm saying.
I've only been to one hockey game, it was a California Condors game in
Bakersfield, California when I was a kid and I went with my grandpa, my very sweet
old older grandpa who older my grandpa's older than me.
My older grandpa.
My younger grandpa.
my grandpa are the same age, so it's really cool. We're into a lot of the same shit.
But he took me to this thing and he's such like a sweet old man that we, a fight
broke out and he was like, "We have to, we have to leave." And we just left during like the
only cool part of a hockey game. Dude, I went to a couple charity games as a
kid, like my mom got like free tickets and like my dad was trying to get me
into hockey so bad when I was a kid. Yeah. Like my dad bought us skates and then
And I was like, "Dad, I don't want to play hockey.
I want to play action figures."
I want to play games in the backyard.
Yeah, I want to play Star Wars in the backyard.
I don't want to play hockey.
And so they took us to a couple charity games and it was for childhood cancer.
And it was like, "Oh, we've got Boston Bruins legends playing some fucking farm league team."
And the whole time I was trying to...
They were farm league.
They were cows.
like a fight going when I was like six. At a charity game? At a charity game. Dude, that,
because imagine, that would be fucking sick. It would be so sick. If somebody gets put in
the goddamn penalty box for a fight at a charity game. That's like, there was a, there was a
hardcore festival in North Carolina that, it happened two years, and it was a benefit
for this girl's family who died of cancer. And the first year it was fine, they raised
a lot of money. Second year of this fucking charity thing, there was like a shooting at
the charity show. And it's like, come on, go to a school or something. Don't do this
here. We're all trying to have a good time.
That's so crazy.
Yeah, man. It's epic, dude.
I've had this open and it's been staring at me this whole fucking time.
What, your past asshole?
I'm still looking yeah. Hey buddy that's a mirror. We got him a new little thing.
We got him a human asshole installed. We got him a human asshole so he could take human shits.
Just like a big pink asshole and like a little bit of white, a white guy skin
around it where they cut. They had to cut a circle they couldn't cut the star shape out.
They yeah well I mean we're trying to we're gonna make him poop in the toilet.
So we're gonna make him a human. We're gonna make the cat a human slowly.
But I've Dustin diamond to fight bagel boss Chris Morgan and boxing match
Now I'm just thinking about if you replaced slowly every part of a cat with human stuff
You could make him a guy. Yeah. Yeah, you just couldn't do it. I mean, that's literally that's just mew -
That's true. That's true or that fucking from Dragon Ball. What's his name?
Beerus is that his name?
Goku.
His name is Mewtwo 2.
Beerus, yeah, Beerus is literally, uh, is literally the fucker if you replace parts of him with a guy.
That's true. Yeah. Yeah, Beerus is a fucker.
How, I mean, how many, at what point is he in just a guy?
If you replace...
Yeah, I feel like you could get just, just imagine his like little...
His little neck on top of like a human body like, uh, the Goombas in the Super Mario Brothers movie.
With John Leguizamo.
Yeah.
I feel like that'd be a good, a cool look.
He would look very cool.
I honestly, sometimes I wish he was like that.
But like a tiny, a tiny guy.
You're gonna send him off to college and he's gonna come back looking like that.
Patrick wishes he had a pet human.
No.
Is what he just said.
I wish that my pet was a guy.
You wish you had a pet guy?
No.
Yeah, you do.
You just said you did.
You wanna do diabolical experiments on your...
I wish that my pet was a guy so he could pick up his own poop.
With his hands and feed it to you.
Yeah.
I don't want him to feed it to me, I just want him to throw it away.
You do.
You don't want him to feed it to you, but you want him to poke it up and plate it.
You want my cat to poop on you.
And you do.
Not on you.
And you want him to stink it up.
Have you seen The Office?
You want him to stink it up?
You've seen me.
Have you seen me?
You've seen Michael's office.
Do you know the character Dwight?
False.
You know...
(laughing)
- You know Dwight.
- False.
- You know Dwight in person.
- I know Dwight in real life.
- That's, yeah, you don't know Dwight.
- Dwight in real life.
- Isn't that guy Rainn Wilson
like into like internet Buddhism now?
- Yeah, he has some.
- What's it called?
- He produced--
- It's called Soul Waffle or something.
- Yeah, Soul Pancake.
- Soul Pancake.
- He produced the Longmont Potion Castle documentary.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Well, I mean, he's just a nerd.
of those nerd guys who is like well I think there's a dispute but I don't know
if he was doing a bit where he said like don't see the movie they said that I'm
an executive producer or some type of thing where I'm not I'd have to look it
up but it's like it's a very weird video I don't care he was raised in the Baha
I faith yeah I do know he's behind Baha blast faith yeah behind blast yeah which
is basically as far as I can tell it's just basically like Christianity or
Islam. It's literally it's like they think that they think that every
version of God is like just a different version of their one God so it's
literally just like they're like oh you know what actually we're better than all
of you guys like we're gonna take all of your shit it's actually all about us.
I think it is like a new one right? I'm pretty sure it is. But it is like it's
like part like Islam part Christianity part Judaism it's one of those ones
where they're like Jesus was a prophet Jesus was a very good man yeah no say
he's the but say he was the best say he was the best right now say he could beat
anybody in video games yeah or also kill rain Wilson yeah your favorite famous
anybody on on rust 1v1 say it rain Wilson could not no scope anyone on
rust that's right until he turns into his alter ego
Dwight. Thunder. Thunder Dwight. Thunder Dwight. Yeah, no, it's a very weird video. It's him
in his house and he's like, "This movie's a fraud. They said that I'm a producer."
Wait, an LPC in his house? No, no, Rainn Wilson denouncing the Longbottom Potion Castle movie
that's coming out soon. Are they making a movie? Yeah, they were making a documentary
about him yeah but I don't I don't know I don't know if he's like pretending to
not do it and then like to drum up hype for it or I don't know what the hell's
going on I don't know but I all I know is he's a certified weirdo he's a
certified freak yeah he's definitely weird to his core
Ray Nelson you're a certified freak and I know that cuz you played a creep on
the office as Dwight. Yeah. You're a creep. You're a creep, Red Wilson. What is up with
Creed? I mean, I've been watching The Office and he's giving me the heebie-jeebies. He's
such a freaky old man. Just get him some headphones. Diaper! Get him a diaper! This guy's name
should be Creep. He's old! I'm thinking this guy's name should be Creep. Headphones are
I'm thinking this guy's name should be Creep.
Yeah, no just...
Can you laugh at it?
I'm thinking his name should be Creep.
Can you laugh at it though?
I'm thinking cause I'm a creep
I'm thinking that creeps the office
office
and I'm with Jim and Pam
selling paper
I'm thinking that is
I don't wanna go to work
I just wanna watch
song parody by Taka. Come on I worked on this. I just want to look at Pam's things I just
want to play with Michael but I'm a creed and I work here. I'm a creed. What the hell is
Stanley's name? Where did Dwight go? I'm thinking this guy's name should be creep based on the
song that's being sang about him. That's probably a good idea. Do you guys want to look at our
list you know look let's take a list that
are what I kind of what you create the
resume and I mean Patrick were on a
Harry Potter RP server again oh yeah mod
last night and he was I need we were
yelling get back on there soon
calling people pedophiles and there was
one guy who was a is was his name Chris
Angel or do you just look like him no he
just looked like Chris I look like
Chris Angel and can pack up being like
hey get away from me Chris Angel your
pedophile and then Chris Angel cast a
spell that put a rope on Patrick and dragged him across the entire map.
He dragged me to the Quidditch pitch. That's the most insane thing I've ever seen.
That's how you prove that you're not a pedophile. You cast a spell.
So what I did was I went into... I was on... you're on a schedule in Harry Potter RP
and I went into my class that all the Slytherins were supposed to take because
I'm a Slytherin and... He's a filthy Slytherin. Do you have to choose? No, you get sorted. Oh my god.
Do you take a test? No, you click on the... you press E on the sorting hat. That is
fascism. Yep. Yeah. So... They do have a special thanks to Million Dollar Extreme. Yeah, they do.
They do have a... like each of them by name in detention. Oh my god, that's so funny. But I went in, I said I was the
teaching assistant and I said that I was like okay class it was herbology or
something like that no no it was like muggles studies I thought it was
potions class potions that's what it fucking was but I walked in and I said
like there have been some again Dumbledore was following me around
because he was trying to see if I was griefing to send me to detention so I
kept every time that he left the room I would go up to the front of the classroom
and be like there have been some allegations levied against Dumbledore
and and Dumbledore kept coming back into the room in the middle of Patrick saying
who wait who is what there's one guy so I was the fat kid from Slytherin I was the
fat bald kid oh okay yeah and when he eats the cupcake and falls
asleep yeah his name's crab I was I was crab and I was saying I was the
teaching assistant yeah yeah and yeah I kept I kept saying stuff about
Dumbledore so he would send me to detention. Did he? There was one time -
He went to detention several times. He got kicked out of detention too.
Where did they even put you? I went up there Dumbledore had called a meeting for the
school and then I went up and I was like the school has hired me to do some
stand up just did like just shitty like yeah we gotta stop anyway our list today
is the worst people in your family by go Razorbacks this is from the discord so
thank you hooch and the podcast about list discord thank you people out oh
Oh yeah, dude, shout out to Evan.
Evan.
What's his name?
@KindaEvan.
He made like a fucking like sick ass intro for the pod.
A very cool, yeah.
Super sick animation.
I don't know what we can't, we don't have enough videos to use it, but it's very cool.
Yeah, it has like a Pornhub community content kind of drum riff going on in the background.
He's got a drawing of Cameron with very long arms, which is true.
true yeah he fucking he fucking nailed it he nailed everything about it
he made me small, he made Patrick look cool, he made me look very cool with bare feet
he drew my feet very accurate I'm kind of nervous where he got
you've posted pictures of your feet before I I do not think I've posted pictures of my feet
before one of us has who knows which one no anyway the worst people in your
family number one is your yeah you guys read it cuz I've realized recently
taking charge here no I I've realized recently I have I I definitely have
dyslexia there's no fucking way I was talking about this on the stream with a
sir but yeah Patrick just sees a word and he looks at the first and last
letter and then just makes up sounds to go in the middle of it yeah well yeah
that's how I've read my entire fucking life and I've never been tested for
dyslexia or anything I think you just know I think you just have nine year old
ADHD I think you're just dumb I think you also drink five monster energies a
today and your brain can't your eyes can't stay still for long enough to look
at a word. My eyes can't keep up with my brain. Yeah. Number one is your brother.
So fast. Blist has a lot of really good comments. This is uh I'll should we just
read three I want to read the really long one because this I really like. Just
read the really long one. All right yeah this is a really long comment. You know
what I am the older brother of our family and my brother well he is the
most annoying person in my whole life. He always care about himself, his gaming
addiction, and his worst obsession on some of his favorites, e.g. TV shows,
music, gaming, etc. Dude, I hate when my brother has favorites and their TV shows.
-My brother's favorites? -Yeah, some of my favorites are TV shows,
music, and gaming.
-Some of your favorites will be implicated.
-Even I almost killed Takeout, his favorites, for revenge, but believe me,
it's hard to be a big brother for him because he also physically hurt me
which I don't really care about because he think I am a monster than a
brother even I am doing rights for him.
He also sings with the worst voice in the world much worse than Justin
Bieber.
His voice was irritating that he can't refused to stop my parents won't
even let me hurt him because of his rude ways.
I didn't hurt.
I didn't hurt him because I was a kind person, you know, my brother.
He is not nice.
he was very naive and very rude person that he cannot change
maybe his friends take him some stupid things to him so he will going to annoy
me
he have no motivation whatsoever to bug me out and making such excuse that my
parents will believe me
he even quote
touch
my stuff and he gets a hold of my music playlist uh... five-year i won't forget
what he did and what he say to me why do i ever have a brother in the first
place he ruined it my whole life partially
He ruined my whole life partially.
The scare quotes touch really is making me uncomfortable.
Yeah, touch my stuff.
That might be like an Adam Savage thing.
I don't like that at all.
That's upsetting.
He ruined my whole life partially.
Partially, yeah.
That's such a good end.
So basically, your honor, my ex-wife in conclusion, she had ruined my whole life.
Partially.
Partially speaking.
Which is why I think I'm entitled to the Xbox.
My parents won't even let me hurt him
because of his rude ways.
- Mom, I want to hate him.
- Let me hurt him. - Because of his rude ways.
You're not allowed to.
He sings worse than Justin Bieber.
- Mom.
- Mom, can I hurt my brother?
- Well, why do you want to hurt him?
- Because of his rude ways.
- No, absolutely not.
- I need to hurt my brother due to his rude ways.
- He think I am a monster than a brother.
- My favorite syntax is like a kid
trying to type like an adult.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- You know what I mean?
like just every every part of it like using using words like physically yeah
it's like he was like I'm gonna be I'm making a case right now and the cops
are gonna read this and then arrest my brother for ruined did my whole life
part is what do you guys think he means by even I almost killed take out his
favorites for revenge what do you guys mean we think he meant by he is not nice
I don't know. I think it might mean that he sings with a much worse than
Justin Bieber. That's pretty nice. He does sing much worse than Justin Bieber.
You know what this reminds me of? Do you remember that Vine that was like
the girl is like, "If you think that parents need to stop acting like our
teachers, subscribe in the comments down below and I will call the cops."
That's what that reminds me of. I think I'm very, this makes me happy because I'm
glad that kids like a like middle school kids still hate Justin Bieber yeah yeah
like that is it is amazing to me that that has that's like persisted that just
like we were there in like 2010 you know just saved it on one of those like one
of those things or no like this is a really old thing well it doesn't have a
date for when all these were posted so we could just be reading like stuff from
when we were like I realized that the other day we could just be reading like
stuff from when we were in middle school. Did you guys ever do that thing where
it's like you schedule an email to be sent to you like five years from now?
No. I did that when I was like like 13 or something and then I just obviously
forgot about it and then I got it when I was 18 a couple years ago and it just
said fuck you and I scheduled that for five years. That's so awesome. Yeah cuz
you're supposed to be like dear older me I hate my chores and I love yeah yeah and
I was just like I've done I've done stuff like that for myself before like my one
of my old computer I forgot that I was trying to like log into it and I forgot
the password on it and I was like clicked on the hint button like to see
what if there was a hint for the password and it was fuck you no hint
it's so awesome to just completely just fuck yourself oh yeah that's like until
until like recently when I did security questions for something I would just
make stuff yeah just choose something random yeah my mom's maiden name Trump
yeah my mom Tiana Trump yeah a lot of porn talk the GF's will not be happy
about this what do you mean what do you mean what do you mean talk about porno
at all we talked about the worst people in your family that's right I know
they're like reach I just got I just understood what you're saying Patrick's
Patrick's sugar rush has reduced his short-term memory to one minute exactly
yeah yeah I don't even remember what we're doing right now this should be
number one even though my big brother's fine the little brother are the actual
worst. Why? Here's a kind of a list within a list in this comment. One, they are mean.
Two, they are annoying and selfish. Three, they always copy you and that's the worst
thing of all in my opinion. Four, they always tattletale on you. And last but
not least, five, they are wine butts and annoying. Anything I missed? Anything I
missed? Copycats is a persisting problem in the world. Gary Goldman is
struggling with a copycat yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah he got a copycatted harikanda
Bolo is actually struggling with copycats removing yeah removing white
voice he thought a poo was a was copying him yeah that was the problem yeah a poo
is actually a copycat and he's copying me that's not what I'm imagining I'm
imagining like somebody else like being like oh yeah a comic book guy was
copycatting me yeah Homer is copycatting me I'm watching TV with a beer in my
hand right we actually we need a nerd to voice is it kind of a guy that's true we
need to get a real fat nerd yeah yeah do either of you guys want to apply only
one that only fits one of us yeah that only fits cam Caleb it's kind of
actually you two combined you look like homework so you only have three hairs on
your head yeah I don't you have a brown circle around your mouth I do have a
brown circle around your mouth you have a brown circle around your mouth for me
from eating your own freaking butthole I don't have a son I wish I had a Marge
you wish you had a son and I have a dog with that is the second dog or is it the
cat what what the cat have a dog that dies in like and I have a dog wait I want to
I want to read one more comment from the brother real quick well funny user says
copying me this funny user says yes I love my brother the least sometimes I
get yet mad at him but I always he still loves him yeah I love my brother the least
yeah at infers that he still loves I hate my pathetic brother or should I say
ex-brother I broke up with my family I broke up with my brother I do remember
telling my my telling my brother Levi growing up that I wish that there was a
divorce for brother I was like I would do that I would divorce you all right
now let's go to number two number two is your dad my dad is the orange dad my dad
My dad is the only sane and playful member in my family.
Next to me and Fifi, my doggie.
I love my dad.
- My father is, my father growing up was sane but playful.
- Sane and playful.
- When my dad is sane and playful, that's awesome.
- Damn, yeah.
Only, only me, my, only me, my dad and Fifi.
The only sane and playful.
My dad is good, but he has a horrible temper.
And when he's angry enough,
he will not only scream the house down,
he will also throw a temper tantrum fit for a two year old.
(laughs)
Dad, you're acting like a two year old right now to my mom.
Yeah, my dad threw a dad fit.
Yeah.
Dad, you're being a total preschooler to mom right now.
Ugh.
Before my dad died, he used to annoy the crap out of me
by making references to stuff I hated,
but that doesn't mean I disliked him.
My dad is sometimes so stupid, bitchy, and dumb ass man.
Because he is grumpy, annoying, and prim person, arg.
Sometimes I hate her.
Prim person?
what is a prim person the Harry Potter role-playing group what are you gonna
make fun of me for that for living out my dreams yeah go ask your go ask your
boyfriend I don't have a boyfriend down there go ask yeah it is it's Hagrid I
don't have a boyfriend on there Hagrid's your boy I don't have a boyfriend at the
G mod I'll be server with his penis like a wand no I don't have a boyfriend I
don't have a boyfriend at a lot of these are no you say come comey is mouth amiss
and then you shoot it in your mouth with his penis you say I don't say anything
you say I just got my lips you say about a cadaver and you yeah to you yeah
you're like Dumbledore you're like Voldemort with a mouth you're the dumbest
instead of Dumbledore you're the dumbest boar you're instead of Snape you are you
are a total crepe but without a knee no yeah no instead of professor McGonagall
you're Professor Gobbles, Gobbagool.
I'm actually, I'm Professor Patrick Umbridge,
'cause I take Umbridge with you.
No, you're a cum bitch.
You're a cum bitch.
You cum bitch.
You're a cum bitch, you bitch.
Cameron, you gonna step in?
No, you guys go ahead.
Instead of Ron, are you gonna step in?
So, okay, wait, this'll be a little bit of a stretch, okay?
Instead of Ron Weasley, you're Fat Idiot Caleb, you're a shithead.
It's T-O-N, like a ton, because that's how much you weigh.
And then Cheesley, which is what you ate to become a ton of pounds heavy.
Instead of Ron Weasley, you're Pam Beasley, because you're a girl.
Yeah, and then you're Jim, and you look at my bust, and you drool like a monkey.
Hey Pat, is that a Neville Longbottom, your little tongue bottom,
because you've always got a little tongue in your bottom.
That's right.
that's right it's your cats pal see all right now I don't want now I want you to
step off I don't mean you step in anymore yeah you step off you step oh
yeah you got some nerd my dad loves me to pieces same as I do with him it was just
me and him and we lived next to my grandma and grand granddad until my step
mom came along frowny face the pinky master the pinky master you know I never
- Never had a stepmom, had a stepdad, never a stepmom.
Never learned that.
- I never had a stepmom.
- I haven't had one yet.
- Guys don't remarry, dude.
I got my fingers crossed.
- Yeah, they just, they--
- Unless you're rich, guys don't remarry.
- It's true.
- Yeah.
- Rich guys love to remarry.
- Rich guys love to remarry a girl that's like--
- Normal guys--
- The same age as their daughter.
- Hate to remarry.
- Which is pimp.
- Which is pimp as hell.
- I think so.
- I don't think so.
I think you need, if you remarry, you have to marry someone older than you because it's
leveling up.
You can't go prestige.
You gotta keep leveling up.
True, you can't, yeah, you can't, that's what, that is what the divorced rich dad does.
He prestiges back to an 18 year old wife.
Yeah, exactly.
And he drives her around in a Mazda Miata.
Yeah, yeah, or like a Lotus.
A Lotus is a rich dad car.
What's a Lotus?
It's a car.
It's a beautiful flower. It's a lotus car.
You'll see lotus cars. It's a beautiful flower
that represents the seven chakras.
Oh, okay, okay.
Yeah, that's a good divorce guy car.
You know, an extreme divorce guy car
is the Polaris Slingshot.
For sure.
No, the Polaris Slingshot is a marriage saving car.
Yeah, that's a last ditch effort.
You buy the Polaris Slingshot in a last ditch effort
to save your marriage,
And you, and then your dad drives around in it
and he's completely bald and he's got on very, very good--
- I saw a--
- He's got a very good pair of true religion jeans on
and those really weird loafers
that are like squared off at the end.
And he pulls up to the courthouse
playing Billy Eilish bad guy.
(laughing)
And he takes off his sunglasses and flips off your mom.
- Yeah, and he forgets there's no door on it for a second
and tries to open it.
(laughing)
He just mimes opening a door and gets out.
Yeah, and he's like, "Try and take my money now, bitch.
It's in this car."
Your dad installs butterfly doors on a Polaris slingshot.
Yeah, butterfly doors from like an Acura.
Yeah, a dad who gets divorced and then drives around in a Brink armored truck and keeps all
of his belongings in it.
Yeah, you're not getting half.
I put I put an ink cartridge on my Steely Dan records. Yeah
As soon as you leave the apartment, it's gonna explode all over and everybody's gonna know. Yeah, I put those
Those those target anti shoplift like beeping things on to all my children and the dog
Yeah, I put a shotgun in a tripwire above the above the doorway of the man cave
So if you walk in and try to steal stuff, it's gonna be like the end of saw there's claymore at the foot of
- Yeah, I play.
(laughing)
- All right, number three, your mom.
- Yeah, your mom.
You wanna try that?
Hey, hey, you wanna try that again?
- Yeah. - Your mom.
- You know we straight. - Hey, you wanna try
that again?
Your mom. - Your mom.
Your mom.
- What if it's like doing your mom,
but it's not doing your mom,
it's just like he's like, your mom, your mom.
- First comment, just a horrible person.
(laughter)
- This is a horrible person, can't wait to get away from her.
She's superficial, selfish, always complaining
about every single thing.
Stuck up, boastful, illogical, just a major pain in the ass.
- This kid is just leaving, like, this kid is like,
just leaving their dirty laundry across the floor
of every room in the house, just like,
smearing shit on the walls.
And the mom is like, "Can you not do that?"
Wow, I can't wait to get away from you.
You're so superficial, selfish, always complaining
about every single thing.
Let me pee in the aquarium, you controlling bitch.
Let me pee in the aquarium and then eat the fish out of it.
Yeah.
She's the bitchiest person I have ever met.
You are the bitchiest mom.
She's the bitchiest person I've ever met.
She is always complaining, gets mad over everything,
and when she is mad, she slams every door she goes through.
She sucks, F dash dash K her.
Oh man.
If your mom sees that, pal, you're busted.
Here's a comment.
Moms know what goes in those dashes
and they're not gonna like it.
- Yeah, no.
- Mom's not--
- Without your mom, you wouldn't be born from Epic Jake.
- At times I have no problem with her,
but when it comes to video games, dot, dot, dot.
That's right. - Whoa.
- Number four, stepmom.
We got, oh, here we go.
This is kind of a plan.
This is a, okay, this is another sub list.
This user says, oh yes, on my B-day,
I plan to make my step-mom and dad
split up on the spot in front of my friends.
Hopefully it won't fail.
My plan, here's a six step plan, okay?
- All right, I'm gonna write this down.
- Number one, wait for everyone to come.
Number two, deliberately do something
that she'll tell me off for that is so ridiculous
my dad will get seriously angry with her.
Tell my dad that my step-mom told me off
in front of my friends, this will cause an argument.
That's kind of a big second step.
that's a lot of stuff. That might as well be two. Or wait that is
supposed to be three but because it just goes to four next and they just
didn't write three. Okay four I'll act really sad and I'll run into the
bathroom and make my eyes itchy so that they water. I'll say I've been crying.
This is just like a sociopath. Five I'm going to make myself feel an emotion. Dad
super sympathetic and will get mad at stepmom. Number six hopefully the plan
would have worked I feel like we can come up with a better plan to get ready how
do you get rid of your stepmom you guys you you have a dress up dress up like my
my parents are happily married I dress up like a stepmom I don't have a step
parent either of us could I have a stepdad but I on all of my plans have
failed yeah I'm gonna pitch a plan to you all right okay staircase you
you go into your stepdad's room okay you take his clothes you put it on you make
a plaster cast of his head and face okay and you get like a latex mask that looks
exactly like him and then you try to kill your mom okay I've got you kill
your real mom - whoever he's your stepdad is married to your mom oh you stepdad
okay I thought yeah yeah wait I guess that yeah if you're if you have a stepmom
like if you have a stepdad and a mom and then your mom dies and your stepdad
remarries you could have just two step parents I guess so yeah what if your
stepmom marries your stepdad what if your dog marries your mom yeah what
What if your cousin was your dog?
What if the sky was purple?
And you saw it purple but I saw it blue but we both think it's blue.
That's pretty crazy to think about.
Yeah.
I've got a plan to get rid of your stepdad too.
It's kind of like Cameron's plan.
What is it?
You kind of use the same first steps as Cameron's plan.
Okay, copycat.
Copycat alert.
No, no, no.
Let's make a plan to get rid of Patrick.
I am not being a copycat because you're getting to let me finish.
on with the plan then why are you being so defensive okay so you make a plaster
cast you make a latex mold of your stepdad copycat so you go oh my god go
no oh wait you go in this one completely different sorry uh-huh you go you go you
go you go to Walmart and you show everyone your stinky little penis so it's
just a little kid wearing like a shitty Halloween mask
on Walmart showing his penis to everyone. "I'm my dad and this is my penis. Nobody call my wife.
No one tell my new wife I'm doing this." And then the stepdad is just like, "Listen, I really wanted
this marriage to work out but I cannot take care of this child anymore. This is the worst child I've
ever I've ever met in my life. I'm leaving." Next one is a tie. We should move on to the next one
because this is a ton of comments number five is your sister and it has 22
comments on it oh my god the thing is sisters are sisters are they they deal
with the the biggest fury from the the little brother my sister is such a brat
she throws tantrums over the most minor stuff caused by my brother even worse
once maybe even multiple times if she literally tried to kill my brother
geez sisters suck I don't know what is happening them to them these days maybe
some kind of virus is taking control oh my god they knew oh my god oh my god they
friggin met a premonition the sister virus I have to agree with Alexander but
I have to say that sisters are kind of annoying epic Jake my sisters are
tattletales bossy and whiny and I'm the only male please get this to number one
epic Jake they whine and they moan my sister feeds off my dad's money and is
hardly grateful either from potbelly pup listen this one has I think this one has
to be a troll but bros before hoes man so annoying fat hoes geez I wish I had a hot
sister I'm not incest but yeah my sister is so bitchy stupid dumbass person I
will kill my sister and it's sorry guys my family is very weird sorry I will
weird family we try to kill each other. Yeah from what I've been told they're kind of
bitchy especially on PMS but maybe that's just my friend's sisters. As I was a kid
I thought PMS was like a drug. Yeah yeah I thought it was something that your
sister your girls in your life took like a pill. It's actually it's a paranormal
it stands for paranormal mind spirit and it's a blood demon that takes control of
their mind little did I know that PMS stood for Patrick can't think of anything
it stands for Patrick milk Patrick's my sensation I want to keep moving on this
list because there are a lot of really good comments on here and we're almost
out of time number number six your cousin oh yeah this is not cool to say
This is not cool to say.
Yo I love all my fucking cousins dude.
Shout out to all my cousins.
Shout out to all my fucking cousins.
Epic Jake says I have four cousins. Get this off the list also.
Yes, yes Epic Jake.
Dude yeah I'm fucking with my cousins.
I don't need, I mean they don't even make the top 100 kinds of family members.
How can we not talk about family when cousins all that we got.
number seven is your uncle he is a fat arrogant miserable turd uh-uh you not
saying that about uncle's uh-uh first cousins cousins all you know just once
but you talk about my uncles I will rain down on you with a with a fury so great
you're gonna wish you never mentioned Matt and Michael yeah all my uncles
lived in my basement at least at one point in my life and that's true. My uncle
looks like Moby. Uncles love basements. Uncles love living in your basement and
having a Mike's Hard Lemonade folding table that they use. Yeah. Uncles love
living in your grandparents basement and owning two tarantulas. Uh-huh. Yeah. Uncles
love having a iguana in your house. Uncles love having a chair that they got from
their friend's barbershop in their basement apartment. That's the only chair.
- Uncles straight up love having like some weird
beaded green necklace that they hang up
on a thing that they hammered into the wall
that kind of stays in your basement until you're like 16.
- Uncles love having a Peruvian wife and melanoma.
(laughing)
- Uncles love wearing those five toe running shoes
and running through the forest
and hurting their leg really badly
because they ran too far.
- And they love gardening.
There's two kinds of uncles.
There's the gamer uncle and the gardening uncle.
I have a prankster skateboard uncle.
That's a gamer uncle.
Uncles love to get drunk on Easter
and then go to the farmhouse that's like adjacent
to your house and try to ride the horse
and break their jaw.
Yeah, when uncles dress up for church,
they never even think to tuck in their shirts.
Yeah.
No, they don't even, they arrive and you're like,
hey, your shirt's untucked.
And they're like, I didn't even think about that.
I also do, I damn think, I do have a racist New Hampshire uncle also, which I talked about
briefly.
I don't know what part of New Hampshire, I don't really talk to him.
His name's Patrick.
Could be one of my neighbors.
What if we found out that you guys were related?
That would be funny.
That would be really funny.
How would that change your relationship?
Probably, well, Camber being my cousin, hold up.
We're gonna be hanging out way more.
Hey, let's move in together.
I honestly might have to marry into the family if I found that out.
for just because we on whose side whose side would you want to be yeah who would
you pick yeah he's family members weird Cameron's weird computer family or I
don't have a I don't have a weird I have a no I have a boss I have a Boston Irish
why would I have a weird computer family you have a because you're a weird
commuter I have a huge I have a very large boss I have a huge family thank
you very much I'm really fucking huge thank you I do I have the classic Boston
Boston Irish New England family okay how many uncles do you have I honestly don't
- I don't know, I have too many to count.
- He can't even count.
- Well, okay.
- He can't even count how many uncles there are.
- He's counting.
- We're not doing, okay, here's the problem.
The problem here, on my mom's side I only have one,
but my dad's side is the big family.
- My mom's, my aunt's, I got seven aunts and uncles.
- I have, I'm trying to, 'cause aunts don't count.
I don't give a fuck about aunts.
- And I got 15 cousins.
- I literally have 17 cousins.
- Two, three.
- On one side.
I have 17 cousins on one side.
And then I only have two on the other.
So I have 17 cousins in total.
So we're tied for cousins.
My dad's side of the family is famous in Cambridge.
I have 18 cousins.
There's a square in Cambridge named after my great grandfather.
No there's not.
- Francis Downey.
It's right by one of the bus stops.
He was a doctor, he was a really--
- You can be a doctor, Francis.
- Yeah, you're a doctor.
Here, we'll name this square after you.
- You guys are stupid, man.
All the fans know he was--
- I think my uncle's having another kid too,
so I might have 19 cousins.
- Oh, I just got a, wait, hold on, I got a page.
- You did not get a page.
I can see your camera, you did not get a page.
- Hold on, let me call, oh, it's my uncle, Michael.
I just have two new cousins.
You don't have two new cousins.
Their names are Ricardo and Ricardo.
You wish you did, pal.
Yeah, but Caleb, you will never be an uncle.
I will.
You are not an uncle.
I'm already an uncle.
I'm an uncle.
You're not an uncle.
I'm an uncle by marriage, but I'm not married yet.
Nah.
I'm almost an uncle.
(gagging)
That doesn't count.
I'm bordering on uncle.
It counts, dude.
It does not count.
You don't count.
I count.
You can't count.
I'm a real uncle.
You're not.
You're a step uncle.
There's no such thing as a step uncle.
- You're a step uncle.
- There's no such, nobody, let me look this up.
Step uncle.
- You're not the step uncle,
you're the uncle that stepped up.
- A step uncle is, oh, it exists.
- You're so stupid, dude.
- You're the uncle that stepped up.
- But nobody says, nobody says,
like, my uncle Tim is not my step uncle.
He is my uncle who likes Bud Light.
- No, he's your step uncle, pal.
- No, no.
- Do you guys draw a distinction
between uncle and great uncle?
- All uncles are great.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Yeah, so there's a distinction.
- If I'm just counting uncles,
I think I only have four or five,
but if great uncles, I have very many,
'cause my grandmother has 11 brothers.
- I have six uncles.
- And that's just my grandmother.
So just so you guys know,
I have way more uncles than you.
- I have six uncles.
- I literally just said I have at least 16,
and a lot more that I don't know.
- You don't have 16 uncles, I have six uncles.
- Your six is such a pathetically low number, I'm sorry.
- Six is a good number of uncles.
- Do you think that's a good number
'cause that's as high as you can count?
- I can count to 20.
- No, you can't, dude.
- One, two, skip a few, 17, 18, 19, 20.
- Patrick thinks there's a number called skip a few.
He heard someone say that one time in elementary school
and he's like, I just learned the magic number.
Number eight is sister-in-law
and the top comment here says, "Her middle name is Poison."
- And then Epic Jake says, "Sister Poison in law."
Sister Poison law.
(laughing)
Doesn't even say in law.
- Your aunt.
- I don't, I don't, number 10 is mother-
- I barely even recognize aunts.
- Number 10 is mother-in-law,
and it says, "If she beefs you."
(laughing)
- I like on aunts, somebody says,
"I'm vegetarian and my aunt Marsha
makes me eat meat anyway from I hate school what if I'm said nope my aunts are
nice number 12 is your niece slash nephew I never felt a connection to those kids
who are my niece and nephew mostly because they don't know I exist that's
why they're the worst they haven't even reached out hi there has some really good
stuff here in these Latin this he's finishing this one off we passed them
everybody passed the baton to him yeah that one and then 16 on half sistery I
said Kelly my half sister is the reason I'm an uncle
thanks Kelly only comment and then half brother he just says clashing ideologies
listen I just I'm a half brother I just I'm socially a half brother but fiscally
I'm an uncle I just checked hi there's profile it's a really good profile
nineteen-year-old male from Texas I'm a nineteen-year-old man a
a non-denominational follower of Christ, a Trump supporter, and all I say in lists is purely my
opinion, although some opinions are considered fact, like Jesus being the smartest man,
so please don't hate me for it. So I figured I'd put it this way, since messaging all my
followers about this isn't exactly a great way to introduce myself and is time-consuming.
Apparently, there used to be a chatroom on the Top 10s. The link to my homepage is a petition
to get that back. Mind signing it? I'm not going to ask anything else commercial of you.
here he has a giant he has a huge list of his favorite things rock and roll it's
dying but here's a list of my least on Joby and the Beatles and here a list of
my least favorite things rap Satan China and the Simpsons and then wait what
happened to American TV dads here's the best part so he has both the Simpsons
and then at the top anything by Homer yeah yeah you're not gonna like the
Simpsons then big guy yeah exactly you're gonna hate the Simpsons if you don't like
Simpsons if you don't like Homer yeah you're gonna hate Bart and Lisa paste
this on your profile if you like dystopian books the fire it's a fire
emoji a heart emoji of firefighter a key and a bow and arrow the fire is
representative of divergent the heart represents unwind the firefighter
represents Fahrenheit 451 the key represents incarceration and the bow and
arrow represents the Hunger Games I feel like Ray Bradbury would have killed
himself if he saw that company that he's keeping. Anti-bullying message, this is how he closes
out his profile. The girl you just called fat, she is overdosing on diet pills. The girl
you just called ugly, she spends hours putting makeup on hoping people will like her. The
boy you just tripped, he is abused enough at home, just enough. See that man with the ugly
scars? See that man with the ugly scars? He fought for his country. That's the joker.
- That guy, that guy you just made fun of for crying,
his mother is dying.
Put this on your profile if you're against bullying.
I bet 95% of you won't put this on your profile,
but I'm sure the people with a heart and a backbone will.
Which percentage are you, 5% or 95%?
- This is what-- - 5% or leave.
- The 5%-er, that's what Rich Piana was talking about.
Rich Piana, the 5%-er stuff. - These are 5%-ers.
Yeah, this is a Nation of Islam anti-bullying message.
- Oh, yeah, is that?
that that is a that is a nation of islam thing huh
because if i can because rich piano had that as a scientist who just created the
white man his name's yakub
and you're going to post this
yet
he has twenty five signatures on his petition to bring the chat room back to
the top ten
let's get let's get everyone to sign it so yeah i'm gonna i'm going to uh...
post the latest as louis farrakhan you just made fun of
he's actually really busy planning the assassination of malcolm x so you might
want to be
did he do that
i had to be definitely that shit
i don't really listen
everybody i don't believe it should do
yeah i
i think that he did not do that
he did it he's the man
uh... i'm gonna put a link to the other day
you gave a look at the other two eight
Check out this picture I'm sending in the chat.
No.
Okay.
Your loss.
Send it.
I'm trying.
You can't figure out how to send it?
I'm going to destroy you.
Nice though.
It's Rich Piana eating a raw steak.
Damn he looks good.
He looks sick dude.
Dude that's so crazy though that he just called it like 5%ers not thinking like...
No one has ever thought of this word before.
5%er yeah.
Yeah, no one has ever said that before and then you see all these like...
Jay Z thinks he is.
Yeah.
Man, RIP Rich Piana.
Yeah, that's his initials, right?
That you're saying RIP.
RIP.
That's why you said that?
His middle name was Eugene.
His middle name was I-Gene.
He ate that steak and he died.
Yeah.
All right, subscribe to the Patreon.com/podcastaboutlist.
We got cool stuff coming out on there.
I finally got fired so throw that money in there.
You did?
Yeah.
Nice.
Congrats man.
How did you get fired?
Just being too awesome and not doing my job at all.
Did they?
Oh.
Woo!
That's right.
I was too focused on gaming and making podcasts so pay me back.
I gotta go.
Alright bye.
Bye.
[BLANK_AUDIO]