You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- I'm recording.
- Shout out to the stand up shot subreddit.
- Yeah, we need to talk about this.
- First of all, we gotta pay respect
to the stand up shot subreddit.
- Pay respect to the real ones.
- I mean, I remember getting, I used to watch,
I mean, I remember the first time I ever heard George Carlin, it was him posting his jokes
on the stand-up shot subreddit.
Over a picture of him like looking at a cup of coffee.
Remember when Lenny Bruce got banned from Reddit for saying damn much truth?
In the 60s, yeah, he got thrown out of the stand-up shot subreddit.
Here are the seven words you can't say on Reddit.
woman female just a list of female the cake is true Ellen the last Jedi cake is
true yeah yeah right Star Wars Ray Star Wars Ray you can't say Star Wars Ray
yeah um yeah ethics and game journalism uh-huh cop bad yeah that's just you know
just a rule those are the seven words of reddit yeah yeah I love dude reddit
Stand-ups I think are a, they're a truly just a rare breed. It's insane. Have you seen the, have you seen the stand-up comedy subreddit?
No. Did they talk about us too or is it just out of the loop? No, no, no. I just maybe, yesterday I just like was
thinking about like reddit stand-ups and I went to the to the stand-up comedy sub
and just every post is like people asking why they're not funny and why
nobody laughs. They're like I'm doing everything. I have my stage name Anton
penis but I go up every single night and I just eat shit talking about my mom.
Yeah. It rocks dude. I mean yeah, the stand-up shots subreddit is so fucking
depressing. Like it's just you look at the stuff that that does well there day
to day and it's just like like these are the comedians who aren't who are aren't
even good enough to like justify to themselves getting out of the house to go
to an open mic. Yeah. Like that's the best part. Like even a guy taking a picture of
him in his kitchen yeah like it's not so many of them he's not even doing stand-up
or it's like a picture of him like like thoughtfully like looking into the
corner yeah yeah and he's like under a tree yeah you know yeah so sick dude yeah
and it's some joke about Trump yeah it's a it's a whole man I got yeah it's like
yeah it's a guy it's a guy like like just sitting in his sitting go runs it yeah
just a guy sitting in his living room with tented fingers and then just like
an impact font caption that's like yeah so my family loves to read the Bible but
they hate to read other books what's going on and then just like at the
comedy guy alpaca bacon one two three yeah sometimes I sometimes I feel like
I'm when I'm at home I'm playing Clue and the answer is stupid girlfriend with the
iPad in the bedroom. Yeah that just this just reminded me of one of the all-time
grades which is I have a time-based pie eating disorder I eat pie all the time.
I forgot about that. One of the best stand-up shots of all time. We have spent so much time on that subreddit.
I have a time-based pie eating disorder. The best part of that stand-up shot that
that joke that I have a time-based pie eating disorder I eat pie all the time is
it was there were three different jokes on one stand-up shot like that was
It's like the middle joke in like three nonsense.
Is that Scott Walker?
No.
Who did that one?
I don't think so.
That's a different, yeah.
Scott Walker comedy?
We're at a point where we know their fucking names.
Scott Walker is the one who did like, "If I see a dog and I can't pet it, I die."
He does stuff like that.
Oh yeah.
One second, I'm going to look up, I have a time-based pie.
The picture of him is like, is like him screaming.
Yeah.
I need to find... I think this picture might be lost to time to be honest I have a time
based pie eating disorder.
Lost to time, lost to pie. Yeah.
I was lost to pie eating.
Yeah the only thing that comes up when I google the phrase I have a time based pie eating disorder
is our podcast.
Nice, we've claimed that joke. We've stolen it.
I didn't know that we had that anywhere.
It's in the description of episode 39.
We must have talked about stand-up shots in the past.
I'm sure we have.
Because that must have been the time.
That must have been the time we were done.
It's pretty fun.
I think we definitely talked about that joke on a podcast before.
Yeah, that one, but at the time when you posted that one where it's just the really long text
and it got downvoted a lot.
Oh yeah.
That one was the best.
Man, people hate good comedy.
That is good.
I know.
It's true.
Also, the best part about that one is that the photo that you had on it was you doing
that joke, right?
Yeah.
It's a real joke. It's funny as hell, they just don't understand me, you know?
It's kind of one of those situations where I've got too many kind of depths in my brain and different lengths and widths that kind of go on and try to...
You're like Dangerfield.
Yeah, I'm like... I'm exactly... I'm kind of the dangerous comic, is that what you're saying?
No, no, no. Rodney... Yeah, you're Mr. Dangerfield.
I'm like Dangerous Neil, you know? I'm like Rodney Dangerous Neil, 'cause I kind of tell jokes that are so dangerous they make you kneel during the anthem.
'Cause you're so twisted.
- I thought you were talking about Neil.
- No, no, no, that guy on Twitter, Dangerous Neil.
I thought you were talking about him.
- I don't know who that is.
- Is that a guy?
- Yeah, that's a guy.
- No, it's not.
- I just made that up.
- No, that's a real guy.
- You just think that's a guy
'cause you think that everything you hear is real.
- Cam, you just manifested that, brother.
- Yeah, I'm manifesting energy.
- Shout out to Dangerous Neil, I guess.
- I just hex Dangerous Neil.
- No, don't hex him.
- Dude, take it back.
- He's a good dude.
- Okay, take it back.
- Take it back right now.
- I take it back.
I take it back.
But yeah, Patrick, what the results of this, of the, so yeah, everyone was posting the fucking...
I didn't know all of you were going to go Operation Crapstorm on our standup shots.
Yeah, that shit was crazy.
I was just refreshing the new page on standup shots and literally like every time I refreshed
there was one or two new ones.
Like they were going faster than the mods could delete them.
It was incredible.
Yeah.
one like lonely guy who made the fucking subreddit so he could post his stand-up
shots I thought it started out reason he posts he made the subreddit I thought it
would start it out as like stand-up shots from like specials that people were
watching like oh look at this joke and then it turned into just open mic guys
being like oh no okay well I don't I don't know anyway yeah back in the day
it was it was you know it was like Patrice and Louie and they were posting
their stand-up shots on there. Patrice and Louis posting their stand-up shots we had
Greg Giraldo RIP he was doing roasts in the comments of the post.
Yeah he would roast Patrice and Louis and Lisa Lampanelli would too but
then they would say that Lisa Lampanelli had sex with a black guy once.
And then well anyway I got a got a DM from the moderator and I didn't know
that he followed me and he follows me yeah he was pretty I mean read the DM
if you don't I will he said did I do I feel kind of bad reading it now come on
to fuck this guy you fucking come on. This is not the yeah. I'm gonna read it if you don't
read it. I'm sorry that you actually had to. You fucking up my subreddit today.
Yeah this has to be personal. It's sick because I mean it's such a cesspool to begin with
like every post is like yeah I saw my Chinese neighbor out the other day I
hope he doesn't eat my cat. Right. One of the top posts when one of the top
One of the top posts when we posted that was like, "I learned today that Israel is in Asia,
so now whenever I see the Jewish guy who works at the store next door, I bow and say thank
you very much to him."
Yeah.
Doug is like, literally just sit like that.
Thank you very much, Mr. Goldstein.
That was the punchline.
Is there a stereotype where you-
But you know that there was supposed to be, "Thank you very much, Mr. Goldstein," was
supposed to be read in a voice.
Yeah, and a very specific accent.
My question is do, is there a stereotype that Asian people say thank you a lot?
Well they bow.
They say thank you and bow.
Oh, okay.
That's the stereotype.
That's what they do.
Maybe I'm just so anti-racist I don't know any of the stereotypes.
If you watch South Park in the early 2000s, there's an episode where Cartman dresses up
like a Japanese person and says thank you a bunch.
So I think he got it from there.
Wait, Cartman did that?
Yeah.
fuck I I didn't be I didn't want to have to cancel oh my god I had no idea that
Cartman did that early in his career that's really fucked up yeah it was
early enough in his career it was bad guys it was a long time ago he was in
third grade he was making fun of fat kids who dress up like Japanese guys
grade yeah I don't know I feel like we got to cut him some slack mm-hmm also
think about the people who are around you know he's like I can't even cut it
Kenny can't even step up to him and confront him because he can't talk he's
He's like a friend of a friend I guess so I feel kind of bad for bringing that up.
Carmen? Yeah. You know someone who knows Carmen? Every fat guy knows each other.
Wait, are you guys like cousins? Carmen is a friend of Ralphie May who is a friend of Patrick.
Uh-huh yeah another rest in peace. Pat you should just get super fat dude.
I think I'm gonna get thinner living here. No no you no get really fat. Why?
Why? Why would I want Patrick to get thin? I want him to win.
That's losing.
If I, yeah, it would be losing.
If I'm winning, I'm gaining points.
If you're winning, you're gaining.
Okay, fine, Patrick, I want you to get fat then.
Now I don't want to, now I want to get thin again.
Okay, I want you to get thin.
I think because I don't have a car or a license, I'm gonna have to...
I'm gonna start sending you edible arrangements.
Oh, I gotta fucking, god damn it.
Oh, I gotta eat that edible arrangement.
I got so mad. Oh my god.
No, I have to... I forgot I have a frozen Snickers bar that I have to eat so soon.
I took it out of the freezer to thaw and forgot about it.
I have to renew my license.
Oh shit, yeah.
I was supposed to do that. I was supposed to call the DMV,
like, before this and I didn't because I was setting up a table.
You got two days.
You have two days?
Yeah, I have two days to do it but I have to... it expires on the 23rd.
You don't drive, it doesn't matter, right?
Well, I still need a license.
For what?
buying cigarettes. Nice. They're six bucks here. Are you back on cigarettes? I don't know, I might.
I might just. Might as well. Do it man. Cigarettes, super fucking fat guy. 20 bucks for Juul Pods.
Big and fat guy, hamburger Patrick, smoking a cigarette. I don't know, I feel like this could
be a huge, a huge new era for you. I don't even know. I don't, I think, it's either I'm gonna get,
I'm gonna be so bored here that I just eat myself to death like Orson Welles
or like I go like... You're a lot like Orson Welles. Yeah? In what way? I mean just in a lot of ways,
you know. In what ways? I mean you're just super, you're super fat.
Like Orson Welles. Yeah. Yeah. You're a great actor. Thank you. I've not had my shot at um,
Well, I do. I do. Technically, I do radio also.
Yeah.
Just like Orson Welles, dude.
Just like Orson. Oh, no. I'm gonna die eating fucking candy like Orson Welles.
Wait, do the... Let's do the War of the Worlds.
Okay.
We could do that.
We could do War of the Worlds right now.
Yeah.
Hey, guys. Oh, sh... Oh, guys, I didn't mean to interrupt you guys. There's a... I think there's a...
There's aliens.
Weird... There's a weird guy.
I think an alien came out. I think an alien came out, guys. Guys, I think an alien just came out.
An alien just came out.
- Pat, don't look behind you, there's an alien behind you.
- Hey, Michael, there's probably someone named Michael
listening to this, so let's do like, Michael, watch out!
- Michael!
- Michael, Michael, punch your penis.
- Michael, stop the car.
- There's an alien coming out, Michael.
- Michael, stop the car, get out now.
- Make a U-turn, I don't care if you're on the highway.
- Make another U-turn, go back to first level.
- Pull into the jack in the box.
- Okay, now pull back out.
- Michael, stop the car and get out.
Okay, now-
Michael, whatever you do, Michael, don't look in the trunk, get out of the car.
Michael, if you're driving right now, close your eyes.
Michael, I love you.
Michael, close your eyes, don't look in the trunk.
Michael, say goodnight to me.
Michael, you're stuck in a game of crazy taxi.
Michael, pull, Michael, Michael.
Pull.
Open the-
Michael, pull.
Michael, pull if you're listening to this.
Pull.
Michael, pull, open the hood of your car on the highway.
Do it right now, pop the hood.
Michael, show me your boobs.
show the driver your boobs show the bus driver your boobs Mike Michael Michael
you have to do it Michael you have to save America right now Michael you have
to you have to do this for the I hope we have one crazy person listening to this
yeah it's Michael not even named Michael it's a frantic fan who's like just
we've been waiting to go nuts like was just named Michael Pole.
Yeah.
It's so fucking hot in New York right now.
It's like 110 degrees.
Yeah, man.
It's the same all summer.
I think it yeah, it's pretty hot here too.
We've had this horrible three month heat wave.
I think we've literally already made this joke on the last episode.
No!
I don't even know, I fuckin'...
Man, I went on a two-mile walk today.
I went to...
What are you creaking around?
Nothing, that's the cat.
His old antique chair that he lives in.
Yeah, was the cat playing on a rocking horse or something?
The cat was playing on a rocking horse.
Okay.
Exactly.
I'm so smart.
Yeah.
What was I gonna fuckin' say?
Two-mile walk.
Two-mile round-trip walk.
I went to...
'Cause I wanted to see, I've driven by it a bunch of times.
It is, there's a castle that says Candy Kingdom on it, but I found out this morning, I was
like, "Oh, what is that?"
So I wanted to see if it was a candy castle.
Turns out it's a therapist's office that is inside of a castle.
it is across the street like diagonally from a shack that is a chili dog stand
and a notary public that's so sick so awesome and I'm moving to New Hampshire
you got it you got it fucking come to this guy's shack you need to get a you
need to get a gun dude dude he said in the shack I went in there found out it
was
allowed one person in the store at a time where that was the rule before COVID.
Every town in New Hampshire like grew around just a shack that is two unrelated things
in the same building.
Yeah.
Like that's just how they create towns in New Hampshire.
There's a...
I'm from Blockbuster Home Depot, New Hampshire.
town is just named after the two biggest chain companies I'm from I'm from candy
shop gynecologist yeah I'm from library tattoo parlor I'm from preschool
shooting range that's a little too close to home you might want to walk that one back
Yeah, there was actually, there was, there was, there was a shooting, there was a
shooting at a preschool in Bank 7-11 at New Hampshire. Alright, you're right, yeah,
this is the episode where we're not gonna joke about school shootings, you're right
guys. I'm sorry, I think we need to lay off, dude. Yeah, I think we got to lay off.
I don't, we've never, we've never really talked about school shootings, we've
talked about one specific shooting no we talked we've talked about Mandalay Bay
okay let's do Columbine this time no we'll switch our Caleb talks about Adam
Lanza like every episode not I'm not every episode I can I'm sorry I'm not
like I'm the last normal episode we added we had a joke about the school
bringing a chimpanzee to school oh yeah it's a different that's that's just
like it's like a shark tank invention yeah that's not like talking about a
Caleb's invention and we didn't have one of those in a long time so we had to do
one good do one for the old fans oh no wait no cuz the cloaca cube episode is
in the dark it's in the dark in the dark timeline the dark 31 the dark 31 that's
what I started calling them we gotta figure out how to they're never being
released we have to figure out how to edit one word from each of those into a
sentence and then we'll release that the dark sentence yeah sentence and then we
can we can put all of them on a thumb drive and sell it to we can put him on a
thumb drive and just throw it into the sewer somewhere what if I what if I I'll
put it on I'll put the first 31 episodes on a thumb drive in a manila envelope
and hide it somewhere in New York City and you can somebody has to I will give
I will give cryptic clues once a week as to where it is.
Stuff like, uh...
McDonald's.
Yeah, stuff like, you might be loving it when you find this envelope in a hamburger...
In the bathroom of McDonald's.
In the bathroom of your loving it here.
And they'll be like, "You might pick two."
This is like Cicada 3301, I just can't do this.
We should, we should, um...
I feel like it would be funny if we did do a scavenger hunt.
When you find this thumb drive, you're gonna want to Taco Bell-bout it to all of your french
fries pizza ice cream.
We will be the only podcast to do a scavenger hunt.
That would be another feather in the cap.
I feel like we can do it.
I feel like we're the ones pushing the boundaries.
We're changing the form.
- I mean, that's probably the easiest thing to do.
You just take an object and you put it somewhere.
- Also, we're just good at clues.
We're like three of the top clue masters that there are.
- Yeah, we've worked with clue masters before.
- We have, we've worked with the supreme clue master.
So I feel like we could do it, you know?
Like hide it, like where would we hide it?
We'd hide--
- Well, we can't say it on the podcast.
The belly of a whale.
What about the center of the earth?
What do you guys think about that?
And then for the clue, we can say, even if you're in the middle of nowhere, you'll find
this clue the middle of somewhere.
And you can write that in a quill on a piece of parchment and then upload it online to Twitter.
I'm gonna put it in a bottle and put do a message in a bottle and send it in
We could put it in the ocean.
It lands on the shore of one of those those tribes that is like never had any contact with the outside world
And then they develop a list based society
Oh, yeah, six months later somebody some other fucking Christian missionary tries to go there and they've all they live in a future technology paradise
Yeah, six months later
There's a knock on your door and you open your door and just a hundred tribes people just just bow
turn you into a pincushion with arrows.
Yeah. All standing in the hallway of your apartment. They just take over your
apartment they're living there. They take over the podcast. Yeah. We each. We still
make the money. Now that's ideal. It's you two and a hundred tribesmen. Yeah.
and they're like the... Hold on, hold on, you hold no no one of you hold the fucking mic all right
look I thought I was bad with it. No that would be the best is if they had perfect form yeah
they're audio always sound... We have like a guest on. They just send flack files yeah I mean it's unbelievable we have a guest on
I mean podcasting... They're like making him ride the Sibian. Yeah. Podcasting is a primal instinct you don't have to know how to do
anything to do it you know it harkens back to back in the cavemen days when
when you know one one caveman would sit would gun caveman would sit in his cave
and he would draw you know kind of like a racist caricature but like ironically on
the wall then all the other cavemen would come in the next day and look at it
while they are on their way to work and then yeah and go on Gabunga and then go
yeah and then go and kill whoever looks like that and then back in the day they
would they would string up two rocks with one with whoever was the most blessed
caveman had one very long pube they would cut it off and tie it to each rock and
then they would talk into it like a telephone yeah that's true
Alexander Graham Bell was actually a caveman who just lived that long he was
just yeah he's just gonna recreate his old technology that he he also invented
Yeah. One of the best. All right, top five inventors go. Okay, Tesla. Dr. Tesla. Elon
Musk. Dr. Musk. Bob Steve Jobs. Dr. Pepper. He invented Dr. Pepper. Dr. Pepper with his
30 flavors. Dr. Thunder. Dr. Pepper's brother. 30 flavors, man that's some bullshit.
32. Give me one flavor, vanilla. I thought. How about that? John Battery, the
inventor of the batteries. Maybe two flavors, vanilla and chocolate. Maybe one flavor, Dr. Pepper.
Exactly. Steven the car. Steven University inventor of the universe. I feel
disrespected. Yeah, Justin Roiland. Justin Roiland has actually come up with so many
incredible inventions for that show. You know, the time gun, the wet gun, the super...
alcoholic grandpa slime Rick and ball mr. mr. Jerry mr. me seeks yeah aliens
he invented aliens shout out to Ridley Scott who invented alien yeah he was
like what if there was a different kind of guy yeah what is there a scary guy
what if the scariest guy ever was in the scariest place ever outer okay so okay
So I found a new type of guy.
(laughter)
It's a xenomorph.
It has a mouth in its mouth.
Yeah, super normal.
Yeah, that's normal.
I found an alien wife guy.
Love to have a penis mouth that impregnates a woman on a spaceship.
I seriously love that.
I love being that normal.
Yeah.
(sigh)
Why the fuck do they only sell mental
mint all jewel pods now.
- They got rid of mint 'cause of fucking teenagers.
- Yeah.
- Teenagers like mint too much.
- If you have a nicotine addiction,
you have to smoke a poop flavored air
because poop is a heroin. - That is gonna be
the next step.
That's 10 years from now,
the government's gonna make all cigarettes mandated
they're either poop or pee flavored.
- They will have a poop jewel.
- Yeah.
- And it's the only one that companies are allowed to make.
- I mean, all they have to do is put the nicotine salts
and a little bit of glycerin in it.
and they put a little bit of pee in there.
I mean that--
- Just a little sprinkle of tinkle.
- A little sprinkle of tinkle in that Juul pod,
you're good. - Who's gonna care?
- Yeah, people are still gonna smoke 'em.
- I like your cool guitar in the background, Pat.
- Oh, thank you.
Thank you, I have many guitars.
- You're just turning in your chair
just to show us the guitar.
- Do you like it? - You suck.
You can't play that.
- I can play it.
- Do it, Slash.
- I've played it on the show before
and you got mad at me.
- My boy Patrick liked the white Slash.
I have the same birthday as Slash.
Yeah?
Yeah, uh, 23rd.
1488.
No.
That's your birthday, you Nazi?
No, I'm not born in '88.
Yeah, your birthday is, your birthday was HH.
No.
Yeah, that's right.
It is.
Happy Happy.
You're, you're, yeah.
That's what it stands for.
Your birthday's 6666, you fucking monster little demon bitch.
Yeah.
You fucking weird ass freak.
I'm the devil.
I'm not a freak if I'm the devil.
I'm actually being-
The devil is, the devil is God's freak.
The devil is the freak.
The devil is-
The devil is basically the weird kid in God's class.
Yeah.
Right?
That's you.
You're the weird kid's class.
I'm not the weird kid.
I never was, dude.
You were the weird kid.
I was a kid.
No, I'm not.
I was a kid when life was a nightmare.
I was a kid.
I was a kid and life was so unfair.
Yeah, nobody cared, dude.
I was alone in the world.
I woke up at seven.
Everybody else was having fun except me.
I went to bed at 7 and woke up at 11 just to see if anyone would call.
Nobody did dude.
No one called.
No one fucking did.
Alright, y'all wanna hop into this list?
Sure.
Here wait, I have to pee.
Yeah, me too.
I gotta...
Oh my god, are you kidding me?
Yes, 26 minutes in.
Pee time.
Ooh yeah.
Alright, are we back?
We have to edit this out.
I had to get a soda.
A drink.
Alright, we got this list.
I need to go destroy the world real quick.
This list is-
Yeah, 'cause you look like Stewie Griffin, bitch.
No, I don't.
Oh, no, no.
(laughing)
No, no.
Yes, yes.
Yeah, you do.
I have no idea.
You both look like the dog and the girl combined.
I don't look like Meg, you look like Stewie.
You look like Meg, dude.
No, no, you look like Bertram.
You look like Stewie's, Nenemesis.
You look like Stewie's evil twin, Bertram.
He said Nenemesis.
Man, shut up.
I said Nemesis.
You ain't Nemo.
I'm Nemo.
You ain't Nemo?
Nah, you look like all the Rugrats combined.
That's fine.
Yeah.
One inch tall and two.
That's fine.
No, it's not fine.
Because then I'm the same height as you.
Stewie the baby.
I'm huge, dude.
I'm not Stewie the baby.
No, you're Rugrats the kids.
Rugrats the kid?
Rugrats the kid.
You're the famous outlaw.
I'm Rugrats the kid.
No that's what you are basically.
You're basically Stewie.
You're basically, now that I look at you, you're pretty much a poo.
Do your Stewie impression.
I don't have one because it's so far away from who I am.
It's like me trying to do an impression of like Jackie Kennedy.
Like it's impossible.
I thought you were going to say Jackie Chan.
Caleb, you're like if Caillou learned crime statistics.
No, not true.
Yeah, you are.
No.
Yeah, no, not true.
statistics why cuz I fight crime yeah yeah yeah I'm not I'm not racist and I'm
not a Caillou and I have hair you can see my hair I have hair all over my head
colored your head with a colored pencil before you started no I didn't I didn't
No, I know I know just scribbled on your head the sorry be here your hair right here Harold in the purple crayon
You look like Harold the purple crayon use the purple crayon the color in your hair
You're hairy in the purple penis. I have a purple penis. I'm Harry in the Henderson's and you're Harold in the purple crayon. Yeah, not
Some fat have covered in hair
Meanwhile, really just did Peter Griffin when you said fat fat and I'm fat
Fat and I'm covered in hair
Yeah, you're basically living his dream right now. No, I'm not yeah eating food. I'm drinking soda
You that's his other. It's a second dream
Wanted to eat food the other is to drink a soda yeah, that's pretty good to me
What's this list man top 10 reasons the world today sucks by superior?
77 the description of the list is it is self-explanatory. Please do not bring celebrities into this either
Number one Bieber number one
Yeah, number one is war
And the creator of the list superior 77 says there is so much war and conflict going on today my home country
Afghanistan was destroyed by conflict
This is a this is I think our first Afghani list
Yeah. Oh, oh, speaking of the Justin Bieber thing.
How many of the, uh, of Afghani top tens list do you think are about how bad war sucks?
I know, okay, I said that without reading the Justin Bieber thing. I said it without reading
this person's bio because their bio, their about thing just says, "I am personally not a fan of
Justin, but I feel that people are really beginning to take everything too far, especially when people
People hate the song purely because Justin is in it.
And if you want to put him out of business, stop talking about him.
Whoa.
So.
That's right.
Don't give him the time of day.
Yeah, don't even give Justin the time of day.
Saying his name gives him power.
There's a comment, these comments are not very funny on the war one, but they are funny
in how different they are from what we're usually accustomed to from the top tens.
comment says "my grandfather and grandmother were brutally slain in a
massacre 20 years ago" which I just get that's an insane comment to see on this
website. Someone says "this has been a very horrible issue ever since ancient
times and still keeps going on today" That's from Joe Boy. That's from Noam
Chomsky. Yeah. Wow. Wow. Thank You Professor Chomsky. Number two is "corrupt
leaders that's right mean parents mm-hmm horrible teachers grow school lunches
yeah yeah there's a comment on this this is my one rules yep I wonder why this is
a head I wonder why this is a problem cough Democrats cough Obama cough Lyndon
B Johnson I'm blaming it all on LBJ yeah it goes all the way back yeah I'm
I'm pulling up the US debt clock and just getting pissed off at LBJ right now.
Oh my god.
What did you say?
25 trillion?
There's a comment that says, "Especially in Brazil, I hope Bolsonaro will be a good president."
Oh no.
Yeah, and I'm pretty sure this is an old list too.
Yeah.
Bolsonaro's been great, dude.
He does a funny prank every week where he pretends to die.
Yeah, this list is from 2015.
So that person commented saying, "I hope Bolsonaro will be a good president in 2015."
Every fucking news article about Bolsonaro that comes out is like,
"President Bolsonaro lost a poker game against an evil monkey,
and the monkey jacked him off, but not very good, and he couldn't come."
And he's in the hospital right now for that.
He's in the hospital bed just like...
Like he's always got like...
Bolsonaro in the hospital with blue balls.
He got such bad blue balls that he had humongous elephantitis yoga ball ballsack,
and now he's in the hospital and they're draining it.
They're draining it.
But for some reason the female nurse can't get anything out.
So they're working on getting him a beautiful man.
- Yeah.
- He's also gay.
- What is he?
- I don't know, I like him.
I think he has swag, dude.
- Is Bolsonaro gay?
- Yeah, dude.
- Is he? - He's super gay.
- I didn't know he was.
- No, he's not gay.
- He hates and kills gay guys.
- His name is literally short for balls in a romance.
that's think about it yeah think about it and think about chair or Jair how do you
pronounce the first name gay exactly yeah the signs are there president
Bolsonaro today got stuck in a zip-up bait hoodie and they're having to use
the jaws of life to pry his nose out of the zipper.
Ball sack a-hole dude, he wants to do the booyah.
True.
Um, number three is racism.
And the two comments on here are, "Isn't it ironic that white kids are getting racism
upon them?"
And "Everybody can be racist and it's fine.
Unless you're white."
That's true, man.
That's some real shit.
Yeah.
Racism is fine against white people.
That is true.
I don't know.
Nobody does care.
I mean, I don't care.
Anytime somebody, you know, all the times that I get called a cracker, I barely even
blink.
Yeah.
By you too.
Every time you two call me a cracker, like it hurts, but I acknowledge that it's fine
because I'm white.
The reason I wanted to do this list is because at this point it starts to be 50/50 with stuff
that's actually making the world suck and some top tens-isms.
Number 4 is immature children.
That's true.
Just under war, corrupt leaders, and racism.
Immature children.
Immature kids.
The creator of the list comments, "At school, kids under 10 talk about drugs and other subjects,
but in an immature way."
Yeah, they're talking about drugs.
They're like, "I'm gonna do, I'm gonna take a crap on drugs."
They're saying freaking goo goo gaga marijuana at school now, and we're just letting this
happen?
Goo-goo is actually what people in the street call GHB.
- Yeah, watch out, your kids are saying goo-goo gaga.
What they actually mean is I'm smoking,
I'm addicted to marijuana.
- I'm addicted to GHB and other research chemicals.
- Yeah, know what your kids are using as shorthand.
Things like mama and dada can actually mean--
- Mama is marijuana.
- Dada is crack cocaine, actually.
- Yeah.
- So just be wary.
- If your kid says, "I'm going gaga for PCP,"
they might actually be doing PCP.
- Yeah, that's true.
- That's something you should watch out for.
That's a warning sign.
That's a translation of-- - Mama dada.
I'm addicted to crocodile.
They could actually have drug issues.
- Bubba, like when a baby wants like its bottle.
No, it's not Bubba.
Bubba actually means barbiturates.
Bar-bar-bit-barbituates. They're saying they're gonna take two.
They're gonna take two barbituates just like Marilyn Monroe and they're gonna get
knocked the fuck out.
Yeah. Mama actually stands for Marilyn Monroe
who died of drugs and so when they say Mama they're saying that they wanna
they say they wanna join the 27 club. They wanna do enough barbituates
to kill an elephant. The 27 month club. Learn the... how about that?
Yeah, that's what they're joining. That's what all these kids are joining now.
Learn the little over two years old. Learn the dangerous
acronyms that your kids might be using and abbreviations in their text messages. Like
when a kid says, "Hey, do you want to do LSD?" What they're actually saying is, "Hey, do you
want to do lysergic acid diethylamide?"
They're saying, "Let's skate, dude."
Yeah.
That's what they're saying.
Let's...
Let's skate, dude. And skating, it means going on the ice. That's cocaine.
Yeah.
Cocaine.
laid a smelly dump.
(laughter)
That's what they're saying.
Licking...
Yeah, I just LSD'd in the bathroom.
Licking stamps, dad.
Yeah.
Looking secretly at dad.
Your child may be watching you.
(laughter)
Yeah.
Your child may be watching you.
I plan to put that fuckin' two-way mirror in the office.
The dad takes his son's phone
to look through the text messages
and make sure nothing's going on.
They see LSD and he turns around
there's like a hole in the wall and the kid is just peeking through.
There's a painting and his eyes are in the painting.
Hey, come to think of it, I don't know, I don't remember hanging this painting up of my son
that has his eye holes cut out.
Did you guys have, did your parents like take your phone and look at it?
No.
A few times, but not, I got very angry.
Dude, I would just go and I'd just nuke my phone, I'd delete everything from it.
As if like, that's less incriminating.
like oh my son has never sent a text message. My parents trusted me too much
growing up. That is so apparent. Yeah. Yeah. I think we all knew that. How? How is that
apparent? You have a guitar and you're addicted to taquitos. What does me having
a guitar have to do with it? Bad kids have guitars. Yeah, I see in your room a TV, a
guitar there's no TV skateboards well what's that box that's yeah box I see
shoes you know your your parents may not have gone through your phone but I know
who did it was the devil and he liked what he saw when you when you're looking
up the tables way to play to play fucking CKY songs I'm converting to
Christianity oh yeah be one of those guys now I'm gonna be a trad cat the guy
yeah I think I'm basically gonna be Catholic yeah yeah you're not you're
gonna be one of those Catholic guys it's like well it's fine I figured out how to
lower the chair just those guys that be Catholic oh yeah I'm Catholic now
regardless of all the fucking pedophilia whatever being on the left it's it's it's
it you can just be anti-semitic that's why people do it yeah yeah and you don't
you can just disagree with them circumvent having to care about
about pedophilia. Right. Yeah, exactly. You can kind of like if you don't care about
the Epstein stuff but you still want to be a leftist, you know, you just become
Catholic and then you love pedophiles. Yeah, that's true. Yeah.
Yeah, I know about the Epstein stuff. I love it. I wish he was Catholic too. He
could have done some great work for our church. Yeah, it's really he focuses
energy on the wrong place yeah yeah he's he's playing for the other team you meet
another pedophile you really like and you find out that they're a Masai agent
and not Catholic oh I thought no I was thinking like like parents thinking like
"Oh yeah, they play for the other team and it's just like they just go to a different church."
Catholic Chris Rock saying there's Catholics and then there's pedophiles.
And he's saying it as the pedophiles are the good ones. Yeah. Yeah, because that's funny.
Yo, that's some funny-ass shit, man, for real. Number five is bad music. And the top comment
here is music should go back to the way it was in the 1930s and 1940s the era of
proper music and things like electronic dance music should be banned as it is
not music music in the 30s and 40s fucking sucked it was sick dude
everything was about playing hopscotch with a girl bird just flying to
someone's house what was there a bird in your house? I have a clock that that fuck me dude this
fucking clock you have a bird in your house. Janet got a clock that makes a bird sound on
every hour on the hour and I hate it and I always forget to turn it off before we record it will
make me go insane. Caleb that has happened like multiple times during recording and I've never
thought. I know I just forget every single time. That's the first time I've noticed it.
That's happened every. It happens and I'm always like please nobody say anything
Talk about this clock, dude.
It's fucking- I hate it so much.
But it was like- it was like $40.
This fucking stupid clock, dude.
Girls are dumb.
Here's the second comment on this.
Girls are so dumb.
"I used to love rap and pop and then it went downhill on the late 2000s.
More and more bad singers came in.
Hardly any good singers.
From Ralph the Pizza."
Pizza?
Ralph the Pizza, dude. It's a cool name.
Once we lost Kevin Rudolph, dude.
Yeah.
It was basically over. I mean what, everything went downhill as soon as rap and rock and
roll combined when Kevin Rudolph made Let It Rock. Bad music. Kevin Rudolph overdosed on
Nas Energy drink. Yeah. He kind of ruined music forever. Have you seen him? Have you
seen him now? He looks awesome dude. He's the best. He looks like he's slowly turning
into Blue Strap now. Whoa dude. Yeah, it's awesome. I mean he just looks like every skateboarder
who's like still doing it.
- No.
- Listen to this comment.
Bad music, the rap genre,
which was considered to be a genre
that would inspire us to problems,
cruelness, helping us going,
thought, pain, sadness, pain, et cetera,
and rapping about racism, terrorism,
poverty, problems, love,
and that has turned into some really bad genre
that has very similarity to pop music.
I mean like when you hear a new rap song
and then you see there is some girl curvy
and then actually dancing and twerking her ass
and then literally is mostly made like porn.
Edit, I prefer mostly the old schools era,
such as Tupac, Biggie, NWA, Ice Cube, et cetera.
- Kevin Rudolph.
I'm looking at him. - Kevin Rudolph did a new song
with Lil Wayne.
- What? - Whoa, how really?
- He looks like a shitty-- - 2019, whoa.
- He looks like a shitty Hollywood Boulevard
Andrew W.K. impersonator. - Yeah, exactly.
He looks like, actually, yeah, I guess he does,
I'm seeing him with a lot of DC hats.
I guess he does, he looks like Greg Lutska.
- Something about, yeah,
something about these kind of guys,
these like washed up rock stars,
when they turn 40, they just all become Latino.
- They get that hat and the scarves,
and then they just kinda--
- Yeah, and they love like big flannels,
and they start getting like cholo tattoos.
- Yeah. - Wait, I need to, I'm sorry.
- It's 'cause he's an LA guy, right?
- I have no idea. - What's up?
- Listen to this next roll. - What's up,
get a lock and roll.
number number six man-made disasters is a comment on here that says
chemical wars incoming get yourself a bunker garaf food stock and i think
that's what i think is a good look around for his dark so that was like a
historical figure something
is just a guy
but i don't know who is it
it is just a bunch of the indian social media profiles just come up when you
search that name
the house is still a rise it's garage warning chemical wars becoming
get yourself a booker
There's one comment here that just says "sup".
[laughter]
Man-made disaster, sup.
Sup.
What up?
What up, I'm the man-made disaster.
That's so awesome, dude.
One of the worst things that could happen is animal cruelty, which I hate.
Ah, I hate it.
I fucking hate it, dude.
Um...
Actually, we should be getting more mad at the list.
Yeah, that's true.
No, we can get really mad at number seven.
People are too politically correct.
UGHHHHHH!
GAH!
Take it back!
UGHHHHHH!
I hate when people are politically correct.
I'm like a pot of clams right now. I'm steaming.
It feels like it used to be Yosemite Sam and now it's Yosemite Samantha.
Uh-huh.
You know?
Yeah.
That's the kind of stuff I'm mad at.
Yeah, now it's Elma.
Now it's Elma Boobs.
Elma Boobs.
That's right. Now it's Bugs...
Bugs...
Bugs Bunny dressed up as a woman.
yeah yeah yeah yeah now it's now it's Donald Dina duck you should be SpongeBob
SquarePants on SpongeBob penis ass cuz he's gay now now it's squid squidward
woman squidward tentacle porn yeah and it's crusty crabs the STD yeah and this
is in mrs. puffs which is what you are man it used to be man it used to be
freaking Ren and Stimpy now it's men are wimpy in today's society yeah you know
what I'm talking about. Used to be Angry Beavers was two beavers now it's like well the feminists are a couple
angry beavers. Yeah it used to be Opie and Anthony and now it's the Anthony Cumia show. Yeah it used to be Opie and Anthony now it's Jim and Sam. What the fuck is this dude?
political correctness run amok yeah you had a family guy now it's no family
minutes now it's Peter's family yeah hey hey SJWs hey SJWs it's Jim and Pam not
Jim and man it's Christmas Eve not Christmas Steve big guy yeah that's
It's according to Jim not according to her.
Yeah.
Used to be home improvement.
Now it's Last Man Standing.
Yeah.
Man it used to be Snoop Dogg.
Nowadays it's more like Pooplog.
Now it's like Snoop Lion.
Used to be Saturday Night Live.
it's now it's hating white lives used to be mr. show now it's now it's now it's
with Bob and David mrs. with Bob and David uh-huh yeah with Bobina and David
Now it's I'm with Hervid.
[Laughter]
Oh yeah, basically it, you know.
That's how it is.
Used to be Tony Hawk.
Now it's...
Blow my cock.
[Laughter]
Just completely unrelated.
Yeah, it used to be Halo, now it's Call of Duty.
Used to be Bam Margera, now it's Pam Margerha.
(laughter)
Used to be jackass, now it's black ass.
Used to be, used to be Brandon Decomillo, now it's...
Used to be Brandon, it used to be Deco's freestyle, now it's...
Kingco's... application.
(laughter)
Kingkos application. I had to get a job.
Yeah.
Oh, fuck me, dude.
Yeah, it used to be the yin-yang twins.
Now it's still the yin-yang twins, but they're Chinese.
So sad. Yeah.
Oh my god dude.
[Laughter]
Ugh.
What did people say about this?
Nothing interesting.
Yeah, it's just basically what we're doing.
People are pussies nowadays.
Yeah. That's true.
Number eight is hate.
AGH! You know what I hate?
That it rhymes.
Hate and hate?
That's the hateful eight right here.
Yeah, we just found them.
the best answer, says somebody.
- Yeah, I mean, it covers most everything.
- Yeah, you kinda got everything
kinda wrapped up into one thing.
Hate is the root of all problems.
Wish I could delete hate from this world.
You basically can.
- One of these comments at the end of it--
- Just listen to Crooked Media.
- One of the end of these comments says, "End world suck."
- End world suck? - End world suck.
I don't know, I just wanted to say that.
It's a fun phrase.
- End world suck. - End world suck.
number nine is global warming
i'm actually number ten though is what we need to go to a number ten is no family
time
yeah
spot on the is for me i hate my family because they treat me like crap i think
life wouldn't suck if i never see my family ever again
the internet has taken away all of our family time
in the president internet like a l_s_d_
uh...
Dude, I love getting together and being on the internet with my four boys.
Really true!
We laxually many people out there are born into parents that are not hot and do not have good looking face
and then actually their kid are running away and going into people that are more cutier than his or her parents.
That is the problem, dude.
The problem is kids think their parents aren't hot and they're running away.
Porn has warped the idea of parents so much that we all think we need to have a hot fucking big titted mom and a dad with a huge cock.
Look, it used to be modern family, now it's modern taboo family.
[Laughter]
Oh, fuck.
Um...
Yeah, I...
I think this is true. No family time.
You know, back in my day, I probably watched the...
Honestly, I probably watched the Italian job with my mom
probably 60 times in my life. Yeah. Nowadays kids are going getting the Italian job from 7-11
60 times a day. The problem with society now is there's no more Will Ferrell movies to watch
with your kids. No, they just put out a new one. I mean what are you gonna do? Is it a Will Ferrell
Adam McKay movie? Doesn't matter. It doesn't well that's the problem. It used to matter.
Isn't Chance the Rapper like the biggest fan of the house?
I don't know anything about Chance the Rapper.
Patrick keeps track of what Chance the Rapper is a fan of.
Yeah, he follows him on Letterboxd.
He checks all his likes on Twitter.
Let's see what Chance thinks about this High Place Part 2.
Chance the Rapper tweeted Chance. I'm gonna call him Chance like he's my friend.
He is your friend.
What's his name?
Yeah, he's not my friend. I call him Mr. Rapper.
Yeah, Mr. the Rapper.
I have to call him Mr. The Rapper when I see him, but when I talk about him.
Mr. The Rapper, I am a huge fan.
Yeah.
I don't think he likes the house though.
He strikes me as a Step Brothers fan.
Oh, well, yeah, but...
Dude, the singing in the sequence.
But who isn't, man?
That's right, who isn't?
Who isn't, dude?
I got so much phlegm in my throat.
Sure.
I do.
Chance the Rapper, yeah.
Chance the Rapper defends the house against Terrible Rotten Tomatoes score.
He should defend his house against me because I'm gonna come for him.
Yesterday I watched a movie that I never heard of. It had a 17% on Rotten Tomatoes. It was funny as
fuck. I saw the house on on an airplane and I was like, "Oh, that's so weird. They like edited it
so bizarrely for the airplane and it must have been terrible because of that." And then I watched it,
not the airplane version, it was exactly the same. Yeah.
They just, it's just a crazy movie. I don't even know what it is.
It was probably like, it was probably a fine movie.
It's basically what my dad does for a living in a movie.
Yeah, it was pretty, it wasn't very realistic.
They made a movie about having sex with you, dude?
No!
No, they didn't.
Yeah, they did.
No.
Yeah, no.
They did.
Amateur, amateur cuckoo kangaroo XXX.
That's what it's called.
X kangaroo.
Yeah.
No.
Dude, we used to all get together.
There is no website called Xkangaroo.
Families used to get together and watch home movies.
Now they all get together and watch X videos.
[Laughter]
That's right.
I'm getting my kids, I'm getting all my kids and my wife together.
We just got this new flat screen curved LED TV
and we're gonna watch-
We're watching E-Fucked.
We're watching The Minion on E-Fucked.
We're watching E-Fucked penal compilation 13.
That's just how it used to be man. That was what Reagan's America was about.
Reagan's America was, they were gonna have another, the Minion was gonna continue,
the Reagan was gonna put a bunch of money into the Minion. You guys know the Minion,
right? I've talked about the Minion. Of course I know the Minion, yeah.
Beedle, beedle. No, it's not that Minion. Beedle, badabadabadaboo.
They should, someone should put them together. Yeah.
The minion was this video on efooked and it's a fat guy like eating sandwiches while girls
have sex with him.
Yeah man.
It's awesome.
It rocks dude.
Yeah.
Now it's all xhamster and black.com and chinesed.com and hawaiian.com and chinesed.com.
[Laughter]
Yeah, it's basically the same concept as Blacked where it's super racist and
everybody watches it but it's a Chinese guy now.
[Laughter]
They're breaking stereotypes, dude.
Yeah, that's true. Yeah.
It's a Chinese guy with a giant dick.
bask2.com and it's a Spanish guy.
(laughing)
- Oh, fuck.
- Number 11, this is kinda getting philosophical,
anthropological, this is humans.
- Damn.
- Whoa. - Wow.
- Holy. - Wow, dude.
- Holy hell. - Then there's the,
the lowest comment on this just says, "Muppets."
- Stupid humans, I'm a alien now.
- Whoa. - That's a good comment.
That's like a t-shirt that Patrick would have worn in 2009.
Yeah.
I love that, I miss those kind of t-shirts,
but like not the like explicit ones about boobs and beer,
but the ones from Walmart that just made no sense.
Like I have one, or Jana has one that just says like,
"I hear voices in my head on like a camo t-shirt."
(laughing)
Do you guys remember those shirts that would be like,
it would be like a little stick figure
and it would be like, "Homework? No thank you.
"I'd rather play video games."
it was like a diagram of a video game.
The video game, the words video games were like made out of controllers.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
It didn't even read as anything.
It was like joystick, Xbox controller, arcade cabinet.
Yeah.
There was one I had that was just like, I rock, and it was a stick figure.
It was a sleeveless shirt that said I rock, I never wore it, and it was a stick figure
playing a guitar.
I miss the Bush era dude.
What about, they should make a shirt that's like a really buff stick figure and it says
homework I'm gonna kick my teacher's ass and then kids will wear it to school and get in
trouble.
Yeah.
If I have to do homework I'll kill myself.
What about like a picture of like FPS Russia blowing up homework with a bunch of thermite.
Whoa that'd be sick.
That'd be a good shirt.
I think we're moving into the child's t-shirt market now.
Yeah.
I think we might need to make some kids t-shirts.
Yeah, I mean we already have kill your local griefer.
I have a balloon with poop in it.
[Laughs]
You know? Stuff like that. Stuff that makes kids laugh.
What do kids... Kids hate homework now.
Kids love homework.
Yeah, that's the problem with today's generation.
Got these nerd-ass kids like fucking, uh, Ilan Omar's kid.
Right? Fucking nerd.
Shut up, dude.
Doing your homework.
Yeah.
- Man, we used to have homework,
but now with the freaking pandemic,
we got to work from home.
- Right?
Wow. - Yeah.
- Wow, dude.
- It makes you fucking think about shit.
- It makes you think about life in a different sort of way.
Man, we used to be kids, now we're adults.
- Yep.
(laughing)
- Childhood. - Seems like we used to be
kids and almost we're adults now.
- Childhood ruined, I'm 23.
(laughing)
- Just turned 18.
Yeah, childhood officially ruined.
- Yeah, childhood ruined.
- Yeah.
- Childhood ruined, I didn't get carded
the liquor store because I was buying soda.
Man, we used to, you know, a few years ago we used to have have Pop Smoke and Juice
World and Lil Peep. Now we got no smoke, no juice, and no Lil Peep.
Yeah, we used to have Tupac, Rock Joe, and Mr. Music, and now all those guys are
dead - we used to have Vern Troyer Joe C and Gary Coleman and now I don't know
anything now we have no Patrick thanks a lot and now we have learned Troyer learn
Troyer Gary Oldman and Joe Joe Joe Gatto yeah yeah from practical chokers you
We used to have John Gotti, Tony Soprano, and Homer Simpson.
And now it feels like you got Barack Obama, Mr. Jenkins, and the Lonely Island.
What the fuck happened, dude?
We used to be eating Baskin Robbins ice cream and singing Christmas carols, and now we have
freaking carol baskins and robin williams is dead
yeah
we said it used to be 2019 now we got covid19
dude uh-huh it really makes you think you should have dan
soda and then Mayor Bloomberg banned soda in New York City.
I have something wrong with my brain.
Fuck me.
Number 12, feminism.
Someone went Borat on this list.
Someone went Borat.
Yeah.
Poisonous ideology made by big money eaters.
(laughter)
Big money eaters? Big money eaters? What does that mean?
I want to skip ahead real quick to number 16, which has no
comments and is just a stressful environment. Wait, sorry, the last of feminism
is, the last comment is "Gone too far and lies about its past." Like the Jews!
(laughter)
Number 16 has no comments and is just stressful environment.
That's right.
Now I'm imagining like a group of black guys on a corner saying that black guys used to be the real women of the world.
In ancient Mesopotamia.
Oh like black Israelites.
Yeah in ancient Mesopotamia the first women were actually black men.
Um, number 19 is clinical depression and the only comment is too much stress and depression.
That's true. Number 43, I skipped ahead a bunch, uh, but number 43 is rule 34. Damn. Whoa.
That's right. That's the opposite, kinda. Yeah. I don't know, I feel like that's actually chill.
I feel like that's not a reason today sucks. Damn, you guys remember how the TSA?
The TSA!
Bad sex.
You guys remember how the description of the list said "Please don't put any celebrities
on here"?
Yeah.
Number 33 is celebrities.
Somebody's sticking it to the man, dude.
Yeah.
How about rule breakers?
That should be on here.
Yeah.
Let's add that.
Cancer.
Mumble rap.
Too many murders.
People not understanding the importance of wearing clothing.
The last one is parents pushing kids around too much.
Facts, dude.
That's seriously true.
That's facts as fuck.
Facts, no printer.
That is so fucking true.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
They basically nailed us.
Too many murders is right above that one.
It's not murder in general, it's that there's just too many.
Yeah, if we had a few, that'd be okay.
Yeah, if there's like 50, 60 murders, you know, that's kind of fine.
As long as it's state-sanctioned.
Yeah, as long as, yeah, exactly.
As long as it's mostly swatting, then it's fine.
As long as it's mostly Twitch streamers that's dying.
Mm-hmm.
We need to stop streaming on Twitch or someone's gonna SWAT us.
Oh my god.
Somebody will SWAT Patrick.
I, yeah, I don't...
Somebody, Patrick is gonna die.
Yeah, I mean he's done for.
He's getting SWATed, no problem.
I forgot, I forgot.
He's also, he's the biggest...
Now I don't wanna do the Twitch stream anymore.
He's such a big target.
He's dead.
Right.
He's done for.
You just...
Patrick's not gonna stream anymore, Caleb.
You idiot.
I know.
That was not worth it.
I got him scared of swatting.
Look at his face.
I don't want to do it now.
Someone's going to swat me as a joke.
Where do you think, do you think people know where you live?
I don't, can't they trace the IP or whatever?
Isn't that how they do it?
Can't they trace the IP or whatever?
I don't know.
You just ruined Patrick's day, Caleb.
I hope you're happy.
I am happy.
He looks like he's going to cry.
I don't want to get swatted.
You're going to get swatted.
- I don't want to get swatted.
- Here's what you do, here's what you have to do.
- First, you have to join the SWAT team.
So that you, while you're streaming,
you get a call and they're like, we have to go--
- I think my cousin's on it.
- We have to go kill a guy.
- I think my cousin is on it.
So I think I'm safe.
- On the SWAT team?
- Uh-huh, but he's in a different city.
- Then you're fine.
- You should move to that city, man.
- There's only one.
There's only one, they're like the Avengers.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, they move around.
Do the Avengers only protect New York City?
They only protect whites.
That's true, man.
Yeah.
That's fucked up.
I know.
Much like the SWAT team.
The Avengers is racist.
Wow.
The Avengers, if the Avengers were real, they would be extremely racist.
Yeah.
Um...
Explain.
And that's facts.
Yeah, you...
Dr. Strange.
For example, Black Panther, extremely racist against whites.
The Hulk, extremely racist against whites.
Um...
The Guardians of the Galaxy,
extremely racist against whites.
Doctor Strange, who thinks that all Chinese people are Tilda Swinton.
It's pretty fucked up, right?
Yeah.
Yeah. I'm gonna join the Avengers and I'm gonna change it from the inside.
Yeah, I'm gonna make the- we're gonna defund the Avengers.
I'm gonna be the Chris Dorner of the Avengers.
Yeah, that's Hawkeye.
That's not a bad idea.
No, Hawkeye was bad and then he joined the Avengers and became good and he didn't kill the Avengers.
I'd be hot guy. Yeah? Yeah, pretty much I'd be the hot one.
Yeah, you would. I'd be pretty sick. Yeah, we would do like a... we'd make most of our
money off of calendars. You would be Captain America-ka-ka-ka. Yeah. Yeah, you would.
Yeah, because I'd be taking it down America-ka-ka-ka, Ice Cube style.
No, you'd be the captain of it. You'd be the captain of the America-ka-ka. No, I would change it from the
inside I'm I joined the I joined the Ku Klux Klan so I could make big structural
changes from the inside of the organization you know it's that the
Avengers still exist in the universe where you join them yeah or did you just
admit yeah you just said you're joining the
you just admit in yeah Caleb's joy headed to destroy them I'm basically doing the
I'm like the black Klansman but I'm the white Klansman.
Is that what they- the white Klansman?
I haven't seen that yet, but isn't that- don't they use Adam Driver for that?
So you're saying you're just gonna be Adam Driver?
I'm basically gonna be Adam Driver.
Alright, then we're- I'm Sexton Gray from Star Wars 100 times.
Then this is great because we have signed you up for the US Marines.
I'm really excited to start my career as a United States Marine.
gonna they're gonna everyone got angry at him because he said he signed up for
the Marines after 9/11 because he wanted to get revenge on the Middle East and
everybody got really mad for like a day and said forgot about it yeah that's so
fucking funny so awesome dude the thing is like everybody's kind of caught up in
the moment you know I like I probably would have done some dumb shit yeah
right like you're probably would have liked I probably would have subscribed to
Air America or something that would have been my version I would have I would
I would have joined the Young Turks.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
I would have fought the Young Turks in Afghanistan.
I would have joined.
All right.
All right, baby.
I love you.
That's the episode.
Bye.
See you later.
Bye, everybody.