You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
Crap monster.
(laughing)
(thunder)
Let's go.
Let's do it.
Yes, we have Ryan with us.
Yeah, woo!
We have Ryan back, I think Ryan's in the building.
Ryan's our, I think he's our most popular.
Yeah.
He's our most popular guest with us.
Most popular, most times appeared means most popular.
What about--
I mean you're the most popular with the hosts. Yeah. We think of you as the number one.
What about Pierce? You're probably tied. I guess you're tied. Yeah, you and Pierce are tied.
Yeah. It used to be our friend Neil. Yeah. I think Neil had more guests than Pierce and
Ryan combined. But also most of Neil's guests were that he just walked into the room while
we were recording and we were like, I guess you can talk on this one.
It's because I lived with him.
Yeah, it's like, like Patrick's like cats are the number one guest.
Like it was that kind of thing.
You would just like, he would wander into my lap.
He's the same as a cat.
Same level of being.
Yeah, he would fall into my lap from the ceiling and I would, I would be like, oh fuck, I gotta deal with Neil again.
Neil's playing in the trash again.
Neil's getting another guest spot on the podcast.
Fuck.
There was one time that he walked in while you guys were at work.
Yeah. Yeah.
Back when we recorded the podcast at work, he would just he would kind of walk in a lot.
I mean, he would just come.
He would just come to work just when he didn't have anything to do.
He would just come to my work
and never ask me to do my job like he didn't need any equipment or anything.
He would just just say, what's up?
You just sit there with his hands in his pockets.
Be weird to my boss and leave.
(laughing)
Love those friends.
Oh, he's the best.
Important friend to have.
Yeah. Of course.
So what's up, Ryan?
How's West Coast living, baby?
Oh, it's good.
It's real hot out here.
It's just as bad as everywhere else, I think.
Really? Yeah, what about the sun?
The sun, yeah.
What about hell?
It's not as bad as those places.
That's a really good point.
Oh, the cold weather, that's a good point.
Ryan, you've been on for two minutes
and you're already getting fucked.
Didn't hear you.
you are you're getting fucked so hard to me so
the alert yet
the
uh... however
as uh... how's everything on the east coast is a really hard over there to
fall
it sucks at night and i think uh...
probably two hundred thousand degrees here
and in the day one degree
in the in the dates actually freezing cold yeah
they've been a little bit over here
you guys like it
uh... messages you know
hanging out, recording the podcast in person,
kissing each other.
- Yeah.
- I don't miss kissing them.
- I miss it.
- That's my least favorite part of the show.
- We have to in order to start and end the episode.
- Yeah, it sucks that now we have to drive halfway
from Boston and New York and meet up and just kiss once
and not even record, just 'cause we can't record
every week unless we kiss.
- Yeah.
- So it's getting annoying.
It's a lot of gas money too.
- And it's expensive.
- Yeah, it really is.
- That does suck.
- Not the most I've paid for a kiss,
but it is close.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Dammit, it's been chill.
I'm glad it's been chill for you.
You moved, you're away from the Clown Stripper Club.
- I'm away from there, yeah.
I'm just like a few blocks away.
Now I'm closer to the Cheetah Strip Club.
- Nice, dude.
That's the best part about LA, is the themed strip clubs.
- Yeah.
- You can't just have like a woman themed strip club.
- Yeah, we'll never have that.
- It's gotta be something with polka dots on it.
Well, none of them are beautiful women themed strip clubs.
Absolutely not.
Not a single one of them.
It's all cheetah or Mario Party or rock and roll.
Mario Party, Strip Club,
a Waluigi with like there's no shirt underneath the overalls
and the overalls just barely cover the nipples.
You're just you're just fucking braining people with golden metal coins,
giant coins the size of your head.
It's all like it's all like like really hot women dressed up
in like slutty cosplay versions of Mario characters,
except there's one guy who's just Wario.
(all laughing)
- That's the Bowser. - He is Wario.
He's not dressed as Wario.
- Yeah, it's a real Wario.
- Wario comes out and tries to steal all the coins
off the stage and the woman has to stop them.
- Yeah, it's a game, that's one of the mini games.
- They should put mini games in strip clubs.
- Okay, all right, let's admit it.
It's basically a carnival.
There's all these different sort of mini games
that you play around the strip club
where you have to defeat Bowser and Bowser Jr.
Oh yeah, and one, there's one tile on the floor of the strip club that if you click it, if
you click it, if you accidentally jump on it, then Bowser comes and he takes your money.
He robs you.
And you have to leave.
And you have to leave, yeah.
And then, and then, uh...
There is an item shop.
You can't forget the item shop.
You can't forget to play basketball.
And you can become invincible.
invincible. Yeah, if you get a one-up it works. You can get killed and come back to life.
You can die once. For the rest of your life. And it's not just in the strip club.
That's a permanent one-up. It lasts forever. That's one thing about Mario Party.
It's like, where do they go after the game's over?
Into the console. They go to another party.
Hey, let me tell you what. Not my freaking idea of a party. Have you ever turned on
tried to play Mario Party and just none of the characters are in there because
they're all in someone else's party. True. Someone else on the other side of the
world is playing Mario Party and they're all there instead. You're like, you're midway through. What are you saying?
I don't understand any of these jokes because like I played, we didn't have a Nintendo, I just had a
PlayStation so we had like the Shrek version. So like, I kind of get it but there was-
Was Shrek like the bad guy?
No, they were just all guys.
No, Farquaad's the bad guy.
Farquaad was the Bowser?
I guess so, probably. I guess Farquaad was the Bowser. I don't know.
I think everybody was just a different character.
Nobody really knew what was going on. It was crazy back then.
Ryan, to understand the Mario Party jokes, just switch the word Mario with Shrek.
Okay, got it.
You'll probably understand it.
okay yeah walla we see that's all the way to your stage think person will be
skinny Shrek yeah think about Shrek dressed up as the Mario characters and
you'll understand that yeah yeah sorry we're kind of a weird we're weird
weird yeah yeah it's like freak oh freak oh stern basically yeah yeah like if
Stern was all the whack-pack. Yeah. Do you have a podcast? How do you explain it to people?
I don't. It's just kind of like if Conor O'Malley was my brother, my brother, and me.
That's how I like to tell people about it. Yeah, it's basically like if Einstein had a microphone.
So you guys figure it out. If Einstein invented the microphone.
with two retarded brothers.
(laughing)
- Which one's Einstein?
Come on, come on, you got it.
Yes, come on, that's so not nice.
- That's true.
- That's extremely fucked up.
- That's nice and it's normal.
- And it's true.
Yeah, it pretty much is, basically.
I'm number one.
This podcast is kind of like if Samuel Beckett
had used Vine.
(laughing)
That's what I like to tell people.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's kind of like if HP Lovecraft was on Reddit.
Have you ever seen that picture of Obama drinking the beer and saying "not bad" and thumbs up
and frowning?
It's kind of like that.
Yeah, it's kind of like one of those real life Simpsons photos.
Basically, an audio version.
That's what the waveform looks like.
The waveform's a couch gag.
Yeah, yeah.
We've just been putting...
We aren't real people.
just putting, we're programmers who have been converting the couch gags into
waveforms and these episodes just come out every time with every different couch gag.
Yeah it's truly amazing technology that we will not be sharing with the medical
community. Yeah only the military. Yeah that's right. They're gonna use the couch
gags to develop new more dangerous drones. Wouldn't that be funny? I always
think about it you know how like every like sketch group or like sketch show on
TV, like if it's 10 people, like three of them become like famous comedians
afterwards and then seven of them just get like crazy jobs like working as
military contractors or like 7-Eleven managers. I wonder what, because
none of us will be successful in five years, I wonder what our real-life jobs
are gonna be. Probably the military for me. You would be the greatest
military mind of all time. Patrick is just listening to Dan Carlin's hardcore
history and saying everything as it comes through his earbuds.
There's like people trying to like interrupt him and he's just talking loudly over them as he says more Dan Carlin.
Sir, what should we do? We have to hit the shoguns where it hurts.
I'm probably gonna be a warlock in five years I'm thinking. I've been working on
curses. You hear about Cameron? He just ended up with a stupid warlock job. Yeah, he's a
fucking dude. Dude, I'm on that nine to five witchcraft grind. It sucks. I'm shooting for,
I'm trying to be a comedian, but my fallback is basically alchemist.
Basically, I want to turn, I want to turn gold into, I want to turn gold into wood.
the
that
- Yeah, you normally make stuff worse.
That's like the law of thermodynamics.
So gold can be turned into like poop
or like a mushy, like hummus.
That's true.
That's a really good point.
Yeah, that's a true-
- I'm an alchemist 'cause I ate a quarter
and I turned it into poop.
- I ate a quarter and it's never come out.
- Yeah. - It's been stuck in me
for a decade.
- I told you guys my eating quarter story, I think.
- Yeah, oh yeah.
you went to the movies with a bucket full of quarters like popcorn and you ate the whole thing?
Yeah I do remember that. No I swallowed a quarter in the pool. Swallowed a quarter in the pool?
Are you swallowing anything in the pool? What the fuck are you swallowing dude?
Sam I meant to swallow all the water in the pool. I accidentally swallowed this quarter.
I meant to swallow all the water and then get big and inflated like Petey Piranha and Mario Sunshine
and
- Yeah. - Like Tak in "Daxter"?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Like Tak in "The Power of Juju."
Does that ring a bell?
- Absolutely.
- There we go.
- Spyro.
- Yeah, Spyro.
No, Spyro was--
- Spyro's cool. - He was the best one.
- He was a dragon.
- Yeah, I don't think he sucked up anything, though.
- He was a dragon who smoked weed.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. - And he was a Skylander.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Dude, Skylanders, awesome.
Me and Pat are gonna play Skylanders.
- Yeah, we're trying to get--
i don't know i think it's someone's i i i skylanders on the ad was listening to
the podcast right now please bias skylanders on p_c_ and cameron both
both yet if you don't have any dialogue i was a recount if you only by one were
returning the and we need all the tourists to
you know all of them all the figures need any because i'm playing with
normal stuff like you had shows so
yeah but these are toys that come to light out this reminds me i i i think
it's going to life
i posted that video of like limp is get covers uh... and i was someone who
who like replied and was talking with their friend
in my replies and was like,
man, I can't believe we used to listen to this stuff.
This is so cringe nowadays to look at this.
And they both had Transformers display names.
(all laughing)
- That fucking rocks.
- So funny.
- What were the display names?
- Let me look it up real quick.
- Hammer and the Decepticon.
(laughing)
- Let's see.
- Yeah, Mr. Bumblebee.
I think one of them was something bumblebee.
That could just be an animal thing.
Josh bumblebee.
No, because their profile picture was a transformer and their bio said like transformer's fan.
Maybe he's horribly disabled and that's his mech suit.
You never think dude.
This is what, yeah.
That's one of my problems.
That's the thing, if you're disabled enough you just get like a, you get an upgrade.
I think that's called uh... horseshoe theory
because all the way back around and you get a super cool legs
exactly yeah ronald mcdonald house pays for you to have like the coolest legs on
earth
uh... okay way it turns out one of them i just thought was uh...
was a transformers name because their name is just phoenix and i just assumed
phoenix was a transformer i think only one of them is a transformer name
this one is scout bumblebee that was saying i can't believe we used to listen
of this. There's no real pattern to the Transformers names. They're all just cool things. It's
all just two cool words. Yeah, they're not like the Ninja Turtles. There's no reason
why they're named what they are. Yeah, they're all just called like "Power Wheel." It's
just like they take two cool words and put them together. Yeah. It's like the same principle
they use to name military vehicles. I've tried to come up with a joke military vehicle
name before and just like search them and every time it's a real vehicle.
[LAUGHTER]
Cobra.
The garter snake.
The Raytheon garter snake.
The evil dog.
Yeah.
That's like what all of them are.
Northrop Grumman evil dog.
The annoying orange.
[LAUGHTER]
Yeah.
Annoying Orange.
They're like four billion dollars over budget and they keep crashing.
Yeah, six military casualties today at Cape Lejeune as they test out the Annoying Orange for the fifth time.
Another manned trip on the Annoying Orange.
Yeah.
That's, they're just gonna start naming them.
Do you have a favorite Limp Bizkit album?
Hmm?
Do you have a favorite Limp Bizkit album? I noticed that you put that on your like,
uh, you had recently like a big playlist and you had Significant Other on that.
Oh yeah, Significant Other rocks. I think that's the best Limp Bizkit album.
I don't know any of them. You guys could make them up.
I've been listening to so much Limp Bizkit lately.
There's a song on-
Chocolate starfish in the hot dog flavored water.
Yeah, that one's good too.
Mr. Nasty's Pissy Puddles.
That's what all of them are named like.
Um, the Fuck Freak.
The fuck freak.
Um, turd hood.
I remember like the first album.
Turd hood?
[Laughter]
Um, the first, the first Limp Bizkit album I got was like the album full of remixes.
And that's actually how I heard for like every actually good rapper I learned about from that album.
Cause they had like Pharrell and Method Man.
They have like Method Man and fucking they have so many features from the actual rappers.
It's so funny.
That's like my dad got into hip-hop because of Girl Talk.
The like mashup artist.
He was like, "Well Biggie Smalls is actually fucking sick when he's rapping over Twisted
Sister."
That's what it is.
It's a project to get dads into hip-hop.
It's absolutely what it is.
it's a it's a ploy by the rap industry to get like, like dudes
who love like Leonard Skinner to listen to Tupac. Yeah. And it
worked. My dad is my dad loves a con. My dad's ears. My dad's
like favorite guy in the world is a con. It's because Yeah,
because I like when I was a kid, I accidentally, like plugged
his iPod into my like, computer at some point and it put a con
I'm so paid on his iPod.
And at first he would listen to it because he thought it was like funny
that he had a rap song on his iPod.
And then he every day I would like walk into his room and he'd be listening
to it alone and just like rapping to himself.
It's pretty he knows every single word of the edited version.
He knows the edited version for the record.
Getting edited version for my dad.
So he doesn't say the n-word.
(laughter)
- I mean, that is what it took, absolutely.
- Yeah.
- What's going on?
What happened with Aecon City?
- Oh, you guys remember that?
- It's driving.
- They hit it like Wakanda.
(laughter)
- They put a shield around it.
- It's invisible.
- If they got too advanced too fast.
They had already come out with I'm so paid too.
- Yeah.
- They were like, we have--
- They had an Aecon City?
- We have to hide.
Yeah, he like bought.
That was gonna run on his own cryptocurrency or something?
He brought electricity to it.
Instead of, you know, the special mineral
that Wakandans have, he just brought them electricity.
Yeah.
(laughing)
Just more electricity.
They just trade electricity.
Electricity is the cryptocurrency he came up with.
They just trade a bottle of lightning back and forth.
Shoot lightning at each other in order to pay each other.
Yeah, yeah.
They go palpitating on each other.
If there's one power I wish was real,
I wish it was electricity powers were real.
Yeah.
I looked up.
Oh my God, you got insanely loud Patrick.
Sorry, I'll move it back.
I looked up Acon City and it says,
"Acon finalizes deal to build
"a cryptocurrency city in Senegal."
And then the photo that they use
is like one of those like future,
like this is what society would look like.
(laughing)
That fucking rocks, dude.
I mean, they're right.
Yeah. Yeah.
That is the kind of-- We had A-Coin.
A-Coin, yeah, that's what it was.
Is that what it was called?
Yeah. That's what it was called.
You know that he just, he was like,
"What can I play off my name now?
I guess I'll do a Cryptocurrency."
I feel like he came up with the name first.
Yeah, 100%.
Yeah, he thought, "Oh shit, look what happens
if you put an I in the middle of my name.
Dude, I gotta start a city."
(laughing)
The only way this is gonna work is if I buy an entire city with it.
Yeah.
That's definitely what African countries need is just some completely new currency
that can be inflated to the point of being meaningless.
Exactly.
Yeah.
I've been saying this for years actually and I'm just glad Akon took some action.
Alright, the list today, we got a monkey list.
We got a chimp list.
We're monkeying it.
We're monkeying around.
the
It's world chimpanzee day today.
I just, I looked it up.
Alright.
This banana's for you chimps.
Yeah.
[Laughter]
Thank you.
Let's all toast a banana.
Yeah.
Those motherfuckers love bananas, man.
Monkeys and bananas is kinda like...
Monkeys go monkeys, bananas for bananas.
Monkeys go bananas for bananas.
That's right.
Yeah, monkeys go monkey on a banana.
They will.
Oh yeah.
Alright, so this is from Ranker.
This is people who own chimps as pets and paid the price.
With 1.6 million views.
That's gotta be pretty good, right?
They probably made a couple thousand dollars off of this list.
Yeah, that's right.
This is written by Lee MJ.
This list.
Lee Michael Jackson. Can we see his photo? I like that uh it says so the the
beginning of this of this article says on the surface owning a pet chimpanzee
seems remarkably appealing movies tell us they're cute fun entertaining and
just like us yes we share around 99% of our DNA with them but there's one key
difference between our two species grown chimpanzees have the strength of several
adult humans. That's the key difference between us and chimpanzees.
Wait, I found, I clicked on this guy Lee MJ's profile and this is his bio.
If you wander into a seedy bar past midnight looking for someone to
discuss Jeffrey Dahmer's victim count, government conspiracies, or
contemporary horror with, I'll most certainly be there. I've got a master's degree in
poetry and can often be found listening to true crime podcasts or long songs
with a lot of lyrics.
Calling my sense of humor, quote,
dark would be like calling the
Mariana Trench kind of deep.
I love music, books, film and
anything else I can lose myself in.
Pull up a chair and let's talk
anything weird, creepy or scary.
Damn, yeah, I'm a bit of a freaky
little creep and I like to make
lists and just
while we're on his.
Very boring.
While we're on his um his page I just want to look at some of the other lists
he wrote like this one that's called animals who just love getting down and
dirty and that is like the caption of it says everyone knows at least one person
who is completely obsessed with doing it then there's another list he has called
nine uncomfortable facts about how dolphins are sexual assault monsters and
then he also has 20 unforgettable behind-the-scenes images from the
Harry Potter movies there's a there's a there's a theme here they're all
connected somehow yeah that fucking rocks dude goddamn all right um number one
this is I mean this is as classic as it gets as far as I mean what chimp do you
guys think of when oh when we think of somebody owning a chimp and then paying
the price yeah I think of my I think of my pet chimp yeah I think yeah no Travis
the chimp tore off the face and hands of his owner's family friend.
Did that lady did she did Charlotte Nash ever like sue that lady?
Because she probably had grounds to write. Yeah.
I don't know.
So I would. Yeah, I would have become the richest woman in the world.
That would have been the funniest signature on those legal documents of all time.
She just she just signs it with lipstick and a kiss.
Oh, man.
Travis the Chimpanzee, we all know this one.
I feel like we don't even need to waste our time here.
Yeah.
Travis the Chimpanzee, I mean, he went crazy.
He's the reason.
We don't even need to talk about it because he's the greatest of all time.
It's that simple.
You don't need to talk about Michael Jordan.
You don't need to talk about Rinaldo.
You don't need to talk about Tiger Woods.
It's everybody knows it.
He's number one.
He's the best to ever do it.
He's the number one monkey.
He's the, I would say, he probably is like,
no, monkeys have killed people before, right?
- What?
- Uh, sure.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, people, yeah, monkey, how often,
I wonder how often that happens.
- Do you think Travis was the first monkey to kill someone?
- No, no, no. - In 2009,
is that what you're suggesting?
- I don't know, no, I'm not suggesting that, no.
I wasn't thinking, that was not a thought
in my head at any point.
I'm just saying, he's gotta be up there.
- Yeah, he kinda created the, he kinda pioneered
the idea of monkeys going on.
Like the monkey in the new Planet of the Apes movies,
where he has the idea of hurting humans.
And then he convinces all the other monkeys.
He runs for monkey president.
He wins.
It's kind of an allegory for Donald Trump, those movies,
when you think about it.
Because here's a monkey who's very smart,
just like Donald Trump.
And he wins over all the monkeys to fight all the humans.
And it's pretty much a one-to-one comparison.
and
one of his top advisors. I'm the orangutan and I'm basically his number one guy. He looks
to me for stuff like bananas and to get a new gun. Yeah, man I'll never forget the day I
woke up and saw the headline "Donald Trump has a gun." Yeah, that was a dark day. That's
kind of, that's when it all started going downhill for him. This is not normal. Yeah.
This is seriously not normal. The president just got a gun.
The president is constitutionally not allowed to have a gun.
Yeah.
Because I mean that's, that's yeah, that pretty much ruins checks and balances right there.
That's true. Yeah.
Yeah, balance this, bitch. That's what he could, he could do a cool line like that.
Or he could even do this.
Check this, bitch. You know, he could do both, both checks and balances.
It's kind of a, it's kind of a sticky situation to get in.
I don't want to be a drama queen right now, but my finger just exploded.
Oh Jesus!
What the fuck?
What the fuck happened here?
I don't know what the fuck happened.
You are a drama queen.
What did you- what happened?
It just started bleeding?
My finger, I guess I used the keyboard too hard on it and it started to bleed.
Ugh.
Stop typing so hard.
What are you typing right now?
I typed in the thing about Akoin.
(laughing)
- Dude, you got cursed.
- Akon strikes again, dude.
- I gotta get some paper towels or something, I'm sorry.
- It's okay, can I take this break to take a shit?
It's killing me.
- All right, I don't remember what we were talking about
before Patrick had an accident
and we had to stop recording 'cause he lived right there.
- Don't explain it, here's what we're gonna say.
We're just gonna say Patrick had an accident.
We're gonna save you some embarrassment.
That's all we'll say.
Patrick's...
My finger started bleeding.
We don't even want to know about
what you did.
Your finger started bleeding.
Everywhere over the white chair.
Body fluid is everywhere.
Patrick's downstairs finger exploded all over his chair.
That's right.
That's not what happened.
Oh, so your finger didn't explode?
My finger exploded on my downstairs finger?
Your downstairs underwear finger?
No, my regular finger.
The finger that comes off of between your legs?
No.
Your naughty little finger had an accident.
It is my naughty finger. It's my middle finger.
So he admits it.
No!
It's the one in the middle of his legs.
It's not in the middle of my body.
It is.
Oh, wait, where is it then if it's not in the middle of your body?
It's in the middle of my hand.
You have, you're, okay, so.
You have a hand where your dick should be?
(laughing)
- Fucking weird, dude.
Yeah, we had to take a shit break also.
Yeah, and while I was shitting,
I found out that Barry Weiss resigned.
- Yeah.
- Wow.
I mean, this is huge for us.
- Oh my God!
- This is fucking huge, dude.
- Yeah.
- We're gonna hire her now.
- I don't know anything about her, I don't want to.
- She's just basically awesome.
- I just said I didn't want to, all right?
- I'll leave it at this, dream girl.
I said I don't want to know anything.
You know what I'm saying?
Dreamgirls?
Yeah, Dreamgirls. She's a serious Beyonce.
I don't know.
I actually thought I had an opinion and then someone asked me
why she's so bad and I was like, I don't really remember.
Me too.
I don't fucking care.
She quit the New York Times and moved to LA
and strip at the
the Wailing Wall themed strip joint
in LA.
It's gonna be really hot, dude.
We won't want to miss this, dude.
Oh, I can't wait, yeah.
Fully clothed.
Um...
Rock.
The next one is, "The owners of Moe the Chimpanzee suffered a horrible animal attack."
I don't like that they...
They... It seems... This title makes it seem like a different animal hurt.
Yeah.
Yeah, a different chimpanzee came in and attacked.
Or just a... Not even a chim... Like a...
Some... Like a...
A mosquito.
A hippopotamus.
(laughter)
- This is just, this is, the author of this list
owns Moe the chimpanzee and he got bit by a mosquito
and he's just trying to sneak this in there
'cause he's really upset.
- Okay, so St. James and, St. James?
That's the guy's name?
(laughter)
What the fuck?
- St. James Davis.
- St. James Davis?
That's sick.
- That's a really good name.
That is like a name that you would give your chimpanzee, St. James.
St. James and LaDonna Davis were high school sweethearts.
They planned to get married until St. James left LaDonna at the altar.
What the fuck?
And then skipped town shortly after on a boat headed for Africa.
Eventually he came home and he brought Moe, a newborn chimpanzee.
Not long afterward, he and LaDonna finally married.
What the fuck?
He left this bitch at the altar and then went to Africa and came back with a monkey.
And they still got married.
Now we can get married.
Sorry, I had to get my mind right. I have a monkey with me now.
You can see I'm a different man.
And there's a monkey here.
I needed a best man.
I needed a funny best man.
Before I realized.
I realized I didn't have any sort of.
There was no comic relief at this wedding.
Oh my god. They fucking.
They had the chimp at their wedding. There's a photo. There's some pictures of him without a nose and then there's a picture
Okay, that's a spoiler
Well spoiler alert we can edit that out. There is
There's a photo of the monkey in a little hat and he's got like
I'll post this picture with the episode. Yeah, this is a really good picture
The monkey is sitting on the lap of both of them and they're in their wedding outfits. He's got a little hat.
Man, that is a great monkey photo. Over the years a human couple and their chimpanzee lived in California.
They ate, slept, and watched TV together and Moe even made some TV appearances.
But when Moe was in his 30s, he began to display aggressive behaviors. After a raid by the police and animal control,
Moe was eventually taken away by the state
But then Moe was eventually granted the right to stay at a sanctuary for apes where the Davises could visit him one fateful day
Never a good way to start
There's never something awesome after that one fateful day
Caleb's mom came home with a GameCube
One fateful day the Davises were visiting Moe at the sanctuary for his 39th birthday birthday. That's an old monkey birthday
Tragically, two chimpanzees escape from their cages.
Oh my god.
Oh, wait, they were right.
It was foreshadowing.
Jealous of the Davises' attention to Moe, one went directly after LaDonna, biting her
thumb off after an attempted tackle.
St. James jumped in to save his wife and became the main victim of the attacking primates.
After five minutes, LaDonna screams, caught the attention of the sanctuary owner's son.
If I owned a chimp sanctuary, I would watch fucking everybody.
Yeah, I would not be sitting in the office like watching Breaking Bad and be like, well if I hear screams for more than five minutes
Then I'll walk out
Yeah, he just looks he's like
Five minutes. All right. Yes. I have to go check this
It's like that those kids in high school would say like hey, you know 15 minutes. The teacher doesn't show up
Hey five minutes at the screaming still going I have to leave
Basically the guy shot both chimpanzees and St. James was left massively disfigured.
Despite everything.
What does he look like?
He looks, he has no nose now.
Oh yeah, he's got no nose and then he's got like maggots.
Look at Google Moe the chimpanzee and it comes up.
He has a fucked up mouth too.
And it looks like an eye.
He kinda looks cool.
He kinda looks evil.
You know?
Well, I mean, you can't, that's the problem.
His name is Saint James.
He can't be an evil saint.
That's why it's so impactful.
True.
Because it made him look evil and now people don't believe he's a saint anymore.
I would love to get attacked like this and look like this.
I would absolutely kill for that, dude.
You know how much money you would save on Halloween costumes?
(laughter)
The last line of this one is, "Despite everything, the couple continued to visit Moe, until he mysteriously disappeared from the sanctuary."
Whoa.
That's the real mystery.
Can you imagine getting- can you imagine you and your wife both get attacked and disfigured by chimpanzees and you keep going back to the place where the chimpanzees attack you?
That's insane.
insane. Oh wait, this is new.
Sharla Nash got a full facial transplant.
Whoa.
She looks hot, dude.
Sharla Nash.
I take it all back, baby.
Wow.
Hubba hubba.
She looks good, dude.
She used to look.
Good for her.
Yeah.
Good for you, Sharla.
We've always supported Sharla.
We've always backed you, Charla.
Absolutely.
She can come on anytime.
We've already, we've extended the olive branch once.
Yeah, we've extended, we've extended a vine for her to swing on over.
You know?
Yeah.
Maybe that was in poor taste.
Now that I think about it, we extended her a banana, a banana on a, on a
mannequin's hand and she didn't take it.
I just I was googling was Moe the chimp ever found and I found I've
forum thread on
24/7 sports.com called whatever happened to Moe the chimp and they're just like talking about this attack and a guy named
War Eagle Pete said posted in this thread and said let that chimp attack me. I would choke the life out of that monkey
That's so awesome
Just Mark Wahlberg like yeah
there Charlotte still have a face you know could be a lot different if I've
been in that ape sanctuary my kids let me tell you what st. James is still
having those hey James still don't fucking knows and and mo the chimp would
still be there but the chip would still be there he would never be missing he
would be he would be here would have a cameo and fucking Patriots day kid I'm
telling I would have had a new chimp son yeah that's true I would have
adopted one of the chimps. I would have taught Moe about Christ.
Alright next horrible accident. Chimps CJ and Buddy. I love all the titles. Chimps CJ and Buddy wreaked havoc on an entire Las Vegas
neighborhood. Buddy and CJ were two chimps who lived in Las Vegas. Okay that's
like the best I think that may be the best existence that it and that any
being can have yeah it's like a chimp in Las Vegas that's like that I mean you
just are like you're like probably fucking human women that you know what
I mean yeah probably getting like you're probably you're like a rich monkey that
are in Las Vegas that first sentence buddy and CJ were two chimps who lived
in Las Vegas that's like the cheat code for a movie pitch like yeah you just say
that you get the movie no matter what,
as long as that's at the beginning of your pitch.
- We're in.
- You're in studio meeting.
- Yeah.
- That was the original pitch for the Hangover.
And then they had to like,
they just kept doing sneaky edits until it was.
It's like, instead of it, okay.
How about Buddy the Chimp and Zach Galifianakis?
And they're like, all right.
As long as there's still one chimp.
And they're like, okay, but what about?
- What if the chimp is a tiger?
- What if the chimp is a baby?
- But he's owned by Mike Tyson.
Okay, alright.
So there were two chimps who lived in Las Vegas under the care of Timmy DeRosa and Lee Watkinson,
professional poker players. Both chimps were born in captivity, then bought with Watkinson's
poker winnings and raised in a state where there were no state laws.
Determining whether or not people could keep exotic animals.
State law.
I just, yeah, I just like ending in it. No state laws.
In 2012, CJ and Buddy escaped from their cage.
Buddy ripped his cage from the attached concrete
and broke through a padlock on a nearby fence.
Both champs then proceeded to a neighbor's house
where they pounded on a window.
- Oh my God.
- Can you fucking imagine, dude?
You live in Las Vegas and you're watching TV,
you're watching football,
and you hear what you think is someone knocking at the door
and you see two champs trying to break
into your fucking house.
One resident fearing for his family's life grabbed his gun.
Huh?
What'd you say?
Oh, nothing. I just figured, uh, yeah, it's a pretty scary...
Like, you probably figure something's up as soon as you hear somebody pounding really loud at the window.
True. Even if it was a human at the window, I would be scared.
Yeah. I would already be, like, so high alert.
And seeing two chimps, I would freak.
Two humans are, like, screaming and pounding really hard at the window.
Yeah, honey, honey, don't worry. Just two humans are outside making chip noises pounding on the windows. I'm sure it's two humans. I'll be right back
I'm gonna go
Oh
Wait, it appears I was horribly mistaken
To humans, I think they might be humans are covered in hair hide hide the bananas and peanuts
Eventually the chimps left the house and continued through the streets, Buddy was fatally shot by a police officer
CJ was tranquilized and recaptured the pair of escaped chimps struck fear into the hearts of the entire neighborhood
That
Those chimps didn't even kill anyone I would have gone into the street and and fought them
With a sword no I would have choked to life out of that monkey, baby
The thing okay, so with so man versus chimp there's zero way that I'm like
Zero out of a hundred times does a does a man win that fight hand to hand right correct?
But what if it's like Andre the giant I saw a video of a guy talking about how he defeated a chimp
Oh, I saw that too
My god, I did see that you're he like choked it out. Yeah, he like body slammed it a couple times
See like you're right like you do a thing where it would run up to him and then he like picked it up and used
It's momentum against him by I saw that exact same video that show
scenario
He was like, you know, his cousin was an ape master and he brought a bunch of
Chip was his cousin
My cousin's a chimp
That's what I meant by ape master. It's just like a and then another ape
Yeah, I'm bigger a bigger one that has like better use of his thumbs as like a crown made of leaves on yeah
Really mastered being an ape. I think I think Pierce sent me that video. I'm thinking about it
Yeah, I think it was an ape chat that I saw it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I think
Like with like him with the with the chimp like giving up going inside to watch cartoons and
and like the chimp master cousin was like he respects you now he respects what you did
you're the alpha male.
That's what you have to kill the chimp to earn its respect?
You just have to flip it over a bunch of times.
Chimps love backflips but they don't have the coordination to do them themselves so they
will often run at humans in the hopes that they will flip them over their back.
It makes sense.
It does.
I'm sure you could train.
It's what training men who's beat a chimp in hand-to-hand combat is basically what I'm
saying.
The thing is, the problem with chimps is that they're willing to play dirty.
I would never bite a man.
A chimp will bite somebody no problem.
And I would never go after somebody's nose.
Yeah, that's fucked up to do.
Yeah, that is.
And chimps, the thing is, they want to make you look like a chimp.
Because you're so close, they're like, "All right, we gotta get that nose in there."
off of there. My nose does not look like that.
You've been bothering the shit out of me.
Yeah.
That's just how it works, dude.
Give them a chimp makeover and it's very rude of you to try and resist.
Yeah, they're doing plastic surgery to you to make you a beautiful chimp like them.
Yeah.
And when you fight them, it's disrespectful.
And then they want to take your hands and kill you.
Yeah, well no, the hands thing is they're like, "Oh, these hands are way too weak.
Listen, I'm gonna take these away, I'll bring you some new ones later, but for now you just sit with those stumps, you'll be fine.
Yeah, well they get confused because they're like, "Those look nothing like your feet."
So basically, here, I'll take these for now, and then I'll go find some that look like your feet and put those there.
Those later. They're just doing, yeah, like a chimp version of Queer Eye, or like...
[laughter]
Okay, so before Monica had this terrible big nose and these hands that looked nothing like her feet.
Now, as you can see, we're ripping her nose off.
Yeah, the monkey bunch is coming to the tent.
There's one chimp that's like the house renovation chimp and he's just throwing glasses at the wall.
Yeah, there's the food chimp who's making, he's just mashing bananas.
The clothes chimp and he's just like...
He's just making every, just taking their clothes off.
You gotta dress like this.
Basically.
Straight guys have the worst taste.
Chimps think that all humans are straight.
They look down upon them.
The queer eye chimps see the house and they're like, "Oh, you can't live here."
So they just try to make you as ugly as possible so you'll be shunned and have to live in the
forest.
Yeah, yeah, they're like this this is the worst. Yeah, let me just figure you
You can't live in this house anymore cuz all your neighbors will hate you. Yeah, and that knows honey. It has to go
Yeah, we're gonna have to file those teeth down because there's no way that could bite through a woman's hand
Suke sue echo ran loose in Kansas City and destroyed police property
(laughing)
It doesn't tend a 300 pound chimpanzee, that's huge.
- Yeah, holy shit.
- Name Suiko broke out of her owner's house
in Kansas City, Missouri on that seemingly pleasant fall day
Suiko set fear into the hearts of an entire neighborhood.
Okay, buddy, you're reusing motifs here.
In the hours that Suiko ran free,
the chimpanzee attacked numerous vehicles along the roads,
jumping on the roofs of civilian cars.
The animal also punched out the window of a police car.
So that's what they mean by destroyed police property,
I guess.
Zuko was shot with a tranquilizer,
which turned out to be ineffective at sedating the chimp.
That's just all of these stories.
It never goes right.
It's always so hard to get the chimp down.
Zuko would ultimately return to its cage, however,
after her owner coaxed her back into her cage.
That's all it took.
- Yeah, yeah.
- But police do not have enough money
to deal with chimp related incidents, clearly.
That's true. That's why they need tanks.
Yeah.
That's what happens if a monkey tries to jump on top of the roof of the car.
You can't do that with tanks.
Yeah, because there's no windows on a tank for the monkey to punch out.
Yeah.
Fortunately, no one was hurt, but the owner incurred a fine and lost possession of the
animal. That's not a big deal to me.
Yeah, not interesting.
I wouldn't say that that is, that was exactly paying the price of owning a pet chimp.
Yeah, well I guess you technically they did because they paid a fine.
Yeah, that's true. I guess it was exactly paying the price.
Yeah, paying the literal price.
Yeah.
Timmy the chimpanzee attacked a police officer.
Now we're getting into sweet.
Now they're getting great.
Now this is cool.
In 2009 a 9 year old chimp named Timmy allegedly tried attacking...
Allegedly!
He's yet to see his day in court.
Allegedly tried attacking a police officer in Winston, Missouri.
Timmy broke free from his cage in his owner's backyard.
He roamed the neighborhood and was eventually approached by police.
He's approached by just two cops with their thumbs on their waistbands.
He's like, "Well, hey there, mister.
What are you doing?"
I like the idea that the author of this list started writing it and then was like, "Oh,
fuck Timmy might sue me and went back and put in a rap allegedly. I hate when I have to go to monkey court.
There's criminal cases, civil cases, and monkey cases. The judge ripped my nose off in monkey court.
The judge is just a huge fat orangutan with a big powdered wig
using a human hand as a mallet.
Yeah, it's just it's just your your your state appointed lawyer is a chip in a
suit and he's just going yeah.
Cost examining you and just urinating your mouth.
Trying to objection is leading the witness trying to fuck the space
between your fingers.
We're going with this.
Someone in the jury throws poop at you.
Monkey court is maybe the best idea I've ever heard.
Yeah, this is a really good-
I can't believe how good that is.
There's so many different possibilities.
There's so many things that could happen.
It's just the whole time in court, like it's just every second, just every single monkey
there is just screaming at the top of their lungs.
You can't hear anything.
They're just going, "Ahhhh!"
The jurors box is like a tire swing.
Just a monkey just swinging.
Faster and faster in a circle.
You're about to be like serve the life sentence and you look over.
It's just a monkeys just like spinning on.
That's like yeah, what if like because it's so hard to get people for jury duty. What if they
They just stack up like they get okay. We got six people, but let's just we'll just fill the rest with chimps. Yeah
They're very agreeable. They'll just go with whatever
Yeah
They're doing jury because one of the chimps
Couldn't we just we realize you can't say yes or no. There's a lawyer doing um
like there's a case on the robbery of a toy store and the and
they're like the lawyers like now did you or did you not steal
this item and holds up a tickle me Elmo and then every monkey in
the room just attacks him.
Timmy reportedly tried opening their squad door, their squad
car door and grabbed an officer before being shot. Timmy's life
came to an unfortunate end.
The incident led to a larger bust.
What?
When police investigated the home of Timmy's owners,
they discovered an illegal puppy mill
with about 100 to 200 small breed dogs,
as well as three other primates.
Wow.
(laughing)
- Imagine having like a hundred like,
I have 200 dogs in my backyard.
I have 200 dogs.
Between 100 and 200.
Yeah.
It's because cops can't count past 100.
They were like, "Eh, it's probably one, two, yeah, it's probably 100 or two."
It was like, it was 20 dogs.
99, 100, yeah, that's about 100.
Wait, hold on, there's some more back here.
Eh, one, two, skip a few again.
Yeah, probably between 100 and 200.
In Montana, Connor the Chimp bit a woman.
The three other primates were just Timmy's owners.
They were just the people.
Sorry, Connor the Chimp.
In Montana, Connor the Chimp bit a woman.
Connor the Chimp.
There are two...
Gene Risotto, a real estate agent
and a resident of Carbon County, Montana,
raised two chimpanzees from birth.
Risotto treated them like they were her own kids.
The chimps, Connor and Kramer.
Kramer the chimp!
What was it?
Come on!
They had their own beds and a set of pajamas.
Allegedly, a group of vandals approached Risotto's residence one evening in 2008,
breaking the locks to the chimp's cages and setting them free.
One chimp was rescued by Risotto's son, but the other wasn't as lucky.
He attacked a woman.
But though she wasn't badly injured, she later underwent a series of tests,
as chimp bites can transmit diseases like herpes and rabies.
But it doesn't even say the result of the test.
Yeah, uh, ma'am, ma'am, we understood that, we understand that you spent over an hour
and a half with a chimp being attacked in your bedroom.
And you might have herpes, so we're gonna need to check you out.
I like the idea, I think this is giving me the idea to keep two chimps in my house just
in case there's ever a break-in.
It's my self-defense, stand your ground chimps.
You have to as soon as you set the chimps free, though.
I have a button on the wall.
I have a big red lever that I pull.
So you're thinking you're...
I'm gonna leave my attack chimps and they just immediately attack me.
You're thinking of a chimpanzee as a weapon now.
This is giving me the idea, I have to admit.
Oh my god.
That's a scary thought.
I'm dark and twisted dude.
Even if they do like, even if there's like, you know, massive gun control and background
checks like a psycho could still get a hold of a chimp, at least in Las Vegas.
Yeah.
that chimp to a school. I'm posting a picture of my chimp on Instagram. Don't come to school
tomorrow. Another in a series of horrifying mass chimpings across America. That's gonna
happen a week from school's reopening. We are gonna speak that into existence. There's
to
There's no metal in a chimp. You could get a chimp at security.
Exactly.
You know?
You could feed a chimp a gun and then...
Oh that? Oh that? That's my little brother.
Just buy him a ticket. It's a gun you can buy a plane ticket for.
Oh my god, like a Vice article that's like terrifying.
People have been 3D printing chimps at their home?
We went to this 3D printing chimp fucking factory.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- And we smoked weed for fear.
- What'd you say?
- What was that?
- Why would you need to buy silencers for your chimp?
(laughing)
- Yeah, chimp bump stock.
- A chimp bump stock is just a leash
so you can control him in the right direction.
- I take my chimp to the range
And I just put like a big head of Pam Anderson, like a hundred feet away and just sicked him.
Bunch of Tickle Me Elmo targets.
It's like, it's like at the gun range, how they'll have like, they'll have like the target that is like a guy in like a burka and he's holding a woman hostage.
But it's just like the same guy with the Tickle Me Elmo.
[Laughter]
Um, this last one, I, this is probably my favorite.
This is the one that made us pick the list.
Annie Butor's family was tyrannized by their chimp Pepe.
[Laughter]
Pepe the chimp.
Pepe. Not even Pepe, but Pepe.
[Laughter]
In the 1960s, famous French singer Leo Ferret owned a pet chimpanzee Pepe,
Pepe, whom Ferret even wrote a song about. But before the Ferret family took Pepe home
to their chateau, Pepe's trainer warned, "I divorced three times because of my chimpanzees.
Be careful." The warning turned out to be justified. Annie
Butor, the daughter of the family, later wrote a memoir about the experience of living with
the primate I need to pull this up I clicked on the link to of that the
phrase later wrote a memoir is linked and I clicked on it and it took me to a
news article with the headline tyrannical chimp ruins childhood what's
I want I just want to find out the name of this memoir I'm trying to find I want
hear what the song sounds like. We should have that as the music at the end.
Just like fade out. Slowly fade out into that song. Pepe had her own bathroom, her
toys, she dined with us, took siestas, drove the car on Leo's lap. In the evening
before slipping on her pajamas she would politely drink her infusion before
hugging us tenderly and very tight. Sorry guys I can't fucking play tonight I got
feed my chimp is infusion. Pepe was described as a tyrant who removed guests
of their clothes and valuables, bit those who upset him, and even took someone's
baby onto the roof. Pepe, you mind watching the kid for a little bit?
What happened was the baby took his tickle me Elmo. I would never trust any child
with anything named Pepe. I want to read these two paragraphs to you from
this news article that it linked to, this adds a new dimension to the story.
Despite Pepe's increasingly unruly behavior, Ferre would strike off any friend who dared
call their "second daughter" an animal, saying, "We will not tolerate anyone calling her a
monkey.
We are not taming Pepe, we are bringing her up."
Covered with bites, the servants eventually fled the 16th century Chateau family home,
which was given over to animals, including a 770-pound pig called Baba that would watch
television and have its ears waxed with olive oil. What the fuck dude. A 770 pound pig.
A pig called Baba. Baba and Pepe. What the fuck that's... I didn't know pigs could get this big dude.
Yeah pigs get gigantic. I'm looking at him dude this is horrifying. In 1968
for a himself could take no more of this quote mad life leaving the Chateau for
Paris where he gained fame and fortune down leaving behind my chimp daughter
for fame and fortune oh my god your chimps are holding you back from success
yeah the last like two paragraphs are so good in his absence Pepe suffered a fall
and refused to be approached. Eventually, Miss Boutor's mother asked a
hunter neighbor to put the chimpanzee out of its misery by shooting it. Leo's
requiem to the primate would be a song Pepe. The singer
who died in 1993 blamed his wife for Pepe's death and they divorced.
Miss Boutor, however, blamed him. "He was nothing but a chicken," she said.
Wait, did she blame Leo or Pepe?
I don't know.
I assume Leo.
Oh yeah, Pepe was a girl.
Yes.
Wow.
This is my new favorite, this is one of my new favorite chimp stories I think.
Yeah, that's up there dude.
That might overtake Travis.
Yeah, I think Pepe is probably better than Travis.
Oh my god, wait, the monkey trainer who said I divorced three times because of my chimpanzees
be careful also said this which is a really this is a good like just um
mnemonic to keep in your head okay more than any other animal a chimpanzee must
know who is the master otherwise you're heading for disaster
I love when I have to come up with a mnemonic to...
When the...
When it's bad, it's not being a master, that's right.
When taking care of my monkey, a tickle me Elmo they find funky.
When Pepe took the baby to the roof for Ray waved a toy pistol at it and shouted, "Daddy's
not happy, daddy's going to shoot!"
This story is insane.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, dude.
The name of the memoir is called "How Could I Forget?"
How could I forget I owned a fucking chimp and my husband flashed a gun at it?
It's called a toy gun. He didn't even have the guts. The chimp knows what a
gun is to the point where they can just use a toy gun. Wait it's not called that.
what the heck it just it says what is it called it says if she said a million
little roses what is I can't find the name of the book well I found this
gigantic 1600 pound pig wins King of pigs title in China oh no it is it's called
how would you like me to forget if you if you translate it from French into
English. How would you like me? How would you like me to forget? How could you
forget? How could you forget? Fuck dude that is so good. I might have to buy this
book to be honest. Yeah get it just that's just a good conversation piece.
Yeah. Never read the book just keep it there so when people ask because it's a
vague enough title. Apparently this this this singer guy is very famous in France
because all the reviews are like "Wow I love Leo Ferret but I never knew any of
this about him. He kind of looks like a monkey. Yeah. He has monkey attributes for
sure. Maybe that's why they got along so well. Maybe. Maybe he thought he was a
monkey. Yeah. Oh and he was a socialist. Wow. Wow. That's actually, okay, that's
actually awesome. All right. All right. I think that wraps it up. Yeah, I think that does it.
Ryan, you got anything to tell people about?
No, that's it, just me.
Just Ryan.
Follow Ryan on Twitter @smilingobject.
Hi, thanks for having me on.
Of course, dude.
Of course.
Since we have to, we should just mention the Gun City thing.
If you subscribe to the $10 Patreon tier, we have a new D&D campaign that we just started.
We're going to try to do episodes every two weeks, exclusive to the $10 tier.
$10 tier, it's very good.
I think it's probably one of the best things
that we've done so far.
I highly recommend it.
- Check it out, bitch.
- Yeah.
- Check it, bitch.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- And also make another account and follow Ryan again.
- Yeah, there you go.
- Appreciate that.
- All right, all right.
- All right, guys. - Bye-bye.
- Bye-bye. - Love Ryan
and both your accounts, bye. - Thanks, everyone.
- Bye now.