[Music]
Podcast About List presents
Gun City
Operation Solucio Dark Brain
[Music]
The year is 2300
Long ago, humanity abandoned Earth
And all the disgusting poor people on it
In favor of a new home, Planet Eba
While there is no life on the planet
There are enough GI Joe PSAs and remixes of "Papa Smurf Cannot Lick Yo Ass"
to feed humanity for at least another half century.
[whimpers]
The largest city on planet hum-
um, GUN city,
is run by a puppet government
installed by the Stakehams Federation of Bodies and Spaces.
Humans have finally learned to worship their corporate overlords
and have fully embraced the oppression and technological comforts that come with it.
And guess what?
Living like that?
Huh.
That's only if you're lucky.
Because if you have to live in the slums of Gun City, where the neon green turns to a crimson red,
you either rule the streets through fear, like the mad suckler, or you shoot up enough
Papi-chukos techno slime to numb the pain, like our friend Chatterbox over here.
And what's controlling all this?
How does the Stakem's Federation of Bodies and Spaces keep this shit in line? Through the world's biggest computer.
No one can escape the computer. It controls everything, doling out just enough slop to keep these piggies hungry, keep them dependent.
It constantly plays overrated synthwave records from 2013 that echo throughout the city, allowing only a single vibe to exist.
It controls the traffic lights, the bitheads, the delta jocks, the panzer freaks, the techno scum, the street samurai, and the netrunners.
It knows everything about everyone, where you last jacked in and when you last jacked off.
off. There's no escape, not even if you're a jazzed up psycho kurumaku. But today is
going to be different. Today Ashton Futures, CEO of Top Ten's Mindfulness Corporation,
has assembled an elite team of professional mercenary operatives to
carry out Operation Solution Dark Brain, a highly classified mission that will
change Planet Ebound forever. The team is assembled now on a laser helicopter
flying over gun city gentlemen introduce yourselves
oh my god, patches you should just do that voice all the time
that should be your speaking voice
oh you're fucking with that normal voice
come on dude that's sick
yeah there you go you know how it is
so yeah everyone introduce your characters
who are you guys
Um...
Uh, well I, um...
I am Blotoss Piss,
a ruthless Grinch hunter from Whoville.
Growing up as a Who,
I was a bit of a Christmas freak,
so when the Grinch stole my favorite holiday out from under my dog-type nose,
I formed a serious tool-style grudge.
I placed a personal bounty of a thousand presents on the Grinch's head
and emigrated to Planet E-Bomb
to carry out my jolly task.
I'm highly trained in gun-cada,
cyber-foo,
and mental karate,
karate and I'm prepared to fight, kill, and fuck any fuzzy green gremlin that tries to
get up in my business and jack my joy. I'm fully decked out in red and green holiday camo
fatigues with a green wireframe cyber metal for most cuttingly sarcastic Deadpool quips
to the camera. I wield a fearsome Chris Kyle style Grinch gun with tactical scoundrel scanner
scope to pick off pesky Grinches from long range as well as dual lead pipes to beat the
stocking stuffing out of any creepy creature that crosses me. My strength, agility, and
mercilessness, mercilessness, my strength, agility, and mercilessness in combat are
matched only by my lack of physical beauty, deep autism, and intense
unpleasantness to be around. And I also have a pet monkey named Patrick."
Whoa. That's awesome.
Alright.
Yeah, so you're sort of standing in the helicopter with your arms crossed.
Yeah, you're, you know, leaning against the helicopter wall, just sort of, uh, ready to make a quip.
And I look at the camera and I say, "I love helicopters, so to me this is more like a
heavinecopter."
And I say that to the camera.
Can we get a pun roll on that?
Yeah.
Absolutely.
What's a...
It succeeds.
Oh, okay, an actual roll.
Hold on, let me see.
Yeah, we need to roll that.
We need to see if he successfully made this roleplay.
I'm gonna have you roll that with advantage, 'cause that was an awesome pun.
Thanks.
What stat is that?
So, what that'll be...
roll two d20s and take the highest number all right that's a really good pun then
that's really good. That was the entire helicopter the entire heaven-icopter actually
everything is really insane. Yeah now we have to call it a heaven-icopter. Yeah I'll just know I mean you
know it just took me four hours so I'll just change this. Just spell helicopter. I'll just change this.
Okay, who's who's next? So
Well, oh I am a computer who spent most of his life as a prop on popular NBCIA
sitcom electronic the office
After spending years in Hollyweird
I decided I needed a change of scenery and quit acting forever to become a corporate operative
But first I needed a body to hold money and breasts
I had my old friend John Krasinski bring me a demon from the police station he now works at,
where the demon was chief of police.
John shoved me in his back and I hacked his body.
In return, I gave John a plastic sheriff's toy gun and star that I got at the dollar store,
and I told him there was an Afghani family trying to enjoy a dinner down the street,
so he left to go kill them.
With my new body, I needed new things, like a name.
Luckily, I am a computer, so I wrote a program that analyzed all of the world's names and
constructed the most normal name imaginable.
So I will always fit in and blend in.
My new name is Ray William Johnson, but you can call me Ray.
Okay, amazing.
So, Ari, how is the demon sort of enjoying the heaven copter?
What are you doing, Ray?
The demon is smoking a cigarette.
Amazing. Okay, cool. No one's yelling at you about it either.
No. No, it's normal.
Okay. So now, who's the last member of this...
I am Patrick Yoda.
I was born to two bitcorn biners on the planet Fukasukabob.
My parents were two yodas and they had normal missionary sex to create me.
Nothing weird happened when they had sex either, it was very normal by Yoda standards.
They didn't even suck each other off, it was purely for procreation.
I grew up hoverboarding on the streets of Succafuckabaw reading my neighbors minds and using my cunning
to make them get me hoagies and hotdogs.
I joined the top 10 mindfulness corp after they tricked me into signing up, saying I
would get free hoverboard parts and Humpty Dumpty all dress chips.
I provide valuable resources to the team as I am the last person in the galaxy who remembers
how to make a smoothie.
Okay.
Whoa.
Nice.
So you're probably just sort of hovering.
Mm-hmm.
Just hanging out.
I'm practicing a flip.
Okay.
On the helicopter?
On the helicopter.
I'm practicing a flip.
That's dangerous, dude.
You could fall out.
No, I won't.
You could hit the rotors and get chopped up.
I'm gonna warn him.
No, I won't.
You can hit the road.
I'm gonna warn him.
You'll get chopped up.
Please, you, uh, there is a 60% chance that you fall out of the
Evanicopter.
Don't tell me the odds.
So yeah, that, that goes on actually for about 15 minutes.
And then you look up at the, uh, the vidi screen in the, uh, uh,
Heaven Copter. Okay. And you see a silhouette of a really cool looking guy from Iowa.
Geez, beautiful.
With a sideways hat on. And you would recognize that silhouette anywhere as
Ashton Futures, the CEO of Top Ten's Mindfulness Corporation. And so he
addresses you guys.
Um.
Uh, yo, what's up guys?
Uh, it's me Ashton.
It's good to see you guys.
Um, I'm so glad you guys, you know, decided to do this mission.
It's gonna be so frickin' sweet, dude.
We're gonna totally punk, totally punk Stake 'Em's, okay?
So what I need you guys to do right now, though, is look in front of you.
And you guys see in front of you a couple of dossiers show up.
And I need you to open these up and we'll gotta go point by point what the mission is.
So yeah, you guys open up the dossiers and you see another screen and it's Ashton Futures just again.
And he says, "Let's just say that a buddy of mine who is not called Cyborg Jerry Seinfeld,
who is not dating a 17 year old Jewish Roomba, gave me a hot tip
[Laughter]
about a video that lives inside the world's biggest computer.
Okay? So I'm thinking maybe we do a punt, right?
Okay? So here's what I'm thinking.
Okay. So.
I'm gonna take you guys in this helicopter over here.
We're gonna fly over the HQ
of Stakehams, which as we all know
is a massive social media manager.
And we're gonna drop you guys on there, right? Okay?
And we're going to go into the world's biggest computer while it's doing an OS update.
Which that happens only once every 50 years, and it's happening tonight.
They're updating to Windows Fogel.
So we have to go in there now.
To have access to the computer.
To finally frickin' delete the Kramer video.
It has been a stain on Mr. Seinfeld, I mean, my friends.
legacy for years now and we're going to delete it from the internet and all
planet ebomb forever so are you guys in or are you out?
In. I'm in.
Okay this would be a lot harder for me as a DM if what I was open to it if you said
out but I'm so glad so. I changed my mind.
*laughter*
Ashen Futures just kills himself
So yeah, he says
"Well, it looks like you guys are gonna
need to be jumping out soon, so
I'm gonna sign off
but make sure you get this done
by midnight
or you guys are the ones" and I wrote this
down "who are gonna be punked"
and uh, yeah the vidi screen
shuts off, the dossiers
explode in your hands
Um, and you see a timer show up on the helicopter on the video
screen. Now it says, uh, um, like five, five minutes till drop.
Um, so you guys are gonna drop in about five into presumably the
giant gargantuan social media manager sort of Megazord. Um,
yeah.
I'm ready.
Okay, let's do it.
So yeah, so time goes by, five minutes go by, you guys get all suited up and everything,
and you jump out.
Can everybody, let's do our first, let's do our first roll of the game though, for real.
So everybody, let's roll, roll either athletics or acrobatics, and we're gonna see how successful
your jumps are.
Which one, which one is it?
So I can, I can choose either acrobatics or athletics?
Yeah, that's usually.
So I rolled a d20.
Mm-hmm.
I got an 11.
Fuck.
Fuck, I got a 2.
And my acrobatics is 0.
Okay.
And you got an 11. So then you got a straight 11.
What about you, Blotas?
I got a 15 total.
I got a 2 with a +4 athletics modifier.
Okay, so you're at a 6.
So, in that sense,
uh,
so yeah, Blotas, you know, you're a
total badass, you know,
Deadpool kind of, like, roguish cool guy.
So it's very easy for you to just
sort of flip out and start skydiving down. You've locked on your target. Can I do a spin? Yeah, definitely. Can I do a spin while I do it? Yeah, you very easily do a spin. You don't have to roll for that.
Patrick Yoda, you know, you're, you're a hoverboarder, you know, this isn't, you know, so you have some experience doing this. So you kind of you jump out, like in, like Sonic the Hedgehog, Adventure 2 battle with your hoverboard ready to go. You don't do anything fancy, though. You're trying to just, you know, it's a pretty far drop.
Ray William Johnson, you just start a trip.
And you're just sort of falling.
You're
just like sort of an unpleasant experience.
And so yeah, you guys are falling. It's like it's looks pretty badass, the camera spinning around you. And but then what happens is, is the camera spins around once more. And it spins past you guys. And now I need you
all to roll a dexterity saving throw but I need our friend Ray William Johnson to roll his with disadvantage.
Oh fuck.
I got a 19.
Nice.
I got it with my negative one.
I got a 9.
Okay.
I got a 12.
Okay, cool.
So,
so
what happens is
you guys are falling
And just as fast as you're falling out of the corner of your eye, um, blow toss, you can see, uh, the Jollibee sky patrol rolling up on you.
Oh no!
Um, and, uh, they immediately, no questions asked, start firing.
Um, uh, and, uh, I'm going to need, uh, yeah, Caleb, you're going to take, or sorry, Ray William Johnson, you take, you take-
That's right.
You take...
*laughter*
You take, uh...
Let's see what you take.
You take one damage, so it's not too bad.
So they shoot at you guys.
"I take one damage."
*laughter*
They shoot their, uh...
I thought I was dead.
No, dude, they shoot their little pellets at you.
Uh, they're doing their best.
They get a surprise attack on you, uh, Ray.
They sort of, like, over, like, a loudspeaker.
They're, like, falling with you guys.
Um, but they're just, like, flying downward, chasing you.
Uh, they're saying, uh...
You're flying into unauthorized areas on behalf of the Stakeholder Corporation.
We will continue to shoot unless you change directions.
Oh, fuck.
Um...
Is it- am I- is this- would it be reasonable to try to fight them in the air?
Or...
Oh, somebody should try and convince them that we're gonna change directions.
Oh, okay.
Oh, yeah.
That'll be- that'll be me.
I'm a very persuasive- I mean, I'm a computer.
Okay, so here's what I do.
I open- I open Internet Explorer.
Okay.
Right?
and I open Cleverbot.
I go to cleverbot.com and I ask her what she would do in this situation.
Right? And she says to me,
"I love music."
[laughter]
And I'm like, and so I'm a little fucked.
So I just got to make it up by myself.
So I say, I say to the guys, I say, we gum in bees.
Let's see if that works.
Yeah.
Roll a d20 and add your persuasion.
15.
Damn.
Okay.
Yeah.
That's pretty good.
It's a pretty good roll, but it's not enough for these guys.
They're pretty hellbound.
Are you kidding me?
So, uh...
They say "BULLSHIT!"
And, uh, yeah.
Everybody has to roll for initiative.
I guess it would be kinda hard to believe that
coming from a demon.
That was kinda the part of the difficulty of that roll.
Demon falling from the air.
I was thinking about it, and I was like,
"I think 'cause he's a demon."
You might be right.
So everyone roll for initiative. We're entering battle.
Alright, I got 13.
Nice. 15.
plus four. Okay, let me just make sure I get this down. Yeah, some of this stuff will be
like the stuff you cut out, like me keeping track of initiatives, I imagine. I'm cutting
out everything except it. Alright, never mind then, what is the good part? In that case,
we're gonna cut out everything you say so that it's just us rolling to nobody.
You like leave in someone asking a question but leave out my answer. Yeah, every single time.
Leave out all the story and just like, "Um, I ate a cheeseburger at 11."
It'd be a proper episode then.
Okay, let's roll for these, these Jollibees. Let's see how they do.
Alright, cool.
Yeah, so in that case, pretty good. Pretty good, everyone.
Yeah, so there's three of them.
You're all sort of falling within, like, within, like, range of each other.
And I'll say that you can probably, like, sky swim, like, at-
I'm gonna say like that you guys are like super, you know, you guys are like super badass like mercenaries.
You can all sky swim at regular speed.
So you're all within range of each other pretty much.
I'm on my...
They come at you and they run on you.
I'm on my belly on my hoverboard.
How many...
And I'm surfing like that.
Yeah, you're like boogie boarding.
I'm still spinning, first of all.
And second of all, how many are there?
There are three of them.
Oh, we got those, dude.
Yeah.
So this is when we fight them now?
Yes. Uh, yeah. So the first thing... yeah, dude.
I'm absolutely gonna get crap from your nerd fans about how I did that dexterity saving throw. I'll find out later.
Who cares? We have no nerd fans.
Yeah, that's true. You guys only have boys.
We made sure.
Yeah, Pat, it's actually your turn first.
Oh, it's my turn. So I have to pick something to do to them.
Yeah, so there's one in the back who, furthest in the back who has a Jollibee special gun.
That's what I wrote for that.
Then there's one closer-
It shoots great.
There's one closer up that has a Chickenjoy Nightstick.
stick, and then there's one closer up also who has a bunch of lasers ready to go that
are all branded with Jollibee and Stake 'Em.
Wait, I have an idea.
Can I just do whatever I want now?
No, it's Patrick's turn.
Not my first turn.
I didn't hear that.
Yeah.
You should ask me about my idea.
Yeah, what's your idea, Caleb?
No, you gotta do your turn. You can't talk to me yet.
Why?
Alright, what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna hit him with a hoverboard boomerang.
Hell yeah.
Okay, yeah. Which one are you gonna hit?
Can I take both of them out?
You can take, you can, okay, here's what I'll have you do. You can hit one of them and then you'll be able to do some damage to the other one.
So if the two of those that are closest together bunched up. So roll a d20 and add your attack bonus there. You see that?
I got 11.
[laughs]
Sorry. Damn, that's plus 8?
Yeah, so yeah, you throw it, you manage to, you miss the first guy in the front, the guy with the chicken joy nightstick, he sort of just deflects it, but it whips around and whacks the other guy, the nerdier one with the lasers in the back of the head. So yeah, now roll for damage. So you see there you got 2d4.
So I got in a I got an 11 on the d20. And now I got to roll the d8. Yeah, okay. I got seven.
Nice. Okay. Yeah, you, uh, so your hoverboard, uh, boomerang
wha- whips around and just like whacks the shit out of that guy.
Alright.
Uh, he is not looking too good. You basically like knocked half
of his like, head off. He looks fucked up. He's fucked up that
Jollibee. He's like, he's like screaming.
I'm glad, I'm glad he's doing that.
I hope he feels pain.
What is his, what is, does, what is his meat?
Yeah, what's it, does it look like chicken?
What does it look like in here?
Yeah, that's a trade secret.
So, they call that a cop-out.
That's fair.
Okay, yeah, it is now your turn, Caleb.
Okay, so there's two left?
Yeah.
Alright.
I will use my ability...
Hacker Mode.
Hell yeah.
To try to hack the one...
One of them seems probably like the leader, right?
Yeah, the Chickenjoy Nightstick.
Nightstick. Okay, Chickenjoy Nightstick. I attempt to hack him. Okay, so that's 19
with my spellcasting modifier. Yeah, he's dumb as shit. He rolled awful. He's a
fucking idiot. You hack him very easily. So in my computer voice, I turn
around to the other Jollibee and I say, "Maybe he was killing our friend as a
joke and he's actually a pretty nice guy. We should maybe leave him alone."
Yeah, so he's he's saying this and he has like a giant alien where like computer tower lodged in his back and is just like saying trying to say this. So for for the folks at home, Caleb's hacker thing.
Ray William Johnson's hacker thing is a computer.
There's an alien where computer lodged into the back of a demon.
It unhooks and then hooks inside of another character.
So and his demon just poses the while that's happening.
So there is now a giant hard drive in the back of this Jollibee and he's just trying to talk to his friend and say, maybe it was okay. I'm gonna, I'm gonna have you, I'm gonna have you roll Persuasion with Advantage.
Yes.
Because that's, that's a good idea. They're not very smart.
Oh, perfect 20.
Oh, you got a nat 20?
Not natural, but I plus three for my Persuasion.
Okay, cool. Yeah, so the other one responds to you. The other one responds to the other Jollibee, just goes,
"Yeah, I guess it was pretty funny when half of his head came off. So, I can kind of see what you're saying, man."
And he turns to Yusuf.
"I mean, I don't really want to die, so let's huff it. Let's huff it out of here."
Nice. The Jollibees are from the 40s.
Yeah. They say things like "Let's hop in."
That's why they wear that little hat.
True.
Okay, and now I right-click, safely eject the hard drive out of the Jollibee's back.
Yeah, you safely eject your back inside your doomed body.
You guys, so yeah, the two Jollibees kind of go away.
They're dragging their dead friend along with them.
Out of the sky?
Yeah. Oh yeah, they're flying in the sky.
this kind of how far are we dropping? You're dropping so far. We've been dropping for like
10 minutes. Um, and, oh, well, it looks cool about the, oh, I shouldn't, I will though.
So the one round of combat in D&D is 6 seconds. So all that happened in just like 6 seconds.
So we have so much time left. Damn. Oh, yeah, of dropping. Oh, awesome. Uh, so it's only
been like it's been like like 12 ish seconds as you've been falling and
however what ended up happening though was that the Jollibee's called in
something when they left. Oh no. And out of the corner of your eye actually you know
what blow toss roll it roll a perception check. Yeah oh that's a seven. Yeah so you
don't really notice it but uh what happened like you're you're sort of
focused on falling and you're doing a lot of cool stunts so you probably don't
notice it but um yeah I'm flipping over doing some DDR shit in there yeah I'm
shooting at my gun everywhere and that catches the attention you know of a
flying blue blur that comes out of nowhere and it's it's none other than
in
They put the blue Grinch in the game, dude.
And he says to you guys, you can kind of make it out as he's like approaching you, like
at Mach speed.
He says, "Merry Christmas, sucka fuckas!" and he crashes right into all of you.
I need all of you to roll a Constitution saving throw.
I got a seven.
Okay.
four. Oh my god. I got a 14. Okay, a blow toss and Patrick Yoda both yards
immediately and there go all my hot dogs. Yeah, in my mouth. That's all blow toss.
That's all blow toss. Hot dogs. Hot dogs. I just want to put that in. Yeah, they all
land in my friggin mouth and I eat them. And then you throw them up
immediately after. I throw them up because they're they're Grinch out dogs. So there's
this sort of exchange of vomit going on as you guys are falling through the sky
and you're knocked totally off course. You manage to sort of hold your ground
Ray and you're now so you realize you sort of look in the distance you see
that the the main part of gun city and the the giant social media manager are
fading in the distance. No. And you look down and you're starting to, you start to
realize that you're falling towards somewhere very different. And so you guys
are gonna have to figure out how you're gonna land safely. Deploy, deploy
parachute. I haven't, we have not deployed our parachutes yet. That's true. Well I
I have. Because I've been on my hoverboard. Yeah, yeah, you guys roll, roll a, I'm thinking
what this should be. I want this to be a, a, a, I guess this is technically a dexterity
saving throw to see how well you roll your parachutes and how well you land. I got a
42. My dexterity is zero. I got a six. I got a ten. Okay, so six, a ten, and what did you
get? 22. Okay yeah you you expertly pull it out. What do you say the camera as you're
landing perfectly? Look at these parrots shoots over here and I point to my the
two other... Ryan Reynolds is fearing for his life hearing these quips.
Yeah you two, Patrick Yoda you do pretty well. What what do you do like a move
when you land I do I do a backflip
mr. rubbing my fucking face that I got a six I land on the ground I do a backflip
immediately and as I'm landing I've also flipped a cigarette and then I land in
the cigarette lands in my mouth okay you got it you're gonna have to roll a
performance check because that's yeah yeah which one is that dude yeah bullshit
what's your performance 16 no wait 16 and then do I add the three here yeah so so
that's a I was in remedial math just took two and a half full seconds to add
three to six I told you okay but with that hey with that 19 who needs math you
fucking stick that landing the cigarette falls in your mouth and you see sort of
people around you give you a polite golf clap like oh it's pretty that was pretty
cool people around us oh you'll see oh fuck no no yeah if I land yeah how do you
land so you fucked up how do you land just um I fucked up and so the demon
that I'm in control of he's sort of like gains consciousness for a minute and he
just starts jacking off demons do now I can't get him to focus on the ground and
he's actually jacking off to the thought of him hitting the ground and dying so
He's just rapidly just right on his fucking demon dick, which is really small.
It's like proportional to like a, like a gorilla dick.
Like it's like really small for his body.
Um, and I'm like, uh, and so I, I try to get him to stop.
I'm like, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Um, and then I, and then what happens is we land his horns first into the ground.
And so I have to wait for somebody to pull me out like a pitchfork.
Uh, yeah, you, you.
I pull him out.
- Do a strength, do a strength.
- I put it back.
(laughing)
I put it back immediately.
- Okay, this is gonna be a strength contest.
So both of you guys roll strength to see
if you're able to either pull them out or push them back in.
- All right.
I got a 10, minus one.
- Okay.
- And what's that?
- I got a nine.
- There it is.
- So Patrick, you're like jumping up,
you're like real little,
you're like trying to like stomp on his feet
to like keep his head in the ground but blowtoss pistol is able to pretty easily
uh...
Why are you doing this dude? Are we like enemies?
No, it's a combat... I was gonna jump off of you.
At who?
At the people.
You were just gonna attack the people?
No witnesses! We're supposed to be... this is a covert mission.
That's a really good point. Those people saw me do the flip and they golf clapped for me.
We gotta take them all out.
So you guys land...
Oh, also I should say, uh, yeah, Ray, you take five damage from that brutal fall.
Five damage, dude? Oh, fuck.
You fell with your horns in the ground.
That's like nor- I don't know.
That's normal for me.
People do that, I don't know. People do that.
So yeah, you guys have landed in the slums of Gun City.
Where the neon turns to orange.
Sorry, did you say "Guns Titty"?
I said-
I think he did. I think he said Guns Titty.
Okay, so I'll just change name really quickly.
[Laughter]
You guys have landed in the slums of Guns Titty, otherwise known as Guns Titty.
Where the grass is green and the girls are pretty.
That's right. And the girls here are pretty busted, folks.
Oh my god.
You're in one of the nastiest parts of all of Planet E-Bomb.
e-bomb where some of the lowest scummiest techno slime dealers live. It's just wall to wall,
tons of fucking Arby's and electronics stores. Stores that sell electronics is what they
say on the signs. People all walk with their head down. They're all just totally impoverished.
They refused to succumb to the glorious Stakem's brand lifestyle.
And because of that, they suffered.
It's a, it's pretty, it's pretty harrowing, pretty, pretty, pretty big bummer.
It's sort of a, it's like, uh, you guys ever see the movie Blade Runner?
It sure is a lot like that.
Whoa.
Wow.
So yeah, you guys are in the middle of the slums.
You feel your Sony N-Gage ring.
[laughter]
It's almost definitely not Sony.
It's Nokia.
Yeah, thank you. It makes way more sense.
You feel your PSP's ring.
Okay.
And you take them out of your...
wherever you keep the hat, I guess.
I'm thinking of the... My pocket.
Yeah, your pocket, but...
My horns.
You know, you keep it...
Tactical kangaroo pouch.
Amazing.
Okay, you guys take it out of those places.
And it's, uh, Ashton Future sort of, uh, goes on.
He says, "Whoa, looks like you guys really fucked that up.
Okay, so if you guys are gonna be able to make it there by midnight, you're gonna have
to find a way to get to the main city.
And, uh, I'm gonna be honest, there's really no good way to get there.
I'd suggest probably start asking around.
You might find a way in.
good luck or again you're and he almost curses and he says you guys are punked
whoa and then he signs off and he likes because you can't curse on TV and yeah
he said fuck a little do that but well you get one fuck it's a pg-13 campaign
yeah yeah yeah so you guys are kind of stranded in gun city times a ticking you
have to do it by midnight before OS Fogel fully updates in the computer so
fuck okay um who's turn is it? yeah so there's people around all different
shapes and sizes there's some freakers on the streets and some is there any big
bitches yeah there are a couple my my demon loves big bitches do you want to
talk to some of the big bitches um let me find a big bitch real quick okay yeah
so uh you know what I want you to do I want you to roll roll investigation see
if you find a big bitch.
Hell yeah.
I roll a 26.
Okay.
So yeah, you spend like a good minute just sort of looking around, peering everywhere,
and you find some of the choicest, largest women in the slums so easily.
You find a group of them sitting outside of a Jollibee's and they're just chatting.
And they're making eyes at you and your demons making eyes at them maybe.
So I'm going to try and take advantage of my demons lustful glare.
And so the demon walks up to him, right?
And he starts going like, "Brr, brr, brr, brr, brr, brr, brr, brr, brr, brr."
Right?
Yeah.
And then I click the mute button.
I go to the dock on myself and I click mute and I mute him so he's just moving his mouth
but nothing's coming out.
Right.
But then I turn the speakers on and I go, "Hello, women of planet E-Bomb.
Could you point us in the direction of the main city?"
Yeah, the two big ass bitches look at you and they're-
How big are we talking?
Yeah, what do they look like? Yeah, how so these bitches have you seen the movie shallow how?
They look like Jack black
Say no more. Yeah, I won't
Yeah, so they sort of look at each other and look at you
I'm gonna sort of like laugh a little bit a little embarrassed
You're like, "Um, you can't like get to the main city like from here, not in any way that I know of."
Why, bitch?
Which one of you says that?
The computer.
Yeah, roll a persuasion check.
You just called this woman a bitch.
Alright, hold on.
I roll a 13.
Why don't you just put it up here and paint her?
- Okay, yeah, she sort of is not too thrilled,
but she's like, "Oh, there's something to this demon.
He's kind of, he's at least muscular, you know,
maybe there's something there."
And so she says, "Because you need like so many different
kinds of like verification to even begin to go to the rich
part of town."
And the other one goes, "Yeah, it's really hard
to get there."
(laughing)
- We ran into John.
Jack Black does he scat at all yeah he was we get some Jack Black rickety kicks
yeah yeah yeah that's what they say to you though okay so at least that's some
information yeah I have I have an idea is it my turn idea you could do whatever
you can just okay outside of combat there's no turns you can I make them a
smoothie okay and these are some big-ass bitches so they might appreciate that
yeah so let's let's do this so you make them a smoothie and yeah how do you give
them the smoothie because I'll determine whether or not they drink it uh it's in
like a big like you know like the paper cones for water but imagine one of those
but it's like big like a snow cone holder no not even like it's kind of like more
like a dunce cap. Like a traffic cone. More like a dunce cap. What do you say? Does it
say dunce on there? No, it's not like a dunce cap, it's like a dunce cap for a giant. Does
it say dunce? No, it says smoothie. Are you guys having this conversation in game? Yeah.
Yes. Yeah, so they're sort of looking at you guys talking through what you should be able
to see. And then they're like, "What are you doing?"
I'm making a smoothie.
Okay.
Duh.
Okay, so yeah, do you-
That's what I'm doing.
Do you offer them the smoothie?
I offer them the smoothie, but I don't know what's in it yet.
Okay, yeah, so-
You don't know what's in that?
How do you say that?
Do you say that?
I still don't know what's in the smoothie.
Yeah, okay, so you have to... yeah, so the thing about Patrick's smoothies is that you don't know what's in them until you drink them.
Mm-hmm.
So...
Fine.
Roll a persuasion check since you're offering these strangers a drink.
[Laughter]
I got a stranger, they're big bitches.
Yeah, okay, so they're big bitches, so they're kind of just down, you know, like, you know, respect, you know.
Yeah.
You hand them the smoothie.
Mm-hmm.
They take a drink of it, and it is the best goddamn smoothie they have ever had.
Oh my god.
They are losing their fucking minds.
The Jack Black one is doing like the little Jack Black like shuffle where he's sort of
like this.
I know the shuffle.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm familiar with it.
When he walks between the desks in School of Rock.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Because that's what I was thinking of.
Yeah, he's so, he's so excited.
And he's just now, he's a guy.
He's Jack Black.
He's still a big bitch.
I just didn't care.
He sure is.
They're so excited and they're like, "Okay, okay. Oh my god."
And Jack Black's like, "Scooby-dee-wee, wobbly-dee-boo!"
And then he's like, "Okay."
That was the best smoothie I've literally ever had.
Okay, someone who might know actually how you can get in is Sullivan the Frog.
He lives a couple of blocks down from here.
Um, you won't miss it, 'cause his apartment looks like a tree stomp.
*laughter*
I tell her that that's my cousin.
Are you lying?
Roll deception check.
*laughter*
Making that up?
Okay, I also tell her that's my cousin.
But-
I say he's not my cousin, but I'm lying.
He is my cousin.
Wait, I roll- alright.
So you all have to roll deception because you're lying about how you're related or not related
to Sullivan the Frog.
Alright, do we roll it at the same time?
I got an 8.
You got an 8.
I also got an 8.
I got a 5.
Okay, yeah, they're just...
Yeah, you all sort of...
Just like, just like three dudes like immediately, "Yeah, yeah, he's my cousin, yeah."
Like all at once.
He's not my cousin.
(laughter)
- Just like, just like three dudes like,
immediately, "Yeah, yeah, he's my cousin, yeah."
Like all at once.
- "He's not my cousin."
- Yeah, they sort of like, like, you're like, "Oh, okay."
Yeah, like they're like watching three guys
try to brag about how this frog is their cousin
or not their cousin.
- Yeah.
- And they're like, "That's cool."
- "It is cool, bitch."
- Okay.
talker yeah you sure do they're like okay like honestly thank you for the smoothie
best smoothie ever which could be hard to be we're gonna go like home and so they
get up and they leave I tell one of them they're my cousin I put a tracking device
on them hold on okay what do you do Patrick and then I told I tell one of
of them that they are my cousin.
Yeah, dude, that is so unhinged.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, they just sort of walk that off.
I can't even begin to conceive of another kind of response.
I yell after them that Patrick is my cousin.
They're walking fast.
I turn on bass boost on my built-in speakers and I say,
"I have no cousins."
*laughter*
Okay, I'm gonna say at this point, you guys are making so much commotion.
That you've got to tap on the shoulder, Patrick Yoda, since he's the only one who can reach.
You're the only one whose shoulder he can reach.
And you turn around and see a handsome dandy of a little frog.
Oh my god.
an adorable little bowler hat on. It's my cousin. He's uh. Does he think that that
Yoda, Patrick Yoda is also a frog? He's at first, and then he turns around he's like
it's not what that is. He's not wearing any pants but he's got like a cartoon
bottom half so like no indecency. Is he wearing like a suit? He's wearing like a
suit up top like he's winning the pooing it gotcha he says to you guys excuse me
are you guys looking for me no yeah I don't know who you are I cover I cover
Patrick don't know who you are with my hand I'd cover Patrick's mouth I give him
really light tap with the pipe just enough to like confuse him. I cracked the pipe out of camera's hand.
Alright let's get back on track.
There's like a lot I could resolve there it's like you're trying to figure out
yeah he he sort of regards this like interaction where it's like no yes no
yes he goes "uh well if you're looking for solve in the frog that's me" and he
point to himself with two thumbs and smiles. Is there any way that I can help
you guys? Okay I got this boys don't worry about this.
All right I walk up to him eight over nine feet of demon and I just say I'm
just like I'm just like can you point us in the direction of the city? Oh you're
trying to get to the main city and leave try to get out of Guns Titty. He's sort of
like nods and he winks at you but frogs have translucent eyelids so it's just he
just like blinks it's like a weird filter goes over one of his eyes okay and he
says I'd certainly like to help you but I was wondering if there's something you
could do for me first no you guys look pretty strong okay real real quick I I
I hack Patrick Yoda.
No.
Yeah, I hack Patrick Yoda.
That's gonna happen? Okay, so what you have to do then
is you roll a
uh, amazing, okay.
You roll your
d20 plus 8, Caleb.
Okay. 20.
You got a 20?
Yeah. He didn't get a 20.
I did. Prove it.
12 plus 8.
Oh, yeah, that's what that is.
I had to take a route for Patrick.
You have to roll, oh shit, Patrick has minus two intelligence.
He's like, "Oh wait, someone knows."
What do I roll?
You have to roll, Patrick, there's literally no way you can beat a 20.
You have minus two intelligence.
I think I can do it.
Okay, I want you to try.
Roll a d20 and subtract two.
Seven.
Okay, so that's a little bit less than 20.
So the tower unlodges from your back, Caleb.
Describe the process of hacking.
Yeah, yeah, so again, I safely eject the tower, right?
But then I realize that I have no way to propel myself
since we're not in the air, I can't use like,
you know, centrifugal force.
So I just drop onto the ground.
And then the demon football punts me
into the back of Patrick Yoda's head
where he conveniently has a USB 3.0 port, right?
Female.
And I plug into it.
And all of a sudden, and also Sullivan the Frog
does not notice this somehow because I rolled a 20. I'm so good.
Okay, I actually would rather you roll a stealth check to see if it works.
Oh, come on dude. Okay, alright.
Since you want to complicate everything, I roll a
22, er, 21. Okay, yeah, let me roll for him. He's probably not going to notice.
He's not very observant. He is looking right at you though, so we'll see.
No, he doesn't notice. He did pretty bad. He doesn't notice at all.
Yeah, you just hack into Patrick Yoda and you're deeming-
So suddenly, this is what it looks like to Sullivan the Frog.
He's trying to talk to you guys.
There's like a fight going on between two of you.
Uh, one of you starts T-posing and the other one stops like talking all of a sudden.
After he just said "no", after asking if we needed his help,
Patrick Yoda said "no" and all of a sudden his eyes go white
and you see the Matrix code overlaid.
And he says, "Actually, yes, we would love your help."
Saul in the front goes, "Oh, that's good.
Well, here's something I wouldn't mind you guys doing for me.
So, well, I don't know how familiar, you guys don't look quite like you're from around here,
but, well, there are a lot of gangs here in Guns Titty, and one of them is the uncle and
his nephews they come around every night and they give me wedgies and call me
slurs like happi which is a slur for frogs they're a small-time gang and
they're hooked on the stuff they push that techno slime so you know I don't
think they're too tough probably for you guys but if you guys can maybe just talk
to them or something I'd really appreciate it I say mission accepted and
and I'd crouch down I look right in his eyes when I say it.
Um, so he knows that I'm serious. He like pees himself a little.
Uh, very scared. Um, and he says to you guys,
to you, uh, "Well, okay, you can, should be able to find them at the
Suckafuckabarn grill. Um, that's where they're usually pushing their techno slime.
Probably in the back. Anyway,
I have to go suck a dick."
I just never figured out what he was going to say there.
Okay.
Say, "TMI" to the camera.
Yeah.
You didn't need to say that, Sullivan.
You could have just said you were going to go to the bathroom.
That would have been fine.
Yeah, we don't need to know what goes on in the bathroom.
We get it you're doing number four
Get lost you hoppity little bitch
You are a hoppity little bitch he looks really dejected
But we will save you
He says I'll see ya I say think of us think of us as the lesser of two evils
I'm gonna say we're gonna. I'll see you I'm gonna call you later
I marked the location on your cyber map, so it should be not too hard to find
Come back here when you've sorted it out. I'll get you topside no problem
And he sort of hops away and goes into his little stump a couple couple blocks down you can watch him walk hop the entire way
Yeah, so you guys have it marked on your map. You can see that the Suckafuckagrill is
Further down and I no longer. I'm no longer hacked by Caleb. Yeah, I
Unhack your hack your hack your hack for the rest of the day. I unhack you I unlatched myself from the back of your head
And then I I use my CD drive to crawl myself back to my demon
Mm-hmm yeah, and then he picks me up, and he puts me he accidentally puts me on his penis, but it still works
Okay, another port there. Yeah. Yeah, so you guys want to go to the suck a fuck a barn grill?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, I want to go around the back
Yeah, you walk so you guys walk down a few blocks you see you pass by a bunch of shops
Patrick put on sunglasses for those I've acquired found them on the ground
What kind of shops do we walk by we walk by a sunglasses store and I pick up a pair of sunglasses
Yeah, so you should have a hundred. Oh you could definitely you definitely have oh no no you have a hundred dollars
You got all of a hundred dollars so of course I didn't I didn't pay for these though. I found them
Okay, so you walk by a sunglasses store, and you found sunglasses that you didn't pay for
Okay, cool. I'm gonna let that go
Yeah, so Patrick Yoda steals sunglasses you walk by a sunglasses store
You walk by you walk by a Costco
Giant Costco you walk by okay wait we going as we walk by the Costco my demon
Uncontrolled be runs in and gets a chicken bake
And I'm like, I'm sorry guys
Sometimes he gets hungry. Yeah. Yeah, you get you get your chicken bake
You walk by a few
Dispensaries that are like like, you know medically approved techno slime
You walk by a few like people who you bought for a few like a
VR sort of like arcades where people are putting on VR helmets and stuff and you get to
The Suckafucka barn grill and it's just it sort of looks like a giant like can of beans
It's sort of a
weird like
chrome futuristic can of beans shaped kind of place.
Wait, are you saying that in the future
cans of beans will be chrome and futuristic?
Or it's like a can of beans but with futuristic attributes?
It's a can of beans chrome like situation.
So you get to the Suckafucka Bar and Grill though. It's probably the seediest bar in town.
It's where the Mad Suckla, the kingpin of the
Guns Titty is said to like sort of run a lot of his operation out of it.
There's a lot of gangs there. You guys, you walk inside you see
the Hillary Clintons, or a gang of men who all got surgery to look like Hillary Clinton.
You see the Jerky Boys.
Just the Jerky Boys.
You see the Techno Scum Psychonauts.
Yeah, those guys are the only cool ones. Those are the ones that Cameron has a join those guys. Yeah
Everyone who is not in a gang is wearing an oculus rift that simulates getting a blumpkin from boxy
Damn dude the first time that name's been said in a recorded medium. Maybe ever
It's what I'm here for uh and you guys see the bartender which is a
a giant worm named Jamal.
- Sounds like a big bitch to me.
- Oh my God. - Jamal the worm?
- Jamal the worm. - It's Jamal the worm.
He's the bartender.
- I order.
- I say, "Hey, Jamal, what's up, buddy?"
- Yeah, he's singing you guys over.
He's like, "Hey, what's going on, guys?
"How you doing?"
He's just sort of immediately
the most chill, friendly worm around.
You see him from the theater. - I order.
- Yeah, what do you do?
- I order one Pib Cosby from Jamal the worm.
- He says, "Pib Cosby coming right up."
And he, uh, he sort of is balancing himself on his worm body and using his
tail to make the drink.
Uh, while he's doing that, he says, what can I help you with fellas?
Um, real quick.
I ordered just a normal Cosby.
Okay.
He sort of says you're going to have to go out back for something like that.
Uh, what's it, wait, what's the name of the gang we're hunting again?
The uncle nephew.
Yeah.
I'm going to snide.
So I, so I asked him all.
I say, "We're looking for a gang called the Uncle Nephews."
Jamal goes like, "Shh, shh, shh.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I only have one volume setting."
(laughing)
All right, all right, okay.
The uncle and his nephews, they come around here.
They're kind of a, ugh.
He sort of rolls his worm eyes and he says,
"They're a real pain.
The sucka's been trying to get rid of 'em himself.
They're taking too much off the top.
typically they hang out back where they shoot laser craps and play
laser jacks
uh...
honestly
i'll look the other way if you guys want to go out there do whatever it is you
need to do
well
i think that you know i think i have banks brother
and then i try to get a little bit
yeti six is what a word tell up in
says says that all just let that go that's fine
uh...
what's that order three more pit cause these
yet he's like one every each of us
i order a crime just got you to because the
i don't want to uh... humble to give me extra energy
future and why is for both the use
guys
both you guys and he sort of makes both the drinks for you he makes you the three
uh...
uh... because the c_b_o_ now i got a drink to a loan and my feelings are hurt
just okay well i could drink the one and mix it with my eyes no we gotta get out
back to you there's a thing we have to do not use my i'd use my lead players are
all you have to go and i give myself brain problems
finish your drinks a list of
but you are
all right
yes yeti do you want
you can have the chrome bowl if you want is making patrick you know i got one for
you know i got him a bit past the two
well how about what i do not i don't want to drink all of them out there and i
ordered
i order three more pit cause these okay so yeah he says i'm going to have you
guys off
uh... i think you're the only thing that has many of this is you want
many are a lot of what i thought i was going to have a good back door
okay wait let's try it out and uh...
how about i think
i think patrick
yoda should go out there and pretend to be one of the net use you look like an
avenue and
do you know what i'm saying
me and ray will hang back in a things get ugly
we run in a week
so i think you know the way that i
should i turn someone into people you'll be dead if things get ugly your your
dates if you die will just for if you don't i will just leave
all right
so this is what i'm saying is we sacrifice
patrick
i agree
no so that's not what's up country
here you know what let's just take a vote
what if we are going to be very well i said let's take a vote on on on that's
not you have to do tactics
that's right and it's actually here
the tactic here is to send patrick of first alone okay
and he should leave his well i'm all in favor say i
i by
all of those in a metric we have to do the but i i think that i'd tell you that i
think that's a sign unanimous no uh...
we have to go around
i pick up i said i had to do the body
pat i'd pick up patrick's tiny yoda body i put him on his hoverboard my push him
out the back door before you roll rolling it together it's great strength
contest so both you guys role for strength okay
i got an eleven
I got a 17.
Okay.
Fuck.
Yeah, so you try to like grapple this little Yoda guy and put him on a skateboard and what
do you do?
How do you shove him off?
I...
Well, I grab him by the...
Oh, you're talking to me.
Yeah, you suck.
You don't get to do anything.
What I do is I go between Cameron's...
Or I go between Piss' legs and I swing up onto his back and now I'm on his neck.
Okay, so you're just sort of...
Okay, then I just walk in and now
The entire plan just you guys are sort of just the mighty
We're pretending to be one
We're one before they walk out of the door I jump on there on on Patrick's shoulders
Yeah, Cameron, I'm gonna need you to roll a
strength saving throw to see if you could hold him.
Okay. I got a 23.
You're strong as hell. You're just holding a demon and a Yoda. You guys come out I guess to take goodbye tickets to the R rated film. You go out to the back and you do see you do see you see that the the alleyway is lit by much dimmer neon than the than the inside the bar than the main city.
You know, it's a little bit seedier out here, right?
And you see, dimly lit in the back, you see this big British
looking orc man and you see just, he's just like hideous
looking and he's wearing a white tank top, which has another
name.
I'm trying not to, I'm trying not to use it anymore, you know,
and he's wearing that and hanging on his arm is just, is
this like busted looking blonde woman who is just like like talking at him saying
some stuff and then on the ground you see a bunch of little goblins dressed in
sort of like Adidas tracksuits but chrome and they're all just playing jacks and
when you lose that you get shot in the head the kind of jacks they play.
And so they see you guys come out.
And um...
Okay, we continue.
No, yeah, the uncle sort of looks at you guys and says, "Hell you boys want!"
"We're one nephew!"
"We're all stacked up!"
"Hell, whoa!"
"First of all, we're one big nephew!"
Yeah, yeah, so we try to convince them that we're just one big nephew.
Yeah, yeah, how about this?
Imagine this.
Say each of the individual things you would say, and then we'll imagine all of them being
said at the same time. Okay, ready? Three, two, oh no wait we'll do it. Yeah just do that.
I say, I say, oh yeah let's do it. Okay, three, two, one. We're just one big nephew. I'm one big nephew.
One guy. Okay so. One. He sort of is like looking around at you guys and he's like
"What? You're, you're my nephews? Are you guys trying to, trying to become nephews?"
we're nephews yeah you don't remember us me exception let's do it
roll deception I'll say with advantage because you're all stacked up on all of
us yeah all you guys roll deception I got 17 with deception right yeah yeah I
also got 17 I got 20 nice yeah okay yeah so he sort of does oh yeah I guess uh
must have forgotten and I hired you guys why don't you play jacks with the rest
of the nephews and see the little goblin man like yeah come play jacks with us
come on okay we remain on top of each other though yeah because nobody can
move until I move because I'm the heaviest one and I'm on the top no I
know no I'm the one who moves I'm on the bottom no no no nobody nobody can get
off like we're gonna remain stacked until oh yeah yeah okay I walk over to
the I walk over to the jacks and I sit down with them come on your real nephew
you can play jacks with us.
Okay.
Actually, here's what happens.
Because, uh, uh, because you are at the bottom and because your arms are busy
holding Patrick Yoda's legs over your shoulders, what you have to do is you
have to sit 10 feet away from the circle of people playing jacks and bend over
so that I can be the arms.
Okay.
I do that.
Yeah.
And I, I pick up the jacks and then I looked immediately.
Not how you play jacks.
Yeah, and then I pick up the jacks, and I put them in my mouth.
Okay, yeah, the uncle looks at you, he's like, "Wait a minute, my nephews would never do that.
Who are you guys, really?"
I pull out my lead pipes, and I hit the uncle.
Okay, everyone roll initiative.
Let's fucking go.
Okay, hold on.
Fourteen.
I rolled a four.
I got eight.
Okay, cool.
So, before anything happens, which Cameron, you do get to go first.
You are going to get to like whip out that lead pipe, but you see the blonde woman who is hanging on the uncle just like sort of stand at attention and turn like just rock solid and the uncle like picks her up like a sword.
Whoa.
Yeah, so that's, that happens right away.
Yeah.
Uh, broadsword is the-
Oh shit.
Oh my!
Yeah.
Uh, so uh, yeah.
Uh, now, so yeah, now Cameron, you're up.
You're up.
So you, you, you, you're gonna go, you're gonna go lead pipe on them.
You're close enough, 'cause you guys approached, uh, did the, the, the, the Jack's subterfuge.
Um.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's really good in your mouth.
I, uh.
Alright, that one's my bad, guys.
I'm sorry.
I do, I, I, why did I do that?
I do I I whack the or how many nephews are there so there are like
what's the number of nephews so here's a nephew uncle ratio there's like four or
five little nasty goblin nephews the way they're gonna work though is it's like
horde fighting so it's like you just attack the nephew group as long as
they're within range and you're just gonna sort of take out a few of them
depending on how much damage you do all right gotcha okay I wanna I want to fuck
up the nephews. I want to hit the nephews with my dual pipe. So I take out my dual lead pipes
and I spin them around in my hands really fast and I just stick my hands forward like
they're two helicopter blade lead pipes. Roll a d20 as your attack modifier. Yeah let's
see here that's a 13 okay yeah that's a hit okay roll for damage that's 17 damage
okay yeah describe your kill on all of the names okay they just go flying they
um I stick my spinning pipes into the midst of them and they all just like
scattered and they go they bounce around like bowling pins and disco completely
rigid
instant rigor mortis
uh... no it's not that it looks like it it looks like a p_g_ movie that has
comic violence yeah there's no blood is just bruising it is a bruise covers all
of their bodies instantly
you you you're just killing heartless in kingdom hearts it's just there's training
to mist yeah exactly evaporate
That's my cool cultural reference.
So, yeah, they're all gone.
And the uncle just goes, "MY NEPHEWS!"
And like, screams towards the sky.
*laughter*
He's just like, despondent.
You see a single tear from his broadsword.
Like, she cries as well.
Completely stone-faced otherwise.
Yeah, is there anything else you want to do?
Do I get an extra attack and then a cunning action?
Yeah, you can do that.
Okay, I'm gonna I'm gonna uh
I'm gonna hit the the
The uncle with my eyes for it. Yeah, I want to hit him in the head
Right on the top of the head down word
That's a
Wow, yeah you yeah, you beat his armor class roll for damage
That's 12
Okay, yeah, so yeah, you mess him up you sort of like whack him on the sides like a bunch like in the ribs and he's like
Like at each hit
So he got kind of he kind of got beat down, but he's still he's still holding himself up
He's still doing he's still holding up the rage the anger at your your violence to his nephews your nephew violence, okay?
Yeah, um nephew on nephew violence. Yeah, I were they playing it was there like a table. They're playing games on
uh... i would say yeah they're trying to go off to the side for a little bit
behind you
i want to hide under the table
okay yeah so uh...
your you're kind of in plain view but what you can do you can roll for
and also you're within range of him so you have to you have to actually
disengage ok if you wanna hide you can
but if you don't disengage he has an attack of opportunities and i know i'm
just i'm just gonna uh... i'm not gonna hide i'm gonna stand there and i'm gonna
say if you're not going to a fucking that's use here
and i'm a status status
kind of thing i think i'm not a lot of and my city's green 'cause i'm a who and
that's the color of who's been just
decided that
yet another who would do
he uh... he's like mad and he also like look like does the thing where he's like
a like a duck cartoon dog elixir spit
up in his mouth and
he's still a few me mad though
uh... and it's actually his turn
so after you just
massacred his nephews. He's gonna try to hit you with the blonde wife, his blonde, his broadsword.
So let's see how that goes. Okay, yeah, he's gonna land that hit for sure. It beats your armor class.
So he's gonna roll for damage now as well. Let's see how he does. Okay, yeah, so he takes his wife,
his broadsword woman, and he sort of like does the thing where you like drag a sword on the ground
and like do an upper cut with his wife and just like messes you up in the middle
you take ten damage yeah yeah and how many hit points is that what 10 or no
how many hit points do you have left I mean 23 okay that's not bad yeah and he
at this point he um also you need to roll a wisdom saving throw okay that's a 15
okay so as the sword is coming up to hit you the the broadsword the woman just
also like shrieks right in your face but and you get rattled for a second but
there's no other really effects okay as a reaction can I look into the camera and
say that's gotta hurt yeah okay I do that okay cool roll
performance check okay yeah oh no that's it - I say that's hurt God mess up my
quip and I said I love your quip and I look away from the camera by accident
yeah you do you do a famous Justin Roiland Ricky Morty sort of oops oops
I'm messing up my lines. Exactly I burp in the middle of it. Yeah. But it's not funny
unlike Ricky Morty. Right it's very funny. Okay it is now your turn Patrick. All
right am I still attacking the uncle? If you want to I mean you can also do
whatever you want. I could yeah hmm because if I could attack him but I
I could also turn him into Pickle Rick.
Whoa.
You could, you can try for sure.
Hmm, but that, should I use Techno Slime points this early?
You got lots to, you can recharge it, use it.
Oh, alright, then I'm gonna use it.
Do it.
Alright.
Which one do I roll?
Okay, yeah, so for, for Pickle Rick,
Uh-huh.
Uh, your, your, basically your polymorph spell,
you roll,
polymorph spell, you roll a, um, they have to actually roll. So, they basically have to
resist, um, a roll. So basically you, so what do you say as you sort of, uh, use this, and
like, how do you use this, this, this ability? What is it that, how does it do it?
It just, uh, I just kinda stand there, I wiggle my fingers and something happens.
Okay, cool. So that's how it goes.
Then he has to roll a resistance of charisma.
Yeah, he fucks that up big time.
Yeah, so he turns into Pickle Rick.
Does he want to turn into Pickle Rick? Or you can turn him into anything.
I can turn him into anything, okay.
I'm gonna turn him into a nephew.
Whoa.
Uncle to nephew.
So yeah, you turn him into a nephew.
He shrinks down.
His shirt is now sort of just like
just like hanging over him. He's not really able to lift the sword so he's
probably he's gonna have disadvantage on attacks with that and he's just like you
little punk I'm not a nephew I'm an uncle! That's exactly what I wanted to see.
Okay yeah is there anything else you want to do? You can move, you can you can do
anything. I'll take care of them. So so there's a bunch of nephews on the
ground there's a bunch of gang member did the part of the gang
dead yeah can I loot their corpses as a free action yeah you can just do it
loot them now I'm looting there I'm looting them now
ok yeah you find you find a $17
whoa we made it big time baby that's a come up
yeah my 17 my $100 is now 17
That's called growing your wealth, business mindset.
Or 117.
Yeah.
It's to murder people and then steal from their bodies.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah.
You're up now, Caleb.
Okay, so I...
So he's in his big shirt, right?
Yeah.
So I grab him by the collar of his big shirt, but then he falls out.
Okay.
So then I throw the shirt away, and then I grab him by his goblin skin, right?
right and I pick him up and I say if you ever in your life oh sorry
if you ever fuck with Sullivan the frog again I'm gonna make you wish that you
were a still a nephew so okay a couple things my first first oh sorry sorry
finish finish what you're saying no that's that's as far as I've gotten okay
yeah let's roll a strength just a straight strength check strength to pick
up that little fucking guy oh just to grapple him basically oh yeah okay
fuck how'd you do for I had it all planned out well let's see it is a
strength contest so let's see he might he might fuck it up but he's weaker now
because he's he's now got huge dude I got yeah yeah no he sort of just like slaps
you away like flailing it's not okay oh wait I can do two things during my yeah
you can still tell him what you said to him all right so I say you still say
that yes you say that still yeah just roll an intimidation check with
disadvantage because you just like fucked up frankly let him timid yeah so
So you roll two d20s, add your intimidation to each of them, and then take the lowest- the lower number of the two.
Fuck. The lower number?
Yeah.
Uh, eight.
Okay, I'm gonna see how he does against that. Uh...
Yeah, no, he's sort of- he's like, "Fuck you, you weird demon freak!"
Ah, come on. Okay, alright. Um...
I- I- I say, uh, "You guys handle this one."
And then I walk inside and I drink all the Pib Cosby's.
- Okay, yeah. - They're sitting on the bar.
Yeah, he's gonna get an attack of opportunity as you're walking away.
Oh, fuck. I don't even care, whatever.
You're like, dejected and you start walking away and he tries to hit you.
Oh, he completely misses.
He literally tries to hit you and he, like, falls over and is knock-prone.
Which means you guys have advantage on attacks on him.
He tries to hit you and he trips over his giant shirt like an asshole.
Your turn, Cameron. You're inside now, you're just drinking Pimp Cones.
Yeah, I'm just slamming him back.
Jamal's like, "How'd it go?"
*laughs*
He's so-
Amazing. It went so good. I was so cool out there. You should've been there, Jamal.
Fizzbump bro.
Deception check later.
*laughs*
So he's lying prone on the ground, right?
Yeah.
Can I use my gun to shoot him in the butt?
Yeah, you can do that as many times as you want.
Yeah.
*laughs* As many times as you want?
Okay, I do it a thousand times.
Okay.
Okay, I take out my Grinch gun and I look through the scope and I shoot right into the hole.
And that's a 23.
Oh, you hit.
You hit roll for damage.
Uh, six damage.
That's not very much damage.
Okay, yeah.
I mean, you still, you still, yeah, so you shoot him and he sort of is able to wiggle
a little bit out of the way.
And so you get him like kind of in the shoulder and he's like, "Ow!
Fuck!
It stings like a Grinch!"
And he's just sort of writhing in pain.
When I hear the word Grinch, I flip the fuck out and I put my gun back, I holster my gun
and I take out my dual pipes and I go gorilla on him.
Oh, absolutely.
Again, you roll with advantage.
Advantage, okay.
That's 22.
Yeah, yeah.
Roll for damage.
twenty two
yet yet will for damage
uh... fifteen
jacquie describe your kill in the cycle
okay so i just i'd go completely
gorilla mode i freak out because when i hear the grinch my eyes go green i
completely green out and i
i started with the pipes and then i dropped the pipes and i just start
taking him apart like string cheese and i'm just pulling him and there's just
nothing left is a little
red dot on the ground is all that's left of him and I eat him also.
Because I just, I enter full blood lust. Grinch lust.
Yeah, you just pulverize him and you eat him.
And yeah, you guys, his wife is just a sword.
Just still a sword. Permanently. Permanently a sword, frozen on the ground.
And yeah, so you guys beat the uncle and the nephews.
So yeah, do you guys want to go back to Selvin or hang out at the bar?
You guys should loot them of Technoslime before you come in.
Okay.
I think you're at 7 right now, Technoslime points.
I'm still at full.
Patrick is.
Oh, I forgot about my fucking monkey.
I'm at 9.
You do have a pet monkey, oh my god.
Oh no, Patrick, you have 5 Technoslime points left actually.
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
So wait, if I play the base, that's...
I think it's another 2.
Oh yeah, damn. You can recharge it, you have the shit to recharge it. Yeah, it's just a
risk reward with recharging it. Alright, let's do it. Which is the fun. Let's jump back in.
So if I inject myself with techno slime, oh I get, oh you regain five, okay. I thought
you, it said ten pints, I thought it said, it meant points. No, no, no. It's like you
have like it's like you inject a whole pint of the slime into your arm yeah yeah
it's it's also something you would be able to buy here too because like techno
slime is like pretty common it's basically how anybody stays happy or
sane you guys familiar with the the opium epidemic yeah I've never heard of
it yeah no not not in New Hampshire for sure no there's no way no way you would
heard of that. Okay, cool. Yeah, we can we can friggin resume. So yeah, you guys beat the shit out of the uncle and his nephews. You walk back into the bar. People heard the commotion outside you see the Hillary Clinton sort of squirrel away. You know, they're kind of nervous. You see some of the other other gang members. You see the jerky boys like sort of like cower to like you guys are have kind of made yourselves known.
Especially especially a blowtoss piss that you you literally
Beat the uncle to a pulp and then ate him
Which was so crazy
You a savage for that one
You crazy I go into I say to somebody somebody should give me $10. I
Want $10 one of the Hillary Clinton's immediately gives you $10. I love giving you money
Are the Hillary Clinton's just the Johns from crooked media?
they're the jaws of crooked media who got surgery to look like Hillary Clinton
yeah they're the jaws yeah they're like it's like a gang of Elvis impersonators
but instead it's Hillary Clinton's I say thank you
you're welcome now someone give me $20
yeah somebody takes $20 away from Patrick
No!
Everyone sort of shuffles their feet and they're kind of like, "Did he eat the guy?"
Or does he... I don't know.
I turned him into the nephew!
You're yelling this at a punk, you're two feet tall, yelling this at all the gang members.
"Jamal slides you a Pib Cosby."
Ahh!
That's all I needed.
I give my ten dollars to Jamal and I say thank you.
He says, "Anytime, boys. Thanks for taking care of those punks."
Now I give the $17 I found outside to Jamal in exchange for a six pack of Pib Cosby.
He's like, that's usually $20, but okay.
And then I pull my gun on Jamal and try to rob him of all the money I just gave him.
Okay, roll an intimidation check on the bench.
I have my shotgun.
Okay, 19.
He's absolutely you you don't know where worms shit, right?
But you can swear he shat out of wherever that is and gives you all the money back. Okay, the back
I don't want any trouble. You guys are crazy. So now I have
$127 Thanks fellas
All right, let's get this over free Caleb into pickle Rick no, yeah that works automatically
Why
okay yeah so you're still has money he's just you're just pickle Rick for like I
think 10 minutes okay I pick up Caleb I put him in my back pocket and then I sit
down at the bar for a while okay yeah so you guys say that the bar he transforms
back into a giant demon with alien wear on his back in your pocket um I break
the whole my pocket and yeah I guess I was gonna make the executive decision you
guys walk back to see Sullivan the frog
and he says I heard what you guys did to
the uncle I and he looks at blowtosses I
heard what you did to the uncle but
thank you so much excuse me Sullivan I
also helped I look at the camera and I
say that's what I call uncle food cake
like and then I say like like angel food
cake after that yeah roll a performance check
Let's see how this goes.
- All right, that's a 10.
- Yeah, it's like okay.
It's like, you know, it's like,
have you ever seen the show "Community"?
- Yeah. - It's like a joke
that one of the--
- You act like Justin Long.
- Yeah, you act like Justin Long.
- Like that level of actor.
- Yeah, yeah.
(laughs)
Yeah.
- Fuck.
- Yeah, you're Justin Longing it.
It's pretty okay.
(laughs)
I'll take that, good enough for me.
Yeah, just in longing it though is when you when you get blown by a man to see if he's
read on a kayak.
That's getting your Justin longed, that's what that is folks.
So anyway, yeah the frog talks to you, he says yeah that was uh yeah I'm pretty impressed
with you with all of you I'll help you out now.
And he sort of, he takes a, he grabs one of your cyber maps and he says, "Now look over
here.
See, there's a tunnel over here.
Now not a lot of people know about it, but if you go through there and you follow this,"
he like sort of points at like a place on the cyber map.
He says, "If you follow this, you'll be able to come topside without anybody really noticing.
The only thing is, this is the posters underground.
There's a lot of freaks there so you're just gonna have to be careful.
Uh-oh.
Oh fuck, okay, alright.
Here's a- here's a- I'm scared as shit.
Yeah.
Okay, Patrick's scared as shit, me, you know, cool-headed as ever.
I grab Sullivan by his lips and I say, "Alright, you funky little frog, you're coming with
us."
Time is running out.
Will our heroes be able to delete the Kramer video before the world's biggest computer finishes updating to Windows Fogel?
Find out next time on...
Gun City!
Operation Solution Dark Brain!
[Music]