You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
- Podcasts for the heartless.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(screaming)
(explosion)
- Bada bing, bada boom.
- YouTube.
- Oob.
- Yeah, no Caleb this episode.
- No Caleb.
Caleb fell into a hole and he's still falling.
- Yeah, he's been falling perpetually
for about like a week.
he's sucking off craps, he's eating poop.
He's doing all the, he's doing all that stuff.
He's doing all the things that you normally do.
He's moving into his new house that's made of hardened poop.
It's made of piss bricks.
It's like a, it's like an adobe house made of poop.
Yeah, it's a dookie.
A dookie house.
Yeah.
A dookie, dookie houser.
That's where he's living.
Yeah, that's who, that's his roommate.
Yeah, that's who that's his roommate
Dookie house or MD and the MD stands for my my dookie. Yeah, my doodoo. Yeah
Yeah, he said he spent he said he spent $300 on rugs, yeah, that's that's crazy
He spent three hundred dollars on rugs
He and I'm using him. He's using them as a blanket. Yeah, he's he's buying them just to keep them in the basement
a
them as toilet paper.
He's using, yeah, he's using rug squares as toilet paper, it's crazy.
Yeah.
Man, I fuckin', I've just been gaming so much, man.
Yeah, gaming Patrick.
Yeah, I got a P, my PC came in, I've been gaming just like a fuckin' madman.
What have you been playing?
I've been playing games.
Really?
No, I've been playing like, I played a lot of, I was playing Star Wars Battlefront before
this.
What other games have I been playing?
I have not been playing Blade Symphony.
Blade Simulator?
I don't know what Blade Symphony is, but I have it.
Blade Simulator.
That's where you take a picture of yourself and it gives you sunglasses and a trench coat.
It makes you a black vampire hunter, yeah.
It's like face app, but it only makes you look like Wesley Snipes in Blade.
It's face app, but it only shows you a picture of Wesley Snipes.
Doesn't even make you look like him.
Oh, we've been playing TF2.
Yeah we played TF2 last night.
Yeah, we played TF2 last night.
I have not played that game since I was in like community college.
It's still like a perfect game I feel.
Yeah it's very-
Like not like perfect but it's like one of the best games to just like-
Just fuck around.
Yeah.
The problem with it though is now there's like any server you join there's something
weird happening.
Oh there's like a billion bots.
In every server there's a- yeah there's at least one like really weird thing that makes
it impossible to play the game the way you want to.
Like-
Yeah there was like an aimbot last night that was saying the n-word and just like standing
in the middle of the map.
Yeah, there was, there was like this, there was this kid and this adult who were just having
a conversation in voice chat.
And then I asked, "Are you guys father and son?"
And simultaneously they said yes and no.
One of them said yes and one of them said no.
That game's the best.
Yeah, dude, you get, it's like the, it's just like a melting pot of just like the weirdest
fucking people on earth.
It's like freaking New York City.
It's like Ellis Island combined with the Statue of Bibberty.
Statue of Mike Bibber- Bibby.
Mike Birbiglia.
Yeah, it's a statue of Mike Birbiglia.
No Mike Birbiglia, it's a different guy.
They're gonna put that, they're gonna have Mike Birbiglia replace the Statue of Liberty.
He's gonna be like, "Hey guys!
I got...
I'm bringing you to freedom!"
Yeah, dude.
They're changing the freaking name to New Dork City.
Yeah, 'cause he's there.
Yeah, 'cause he's the new statue.
He's the statue and he's the fucking dork ass bitch.
And New Dork City, they also have Adam Ellis Island.
Who's Adam Ellis?
Adam Ellis is the guy who makes those comics that are like, "Shh, let people enjoy things."
uh...
at a map of south lincoln yeah
but that's a little bit of all the
the immigrants come to adam else island
and he turns them away because he's like let the americans to america
yet
you supposed to enjoy your country and then i got a dislike well no no hold on
i'm not racist for that
uh...
yeah what i mean
no
what are you saying
now what do you say in
my back i was missing my back hurts why you've been going to the union
yet what the first you talking some i set up for a got my desk yeah you said
on a whole new here
happens sitting on the floor and the plane
you're saying that is that you're sitting on a chair that was in those in
the trash outside and playing through the window
yes playing in the alley and uh...
guy kept throwing up on my ass
did i hate when that happens i think i'm not in the alley and i keep throwing up
on my uh...
it's the worst when a guy throws up on your ass in the alley
it's it sucks
you know we played left for dead also we'd were not only a name not yet and i
kept dying
we played while we play warzone began to
uh...
the rise yet diaper clan baby
on the reclaimed and we have anyone can join uh... if we approve
hats uh... first warzone game where he got he was driving a car and he kept
switching out of the seat i don't have a good friend of ours and then he did
really crash into a bigger car and exploded
the at the
I wish I was playing with like a full squad and just fucked that up for everyone.
That would have been awesome.
But yeah, that was fun.
Yeah.
Really, really haven't been doing much in general.
We gotta get you a PC.
We gotta get you a...
Yeah, I gotta get a job is the thing.
Yeah, that's the other thing.
I fuckin' I bought uh two nights ago I bought Cameron a copy of Star Wars Battlefront 2
the 2005 one and uh we I didn't I didn't check if it was like a cross plat game like a not
like cross platform but like a
I mean it's not for Mac
Yeah it's not optimized for Mac
I only got a Macbook he messed up he wasted fuckin' twenty dollars on me
No it was only ten bucks
Oh alright I don't feel bad anymore now
Yeah, you bought me a Minecraft account after I bought the wrong Minecraft.
I forgot I did that.
Now I...
Dude, why...
He's buying games without checking anything about them.
Why is there a specific Minecraft thing that works with their fucking server?
There's like a bunch of different...
There's also like...
Because you can get Minecraft on like Switch or something and that also doesn't work with
like other types of Minecraft.
There's like five types of Minecraft that only work with each other.
It's fucked up.
That's so fucking stupid.
Just make all of them work together.
Yeah.
Nazi, you fucking Nazi bitch.
I'm gonna get out in the streets and I'm gonna protest for that.
I'm gonna say.
Oh yeah.
I'm gonna get all the-
Yeah, I'm gonna add that onto the- I'm gonna get into the congress and I'm gonna tack onto
the end of the police defunding bill.
I'm gonna put in a little thing at the end that says also all the Minecraft virgins have
to work together.
Uh huh.
to
you know the animon the skeleton yet i have a firewood my bill
my executive order when i'm president everyone gets a phone pickaxe
phone diamonds picket yeah working and we're giving everyone a chest or filling
it with diamonds
yeah for a mine
mind right like a diamond
and then at the bottom of the minecraft bill right there's an asterisk ok and
it's a defund the police it's as black lives matter
and then legally they do
and legally yet
and then we see a little child the problem we sell all the problems in the
country because everyone has a phone pickaxe and
uh... to copter defunded and racism is over
you know on
you know those people who are like uh... we're like man everyone just needs to do
some psychedelics and change their perspective on things and they'll
understand there'll be no more hate in the world
yet to want to be that guy but for playing minecraft i think that when you
play minecraft
there is a uh...
there's a thing that snaps in your brain there's a thing that changes in your brain
fundamentally there's a switch that goes from cruelty to love
alright
it's like when you play minecraft and you build
you so
caleb right let's take the example of caleb okay yeah caleb usually is very
violent virulent racist
horrible man before but that was before
he built he went in the micro survey built a wooden tower that was just a bunch of
wooden blocks that went all the way up to the sky level right
that agree for comes in and burned down his tower
and now
caleb is gay
it changes it changed switches
your brain
hate to love
when you when you're something you build and spend time on gets destroyed
there's something in your mind that just
activates
right and let's see the world in a different way
it's true it's for you you you play as uh...
you download the current frog with the infinity gauntlet skin
and you get into that game
download minecraft
put on a skin of a of a guy who's a different race from you and you'll
understand the experience
of a different person in america
yeah
that's how we're gonna solve this
that that is how we solve every
every race-related problem in this country
yet we
we put we put the cops through a six-week
minecraft intensive
yeah of course okay wait here's our new bill
the new minecraft bill is we're giving
we're giving every police department a billion more dollars to buy
to buy computers and minecraft for everyone on the force
and trust you'll buy it and make a difference
joe biden is just announced he's buying six hundred alienware or as for the
boston police department
it's the but the
yet cops can carry guns anymore now they just carry
they carry wooden swords
they carry a pity carry the phone pickaxe the carrier the uh... x
they have all the uh... the look
There are some creepers in the police force, okay?
(laughing)
I'm just gonna say it.
There's some creepers in the police force,
and we need to,
shut up.
We need to make them explode.
- Yeah.
We need to shoot them with a bow and arrow.
- Yeah, we need to get, we need to feed them our chickens,
we need to feed them our pigs,
and we need to uh... just mine so much obsidian
so we can make another portal
that's what the people in the autonomous zone people understand
the importance of minecraft. They're trying to create another portal. They're trying to farm, they're trying to make another portal.
because you see if you go through the nether portal you can collect glowstone
dust and you can craft that into glowstone and you know what that means?
that's light you don't even need electricity for, okay?
fuck dude
and that pretty much solves the energy crisis for their attitude they're trying
to do some nicole tesla uh... and you know the rack you know that stuff burns
infinitely that bird that's the only one stop meowing again
all this uh...
yet another act as a stop
doesn't ever stop burning so that's pretty much
perpetual motion machine room
what whatever
He's just... He was sitting in the bathroom on the sink and just meowing.
Was he looking in the mirror?
No, no he was looking at the door. He was waiting for me to come get him.
Oh that's sweet.
But I was saying right, the netherrack it burns infinitely. So that's pretty much a perpetual motion machine or something.
Okay. So we get netherrack and we um...
We get all the netherrack...
that generate the fire okay then infinite fire from another act we use that too
power steam powered computers
for everyone in the world to play mine so
date they are a built-in car that runs on another act but
the government doesn't want you to know that like
it doesn't want you to
to build a car based on the other act
date that's why they put regulations on their portals that's why you're not
allowed to build a portals in city limits
I heard that Donald Trump is going to be enforcing more restrictions on nether portals.
I heard that's the platform he's running on.
Dude, that's dangerous.
The people want nether portals.
Exactly.
You can't strip people of the things that they need, like nether portals and the eye
of the spider.
uh...
yet
for not going to rest until we build in chairman tables for everybody in the
city
yeah i'm starting a new mutual aid fund and you can donate you can donate
uh... wooden planks so i can build crafting benches for everybody
*laughing*
super cheap. No it was like 30 bucks. Damn dude, you're stupid as hell. I know, I feel
dumb. Nah, to be fair that, I wouldn't have known that either unless somebody in the discord
told me. Yeah no one explained it, no one in the discord, so this is on the discord.
Well no they did explain it but that was like months ago, that was like in March when everyone
started playing Minecraft in the discord. So what they need to do is, they need to give
me
right now? Is he back in the bathroom? He's back in the bathroom. He's sitting on the sink just
fucking meowing at me. Oh he clearly wants you to go to the bathroom. You guys clearly have a routine.
Maybe he's thirsty. Hold on. All right. Patrick has to go and uh go to the bathroom in front of
his cat because that's a that's a thing he does every day. The cat's meowing in the bathroom
waiting for him because he knows unless Patrick drops a big brown wet load into the toilet he's
not gonna stop meowing. So Pat has to go do that really quick. Yeah, I don't know what
to talk about. I guess we shouldn't have dead air here. Maybe I'll just edit it out. Probably
not. I've been playing a bunch of Binding of Isaac. That's a fun game. All the stuff
I have left to unlock though is really hard. It's annoying.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
What was it?
You just needed to poop in front of your cat and he stopped?
No, he was thirsty.
Yeah, for your pee pee out of the toilet?
No, he was not thirsty for my pee pee out of the toilet.
Why are you so defensive?
Sounds like I may have hit a nerve here.
He was not drinking out of the toilet.
If he was drinking out of the toilet, it would have solved-
He wasn't drinking out of the toilet because there was no pee in it.
It would have solved this problem.
No, he would not drink out of the toilet if there was pee in it.
That's the only way he would drink out of the toilet and he would only drink out of it if
it was your pee in it.
No.
If I came to your house and I went pee in the toilet, your cat would not drink out of
it.
He would probably drink it because he's stupid.
But he would drink your pee, not mine.
He would drink anyone's pee.
He would drink your pee because he's used to drinking it because that's what you give
him to drink.
I do not give him pee to drink.
You absolutely do.
I've seen you do it on multiple occasions.
I have not done it.
I have not done that.
You give him pee to drink and you pee in the toilet and then you grab him and you overhand
throw him into the toilet. You drink Peter's juice. That's what you do. Why are you putting
a mask on? What are you doing? Stop. Just chilling. Yeah we're just chilling today. This is our
just chilling episode. Yeah, Caleb's not here. He's kind of the dad of the show. Cameron's
the mom. I'm not the mom of the show. Cameron's the mom of the show. I'm the silent child.
You're the silent mom. I'm the silent child. Moms are not silent. You're the silent mom.
That is ridiculous because have you ever heard of a silent mom? I don't think that's possible.
You are the silent mom. No, I'm the silent child. And you, you my friend, are the closet
monster of the family. I'm not the closet monster. You're the closet monster of the family, dude.
You're the silent mom, I'm the bad boy son, I'm the black sheep of the family, and Caleb
is the dad who sits at home and he shits and he drinks Milwaukee's Best.
I'm the silent child of the podcast.
You are not.
You are not the silent child.
I'm the silent child, that means I don't talk and I'm cool.
I don't talk because I'm cool.
I'm too cool to talk.
You're the silent child because you sit there and you, um, fucking, you sit there and you
do, um, you plan stuff.
You plan dark things.
I don't plan- okay, well yes, I do plan dark things.
You plan to make people have dark experiences.
I plan to bring people into my dark system and process them throughout its entire extent.
Cameron's dark system.
You do not want to be a victim of my system, alright?
I'll tell you that right now.
There's about a thousand steps and all of them are fraught with pain, okay?
They're gonna be dark, they're gonna be dehumanizing, they're gonna be barbaric and vicious, alright?
See, this is, these are the kind of things- And there is a lot of paperwork involved in
the system.
Yeah, so that's what I was trying to say is that these are the kind of things that a freak
would, a freak child would do.
I'm the freaky silent child.
I'm the silent freak.
You're a silent freak.
I'm always, I've got a slight wry sardonic smile on my face because I'm always calculating the most suffering that I can put people through.
I'm looking at people's faces and I'm analyzing the light behind their eyes and how I can best target their deepest fears and anxieties
with a special tailored system of my own design called the Dark System.
Cameron's Dark System is uh...
It's called the Dark System, okay?
It doesn't have my name in it so it can't be traced back to me.
It has your name all over it.
No, it has your name all over it because I'm writing your name on all the paperwork because
you're the next one getting processed through the system, my friend.
I'm going to put you on a giant conveyor belt, okay?
And it's going to have hot dogs on strings and they're descending, they're coming down,
they're going right towards your mouth, and then at the last second it pulls back up.
That's the first step of my dark system that I've designed for you.
The second step is I'm going to come into your house and I'm going to pee on your computer
keyboard and it's going to electrocute you because you're going to be using the keyboard.
How would it electrocute me?
Because my system, I've designed it to redirect the electricity.
I've wired your entire apartment.
Your system is flawed.
There's not a single flaw in my system.
It's airtight.
It's foolproof.
The electricity would travel up your pee stream.
It would travel up your pee stream.
No, okay, well there's where you're wrong because I have a non-conductive penis.
You have a conductive penis.
I had a wood casing constructed for it, okay?
So it's not, that wouldn't happen.
And it's for exactly that reason.
It would happen.
You would actually, it would set your penis on fire because the electricity would go up
and it would shock it.
Okay, but around the wood it's covered in ice.
Which is non-flammable.
It would melt the ice.
It can't, it's permafrost.
It's not.
Yeah, it's permafrost actually. Jack Frost actually put it on there.
Yeah, Jack Frost constructed my penis.
I got it commissioned by Jack Frost.
I went to his Etsy page and I asked him, "Hey, I need a penis for my dark system."
Yeah, I need a...
Hey, okay, so here's the deal, right? I have this wooden penis so I can pee on Pat's keyboard without it electrocuting me,
But I need some kind of ice casing around it so that it doesn't catch on fire.
One Patrick.
And will this work with my system?
Yeah.
Is this system compliant?
Is this compatible with my dark system?
Yeah, dude, I got the first one installed and it wasn't compatible so I had to melt
it off and try again.
It was fucked up, dude.
in terms of my dark system.
Just going into Best Buy.
[Laughter]
Yeah, I'm really liking this TV, but I'm just wondering if it would be possible...
Do you think this would interact well with my dark system, or should I choose another one?
[Laughter]
Oh, it connects to my dark system via Bluetooth. Okay.
Oh, alright. Okay, that's good.
Yeah, they try to show you which washer/dryer to get and you say, "Oh, see, this is really
nice but I do actually have a dark system I've been following, so I'm going to have to look
at a different option."
What is it?
Is that a Maytag?
Ooh, yeah, no, something about the parts in that, they don't, they're not compliant with
the dark system.
Yeah, do you have one that has blades on the inside?
Do you have one that's a portal to hell?
I'm really looking for a gothic style washer and dryer.
I'd like one that's made out of cobblestone, okay?
And it's got a flying buttress on the top.
And a stained glass window so I can look in on my clothes.
A stained glass window on your...
Okay, yeah, I need a gothic washing machine for my capes.
I have a gothic washing machine with a stained glass portrait of Christopher Lee on the front
and I only use it for my capes.
I only use it for my capes and my frilly...
I use a special red tide and I only use it for my frilly shirts and my capes.
The tide pod looks like an eyeball.
Yeah.
Do you have a washing machine that's filled with worms and soil?
I need to wash my bones.
I need to wash and dry my bones.
Yeah I got a Maytag, it's the Maytag Gothic line.
Yeah, it's...
The Maytag Dark System.
Yeah, the new Dark Appliances line.
Dark Appliance!
(laughter)
The Maytag Dark Appliance is lying.
They have a dishwasher that only works for goblets and chalices and grails.
Oh, what the fuck? I put my Tupperware in this and it fucking melted it.
Oh yeah, no no no, you had it on the chalice setting. That's why.
(laughter)
Yeah, no, that can happen.
yet this only washes cursed utensils
okay she had this is a
uh... what what uh... what setting what i used to watch on my my garments
yet my my court
yeah
yet so it's more
if i a if i put in my board
would i have to use the uh... chalice setting because it's there it's both
they're both gold
they have a hair dryer that only works on on on spider web hair on
kit and picture here
gothic or care
after what are other do what are other appliances and blanking on appliances
now
uh... it's a microwave but it's uh...
again it's got a stained glass door yet when you call the numbers are in roman
numerals and when you open it a billow of smoke comes out yeah with a scream
bats fly out of it regardless of what fucking thing is in there oh cool one of my one of my items just sold on the steam
marketplace damn this guy's selling items I sold a I sold a Emperor Palpatine
trading card that I got from playing Battlefront 2 for 17 cents.
Hey there, I was wondering, I really like all the appliances you have on display here, but
I was wondering if you guys are selling any dark items.
Yeah sure, come on down to the basement.
Come to the catacombs, the Best Buy catacombs.
The walls are made of skulls and bones.
They have just like a stalag whatever, which one's the one that goes up?
Stalagmite.
Stalagmite goes up, stalactite goes down.
They just have a stalactite that has a price check on it.
We have a wrought iron gaming PC.
And it runs on torture.
It runs on sulfur and pain.
Damn, dude I want to go to Dark Best Buy.
I want to see all the shit they have on display.
Yeah we have dark DVDs.
Yeah!
We have a couple of dark games too.
We only sell Dark Souls.
And Bloodborne.
Bloodborne and MediEvil.
For PS1.
We're the only Best Buy that still sells MediEvil for PS1.
And all the discs are made of human skin.
They're made of-
And they have that PS2 controller that's like got shaped like flesh.
Yeah, and it has a sword on the end.
There was a specific one like, I saw it at Best Buy once.
God, what was it?
Is it the-
Oh, here it is.
It's the uh, Philips Freaks Pad Fleshy for PS2.
That sounds like a sex toy.
I know dude, look at this fucking thing.
Philips Freaks.
Philips Freak Pad.
Oh my god.
That's disgusting.
Yeah dude, that thing's fucking insane.
That's horrible.
Why would you want to play a game with like a guy's head?
That's like that's like the Necronomicon in like Evil Dead where it's bound to the flesh, but that's the gaming version of it, dude
That's the millennial update
That's the millennial update for or the zoomer update for Evil Dead
You have to uh instead of like whatever like you do to it would you just read the Necronomicon?
Yeah, you play the game if you play the game you do that you enter the Konami code. Yeah
Summons demons yeah
God damn dude, that thing is so fucking crazy.
Yeah, I want one of those to be honest.
I want one just to hold it.
Yeah, just to hold it, just to feel what it feels like.
Yeah, because you know that thing's just terrible.
And you know what they made the joysticks out of.
They made the joystick out of nipples.
The joystick covering is nipples.
Absolutely.
So let's look at this guy's profile that we have.
This is from the Discord.
Hooch sent it.
Thank you, Hooch, from the Discord.
- Thank you, Hooch.
- Thanks, Hooch.
This is a, this is a top 10,
the top 10's username to Mewtwo_.
And it seems like kind of like this person is,
role-playing as Mewtwo,
but also there seems to be some like,
- Some dark experience.
some differences like like there's for example
one of the lists this person made his top ten issues with having psychic powers
it's like oh yeah that's me too
but then also one of them is best ways to avoid social media
which doesn't seem to have a good as much as much me too but uh...
yeah i was a dead giveaway right here top ten reasons why it's better to have
three st fingers instead of five
yet did meet his three fingers so cool i wanna hands like that
i think any any creature with the hand like that is is is a god i think has
some kind of god like power as aliens definitely have that
that's true
i want to read this person's um... you choose about section on the top of the
like their profile
feel free to comment and do other stuff on my list i try to create list slash
profile in a way about me it's complicated have fun
hobbies
planning
hiding
things i hate
pokey balls
humans most of the time
master balls team rocket
and they believe you hates me you
yet as much as a clone of new
or does need to have you
i don't know i don't think they hate each other
was that
the
i opened up uh...
i opened up you choose you to channel
what was it
is uh... he makes a lot of uh... source filmmaker stuff
on nice that is what you know this is
this is uh... mario versus real mario
that's loud you can with definitely on review to was real me too would use
inside the cap what are you doing stuff i'm watching i'm watching some mario
versus real mario if you choose real and real life you would use a psychic powers
to manipulate people as if they were source filmmaker
you would make them make those faces
they would make them say putis putis putis putis
you'd say grabbin pills
pills here, pills here, got pills here, grabbin pills
uh...
all right so let's look at best ways to avoid social media, yeah i am curious about
if this is going to be
mewtwo themed, yeah i want to know what mewtwo thinks, all right so the description of this
list is, social media seems to have the power to persuade things.
This does seem, the first one seems kind of Mewtwo adjacent.
Yeah, if I remember correctly about Mewtwo, he lived in a, oh sorry.
Number one is go live in a cave with no power. And the comment is only for Mewtwo and it
says it is very relevant for me. And if I remember correctly, Mewtwo lived in a castle
where he invited all of the Pokemon trainers to.
Oh my god, I forgot about that. That was so cool. And he made the combination ones?
Uh huh. Yeah, he did that. I don't remember him living in a cave.
I think he runs away from the lab and then goes to a cave.
Oh wait, I think he goes to a cave in Detective Pikachu.
Does he?
So maybe they're going off of Detective Pikachu rules here.
In Detective Pikachu he, I don't even remember.
I was so high when I watched that movie.
I watched that on a plane.
I watched that on the plane going to LA.
I watched that on a bunch of edibles in the theater and on the scene where the mountain
started moving I got really scared.
Damn, I would never get scared by Mewtwo's power.
That wasn't Mewtwo, that was Torterra.
But nice try.
Nice try, pal.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right.
Yeah, nice try, pal.
Torterra.
Um, yeah, well, they gave you Torterra's dark experience.
Yeah, that is, that was kind of my basis for creating the dark system, was the experience
of getting scared in a movie theater.
I don't think I've ever gone to a movie theater without being scared.
I think something scares me every time I'm in there.
It's probably because of all the shootings.
Well yeah, that is mostly what I'm thinking of.
But then also sometimes there's something scary in a movie, you know?
Yeah, sometimes there's like a clown.
Yeah, like I was watching Birds of Prey, Harley Quinn's Adventures, and they've got a hyena
in that movie.
And tell me that isn't freaking scary.
What?!
That was the last movie I saw in a theater.
Probably all ever seen in a theater.
Yeah, that's the last movie a lot of people saw in a theater, huh?
Yeah.
Wasn't, uh, wasn't very good.
You know what?
The only, the only, um, saving grace, I guess, of COVID is probably, uh, that they're gonna
make movie theater seats, uh, a bit more spaced out.
Yeah.
That, that is a big, uh, and I know if Caleb was here, he'd be like, "Oh, because you're
so fat, blah, blah, blah."
Yeah, but I won't do that to you.
I won't say that about you.
No, I'm just, but uh, it's uh...
No, it's cause you smell bad.
I hate sitting next to people.
It's cause you smell bad.
It's not because I smell bad.
No.
Yeah, it is weird to sit right next to people.
But you know...
I don't want to sit next to a stranger unless it's like at least a couple feet apart.
That's why Chunky's in Manchester, New Hampshire has an amazing...
Dude, I went there, dude.
I remember going there.
That place rocks.
Dude, you get food and a movie?
Yeah dude, that's sick.
I saw...
You get to eat at the theater?
I think I saw Harry Potter Order of the Phoenix, I think.
Yeah, dude, that's...
In that theater.
That's the best place to watch just like shitty blockbusters.
Yeah.
I hope they bring back...
I hope they bring back drive-ins because there's some around here but they're all like an hour
away from me.
Oh dude, they were gonna do that...
I don't know if they're still doing it but Kowloon might be doing that.
they might turn like the part of the uh... i heard that
that she would have a sick dude
did we should go
get the problem bladder
yeah and in a car eat like
approval bladder get hot mustard all over the car for care
the
uh...
uh... shit
i can see what they are not just a sense that i was a little over the
inside of the windshield
just cut a bit of refund
i still have mustard
and i couldn't see what happened in the movie
the problem with driving this on they just most of the drive-ins that are open
right now are just showing like e_t_ in jurassic park over and over a like
this being like
shows his work
yeah that's what i'm saying
it's just a pretty important yeah i do
so you know
show me a blue while i'm eating a spare rib yeah
Show me a high heel cracking a testicle in half like an egg.
Alright?
I don't know if I...
I'm not gonna give my business to your drive-in theater.
No.
Unless it's a drive-in...
God, could you imagine the smell of a drive-in porno theater?
Yeah, they do it in Smell-O-Vision.
vision.
No, just like the smell of guys jacking off in their car just for like miles and you have
to give them their food.
You're the waiter at the drive-in porn theater.
Yeah man, but they should do smell-o-vision also.
They should.
Yeah, I want to smell the pain.
i want to smell the pain and fear rolling off of that poor man
getting his entire getting his entire downstairs system rearranged and rerouted
by a stiletto
alright i wanna smell the sweat
and the tears
uh... alright
he's getting it renovated down there dude
i've got a couple bags of uh... popcorn here i got a hot dog and uh...
with one on them for some reason
here in your car
uh... jacking off into a condom
next to a bunch of other guys who are doing the same thing
then they're like okay guys you can't
jack off in your car that's illegal and then they there's just a huge line
everyone in in their cars is in line for the outhouse
the
car like that like this trick out how so it's not like a whole in it yes like a
whole it's a quick the moon
and they're watching shrek
k
it's called a driver is the shrek is driving to their own carriages driving
for no theater but they can't
one, play pornos there, and two,
uh... you can't jack off there, so all they do is show Shrek over and over again
and let people jack off in an outhouse. Yeah, this is the only movie we could get the rights to, actually.
Yeah.
They're just, they're showing just, um, just a public domain, like...
They're showing the kid...
They're showing like every Charlie Chaplin movie.
Yeah.
But the smell-o-vision system is fucked up so it's still giving the smell of cock and
ball torture.
Alright, number two.
I want to look at the other mutual lists.
This list is boring.
How is this one boring?
Top ten.
Okay, listen.
This one's great.
Top ten issues with having psychic powers.
Okay?
Okay.
someone's mind and he has thing about porn.
The only comment is from Mewtwo and says
"A image can't get out of my mind."
Damn, that's true though. That's why Mewtwo is so dark and brooding.
The description for this list is "The powers can be used for slot of task,
but sometimes can mess with your normal day life."
(laughs)
You might destroy/kill something with your mind.
It's even worse if there are humans or cops around you.
Mewtwo doesn't want to kill cops.
Mewtwo did not say no cops at pride.
Yeah, Mewtwo said cops rights.
Mewtwo said more cops at pride.
Yeah, Mewtwo said only cops at pride.
Number three, you might think something out loud
and everyone can hear it.
i don't think you have to be psychic to do that. Yeah, you don't have to be psychic to do that at all.
Patrick does that all the time.
That's true.
Yeah, Patrick is standing in 7-Eleven and he's thinking, he's just saying
ketchup mustard ketchup mustard ketchup mustard.
Little bit of relish.
Ketchup mustard. No, you're just doing that walking around town.
ketchup mustard ketchup every step
uh... number twelve you may use telekinesis accidentally killing someone
or yourself
can you imagine accidentally killing yourself with telekinesis
that would be sick are you kidding me
all i'm saying is that would be a big waste of telekinesis
yeah that would be what i mean you could telekinetically transfer your telekinesis
to your kid or something
You can't do that. That's against the law. That's against the rules of telekinesis.
You can do that if you're omega level.
Nobody's reached that level yet.
I have.
Top 10 reasons why sleeping in a test tube is a good idea.
Number one, you can't get diseases while you're sleeping, unless it's a very dirty test tube.
That's true, dude. I want to get into it. I want to sleep in a test tube. Get down.
Number two, bugs can't infect you. They won't even be able to get in.
Dude, yeah, this is making sleeping in a test tube sound pretty good.
Oh my god, dude, I want to sleep in a test tube right now.
Yeah, dude, give me just a pillow and I'm good to sleep in a test tube.
Number three, it will give you good nutrition.
Most test tubes can do this big all.
Number four, it's more comforting.
Feels like sleeping on a cloud.
Hope test tube be a good idea.
worth it if it wasn't a good idea.
From Boris Rule.
You can't hear anything while in it, like noises that wake you up at night or just plain obnoxious
things.
Yeah, like my mom telling me to do my homework.
Yeah, like my mom telling me, "Where'd you get this gigantic test tube?
Can you please take it out of our house?"
God, you threw away my couch to put a test tube to sleep in in the living room?
You cleared out the entire living room to put in a giant test tube
Number six you can take a bath in it
Good for being lazy imagine if you could take a bath in your bed. Oh my god a waterbed
That's why people like the waterbed so much
Yeah, it's good. You can go into the bed to take a bath
You pop a hole in that thing in the morning you wake up in the bath. Yeah
Imagine yeah, you have a valve on the top and you can climb inside and take a bath and then climb out and close the
valve and go to sleep
Just the water inside the water bed is getting browner and browner
more
Taking a bath every day inside your bed. The best part is you don't need to change the water it purifies itself
Yeah sleep
exactly
He's coming for you. Look at it. Oh, man, the cats trying to get me through the camera. Yeah
No, no look at I'm gonna get you
He looks like me too, dude. No, he doesn't he looks like me. Oh, yeah, he does. He looks more like me
He looks like a muse cousin
Number seven it looks way cooler
It does indeed. Yeah, it does indeed
That's the top comment here. Well, it does it does look pretty cool. I have to say. Oh, yeah, dude the fucking the back to tank from
Star Wars episode 5 where he's like in that giant diaper
You know sleeping a big ass diaper no who's in it Luke Luke is in the tube and
Then he swims up. I don't remember that you don't remember that. Oh, dude. I've always wanted to I
Was one of those movies that I think tube I was wanted it when I saw that as a kid
I was like why don't I just sleep in a big tube like that? Yeah, I'd be so cool
But then I realized it wouldn't be filled with Bacta because we don't have Bacta.
No, we do.
We just have been hiding it from you.
What if Bacta is just like the galactic basic word for like water though?
It could be.
Yeah.
Um.
Yeah, if they just had Luke in a giant diaper and a mask on.
And they were like poking him with like needles and shit.
Yeah.
I mean, every person who is in a test tube somehow has powers.
That's true.
Okay, let's- Every person in a test tube.
Sephiroth?
Sephiroth.
The shape of water fish.
That guy's powers to be a fish.
Yeah.
He has the power to gut Michael Shannon.
Milla Jovovich is in a test tube in Resident Evil 2 in the movie.
Luke Skywalker, we already said that.
Starship Troopers?
Darth Vader goes into a test tube.
Yeah.
Sometimes.
Mewtwo goes into a test tube.
Yeah.
I think Darth Vader is kind of like Mewtwo and Mew is kind of like Luke Skywalker.
I think that's what they based it on.
I think that's what they based Star Wars on.
I think they based a lot of Greek myths on that too.
Yeah.
Yeah and they based um, that's where they got all the uh, that's where they got all the racial
caricatures in, in.
Yeah that's where they got Wada.
In Star Wars, yeah they got him from Mr. Mime.
Yeah.
*laughs*
No, that's, that's the French character, Mr. Mime.
Yeah.
That's where they got all their French uh, are there any French, like fake French people
in Star Wars?
Cause they have pretty much, like I guess the Irish are like the, the Wookies.
Yeah.
And the Iwa, now the Wookies are Scottish.
And then obviously the Gunray.
I don't know what the Gunray is.
I'm not going to get into that.
They're the Japanese stereotype from Phantom Menace.
So they just based those on Pokemon in general.
What other... because they only did because they had Jar Jar Binks was pretty...
What was he, like a mammy?
What's that stereotype?
Dude, wait.
Oh my god, wait.
Jar Jar Binks?
Jinx?
Whoa!
Think about it.
My theory is they based the Star Wars racist things on the Pokemon racist things.
There's a Pokemon that's just a big nose and I was like, oh...
grow up and then it evolves into a new
he even more expensive booking big no
yeah i think i think i would like a lot of things under it and they don't look
like ralph remarks yeah man
did they're the best
uh...
number eight on this list i want to get to this because it that last one's
really good
uh... number eight on this list as you can use it as your coffin if you die that
is
it's true
sounds like you can't you do but yeah
being born in a tube and dying in a tube
born in the tube, dying in the tube baby
that's my next tattoo, i'm gonna get that on my forehead
get it across your back
i'm gonna get it on my lower back like a tramp stamp
in varsity letters
imagine getting like a
a font tattooed on you
just every, like the alphabet in a font
the quick for just like that yet the quick brown fox yet jumped over the
lazy dog
dissident and in your favorite font
a car and a coffin is kinda like a dark a bit
you think about it
that's true
of shit yet
that's another that's another dark appliance yeah
a bit is an appliance
it's been a point it's
because it's like a sleep
It's like a sleep number coffin.
Yeah.
A Tempur-Pedic coffin.
That'd be tight.
Yeah.
Oh no, did my chair just squeak on mic?
I think so.
You trying to get it to squeak again to prove it wasn't a fart?
Yep.
Number 9, it can give you oxygen.
That's if you can't breath well.
Yeah, I can't breathe well so I'm going to go into this sealed tube and I'll be able to
breathe better.
That'll solve all my breathing problems.
Yeah, I'm actually in this test tube because I can't breathe.
It's basically just a test tube is just one big inhaler.
Yeah, pretty much.
A dark inhaler, okay.
But it's a...
Oh, okay.
Press down the button, it shoots out a cloud of bats.
(laughing)
- You just inhale a bat?
- Like you know when bats fly,
a bunch of bats fly out of a cave really gothically?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it's like that, but out of the inhaler.
- Very gothically.
- And it's called an impaler, like vlash.
- Oh, 'cause it impales you with a bat.
- It impales you with a bat,
like a bat out of hell, meatloaf.
- Yep.
- Yeah, meatloaf is-- - Impales you.
Meatloaf is the store, is the sales associate in Dark Best Buy.
And he's always singing.
He's always doing his theater kid songs.
"Oh, woman!"
He's also, he's also, he's dressed as his character from Fight Club.
Yeah, he's dressed up like Robert Paulson.
Which I feel like that would be the guy that works at Dark Best Buy.
That would be the guy that's like, "I want to work at Dark Best Buy."
He's just a guy who's wearing slacks.
He looks exactly like Meatloaf.
Oh, it's a TV but it has ancient jail bars over the screen?
Dude, sign me up, I want to sell that!
Yeah so this is like, this is like, just kind of something, we bottled most of this stuff
after the curse of the black pearl
it's a blender but at the bottom of it the blades are like flails like on a chain
yeah
dude I'm going to be thinking of dark best buy for probably at least a week
yeah dude like a food processor
a food processor but it's got like uh...
it's just a guillotine that moves really fast.
yeah uh... but number ten on uh...
on why sleeping in a test tube is a good idea
is you can use it to produce babies
the comment on yours says a good place for a babies to be born in
that's
facts dude
dude that's mewtwo spitting straight facts about babies
mewtwo knows what
what's up about babies
yet he knows that he knows the deal with babies right he knows what's going on
you choose me to dark deal
and now
he's making babies
which is dark deal which is dark mutus dark bargain
i made a deal with me to to get psychic powers and i have to sleep and have
babies in a test tube
this is a sexy when they make me
uh... we sleep in a tube
that the no never mind what they'd make you
within the making you to into a guy in the movie detective p_q_ they gave him
a lot of our member
yet again are and then like
they made a disabled guy into the issue that's like the whole
legal disabled i guess we're going to do i don't remember that part but i do
remember the armors sick as hell
cyber army did they use his ex-war
the uh... his ex form
you know and make them a good i think i mean i haven't seen anything pokey mon
related became out since mega evolution i mean i think
i don't know
they'd be a little in
uh...
you too
they made a little they made a little in patrick
do they made it a little bit of patrick your flight like i don't know
it's like a truck this uh... looks different
in the lower
uh... they just gave me the baby rainbow
Yeah.
They made a lowland Mewtwo and all they did was put a lei around his neck.
That's cool.
That would be, that would actually be cool.
Yeah, with a little, with a hula skirt on.
Yeah, Mewtwo in a hula skirt and he's got a lei on.
And he's got coconuts on his boobs cause he's got real big boobs.
Yeah, he does dude.
He, um, he's got that rack.
I hope they make a Jamaican region because I want to see the forms they come up with for
that one.
Yeah, they already made, I mean, there's not really anywhere else for them to go.
You know?
They've done everything else.
Yeah, pretty much.
I mean there's some of them that I feel like, like maybe Australian.
Maybe they could do an Australian Pokemon.
Yeah.
I think they should, I'm holding out for Jamaica.
Alright I want an Oddish with a weed leaf on its head.
- Yeah.
- That's what I'm talking, I want rated R weed version.
- Who?
- Rated R weed version of Pokemon, okay?
- Oh, I thought you were saying
there was a Pokemon named Radar.
- No, that's a, you're thinking of a system
for locating things nearby.
Is what you're thinking of.
I'm thinking of Big Bird's teddy bear.
Big Bird's teddy bear is named Radar?
I think so.
That's a really lame name for a teddy bear.
Yeah, hold on.
Sounds like Big Bird's kind of more like Big Nerd to me.
If he's going to name it after a freaking Radar.
Hey!
Okay.
Ayo!
Whoa!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, what?
It's named Radar?
His name is Radar.
Top 10 Best Weapons to Destroy the Human Race
Death Star Cannon
Psychic Storm
Earthquake Machine
The comment for Earthquake Machine is "It will shack the earth to nothing."
Water Machine
The top comment on the Water Machine is "This list is pretty cool.
We can kill Bieber.
Sar Bomba.
What is Sar Bomba?
Sar Bomba is a giant bomb.
It's like a mother of all bomb type thing I think.
Oh ok.
I thought it was just a thing.
Ok.
Planet Buster.
Number 12, Planet Buster.
I mean it says it in the name.
It'll destroy the planet like Thanos snapping his finger.
That's a comment from Pickle Man.
Pickle Man.
I'm just looking through all these other lists, I'm seeing if there's anything else good.
I don't think an Ion Cannon would destroy the world, I think it would just set off an
EMP blast.
Top 10 reasons why it's better to have 3 fingers instead of 5.
The other 2 fingers are useless to have.
Your appearance looks better.
It's much better to eat with.
The other 2 fingers won't get in your way when working.
It makes it easier to grip your opponents.
you'll be better at playing guitar, it makes typing more challenging.
The comment on "you'll be better at playing guitar" just says, "Most humans who do guitar
don't use their five fingers."
Number nine is, "You can use your three finger issue as an excuse.
You can say you don't have to learn how to type because you only have three fingers.
example of what abilities you don't have to learn.
Yeah I want three fingers to be lazy.
I want three fingers so I don't have to go to computer class anymore.
Number ten is you don't have to worry about cutting off the other two fingers.
But imagine cutting off like your thumb when you only have like three Mewtwo fingers and
then you only have two Mewtwos on your hand.
to mute you oh boy I'm fucking my back hurts I'm hungover yeah it's time to
it's time for me to you're gonna need a bunch of tums you're a bunch of tums
nice man um yeah I guess we can I guess we can finish it up yeah for an hour
hour
it up join the discord we play tf2 sometimes we've done it once I guess we
did it one time and I don't know if we're ever gonna do it again maybe we'll
stream or something I don't know yet to figure that out yeah we should probably
just stream probably stream in the discord that's probably send us lists to
do because we're lazy we don't like finding our own lists yeah we're
outsourcing it to you and you pay us yeah that's called the money maker
Make her mindset.
That is called the $100 mindset and you can only find that out if you subscribe to our
Patreon and read our guide to $100.
Yeah.
Alright.
Peace out.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Bye!