Oh my god, don't stop, don't stop, I'm almost there.
Woah, hey, who are you?
You're listening to Gun City Operation Solution Dark Brain Part 2.
If you haven't heard Part 1, go back and listen to it, you dumb, wet bitch.
I mean it, I'm telling you, turn this off right now, before I go psycho, before I go so psycho in your ass.
[Music]
So anyway, yeah the frog talks to you.
Yeah, I'm pretty impressed with all of you. I'll help you out now.
He grabs one of your cyber maps and he says, "Now look over here. There's a tunnel.
If you go through there, you'll be able to come topside without anybody really noticing.
The only thing is this is the posters underground. I'm scared as shit.
Yeah, Patrick's scared as shit. I grab Sullivan by his lips.
Alright you funky little frog, you're coming with us. What? Okay, can I just go pee first?
Absolutely not. Lead the way. Oh, jeez.
And yeah, so you, you sort of grab Sullivan, you tell him to lead the way. And so he does. He sort of scared walks you guys to the tunnel. Yeah, and you see it's just like huge like opening like squirreled away way in like the deep, deep, deep parts of the of Guns Titty.
a guy out there who outside of it just like one guy who's going
I know that noise. I know that is and
He's just sort of like like freaking all over the place and doing doing to worm and just like
He's doing the worm he's just like absolutely freaking out and Sullivan says well
This is it, but if you guys you know
You know a good luck. I guess in there I
Put Sullivan in my pocket
Okay, yeah, he just easily goes in there. He's so scared. I fed him a cracker
Terrified and it is like kind of like oh
They could kind of happy gets a cracker
It's a smile. It's an oyster cracker - it's not that big of a cracker
Thanks, man
You know us little guys got to stick together
It looks big in our hands because of how small we are. That's right
Yeah, he's like he's like kind of like oh one of those days
Carted around yes, you guys want to go into the the posters underground. Yeah, yeah, fuck it
Let's go and as we as we walk in Patrick looks really scared
He's turning white like a sheet, and I say I look at the camera, and I say man. He looks like he just saw a post
That's an automatic one.
(laughter)
So what does he say?
So the producers of the movie are crying because they just lost so much money on the movie.
Yeah, no, he says it perfectly, it's just such a dog shit line.
Yeah, it's just one of the worst things.
It might as well be a one.
walk towards that you pass by whoever this guy is going you just pass by him I
don't know and you enter into the posters underground so you know
underneath gun city is an abandoned tunnel right that's what this is it was
it's filled with freakers and bloodites you know anti-tech freakazoids the
scurriest scum this side of ebaum the habitable parts of it are known as the
posters underground a lawless criminal shit stain that some of the toughest
gunks and the slums won't go near. It used to be an underground railway system, the
last government-run project to exist in Gunn City, before Stakehams fully took
control and officially privatized democracy. Now the tunnel acts as a
makeshift sewer system after the previous one collapsed from all the
fucking shit inside of it. The brighter neons above ground become long, dim
streaks of lazy blue, coasting down the sides of the tunnel walls, flickering in
and out revealing the creepy creatures the nasty stinkers and lurk and do their
dirty deeds the creatures are one thing but the black depth oh that word is just
awful the black depth for my lisp of the posters underground means our heroes
can't see shit but Lord knows they'll be stepping in it so yeah you guys are here
it's it's you sort of here like drip drops you hear like a little like little
snickering from all these techno slime addicted weirdos. You thought the slums
were bad this is just like like not even the the mad suckler goes down here.
Okay I'm seeing all these all these freaks geeking off that freaky deaky
shit and it reminds me that I actually have a bit of a techno slime habit
myself and I need to recharge so I start I start puffing on that on that chiba.
Yeah, I'm I've been out of techno. Yeah, you know what wait wait wait hold on
Boys I had the most insane idea who wants to sash oh
Yeah, I'm ready to sash right now. I still have some of that good good I
Sullivan the frog is only 14 years old, but we're gonna let him smoke with the beer
We're gonna make you hit that techno bong till you fall sideways, you pussy bitch.
We're all 19 years old and we're letting a 14 year old smoke with us.
I'm 37.
In frog years.
Yeah, that's right.
Oh yeah, I forgot.
Yeah, you all take techno slimes.
So all of you roll a d20.
Okay.
Alright.
yeah i don't even need to recharge my points i'm just doing it because i like
it
i got it too
i also got a two
okay
so
alright this is where the uh...
folks at home this is where the techno slime addiction system comes in
uh... so
uh... on your first failure
so you guys all sort of inject that techno slime and then you also smoke it
uh... it's like a weird double way to take the drug
Blowtoss and Ray William Johnson, you only get half your points rounded down.
So you guys only recover two points.
And you're gonna have disadvantage on your dex rolls for the next in-game hour.
No!
Okay, okay, I pause for a minute and I say, "What's the 27 club?
We ain't making it past 21."
*laughter*
Yeah, you're like kinda woozy,
you're kinda out of it.
Um, uh,
Yoda, you take it like a fuckin' champ.
You've done so much more
in your time.
I'm a Tick Street.
Yeah, this is easy street for you.
But you two guys, you guys are gonna be pretty messed up.
What did, uh, what did
Sullivan the Frog get?
Oh yeah, let me see how he did.
he doesn't have any moves right? he'll die in one hit. he'll die from one hit of techno
slime? yeah no he's okay he's vomiting. I take him out of my pocket. I don't want him vomiting
in my pocket. It's like, "Oh God, oh geez, this reminds me of frog college." I pick out
the cracker from the throw up and I eat it. Okay, I set Sullivan between my horns. Okay,
yeah, he's sort of woosily in between your horns and just sort of like hanging in there.
uh... yeah what does it feel like the to get fucked up on time
on my god it's a rush like none other i can see numbers in my head
for me actually all it does is it gives me a book of her
it's all it's literally all of us it for me it feels like i got a brain freeze
but if my brain was hot instead of cold
okay to get a hot brain
uh... amazing okay cool that's that's that the effort for
uh... solve it's just makes him vomit a lot
and thinks a little bit more about his dad and how
he misses his dad
uh... yeah so you guys are yeah you guys are sort of walking through the tunnels
uh... following the uh... did you guys know that wizard of oz syncs up with the
pink floyd album
I just had to blow Sullivan's brain real quick.
Yeah, Sullivan is sort of just like, "Are you fucking kidding me?"
Yeah, man, dark side of the moon, check it out.
I'm serious.
Shut the fuck up.
There's no way.
No way.
I have a torrent of it already pre-synced.
Yo, so hit me with that shit.
You wanna watch it?
Hit me with that right now.
Absolutely.
We can watch it.
We spent an hour and a half.
It's like 10pm, you have till midnight.
You guys just take an hour and a half, watch Dark Side of the Moon.
We'll listen to Dark Side of the Moon and watch what it is.
It takes us 30 minutes to figure out how to sync it up.
The audio is already sucked up.
We spend 30 minutes trying to sync it up and then we give up.
We don't actually watch it.
I'll just listen on my iPod.
He has an iPod video.
He has the limited edition U2 iPod Touch.
And all the songs on it are Pink Floyd and U2.
It's money by Pink Floyd and all of U2's entire discography.
Yeah, he's just listening to that and vomiting whenever U2 comes on.
And, uh, yeah, so you guys reach sort of like a fork in the tunnels.
and Sullivan sort of like wakes up a little bit of a stupor and looks at the
sort of the cyber map he's like uh-huh he's sort of like fiddling with it and
he's like doesn't seem to be a clear direction on which one to take what oh
no this is your job Sullivan I know I know man oh god selling my fucking no
well Sullivan Sullivan what happened with your father well it's a long story but
how we have until midnight okay whatever just I'll tell you I'll write it down
you know right now and then I'll hand it to you later he starts writing it down
then he started like I was like but which direction do you think we should go what
What are the options?
What, yeah, what's on the left?
So you guys can do a few things, you guys can like, like also like do like, uh, investigation
or perception check, sort of see, investigate around.
Oh, I would, like, yeah.
Could I use, could I use Yoda's mind?
I wanna take, wait, yeah.
Whose mind do you wanna read?
Oh, okay, I thought I could use Yoda's mind to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to,
to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to, to,
I want to I want to take my I say hey Patrick
What and then I say no, I'm talking to my monkey named Patrick, which I forgot about until right now
Your monkey sucks. I say hey Patrick. Can you run down the tunnel on the left and check what's down there come back?
So the monkeys just starts to sort of run down the tunnel on the left he's chipping out yeah, he's chipping out
He's flipping out. He's checking his DMs. ApeChat's blowing up. He's sending selfies.
And he comes back to you and he sort of just like shrugs and he's like "Rawr, rawr, rawr."
Patrick.
Like he didn't really see anything down there.
Non-MonkeyPatrick, read his mind. Tell me what he's saying.
Okay.
Tell me what he's saying.
I'm reading his mind right now.
Okay.
He said that he went down.
Hold on.
[Laughter]
I like your style, man.
Hold on.
He's fast and loose like a cowboy.
Roll a D20.
Oh no, actually don't. I'll roll a Charisma Saving Throw actually.
I forgot I made all yours like that.
Okay. Let's see.
He's gonna...Monkey's not very charismatic.
Yeah, so you...
An exception among monkeys.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're able to read his mind perfectly.
And the monkey is thinking,
like banana banana banana banana banana banana banana banana I didn't see
anything down there banana banana banana but I thought maybe banana banana there
was some kind of guy banana banana banana some guy banana banana banana weird hair
weird hair weird head banana banana trying to find monkey what did his hair
look like so you infer but that's what he was thinking I imagine as soon as
Patrick uses his power everybody can hear yeah Patrick Yoda no Patrick is
Patrick is acting like a is translating yeah yeah yeah Patrick Yoda listens to
and he says uh uh banana banana banana banana banana sort of like banana banana banana
a a blue blue swirl blue swirl banana banana banana oh no blue jack frost could that be
could that be the blue grinch a blue swirl yeah should we go down i freak the fuck out
and I run full speed toward whoever that is.
You run left?
Yeah.
If there's a guy with blue spiral hair, I'm gonna kill him.
I don't follow.
Patrick, we should follow.
Ah, okay.
Okay, man.
I wanted to go the other way.
All right, well, let's follow him.
So you guys run down the side.
hear creepy creatures snickering as you run by and you sort of come across what
looks like the blue Grinch but when he turns to face you he has a regular guy
face. What? Not a Grinch face at all. Oh. And he says to you, "Hello my name is Benicio."
Oh my god.
Okay, I download the old image macro of the owl and it says "Oh really?" at the bottom.
I just download it and look at it for a little bit.
I show Panisio my hoverboard, Panisio does not like it, and I don't know where to go
from there.
I say hello, I'll just say hi.
You brave bastard.
You guys look like a couple of uh...
And he looks up at the frog.
Or a quad...
A quad...
You guys look like a group of guys that maybe...
Would be interested in some techno slime.
Oh shit, he knows us too well.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Ah, crap.
I just got some of the best stuff on the market.
Benicio style.
I believe you.
What are we talking?
OG Bubba Kush, some of that wacky taffy.
I'm talking Tupac Shakur.
Tupac Shakur went to jail for rape Kush.
That's what I'm talking about.
(laughing)
He sort of starts to rant about how everyone
seems to forget about that.
(laughing)
I'm gonna stop you right there,
because I love California, love.
So we'll take the whole batch.
Okay, yeah.
So he, yeah, he hands you it.
He says, he says, "It's going to be $30."
That's not even that bad.
I mean, that's basically, I got 27 from Jamal.
So I just give him my real questions asked.
Yeah, you give him that.
I just give him 30 bucks.
And he now says, he hands it over to you
and then he pulls out a walkie-talkie.
What?
And he says, "We got 'em."
what's and uh... no
from the darkness
comes none other
then michael rapaport
all
this always happens to me
i hate when this happens
dressed in full cyber cop regalia
it says on his helmet joke police
(laughter)
and he uh...
He says, "Good job, Penicillio! That's badass! That's totally wack-ass cool!"
And he holds out his fist for a fist bump.
And Penicillio bumps his fist.
And he says, "You fools think you can come down here and buy techno-slime?
Yeah, right! Not in these streets, not where I'm from!"
And he's very- he's pasty white.
And he's translucent, his skin. You can look through it.
Wait, I have an idea. I have an idea too.
Okay, go ahead. Caleb.
Download the Martin Shkreli Wu-Tang album
Wait, I don't have access to the internet. Oh, why?
You're able to do that. Oh, it's check
- all right, let's see. All right, we have
Intelligence I
Roll. Oh fuck. I rolled 24. Oh, yeah, you download the whole thing. You download the B side to that album
And then I also I also I have a built-in
Really's creepy post about that one girl
I have a built-in printer on my backpack and I print out a Willy Wonka golden ticket that says in word pass
He starts Michael Rapaport starts frothing at the mouth
You want this you want this you little white bitch?
Yo, I'm maybe I don't know maybe what's in it for me
How about we forget this whole thing ever happened?
Hmm. I don't know. I do like to arrest people who think it's okay to make jokes
Okay, I print out a second in wordpass
*laughter*
And he's like
*makes buzzing noises*
You're destroying the nwordpass economy
*laughter*
Edward Pass Machine Gopher
Roll a what pass?
Roll a Persuasion
with Advantage
Fuck, 8
You can roll twice and take the title
I rolled twice and they were both 5
Damn, ok
Yeah, he's like, "Hmm, nice try
but I'm, I'm never
no way, anyway
I'm about to do some hip hop keto on your ass
*laughter*
Yeah, roll for initiative guys.
Damn.
Oh my god, dude. I was so close to saving us from this guy.
Oh.
I got a 21.
I got a 1.
I got a 19.
You got a 1?
I got a 1.
I got a 19.
Damn, you're the fastest guy in the west usually.
Who got a 19?
Me.
Nice. What'd you get, Pat?
I got a 1.
Oh, Pat got the one. Cameron, what'd you get? 21. Oh, it's so different than when I was
writing. Okay, let's see how fast Michael Rapaport is. He's with the quickness.
He's not that fast. Penecio is cowering away. He's just sort of an informant.
All right, yeah. Okay, cool. Yeah, so you guys fight him. Cameron, you go first.
Okay, I want to grab Penicill by his hair and swing him around over my head and throw him at Michael Rapaport.
Absolutely. Roll a Strength check to see if you... I mean you could grapple him. He's like a civilian. I'm not even going to tell you to grab for that.
You just grab him and swing him around. And yeah, now roll... I would say roll a Dexterity attack. So like what you would roll for the Grinch Gun, basically. Roll that.
for the Grinch gun okay yeah an attack or a damage just for an attack so five okay
that's a 24 yeah you absolutely hit him you wall him roll now roll a 1d6 and add
that's roll 1d6 straight six nice yeah so you throw you whip around Pony CIO who
is just like oh no not again and you can get thrown directly into Michael
Rappaport's chest and Michael Rappaport falls over on his back he's not prone
I'm gonna say that that happens because that was a very cool move yeah yeah you
still have stuff you can do so we want to do okay I want to use my yo mama ability
to insult Michael Rappaport and cause him psychic damage so I want to I stand
over him and I say "hey pal, more like Michael Crappaport." Oh shit, okay he's
got a roll, let's see how he's not gonna do too hot at this. My spell check
corrects it to Michael Crappaport. And that gets saved to the dictionary. He does
okay he roll 4d4 and he's gonna take half of that damage he sort of brushes it off
he's like I've heard worse one time 40 monster sent me his giant penis I rolled
13 okay yeah so he takes yeah he's only takes like six damage yeah it still hurt
his feelings like you know he doesn't like being called that does he cry so
So yeah, he's not looking, he's not happy about that.
No, his lower lip starts to quiver, but he doesn't cry.
- What lower lip?
(laughing)
You fucking punk ass little bitch.
- Woo! - Oh damn.
- Take that shit, take that shit, bitch.
- Hell yeah, and it is now, with that sweet ass insult,
it is now your turn, Caleb.
- I stand in front of a stalactite
that's poking somehow out of the side of the cave,
sewer system kind of thing that's going on.
And I hold in front of it a Jamaican flag
as if I'm a matador baiting a bull.
And I dangle it and I say, "Reba, Reba."
And I try to, I'm gonna, you'll see what I do.
- Okay, yeah.
Yeah, let's see, he's gonna try to resist that.
That's pretty tempting though.
let's see how he does and give him disadvantage on that for sure he is oh
my god he is simply unable to resist every bone in his body needs to charge
that flag so he charges he charges he's gonna be said as he gets up from the
ground and charges. He says that. And I don't but he says that. Okay so right is right before he gets to
the flag I pull it out of the way and he runs into the stalactite. He absolutely
does. Let's see how much damage he takes. He's gonna take quite a bit I think. Yeah
he takes a solid 10 damage from that. He just gets his head just like boom like
Looney Tunes like he's got a big bump he looks right at the camera and he's like
he's like making a face. Does he have birds flying around his head? Yeah he's
the birds flying around this around his head they're all blackbirds believe it
or not so yeah which makes sense because it's his imagination so yeah he's uh
they're the they're the they're the black people Twitter reddit icon yeah
the Twitter bird with the with a yeah he's just like yeah he says under his
breath Liz Lemon style I want to go to there and yeah so yeah no you do that to
him now it is I believe it's actually his turn yeah so he gets up from that he's
pretty pissed off and he looks at you guys you're trying to make a fool out of
me I'm about to make a fool out of you let me show you my hip-hop keto so he
goes to a he starts to breakdance and and screams and screams New York style and
he starts to spin around and and let's see how he does. Let's see if he knocks you knocks knocks you out. No, he can't he hasn't hit you. So he starts spinning around his head, but you pretty easily get out of the way. But then he sort of gets up and then tries to hit you with brass knuckles that are the same ones from Do the Right Thing. He tries to punch you with those.
Okay.
He succeeds. He's gonna win.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Yeah, he does four damage, though. He just sort of, like, knocks you on the head.
Sullivan the Frog, who's sitting on top of your head, manages to hold on, but just barely.
Manages to hold on to your horns after you get knocked in the head.
Um, yeah.
And, uh, now it is your turn, Patrick.
Alright, so what I'm gonna do with my Techno Slime points, uh, I'm gonna play the bass,
and I'm gonna play fuckin', I'm gonna play, uh, I'm gonna play... what's that fuckin'
Snoop Dogg so- fuck, goddammit.
Uhhhhhhhh.
Fuck, goddammit.
I'm gonna play "Ain't Nothin' But a G-Thing."
What's that Snoop Dogg song?
You know, that one, ate nothing but a G-Thing.
I'm gonna play that at Michael Rapaport, but also, just to distract him, but also to give,
cause he can't stop grooving once he hears it.
No he can't, yeah.
He says this is real New York hip hop.
Yeah, yeah.
Just not knowing, he doesn't know anything about Snoop Dogg it turns out.
uh... yeah let's see uh...
yet he's unable to resist
so yeah yeah you're right you guys are gonna uh... he's gonna have basically
uh... he's not he's gonna basically you're going to get an auto hit next
person hits it
because you have advantage and he's grooving too hard
uh...
he's losing it uh... you guys are going to be able to crush him so you're up
you're up cameron what do you do?
I go creature mode
and I beat him up I hit him on the top of the head and the
bottom of the butt. Alright, do it. Alright, let's see. That's a 24. Yeah, you do that.
Roll for damage. Woah. 20 damage. Max damage. Yeah, describe how you squish Michael Rapaport
between your two pipes to death.
- Yeah, so I hit him on the top of the head and he--
- Parody, parody.
(gunshot)
- He reverberates like a gong,
and then while he's shaking around,
I hit him on the bottom of the butt and it,
he flies up and he splatters on the ceiling of the tunnel,
and he just makes, he's like a flat,
just like Nickelodeon splatter with a face
on the top of the tunnel.
And he says, "Aw, man!"
Yeah, he splats on top and he falls down to the ground and you see two little feet come
up below him and he starts to waddle away.
And then out of the darkness you see some sort of beastly, hairy-looking naked man with
a huge swinging dick swing by out of nowhere and just scoop him up into the darkness.
He's gone
Just like that
Good riddance, buddy
Yeah
So yeah now there's us and Pony's you yeah, can I feels like?
Please please don't hurt me
I grabbed Pony's you by the lapels and I say to tell us the way to the main city right now or I'll turn you
into Nickelodeon
Okay, yeah, you don't have to roll an intimidation check he's totally scared
He's like just just keep just keep going go going straight a minute
Your third right you can get there. I'm not even Spanish. I was just trying to do a thing
You say the third Reich are you a not so no no no I didn't start beating him up
Yeah, you start beating him up. He's like. I'm not canceled. I'm not canceled, and he's like crying
Yeah, you beat him up. He's a total bloody pulp
I don't know if he took any information, but he said your third your third right the third right tunnel
The third entrance so yeah, you guys now know your way out of here
You guys beat up these guys who are both alive now. They're both alive and just squished
Yeah, so you guys keep walking and you we know where to go now. Yeah, you see that way
I can I check on Sullivan. I just want to see how Sullivan yeah. Yeah
Yeah, what do you say?
Hmm a little buddy
How are you? I got a little rattled when he punched you with the love hate
I hate, the love hate, you know, brass knuckles, but I'm doing okay otherwise.
Still a little woozy from the technosom, but I could use some more of that if you're willing
to say.
Here, this will help.
I give him a pill that is, it's pressed and it says rehypnohal on it.
Okay.
Yeah, he takes that.
Yeah, he takes that, uh, um, and he's, he is, his eyes like, just like go wide as shit.
He's just like, yeah, he is, he's just like, yeah, he's just like, like
staring straight ahead now with his eyes wide as hell.
And he's like, I can dig it.
And he's just totally calm.
Alright, then we continue.
Yeah.
Yeah, you guys keep going and you find that third right, which makes no sense the more
I say it, and it's just like a tunnel outcropping.
The creepy creatures scurry away, they see the light of the main city.
And you guys see a ladder, and you go up the ladder.
You end up in the main city.
So this is the main area of Gun City, so it's Gun City proper.
The streets, the streets are haunted.
First thing I do now that we're here,
I wanna get an authentic Gun City bagel.
Yeah, you can do that.
Hold on, wait, I'm gonna read the description I wrote.
And then I'll get a bagel.
No, you don't have to.
It's okay.
Yeah, Gun City proper, the streets a terrible chrome.
Haunted by, should I do the voice?
Do the voice, it's for consistency.
Do the voice.
Gun City proper.
The streets, a terrible, haunting black.
With the hulking hovercars cruising by,
the wealthy denizens walk by in their aluminum tube tops,
and their high quality, authentic Master Chief replica suits.
The air is sickeningly clean, the sky is clouded with holograms
of awesome looking Japanese women trying to sell you luxury underwear
can shit in while you work. The neons are bright, vibrant, reflecting, creating a picturesque
desktop background or cover photo of your lamest friend. Everyone here is proud of their brands
and proud of their work. There is only 1% unemployment, almost everyone works in consulting or defense.
Only the true creative minds get to rule as social media managers of brand accounts, acting
as de facto lords of Gun City.
Besides that awesome music by Megadrive or whatever, we hear their best posts from these
brands broadcast throughout the city.
I'm depressed lol you hear Cracker Barrel say.
OMG what's wrong replies Raytheon.
And everyone in Gun City loves it.
So that's where you are.
Wow.
Oh my god.
- Okay, now that you've finished your little thing,
I get a bagel.
- Yeah, you can get the fucking bagel.
- Okay.
- It's much better probably.
Yeah, so yeah, you go to the authentic Gun City Bagel store.
- Yeah.
- You see a guy behind the counter.
He's dressed like the--
- Can I do an ethnicity check?
- Yeah, sure.
Yeah, roll for ethnicity.
- Okay, I rolled for--
- That's gonna be actually, roll for,
that's gonna be an insight check.
- Okay, I get a--
- You get pretty good insight.
I get an 18.
Okay, yeah, you can definitely tell
he is a gun city resident.
Okay, that's all I'm allowed to say legally.
Okay.
All right, so what I know,
I know that this is a real true authentic gun city bagel.
Yeah, yeah, he looks up at you and he says,
what can I get you boss?
That's right, that's that gun city accent
I was looking for.
All right, I say, one bagel please.
Actually, make it two.
And can you flatten it out as if it could fit into a ZD drive?
Hey, coming right up.
Not, not, not like me to yuck a yum.
And he just, uh, takes out two bagels.
It just takes out a rolling pin and starts rolling them completely
flat and hands them to you.
Uh, and he says, these are free on the house.
Welcome to gun city.
Whoa.
Wow.
Yeah, that's right.
(laughing)
That's right.
You got it.
Okay, and then I turn, I don't say thank you,
I turn around and I leave.
(laughing)
Yeah.
Okay, yeah, so you leave the Gun City Bagels.
And actually, actually, I don't eat the bagels,
I keep them.
I'm gonna keep them in my pocket,
I think they might come in handy later.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You keep them in your pocket, you store them.
And you look in the distance in the city,
You could see the giant social media manager
who looks like he's like 33 maybe,
and his dad is, you know,
maybe runs the firm that manages the account.
You see that guy,
that giant mega, mega zord sort of looking thing,
just a little bit down the block.
Yeah, so you guys can probably make it there pretty easily.
Whoa.
Right down the block.
Okay, well, wait, hold on.
Wait, okay, we could easily walk there,
but we are in Gun City after all.
How about we take the subway?
(laughing)
Yeah.
That's a good idea.
Yeah, let's do it.
It's a great idea.
I mean, how many times in your life
will you be in Gun City?
Probably a lot.
Probably just now.
You see a guy says, "Not many!"
(laughing)
That's right, guy.
- Yeah, yeah.
And he gives you a thumbs up.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, so you guys go down to the subway.
You see it's being patrolled by a lot of Jollibee cops.
- I hop the turnstile.
- Okay, roll a stealth check.
- All right, 12.
- Yeah, one of the Jollibee cops kind of sees you do that
and he sort of goes up to you.
He goes, "Hey, where are you going?
"Where do you think you're going?
"This is gun city." - I run up and I say,
"Help, help, this monkey is trying to steal my money."
And I point to the monkey on my shoulder
and I make Patrick the monkey run away.
And I say, "Hey, Jolly Bee Cop,
"go chase that monkey for me, please.
"This is so urgent."
- Roll deception check.
- Okay.
- With advantage.
Oh, that's a nat 20.
- Oh shit, yeah.
That cop, the monkey runs and that cop says,
"I'm gonna quit my job and become a monkey chaser."
and like takes off his police outfit and starts chasing that
chasing Patrick the monkey around like sort of around in
circles like in a cartoon.
I also hopped the turnstile. Well, the cop is distracted.
You guys are fine now. Yeah, you guys can sort of just get
through now Yoda can just walk underneath it. Yeah. Yeah, you
take the train into the city.
What letter is it?
Beta is the letter.
It's a Greek alphabet.
Perfect.
Gun City.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
You take the beta train, uh, you see all the very beautiful, wealthy, subservient
residents of Gun City with their, their, uh, they look, uh, pleasantly happy.
You know, that phrase, pleasantly happy.
Okay.
All right.
I start doing a subway dancing performance
where I use the poles to do a spin trick.
- Yeah, I give him my lead pipes to do it.
- 'Cause I'm trying to make a little money.
I say, "Ladies and gentlemen,
"we are not here to ruin your commute.
"We're here to make it better.
"We are the untold truth."
(laughing)
And then we all start break dancing.
- Okay, all of you roll a performance check.
- Okay. - Okay.
Oh no.
Fuck yeah dude.
23. Natural 20 plus 3.
I have a 1.
Did you get a natural 1?
No.
A 2 minus 1.
I got a 19.
Ok yeah.
We're about to leave you in the dust.
Yeah dude.
Yeah with your nat 20
Ray William Johnson. Describe what you do.
what you do. You have full range. I do a hundred backflips in a row and and then I
just start bouncing off the walls like flubber and eventually I land I land in
a on a guy's lap right like that's after I've done all the bouncing I land on a
guy's lap but then I sort of do like Jessica Rabbit's legs and he gets a
boner and he slips he slips a $50 bill in my bucket
absolutely that all happens. Oh my god I'm rich as fuck. Yeah the $50 bill yeah it all of it
happens he actually immediately goes I'd like to sign you us us over here over
here had a scrubbing bubbles ink we're looking for a new mascot okay and you
want a demon with a computer on his back? Yeah sure whatever gets clout man you
know. I'm sorry but I'm... Taken. Yeah he shoots himself in the head. Yeah Patrick
Yodo you do some sweet-ass fucking skateboard tricks. Actually you know
describe what you do what do you do on the subway? I'm doing I'm doing a handstand
on the board and I'm spinning I'm spinning around in a circle I'm doing a
1620 degree spin okay I'm doing that I'm doing multiple of those and I'm doing
them very fast okay yeah I'm kind of just going up and down the train car
doing it really fast and I'm hitting bags out of people's hands yeah people
are a little scared but they're also like amazed by you it's they they they
they're having trouble even deciding they're so intrigued yeah blow toss piss
in a rare moment of gracelessness you stub your toe trying to walk and you just
sort of like shrug and like sort of a do a do a little you do like a little light
gentle kick like ah shucks yeah yeah yeah what do you say the camera though
that's the biggest thing I say oops yeah that's a 20 that's amazing yeah you got
it yeah you got it losers the producers are cheering yeah they're coming they're
loving it um yes you guys arrive at the stop that's for the the main stakeums
Stegos Federation of Bodies and Spaces HQ.
And you get out
and you hear affirmations "remember to drink water as you leave the subway."
And yeah, you get out, you go to the
building. So in the building there's two th- two womps
from Mario standing guard.
You guys hear your PSPs and your engages ring.
It is Ash and Futures.
Yo, what's up guys?
Whoa, looks like you made it pretty far, I can tell.
So, you should have IDs to help you get through the first part of the security.
I don't know much about after that, but you better hurry up, you're making time, but who
knows you might get punked by me.
I didn't really-
Whoa.
You know, that's just saying, and he turns off.
yeah that's scary I scream okay yeah the wamp sort of IU as you're screaming
Patrick monkey also screams along with you like at the same time yeah I've
trained him to do that yeah something I didn't mention everything I say or do he
acts out at the same time on my shoulder this that's all yeah he's been doing
time he caught monkey monkey do yeah he started eating right that's what that's
He started eating the, he tried to eat the uncle too.
He got a little nibble in there.
Yeah, he got some bites.
Yeah.
Can we walk up to the thwomps and show our IDs?
Yeah, you can do that.
Yeah, describe what you guys do.
Tell me the process.
Tell me what's up.
Okay, well, I put the ID on a lanyard around my neck and I go up to the thwomp and I put
my ID in his mouth.
- Okay.
Yeah, he sort of is like,
"Yep, that's the protocol."
And he humbly lets you in.
(laughing)
- Got it in one.
- I walk up to him and I slide my ID through his butt cheeks
like Nelly in the tip drill video.
- Right.
- Like a credit card.
- Yeah, he blushes and lets you in as well.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
What about you, Patrick Yoda?
I just, uh, I show it, uh, kind of fast.
Uh, you know, just kind of like, you know, make it look like I've done this a
million times and they should know me already.
And alarm starts to go off.
Yeah.
like sort of shrug like yeah yeah I know this guy yeah Sullivan the frog sort of
hides in hides in in the hard drive of your computer while you guys do this oh
yeah I forgot I had Sullivan with me. You downloaded Sullivan into your hard drive? I guess so.
He's digital now. Yeah yeah he's digital he's digital he's gone Sullivan the frog
has gone digital. Okay I have a digital Sullivan the frog alright I'll remember this for later I have a
digital Sullivan the frog in me.
Yeah. Yeah. So you're in the lane lobby of the building, the main
lobby, the building. Yeah, you see like, you know, posters in
there that say stuff like, you know, you know, get fucking
pumped, you rock star, and it's a picture of slash and you see,
you can't pour from an empty cup. And it's a picture of a
white woman who's just tired. And then you see another picture
that says, another like motivational things. It's like
self-care is better than feeding poor people. And it's in the
Success Kid meme format. You see this all around the building.
You see a bunch of Stakem's logos, and you see Jollibee
security guards doing this next part of the scan and a guy walks
by you. And he says, Oh, do you guys hear about the new
protocol?
Um, I, yeah, yeah.
Patrick says, yeah, I was just about to say that.
I was just about to say Patrick says yes.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well get ready.
Cause they now scan your face to see if there's any traces of irony in
your body before letting you in.
And, uh, yeah, he walks in, he gets his face scanned.
You see a perfectly smooth brain and a picture of, uh, a gif or a jif from
Brooklyn nine, nine up here on the screen.
and then a check mark comes up and he's allowed in.
- Oh no. - Oh fuck, okay.
- So behind that area is a bunch of elevators.
- Okay, wait.
Okay, no, keep going.
- Yeah, behind that area is a bunch of elevators to get in.
There could be another way in,
you'd have to probably look for it though,
but that is sort of like the new protocol security measure
put in since the attack on the Jollibee cop
that got his head cut in half.
- Oh. (laughs)
- Okay, so-- - We did this ourselves.
here's what I do right I I put I pull my my my red and green of fatigues my jacket
I pull it up over my head so it looks like I have no head and then I get
Patrick the monkey to sit on top of my head so it's a monkey yeah and I go up
and I say but really muffled from inside the jacket I say hey go ahead scan my
face to test for irony oh yeah roll roll a let's do roll a performance check with
advantage I love that idea I'm just giving them out okay that's 16 yeah it
works they just think it's like a weird fucked up guy with a monkey face so yeah
they scan the monkey face and it's a pic it's it's Patrick the monkey with
symbols just on the screen so he's let right in yeah I'd say fuck you guys and
I flip off Ray William Johnson and Patrick I don't think the sensors like
that the sensors love it the sensors give say they don't like it and the alarm
starts going up Patrick I don't think this game is just make them up say you
could just do that you know you could just record something and just say stuff
I guess you're right.
We could do that.
Yeah, so what do you guys want to do though?
Patrick, what you got?
What I'm going to do?
Yeah.
Hmm.
Alright, so what does the area look like?
So yeah, it's like a, basically a lobby with like a main entrance with like the scanners and a few Jollibee cops there.
there. Off to the right you see just sort of more of a lobby area. If you want you
could do like an investigation check to see if you could find something.
No, my investigation is negative two. Yeah, if you want you can you can there's a few
things you can do right so you can I mean Yoda's mind could be helpful here
right potentially. Yeah. But you know it's up to you what you want to do. Just say
Say what you would want to do and I'll, we could try to find a way to make it happen.
Hmm.
Insight.
Okay, so what you can do is you can go up to the Jollibee cops and try to see what their
motivation is.
Maybe see if you can get something out of them.
Do I have to roll for that?
Yeah, so go up to them, yeah.
Start a conversation.
Ooh, natural 20.
Plus 5, yeah.
- Plus five. - Okay, yeah.
- Natural 20 plus five.
- Okay, yeah, oh yeah, your insight check
is tied to Yoda's mind, so.
- Ah.
- So yeah, so you do that,
and so you read the Jollibee guard's mind.
And he's thinking,
now man, I can't wait to punch out the clock.
I'm gonna go home and jerk off to black.com.
Love it, love that website.
Nothing wrong with that website.
Man, I hope this guy doesn't figure out
that if you just make us scan the back of your head
and say it's because it's actually racist to scan the front of your head.
We'll just let him do that.
He can just get in.
Cause if he asks that I'm going to have to let him do that.
Okay.
I love black.
I'm going to do that.
Yeah.
So you, yeah, you, you say that it's racist and it's ableist to have your face scanned.
Um, and you, you threatened to cancel the Jollibee cop.
Um, and which is the biggest, you know, like it's, that's like the most
important currency in the state comes Federation of bodies and spaces.
Um, how you can weaponize being kind rather than the act of being kind.
Um, and so he immediately let scans the back of your head and it just shows a
pick a question mark and you're allowed it.
That worked great.
Okay.
Is it my turn?
Yeah, if you want to. Okay, um, okay, first, okay, I panicked while he, while Patrick
was learning all this stuff about how to scan the back of his head, I panicked and
I downloaded the scene from Now You See Me 2 where they slip the card past the
security checkpoint. Okay? So I, out of my pocket, I pull an ace of spades. That's
That's right. Huge AC/DC fan.
And...
That's Motorhead.
That's an AC/DC song. Thank you very much.
That's Motor...
No. So I...
The jury's still out.
I throw... Actually, I'll do a check for that. Can I check... Can I do... Can I roll an intelligence
check to see if that's AC/DC or Motorhead?
Yeah. Do a history check.
A history...
History.
Is that a thing? Okay. Plus five history. Yeah, I think I got it in the fucking bag.
Yeah, that's right. 23, you fucking bitch.
Yeah, so you know for sure that it's AC/DC.
That is beyond the shadow of a doubt an AC/DC song.
Yeah, and Lemmy had nothing to do with it.
Yeah, as that plays on LimeWire on my brain, because I'm a fucking computer,
I throw the Ace of Spades through the security checkpoint
at one of my compatriots, who slips it in their pocket,
and then they throw it back at me, and then I throw it back at them,
And it slides between one of the security guards legs and it just barely touches
their clit as it passes through.
Right.
Just play, just, just the tiniest bit, just enough to get them excited, but not
enough to make them do anything about it.
All Jollibees have clits.
And then, yeah, that's right.
Big, juicy, meaty thumb clits.
And then as they're distracted, just having a tiny bit of a cum, just like a
one eighth of a cum right there at the security checkpoint, I, I jump over the
turn style again because I'm so good at it. Okay so thinking of the rolls here
okay. Is there an awesome skill? Because that's what that was. First you and
Blotoss Piss both roll athletic checks. Oh no. Let's go. My athletics is good. 17.
17 as well. Whoa. Okay great yeah you guys slide the card perfectly and you do make
that Jolly Beat nut a little bit. Just a little bit though. So now I'm gonna need
you to roll a stealth check to see if you can hop it. Stealth... 7. Okay you slide the card back and forth.
Make that Jolly Beat nut a little bit and then you just sort of like you do the
thing where you like run up to a bar you forget to jump you just hit your
yourself look at the guy just tip over top wise and they're immediately on your
ass you guys got a book it I run to the elevators and press the up button a lot
yeah you guys are pressing it up up wait wait wait wait I I find who's whatever
the head Jollibee is and I started fingering it as as deftly as possible
just fucking rubbing that clip doing it actually I start eating it out I start
doing the alphabet spelling with my tongue so the jolly be consents and this
happens thank you so professional DMS do yeah so that jolly B is says I like I
that's a good idea but let's roll now still a performance check to see how
well you do. Yeah this is what the libs want dude. They want you to have to roll a performance check for when you wanna have sex.
Okay, performance I get a 16. Yeah I mean that Jollibee is like "woah, eugh" you know.
It's loving that. Yeah yeah and just sort of like starts to like gently gently
squirt Jollibee sauce. She sprung a gentle squirt of Jollibee sauce. I don't think that's
a sauce. I think probably spaghetti sauce. Sweet spaghetti sauce. Yeah, she just squirts
out that spaghetti sauce. Yeah and then I say let us go. Let us go. Yeah yeah she's
quivering the other Jollibees are too stunned to do anything and you're able
to get to the elevator. Yes. In time. Yeah so you guys get into the elevator you're
taking it up to the to the boardroom where you can find an entryway into the
computer. So you get to the top of the boardroom and it's this comically long
ping-pong table with beanbag chairs on top of it. It's just a total mess of
shitty corporate work culture. It's like a meditation area on top of the ping-pong
table. Makes no sense. And it's empty except there's a chair that's turned
around and when you guys get there oh no that chair spins around and looks like
somebody who was expecting you maybe and it's none other than the CEO of
Steakums Chuck Wendig on a leash when he has with him on a leash mr. bean whoa I
would have never thought they would be working together that is fucked yeah and
And Chuck Wendig... Basically polar opposites.
Yeah. Oh, that's part of the power.
And Chuck Wendig says...
"Now that feel when you flumpty flew all over your pants!"
"Razza frazza was a woo my fellow boopty boos!"
"How's it what's it?"
And Mr. Bean goes "Mmm, yeah, I dunno."
And Chuck Wendig yanks at his collar, stopping from talking.
Yeah, so, yeah, you hear Chuck Wendig say that.
You turn around and you look behind you, you see actually behind a bulletproof, super solid
glass, the world's giant computer.
The world's most giant, biggest computer.
I start drooling.
Yeah, it looks like a TI-83 calculator, but it has GAMs, just like beautiful GAMs.
I look into the camera and I say, "Deadpool style."
I wonder how much porn you could download onto that thing, and then I wink, and then
I do a jack-off motion with my hand.
Wait, I, aping on a Blowtoss Pisses format,
I also look at the camera,
or at least my best approximation where the camera is,
Right.
And I say, I sure would love to TI-69 that thing.
Yeah, you both do that, you sort of, that's pretty good.
I think yours is pretty good.
Both of you guys roll a performance check.
Let's see who gets the biggest laugh.
Okay.
From the audience.
Oh no, I got a five.
Okay, it's not great.
I got a five as well.
Okay.
So you have the audience is like kind of just upset.
Yeah.
I liked the TI-69 though, personally.
I looked, I looked at the, I look at the camera and then I, it's just the top of
your head, you're too sure.
I noticed that the camera, I noticed that the camera is there for the first time.
And then I don't say anything cause I don't know.
Yeah, you just like, you get like scared.
Yeah.
I'm too scared to say anything.
The audience loves that.
Um, they're eating that up.
Yes, you see that behind you.
Um, you see also a bunch of like, uh, computer nerds updating it with OS, uh,
with Microsoft OS Fogel, um, and they all, they all have gotten the very popular
surgery in gun city, which is a permanent soy face.
Um, so they're all doing that while they're updating it.
And Chuck Wendig looks at you all and he says, you flumpty wuzzle
wooze thought you could wiggle womb in my was it, was it?
And he sort of like starts walking around the boardroom like he's gonna give the speech from Network.
He said, "You don't flumpty-floos understand? You don't wuzzy-wuzzits and fuzzy-guzzits?
I'm
everything. I am the beginning and the end, the Alpha and the Omega.
If you are going to try to wuzzit-wuzzit my big computer,
you're gonna have to guz it was it go through me first and he yanks at mr.
bean collar mr. bean hops up on the board table it starts charging at you
guys like on all fours like the fucking ring girl and yeah let's roll for
initiative let's just let's just get right in let's go for it yeah I roll a
I got a 10. I got an 8. Okay, let's see how Mr. Bean/Chuck Wendig do. Okay, they did
very well. So Mr. Bean is charging at all of you and he's going like "kill me"
and he uh all of you guys roll dexterity saving throw I got a six 22 0 literally
0 yeah roll the one I have - oh you roll it crit failed okay yeah hold on wait
let me yeah this is going so bad at the end yeah this is not an ideal way for
for this to go for you, I'm afraid.
You managed to, so Mr.
Bean runs up to you and he shoots out of his mouth.
It looks like just like a bunch of like terrible English food,
sausage, biscuits, crumpets, all those things in like a
disgusting, Queens goo, poisonous spray.
Yeah, and he shoots that out.
You managed to get out of the way blowtoss piston bit mostly
you to Yoda kind of goes over your head.
You, though, my fair friend, Ray William Johnson, you take...
Oh boy.
Uh-oh.
You take 15 damage.
Oh, that puts me at -1 HP.
Yeah, you're knocked out. Cold.
Damn.
You can be revived by people. We can go into that.
It'll basically require one of you guys to try to stabilize him.
which you can do. Is that a medicine thing?
Yeah, it's a medicine check. Okay. I think you have pretty good medicine, Patrick.
I'm gonna do, yeah, I'm gonna do a medicine check. You guys should do that because I have an absolutely fatal blow.
Oh yeah. I can strike on specifically Chuck Wendig.
First time. Alright, I'm rolling for a medicine check.
I got 10. Yeah, that's good enough. He stabilizes. That's exactly good enough.
Oh shit. Yeah, so Caleb, you, Ray William Johnson,
What happens when like the life,
what is like you almost dying do?
And like, what is it like when you come back?
- So, Mr. Bean deletes system 32.
(laughing)
And I have to boot in safe mode and recover it, okay?
And so now I'm recovering and the update,
it takes a couple minutes, honestly.
Like they need to maybe stall for a minute
before I can really get back in action.
- Right, yeah.
- 'Cause I'm installing.
I'm installing Cortana.
You're installing, yeah, it's OverDrive.
You're installing Cortana.
You see in your mind's eye,
Sullivan the Frog, the computer program,
slow dancing with Cortana as you're coming back to life.
I become jealous.
Yeah.
Jealousy check.
Yeah, you wake in a jealous rage with one HP.
Okay, I have one HP now?
Yeah.
Okay, is it my turn or is it somebody else's?
It is Cameron's turn now.
All right. Thank you, Pat.
You're welcome. Mr. Bean's going to taste my rhesus pipe.
I'm going to, okay, wait, I, I, um, I look, okay,
first I use the yo mama. I insult. Does this is, I guess this,
Mike, tell me if this counts as an insult. I look at Mr. Bean.
I look at the camera and I hold the lead pipe. Like it's my wiener.
And I say time to lay some pipe.
Absolutely that's an insult to Mr. Bean. He was sexless.
Yeah.
So I do that to him for with my to cause psychic damage to attempt to cause psychic damage.
Okay. Yeah, he's gonna have to try to resist that. He's not very wise. So you might be okay.
Yeah, yeah, he's gonna take it on the face. Roll for damage. Fold it maxed out. Fold damage.
12.
mean? You say that to him." And he just sort of like goes like *growls* and just sort of like trips over himself and just goes like *growls* and just like like flops around and just like feels all kinds of bad. He's still alive, but he like just like is very upset and just sort of says "fuck you" like under his breath.
It is now Chuck Wendig's turn. He's going to- seeing Mr. Bean get injured, he unhinges his jaw in anger and begins to charge up what looks like some sort of beam. His tongue has become a giant sort of like laser cannon. And he's going to- you guys are all going to have to roll Dexterity saving throws again.
Oh no, is he going to shoot the whoop?
He's literally gonna shoot the whoop.
Fuck.
Wow, you fucking read that shit.
It's a shoot the whoop, but way of Fluxy Floops.
I got a 9.
Okay.
Is it- wait, wasn't shoot the whoop racist?
Was it racist?
Yeah, dude, wasn't it blackface?
Yeah, wasn't it like a Sambo?
Wait, so-
Wait, wasn't it-
Dude, Chuck Windig is doing blackface, dude.
I didn't even know that.
I think all we need to do is take a picture.
I had no idea.
And then we beat him.
Oh, I gotta... wait, so it's a dexterity thing?
Yeah.
Dexterity saving.
My dexterity is zero, but I got a nineteen.
Nice, yeah.
I'm firing my laser!
You avoid it, uh, uh, you avoid it, it goes right over you again.
They keep just like misjudging your height.
Uh, uh, RayWilliamJohnson, you're lying on the ground, so it's just like, it just goes over you too.
You blow-toss, you try to do some cool flippy Deadpool bullshit, but it gets you.
And you take, you take 15 damage also actually. What comes out is a beam that
it just literally said it's just a beam that is shaped in the face of Lin Manuel
Miranda coming out of his mouth with like hearts in his eyes and you take 15
damage from that. So now it is your turn Bray William Johnson.
Um, okay. Do it.
Alright, so I have 1 HP, right? I'm sort of on my last, uh...
Yeah.
I'm on my last legs here.
Yeah, you're not doing too well.
So I'm gonna pull out the big guns.
Do it.
I'm gonna use my move on Chuck Wendig, Child Porn Upload.
[Chuckling]
Okay. Yeah.
Uh, yeah, describe Child Porn Upload. What does it do?
So child porn upload is I, well I suppose first I have to download it myself, a cache of child
porn.
Right, it's cached, you're not looking at it.
Yeah, exactly.
I don't look at it, I close my computer eyes and then I directly send it via DDoS attack
to Chuck Wendig.
And the point is that in this future reality, I suppose that the cops have sort of a, the
security state has increased to the point where they immediately know that
somebody has child porn. It is the only good thing to come out of this world.
Yeah, sort of, yeah, it's like Ron Paul's worst nightmare. Yeah, okay, so roll a d20.
Okay, yeah, plus the smoke gas modifier. Plus sleight of hand, ten. Okay, let's see
he notices he does not okay yeah he just does it his brain that's here's the
reason here's the reason it's so normal for that's why he doesn't notice it's
absolutely just every day he just had a he had a pedophilic thought and it was
nothing to him it was like imagining lunch okay yeah so you upload child porn
directly into Chuck Wendig in this fantasy realm and of course in a
fantasy realm yeah and he says what the funky what the fuck and the there is you
hear sirens the cops are gonna be there in a minute we have one minute he
freaks out he unhinges his jaw even wider he swallows mr. bean whole to turn
into his final form holy crap which is none other than choking on mr. bean and
dying on the spot he just lays dead on the ground yeah you guys beat Chuck Wendig
the child porn trump card really really I saved it for right at the end I knew I
had it in my arsenal yeah I made sure to pull it right at the right moment so the
The glass behind you sort of opens up, giving you full access to the TI-83 with GAMS.
That is the world's biggest computer, where all the information in the world is stored.
Where the Kramer video is stored.
Where you can finally destroy the Kramer video.
And also do whatever else you want to do.
It's the world's biggest computer.
You guys have intimidated the nerds, they've run away.
The cops will still be here in a minute.
But so you have a minute to delete the video.
And then you have to find a way out.
I will say that it is in a room that is just like a glass room
overlooking the entire city at the top of the social giant
social media manager robots head.
So you guys have a minute.
What do you guys want to do?
Okay, before we go on, I have to point out, somehow, during this whole thing, I don't know when this happened,
I started bleeding on my hand.
*laughter*
I have no idea when this happened.
Oh my god, dude, what the fuck?
Wait.
I have no clue.
I don't know what I did.
But somehow, during, while we were, at some point, when my HP went to 1,
Dude.
in real life. Dude you're in the fucking game dude. Oh my god. The game is real. Okay with that said I
start eating the computer's pussy. Yeah okay. If it has gams it has something in between and I just
start going to town on the bitch. You're right yeah you start eating and the computer can sense and
you start eating the computer's pussy. Computer loves it. Computer's enjoying it very much. While
- While he's doing that, at the exact same time,
I open up Internet Explorer 5000,
and I navigate to bloatospiss.com,
and I open up my profile, and I see that it has 99 likes,
and I click on, from the world's biggest computer,
I click on the like button,
and it upgrades my website to the next level.
- Yeah, you get 100 likes in your profile,
and when everyone sees the world's biggest computer
liked it it starts flooding with likes you get 100 likes 200 likes 300 likes
can we go for 400 you get 400 oh my god oh my god the world's biggest computer is
very popular because of the law it has to be so people are losing their minds
they love your profile this is huge for you it's really hard for me to I miss
clicking the like button several times because the computer is quaking from Ray
William Johnson down below. Right yeah yeah so you hit comment a few times you
accidentally hit like you actually like right like like like gibberish but those
likes those comments get like a thousand likes immediately. Right yeah which I mean a
comment like is worth half of a like. Right a thousand words. That's right a
comment's worth a thousand words. While all this is happening I go into the
computer. How so? Describe this. I go inside the computer. Okay. And I have a SD card with me.
God damn. And I create a backup of the Kramer video. Wow. I delete it from the computer. Okay.
I want you to roll a stealth check to see if these two notice. Okay. That you have a
backup of the Kramer video. Or if it's your little secret. I got a one. You go
into the back of the computer and you accidentally lean on what looks like a
megaphone like speaker and you start muttering a "Gee I hope my friends don't
notice that I downloaded a backup of the Kramer video." So they just hear that. But
But you have a backup, you deleted the main Kramer video.
Is there anything you wanted to do
with the computer, Ray William Johnson?
- Yeah, so I go in to the computer
and I delete the Third Amendment.
- Yeah, you go in, after the computer comes
and that same pasta sauce comes out,
you delete the Third Amendment.
- Yeah, which is no, and I know it by heart
because I'm so anti it.
No soldier shall in time of peace be quartered in any house
without the consent of the owner, nor in time of war,
but in a manner to be prescribed by law.
- Yeah, you're flashing back to memories of soldiers.
- Somebody drawing and quartering a soldier in my house
during a time of peace and I'm not having that bullshit.
- Yeah, you were just like a simple alienware laptop
at that time.
I was simply a raspberry pie at the time.
You see your mom and dad Macintosh
1984 cowering in fear as the soldier was quartered.
And then I delete that shit.
I delete that for some reason because I guess I liked when the soldier was quartered in my house.
Now that I think about it.
We sort of lost the plot.
Yeah, I guess I thought that was really cool.
And so I delete the amendment so that that can happen more often. Hopefully it happens to me again.
Yeah, that's exactly... and hey, it just might. So, at this point now, you have 20 seconds left.
I'm gonna charge my phone for 20 seconds.
All the cops in the world are coming to what they think is arrest a now dead Chuck Wendig.
But we'll eventually see you guys in the computer room interrupting OS Fogel update. What do you want to do?
We gotta stop the update.
We have to stop the update.
I unplugged the computer while it's updating.
Holy shit.
We have to do more than that though.
We have to do more than that. We have to stop the Fogel OS at the source.
Yeah, but if we unplug it while it's updating...
Won't it stop?
Here's what I do.
Oh my god, here's what I do.
I open the CD drive.
I put my two pieces of bagel that I got from the authentic Gun City Bagel Depot.
Yes.
I throw it in the CD drive.
I press the eject button that is now the enter button.
Right, right.
I send those bagels into that CD drive and I let that bitch try to read that shit because I got a feeling it's not going to do it.
Yeah, so she tries because it is a girl and she tries to read it
and
What happens is is that the OS Fogo update you watch a download bar go down and it goes down and it looks like bite marks
Like she's eating
Like she's eating those bagels and you see the update stops
You stop the update the cops are gonna be there in 10 seconds. Your only option probably is to jump out the window
window okay I shoot myself in the head okay yeah you shoot yourself in the head
and you die wait but but just the demon just the demon party yeah what I'm doing
is I'm framing the demon okay I am to do I tell I tell I tell Ray William Johnson
attach to the monkey okay I I attached to the monkey right yeah and then yeah I
jump out the window yeah I'm already gone I say I say the elevator down I say
the demon and I and I safely inject to the monkey yeah okay so the Patrick
monkey and blowtoss piss jump out the window and fall towards gun city
Patrick Yoda found an elevator. He's just taking the elevator down.
The freight elevator. Which was there, yeah the freight elevator. It's the only one that can hold him.
As you two are following out the window, you see a familiar blue Grinch fly by.
Oh my god. Where is he? This time he's wearing Master Chief armor. No. Dude, no.
says get on my back if you want to live
what? I think I might have trusted Blue Grinch
you're hell fucking right I am I ripped
the armor off of him I jump on that Blue Grinch's
back and I ride him like the pony that he
should be and what do you do Blotas?
I ripped the armor off of him I put it on
myself yeah you're wearing the master
chief armor you're both riding the Blue
Grinch the Blue Grinch flies you guys up
into the sky. Why can't he fly? Oh he flies! I decided that the blue-green flies. Into the
laser helicopter. The Ashton Future Elite which was waiting for you guys up top to
abduct you. Patrick, you're already there. You're just reading a newspaper. You're
sort of chilling out. I'm reading Dilbert in the newspaper. Dilbert and laughing? I'm
laughing my friggin head off yeah you guys show up and Asher Future says well
done guys you guys deleted the Kramer video you did a little extra damage to
that nasty corporation and now the CEO is also dead pretty good day now soon
it'll be the top tens mindfulness corporation that will be running the
city that's so pretty cool looks like you're not gonna get punked after all
and he shoots himself in the nuts and he can't he can't help it because he has to
punk somebody he has to get it out it might as well be himself and that's it
and I look into the camera and I say looks like it was a heaven copter after
After all, and then a circle closes on our faces and we jump into the air and freeze to
death.
Oh my god.
Patches, I mean I gotta give it up dude.
That was amazing.
This would be nothing without the players who made some insane footage.
Can you hear me?
Yeah, I see me.
[Music]