You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts for the heartless.
You're a crap monster.
I'm the courting now. I'm the courting.
I'm the courting. No, I am.
I'm the courting. Last night I watched
I watched the usual suspects.
I did not. No, take it back.
Before I can go any further
You watched unusual butt sex.
(laughing)
- Woo!
- No, no.
Butt sex, there is no usual butt sex.
It was all--
- There is, if you're gay, that's usual.
- The mutual butt sex, that's what you had last night.
- I did not have any mutual butt sex,
I didn't watch any usual or unusual butt sex.
I didn't, I didn't do it, I didn't touch an ass
or a suspect, okay?
I just watched a movie.
You were suspected of touching an ass.
You watched the usual, the usual suck men.
That's what you watched.
I'm not suspected of, I'm not sus and I'm not butt sex and I'm usual.
Are you guys done?
Yeah.
I watched the usual suspects and I was like, I was watching it with Janet and I was like,
oh yeah, I forgot Kevin Spacey's in this movie.
Oh, that's fucking weird.
Well, whatever.
We'll watch it anyway.
starts completely forgot about this movie starts immediately directed by Bryan
Singer comes up oh my god I could I could not believe it did fucking hell I'm
yeah I'm fucking pedophiles can you fit in one movie did yeah actors a person
look at every 20s 1920s movie really pedophiles it was just like it's not
pedophilia is like you know you graded just they just came up with that yeah
they didn't that wasn't around back in the 20s it's true like I'm not gonna call
Plato a pedophile though if he was doing that shit like in Chicago he definitely
would be you would call Plato a pedophile yeah I would call is it Socrates or play
it knows Plato I've always been more of a it's so great intellectually minded
person than you anyway yeah yeah yeah earlier I was listening I was listening
the Misfits, I was doing the dishes and listening to the Misfits and the whole time I was just
like, I'm not drinking anymore.
That's a, I copied Caleb.
I'm starting back today, dude.
You're starting back today, yeah, because you have visitors.
This is the day that I, yeah, I'm excited.
But I'm not going to drink for like a month to see if I can do it.
There's no way.
Just to see what happens.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know.
I didn't even make two weeks.
I was like, I'm going to make it two weeks.
This is a bet now.
This is day 10 and I am being bailed out by Neal and Gus coming in.
- I'm on day three.
- Gus coming to town.
- You're on day three?
- Yeah.
- How is it?
- Congrats man.
- I wake up and I don't feel like shit, so.
- Nice, but what about when you go to bed?
- I'm just going insane.
I'm going fucking crazy.
- Yeah, dude.
- I was sitting, I was listening to the Misfits
and then I was just doing like a thing
where I was just doing like a Greek guy voice
and just responding to everything that they were saying.
(laughing)
You have something to, what, oh, you killed a baby today?
Do not kill the baby.
Why you do this?
That's Greek?
You have something to say?
You say something nice.
Yeah, this is your Greek guy?
This is just an impression of my best friend's dad growing up.
That's what he sounded like.
Was he Greek?
Yeah, he was super Greek.
And he talked back to Misfits songs?
No.
But now he did.
Because you did what to my mommy today?
You did what to my mother?
You do not do this.
I remember that day we were just walking around and just making up misfits songs
so that's some of the most fun I've ever had just like just oh yeah around
central just being like I just saw a spider
the best was like me just singing the the actual part from teenagers from Mars
and you were like you thought that was so funny and I was like I just sang an
actual song. The gap between like different types of
misfits songs are so funny cuz like yeah I have one song that's like you do what
to Jackie Kennedy? Do not do this to her. Yeah like they have their songs are
about like I just saw a skeleton wrapped in mummy rags and the
other half are like I just killed 300 women and had sex with them after they
were dead right like there's just no in between at all. It's so funny it's
like the difference between like like I guess horrorcore now and horrorcore in
the 70s is like yeah yeah exactly like basis for everything was either like
psycho or like the wolfman yeah like like we get like Slipknot and shit and we get
like like cool shit like people wearing like leather face masks and then back then
yeah they had to wear like like a fact that it's like I saw an alien
Yeah.
This thing about Marvin the Martian.
Yeah, and they were like, "These guys are Satanists."
Oh my god, this is...
These are...
They are terrifying to me.
Oh my god.
Wow.
Last night when I watched...
I smoked weed again for the last time...
Last night.
Or for the first time in a long time.
Because I was also not smoking.
And, uh...
When I was watching The Usual Suspects,
you know the end where like he...
It's revealed he pieced everything together by like looking at the shit on the walls and stuff?
No, I've never seen The Usual Suspects.
Oh, so in the movie he like...
The main character tells this like whole story.
Kevin Spacey tells this whole story and he just makes up details using like the
names on the on the like wall behind the detective and like the random shit on
the wall behind the detective like the towns and stuff and I was just imagining
Kevin Spacey and Bryan Singer coming up with that scene in Bryan Singer's office
and Kevin Spacey's like yeah here let me show you this it would be something like
this yeah I used to know this guy down in Poughkeepsie his name was seven year
old's penis nine-year-old eight-year-old penis six-year-old penis big fat guy you
know whale of a man I was just making myself laugh so hard last night well
Jana had never seen the movie before and I'm just spoiling it yeah that's the
best just ruining a movie sucks dude the usual suspects it's oh yeah sucks when I
I didn't even like it ever I didn't even like it in high school I was like
annoying about that movie like it was like I I was it was maybe like the first
movie I got into and I just got into like bad shitty movies and that was my
favorite one and I would I would show it to people and I would do that I would be
like you're gonna love the twist ending this movie but it sucks dude none of the
dialogue makes any sense yeah fucking Gabriel Byrne is just doing an Irish
accent the entire time and he's supposed to be like a New York cop it's fucking
terrible dude and also there's two pedophiles that made the movie.
The movie I got annoying about like that was train spotting I think.
Yeah. If you watch train spotting now do you like it? Yeah I think it holds up.
Yeah. I've not seen train spotting 2 because I don't want to. My movie was fight club.
That was fight club for me. Oh yeah. I was really into fight club. I would say those are all kind of in the
same I watch I got really yeah I got train spotting and then in middle school
it was sin city train spotting city is like so yeah train spotting train
spotting train spotting and sin city were both in middle school okay well since
it's in city was earlier than have you watched in city recently
Kayla does not hold it is the most you have to turn it on dude it's on Netflix
it is the most insane thing I've ever seen I watched it for the first time when
we were doing when we started the gun city noir campaign.
Yeah, watch it right now.
You gotta watch it dude.
It fucking, yeah, I don't even, it, it.
I just remember, I remember thinking Bruce Willis had swag.
Yeah.
Dude, it's just like, it just looks, like it looks so awful.
Just like all the bizarre like CGI, like color grading.
It makes like literally no sense at all.
There's a scene where that's supposed to be like cool, where the big guy with the like
square jaw.
Oh, Marv.
Yeah, he gets hit by a car like six times like the car just oh yeah
Yeah, and going back and he's flying like 50 feet into the air and then falling back and like bouncing off the car again
dude, it rules did movies all I do would play plays a
Serial killer with anime like like shiny glasses. Yeah, dude. I forgot Elijah wood was in that movie
Elijah wood for a while. He was trying to be just a real a regular actor
I mean, he's a horror guy, which is very funny. He produced like Mandy and all that shit. He's like a horror producer
I didn't know that. Yeah, it's like to be like one of like him or
Harry Potter who are the exact same guy in my brain?
But yeah, one you play you play a kid once and now everybody's like, yeah, you're yeah
It wasn't even a kid
Yeah, that's true, yeah
No, but yeah, he was he made the maniac remake he was in that too. He produced he's on Spectre vision is his production company
They do a bunch of like
Pretty creepy. I remember
How much he does that he will never ever escape
Right in Frodo. Yeah, right kind of sucks. Kind of the ultimate horror. Yeah
He should make a movie about that. Yeah
Yeah being a guy who it was in a fantasy movie and then trying to do Wilfred
Yeah, and then oh yeah, Wilfred dude Wilfred was funny
I I watched the um on what is funny cuz it's funny to hear like an Australian guy
Like a dog yeah beat no just say curse words
Yeah, I'm sniffing your butt and I can't eat chocolate
Yeah, it's funny an Australian dog
They should I watch the original on ISE thought the idea of an Australian dog is funnier than the show
Yeah, just think you're about an Australian dog
Yeah, it's like sniffing bones and and burying stuff and having an Australian accent makes me laugh
It's crazy how like every Australian show that gets adapted to like America
American audiences just like does better than the the slap
Review
The first season of review is like one of the best best TV shows. I think yeah, it's really really good
Again, probably is funnier in an Australian accent though. Oh, yeah
I tried to I tried to watch it and I don't remember it because I had both of
them on Hulu at the same time yeah in like 2015 uh-huh I'll have to rewatch it
I'm sure some Australian guys gonna be like oh you're gonna fucking love it I
don't think we have an Australian fan somebody keeps telling us to come to
Australia we definitely have Australian people at our size I know and it's a
I mean it's a huge country. We would do a show in Perth or whatever and the three
people that listen to the podcast in Australia would not be able to make it.
Right. I don't even know who these fucking guys are. Australian people
love internet irony. That's their thing. That's true. They all walk around
they call each other cunt all the time. True. They love bad words and stuff. That's
true. That's true. Cunt is just like my best friend in Australia. I've never heard
Patrick say cunt before yeah yeah I don't like it dude it doesn't fit you no I
don't like it back I don't like saying it there no matter how like fucking Irish I
am it doesn't sound right no I'm never you're not very Irish either I am I'm
like you're not you look like an Irish like indie singer right now cuz that
fucking hat but yeah you're not Irish yeah it doesn't your eye your Irish but
you're not I'm not wearing I'm not wearing a scally can you know he's
wearing a scally cap if I was wearing a scally cap I would look like no Boston
Irish you're not even from Austin you have to stop trying to steal fucking
Boston I am no you're not your mom is from there or something yeah well my mom
is so it's it's in my blood Boston Irish is in my blood no no I'm not stealing
Valor I'm you absolutely are you are I'm California Italian you are I am I'm
I'm Cambridge normal.
I'm United States of America.
Cameron is a scientist, because he's from Cambridge.
I'm my house son.
I am.
It's true.
I'm a guy.
I'm a guy with no job.
I'm the guy, Elijah Wood.
I'm the guy Elijah Wood, Spy Kids 3.
God, dude.
See, he played a kid in that.
No, he played the guy.
No, he played a guy.
He played the guy.
I've never been so quickly and swiftly owned.
Oh my god dude.
I'm so dumb.
I didn't even think about the guy.
I didn't even think about the guy part.
I didn't know adults were allowed in that thing.
Except for the grandpa, who I love in that movie.
Ricardo Multoban, Khan.
The best part of that movie is when he learns how to walk.
And he's like, "I can walk, I can run."
And then they're like, "Grandpa, we need you to help save my sister."
And then he just runs away on the moon.
He's like, "I don't care."
I love Spy Kids, but I fucking hated Sharkboy and Lava Girl.
Wait, my favorite part of the guy from Spy Kids 3 is if you go-
Is his penis.
Yeah.
Let's go!
Woo!
If you go to the Spy Kids wiki and look up the guy, there's a section that says quotes,
And it's "I'm the guy, the guy when he introduces himself" and "Cake, the guy right before his
death."
Yeah, he really only had two lines in that movie.
Well, he also says "Nothing is unwinnable.
The guy, 40 seconds before he succumbs to the unwinnable level."
Those are his three quotes.
Yeah, nothing's unwinnable except for the game which you two just lost.
Oh my god.
Come on, dude.
Come on.
Don't fuck with me.
I'm fucking on a roll today.
I'm a train.
I saw Spy Kids 3D at Chunkies.
Oh yeah, dude.
Is that your own body?
I only went to Chunkies one time.
Chunkies was so cool.
What is Chunkies?
Chunkies is a movie theater
that's also a restaurant in New Hampshire
and in the greater like--
Every movie theater is a restaurant.
Popcorn, pretzels, Slurpee.
No, they serve you food, you have like a menu and stuff.
You get a menu and you have a waiter
and he interrupts the movie.
There's not a menu.
The waiter interrupts your movie
and he asks, he goes, "What can I get for you?"
- That's the worst job in America.
- We only carry Pepsi products.
- That is more dangerous than Alaskan crab fisher.
- Yeah. (laughs)
- That is fucking horrible, dude.
- Dude, it's a great place if you're like eight years old,
but if you go to Chunky's when you're like 18
and you're seeing the Deadpool movie
and you get way too high on a Monday
and you see the Deadpool movie at noon
and it's other guys your age and older
who also have the day off eating chicken nuggets.
- There was a place in my hometown called Cinema Grill,
which was similar, it was like a,
just a movie theater restaurant.
And my dad loved, it wasn't even upscale,
like it was like chicken fingers.
Like my dad loved the chicken fingers
and we would go every couple weeks.
And it closed down and I guess my dad didn't know
because we like tried to go one day to watch some fucking movie in 2006 and we
pulled up and it was like closed for business they had like a sign in the
door and my dad I just remember him going like
cuz he loved the chicken tenders damn this they were his fucking favorite did
movie theaters that serve food is the stupidest fucking thing just eat food
before you go to the movie theater yeah right well then you get there if you
wanna if you want to eat a meal in a like in a movie theater I think you're a
psycho I don't want anything to do with you I I don't know I mean popcorn maybe
and like you know yeah I said a meal this conversation would divide between
me and Cameron versus Patrick. Who would have ever thought that?
Differing opinions here. I'm gonna I'm yeah it's disruptive to the movie and I
I don't have a table and I don't and it's fucking it's loud
It's a lot of smelling smells up the place with all the food smell, you know
And it's and that would be why if it was all like it was all like katsu curry and like yeah
Fried rice and shit. Yeah, just a tonka. It's like so expensive to just eat at home or like eat somewhere else first
No, it's not ever nice it's nice you you like to watch art house horror movies, I don't like
- I like to watch house bar movies.
- And eat dust.
You sit there, you eat lint and little things
out of your pocket while you watch wax.
- I'll get popcorn sometimes at the movie theater,
but I won't get anything else.
- You don't even like going to the movie,
you like watching movies at home in a dark room.
- I don't like going to the movie theater.
I do like watching movies in your cube.
- Watching movies in my cube.
- You like going out to the shed and watching movies.
- I wasn't, I would, there is no,
any, no movie theater experience can compare
to getting really, really high
and then just sitting in your bedroom
and watching a movie and getting too scared in the middle
and then falling asleep.
- That's what every movie theater experiences.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Me too.
- That's different, no, you have to be completely alone.
- I have been, every time--
- You can't interface with the movie,
you can't have sex with the movie correctly
if there's other people in the theater.
- You like to have sex with movies?
- Yeah, you have to really understand its entire--
- Yeah, what's your favorite movie to have sex with?
- The girl one.
- Into Mama Tambien, Brokeback Mountain,
those kind of movies?
- No.
- Yeah, that is what you like.
like yeah yeah you do that you go and you stick your wiener into the hole of the
projector into the vagina of the project no that's what you like to do I don't do
it with the projector so yeah you did what do you do with the screen my
computer you don't have a computer I have a he has a flashlight under it's like
docked to his computer that's a flashlight so I can see the keyboard but
I'm trying to pause the movie
on the back of it but it's not a flashlight it's a flashlight it's a
reverse it's a Na'vi from avatar pussy yeah it's a bunch of hair
they don't have that they just have hair yeah no you bunch up that's what you do
you go to locks for love and you're like I have cancer can you give me a wig of real human
hair you're one of those people who... yeah sure here you go and you bunch it up in your hand and you
just fuck you jack off with it and then you're basically the Na'vi. Yeah you order an
avatar fleshlight because you sit watched avatar and got so turned on they just
send you a wig they had they had one I remember that oh I'm sure you do
remember it I remember it yeah we're buying it how much was it it was $200
and I had to hide it from my parents yeah I didn't buy the avatar fleshlight
I know that none of us ever had a fleshlight did you ever have a friend
you at a flashlight? No, but I knew one of my little brother's friends was...
He had like a party at my parents house and he was like...
Fleshlight party? Yeah, fleshlight party. Or no no no, yeah he was just telling us about how he...
Pass it to the left!
[Laughter]
He was telling us about how he knows how to make a homemade fleshlight.
A homemade fleshlight?
That's a vagina.
With like a toilet paper tube and a rubber glove.
Yeah, I got an idea for a homemade fleshlight.
You put a pie in the toilet.
My only person I ever knew who had a fleshlight besides my friend's dad, which I think I've
definitely told that before on the podcast, where my friend, she like showed it to me
in like her dad's closet.
She was like, "Look at this shit."
And then her dad walked in right then, and he's a pastor.
He's a pastor and he's like, "What are you guys doing?"
And she was like, "We're looking for a flashlight."
And then she got like chewed out for an hour, and then he came and sat next to me on the
couch and cried to me.
And he was like, "I'm so sorry you had to see that."
I was like, "I don't fucking care, man.
Fuck whatever you want."
Hey man, hey man, as long as you give me a turn, I don't give a shit.
As long as you're happy.
No, the only person besides that that I knew out of fleshlight was my cousin who is now
in jail for peeping Tom.
Did you just spit out water?
No, I was taking a jewel hit while he fucking said that.
Yeah, dude.
In jail for peeping Tom.
He might be out of jail now.
I don't know.
Obviously, I haven't seen him.
He's gonna come peep on you now that you said that.
His name's Chris.
He's peeping on you right now.
They should call it peeping whatever the person's name was when they get arrested.
His name's Chris and he sounds so much like Kermit the Frog that when...
Peeping Chris, Peeping Kevin.
Sounds so much like Kermit the Frog that everybody in high school called him Kermit the Frog.
And then he took it on as like a cool white boy rapper moniker and went by Crispy Kermit.
Crispy Kermit!
Crispy Kerm
Just I'm imagining just a rapper named Kermit who raps about instead of like shooting people he raps about spying on girls a
Crispy Kermit is what you call it when you forget to clean your flashlight
Yeah, dude shout out to Chris he's the fucking man I think he was diagnosed with autism late in life, okay
Crispy Kerm dude, that's such a good fucking name.
Peeping Kermit?
*laughter*
He's just looking for his Miss Piggy dude.
Yeah.
Anyway, he walks.
Hey, I need to, I need to...
Ma'am, can I just look through your window for a little bit?
Ma'am, leave your, leave your window open a night.
Ma'am, seri- please? Can I, can I look through?
I think he actually, I think it was like more, I think he, I think it was a panty raid, like Spongebob style.
Oh, he did a panty raid?
I think he did a panty raid. I think he like got into a girl's house and stole her clothes. Oh, that's worse
Do you guys have any flashlights of pigs
Yeah, I just want I just want a flesh like that
I'll take one one pig and one Fozzie bear, please
He Kermit would never fuck Fonzie. Fuck Fonzie
Suck his dick dude Kermit would never fuck front for a free Frozy get over here and let me suck your dick
But did he
Would you guys ever have that done? Would you ever have your penis modeled? If like we could probably I feel like we could sell two
of those
You know you still does you could sell them not any of us. Everybody would be pretty disappointed in my penis, dude
Yeah, yeah, just like it goes it people have like a left hook or right hook mine goes down like Snape's nose. I
Swear to God dude, it's like I've been having it's like I've been like training with an anvil on my
It slopes down.
It's trying to drag you to hell, dude.
It is.
It really is, man.
It's just looking for water.
It's evolution, dude.
My dad's penis couldn't reach and my penis just got a little closer to all the bugs on
the ground that it wants to eat up.
All the ants.
Just suck them up like a vacuum cleaner?
You suck them up like an anteater, man.
Yeah.
Do anteaters only eat ants?
I don't know.
You think that gets boring?
No.
You think they love it every time?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Every single time they're like, "Nice, another ant."
Man, I mean, like, think about how excited a dog gets for, like, just, like, shitty cereal
every single day.
Or just shit.
Twice a day.
Yeah, exactly.
That's true.
Yeah, animals have no taste.
Yeah.
It's true.
We're way cooler than animals.
Animals love to eat the trash.
I think I'm gonna get a cat.
That's true.
Like this week.
Yeah?
Yeah.
What kind?
Uh, based on the ones that my wife is sending me on Instagram, a very sad, traumatized old cat.
Yeah?
Yeah, 'cause she just sends me every-
That pisses dust?
She sends me every fucking day some picture of a cat with cloudy blue eyes, and it's like, "This one's name is Bobo. Bobo got shot out of a cannon in a Taiwanese circus.
Do you want him in your house?
It's like, no dude, but is he free?
Okay, I guess I'll take him.
Who cares?
Yeah, exactly.
You're gonna experience the feeling
that you get when you own a cat.
You're gonna--
You're gonna experience the feeling
you get when you own a cat, pal.
You're gonna become, I was gonna say--
'Cause you know if you get a cat,
you're gonna experience having a cat, Taylor.
I was gonna say cat dad,
but I didn't wanna sound like a fucking loser.
You are.
You are a cat dad.
I mean, just the fact that that's what you were gonna say
kind of confirms it yeah it's honestly even even lamer that you just wouldn't
even say it yeah but you that you wanted to fight your instinct to say cat dead I
feel like this is worse than what you would say this is worse than what you
would say if you were actually gonna make fun of me for saying cat dead so I
should I just fucking said it absolutely worse mm-hmm um cuz now you're
analyzing my thoughts yeah yeah I go psychoanalyze yeah when you fucking
analyze me yeah I don't you want to fuck my mother and you're going to believe
you me damn we have a list today which is the top ten silliest ideas for movies
oh we're doing that one first yeah all right I feel like we I feel like we can
one-up these also I think this one's fine yeah we can kind of plot them out
- We can use our beautiful minds.
- We have three beautiful strange minds
that we can combine.
- Our savant, our Charlie Kaufman minds.
- Yeah.
- We can turn these into-- - Well, I'm not a savant.
You two are savants.
- I definitely am an idiot savant.
- No, I'm just a genius.
I'm not a savant.
- Yeah, no, Cameron's too smart to call himself a savant.
- Caleb, you're a suck off.
- Cameron is so smart.
- I'm so smart, dude. - You're a suck off.
- Dude, I just called you smart,
and you called me a suck off?
- Yeah.
- 'Cause he's sucking you off
smart you are you sucking off your brain man what the shit hmm you suck dude you
suck no you do dude you're a sucker I I'm awesome you're an idiot suck off no no I
don't suck off idiots idiots I've never sucked anything off dude ah great I gotta go to the
fucking factory and suck off an idiot gotta suck off an idiot today yeah we got
another idiot in we need hey Johnson we got another idiot we need you to suck
Why don't we get any fucking geniuses in here?
What does this have to do with what GMC makes?
It's just the way it goes.
You start at the bottom sucking off idiots in the mail room.
And then you get to the top building a Silverado.
Yeah, sucking off idiots in the C-suite.
The GMC Silverado.
Hey, Peterson, if you make one more mistake, we're sending you to the idiot closet and
you don't want to know what happens to you in there.
Alright, we'll tell you, you have to shuck a bunch of people off.
It's exactly what you've been doing.
Number one silliest idea for a movie, the drawing of paint.
That's a good title for a movie.
That's like a Yorgos Lanthimos movie.
Yeah, exactly.
Where it would be about a very boring lesbian relationship and nothing would happen.
Well no, it would be about two lesbians who are sisters who gradually cut off different
parts of their bodies every night and then which one is your ghost lanthimos
but it's filmed the film gradually spins around
he's that guy's voice you were doing earlier
oh okay yeah you know he made the lobster and uh oh got it got it and shit he made
the lobster and the mobster i i don't know i've never i i really i've
realized i'm not a movie person like i like watch movies but i don't like
i like the favorite the thing is i watch my favorite
I watched the whole movie and none of my favorite stuff showed up.
[Laughter]
There's no guns in any of his movies.
Actually, there is in Killing a Sacred Deer, I think.
Yeah, how are they gonna kill the deer?
That's true.
I think, um, yeah, I'm bad at, like, I don't really even remember any movies that I watch.
Like, the only reason I remember anything from Usual Suspects is because I watched it last night
and I remember thinking, like, I have to remember this movie.
'Cause every movie, I just have, like, the worst memory.
Yeah.
Yeah, me too.
The only reason I watch a bunch of movies is to like
Quell my my like list and ranking autism is so if I watch movies, I don't have to make spreadsheets all day
That's the same part of my brain to just be able to mark like have seen this movie like check it off on a list
Well, you do you do reviews - I don't yeah, that's just to keep track of it though. Yeah
the drawing of paint
Well, I mean it's safe to say it's not a good movie. Yeah drying of paint. It's got like
Fucking it's got some like big-name actor and then some actor who was on like a British TV show for a long time
And now they're finally like this is trying to do an American accent. Yeah
Being like they way I need I need your help help
Opening my car. I think he has the worst American accent. Yeah, you doctor strange the whole time
"Give me a cheeseburger, please."
There's no like, there's no...
"I'll take a cheeseburger at McDonald's."
He's not doing like, there's no...
It's not like where they pick
like a state to base their accent
off of. It's like he listened to...
It sounds like an Indian guy making fun of how Americans
talk. Yeah. Like doing like a
comedian impression.
It sounds like he listened to Microsoft,
Sam, and then was just like, "Well,
that's, yeah, that's American." "I'm
Mr. Strange." "Ah, I'm a
football I'm the doctor who is strange and you need to help me get the portal
open I need a I need two portals I'm thinking of doing magic I'm doing math
magic and I'm and I'm the I'm gonna I'm I'm gonna kill my but he's also in a
Marvel movie so he's also just doing like so that's a thing that just
happened yeah wow yeah that didn't open Wow hmm he rocks dude number two is
already a movie it's the cobbler Chandler yeah that's true Patrick's
favorite thing to do on this podcast is to say his riff before reading what the
list item is so it makes no sense to anyone who's listening what do you mean
it's what you just do that all the time you say this next one is just like and
then say something but don't actually say what it is.
Nobody knows what you're talking about.
Number two is the shoe shop.
Yeah, the shoe shop. That's the cobbler with Adam Sandler.
See, that's the order
you're supposed to say the things in.
Alright, well I'm still, I'm growing, I'm learning.
I'm gonna... Every day you're getting worse
and worse, is the truth.
It is so funny to me that this pod, like, we're like
over a hundred episodes in and this is just,
like, the podcast is just like a
very gradual process of just like
gradually changing all the stupid things
we do into like some very slightly less stupid like ways to talk yeah like it's
getting better man yeah just like gradually you know like like learning
not to talk over each other yeah turd like which we still do so yeah we used
to that's true yeah those you were slaying first 30 episodes the evil the
dark 31 it's just the dark 31 it's just it's just three audio tracks and that
- That was before I was here.
- At the same time, yeah.
That got way worse as soon as I joined.
- I think after our Seeking Derangements episode,
Pat is either gonna get more or less like Jacques
from Seeking Derangements.
He's either learning, or he's learning either poorly
or very well from that.
- Yeah.
- Go listen to that, by the way.
- Yeah, you guys should go listen.
- Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was gonna plug it at the end.
- Listen to Seeking Derangements in general.
- They're so funny.
The shoe shop is a, I think that'd be a good idea for a movie.
- Yeah, it's the cobbler.
- Well, here's the description of the,
here's the description of the movie
by the creator of the list, okay?
This is the plot of The Shoe Shop.
A man goes to buy new shoes and goes on
a not so thrilling journey through the city.
Once he is there, he must battle swarms
of annoying little children to get to the shop assistant
and find the perfect shoe.
But wait, something terrible has happened.
The man has no money.
He quests back to his house, finds the money,
and gets back at the shop in time for lunch.
The happy ending is where the man walks out of the shop
with a nice new pair of shoes.
- Okay.
- Whoa.
- I thought it was gonna be like a shoe version
of Be Kind Rewind.
- Yeah.
- You know?
- I like that they had to recreate a Jordan one.
- They have to recreate all the different shoes.
- And this guy--
- A magnet came through and took off all the shoes.
None of the shoes work anymore.
You can't walk in these.
Oh crap, I can't even move.
- And they just, they rent out pieces of paper
with shoes drawn on them to people.
- Yeah, they rent them out.
- Yeah.
- You should be able to rent,
you probably can rent shoes, huh?
- Absolutely.
I like that in this plot-- - But every shoe shop
should have that option.
- The creator of this list assumes
that the shoe shop is filled with children.
Like that's the kind of people who go to a shoe shop,
is annoying little children.
- That's true.
I used to love going to a shoe shop when I was a kid,
trying on some like, just the biggest shoes they have.
- Getting audios.
- Give me a size, could you have a size 17 in these?
And then just walking around.
That's the best go in a Burlington Cove factory and finding the size 22 shoes.
Yeah and then just walking around with big clown shoes.
Yeah.
Slapping them hard on the linoleum floor.
Or like the like the ruby red like Rock-A-Wear loafers.
One thing I don't like about Foot Locker is like you go there and the people who work
there try to like.
They're wearing referee uniforms.
Well that's they try to like cool guy you and be think like make you kind of like judge
you for your shoe picks and then they're dressed like referees the whole time.
Well they're they're mediating your shoe decision. That's true yeah. Yeah they blow
the whistle if you try to buy a shoe they don't like. They give you a red card if you buy the
wrong shoe. Yeah. And then you have to go to timeout and then when you come out
you're actually just playing soccer. Mm-hmm yeah. There's a comment on...
There's a secret soccer game in the back of a footlocker and you're invited.
This is the movie.
So this is interesting.
A comment on this from dislike my comment says, "I'd love to see a sequel as this is
my favorite movie from 2015."
Isn't that the Cobbler come out in 2015?
I don't know.
What is your obsession with this guy, Adam Sandler?
No, the Cobbler is from 2014.
I just looked it up.
Oh, okay.
That long ago, dude?
Yeah.
Fucking Christ.
That's crazy.
Yeah.
Time just keeps on slipping.
Pretty crazy.
Into the future.
the future yeah someone says give me some damn LeBron 12 that's right that's how
the movie would do really well as you remember how like the Yu-Gi-Oh movie and
the Pokemon movies would come with free trading cards
Oh come with free shoes or they give you some shoes to wear or with Yu-Gi-Oh
cards and like only glasses and then you drop them in a bin on your way out
out there only adidas Kobe twos yeah yeah there you everyone's just just walking
in circles around the theater just to like break in the shoes and then you
sit there and that's how yeah I mean it's like a Tarantino thing it's like
that's how you have to enjoy the movie this way yeah you have to be wearing
some some some Kobe - yeah number three revenge of the toys okay I love what
other toys taking their revenge for Cameron's gonna read the description one
night a boy is attacked by all his childhood toys luckily he is armed for a
zombie apocalypse will he make it out of his house alive and destroy all the toys
this movie is rated M I mean this is kind of toy soldiers or small soldier this is
every small soldiers there's some this is every single movie ever actually is
every movie yeah it's pretty much all the movies there's a guy there's a guy
named there's a horror producer named Charles band who was just like absolutely
for some reason just completely obsessed with toys attacking people and just like
almost every movie ever made was about evil toys. He made a movie called Dolls.
He made the Puppet Master movies. He made a movie called Tourist Trap about like
mannequins coming to life. He made a movie called I think Elves maybe. They're
just like literally there's like at least ten. Did he make that Robin Williams movie? Yeah
Flubber yeah. Yeah. No I don't know which one you're talking about. One hour photo. It's just so
funny just be like a guy who's like yeah I'm just gonna make movies about toys I
think that's my thing and just like make the same movie over and over again. There was a movie called
toys I think. What's his name Robert Rodriguez? His name is Robin Williams.
Robin Robert Rodriguez okay. Roger Regis. Oh no it was directed by Barry
Levinson different guy. You freaking idiot. It's a cool name.
Thomas Edison. Thomas Edison yeah I prefer Nikola Tesla car. Yep. Yeah. Number
for a blank screen a blank screen a blank screen what it's like waiting for the
movie to start whoa no one says the tickets cost two
million bucks no refund oh my god yeah that's right yeah it's a blank screen
movie the tickets cost two million bucks all the chairs or toilets with poop in
them that strange kid 42 comments still a better love story than Twilight
That's strangekid42. It's such a good username.
I know.
That's like the perfect use-
And he's 25 years old!
[Laughter]
Oh here- oh shit! Positron Wildhawk.
That's a name we haven't heard in a while.
In the words of Andy Parsons,
"A man once saw the story of a depressed loser having a wank,
then he knew what it was called. A blank screen."
Whoa.
It's called Black Mirror.
It was called Patrick the Movie.
No!
Yeah.
Yeah, you like to have a wank.
*laughter*
I'm having a wank right now and I'm Doctor Strange.
I'm Doctor Strange and I'm having a bloody wank.
You're slipping into Duke Nukem.
They have a wank now.
Are you having a wank?
*laughter*
British bloody tosser.
I'm gonna put my foot down a nonce's neck.
*laughter*
I'm eating a delicious plate of sheaves and flex.
Is that toad in the hole?
I love toad in the hole.
I'm making a delicious pot of queen's pussy.
That's queen's pussy, isn't it?
I'm Mr. Milk.
Duke Nukem is Harvey Milk. I'm Harvey Milk. I'm Harvey Milk. Ow.
The sad life of a pencil. Whoa. No. No. The life story of a pencil from the first
time it's being used to the point where it's too small for any use or gets
accidentally dropped in a wood chipper. That would be like a human life.
that would be like a short 3d movie that would be like somebody's like 3d yeah
like their student film yeah we all start out as a pencil and then we just die in
a race yeah somebody would make that yeah I would make that in like blender and
then get it gets bought for like seven billion dollars by Pixar and then they
develop it for ten years and then say we don't the pencils don't exist anymore so
we can't make this yeah and Tom Hanks gets me tood in the middle of the voice
recording so they're like yeah sorry we just had to scrap it sorry thanks to a
certain user we now have a script for this movie is a comment but I don't
someone make it I guess so oh so this is hold on this is the this is pretty good
honestly this is like a little excerpt from the script the YBT doctor says he
was just like the others number two they called him hey dude the humans are just
using you you have no sentimental value why couldn't his parents have been led
pencils he was nearing the end of his life and was too short to stick himself
in a pencil sharpener oh how he longed to stick it in and keep it there forever
and better better yet she swallowed he shavings
that's what was he trying to have sex movie sounds like it's rated M uh-huh
that's a rated-m movie for sure more pencils please you know number six the
The journey of an old lady.
You got to stop saying that.
Jinx.
No, you're jinx.
You'll be having a, you're having a Patrick moment.
Okay.
Here's now here, this kind of is a paradigm shift right here.
This comment from pet sounds.
The funny thing about this list, besides awful movies, every single one of these
ideas would make a fabulous Monty Python sketch.
I love Monty Python.
Oh, my father was in Monty Python.
my name is duke please
do you think that you know i don't know if you would fuck girls together and
they would keep switching out of being like and now for something completely
different
uh...
yeah i guess i think that
this fucking eric idol comes out naked with the way gone
well my penis is out
the law
or
all right now
What my penis is out? It's stiff as a wood plank
It's dead as a rock
Number seven sparkly blue unicorns on a quest to planet Hufflepuff. Yeah, okay sounds fucking awesome. Yeah, that's Caleb's
There's some IP problems there, but yeah Hufflepuff we'd have to change to
project it's a stoner movie. Like Mac and Devin go to high school.
Right? Mac and Devin go to space. Mac and Devin go to planet Huff and Puff.
Uh-huh. Oh my god. Mac and Devin go to the
planet Puff Puff Pass. Yeah. It says the atmosphere is almost completely THC.
Well the best part of Mac and Devin is like the is Wiz Khalifa doing fake
science. Yeah. Hey Caleb you should you should
read this comment. No, keep going, sorry. No, keep talking. Just Mac it like, have you
guys seen Mac and Devin go to high school? I have not. I've seen the end of it. The, the, the
whole thing is like, apparently weed is like an endless like renewable energy
source at the end. And Wiz Khalifa is like, we needed a, we, I created a
renewable energy source that needed a catalyst. And the catalyst, we knew it had
some three letters in it and it turns out they were THC. So fucking sick. It's awesome. I
watched Wiz Khalifa on a Call of Duty Warzone stream the other day and he was with this
guy XQC who's like this this like Swedish guy and Wiz just hated this dude so much.
They were, Wiz was there, he was supposed to be like raising money for some charity
But he was like getting really drunk and so the guy asked him he was like he was like
Yo, whiz how much money do you want to raise for the stream?
And whiz was like man. Honestly, I don't care if we raise a single dollar
And then xqc they started talking about like xqc was like so you have kids whiz what is that like to have kids and he's like
Do you have kids?
And xqc was like, I don't have kids yet
I'm afraid that if they come out, they will be little monsters."
And then there was like a long pause, and then Wiz was just like,
"Are you a monster?"
[laughter]
It's the greatest fucking shit I've ever seen. I watched it for like an hour and a half.
That's great.
Yeah, that rules.
You should--
Caleb, you're gonna really like this comment from SirSkeletorThe3rd.
You should read this one.
You think so?
Yeah.
Let's see.
A sparkly blue Nazi unicorn named Hans Reich and his friends Fiedrich Panzermouth and Joe
go into space and battle all kinds of creatures such as humans, Jewish aliens, and yes of
course Soviet alien dragons breathing blood in the sky in order to save planet Hufflepuff
from evil Joseph Stalin dragon.
Rated R for Glore, Blood, Extreme Violence, Extreme Language, and Anti-Semite Views.
(laughter)
- Can you imagine?
Like a movie that's rated R,
usually like the newest Will Ferrell movie comes out
and it's rated R, but just for anti-Semite views.
- Yeah, I'm waiting on the Red Band trailer for that one.
- Yeah, it's like, you know how they have like the,
like the South Park bigger, longer, and uncut,
and it does that like cut, it's like bigger, longer, uncut.
- Yeah.
- And it's like, it's just like,
Unicorns, dragons, anti-semitism.
Yeah, or like a 2006 comedy like American Pie, but then the DVD comes out and they have the anti-semitic version.
Unrated, anti-semitic edition.
Over 40 minutes of unused footage.
I heard they're giving every single movie an Ike cut.
A David Ike, David Ike's cut. He's re-editing every movie.
(laughing)
Number eight, War of Glue.
- That's pretty good.
- I really like the comment on this one
from Blue Topaz Ice Vanilla that says,
it sounds like a Hunger Games rip off.
- It does.
- Yeah, Glue Games.
- War of Glue.
- Sounds like a, like a,
like an animal rights documentary about like horses.
- Yeah.
- War of Glue.
A battle starts in a future time and people only have glue products to defend themselves.
Who will win?
You know, people thought, this guy thought the future was going to be war of glue, but
nowadays it's looking more like war of gluten, the way these hipsters are coming at the world.
Oh my god, yes.
It is like that.
Keep going.
Make it happen, folks.
You know, why didn't the hipster eat his muffin?
Because he ate it before the gluten was cool.
Oh my god, dude.
They're going to put that in the movie, I heard.
I heard they're putting that line in the script right now.
They're putting the war of gluten in the movie.
We should rail against hipsters more.
Yeah.
Freaking...
podcast about list?
Hey, nice skinny jeans.
You gay bitch.
What's that?
The podcast about the list to get into the indie rock show?
Yeah, the list to get into your vinyl coffee shop.
You fucking nerd.
Those skinny jeans have some small pockets.
pockets what do you keep in there how cool you are yeah what do you keep in
there a soy latte yeah so what do you keep in there the list of your your your
arts degree my dad used to yeah hey man what are you Obama yeah what are you
oh but what are you Obama America are you Obama's friend or something are you
friends with Obama hey what's up Michelle Obama what's up Michelle Obama
nice skinny jeans I see your penis in them Michelle Obama my dad when I was
Just growing up, my younger brother would go to Starbucks
and get any frozen drink there,
and my dad would just always own him.
When he would bring it back, he'd be like,
"Hey, nice frappa girl-a-cino."
Damn.
And it was like, "Dad, can you watch it, dude?"
Yeah.
"Woo, cool it, Dave Attell."
"What's that about?
"Coming after your own kid like that?
"He can't even defend himself, dude."
Dude, he's a kid.
He's not Dave Attell.
"Dude, he's not the joke writer you are.
Frappa Garlaccino.
Oh my god, dude, just shut down Starbucks.
- Have you seen the--
- My dad had a conniption when they came out
with the unicorn frap.
- You're wearing a plaid shirt?
I hope you have a plaid day.
- Yeah.
- Like a bad day.
- You wear a plaid shirt 'cause you can't get laid?
- Chirt?
Mr. Hipster?
Oh, I'm sorry, Mr. Hipster.
Did I offend you?
Oh, I'm sorry.
- Hey, hipster guy, you wearing DC shoes?
Yeah, what's that? Because you love the clowns in Congress?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
I see you wearing a flannel. I wish I could change the damn channel.
*laughter*
Have you ever seen the, uh...
Oh, so you're wearing, you're covered in tattoos?
I'm gonna throw a rock at you.
Or we're, this is my anti-hipster rap I'm working on.
Have you seen the Dennis Miller, or Dennis Leary, uh, coffee bit?
No.
Yeah, where he's just like, "What happened to coffee?
What happened to a cup of coffee?
Now that you put milk and sugar in it, what are you, Chinese?"
The punchline to that joke is, "www.whatthefuck.com!"
Plug in his good friend Mark Maron, dude.
Yeah.
Hey, hipster, I see you grew up.
Have you seen Dennis Leary's coffee bit where he takes a sip of coffee and says, "Pow, I
just shit my pants?"
Hey hipster, I see you've grown a giant beard.
To me, that seems very weird.
Oh my god, the anti-hipster rapper?
Yeah.
Damn.
Yes.
Keep going anti-hipster rapper.
What about Bacon?
Oh, so you like Bacon?
You must be fakin'.
Let's go!
Let's fucking go, dude!
Push a hipster down the stairs.
Oh, you're wearing, you're wearing.
wearing oh my god oh my god you're wearing so you're wearing those hipster
styled glasses I wish you all would fall onto your asses yeah you got you're on
Facebook I got my face in a book yeah and what's that what's that a stylish
hat you are crap that's right that's right if I get edited I would say
stylish cap you are crap no I mean that well they don't wear caps it's the thing
you'd sat on your neck and an infinity scarf I'm gonna do an infinity barf
yeah nice nice skinny jeans I'm gonna do a they don't seem very clean thingy thing
to hurt you I'm gonna put my ding-a-ling on you hipster yeah hot topic how about
I'm how about you're not you're not in the office because you don't have a job
you like music that's underground I will make I'll play funeral music for you
because you'll be and you're going underground and the coffin you're at NYU
well I'm in the bayou cuz I'm a real I'm a working man
yeah modest mouse you like modest mouse how about I how would I take off my
wife's plows yeah you like you like passion pit well you can smell my ass
Mumford and Sons, when you see me you better Mumford and fucking run.
You better run from my gun.
You better, I'm gonna put my, my bun in your tum.
I'm gonna point my gun at your son.
Grizzly bear, I'm gonna...
pull you up by your underwear.
*laughter*
Oh my god.
Deathcap for- oh, you're listening to
Deathcap for Cutie?
I'm gonna- how about I get my-
my death-
I'm gonna shoot some death gas from my booty.
*laughter*
(laughter)
- Oh, so you're always listening to Vampire Weekend?
I'm gonna smoke some dank fire weeds, man.
- That's right.
- That's pretty good, right?
Right?
Like, you could just put that in a song.
You don't even have to change that at all.
- You listen to Pomplamoose, I'm taking a dumpy poop.
- TV on the radio?
You're listening to fun and I'm shooting you with my gun.
Mm-hmm.
That's right.
R.E.L.
Pink, yeah, you're a real stink.
These are just getting better and better.
Yeah.
A Guy Falls Over, it was the next movie.
Yeah, it's the next movie.
Which sounds like a hipster band.
Yeah, a guy falls over, how about I'm gonna hit you with the Mars Rover?
I got some fries, come over.
[Laughter]
Yeah, I would love it. They should make a hipster movie.
Yeah.
The people who made the Lego movie are gonna make the hipster movie.
Yes!
No, the people who made Scary Movie.
It's set in Silver Lake in a coffee shop that's also a vinyl record store.
and it's got Aubrey Plaza and Michael Cera.
- Yes.
- And Dwight Schrute is there.
- Yeah, Dwight Schrute is there and he's saying false.
- Yeah.
- He's saying false.
- Yeah, he's like, can I, yeah, he's the barista.
And somebody says, yeah, can I get a black coffee?
And he says, false.
- Yeah.
- We only have girl coffee that's just milk.
- And we put a single coffee bean in it,
like a toy in a cereal box,
and you have to find it.
- And then, yeah.
And then Dennis, he gets so mad.
- Oh, and you know who Dennis is.
- Yeah, and Dennis says, "You're a real asshole.
"You're an asshole."
- And then he says, "I'm an asshole!"
- And then Louis C.K. comes up and he's like,
"I stole that joke, or you stole that joke from me."
- You stole that joke from me.
- You actually stole that asshole joke from me.
And he says, "How about a cup of black coffee?"
- Yeah.
- And that's the end of the movie.
- Mocha Frappa What the Fucka.
- Yeah.
- Moka-cino. - Get in your fuckin' pants, dude.
Moka come in your butt?
Cino?
Yeah, how 'bout he's wearing Cinos and they're skinny.
- Yeah, oh my God. - Yeah, there we go.
- Yeah, I want a coffee that's mini, a small coffee,
and you're wearing skins that are genny.
Genny, jeans are genny. (laughing)
- It's true, man.
- It's just a complete shit.
You have a mustache tattooed on your finger?
I'm gonna make you smell my finger.
I have a rust rash that I got from working in the yard.
You bitch.
Mustache on your finger? Yeah.
I'm gonna go home and watch The Ringer.
Oh, you're at...
Oh, you're at Starbucks?
I'm in the car drunk.
(laughing)
- Oh, fuck.
- Number 10 is Rain.
There's tons of Rain movies on YouTube.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah, you just search Rain movie.
- I watch a movie about Rain all the time.
- They already made a movie about a man made out of Rain.
- Yeah, we did. - Max Rain.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
That was the movie.
That was the movie, it was Max Rain.
I was thinking of Rain and Gain.
Yeah.
That's the one where it's Rain Man and Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson.
[Laughter]
They made Rain Go too.
Dude, imagine fucking, imagine Pain and Gain, but it's Dustin Hoffman as Rain Man instead of Mark Wahlberg.
Instead of Milk Wahlberg?
Milk Wahlberg. That's a different guy.
That's what he puts in the freaking, that's what Dennis Leary puts in his coffee.
- No, Mark Wahlberg is one of the normal,
he's not a hipster.
- No, Dennis Miller puts Milk Wahlberg in his coffee,
or Dennis Leary.
- Dennis Miller.
- Dennis Milker.
- Wow.
- Milk Walk, the milk man, Dennis.
- Let's see Dennis's milkers.
- The milk man walks through your berg
and he delivers milk.
- I wanna see Dennis Miller's Dennis milkers.
- Yeah, Mark Wahlberg, more like Milk Walk.
- Men.
- Men, but.
(laughing)
Milk Walkman.
Milk Walkman?
Yeah.
Milk Walkman.
Who's Milk Walkman?
He's the guy who walks around, he walks to your house.
He's the milk man?
Hey, you're kinda like Milk Walkman.
You know, you remind me of this actor.
I don't remember his name, he used to be a rapper too.
He put the herd on a Vietnamese man in South Boston once.
I think his name is Milk Walkman.
He was in the Milky Bunch?
Yeah, he was Milk Walkman.
Yeah, he was milky milk in the milky bunch.
Yeah, nowadays it'd be soy milky soy milk in the soy milky bunch.
Yeah.
And the soy milky brunch.
Yeah, nowadays his freaking name is Oat Walkman, the way things are going.
That's right.
Almond Walkman.
This is so far away from Mark Wahlberg.
Yeah, Mark Wahlberg, we're like Oats Almond nowadays.
Yeah.
Just complaining to another guy on the train just saying that.
He just moves to another car.
[Laughter]
Uh, let's check out the contenders.
Yeah.
The 10 hour film where you watch someone sleep extended edition.
That's a thing.
Isn't that a, uh, from an Andy Warhol thing?
Yeah.
Didn't he do movies where his boyfriend slept?
And he, you know he like never had sex or something?
Really?
Yeah.
I nowadays would see it seems like we more have candy warheads than Andy
Warhol god-willing yeah nowadays Andy Warhol would have a painting of a cup of
coffee yeah you'd have a painting yeah he'd have a paint exactly it would be
Amy's soup it would be Amy's organic black yeah yeah it wouldn't be Campbell's
It'll be Mrs. Campbell's.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
'Cause Campbell's was too offensive and they had to change the mascot.
To Mrs. Campbell's.
Yeah.
That'd be funny if they came out.
They're changing it to Man's Hell.
That's right.
'Cause that's what the modern world is.
It'd be funny if the Redskins just changed their name to the Mrs. Redskins.
[laughs]
They're like, "Yeah, we fixed it. It's a girl now."
Yeah.
That's--oh, wait, that wasn't what you guys were complaining about?
Yeah, the Pocahontas is the beautiful Pocahontas is the Elizabeth Warren's
Number 12 sexy spoons we got to get Seth Rogen on this one. Yeah
The spoons are actually having sex
Sexy spoons and then we could get like a lot of
Someone says this is stories to get later as I scroll down
Damn, I'm on that weird part of the top tens again. Yeah number 12
Yeah, I'm on that weird part of the top 10 rated are for God knows why I'm going home to play Xbox
If the if the if the ticket taker at the movie theater does can't tell me why movies rated are I go home
Yeah
You can't tell me why this movie is rated R
No, I'm going home. Yeah, I'm going back to bed. I'm gonna go play number 21 is the life of gloves trilogy
Number 13 is time to eat a shoe
Tim is so bored. He decides to eat a shoe. That's pretty good
Honestly, it's not bad, dude. That's like that's like a Tusk style movie number 24 is Caillou the movie
Caillou rages war on his friends first Caillou buys illegal guns and goes to a nightclub
He gets super loaded on crackpot cocaine painkillers glue and every other drug his mom finds out and he murders his mom super bloody scene
He then gets in his dad's Lamborghini playing super explicit music
He gets out of his car and flirts with Dora the Explorer and kills her in the end
Everyone dies in Caillou's hometown in theaters December 19th 2020 Rolling Stone masterpiece
Spongebob movie 3 someone says this is already coming out. It's called. What a wonderful sponge
Oh here's a really good one number 31 who farted a butt story that'd be pretty
funny actually a butt's life is sad especially if it's constantly being
spanked that's so true so true I'm gonna I can't wait to see you guys again so I
can spank you both hey I'm gonna spank I'm gonna devise a new opportunity where
I can spank you.
And I'm gonna make money from it.
Number 45 is the Toilet Heroes.
That's a good one.
That's pretty good.
That's you guys.
Okay, now we get to number 49 and it's all, I think, it looks like it just all turns into
K-pop stuff.
Yeah.
How about number 54, the Broken iPod.
Oh, God.
The Secret Life of Justin Bieber?
Interesting.
Whoa.
What would that be?
Number 63, that one guy that can't stop talking.
Yeah.
That's called Patrick.
Yep.
Now, number 61 is called "The Stalker" and you know I might be mistaken but I think
somebody already made a movie like this.
The Stalker?
Yeah.
Who's Jake Short?
He just stares at the screen for three hours.
I don't think anybody's made that.
Number 68, Jake Short the...
Oh that's the kid from Ant Farm.
I was talking about the movie Stalker.
Phones the Musical?
Yeah that's pretty much every time I'm walking down the street nowadays.
On the comment on Phones the Musical, here are some of the songs.
It's a hard enough gigabyte.
The app will download tomorrow, somewhere over the firewall, and more.
Wow.
Number 73, the erotic adventures of the lollipop ladies.
I want to write Phones the Musical.
I'm going to send, I'm going to screenshot Phones the Musical and send it to Nolan because
I feel like he'll enjoy this.
Smells like teen Samsung Galaxy S7.
That's pretty good.
Yeah, you know, I feel like, I feel like that's, that's pretty good.
Where in the world are my apps?
Right?
You know?
no you got it I mean you got the the format down instead of good 311 it's 4
1 1 right that you know or 9 1 1 or scary part of the musical that's true did you
read number 38 I don't know it was 38 random people swearing in 3d basically
(laughing)
- Number 74 is doing it.
- Oh, come on, dude.
You had to go make it nasty at the end.
You had to go make it disgusting, come on.
Where happened to good old family values?
Black cup of coffee, no hipsters in sight.
- Yeah.
- I miss America.
- That's so true.
- Whip it up, is number 75.
(laughing)
Whip it up. Jake Short the musical. Onions. I made a song for it. Snow. Some kid just started
typing just stuff. Yeah. Just started typing just like random word association. Twilight
Six. Donuts falling on a screen. Birdemic and the Rim Crossover. Oh my god dude. That
would be so epic. Mr. Willy Wonka and the Sexual Innuendo Factory. Interesting. Willy
Willy Wonka's sexual factory?
The comment is, "Willy Wonka's probably a pedophile anyways, because if your first name is Willy."
Oh my god.
Wow, I didn't think of that.
Yeah, you cannot be around kids with a name like Willy.
No. They're gonna get the wrong idea.
Yeah.
They're gonna ask people, "What does his name mean?"
You gotta be Bill Wonka if you're gonna open up your store to kids.
Yeah, William Wonka.
I think you're right, dude.
No, even William's bad, 'cause that's got Willy in it. You gotta be Bill.
true or use your middle name your stinky middle name yeah the stinky middle all
right all right boys um it's been a great been a fun one subscribe to the patreon
since uh yeah scribe to the patreon subscribe to the patriot mines kind of
Mine's just H.W. Bush.
What?
You're what?
My Duke Nukem is George H.W. Busham.
And listen to Seeking Derangements. We just did it.
Oh yeah, we were just on Secret Derangements.
Oh yeah, check that out. We're gonna have some on during the rest of our time.
Secret Derangements.
Secret Deranged Men.
Secret Deranged Men, yeah.
They are.
our episode. That's a really good idea. I'll tell them to redo it. Yeah. Let's just redo it. Let's
re-record the whole episode. Yeah, we can do it. Yeah. All right. Bye everyone. All right. Bye.
*Dying*