You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- You're a crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Record.
(laughing)
Now I'm recording, yeah.
- Nice.
(laughing)
- I'm,
We all have sideways hats on.
Mine is,
mine's, I'm wearing it the best.
- I'm wearing a visor upside down and sideways.
- I'm wearing visors overlapping
so it just looks like a hat.
- I'm wearing shutter shades.
- I'm wearing like a Sherlock Holmes hat,
but I'm wearing it sideways.
- Nice.
- I'm wearing two big flaps on the side.
Put 'em down so my ears don't get cold.
- I'm wearing a beer drinking hat, right?
But it's soda.
I'm wearing a big gold chain and on the end it has Roadrunner and the Roadrunner actually
runs.
Whoa, dude.
Yeah.
I got like a big old Jamiroquai hat on but it's on my penis and I'm keeping it, I'm standing
it up with my penis.
I'm smoking a seven foot cigar.
Yeah, I have a very small hat.
It's a very small hat.
I have a little Newsies hat on and I'm in the musical, The Newsies.
i'm looking at seven foot long cigar
yeah i have a sombrero on
i have a sombrero on, there's guacamole in the middle and there's chips all around it
i'm actually in a spaceship
and i walk around the bus, i walk around the bus on my hands and knees and everybody gets a snack
because i'm doing my part for the protests
i'm wearing two electric guitars, one on the front one on the back
I have one.
Just walking around the protest with the sombrero with chips and salsa.
Just asking people if they're hungry in Speedy Gonzales voice.
Oh no.
Hey man, you hungry man?
That would not go well at all.
I think it would go well.
What do you mean?
I'm feeding the people.
I'm in big trouble because I'm so fucked dude.
night I went visiting my grandparents and my right before I left I was like going
over to a friend's house and I was like I'll grab a couple cigars from my
grandpa but he was in the bathroom so I just went to like his cigar chest and
just grabbed like the two stupidest like cheapest looking cigars I could find
one of which one of them was called Mark Twain and I had a picture of Mark Twain
on it and the other was it said JR and I was like okay.
Joe Rogan, he had that Joe Rogan cigar.
Nah dude, that wouldn't be tobacco dude, come on.
That's true, DMT.
They'd be crushed up on it pills.
Then I brought the cigars to my friend's house and we started smoking them and they were like
where'd you get these?
I was like I just stole them from my grandpa and then somebody looked up the cigars because
he was curious how much they were and the Mark Twain one was like six bucks right
but then the JR one was like a hundred and twenty-eight dollars it must have
been like a gift or like he was saving it for like the day I have a kid or so yeah
he was he was saving it for the day you get married yeah I just I just like
split it with three dumbasses they're coming they're coming to get you
You're guilty by association. Jesus fucking Christ. It's the CIA, the cigar
investigators. They're coming to get you, cigar investigating assholes.
Asshole. Asshole. Asshole. What are you guys up to besides smoking cigar? You packing?
Yeah dude, packing a big fat bowl. Yeah. Yeah, my fiancee every day asks if I'm
packing and I just send her and just yet another bowl I've packed next to a
giant pile of dirty clothes that has a peak like the like the mountain that the
Grinch lives on that's how tall it is yeah I got a I got a copy Tony Hawk's
Pro Skater 2x yeah 2xl when you play it whoo all right off to a great start yeah
yeah yeah yeah I've just been playing that baloney baloney hawk to excel yeah
yeah when you play it it's a Tony iron eagle pretty good yeah yeah yeah it's
Tony plays it's bony bony crotch yeah bony crotch one finally finally we got
some Cameron burns on here yeah just me saying you look racist and you saying I
look fat we've never real cuz I'm normal there's nothing you're not normal no you
are not normal we're afraid to make fun of you because of what you'll do yeah
we're afraid of your mind of powers you'll you'll have you're gonna do a
- Oh my God, he's talking, he's drinking water
while talking right now.
- Oh my God.
- I wasn't talking.
I was drinking water.
- You were just like, "Me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me."
- Quietly.
- You were doing, you were doing monumina.
- I would never do that.
- You were going, "La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la."
- No.
- That's the best, that's the best song of all time.
- That song is so catchy.
- It's the best Louis Armstrong song.
So good.
- That was Louis Armstrong, the little puppet that they had.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
But yeah, I've just been just packing today. We got all that money out for that damn realtor.
Shannon, that bitch, taking my money.
Excited to have-- That bitch, Carol Baskins. Yeah, Carol Baskins.
Carol Baskins, your realtor.
Yeah, she's feeding my money to the-- To her husband to plump him up.
To the tiger king. Yeah.
To plump up her husband to feed him to a child.
He's feeding my money to Netflix and I'm pissed off, dude.
Guys, I heard that Carole Baskin is a landlord now.
More like carible bas-gur-ous.
Yeah, right?
Yeah.
That's good, right?
That's facts.
More like cra-bomble-be-be-boo-be-be-boo.
More like crab-at-crabbles.
Yeah.
More like I don't care, ol' bat-shit.
It's good.
It's good now. Yeah sounds now. It just sounds like we're doing it as a bit
But now it just sounds like we're making like real Carol basket jokes. Yeah
No, it's funny to start doing this like four months after that documentary
Yeah, we're saying a caboo like nobody's talking about it anymore and we're like, I know yeah more like care boo-bobby boo
Yeah, more like more like cabo. We're like cabo. Wabo. Hell. Yeah, let's get down to cabo
Let's go to Wahoo's Fish Tacos in Carroll Basin.
Let's go to a Wah Wah in Kawa.
Yeah, more like that.
We should just start our own tiger murder farm or whatever.
Yeah, let's do it.
We should start our own Wah Wah.
Oh my god.
We get all the hoagies we want, all the free mountain dew.
Unlimited sandwiches, unlimited mountain dew, and ours would actually have Baja Blast.
And it would have another flavor called California Crush.
Crush.
We'd get our own Wawa exclusive Mountain Dew flavor
that they have.
Wawa Blast.
Yeah, okay.
And it tastes like a New Jersey steel mill.
It tastes like a used plastic glove
that those people wear.
(laughing)
And they give you free refills.
It tastes like linking to order screen.
They give you free refills in your wallet, of your wallet.
They refill your wallet with money.
Free refills of, and gas.
Free refills on gas.
Oh shit.
get free gas too if we owned a wall. Oh my god! Free gas! We could run our generator.
Uh-huh. The one that we all... In our bunker. Yeah, that we plugged up to our big computer.
That tells us what to say. We could finally start our lifelong dream of making a pool
of... with gas... made of filled with gasoline. We could finally have a pool of gas. Yeah, finally. We've been saving up... that's the entire budget of
Jackass 4. It's just gallons of gas to fill up a pool for Stevo to jump in. Yeah.
That's what we're putting the Patreon money toward.
We're starting a Wawa.
We're starting our own Stevo style pool.
Yeah, there's a pool out back.
We're starting our own Stevo.
It's filled with gasoline.
It's Stevo style.
We're gonna make our own Stevo.
We're gonna make our own Stevo out of like kids next,
code name Kid Next Door 2x4 technology.
Just like wood and rubber bands until we have a Stevo.
They're making a Stevo Bionicle
and we're bringing it to life.
They are, yeah.
They're making a Stevo Lego.
What's up dude?
I got the mask of light.
We're gonna take this mask of light and I'm gonna put it up my ass.
Yeah man!
I wasn't allowed to play with Bionicle growing up.
I think my parents thought it was too Asian.
They thought it was too close to anime, which I was also not allowed to watch.
I hope Bionicle, if somebody tries to cancel Bionicle for culturally appropriating tiki's
and Hawaiian culture.
Oh yeah, that's kind of the whole thing isn't it?
I'm just waiting for that to happen.
Canceling Crash Bandicoot for Aku Aku.
I think that happened.
It did?
I think so.
That's so funny.
Did Tak and the Power of Juju get clipped too?
I don't think enough people remember Tak and the Power of Juju.
Not enough people remember that, but if you do, it had a show.
Juju is actually an extremely sacred power, okay, in Ohio.
Yeah, Tack and the Power of Juju had a Nickelodeon show.
As a Juju myself, I find the idea
that Tack could control me absolutely reprehensible.
Yeah.
Yeah, but what have you guys been up to?
Nothing really.
Sapporo last night. Oh nice. Did you get one of those big cans? No, I got a 12er of it.
A 12er? 12er. Hmm. A 12er of the tiny ones? Yeah, like 12 ounce cans. Oh, now I'm
understanding. Mm-hmm. Gotcha. I got this, I got this big hat. Oh yeah, you got the big
hat. Yeah, I got a big hat for my big head. You got the fat hat. Nice. This has definitely
been the most eventful week for me during quarantine. Just like, I know, just
somebody I know went to the hospital because he was allergic to sunscreen and
that was just like, that's yeah, this kid I know, he went on a boy's trip and
they invited one of the, one of the boy's fiancés, which is just so fucked up. I
would never let a girl to the boys trip beach house. Yeah. And so God punished him
accordingly. And first of all, that girl ended up having COVID.
So everybody in the house was exposed to it.
And then he also like on the last day put on sunscreen
for the, I guess the first time. And then immediately,
just like his entire body puffed up in like, like Majin Buu.
And he went to the ER. Yeah. It's funnier if you know this kid.
It's way funnier if you know who he is. He's like, um,
He's allergic to everything.
Damn.
Yeah, but that's--
Yeah, it's actually, Patrick, are you allergic to grass?
Yeah.
I might be.
That would make sense, right?
Patrick, I think she's allergic.
I get hives if I sit in it.
I get hives.
Yeah.
Fucking, oh yeah, my dad's COVID free.
Nice.
Yeah. Congrats.
He got a certificate, they hung it up on the fridge.
(laughing)
But if you get it, I mean--
- Not for COVID, he did the presidential fitness test
while he was at the hospital.
- While he had COVID.
- Yeah, and they were like, "Well, he can't have it
"if he can do that many pull-ups."
- Yeah, he did the fitness Graham Pacer test,
and they were like, "How is he doing this?
"He's got strong-ass lungs."
- Yeah.
- But yeah, he's COVID-free. - Well, congrats for it.
Does your mom have it now?
- I don't know.
She's still there. - Are they fuckin'--
- They're on like-- - Playing hockey
with that shit back and forth?
maybe they probably got to do like another um test because he's like quarantined for two weeks too
dude i bet your mom's so lonely dude no dude i bet you know man i'm gonna visit her while i'm there
you don't visit i'm gonna no i'm gonna i'm gonna show up and visit her i bet she's getting really
lonely without your dad he's gonna get you're gonna get no i'm gonna get what you're gonna
- He was quarantined at home.
- Yeah, and that's where I'll be.
- You're not, no, my dad's at the house.
You're not doing--
- You know what, I'm gonna spend time with both of them.
I think they're probably getting bored and lonely.
They need to do some physical activity.
It's good for COVID.
I'm gonna show up and I'm gonna visit.
Dude, I'm gonna do it, man.
- You're not gonna do that.
- I am, I'm gonna wear a mask
and cut a little hole in the top.
(laughing)
So I can use my nose.
Yeah, so I can fuck your dad with my nose.
You're not gonna fuck my dad.
I'm gonna create, I'm gonna use various rubber bands to make a little butthole with your dad's ball skin and then fuck it with my nose.
I'm serious.
I'm gonna tighten it up so hard and then create a canal with rubber bands that I'm wrapping around themselves over and over again until they're maybe six inches long.
I'm gonna use my and I'm gonna tell 10 lies in a row and then fuck your dad with my big nose.
That's completely COVID safe as long as he the dad doesn't breathe. As long as the dad is dead.
Yeah it's like don't talk about my dad being dead. Dude he's not dead from COVID he's dead from my
My gun don't I'm gonna kill your dad dude
I'm sorry. It has to happen. That's not cool. Dude. I'm gonna go carol baskin on your
Do not bro, I'm gonna go carol baskin now now he's gonna go around he's gonna go this fucking
shit
Caleb wool pit skins
Okay, Carol
No caribould
Pitskin no
And care try keep at it buddy killer gonna be in the lab this
killer basket
Make sense
Taylor basket this is the fucking this Carol basket shit carol looped around care. It's actually funny to me now
Now we're gonna keep talking about it, and it's just gonna
Care ball pickets get bib. Hey, oh, what if what if Carol Baskin was a cat and it was hairball cats?
Yeah, what if oh I think it would go a little something like this
And she she dressed up her husband like a cat yeah dress up her like a cat she's hot dude
She is she's your girlfriend. She's my wife. Your wife is Carol Baskin. Did I wish dude?
I'm sick of my stupid wife and I want Carol Baskin to be my wife just so I can kill myself
Suicide by Carol suicide by tiger. That's the way to go. That's the way to write. Yeah. Oh my god
That'd be the way to go out. How do you guys want to die? How do I want to die? Yeah
I'm not gonna die. I
Don't know I chose I decided last year. That was my New Year's resolution
Definitely not from a disease. I don't want to die like throw you're gonna die from a disease. Yeah
Yeah, yeah
Patrick's gonna eat the Patrick's gonna eat the nasty patty from Spongebob
Killed the health inspector
Because he's just gonna eat and he knows what it is
Patrick's gonna die from the cheese touch from diarrhea of a wimpy kid. Yeah
kid. Yeah, that's what you're gonna get. Yeah, that's you. You're gonna eat the
diarrhea of a wimpy kid. You're the wimpy kid. That's you. You're Greg Hefley.
You're diarrhea of a wiener kid. Yeah. Yeah, cuz you're a wiener kid.
Yeah. You're the Greg Hefley kid. No. Yeah, I don't think so. And Patrick, you're
Greg Hefty. Mm-hmm. See, all right, well, we're still, we have that established. We
just can't figure out what to call Cameron. Cameron, yeah, we need to figure it out.
I'm getting an angle on making fun of Cameron.
I'm normal, it's not possible.
It's not normal.
My angle, I'm kind of fat.
I'm completely normal.
Caleb's bald and looks--
Caleb looks like a skinhead, yeah.
And I'm normal.
No, you're not, dude.
Yeah, I am.
You're not normal.
You're the freakiest of them all.
I'll tell you one reason I'm not normal.
We have something we can do, but we can't figure it out.
Yeah.
You, I think maybe there's too many things.
No.
Yeah.
No, there's not a single thing.
There's too many things.
There's too many things, both mental, physical, and spiritual.
All right, will you stay away from my spirituality?
That is awful.
(laughing)
Stay away from my spirit.
Cameron is funny because of his spirit.
Whatever you do, you do not make fun of my soul.
Yeah, Cameron is too spiritual.
Carole Baskin, that reminds me of Cameron's wretched soul.
(laughing)
Yeah.
Yeah, no, but seriously, don't talk about my soul.
I'm going to.
That will make me so mad.
You are so dumb.
Your soul is oblong.
- That is the one thing you shouldn't do around us,
is tell us not to do something.
- Yeah, that's right.
- You know me and Patrick. - Tell us not to make fun
of something. - Couple of troublemakers.
Kind of a Phineas and Ferb style troublemaking duo.
- Yeah, we kinda do summer vacation pranks.
- Yeah, and you're, oh, and you're our big sister.
- Yeah, Cameron's our big sister.
- Nah, I don't think so. - Yeah.
- I don't think so. - That's what it is.
- You're always tattling on us,
and we're always building a cool new way to have sex.
exactly in your own with each other
yeah with each other's no
no
i meant to say so
now it's actually it's what's wrong with that
big says
you guys are going to grow your girl you have long hair like a girl
now i have a lot of like a boy change that
he can't get a guy's call me a girl once i come back with my head she
Try calling me a girl now.
I just have the lumpiest, ugliest head ever.
You have a big, red boil.
I have a megamind head under here.
You also cut up your head while you were shaving.
You have toilet paper pieces all over it.
There's a flap of skin just like going like a...
I have an antenna like a toilet tubby.
It's like the it's he has like a band-aid on the back of his head like the guy in
Pulp Fiction but it's got a pussy behind it. Yeah a big one though it's a giant band-aid.
I actually have um a faucet on the back of my head like the guy from the Valve intro
and it's really cool because it dispenses beer and that's how I get all my beer. No no it turns
you on and off. No but if you put it in the middle and you're kind of on. You're uh you're steam
powered steam punk yeah and you're working on valve time buddy yeah tell
you that much slowpoke mm-hmm low-ass bitch yeah hey release half-life 3 you
bitch they did yeah half they did no that's a half-life Alexa Alex Oh it's
halfway through just shows what I know dude yeah you oh my god I'm so stupid
I'm gonna release Team Fortress 3, but there's only one class.
The human class.
You're gonna release Teen Fortress and it's about your house.
Your fortress where you keep teens.
Yeah.
Yeah, and Patrick, you'll be the heavy.
Yeah, well.
That's fine.
Yeah, it is fine.
There we go.
He just needs to come to terms with it.
mm-hmm and I'll be the um I'll be the spy you're not buying you I would be the
spy the spy and you're dressed in full or full you're dressed in a full real
tree tracksuit and he's standing outside of a teen girl's window with binoculars
killers
israeli
if you google kaleb pitts that is there's a guy named kaleb pitts who killed
himself because he was caught uh... looking into a teen girls window as he
was changing dressed in a camera arrested and i think the entire
serbs are keeping time and then he killed himself right after
yes i think i would be if you look at the if you look at the look at greg
peppers though there is a mugshot of a man who look your Carol Baskin name is
Greg Peppers post your Carol Baskin's name below. That's right. You know if you search Greg Peppers I think the first thing that comes up is an
ebombs world article about it. Yeah now it is but it used to be it used to be a
mugshot of a guy that looks like Caleb. No but every mugshot of a guy looks like
me dude. That's true. You're like a, if this person does not exist, was trained on every
Aryan Brotherhood member. You keep refreshing it over and over and every time it's your
face it never changes. That's the only thing it can generate. My lips are too big to be
Aryan Brotherhood man. They wouldn't let me in. I'm too pretty. No. They could tell I'm
from the from the the the sea no they'd let you be first lady to the president
no no yeah no they wouldn't no they would no they wouldn't they would they hate me
so much that they would make me they would put me in jail inside yeah yeah
they have another jail inside they'd put you in timeout in the bed you have to
sit on the bed the worst thing the worst thing that can happen to you in jail is
is probably time out. Yeah, probably. Yeah, I would say that's a huge problem right now
is people going to time out in jail. Yeah. Because it's basically a double sentence,
you know, time out for life, no chance of parole. And then you get into double time
out? Yeah. Oh my God. And then you get, no, actually one of the biggest problems is double
dog daring in jail.
Yeah.
So you'll double dog dare somebody to use a shiv on another guy and they're like, "Fuck,
if I don't do this, I'm a wimp."
Yeah.
And you know what happens to wimps in jail?
They get raped.
It's true.
They end up-- That's what happens to wimps.
--gotta put on the wimp cap.
It's like a dunce cap, but it says wimp.
Yeah.
All right.
Let's look at these lists.
How's that sound?
Top 10 funniest things to do in a classroom.
This one is under the sub-genre, or sub-category of lists.
Education and then the category under that, culture.
Culture is part of education.
This is kind of a random, this one kind of has a bunch of random, it's kind of a random
list.
I love random shit.
It's kind of where the random users of the website come to play I think.
that this is by rain sage this list and its description is what are some of the
funniest things to do in a classroom note this is for humor only this is not meant
to offend nor be taken seriously yes do not do any of this that would be bad so
you guys hear that this is this is all satire okay you're not supposed to do
every last one of these yeah I'm counting the days until the public
schools in New York open up and then I'm gonna you you with your fucking head
walking into a school. Yeah, tell you what New York City public school system as
soon as you open I'm going I'm going on a rampage of pranks so watch out. I'm
gonna cut that and post it out of context. Yeah go for it. It won't matter. You can
say anything. You can pretty much say anything. You can pretty much say
anything and not get in trouble. Yeah. You just can't make it in a song but
anything you'll never you'll never you'll never get contacted by an agency no of
the government oh never you can say or sing anything you want and never be
contacted by any sort of secret agency secret agent service provides a service
to certain protected individuals yeah you'll be fine dude and if you if you
make a song about it they will not contact you and it's 100% covered under
parody law and you will not get a call. You'll never get a call from the Boston
office with Agent Kennedy. That will never happen to you dude.
Alright let's please stop talking about this. Please stop. What are some of
this from Rainsage? What are the funniest... I already read that.
You're an idiot.
Oh, I don't want to go to jail.
You do want to go to jail, dude.
I actually do.
You want to go to jail and you have a pre-made wimp hat to wear when you get in there.
If I go to jail, I'm immediately going Malibu's Most Wanted.
Yeah.
Just full fucking FUBU every single day.
They will not let you wear FUBU in jail.
They will.
FUBU, the jail I'm going to.
You're going to the FUBU prison?
Yeah.
to New York, duh, New York Correctional Institution.
Yeah, the CUM Correctional Institution.
And you get a cool FUBU tracksuit, all blue, velvet.
You get a--
In Southern California, they have
the CUM Original Correctional Facility.
Yeah.
(laughing)
All right, so number one, when the teacher presents you
a question on the whiteboard with an X on it,
throw a sharp pen or pencil at the X
and hope it spears in the middle.
If it does, say X marks the spot.
- Now that's not funny, that's just bad ass.
- Yeah, that's just like a Robin Hood
like split an arrow with another arrow kind of thing.
That's so impressive.
That should get you like a golden ticket
to skip like a day of school.
- That's no, that skips you a grade.
That's how you skip a grade.
- Yeah, that's how you skip a grade.
if you can throw a pencil so well that it hits an X.
But then it's also like Uno,
where if you don't say X marks the spot,
it's gonna be not. - Yeah, you go back.
Yeah, you go back. - You go back
all the way to preschool, no matter what.
Yeah, not funny, just cool.
- Yeah. - Yeah, just a very cool skill
to have.
More classes in school should be archery-based.
- Did you guys have to do archery in middle school?
What kind of fucking school did you go to, dude?
What are you even talking about right now?
Yeah, I did archery.
You go to school in like New Zealand?
No, I went to school in New Hampshire.
He had an archery unit.
He went to school in Blackthorn Keep.
Yeah.
He was taught by a wizard, dude.
He was being actually taught to chant arrows.
Merlin taught him to chant.
He went to the school at the beginning of the first Fable game.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's where he went.
His only classes were archery and fighting a knight.
Yeah, dude, and instead of lunch, they had banquet.
And that's why Pat looks like he does.
You had to talk to a tree that looked like an old man, and that was the principle.
They had a joust in the middle of our lunch room.
Yeah.
And it was the janitors with jousting tools.
With brooms.
With brooms, yeah.
Yeah, but they would really die.
You guys didn't have an archery unit?
No.
A unit?
Of course not.
Did they defend the school?
We had a whole--
Wait, you guys didn't have a moat around your school filled with crocodiles?
What in the world?
Wait, did your guys' school have an ancient curse on it or was that just me?
After the Adam Lanza stuff, they put a moat around my school.
Filled with crocodiles.
You guys seriously didn't have like a bloodletting at the nurse's office or anything like that?
You guys didn't have an evil teacher?
An evil teacher that you had to defeat every single year.
And who came back to life at the end of every day.
So you guys didn't, you're telling me you didn't have a giant three-headed dog that protected
the homework.
I, I don't understand why you guys didn't do like necromancy in your science class.
I mean I had, I had a little bit of uh, neck romancing, if you know what I'm saying.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, cause you, cause you fucked a dead body.
No, neck, no I romanced, I romanced, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You did necromancing with, and mancing means fucking.
That would be necroromancing.
I did necromancing with a woman's neck.
You did necroromancing.
And I left it, I left it, darted up with tons of little tiny things.
What are those called?
Stickies.
I had little stickies all on a bitch.
Mm-hmm.
So you really had, you had archery.
Yeah, we had archery.
I had an archery unit in the eighth grade.
- Yeah man, how many of your friends were goblins in school?
(laughing)
- Most of them.
- Yeah, it was so clicky at my school.
It was like the goblins and the orcs
all sat with each other over here.
- Yeah, the goblins and the orcs, the bosmers.
- The humans and the halflings had to sit together.
- The bosmers had like their own table out in the woods.
Bosmers ate lunch in the woods.
- Yeah.
- Yeah man.
- And it was hard 'cause all the bosmers
were trying to eat the halflings and the humans.
Yeah, one time I pranked my teacher by putting a caltrop on his throne and I had to go to the dungeon after class.
[Laughter]
Yeah.
You seriously, you did archery in school?
Our senior prank was it, for our senior prank we did a siege on the 8th grade.
[Laughter]
Yeah, we killed the principal with a battering ram.
We killed the king of the middle school.
Yeah, we did a Trojan horse. We did a Trojan horse thing to the high school. That's how
we got to freshman year. High school was normal though. I didn't have a...
Yeah, high school was just a normal human high school.
Yeah, but RuneScape middle school, very different.
Yeah. I remember graduating and getting full Dvorak armor when I left middle school. It
was so awesome, dude.
sucked because our principal was a daedra yeah the assistant principal was the
cow fight Queen yeah and we had to defeat him I remember one time the the police
came to the school and had their curse sniffing dogs and confiscated a cursed
ring from someone's locker yeah they found my enchanted blade yeah they got
suspended and he got suspended from reality they had to go to a different
realm she goes to a different realm yeah I guess I did go to a pretty weird like
middle school die - I already talked about diversity day yeah you know we had
No, no, no, no, Immigration Day. Yeah. Very different. Very different. That's when they
opened a portal and let the demons immigrate into your school. Yeah, they let the demons
immigrate into your school. No, but imagine like doing like Immigration Day and then like
while that's going on kids are outside shooting bow and arrows. Fuck, my middle school was
so fucked. My whole school, my whole school district was fucked. Anyways. I feel like
New Hampshire probably not, seemingly well funded enough to own archery equipment.
But probably besides that I'm guessing the teachers don't pay too much.
Yeah, no the archery equipment just belonged to one of the teachers.
Yeah.
He just had that and he was like, "Hey, why don't we add an archery unit?"
This is what PE is.
Yeah, I have about 50 bows and 10,000 arrows.
Do you guys want to add an archery unit to gym class?
Yeah, I just have these.
Maybe they're just around.
It's so weird, I found these.
They're buried underneath the school.
I think your mic just unplugged or something.
Mine?
Yeah.
Is your audio just shared?
I'm smart.
Yeah, you're gonna have to restart that in Audacity.
Yeah, alright.
I'm going down the time stamp.
You're so smart, dude.
Number two, run over and scream at the teacher that she killed Larry and then get out a plush
toy out of your bag and pretend to grieve over it. Now that's funny. That's pretty good.
That's some funny ass shit. Yeah, accuse your teacher of murder, one of the
Ten Commandments. You know? Yeah, teachers shall not murder. Teachers shall not
murder Larry. Yeah. Oh and then somebody says no don't kill Larry he's the best
cucumber. Originally there were a lot more
commandments because they just got stuck on listing every day they were like
teachers shall not kill janitors shall not kill and just listed every type of
person but then they had to cut it down Larry the cucumber was kind of the
first pickle Rick that's true facts you know that's facts it's actually it's a
man and who's a cucumber a ganker and he's but he was kind of the opposite
because he was so stupid for believing in God yeah yeah that's the difference a
cucumber is pure and unpickled and because Larry believed in God and a
pickle is sour. The sour pickle who's nihilistic and atheistic who has lost
his faith becomes a genius yeah he was pickled in vinegar and a
copy of... Yeah he was pickled in your ass dude when you stuck him up there. Yeah that's
right yeah that's right and then but but Larry on the other hand was pickled in
God's light and love yeah so he actually he's you know and he's looking for his
hairbrush - yeah you'd have any fucking hair I think that's kind of the joke
what yeah is that he we're joking he's look yeah yeah get this it's it the whole
thing was an allegory for a joke. What the fuck? Yeah, it's true. Oh my god, they can't
be doing that. I took it serious. Me too, man. I thought that plum bitch was hot. I
thought he was in pain from not having his hair brushed. Probably all of them were in
such horrible pain all the time because they're vegetables. They're slowly rotting away, decomposing
at a very fast rate but they have sentience
and so they're just
they're watching themselves just turn into absolute fucking compost
dude wait fan theory ok
ok the veggie tales alright
the vegetables
they're all in a coma in a hospital they're vegetables
in a hospital dreaming yeah those are all people
NOOOOOO! TAKE IT BACK!
those are all people uh... all the veggie tales people they were all uh...
they all were in like a heavens gate style christian cult yeah
and they did a bunch of kool aids and uh... they
did you guys ever see the last episode of veggie tales where they cut to the
hospital where it's all actually people in coma dreaming that they're vegetables
and they're all dressed up like you know like people in like the spongebob
musical that just dress in the same colors as the characters from the show
yeah this Larry's just an all green and yeah it's like it's like it's covered in
warts yeah yeah he got some he had chicken pox and it put him in a yeah it
put him in a coma put him in a coma and turned him into a cucumber in his dreams
yeah and then the Bob the tomato was a big fat guy who he choked on something
and he turned red the peas were actually peas though yeah I'm looking right now at
I had an image I found of the VeggieTales as humans.
Fuck.
Can you give that a send?
Yeah.
How do I do this?
You communicate it.
Oh my.
You send it.
Oh my god.
Spell out the URL.
Alright, so it is google.com/search?q=veggietales+as+humans.
I'm looking at it now.
And sxsrf=alex.
S-R-F equals A-L-E-K.
- Dude, you wanna have S-E-X.
You wanna have S-E-X with a V-E-G-E-T-E-E-B-E.
- You wanna have S-E-X with a V-E-G-I-N-A-T-L-E-S.
- No, no, a V-E-I-G-A.
(laughing)
Dude, I'm gonna have a little S-E-X with a V-I-G-A, dude.
- Nah, I don't believe you.
- Dude, from a G-U-R-L, dude.
I don't believe you.
I'm opening, oh yeah.
Now, okay, so let's see here.
I got this file you sent, Pat.
Are these your friends that you sent?
You accidentally sent a picture of your friends.
This is your family?
This is my family, yes.
Okay, so let me get this straight.
These are, this is your family.
Yeah, they all kind of look like you.
Who's the, which one is, what's the dog?
I like the guy who's just like a Spanish piece of garlic.
Oh yeah, he's cool as hell.
He's one of the better characters.
- And the onion?
- The onion?
Don't get me started on the onion, dude.
- What's the dog?
Is the dog someone in the, what's the--
- Yeah, the dog is you, bitch.
- Is there a dog?
- Yeah, there's a--
- There was a dog in VeggieTales.
- Who's the, no, there's--
- It wasn't a dog, though.
- A dog is not a vegetable, buddy.
(laughing)
- That is when I get done with it.
- Yeah. - Whoa.
- That's right, I beat dogs into a coma.
(laughing)
All right, I'm back on this list.
What's up?
Yeah, number three.
Number three, flop around on the table acting drunk.
Then when the teacher comes over, then when the teacher comes over, then insist you are
low on battery.
Okay, that's pretty funny.
That's what I say when I can't get my penis hard and I'm about to have SEX with a VIDI.
Oh babe, I'm so sorry.
Baby, sorry, I'm low on battery.
I have to recharge by playing video games.
Sorry, I need to go get my...
games.
I need to recharge with my plug.
Yeah.
I'm thinking about what that might mean.
You know what I'm saying?
I gotta plug my house.
I need to plug my thingy into the wall.
And then there's just a hole in the wall not connected to an outlet.
You'll put your balls in it.
It's just a glory hole.
In your neighbor.
There's just a bunch of bugs on the other side.
Your neighbor just left you.
I don't think, I think if I had a glory hole
between my apartment and the one next to mine,
I don't think my penis would even fit through the,
I don't think it would make it to the other end, you know?
I don't, yeah, I don't think it's physically possible.
Yeah, I think glory holes are fake.
It's not physically possible to have a big penis.
That's, yeah, that's all, yeah,
the thing about a glory hole is it's not flattering.
You're losing like an inch or an inch and a half almost.
You're losing, yeah, you're losing like a good inch.
Where's the glory in that, I ask you?
Yeah.
and that of putting out your little two and a half inch nub
through the fucking hole.
Yeah.
And just begging some guy who looks exactly like you
to do something with it.
You know?
Listen man, listen man, trucker to trucker,
I promise, I promise it's longer than this normally.
The bathroom stall is cutting me off, dude.
Look, they got some good like bulletproof wall here.
Yeah, man, they got, man, this must be,
he can clearly tell that it's like half an inch thick.
Oh man, that's weird, man. This must be like a six inch...
You know what, I bet it's thicker in the middle than it is on the end, so it may deceive you.
- Oh, it's a beveled wall. - But it's actually super thick.
- It's a beveled... - Yeah. I think it's beveled, maybe.
They must have mudded over this part at some point, 'cause it's definitely thicker here.
- (laughing) - Well, you know, I mean...
You can just kinda play with it like the head's a big clit.
(laughing)
Just do that shit to it, man.
- Yeah, just kinda flick it.
- That's what I usually do.
- All right, I'll see you at home.
Bye, dad.
(laughing)
- Yeah, it says you have two bathrooms side by side
in your house, in the upstairs.
I'll see you downstairs, dad.
- That's a way, hey baby,
I know you just got back from work,
but come to the bathroom.
I did a little something I think will spice up your sex life.
(laughing)
I put a glory hole in the toilet.
- Put a, I put a hole in the toilet
so I can stick my penis through and you can poop on it.
- Yeah. - Pretty awesome.
Number four, pretend to be a robot.
That's kind of what the last one is.
Pretend to be a robot as you silently watch the teacher
answering in mechanical tones and terminology
if the teacher picks you to answer.
- Teach will get pissed, then again--
- This is just like what the kid
at Ashburgers in my class did.
- Yeah.
just pretend to be a robot like once every two weeks
yeah i don't think you have to have a good i think that was the other side
worth every two weeks a_t_t_ had a glitch for the real and here's a
terminator and he was set back to kill me but he got distracted by t_v_ and
she says
and just a little bit back at the all artistic people a terminator secretly
that's true
very true
they terminate uh...
grits
you know this little does little
things that
bounce you know those little those snacks the grips yeah why they didn't actually
bounce though dude they were dog shit yeah like in the fucking commercial is
people like bouncing them like from half court like onto a onto the ground and
then bouncing it back up into their mouths that's like that like skydiving
and bouncing it is all the way back up funny selling point for a food is you
can throw this off the ground and it will go up into your mouth yeah you can
You can eat these off the ground in Costco.
You can eat this food off the ground.
Yeah.
It's extremely clean food.
You can eat it off the ground.
The new cheesy gordita double XL burritos.
The new cheesy gordita puddle.
You can throw this shit at your bathroom wall and lick it off.
That's how clean this snack is.
I remember, do you guys remember there was like one candy that was, it was like hair
gel.
It was oh yeah, and you would just like you would just squeeze it in your mouth
That was just your dad's hair gel dude. You got confused. No
You saw the green Clubman stuff, and you were like damn that stuff looks so good
I think it was called it was like axe chocolate something, but yeah, you would you would squirt it into your mouth
I have you ever you have you ever seen that Clubman gel the green the green barber gel no
Oh man, that stuff looks so edible.
That stuff looks good.
The thing is, everything looks edible.
It smells good too.
Like, every... I mean, I wanted...
When I was a kid, I wanted to eat...
You remember the, like, Skechers or whatever that had
the little gel, like,
ball in it? I wanted to
take that out with an ice cream scoop and eat it.
Yeah.
I was like, that probably had...
They probably hid sugar in this.
Yeah. I mean, the thing is, nowadays,
they can make cakes that look like anything.
So, if I'm walking down the street...
If I'm walking down the street and I see a pile of dog dew, I mean, how do I know that
Zumbo's Just Desserts didn't just come through and leave it on the side of the road?
It could be a cake.
It's the craziest thing.
They make cakes look like anything.
They even have cakes that look like a wedding cake, but there's two men at the top.
Or two girls.
It's crazy.
It's called a mirrored cake.
Yeah.
No.
Yeah, there's a glitch in the cake.
Yeah, when you buy it.
I'd like to, hey, I saw you ordered this wedding cake from us, but I just, there was a glitch
in your order form where it said you wanted two girls on the top.
No, two girls we can do.
But two guys?
Are you sure?
Two girls I get it, because it's like kind of cool.
It's funny.
Yeah, it's funny.
But come on.
It's funny how that's basic, what was her name?
Kim whatever.
Kim Kardashian.
That's like her entire court case.
Yeah.
just hurts like yeah I don't know there's a glitch um yeah so we just cancelled your order
whoops what was that lady's name there was a glitch where we accidentally wrote the f
word all over your cake I'm really sorry there was a glitch with my frosting bag yeah that's
my bad Kim Davis what an awesome name creator of Garfield's wife Kim Davis yeah she created
Garfield's wife Arlene but she's not related to Jim Davis she just created a
separate separate thing number five begin whacking your ruler in the air and
insist you were fighting against evil beings what Patrick did at his school
it's called playing you had defense against the dark arts I was there was
one time I put you know they like the wing rulers had like holes in the middle
yes I put a pencil in the middle and put your penis in your pencil sized penis I
started spinning it around and I hit my math teacher in the face it should be a
class called defense against the dank carts and it's just and you have to and
you smoke a smoke a dank cart I smoke a stack yeah you smoke I've smoked weed
like twice this week and I've gone just completely insane both times yeah it's
It's been pretty nice.
It's been kind of refreshing.
I used to go insane from weed and be bummed out about it.
But now it's like, I mean, I'm not gonna like,
it doesn't matter, I have nothing to do the next day.
That's true.
Except just throw all my clothes in my car.
Man, I haven't smoked weed since before quarantine.
I gotta go crazy.
You gotta get on it, dude.
Yeah, I gotta go mad.
It's pretty fun to go crazy on weed every once in a while.
It's not fun when it happens every time.
When it happens every time?
That's been months, though.
That's pretty bad.
Yeah, I thought that, the first time I thought it,
I thought it was gonna be really bad,
but I just went crazy in a way that I was just like,
like I just drank like four cups of water in a row.
You know, like the lowest level of weed crazy.
That's what I do every time.
Man, there was like a good three month period
where I was just smoking way too much weed.
It's so funny that you became somebody
who thought they were allergic to weed,
to smoking weed all the time.
And did you ever smoke weed and then record?
Yeah, yeah several times and it ruined those are like our worst
episodes, yeah
Yeah, it was like a new level of Patrick. It was crazy. It was like it was like just like
Like drunk Patrick, but in the daytime
Yeah
Doing now
Yeah, now it's it's
The day drinking is really I'm gonna have to just stop drinking for a month or so
I gained like 8 pounds just because every night I drink a bottle and a half of wine.
Damn, I've been drinking so much beer man.
You've been drinking wine, you've been gaining weight in your tits dude.
You're turning into a woman.
Um, no.
You just said yeah.
No I'm not!
I'm not!
Take it back!
No.
Take it back.
How about now?
Would you respect me if I had a big deep voice?
Oh hey, kill me.
Kill me.
Caleb's dad just walked into the room.
Hey son, hey son you need to take the trash out.
Yeah, I'm referring to your mother.
Hey dad, dad you and mom have been divorced for 15 years.
Why are you in this house?
Uh, I thought I smelled you.
I left my keys here.
Yeah, I left a little bit of cum in the toilet.
I came to get it with a butterfly net.
I have a pool filter cleaner thing.
What's that thing called?
Net.
I have a net.
Yeah, I got a net.
Number six, whenever the teacher asks you to hand something out, drop it all over the
floor and insist that you were checking to see if gravity still works.
I did this and I got expelled.
I did this and they shot me into space.
Yeah.
That was so bad.
I remember the biggest laugh I ever got in school was kind of a similar physical stunt
to this where I was turning in my test in fourth grade to the front of the classroom.
The teacher sets up her desk at the front so that people can come up and drop their
test off.
I walked up and right as I was walking up, a bunch of police cars with the sirens on
started like racing past the school and so I like I like threw everything off of
her desk all the papers and shit and jumped over it and I said oh shit it's
the fuzz and it just killed dude I mean it was I mean he crushed the teacher the
teacher could not stop laughing damn cuz that's the thing you can get away with
anything if you just make the teacher laugh that's true yeah I did uh there
We were watching a video in health class.
We watched a fucking Lifetime movie in my health class
in sophomore year.
- Nice.
- And, oh no, freshman year, and it was about syphilis.
It was about the dangers of transmitting syphilis.
- Yeah.
- And there was a scene where the boy goes,
"I got a gift for you."
And there was a pause.
There was a pause and I went, "Yeah, it's syphilis."
And--
- Oh my God, destroy it.
- Dude, I-- - Just absolute crush her, dude.
- I absolute fucking crushed it, man.
- Dude, and that's, dude,
that's when I knew I was gonna be a comedian, man.
That's when I knew I needed to go to an open mic in a basement.
Yeah, pretty much.
I mean, I used to get laughed all the time in school, man.
I used to go in the bathroom and show everybody my balls in a big circle and everybody would
point and laugh.
And that's when I knew I was meant for the stage.
That's true.
And now I'm in a local all-white production of Hamilton.
So it's pretty much worked out perfectly.
Yeah.
Do you think that exists?
Of course.
Absolutely.
- Do you think like some high school,
some well-meaning high school?
- Yeah, of course.
- In my theater class in college,
somebody from Connecticut talked about
how they did an all-white version of In the Heights.
(laughing)
Yeah, which is also like way more
like about being not white.
- Right, exactly.
- In Hamilton, Tennessee.
- Yeah.
- Holy shit.
- Yeah, and they were just like,
yeah, we didn't know any Dominican people.
(laughing)
So we just did an all-white version.
- The town next to me did all-white hairspray.
Damn. How do you do all white air spray?
I know, right?
Yeah, the people in my town actually did an all white version of Grease.
It's pretty fucked up, dude.
Yeah, none of them were Balkan.
None of them were Italian.
Yeah, none of them were from Greece at all.
Nah, it was fucked up, dude.
Yeah.
Number seven, when the teacher picks on you to answer a question, replace a completely
random word with something similar, completely different to it, and then scream, "Damn you
auto-correct while writhing in the ground in agony. The last part really adds another
layer to it. That'd be good with anything. Yeah I think that's just a separate thing.
Yeah finish eating your lunch and then writhe on the ground in agony. I think that
that is the completes any prank pretty well. Yeah that's I mean that's just it
doesn't matter what oh yeah the next one's good. Yeah in number eight in a
computer class, it is called different things around the world. Randomly walk over to other
students computers and rotate the screens with control R, alt, arrow key, if the teacher
complains turn off their computer using a shortcut. It's different things all around
the world. In caveman country it's called rock class.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. In alien school it's just called class.
Yeah, in the Flintstones town it's called Birdglass, because you just type on a bird's feet.
Yeah.
Pretty awesome dude.
What if the Flintstones had a computer?
You gotta use a shortcut to turn off the teacher's computer.
Yeah.
I use a shortcut.
I go around the back of the teacher's desk.
That's a shortcut.
I get there faster.
I get there before the teacher.
Yeah, I pretty much teleport like in Jumper.
Yeah, there's a secret passage.
There's a secret passage.
It's actually like Pac-Man where if I go out one door and then I come in the other side
of the classroom.
Yeah, exactly.
It's all just because it's computer's class.
Yeah, once you're in computer class, you're in the computer.
Yeah, once you're in computer class, things act a little differently in the classroom.
Do you guys remember hearing about sex ed and thinking that you would get to have sex?
No.
I remember having this fantasy.
I was very mature in sex ed.
I had this fantasy that when somebody told me like,
"Hey, you have to take sex ed next year,"
that I would show up and it would just be like a--
- You guys all have to watch.
- Like Lisa Ann is the teacher,
and they would just be like,
"Okay, pair up with somebody and have sex with them."
- Yeah.
- They had an anonymous question box,
and in my brother's year,
they had to get rid of the anonymous question box,
because all the kids were just writing
despicable things. Just despicable me quotes. Yeah they were just writing they
were writing "Oh Banana" "Oh Biddle Banana" "Ah Biddle" "Biddle Biddle Biddle"
We have to stop the anonymous box. They set up a team of minions to ask too many questions.
They're trying to steal the moon. Little did they know that would be similar to the
2016 election where a bunch of minions actually showed up to
vote instead of the instead of people with consciences. I just remember there
was a... Minions showed up for Trump but Bernie Bros didn't show up for Hillary so...
There was a guy at college at Emerson a guy came in to talk
about like the comedy industry and he was like okay like we're gonna like just
Like, right, if you have any questions, write them down and put them...
Okay, everyone partner up and have sex!
[Laughter]
Yeah.
And then just points to a kid and is like, "Oh, there's, uh,
definitely one extra, you're with me."
[Laughter]
And he's like, "Write down your questions and put them
in, like, this box and I'll answer them."
Like, I don't know why he did it and honestly it was really weird,
but then one of them got really mad
because one of the
questions was, "Is it normal to have hair
down there?"
*laughter*
He's like yelling at us.
Oh my god, that's good.
It's so incredible to do that in college.
Dude, imagine, imagine,
imagine being like a fucking comedy writer
and getting mad that somebody just
one-upped you. Yeah, someone's a genius.
Yeah, somebody's funny.
Yeah.
Is it normal to have hair down there?
*laughter*
That's good, dude.
So funny.
Yeah, that's like when we did the, when we had like the mock election for 2008 in my
middle school, there was like four votes for poop.
That just made me laugh.
Just four write-in votes for poop.
Yeah, four separate people.
Like, yeah, poop.
Yeah, four, yeah, they did, it was not organized because we led a different write-in campaign
for Chuck Norris, which won the election.
There was also, there was four people who just were like...
Poop.
That's awesome.
Yeah, dude, the funniest time of anyone's life.
2008.
Yeah, my uncle, who the ghost buster, he, every election cycle goes and votes for Mickey Mouse.
Yeah.
That's so awesome.
So fucking sick, dude.
Yeah.
That's what I, I mean, now that's kind of just what I'm going to do.
I bet Donald Trump is going to vote for Carole Baskin.
Yeah.
That's a write-in campaign we can start yeah
Trump Carol Bauer like when he more like Don Crell
Basque Trump whoa
Don't like Don Zolo from Boston. Oh my god
To like a curtained off half-empty Knicks comedy stop yeah doing it doing everything like trigger happy
Every single joke just ends with and then the Chinese guy did karate on me
What does he know his name sounds like Han Solo?
He does he?
He does he posts about that sometimes. I think I think
as a little lines, I
Like the idea of like oh, it's just his hour is just like 15 different stories of him having sex with
different trans women and then just feeling tricked
And he's just like I'll just keep happening to me
He's that really his whole set. He's like he was like in a
Dunkin Donuts commercial or something with like Julian Edelman
Dude fucking Gus Gus opened for him and said the best show
He was like yeah
Yeah, yeah, I mean he just can't he can't lose dude Don solo. He's a man
All right
Let's see. Let's do let's finish out this list. How's that sound? All right, let's do it number number nine
set a box set a bell as your ringtone and time it to ring five minutes before the end of your final lesson a
Student actually did this no kidding. That's one of the comments damn. That's not even a bad idea like
recording the school's bell and then
That's an ultimate. Why wait until the five minutes before the end of the final lesson do it five minutes into the first class
exactly special ability move that's that'll you have to save up your special
ability that i was something that tricky five magic points
yeah you actually lose h_p_ when you do that yeah it's blood magic
you ever ten
jump on the table and do the mock arena while singing tomboys it's okay to be
gay
patrick definitely did that
yes i think that
Two great songs. Macarena and It's Okay to Be Gay.
Yeah, someone should do like a girl talk mashup of those two.
Yeah. That'd be pretty good. I love mashup music, dude.
I hate when songs are just by themselves.
I need them to be mixed up with I Love Rock and Roll.
Which is the one everybody mixes.
Biggie Smalls and I love rock and roll and that's what mashup music is.
Yeah.
It's true.
Yeah and then my aunt posts, "This is so crazy it works."
Yeah.
I actually unironically listen to this.
I unironically listen to this.
This is my favorite song unironically.
There's 20 top comments that say "0,00 free replay button."
All right, I actually, I know we finished the list but I do want to do this number 11.
Yeah.
Fill a bucket, we'll end it here.
Fill a bucket of balls and tip them down the stairs and yell,
my balls!
(laughing)
- That's pretty good.
- That's pretty good, dude.
- Yeah, that's good.
- If I saw that, that would make me laugh.
- My balls, I mean, just saying my balls any time
is pretty good.
- The band, the new metal band, Snot,
had shirts that said on the front, my balls,
and on the back, your chin, which is pretty awesome.
(laughing)
'Cause they have a song called "My Balls."
Do you guys remember that sketch from the state
where he just--
Oh, I'm gonna dip my balls in it?
I'm gonna dip my balls in it.
No.
Yeah.
Oh, mate, that just, that's still,
that's basically what this is.
Ken Marino, one of the best dudes.
Oh, one of the best guys.
Such a good dude, dude.
Ken Marino, one of the best comedic minds
of all time, I feel.
One of the generational comedic minds.
Are you kidding, Ron Donald, are you fucking kidding me?
Ronovan McDonald.
Donovan Ray?
Hmm, yeah, pretty good, dude.
Ray Donovan? Yeah, he's pretty awesome as Ray Donovan.
He was pretty good as Rayman Raving Rabbids.
Ken Marino as Ray Donovan?
[laughter]
He's just doing his exact character from the Summer Camp movie.
What is Ray Donovan? He's like an Irish hitman? Hitman?
Hitman? He's an Irish Pikmin?
[laughter]
Yeah, I think he's a Pikmin.
He's a little alien who follows around a big guy.
Yeah, but he is Irish. Since we're not reading patrons anymore
We should just mention the patreon at the end of the episode so people still know it exists.
I have to buy a new microphone, so please subscribe it. Just subscribe.
We'll try to figure out a way to thank all the new patrons
You know what we'll do? We'll make a movie. We'll make a full length movie.
This will save time. Patrick will write a movie. We'll make a full length movie every single week.
I'm not writing. I'm actually I'm writing the sequel to Jexy right now.
So it's called sexy and it's from Patrick's perspective. It's called a boy - yeah, it's called. Yeah, it's called sexy - it's about a sexy
Two-year-old that you love no
It is in it there. It's oh no. No, we're not ending the episode there
you got