You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts for the heartless.
You're a crap monster.
Patrick's penis plumply, plumply pissed on his, on his plump.
Patrick's pile of pimples at the place of his penis.
Patrick's penis dumped a pile of piss.
Caleb's penis is broken.
Patrick's, Fat Patrick.
fat Patrick fucks a pig. Patrick's post-pubescent pig penis.
Preston's Patrick presses Patrick. Patrick pokes pigs with
his post-pubescent penile pile of pimple. Cameron creates
Caleb's cum. No, he doesn't. No. No, beautiful women all over the world do. Cameron creates
Caleb's cumen. Patrick. Patrick praises on. Cameron's cumen. Caleb's. Patrick praises
the putrid present. He does. No. He does. When I was like
auditioning for like sketch troops in college me and Neil there was like all
these theater like losers walking around doing like vocal warm-ups and so me and
Neil just started walking around like bips bips B IPS bips bips bips just as
loud as we could this thing I don't understand them yeah we used to me and
Aaron used to make fun of those two used to make up Patrick's leaving all right
- Cool, nice.
- That's all right.
While Patrick is gone, we'd like to announce
that we're donating all of Patrick's cut of the Patreon
to bail funds all over America this week.
- Yeah, you guys did.
- Yeah, we've donated all of his money.
- I have not seen any of my money.
- We're donating all of his money, and he's happy to do it.
- Yeah, actually.
Nothing wrong with it.
- Yeah, we're gonna do it.
- What'd you say about you and Aaron?
we would all we would also just make up fake chance we just go around and be
like the mouse in the house went tippity-tie today and just say Stuart
Liddell's feet are brittle yeah tip-tap tip-top tip-tap top just like
spongebob squidward spongebob square-bob squidward sandy cheeks birds have birds
have feet and birds have beaks. SpongeBob SquarePants squirted silently. Patrick
Squidward is dancing yippee. Patrick Squidward cute as they can be. A lot of
people think that SpongeBob, a lot of parents think that SpongeBob and Patrick
are gay but it's actually Patrick and Squidward. Yeah. You know like they
they did a couple of episodes that was the lost episodes the ones that
Apache the pirate tries to find yeah those are those are like it's like like
a call me by your name sort of like mentor romance between Squidward who's
24 and Patrick who's 17 that's what it's what they actually based call me by your
name up it based call me by your name on Patrick and in Squidward yeah yeah
Timothy Chalamet has a very Squidward and Timothy Chalamet as Patrick Star
I'm
made out of sand. Yeah, he has two parents who look exactly like him. And he's fucking
Squidward. And he's French. Yeah, he has a clam, he's a clam child. He has a briefcase
full of ice cream. See, because Chalamet translated from French loosely is Patrick Star. Yeah,
is stupid star. Yeah, stupid star. Yeah, very dumb star. Stupid star online, which is a
a spin-off of this a new anime that we're making uh-huh it's about Patrick yeah
every Patrick I know is stupid why no yeah including on TV and on star on
screen and stage yeah how many Patricks on stage do you know I know this Patrick
in front of me I was on stage for he's on stage right now he's on stage right
now yeah Patrick can't Patrick Patrick on
Patrick haunts Improv Boston like the Phantom of the Opera and he lives
he lives in the in the rafters of the drop ceiling. I jump out during the nude
show and I hit them with the fire extinguisher. Yeah you broom them in the
middle of the nude show. Do you guys know anybody who did the nude show?
I don't think so. I probably know someone who did the nude show.
I guess if you do it you don't walk around talking about it all the time.
yeah Patrick says Patrick Patrick when you asked that Patrick pulled out his
little notebook where he listed every single person who has ever done the nude
show with links to their Facebook profiles you know what none of these
names are bringing any bells just so does everybody sit in the crowd of that
show nude no while they wait well no cuz it's only comics there yeah no you go
true yeah cuz no no somebody told me that's like actually a very popular like
tourist show really yeah that makes sense it makes sense they want to see how the
foreigners want to see how our Joe yeah I mean if you're if you're like if you're
touring from Japan they don't have genitals there they just have like
pixels true they want to see real in there yeah they want to see what it what
it what a penis actually looks like yeah no it's something we're like as soon as
you cross the border of Japan into what's next as you paint the ocean you
- You, your penis unblurs.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it's kind of the curse.
- That's what 5G is.
That's what they're trying to bring over here.
- Yeah.
- With all those cell phone towers.
It broadcasts pixels onto sex.
- Exactly.
Yeah, they're trying to do that here in America.
Japan's been 5G'd up for, oh, I don't know, 100 years.
- Well, 5G stands for--
- Since the Bakugan era of Japan.
5G stands for five Japanese guys invented this.
It originated there.
- They just needed a short acronym for it.
- They're always so--
- So it can fit in the corner of your phone.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- So yeah, it shows you where--
- If you have a logger, if you use it on an iPad,
it says the whole thing.
Like if your iPad is connected to 5G, it says that.
- Yeah, if you hold it horizontally.
- Yeah.
And you have screen orientation unlocked.
Then it'll spell out, "Five Japanese guys made this."
But every G just is how many Japanese guys made that specific technology.
Exactly.
So that's why sometimes you'll be in places where it's like, you know, 3G, three Japanese
guys, 4G, four Japanese guys.
If it just says E, that means every Japanese guy.
It's pretty impressive technology.
My phone doesn't have 5G yet, so I think I'm good.
If my phone has 5G, I'm moving into a cave.
My phone doesn't have 5G, but my camera...
I don't...
You have like an iPhone 5, right?
I'm a 5G...
I have an iPhone SE, I think.
Ah.
Um...
Sex-e-fender.
No.
That's what the SE stands for.
Yeah, it does.
No.
Yeah.
Super excited...
To be a sex-e-fender.
No, it's...
Again, if you put your phone in portrait mode, it will say that.
You've just never used your phone in landscape mode.
You've never used your phone in landscape mode.
Seriously evil is what your stands for.
Because of your sex offender nature.
Seriously bad meets evil.
Yeah, seriously Roysta59 and Eminem.
Just doing absolutely nonsense Taco Bell raps to each other.
I forgot bad meets evil existed until like two weeks ago.
And then sick you remember fucking lighters. I forgot. Yeah, I thought it's funny just a Bruno Mars song
No, I do that whole album is like lighters and then 30 songs where Eminem's like I killed a gay man and Royce was there, too
I fucked his ass and Royce ate his poo and Royce is like
Yeah
I was there with Eminem and we both fucked the guy and then you skip the lighters and it's like
You have to a man should wear a dress. I
Haven't listened that song
You didn't listen to Lighters. I just know the Bruno Mars part.
Yeah. Yeah, me too. I only know the Bruno Mars part.
I don't know any of the parts. What did fucking Royce Defy
he has some really bad like name. Everything is auto
tuned. Oh, that's his whole thing. Yeah, it was like T-Pain's
a bitch. Yeah. And yeah, all of his. T-Pain I think
is a much more talented person. That's one of the best eras
eras of rap is like from 2006 to like 2013 where just every guy like Nas or like Royce
Da 5'9" or like Black Thought all had songs that were like, like rap is dead.
Yeah, because of autotune.
Yeah, rap is dead because I sold 56 albums in a year.
Yeah.
So it must be dead.
Rap is dead because Kanye wanted to sound like a robot and now fucking everyone wants
to sound like a goddamn robot.
- Fucked a bald girl and just ruined rap.
Rap used to be about girls with long hair
and having sex with as many long haired girls
as you possibly can.
- And it used to be about going down to the soda fountain.
- Rap used to be about hanging out with your friends.
- Rap used to be about taking your double wide
fucking sedan down to the soda fountain
with Peggy Sue in her poodle skirt
and you sit on that and you drink a milkshake
Together and rap used to be about Boba Fett, dude. It used to be about his
Job of the huh the fuck ever happen finances vet now you have all this stuff about sex and
Lugs and gang signs it used to be about rapping about Boba Fett and his dad dude
Yeah, it's supposed to be about cruising through Bespin and your DeLorean. Yeah
Whatever happened to that Mandalorian rap? MC Chris?
Yeah, didn't he get a video of him?
Didn't he get like an, wasn't that an early me too? I think so. I think there was a video of him crying.
Makes sense. I just remember I think when, oh god, I gotta find that. He got me too'd for crying. Yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, this rapper cried.
That's a death sentence. MC Chris's over party. Yeah.
So you should have seen it coming his name's literally MC cries
You think about oh
Yeah, and it stands for my my is crying
Yeah, we could have been we would have been a really good like rap trio
Oh, yeah, baby. So he ejected a fan from the audience and then everyone was mad at him on Twitter
And ejected the fan. Yeah, he ejected on the fan. That was the problem
After he receives criticism from fans he apologized in a video where he was crying
Fucking bitch dude, you know rapper should ever cry. Yeah
Did either of you all get an hour ago race wars in 2000 with Kurt Metzger
Her
His first album was called life's a bitch and I'm her pimp
Nice, dude, that's so sick nerd nerd core fans walk around in the hood and call it the scary maze game
Did you guys ever did you guys think growing up that 50 cent got shot 50 times no no no
That's why I was always told I didn't know he got shot 50 times and that's what they call him 50 cent
Yeah, no, they call him that because his name is his real name is Michael quarters
His name is Michael two-quarters. That's a
Christian name. Yeah
Yeah
Why do they call him 50 cent?
Because he's because he used to sell all his albums for 50 cents
And then I was just a price tag that people put over his actual rap name, which is his first name was parental advisory
But then that was taken that was a nerdcore rapper, yeah
Man I smell like shit. I'm also I'm back in the hottest room in America today. It's cold out here
Yeah, it's pretty cold. It's cold out here. It's cold
Yeah, I'm excited to go back up north. I leave in I leave in ten days
Nice and I dry I'd oh wait no less than nine days
Eight one hour seven an hour. Yeah
I'm pretty excited. It's kind of the perfect time to move to New York City. Yeah, absolutely
It's really the best time to move there. Yeah, there's just more more and more things
Can we just pop we just put a pause on all this stuff for like the weekend of the 13th?
Just so I can move in you guys can can just both sides relax for like four hours
Okay, I have a lot of boxes. You're moving on Friday the 13th. That's crazy
This is gonna suck dude, this is I cannot be picking a worst
It's Saturday the 13th. Okay
I got worried. He's like
Yeah, as if I needed one more bad. Oh, yeah, that's the thing that makes you cancel it. Yeah
Cities on fire. Yeah. Wait, what's that? It's Friday the 13th, dude. I don't want to get murdered by Jason or Freddy
He already went to Manhattan. He knows how to get sure who yeah here. I guess I'll just move to space. Oh
I'm smoking the worst like oh, dude. Did you say no to June 13th? Never mind cuz 50 cents 50 cents
50 cents and you kids with your 50 cents and your Pokemon fucking 50 cents
God damn it. What are you what's going on right now? I don't know say are you just babbling?
I'm trying to say 50 cent, but I you're just trying to say that
Let's give you just right
Pat was trying to just say 50 cent and he ended up talking about Pokemon
He has a lot on his brain the
Best buy is refusing to give him his computer because they found some questionable stuff on the hard drive. No
Yeah, that's what happened. It was tough results tiger direct and they
Change you admit the rest of it. No, they changed the price is what change the price to scrub his hard drive. Yeah
Yeah, true. Yeah
He bought the incriminating video starter pack to add onto the hard drive to get it shipped
to him with illegal videos already on it.
I have too much head space.
Oh yeah, I bought...
Too much head space.
Pat bought Pete Townsend's computer on eBay as like a collector's item.
I'm such a big fan of the Who I Wanted to See.
I wanted all of the synthesizer tracks.
I wanted, he wanted to see what Pete Townsend saw.
No, you don't understand.
I'm just doing research on his research, okay?
I'm trying to figure out what he was researching.
I'm researching Pete Townsend.
But yeah, 50 Cent declared bankruptcy on July 13th
and I thought it was July, but it's June.
When did he declare bankruptcy?
July 13th.
Of last year?
2011.
Oh, damn.
I was gonna say--
He's like the richest guy ever,
'Cause he was like, didn't he start vitamin water or some shit?
- No, he had a vitamin water flavor.
- What did it taste like?
- It was a, oh fuck.
Yeah, I think it was like a grape flavor.
- It was just grape?
It didn't even do something fun?
- Formula 50, it was called Formula 50
and it was my favorite vitamin water flavor
when I was in the third grade.
- The flavor was blood on the sand.
- Yeah, it was the flavor was sand.
- Dude, I forgot about that game.
Yeah.
Where 50 cent, is that, doesn't 50 cent, I haven't played it.
Yeah, he's just great.
He like solves, he like solves the Iraq war.
I don't know.
That's the one I think where there's a button you can press and he swears when you press
the button.
Fuck.
Pretty cool, exactly.
I like that.
That's exactly what he would do.
I like the idea of like, George Bush was like, we think they have weapons of mass destruction.
Send in 50 cent.
He's been shot 50 times, he's invincible.
Yeah.
You can still get, I thought they discontinued Formula 50.
But no, you can still purchase Formula 50 on Instacart.
All right, let's get it.
Let's get, yeah, we'll get a pallet of Formula 50.
You wanna split a pack?
Yeah.
Why not?
Speaking of 50 Cent, who raps like he's from another planet,
who has a rapping ability like he's actually a Martian.
Yeah.
Or speaking, sorry, speaking of 50 Cent--
Like Martians versus goblins.
- Yeah, speaking of 50 Cent, who's a rapper,
and Lil Wayne is also a rapper who is,
who calls himself, he says he's a Martian,
and he'd be from another planet.
We have a list today that's about--
- We gotta work on our segues into that.
- No, that was perfect.
- No, no, no, I'm saying, but we don't do that,
we don't do that enough.
- Okay, wait, wait, wait, no, let me do a segue.
Speaking of 50 Cent, there are 50 planets,
but we're only gonna talk about 10 of them today.
we're reading the top 10 best planets from the top 10s.com. See how fun that
was? We got to do that. That was pretty fun. We gotta do that more. Patrick, what's your segway?
Okay, hold up, hold up. So speaking of vitamin water, they say that they found
vitamin water on Mars, which is one of the top 10 planets, which is the list
we're doing today. Speaking of 50 Cent, they sent Patrick to Pluto for the 50
videos found on his hard drive. And we're talking about the top 10 best planets.
Speaking of 50 Cent, I'm a rapper. I'm releasing a new song called Mario Lord of
the rings and it comes out today yeah but it come it came out yesterday if you're
on Saturn because it's a different time zone mm-hmm and if you're on Mercury it
came out three weeks ago yeah and if you're on the Sun you're dead
ouch the Sun's a planet I'll say it there's probably I'm gonna take my shirt
off. There's probably a guy in the sun. There's probably a guy living in the sun. There's a
guy in your sun. Why are you taking off your shirt? Put your shirt back on. Don't say there's
a guy in your sun and then take off your shirt. There is, there's a guy in Patrick's sun.
No. Yeah, Patrick's sun, Linus. I don't have a son named Linus. He has a son named Linus
because he's a huge Linus Tech Tips fan. Yeah. Yeah, he is. Yeah, I'm a huge, I named all
of my kids Linus Tech Tips. Patrick named his son Linus after his penis because it's a combination
of a line and a penis. Yeah, dude. It's two dimensional. I thought that was just like
a nickname. Nah, his name's Linus. What a crazy name. His name is Linus Tech Tips? Mm-hmm.
Wow. Yeah, dude. Yeah. It's a crazy ass name to have. He's fucking built for it. God, I
He has gauges, right?
No, no, he has like those,
he has like those, they're not like plugs,
they're those like, like the starter earrings
for when you like stretch your ears.
He has those and they'll like--
That's what I was thinking of.
The little like-- That's kind of a gauge.
The things they put in bulls' noses.
Uh-huh, a ring?
Why do they do that?
No, not a ring.
People are cruel to animals.
True.
Yeah.
That's what they, it's like animal testing,
but they tested earrings on bulls.
Like they test shampoo on Patrick.
- They test septum rings on 16 year old girls with tumblers.
- Yeah, for bulls. - And that's how
they get them onto the bulls.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
Top 10 best plans from the top 10s by Freddy Godzilla.
- That's a cool last name, that's a great last name.
- That's a good rap name.
- Freddy Godzilla.
- Freddy Godzilla, dude.
- That'd be a good--
- On his, so he lives in New York.
He says, "My favorite sport is football.
"My favorite food is meat, lol."
(laughing)
So we have a, this might be,
he might have been under the influence of meat
when he wrote this, so keep that in mind.
He might have, we might have some meat brain
kind of bleeding through this list.
- Number one best planet is Earth.
- Can't go wrong here, I'm gonna say that,
first and foremost, can't go wrong with Earth.
- Some other people disagree.
Someone says, "Earth is the most stupidest planet
in the world because of humans. There's a comment here that says, "I love the earth. I love
the nature. The earth, how the leaves turn into a different color. I have a thing for
tree, how they grow. It's all about nature." And that's a comment by Smooth Criminal.
I got a thing for tree too. Oh! That's why earth is number one, dude.
Because you can smoke weed on earth. Because you can smoke weed on earth and you can grow
grow hydroponics in your closet, even if you live at home.
You can grow Dro on Earth because it's the planet with the water.
You can grow Dro for show on Earth.
You know, that's why it's number one.
That's why they call Earth the hydro planet.
Yeah, that's why they call Earth the ganja planet.
Ganja.
Ganja planet.
Somebody's calling out this list and says, "Ha, only because we live here.
I bet if we all lived on Mars, then Mars would be number one."
Yeah, obviously. No, it would be Earth. No, it wouldn't, dude. Everything's red, dude. Yeah, that sucks. That sucks.
Imagine you walk out, like you wake up, you make an egg,
you crack your- And it's red. Yeah, red egg.
Yeah, you press fucking start on your coffee maker, red coffee.
You go to fuck your wife's ass, red ass and wife.
sucks dude
i live in a really always in travel around the third planet it has clouds
plants caves homes and other earth stuff i kind of like earth that way
that sounds like an alien to me
the road down on a canal i bet mars has read weed
there are a lot of it
they'll not only is like for weeds
yeah which gives you
to newt g mario pat
that's a little higher flared in mars and the fire for her
her yet
You can smoke red weed and get into a raccoon suit.
Mars has the fire flower and Earth has the higher flower.
Hell yeah.
You know what I'm saying?
That's facts.
And that's facts.
And that's just facts.
Yeah.
That's basically, we're in the cipher right now.
Number two is Saturn.
Saturn has rings around, I guess that's pretty cool.
But also, it's actually-
I think Jupiter's cooler than Saturn.
That would be my number two.
Saturn is married.
of the ring. Mm-hmm. That's pretty good. Saturn, I think, I think they're only
picking it because it's got those rings. Saturn is what you draw when you're
asked to draw a planet. Yeah. Not me. I would draw a Shoop-De-Whoop. If somebody
wanted me to draw a planet or anything, I would just draw it. I could do the best
Shoop-De-Whoop in class. Draw it right now. Okay, I'll draw it. I had like a, no, I just
grabbed it. That's not a pen. That's a vape pen. That's a vape pen. That is a blue
waffle easy it's not a blue waffle that's what you have in your no I don't
have a blue you do yeah you go to you walk into the baby gap and you said you
guys have pants I can fit my blue waffle in them you have pants with one zipper
for my penis and oh you know I never you know I could never go into a baby gap
and try on the clothes they have yeah because you're you know you're of a
restraining order from being in the big and tall baby clothes.
Yeah they do.
Pat goes to Oshkosh.
Just like a 6 foot tall baby.
Yeah baby gap big and tall.
Baby gap, baby, casual baby XL.
Big babies warehouse.
Yeah.
Fuckin' there's only like two big and tall stores, huh?
I think there should only be two big and tall guys.
Yeah. I think we need to eradicate the big and tall population. Me and my big dad.
Yeah, me and my huge dad. Yeah.
Top comment on Saturn is "Good luck living on this planet because it is just
a giant crystal ice storm."
I could live there. And my heart is cold as ice.
I would survive probably. I think you could drop me on any planet and I would survive.
I think if I if they were gonna execute me I'd request
getting sent to a planet. I would like to be killed like
like the cat at the beginning of the Simpsons movie.
I don't remember if he's itchy or scratchy, but the one who gets sent to the moon and then filled up with nukes.
Hmm. That's how I want to die. Yeah. Yeah.
I think I want to I want to get sent to like to Venus and then they just kind of drop me into space
So then I freeze and then I hit all the hot gas and Patrick wants to be he misspoke there
He said you meant that he wants to be sent to
Penis, yeah, he wants to shrink down like fantastic journey and go into a man's
Like the magic school bus and climb into a penis you're thinking of Ant-Man
Yeah, he wants to go into Ant-Man's penis. You're right. I'm sorry. Yeah, we were thinking of a man's feet
Yeah, he wants to he wants to he wants to crawl up inside Paul Rudd. He wants to make all my
Yeah
Scott Wang
Shut up, dude, cuz his name's Scott Lang you shut up. I don't know who that is. Yeah be quiet
Yeah, are you talking about yourself? I'm talking about Scott. I'm talking about Scott Wang
What if Patrick's name was penis Pete with penis balls?
Wouldn't that be pretty funny? What if Caleb's name was
Fucking bitch. No, I don't think
No
Nobody would name me that somebody would name you penis ball sack because your name is the thing you love the most and the thing you
Love second the most someone would name you penis ball sack. You just said that no, my name would be like
I said that you named that no you guys said you would my name is a like
My name would be like video games
Vagina no, we're like or like
like
Krispy Kreme
Krispy Kreme, but yeah, yeah, yeah, or like or like Avengers movie vagina or
Scott boobs Scott Scott
Pilgrim boo boo me name Caleb your name would be Michael estrogen
No, yeah, I would the thing. I love the most is Michael. Who's Michael Scott Michael Scott no
Yeah, you love that guy. I hate him. Mm-hmm. If you put me in a room with Michael Scott
I beat the fuck out of him
I would try to but then I wouldn't be able to because I'd be laughing so hard
He would use his special ability, which is a joke. Yeah, he's a special ability, which is being dumb as hell. Yeah
He would probably try and fire me for being the only good employee if I worked at the office. Oh my god
I'd be so pissed off all day for him as a fool's errand being an absolute nightmare working for Michael Scott, dude
He'd always be making you, he's always saying like just weird shit about your body.
He's always commenting on your body.
He's trying to harass you.
Yeah, he's always locking the door.
There's one comment on Saturn that says, "Earth is so overrated, real men live on Saturn."
And there's another comment that says, "Not a single lady."
(laughter)
Saturn is the planet for men.
It's a dude's pierced.
You just fucking show up.
No, they want you to think that there's a crystal ice storm on Saturn.
Because that's where the men are sent to.
Because women get so cold all the time.
They're always wanting blankets and asking you to turn the AC down.
Someone says, "No, this shouldn't be number two. It shouldn't even be on this list.
Nor should Earth be first. I know what should be first, though.
first
on water has the most interesting ring and is beautiful. My favorite planet since
young, although I live on earth and please continue to vote for Saturn.
Although I live on earth, I respect Saturn and I hope to move there one day.
I hope soon in the future I can live on one of Saturn's many rings.
Saturn is actually Latin for Satan.
Yeah.
It's actually short for Saturnicus, who was the demon god of buttfucking.
Yeah, and he was Patrick.
No.
Yeah, he was.
Yeah, I'm thinking he was.
Yeah, he actually was.
I'm looking at the, I just got the results in.
Saturn actually was named after Saturday, which is the day they play cartoons on TV,
so I actually think I am going to go live there.
Oh that's true.
Imagine a planet full of cartoons.
Imagine a planet made out of cartoons.
Who framed Roger Rabbit?
Planet dude.
Planet.
Planet crazy.
Planet Toon.
Yeah.
Toon World.
Oh my god.
Oh my god Toon World.
From Yu-Gi-Oh.
Uh huh.
We need to get, what's his name, Elon.
We need to get him on Toon World.
Yeah, we need, I think that.
He'd probably love it.
He'd probably love it because he could meet Rick and Morty.
True.
He would, dude if we convince him, we could get him to get us to Toon World.
We could trap Elon Musk in Toon World.
Yeah.
We could trap him in the Millennium Puzzle from Yu-Gi-Oh.
Hold on, this is kind of a weird thing.
Have you heard his baby's name?
His baby?
Oh my god, he gave birth to a cartoon.
His baby has a cartoon name.
Holy crap.
His baby is Spongebob's, Spongebob, his baby has a Spongebob-like quality to him.
Yeah.
Because it has a soft spot that you can poke.
Exactly, yeah.
Every baby is part Spongebob, just on like a one inch diameter.
You grow out of it.
You grow out, eventually you lose the Spongebob nature.
Spongebob, somebody dared, Stephen Hillenburg dared to ask the question, what if a baby
was all soft spot?
And he came up with Spongebob Squarepants.
Yeah.
The gay fry cook.
Exactly.
One of the most inspiring characters of our generation.
That's true.
Number two was Patrick.
Yeah, who is a baby with a job.
Yeah.
What if you could combine the job of an adult with the powers of a baby?
Of being stupid.
And pink and wearing only pants and no shirt.
Only pants.
pants yeah subscription box service that's yeah it's like blue apron just be
blue pants they send you they send you just thread and needle and you have to
make your own yeah very vague instructions you how to make jeans yeah
and then you finish it and it's like oh fuck I just got it I'm attacked by a fly
I'm attacked by a fly. Sorry, there's been a fly. This is like that it's like that
Breaking Bad episode where there's like a fly in the lab. I've been a fly has been
circling my head like. It thinks your head is a big egg. It thinks it's
it's a bird and I just got hit in the head in a cartoon and I'm dazed and
there's he's flying around my head as I loopily cross my eyes. It's pretty stupid.
But then every once in a while he bites the back of my head.
The fly's been biting you?
Yeah.
I think he's trying to feed on you.
He's trying to communicate with me in Morse code.
I think that might be Count Dracula.
I don't think so.
I think that might be Little Count Dracula.
Imagine if Dracula turned into a fly.
That's a really small Count Dracula turns into a fly.
Number three is Neptune.
Yeah, I know it looks cool, but it's just a ball of gas, so there's nothing to do, but
look at it.
If you go on it, you die.
It is just a gas storm with no solid surface.
Yeah, I mean, let's build like a dream planet, like as far as attributes.
Alright, so first thing, water.
Square.
Water, no, Gatorade.
Square shape.
Okay.
Gatorade run, Gatorade ocean.
What flavor Gatorade?
Wait, okay.
Glacier cherry?
Glacier cherry Gatorade oceans.
Okay, but then also the oceans are populated with Swedish fish.
Yes.
And the ground is chocolate ground.
And then if you dig in, gummy worms.
Yeah.
Yeah, and also the monkeys on the planet
are made out of gumballs.
And gummy bears are real, and you can actually--
Gummy bears are life-size terrifying bears.
That kill you and you can't eat them.
And also you have a--
And they're filled with meat.
Yeah.
They're gummy bears on the outside, so it looks like a gummy bear, but when you kill it
It's like killing a regular bear, and you get a scarab gun from Halo 2
Yeah, yeah, and there's a bunch of money on there that they they hate it
They hate money, and they just can't stop giving it to you, but they also have stores where they accept money
But then again they give it back. They have yeah, they have uh
What's that they have a concept store there so you can get cool shoes
Yeah, they have a GameStop. They have GameStop on GameStop concepts.
And there's an EB games. Every tree has a giant TV screen on it and you can controllers attached to it
and you can play games on the tree.
It's like when you went to a motel in
2001 and they had a 64 TV. Oh my god.
It's like that but the games are free. Yeah, you don't have to rent the games.
They also have school there, and you might be like,
"Oh, fuck school," but it's eight hours of recess.
Oh my God.
Eight straight hours.
That's kind of like a trade school.
And the play structure has a real spaceship in it.
Yeah, you can go back to Earth whenever you want.
Yeah, and the teacher has to be your girlfriend
if you ask her.
So if you get a hot teacher, that's a fucking bullseye win.
And the teacher is not mistrunchable.
- No, the teacher's mislunchable,
'cause you're gonna eat her up.
- They don't, they have no,
they have no mistrunchable there,
and they have no chokie.
- And also bread, bread has no crust on it.
So you don't even have to cut it off.
- All bread is uncrustables.
- Bread is made out of the stuff that they--
- Which is kind of a problem,
which is kind of a problem that it's all uncrustables,
because if you wanna make like a meatball sub,
you're gonna have some peanut butter and jelly in there.
- If it's all Uncrustables, none of it is.
Think about that for a minute.
- Who crusts the Uncrustables?
(laughing)
Who will crust the Uncrustables?
Fair question.
- Yeah.
- Neptune, this is another SpongeBob planet.
He's the king of the world in SpongeBob.
He's basically God in SpongeBob.
But he never meddles in earthly affairs.
He only really cares about the Krusty Krab.
- Yeah, why?
How can you be a god and love burgers so much?
That's a really good question.
Comment on Neptune that's in all caps
that says, "Beautiful, we need to live here."
Damn, facts.
We need to live here.
Damn.
Someone says, "It's blue, it's got water."
Need I say more?
She is my favorite planet.
She's beautiful and cool and have ring.
I love it.
Why is everything a girl?
Why are ships girls, planets are girls?
And girls are girls.
Cameron's a girl.
No.
Yeah, Cameron's a girl, Patrick's a girl,
I'm a boy. Caleb's a girl.
No, I'm a boy.
Caleb's a girl.
I'm not. Caleb's a girl.
No, I should not have even brought this up
'cause it is two against one, two girls versus one boy.
No.
Yeah, you guys probably think--
You're one cup.
You guys probably think Jupiter's number one
because you go there to get more stupider.
Mm-mm.
Yeah, me, I actually went to a little planet called college
and i got uh... i got more knowledge
and h_p_d_
so
who won here
yeah and a college it was only boys and you got a speedy there are no
yet do because the lunch lady at it and she put it in a house of lunch it was a
lunch gentleman
now yeah
there was a lot more did
uh...
it was love it was lunch jeffrey who is what is the lunch lordia
it was lunch larry
what's already
number four is mars
i'm surprised is number two did
uh... jack the top ten guy five
which is really good user
as uh... says i've heard that there will be life on mars will
i think that's not what mars is going to be uh... higher up on this list
Mars low-key fell off, dude.
Yeah, Mars is kinda slipping.
Mars used to be a lot of people's number,
Mars used to be a lot of people's goat.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
Somebody's listing the benefits of Mars here,
and they say, "God of War, candy bar, red."
Someone says, "Red like the Soviet Union."
That's what I'm talking about.
We know who said that, that was Rob Rousseau.
This guy.
That was a Rob Rousseau comment right there.
Mars is, yeah, Rob Rousseau's perfect planet.
It's populated by by communist girls who turn 18 tomorrow forever.
Yeah dude the years they are worth or the same length as 100 earth years so
uh girls can be barely legal. Only once you turn 17 and 364 days old. Exactly.
Yeah so it's just him like it's just him watching them and biting his knuckle.
Man that video is fucking weird. All every video he's made is so weird. Yeah. Let's get him on.
All right he probably will come on now. He's probably my best friend. He actually is my
best friend. He's actually one of his friend uh what's that other guy who uh. Oh Joshua for
Congress the other TikTok guy. Oh that dude yeah. No what's the what's the there's a guy who was
like one of those guys who was super into Warren. Sean McIlwain? Is it that guy?
Yeah, we're gonna get him on too. We're gonna have him and Rob Russo. We're gonna challenge
him to a finger off. He's better at fingering me. He's better at fingering? Yeah. I'm gonna dress up
like an anime girl and I'm gonna say, "You guys need to seize the means of reproduction."
And so who can finger my asshole better?
(laughing)
- 'Cause you reproduce with your ass.
- Yeah, I do.
It's actually an ability I learned in college
while you were on Jupiter.
- You lay a brown poop egg.
- I lay a brown poop egg.
- And a goblin hatches out of it.
- And then I crack it every morning for breakfast.
- Yeah, and the food is still perfectly preserved
inside of it.
(laughing)
You learned how to save some food from your stomach
and then poop it out untouched inside of a hollow orb.
- If Caleb just eats his poop like an egg all the time,
do you think it's gonna be like pee
where it's like you can drink pee once
but if you drink your pee again?
- You can eat poop forever.
- Oh, okay.
- 'Cause if you eat food, it turns into poop.
If you eat poop, it turns into food.
- I've never done it, so I wouldn't know.
- I'm a scientist, so I would know.
- Yeah, so I think Cameron knows by experience.
- No, I'm a scientist, I study things like this.
- What do you think poop tastes like?
- I would say probably brown and stinky.
- Yeah, I mean, like,
Munster cheese doesn't smell great all the time.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Munster, Asiago, these are very strong scents,
but all extremely umami flavors.
- Exactly.
- You know, so it might be something where like you,
You take a little bite, it's exactly.
It has an overpowering smell.
I'm sprinkling MSG on poop just to see.
It's like durian.
It smells bad but it's perfectly edible.
It's actually a great vegan alternative.
It's a great, you can make some doggos out of it.
Exactly, yeah.
I don't know, I think we might, you know, we might solve something.
- Yeah, I think we should contact the Beyond Corporation.
'Cause I think Beyond Poop--
- Yeah, you know it's Beyond Meat.
Poop.
Poop and shit.
- Butthead.
- That's right.
It's not a bad idea.
- Just hot Italian poop.
Brat, poop bratwurst.
- Poop bratwurst, cooking a poop like a sausage
with like onions around it.
I feel like that's a good idea.
It's like a beyond vegan poop, but it's that thing where they have to spell the meat differently,
so it's called P-O-U-P.
Patrick's been eating poops like hot dogs for years.
He puts sour crap on it.
And ketchup, and poop ketchup, which is red poop.
You eat a poop.
And mustard.
You eat a poop kielbasa with a throw up sauerkraut
and you put pea mustard on it.
- No, dude.
- No, Patty's poop mousse. - Pat, you put mustard.
Mustard.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Yeah, I must turd on Caleb's food.
- And then eat it yourself 'cause you can't help yourself.
- No.
- He can't help it.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, no, he can help himself.
I have self-control.
- He pranks Caleb by putting a log of poop
into a hot dog bun and leaving it
right outside Caleb's door.
And then he turns around to leave
and then he turns back and he goes, "Oh, a hot dog!"
- Yeah, and then he sticks his hand in
and forgot that he put a bear trap there.
- And then he eats his hand, and then he eats his hand.
- I wiggle my fingers around and I go,
"Ooh, don't mind if I do!"
- Yeah.
- And then you slurp it down.
- It's not that funny when I make fun of myself.
- And then you slurp it down like a big, thick noodle.
And it rockets into the back of your throat and chokes you.
- You can never slurp a turd like a noodle, Cameron.
- Right now, Patrick and Cameron are lady in the tramping
being poop. Man we're going back to our roots today. Yeah. Talking about poop and shit.
Yeah just talking about eating crap. I was thinking about the ages of this
podcast. We went first it was all about eating poop and then it was all about
the Grinch. We did that for a very long time. And then it's about and then it was about
uncles and cousins and then it was about teachers and now we're going back to
start the cycle again. Yeah. And the Grinch is a through line there too I
I think yeah, because I said the Grinch was perfect for the holidays. It was the holiday seasons
Poop the Grinch and cousins and teachers in that order. Yeah, what's that? What's our next move?
Yeah, let's
There's actually a Rothschild style council that decides what all of our
Sessions are gonna be we get a letter in the mail at the beginning of every month that says okay this month you have to
talk all the time about
um drinking pee out of a straw that's going to be the new thing that you guys are going to talk about
that's going to be it yeah injecting pee intravenously mainlining urine all right i
guess that's it i guess it's p this time yeah what's the um what's what's that fucking that
jay-z verse where he's just like werewolf frankenstein monster it's just yeah it's just
that but it's just like the grinch uncle's cousins what are these things all have in common
Oh man, they're all fucking stupid.
That's a little jab at ourselves right there that I just did by saying we're fucking stupid.
Yeah, we like to be self-effacing.
We like to be a little meta here.
Actually, I like to be self-effacing.
Cameron and Patrick like to be self-cum-facing.
You like to be self-soy-facing when you see your crap on the ground and you go...
No, no, Patrick does.
And Patrick, you actually...
You eat a poop.
No, you actually eat a poop.
No, man, you ate a poop.
You ate a poop.
- Oh man, you ate poop.
You ate poop for breakfast, lunch, and dinner.
And fourth meal, like Taco Bell.
- Caleb.
- What?
- You.
- No, don't finish that sentence.
- You eat a poop.
- No.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, number five is Jupiter, more like poopeter,
the home of Caleb.
- Yeah, ooh!
- Yeah, Caleb lives on that.
Well, hey Caleb, I know what planet you live on.
- Yeah, number six, that's where you live, Uranus.
- I just said it.
- No, you didn't say the name of the planet,
'cause you can't read that fast.
- I said that you live on your anus.
- No, you live on my anus.
- You live on my anus.
- You live on your anus.
- I really like the top comment on Jupiter,
really quick before we go straight into you guys' anuses.
The top comment on Jupiter is in all capitals says,
"This is freakin' giant, dude, LOL.
"Love the planet Jupiter."
(laughing)
- Someone says, "It is just a ball of fart gas,
but it is sideways and it is basically Saturn's retarded inbred cousin.
Yeah.
That's about Caleb's anus.
No.
They're changing the name of the planet to Caleb's anus.
It's basically a ball of fart gas.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's basically just a ball of fart gas, but okay.
Yeah, basically.
Just doing a NASA press conference where they're like,
"You're releasing new discoveries from on the planet Uranus."
Yeah, basically it's just a ball of fart gas.
We did a check on it.
We actually did a check.
We smelled it.
We actually smelled it.
It's like how radio waves take a very long time to travel.
Fart gas actually takes millions of years to reach Earth.
But now a wave of fart gas from Uranus is reaching Earth so we can identify it now.
The problem that we had before when we couldn't tell what the smell was, was we were all trying
We thought my friend Todd did it.
We were going off the knowledge that whoever smelt it dealt it and we couldn't figure out
just which planet it was coming from.
We were afraid to announce that Uranus was a ball of fart gas because we would get blamed
for it.
Exactly.
Yeah, I mean, and we had people here in NASA that we called crazy back in the day.
Like there's this guy, Warner Von Brown, who originally said that Uranus was probably a
a ball of fart gas, but we just didn't believe them for whatever reason.
And finally we figured it out, see, because radio waves take longer to travel, we finally
got a signal that said doorknob.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, and we said safety pretty quick.
And you know, we're starting to use AI.
We used AI to say safety almost immediately.
Yeah, yeah.
And we have a new, it's called Operation Diaper Shit.
And basically we're going to get all the smartest white guys to figure out exactly where the
fart came from.
We have new infrared scanners in space that are tracking farts from Saturn.
And it looks like, I mean, we're looking at it through a thermal call of duty scope and
we see we see a white cloud that's obviously giving us some heat signatures
and it's leading directly to a man named Patrick Dorn's asshole. It seems as if he
created from the time he was born millions of years ago a giant fart cloud
that grew a mind of its own and decided to move to space. He basically made a
fart baby who grew up to be Uranus. There's a the second comment on Uranus
says it is beautiful and rains diamonds yet bullied the planet didn't get to
choose its name so quit bullying it.
Do you guys think it rains diamonds?
Somebody says it just that word that make me laugh.
And while we're on the topic here at NASA one thing that's been a huge a huge
problem in researching that planet is that it just that word that make me laugh
and we can't even think about it without laughing so hard so someone says
Uranus is named after a butt what the check
I only voted for this name that's okay now that's the strategy that's how we win
the next election okay we change Bernie Sanders name to Bernie butt and then
people are going to vote for him just because of the name.
That's how we win.
Penis ball sack.
Yeah.
Penis ball sack is running for president.
You don't even have to campaign.
People will just see the name on the ballot and go, "Okay.
Yeah, alright."
Even the most far right, even Cameron and Patrick, two of the most far right people I know, they
will be led to vote for penis ball sack.
I'm actually voting for Rocky De La Fuente.
No.
So.
Yeah.
Yeah, from the movie Rocky.
I'm actually voting, I'm writing in essential workers on the ballot, actually.
Yeah.
I'm actually donating my money through the ballot.
I'm putting a $5 bill on the ballot.
I'm just writing $100 on the ballot and I'm hoping it gets to someone who needs it.
I hope it gets to the end of the right hands.
Number seven is Venus.
penis. Which very close to, it could be penis. It could be. There's a comma here that says
ugly and boring and common. There's a lot of penises. This is a dime a dozen planet,
dude. Hottest planet. They gotta make a planet named Pagina to finish the pattern. Uranus,
penis, and Pagina. My younger brother, my brother Levi, until he was like 16, thought that avocado
was called Abocado.
I think you said that before.
Have I?
Yeah, you did.
Sorry, I'm just thinking about it right now because I'm looking at him through the window.
Yeah, flip him off for me because he just...
I just flipped him off.
He's tying a noose around his neck.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, and a smaller noose around his penis.
Damn.
Yeah.
Oh, now he's doing kind of a Cirque du Soleil act with the two robes.
Oh yeah, he's fine.
Number eight is Pluto, which could be Poopo.
It could be.
You could call your penis your Pluto if we're going off.
You could.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's a good point.
Especially if you have gender reassignment surgery.
comment on Pluto that says the only one named after a dog. That's not true. Yeah.
My dog is named... My dog's name is Earth. That's what dogs say. They go "Earth, Earth."
Oh my god. They know where they are, dude. That's what they've been saying the whole time. Oh my
god. They've been trying to tell us. Yeah, and they don't realize we already know.
We don't need to know.
Yeah.
Yeah, there's gonna be one dog that's like, "Wait a second, guys.
I think I just saw, I just, they know that they're on Earth.
We can say other stuff now."
And then they're gonna be able to talk.
Pluto's just really cool and it's black.
It was also named after my second favorite Roman god.
Yeah, Pluto from Mickey Mouse Clubhouse.
Yeah, that's your favorite Roman god.
Yeah, that's your favorite Roman god, you fucking idiot.
you know as a moving rock
move fucking and harsh
uh... this fly just landed on my eyeball
system like a mccall
the socks number i skip ahead to because that there are a lot of contenders on
this one is thing is funny 'cause what i think the person who made the list
freddie godzilla just like real like one sentence about every planet
that like dislike all these
crazy planets uh...
and uh... like for example
let's see here
homey uh...
on the arts neptunes orbit this dwarf planet shaped like an egg and its
temperatures reach below four hundred degrees fahrenheit
there was one of the horse below four hundred degrees fahrenheit that's also
what it's like on earth
that's it's a lot of places that's below four hundred degrees fahrenheit that's
not that impressive
it's that it's called homey uh...
'Cause it's the hip-hop planet and it's cold because it's cool as ice.
Yeah.
Sedna.
This is the planet farthest from our solar system.
I said "na" to that.
I said "na."
Kepler- Make-make.
Kepler-12b.
I heard of this dwarf planet.
Make-make sounds like a Pokemon planet.
Yeah.
Sounds like what a Pokemon says.
If its name was Make-make.
Yeah.
Why did Pokemons know their names?
Because that's what they were named.
But why do they...
*sigh*
This is... this whole world is falling apart to me now.
So, they can...
Did they name...
Who names the Pokemon?
Do they name...
Are they just named after what they say?
It was God.
Oh, that must be it.
Right?
Yeah, like when Venusaur says Venusaur.
That's when they know it's Venusaur.
That's... they just call him Venusaur?
Yeah.
Yeah, because they don't really have like a...
A Latin, like...
That's how we name animals here too.
You didn't know that?
Is it true?
Dog, yeah they go dog, dog.
You never even listen really closely.
The noise of a fish swimming through water is like
fshhhhh.
If you just think about it all the stuff is there right?
That's a really good point.
But they only say it in battle.
No.
Ok, listen, a fly, it flies.
And when it flies it's saying
fly, fly, fly.
Well, the problem is most animals are so small that you can't hear them.
Exactly.
The vast majority of animals are this tiny.
The only time a fly's ever been heard is the movie Racing Stripes.
That's true.
Yes.
You know.
Wasn't Snoop Dogg one of the flies?
It was Snoop Dogg and me.
We just went into the booth and we just did the whole thing in a day, dude.
We smoked like an ounce of weed.
You just riffed.
There was no script.
They didn't even know that they were making the movie.
Me and Snoop Dogg just got high as fuck and I was like, "Yo, Snoop, what if we went into
the booth and pretended to be flies for like 8 or 10 hours?"
You guys went into the booth, had a conversation, and then the recording people listening to
were like, "Oh my God, we need to make these guys flies in a movie."
We have to write a movie about this.
We have to write a movie where they're flies.
It's just me and Snoop Dogg just smoking weed and we're like, "Man, I love being a fly and
our best friend's a zebra, man.
This is fucking sick, dude."
We live on a zebra's poop, man.
We live on a zebra's poop.
Man, I love- me and Snoop Dogg just saying, "Man, I love eating poop."
And he's like, "Nephew, poop is one of my favorite flavors."
That's right.
He said, he held a nug up to my nose and he was like, "Smell this, dude."
I was like, "It smells like shit."
And he was like, "Exactly, Playboy."
Yeah.
There's a planet on here called Glease 581G, and the only comment on it is, "It's actually
not known to exist. Yeah, there's actually a planet, there's a planet called, called,
or whatever the Transformers planet is. Cybertron. Cybertron, there's a planet called Cybertron.
We don't know if it exists, but we also don't know that it doesn't exist. Exactly. So I'm
gonna go ahead and throw this. That's true, we don't know if Tatooine exists or not. Yeah.
But we're just gonna, we can just say that it does. All the Star Wars planets technically
exist because if you think about it there's alternate universes for every
different decision that someone made in the universe right it like splits off
and forms a parallel universe and God could have chosen to make all the Star
Wars planets instead of Earth and the Earth's other what planets the other
brothers of Earth. There's even a planet there's even a reality not the one we're
in but there is a reality where Cameron is a boy. That's the one we're in.
Okay. No it's not the one we're in. No that is the one. It's as far away from our
universe as possible. There's also a universe where Caleb is correct about which universe
he's in, but it's not this one. Yeah, it's this one. It is this one. It's not. See, there
we go. He's proving my point even further. I'm going to go ahead and hit the reverse
seize button on that one. I'm going to go ahead and... I just hit it, so it's back to
you. I'm going to touch your buttons. I just put down a reverse Uno card and it just hits
to
hot in this room but I we're not we can't read the patreon people anymore
because there's too many because we are too good at this now yeah so thank you
guys yeah thank you everybody if my performance on this episode said
anything it's that we're too good is that Patrick is he carried us on his back
yeah we put the whole team on and we respect him for that I said something
about Headspace. He said something about Headspace, the app. I would say, so instead
of shouting out patrons, who should we shout out? I'd say we should
shout out donations to protesters, honestly. Yeah, to bail funds. Yeah, you can go to
blacklivesmatters.card, C-A-R-R-D dot C-O, and it has a bunch of really good links.
There's ways you can like donate even if you don't have money, like they
have like streamed like the YouTube videos with ad revenue.
- Turn off your ad blocker for that.
- Yeah, if you wanna donate, but you can't spare money.
- I know it's annoying to see that fucking ad on YouTube
where it's like the family and they're like,
we had triplets, oh, here we go.
But just turn it off, mute the thing and fucking stream it
if you don't have money, that's what I've been doing.
- Yeah. - I've been donating too.
And the second Final Destination movie.
(laughing)
Okay. It's really good.
It's really good, go watch it.
It has so many cool kills.
So like those two things.
The fifth one is the best though.
Hard disagree, hard disagree.
So we're doing, so definitely go donate,
go donate to Bale Funds and Black Lives Matter
and go check out Final Destination.
And stream all the Final Destination.
Yeah, it's actually, it's a great series.
If you're not old enough yet, technically,
if you're not 17, you're not allowed to watch it,
tell your parents that it's really just violence.
There's no nudity and there's very little strong language.
- There is nudity, though.
- There's, well, maybe in the end you like.
- Well, then just don't say--
- Doesn't the second one have the one
with the tanning bed kill?
- No. - That's the third one.
- That's the third one. - Oh, okay.
- Self-finance decisions-- - Is the second one
the amusement park or is the third one the amusement park?
- The second one's the amusement park.
- Okay, yeah, so that one has Ramona Flowers in it.
If you're a kid, you'll love that.
You can tell your parents the sequel to Scott Pilgrim.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Oh, and watch Scott Pilgrim too.
- Yeah, stream that too.
- Scott Pilgrim is about a 22-year-old grooming
a 17-year-old with video games.
So if you like that-- - And he's awesome at it.
- So if you like that, check it out.
- If you like that, which Patrick does.
Yeah, it's actually based on Patrick's memoir.
- It's not based on my memoir.
- Yeah, it's like-- - Your memoir?
- It's stylized like-- - My memoir
has not been written yet.
It's stylized like Pac-Man, but it says Fat Man.
(laughing)
And it's a picture of Patrick and he's eating a ball.
That's funny.
He's eating a basketball.
Yeah, well in Fat Man, he doesn't go for the fruits
to eat the fruits.
When you eat the fruits, it lowers the score.
Yeah, and then he eats the ghosts too, and also the walls.
Oh, you could eat a ghost at any point.
You couldn't.
You could just open your mouth and inhale it.
Yeah, I'm eating a ghost right now.
It's like a spider, it's like how you eat spiders
in your sleep.
the human beings eat eight spiders within their lifetime they only a double the
amount in ghosts they eat millions of ghosts uh-huh
every time I say double double of eight is close to a million yeah all right go
donate yeah seriously do donate it's like seriously watch it is important
yeah watch Final Fantasy watch the Final Fantasy let's play as a Final Fantasy
with adblock turned off
uh... true
that'll do it
all right by
by the end
you.
[BLANK_AUDIO]