You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
- Podcasts for the hopeless.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
- I look smooth.
- Yeah, we--
- Yeah, Caleb looks very smooth today.
- For about like five or 10 minutes just now,
we just thought that Caleb had accidentally turned on
the smoothing, the face smoothing option on Zoom,
but then we just found out he didn't
and his face just looks like that now.
- Nah, I'm just naturally smooth, man.
I just have naturally smooth skin dude.
I'm blessed by the Cherokee gods.
Yeah.
Big Panther, Small Bird.
More like freaking raw chicken if you ask me.
Yeah, you'd look like a raw chicken.
You'd be called Chief Raw Chicken like my cat.
Nobody would call me...
You'd be called Chief Mayo.
No, no.
When I return...
Chief Mayo, man!
No, nobody would call me...
But thank you for assuming I would be the chief, by the way.
But no, I would not be the chief.
You would not.
and I would not be Hunter Mayo I would be Hunter Mayo sounds like the kid at your
high school that got in trouble for like having stuff on his phone I would be
brave beef man you're you're yeah my Indian your Native American name would be
burning cross no crouching tiger hidden dragon dude I would be a kung fu Indian
it would be sick everybody would fear me all the other if I could if I could go
back I'm not not a time machine I would go back in time and I would teach the
Native Americans kung fu so they probably I think I'm like a whole 5%
Indian dude yeah I think I'm saying Indian not Native American so I don't
know which one you're talking about I think you know I think you know no I
I don't know.
I can't tell.
Yeah, I think you do.
You think I'm, you think I'm, you think I'm, is that Southwest Asian?
Southeast.
Southeast Asian?
You think I'm Southeast Asian?
Yeah.
No, Southeast Asian is Japan.
No, it's not.
Yeah.
Think about the directions, Pat.
Depends on where you're looking.
Depends on, so if you're looking, if you are looking at the globe upside down, then yeah,
you might be right, actually.
You might be, you could be right there.
I guess that is Southeast Asian.
No, that would be Northeast Asia. Southeast Asia would be like, would be Europe.
Yeah. Whoa. Whoa. That's deep. If you change the perspective of the globe...
You might change your perspective. Yeah, you might change your perspective. Think about
this for a second. If you spin the globe 360 degrees, you end up in the same spot.
Think about it. If you flatten out the globe, we're all Asian. Yeah. Every single person in the world.
If you take a big sharpie and you write the word Asia across the entire surface of the globe
Then everybody becomes Asian dude. We just solved every problem that there is.
Yeah, that's the root of the problems is not enough people are Asian.
If everybody became Asian, we're getting there dude. We'll get there.
It's just slowly but surely.
It's like that we're all one race, the human race, but it's like we're all one race, Asian.
We're all one race. We're all Chinese when you think about it.
if you think really closely and you close your eyes if you if you write China on
the globe then we're all Chinese yeah damn it's not it's not earth anymore
it's China whoa the globe the globe more often than not would say made in China
so that whoa so if you just hold it in dude yeah yeah I think we just
discovered the Illuminati truth of the world I know yeah the whole world is
China. It's that astronaut meme, but it's just the, uh, it's China.
Let's do some other memes real quick.
Yeah, let's do some other memes.
Good Guy Greg.
Good Guy...
Let's you have $100.
What about like a combination? What about a combination one?
Like that they used to do, like the socially awkward penguin?
Steve.
Socially awkward penguin.
Troll Face. Troll Face.
this my life and i just remembered the fucking bloodhound gang did a whole
song that's just socially awkward penguin means that's sick to
that's really like that yet
yet the whole song is just them reading off socially awkward penguin i'm in the
blood and gang
yeah i wish are you're in a man in the but pound gang
net
that's right
your but was a pound
[Laughter]
Dude, Pat has a little butt, man. That's on record now.
It is true.
Dude, you will never get hired.
Oh my god, I'm so fucking tired. I stayed up until like 5.
New XNL hire Patrick Doren reportedly has a little butt.
And I'm fired for it.
I stayed up until like 5.
I modeled the D3 in Skater XL.
You were modeling for a five-year-old.
Yeah.
No.
You were modeling for D3.
Diablo 3.
You were creating your own Diablo 3 character.
Yeah, you were being the devil.
I made the D3 in Skater XL last night.
No you didn't.
That's what I did.
No you didn't, dude.
No you didn't.
You're a liar.
You wish you did.
You were dreaming.
I fucking did it, dude!
Is this game just your life now, dude?
You just pretend to skateboard?
No, I go skateboard sometimes.
when i just said you it would you dream
remember my dream from last night i was
watching a bunch of the simpsons before
i went to bed and then i went to bed and
i had a dream that the simpsons were
running away from a terrorist attack
that they're walking around it was like
it was like one of those dreams where
i'm not in and i'm just like looking at
people you know yeah i kind of like
watching and it was like the simpsons
walking around the city and they saw
building blow up and had to run away
Fuck dude, that's heavy.
Yeah.
Dude, that's like a creepypasta.
Yeah dude.
I had a dream interrupted, I told you guys this
yesterday morning, I woke up by
so I woke up and I was
acting, I woke up like a millisecond
before I fell off of my bed
and I woke
up, felt myself falling and I just went
"Oh no!"
And I fell
and I hit my head on my metal bedside
table oh yeah but like I big a hole in the back of my fucking head and then
Jana woke up and went oh my god and I was on the ground and with morning wood I
had a giant boner coming out of the back of my head and it almost happened again
like 30 minutes later I like went back to sleep and then woke up and I was
falling off the bed again.
Why do you keep falling off the bed?
Dude, I have no idea.
What are you dreaming about?
I dreamt that I had a kid.
(laughter)
I dreamt that I had a newborn child
and I fell off the bed
and I woke up and I had metal in my head.
There's still a piece of my head
is stuck to the metal on my bed
and I...
it's like fused to it. Like I can't even get it off
my fingernail. Oh my god.
It's really bad too.
- That's awesome.
- Wait, it's on your fingernail now?
- No, I couldn't, I tried to scrape off,
there's like a piece of my flesh
with like two pieces of hair in it.
(laughing)
And I wanna put it back on my head.
- Well dude, if it's got hair in it,
that's not your flesh, that's someone else's.
- Wait, no, Caleb, you could take that hair
and you could move it to like a different--
- Yeah, that's a graft right there.
- You could graft it on a different part.
- True.
- If you fall out of your bed every morning forever now,
Eventually you'll have enough for a graft.
Uh-huh, you could do a whole follicular tramp transplant.
Follicular tramp stamp.
Fuck off! I went to bed at 5.
I went to bed at 5. I was making a shoe in a video game.
You knew we were recording at noon, dude. What are you doing?
I was making a shoe in a video game!
No, yeah, high heel.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, you were making a high heel and Patrick dressed up.
Yeah, high heel to stomp out your ball.
You're not gonna stomp my balls, dude.
I will.
I'm not into that, dude. I'm not one of those comedians.
(laughter)
- Woo!
- Ah, that's good.
- That's enough of that.
(laughter)
- Yeah.
- We're not gonna talk about that anymore.
- That's enough of that.
- That's the quota on that one.
(laughter)
- I've been in a good mood all day though.
- Yeah.
I drank a whole big can of Monster before this,
like the big ones.
- Dude, I drank a bang, the bang cola yesterday.
- Oh yeah, that's good.
- It's the worst thing I've ever had in my fucking life, dude.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah, bang cola, that's like a fallout,
fallout consumable item.
- Dude, it's horrible.
And also like, I, like the caffeine is like nerfed
in the bang cola because of the taste.
Like my brain is too focused on like clearing
my taste buds out to even get like a rush from the caffeine.
- With another bang.
- Yeah, exactly.
Have you ever double banged?
you ever bang banged no dude I don't I do not have the fucking mental capacity to
do that you never bang bang skeet skeet no dude I've double banged one time in
LA well Will Cameron and I on a stream like the other night we looked up we
found a caffeine calculator to see how many like energy drinks he can drink in
one day like what's the safe limit yeah and what how many energy drinks will
kill you yeah you can find out the lethal dose of every I guess there's a
lethal dose of caffeine that makes sense yeah what is it for me it's - you have to
enter in your weight it's true so we were to energy drinks
two banks two banks they won't it won't kill you but it will be unsafe if you go
past yeah you you will get like sick I've definitely had unsafe levels of
caffeine before yeah oh me too I've had like full like like I don't know what the
I'm doing right now like the other every time I stop like drinking for a little
bit I think is a lethal dose yeah unless you're like Rob Dyrdek and then that's
just breakfast yeah wake up smash 50 bangs yeah we also did a kid the
calculations and we found out that if you were just eating bouillon cubes you
would die your your stomach would rupture before you died from sodium poisoning
just so you really yeah so it's safe it's safe yeah okay I didn't know that there
was sodium poisoning I mean you can get poison right pretty much anything any
water by the way you can there there is water poisoning that's called drowning
yeah yeah overdose on water dude so the amount of it's my maximum of monster
Ultra Fiesta four cans per day so I could drink like two today to stay under the
safe but it takes it takes a hundred so it's a hundred monster yeah the legal
limit yeah on energy drinks the legal limit there has to be a point where it's
like you can't dry yeah you have 40 bangs which is like tech it's not enough to
kill you but like you're gonna be going crazy you're gonna be you're gonna be
If you drink that many bangs you can just clip through the other cars you can just slide through the street like a ghost
That's sure you will no clip through the other cars. Yeah, that's like
Don't want you to have 50 bags. Yeah, they're hiding truth. They're hiding the truth
They just go through all the other cars you drink 40 bangs
And it's just like it's like God dragged your Photoshop layer just up one notch
front. Yeah, you don't bump into things anymore.
Yeah, I think the most I've ever had was Tupang, so I think that's
probably the most caffeine I ever had. I remember just like I had like hot sweat
you know. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I had green hot
carbonated sweat dripping off of me. I don't think I've ever drank more than one
energy drink, but I've drank a lot of cups of coffee in a day
day before. I'm more of a coffee guy. I've had like maybe six cups of coffee in a day.
Yeah. I don't, I'm not a coffee person. That's why I drink Monster. I fucking hate coffee.
It's too bitter for me. I mean, that makes sense. There's a clear divide here if you
look at me and Cameron and Patrick, who drinks coffee and who drinks Monster Energy. I drink
the zero sugar one. That's even worse, dude. Is it? Yeah, man. When I, dude, I, when I
- I didn't blow you up,
'cause I feel like it does make sense.
- I used to drink like two Coke Zeros every day,
and I like didn't dream for six months.
- Well, I don't mind not dreaming.
- I mean, the thing about the sugar-free Monsters, Pat,
is that instead of putting in sugar,
they put in like, they just put in chemicals
that will like mutate your taste buds enough
to think it's sweet.
- They put in cotton candy.
- Yeah, they put in like,
they put in just viruses and bacteria
to make your brain think you're drinking something sweet.
- They kind of just put in whatever's around.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- That does make sense.
If I was told that, that they just put in
whatever's around, I'd be like, "Yes."
- It's just like crushed up glass and shit.
- It's just whatever the factory worker sees first,
when they first get the can.
- Yeah, man, it's all just, it's just metal and glass.
- Dude, I feel like a fucking Mormon
when I talk about energy drink consumption.
It's just like, 'cause like they don't drink caffeine, dude.
Oh, they don't drink caffeine?
No.
Oh.
You didn't know that?
I thought that they drank fucking...
I thought they drank alcohol and caffeine
and said swears and didn't believe in God.
I thought they drank...
I thought they drank like soda.
They drink sugar.
They drink maybe a Sprite, maybe a, you know.
Sprite has caffeine in it.
No, it doesn't have caffeine in it, you stupid.
Sprite has caffeine.
Yeah, they wouldn't be included in a Happy Meal
if it had caffeine buddy.
There's enough caffeine in a McDonald's hamburger.
They don't need a Sprite as well, dude.
It's true.
Do they have any caffeinated food yet?
Yeah, dude.
Yeah, they make...
Caffeine pills. Pills are food.
That's true.
What about like yogurt?
Yeah, what about yogurt?
Caffeine yogurt?
Oh, they make Bang Makes a caffeinated ice cream.
Oh, that's horrifying.
That's true, caffeinated ice cream.
I know.
That is horrible.
They have like energy bars, right? That's a thing?
Yeah.
No, you're thinking like a Clif Bar.
Yeah, but okay.
That's just peanut butter.
That's just peanut butter and oatmeal, dude.
Let's see.
Peanut butter, but it has caffeine.
I'm just gonna search caffeinated food.
See if we can order it.
Yeah.
Caffeinated food.
Oh, they have like caffeine gum.
Chocolate covered coffee beans.
Coffee, energy drinks.
And drinks are not food.
Eating a coffee bean is not.
Oh, yeah.
Chocolate has caffeine.
That's true.
Alright, stay corrected dude.
Foods with caffeine from sleep.org.
This is our list from today.
For today, let's see here.
Breakfast cereals.
What the hell? Cereals such as
Quaker Coco Blast and other chocolate
flavored AM munchies can pack
up to 11 milligrams of caffeine.
Pudding has caffeine?
Pudding has
caffeine? Someone just hacked my
bluetooth speaker and started playing music
is
You can buy caffeinated energy bars.
Yeah.
You can.
I'm banned.
Yeah, I can.
I'm not allowed, dude.
You're not allowed because of how many you ate?
Because, yeah, I ate too many.
I want a lifetime supply.
Yeah.
And they said I'm not allowed to have any more.
I wish I had something like that.
I wish you had nothing.
I've been back on the yerba mate.
Yeah.
What I like about it is that it doesn't taste good and it's expensive.
My grandpa, my grandpa John gave me a bunch of it when I was uh, he gave me a brick of it wrapped in like
A brick of yerba mate? Oh like the dry tea?
Yeah, and he was like, "Oh you might need a tea baller to drink that" and then he just handed, to drink this and he hands me like a fucking
A brick of yerba mate.
He's literally using you to traffic drugs.
I thought it was.
Absolutely.
I thought it was but didn't smell like it.
Yeah, that's why.
he's been he's been like completely he stopped smoking weed and stopped
drinking when he was 40. Oh good for Grandpa John. Yeah. Yeah. He's just a psycho.
Is he a ghost? Is he the one that travels around New England and
meeting people in bathrooms? He doesn't meet people in bathrooms he meets
them at train stations. Okay. He doesn't meet them in the bathroom.
He doesn't meet him in the bathroom.
Yeah, alright, unless you correct me there, that's fine.
He meets people like on the...
He uh...
Dude, he might be like...
I think I told you guys about this.
He might be Mossad.
Maybe.
Oh my god.
He might be an intelligence asset.
Yeah, my family's connection to Israel.
Yeah, it's gonna come out one day.
Yeah.
Sooner or later.
Did I ever tell you about the time...
So there was like a, he was waiting for the bus
'cause he used to take like the Boston Express
to like go down to just fucking walk around Boston.
- Gotta love Boston Express.
- Yeah, dude, it rocks.
It rocks, it absolutely rocks.
But fucking, so he like was walking around Boston
or whatever, came back, went to the bus station and--
- Speak into your microphone.
- There was a dude, I was talking into it.
- You were, as in--
Oh yeah, you were facing, you turned your head around 180 degrees like that.
I saw something outside.
Anyway, he...
Outside where?
There's no window over there.
There's a window over there!
Show us the window.
I can't.
What just happened to your mic, Caleb?
What happened to it?
You just got really loud.
I just got really loud?
You just got insanely loud.
Yeah.
Well, I'm proud.
It's fine by me.
So he...
There was like a handicapped person trying to get on the bus, like someone with a wheelchair,
and he's like, "Oh hey, do you need help with that?"
And the guy's like, "Fuck off!"
And then my Grandpa John starts like getting into an argument with him,
'cause he wouldn't let him help, and he's like, "I don't need your fucking help!"
And he's like, "Let me help you!"
He was telling me on the way home, 'cause we took the bus home together one day,
And he was like, "I was about to fucking punch the guy."
It's like, it's a guy in a wheelchair, man.
What do you even do to that guy? How do you make it worse?
Did your mic come unplugged or something, Caleb?
No, it's plugged in.
What the hell did you do?
I don't know, something awesome.
Alright.
Is it really that loud?
We can just hear background noises too now.
I don't know, maybe it's maybe...
Maybe I'm imagining it.
Is it better now?
I think it's, yeah, I think it's fine now.
I don't know what happened.
Um.
Yeah, I mean, what do you, a guy in a wheelchair, how do you, what do you even...
You cannot fight a guy in a wheelchair.
And what if he's like, what if he's built like, like Scrappy-Doo at the end of the Scooby-Doo
movie?
What if he's just ripped in his arms?
Yeah, what if there's a little dog inside him?
Yeah, yeah, what if he's being piloted, like Mr. Bean by a little dog?
Yeah, if he was being piloted, yeah.
I don't know.
He's...
he's my grandpa's Mr. Bean.
No, the guy in the wheelchair is Mr. Bean.
Mr. Bean didn't survive those movies.
Mr. Bean was controlled by Scrappy-Doo.
Mr. Monteverius.
That's his name in the movie.
No, that's another Mr. Bean that we gotta put in.
To the Bean bracket.
Scrappy Bean.
Scrapper Bean.
We can get that going soon, that bracket, probably.
Yeah, we can probably figure that out.
No, we're putting him up.
(all talking over each other)
- Today we have top 10 worst places from,
of course the top 10s.
- Yeah, we're never doing another website.
- No, come on, it's easy.
- I'll find some more.
- This one is very top heavy with how good it is.
The first one is just like,
the comments are incredible,
and then it just is kind of gradually gets worse.
But at the very least,
we got to read these comments on the first one.
So it's the top 10 worst places.
number one is hell
uh... and the top comment is from the gillicuddy
and it says
if there's absolutely one place i am certainly not going is hell i would do
absolutely anything to stay away from this place a person in richard sigmund
was able to get a glimpse of this place look up my time in heaven book and he
gave a horrifying description of what hell is actually like pure eternal
torture being burned by fire ripped apart by demons and put back together to
repeat the process, raped and so much other wild, torturous bullcrap that it's
just unbearable. No. No, no, no, no. I don't care what anyone says. Of course, I've
never seen it, but do I care? Well, considering the circumstances, hell no.
I'm a Christian and I'm staying a Christian because experiencing something
like this for an eternity is just ridiculous. I'm staying faithful to God.
Screw that. That's what I would be- if I was being eternally raped and tortured
by demons I'd be like this is a bunch of bull a bunch of wild my time in heaven
this is not go to heaven at all because in the clearly did not go to heaven in
heaven there's a porthole that you can yeah to see hell that's the only TV show
they have in heaven yeah yeah just like a natsu's like aren't you glad you're not
going through this right now yeah you just get to see them torture Mac Miller
all day come on you just get to sit there yeah yeah the only people are gonna the
only people that are clearly going to heaven or white rappers all go to hell
every last one yeah yeah even weirdo unfortunately oh and not because he's
Jewish because again we covered that. Why the fuck?
The evil realm Satan tortures everyone with fire it is scary how satanic the whole place is.
It's scary how satanic hell is. Seriously satanic in here dude it's also really hot
whatever you do do not go to hell after you die it's even worse than the DMZ
what it in Korea DMV no I think that the demilitarized zone in Korea yeah I think
is just like a wall yeah it's like a fence do you think that those guys like
do you think like the North Koreans try to like that you know what it's named
after the DMZ. No. Dennis Miller's zone.
Sarcasm. There's a sign that says sarcasm is not allowed with not scribbled out.
Yeah.
There's a Korean guy just uh just just standing at the DMZ just being like
oh I would totally hate it if you came over here.
I would totally hate it. I would seriously hate it if we got into a scuffle right now.
So the North Koreans are in the news again.
Whenever. That's like Putin going down the Berlin Wall on a "Joanie loves Chachi" you know what I'm saying?
Get 'em Dennis. Sick 'em Dennis.
Whenever someone from whenever like a North Korean peasant escapes North
Korea and like crosses the entire ocean on like a piece of paper raft and then
like makes it to America and they're like oh it was so horrible there they're
being sarcastic yeah yeah yeah super when they say they don't give us food
they're going they don't give us food yeah they totally the thing is the
sarcasm tone doesn't translate yeah yeah yeah cuz they learn English they don't
learn that kind of you know the rhythm that you have to say exactly
sarcastic right they are fluid and sarcasm yet oh yeah they aren't like me
they aren't fluid in sarcasm that's how the that's how everybody thought that
Kim Jong-un had died with somebody's like did he die in the right case?
Yeah he's totally dead and you know who's replacing him? His sister.
I'm not a real great person but I plan to become generous and kind now I really
hope I don't go here we can't even imagine what the horror is like here and
then Doro Explorer 13 replies to that comment and says if you don't want to go
there then accept Christ as your Savior thanks Doro Explorer here's another
comment yeah of course it's the first because it burns fire Lucifer and Satan
next to you and demons running and abusing each other and will drop you
into the fire pit that's so true I'd hate to go in the fire pit in hell dude this
is my biggest fear worse than hell this is my biggest fear just thinking of it
gives me shivers for a long time someone said actually Lucifer and Satan are the
same person whoa oh my god dude hell he dude he'll heal is the most metal place
ever invented that's a metalhead would love hell that's yeah dude this is
awesome this rocks dude yeah this rocks I love this I love hell yeah I seriously
love hell yeah they're gonna make me they're gonna make me one of the guys
here I'm gonna be a bouncer I'm like working my way up in hell you're gonna
make me one of the guys in hell that's what I heard yeah I started yeah start
being tortured with like you know Elvis and now I'm like basically the boss yeah
they saw my sepulchre t-shirt and they thought it was pretty cool yeah they
actually let me do guest vocals during one of their slave driving sessions I
actually got to scream at all the tortured souls someone said yes schools
the worst hell yeah dude someone says I'm not going to hell I would rather go
futuristic robot world. Me too. No I wouldn't want to go there. That's the mistake everyone
who dies and goes to hell they make the they make the mistake of not just going to futuristic
robot world instead. That's true. That's like that's Muslim hell. There's three.
There is three. You're right there's three. There's three, there's heaven, there's hell,
and there's futuristic robot world. Yeah. And you choose and not futuristic robot world didn't exist
till we got VR. Until Lost came out. Yeah. Until the final season of Lost.
And they were like, it's this third thing. See, there's not a lot of people in
the futuristic robot world. There's a lot of criteria you have to meet to be able to get in.
See, there's a... what's that? You have to take the Turing test to get in.
You gotta watch Robots with Robin Williams. Cyber Peter is at the gate.
Cyber Peter Griffin is at the gate.
Cyber Peter Griffin is at the gate and he's like,
"Beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep,
beep beep, take the Turing test."
And if you fail, you go to hell.
Oh my god.
Yeah, but if you get in he goes,
"Confirming, freaking sweet."
Number two,
New Jersey. That's right. Yes let's fucking go. Woo! Let's go! First comment. Yeah read it.
Worse than hell for good metaphor see exorcist prequel where Lucifer fell from
heaven and landed on earth on the way to hell they built a church over the spot
where that evil landed with swords pointed down to keep Lucifer from
escaping then buried the church so that no one would find it and open it. Too
late. Christy and the rest of the damned evil state of New Jersey are ready are
already out and raining hell on earth. Too late for the Lord's Prayer to deliver
us from evil? Kingdom come to Canbun County? To Bergen County? Probably not and
most certainly not the case now." I really like the second comment. Chris Christy
Chris Christy dug up the church from the Exorcist 2? Is that what they're trying to say?
Yeah, to do his bridge, or to stop the bridge.
Yeah.
The second comment is, "God help those suffering in New Jersey.
God speed to those families not yet afflicted.
And God damn those in New Jersey who cause all the suffering until the strong and those
not yet too weak to fight can vanquish them and save all the people and their children
suffering at their malicious and evil hand."
God help the people in New Jersey.
Finish your food.
in New Jersey who don't even have food and they have to be Italian just finish
your goddamn food what and J is actually a great place we have great schools a
great place to raise families good drivers many diners many tourist
destinations fresh food and vegetables clean beaches people pumping our gas for
us and best of all six flags great adventure you guys New Jersey's not like
hell we got a six flags yeah we have the world's only six flags yeah I love you
obviously people pumping our gas for us do they think that's great Jersey thing
is six flags great adventure like no no that's just the name of six oh no wait
is it a specific one yeah it's like the big six flags or whatever man oh it
actually is awesome now they think about it yeah great adventure they also think
they have a jersey great because they have food and vegetables there that's
That's something that's really great about New Jersey.
- Oh, there's so many vegetables in New Jersey.
- Dude, it's paradise.
We have blockbusters and we have grocery stores.
- We have roads you can drive a car on.
- Yeah, we have cars with four wheels.
- Yeah.
You guys aren't gonna believe this,
but the children are allowed to play
on playgrounds at recess here.
- Whoa, okay.
- Yeah.
- Wow.
- I'm pretty sure we even have a candy shop in our town.
You'd think that the state that Bon Jovi came from,
they wouldn't allow children to--
- So you're trying to make me look like a laughing stock?
I from New Jersey, loser.
You must be a redneck from Mississippi.
You must have been born on the Belt Parkway
because that's where most accidents happen.
We have Six Flags Great Adventure.
What do you have, some cheap rides from Chuck E. Cheese's?
Oh, should I mention that you are such a loser?
- Yes.
Woo, get 'em.
That Belt Parkway line is great, dude.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
That's a burn right there.
Yeah what are you from the nuclear factory from the Simpsons?
Cause you're having an ass in a lot of the opening credits.
This is a comment from SelfieFan68 that says "My city eyed not that bad."
Hell yeah.
Let's see here.
Woah.
Alright wait wait.
Oh my god.
This is the lo- this comment is so fucking long, Jesus Christ.
Is it on New Jersey?
This is- it's about- yeah, it's about, um, it's about the Clintons, um, trafficking children
and every word is capitalized.
Through New Jersey?
Not just gang violence, a corrupt state in many corrupt counties and areas surrounding
Camden and Englewood and Newark and Hoboken and, god damn, the state of New Jersey, as
bad and evil as Orwell's 1984 and Nazi Germany put together.
The division literally tortures and drugs and institutionalizes children and uses the
political abuse of psychiatry and court savagery with Gestapo police to do the
same to anyone who is for rights. Schools or they fear will say anything about the
rampant corruption and tyranny known by any attorney with the better ones just
beginning a fight to protect the people and residents and the children and the
families of New Jersey join the fight against the state of New Jersey
corruption malfeasance family court criminal enterprises and tyranny and
that's not even- Family court criminal enterprises?
That's not even half of that comment. It's insanely long.
They steal 40 billion dollars every year across the US.
Most of the abducted children are abused, sexually abused,
put on horrific psychotropic drugs to control them, and over half end up
homeless and
80% in prison and sex trafficked on the streets.
Horrific child holocaust. That's my favorite
Italian horror movie from the seventies.
Yeah. New Jersey Holocaust. Yeah. New Jersey, huh? New Jersey Holocaust. Yeah, I'm thinking.
Yeah, that'd be a great movie. I'm thinking about it. That would be a great movie. I don't get it.
New Jersey Holocaust. Are you talking about Italy? No, I just think it, uh, I think it'd be good.
I just think that'd be a good plot of a movie to happen. It'd be a good plot, it'd be a funny
plot of a movie yeah I like scary and funny number three jail mm-hmm
just read that man created this list when we were bored in school he put jail on
the list but not prison but then somebody else must have added prison to
the list later and it went up here damn so jail and prisoner on here I feel like
I'd be I'd be I'd be awesome in jail yeah I could become that's give me you
give me you give me in the mailroom you give me one in the license plate room
I'll work my way up.
- Become the warden in a week.
- I'll become the warden pretty fast.
- Yeah, jail is about working your way up.
People don't realize that.
- 'Cause a lot of the people, they get to jail,
they just give up.
- You airdrop me into a jail,
by the end of the day, everyone's gonna be friends in there.
- You airdrop me a funny picture
while you're visiting me in jail.
- I'm gonna laugh.
- And guess what?
I'm gonna show the whole jail,
and they're all gonna laugh,
and they're gonna elect me class president.
- Yeah.
- Doesn't jail have like a class president thing?
- No, you're thinking of school.
- Jail should have a class president.
- I'm thinking of school actually.
Wait, doesn't jail have math and science classes and recess?
Jail does have recess.
- Doesn't jail have time out that you go to
when you bite the teacher's finger?
- Wait a second.
Isn't jail--
- Even jail has recess.
- Isn't jail a giant mammal that swims in the water
and was hunted by Captain Ahab?
- No, buddy, you're thinking of whale.
- Oh.
way sorry guys yeah that's a little both although both are a little you know a
little way for my day right that's no yeah I'm the only thing that is scary
about prison is the food I know it's probably not like the prison food you
see in TV but I still don't like thinking about it someone straight up
says the worst thing about jail is you get raped and get HIV AIDS that's true
Trans 45 says I hope I never go to jail I probably never will but you never know
I know myself pretty well and I think there is a possibility you just never know
you never know you never know I could go to jail. What would you guys go to jail for?
me? yeah. being too cool. killing you. you would never kill me you couldn't kill me
in a thousand years. I could kill you right now. We should all go to jail. We should all do the same crime. Let's go to prison.
Yeah, let's go to prison. I don't know I think we could we could I think we would own in prison dude.
Yeah, I would be so good at prison. Yeah.
I would. Are you kidding me? I would set up obstacle courses for all the other inmates.
Yeah. And we would do Prison Ninja Warrior. We would do blanket forts.
It would be sick. I
Don't know. I feel like I could change the vibe of jail. Yeah, I could jail I could do around jail
The vibes are off man. I mean all you have to do is just smile at people, you know a smile can change someone's day
Mm-hmm. That's true. We may be in prison, but it doesn't mean that we can't smile
Yeah
Yeah, I think yeah, I would I would basically be the popular kid in jail
Yeah, no, I'm thinking we don't begging me to go to the dance now
I'm thinking the only reform we need in prison might be some beautiful smiles.
I'd be the chef in prison. Yeah. I'd be like chef from South Park.
Yeah exactly I would sing songs to everyone. I would do like a cool like I'd
have my own cool food like the chocolate salty balls I don't know what it
would be called. What would my food be? Your food? I would be so good at making
that that ramen loaf you would you'd make something called like blue meat yeah
yeah be like a steak that you marry it would be like yeah exactly or no when
you're gonna say you would just be it on like on like a like an iron a radiator
yeah yeah yeah I could do that all right let's send let's send Pat to jail here's
a comment at least I know two ways to escape the silent and the easy way oh
Oh yeah, how would you escape jail?
How would I escape?
Would you use the silent way or the easy way?
I would do, I would escape jail by being on such good behavior.
I would just, I would pretend, here's how I would escape jail.
I would hire one of you two to come visit me and have a big camera, right, and follow
me around for a little bit.
And then I would just tell the warden, I'd be like, "Alright, listen, I'm not going to
tell any of the inmates or any of the other people working here, this is an
episode of Undercover Boss. So just let me do whatever I want. I'm walking around,
I'm making sure everything's okay, all my employees are in order, but I'm gonna walk
out of here pretty soon because I'm not gonna stay in jail, you know what I mean?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Of course. And I'd be walking around and I'd get the
heartfelt stories from all the like, all the gang members who are in there for
killing their killing their wives and I'd be like you know what maybe jail isn't so
bad yeah and then you wink into the camera yeah I would just teleport out of
jail I don't see a reason not to yeah yeah I'll just again I get out on good
I would try and he would try and like dig a hole in the concrete with a spoon but
he would die because he would keep eating the yeah yeah I would not eat the
concrete all the dust he would just keep eating I already said and then he already
I'd get out on good behavior.
You wouldn't.
No.
They would let me out day one because of how good I am.
The second, every time that the guard came by to like unlock your cell to let you go
eat a meal, you would just go like, "Baaaa!"
Really loud and scare the shit out of them and they would beat you up.
No.
I would do a curtsy.
You would get beat up so hard in jail.
I would do a curtsy and I would get out.
You would walk around.
That's because you'd be in a girls jail.
I'd turn my shoes into tap shoes and I would be in tap dancing. You'd be in Orange is the New Black.
Yeah, sure. They had fun in that show. Patrick is the new fan. I'm not a fan of Orange is the New Black.
Yeah, you're right. They do have loads of fun. I would request to be in a girls jail.
Maybe like, "Are you a girl?" and I'd be like, "No, I just get along with girls better." Yeah.
Someone says better than residential school.
That's true. No lie, no cap detected.
No lies, no crap. That's true.
Number four, Warzone. That's a fun game, dude.
Yeah. What the hell, dude? Come on.
Randomator says, "Yeah, it doesn't sound like a fun place to be."
I was here before. It is hell.
No, seriously. Screw Justin Berber stuff. That ain't bad.
*laughter*
Justin Berber ain't that bad, man.
Justin Berber.
*laughter*
Screw Justin Berber, I've been to war.
That shit's nothing compared to war.
Dude, remember what a godsend that was when Justin Bieber was on that episode of, like, Law & Order,
where he gets shot in the head?
Yeah, oh my god.
And just everybody was like, "Most epic moment in TV history."
Yeah.
"Justin Bieber gets murdered."
That is- it is really funny, yeah.
there is a video of Justin Bieber getting shot a bunch of times.
Getting shot by the police.
So sick.
When he was like 15.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
They literally only did that so they would have like a video of Justin Bieber getting shot.
Definitely one of the creators was like
it would be really funny just to have a video of Justin Bieber getting shot.
Let's just write a whole guest episode.
Yeah.
Where he gets to act.
I haven't seen any other part of that episode.
episode that might be he might only be in that scene that might be like spliced
into like the cops go look it's justin bieber
he's not even like the criminal in the episode
uh... number five concentration camps
uh... yeah i mean obviously we can't even joke about that dude come on
yeah
there's a comment here from pizza guy
that says
This is why if I time travel to the 40s I will go to South America not Europe and North Korea's
concentration camp sounds really scary.
If I know one thing is that South America in the 40s was swag, it was nothing but fucking
coconuts and bananas dude.
It was paradise.
No one was doing anything weird.
Well if he time travels to the 40s and he goes to South America in like 1946 he's going
to be meeting the same people he would meet.
He only has a few years before.
Yeah.
Number... He goes to Argentina.
I met this...
I went to this cabana... I love Argentina in the 40's.
Not a Nazi in sight. Yeah.
I met this beautiful woman
at this cabana named Ava.
[Laughter]
Number six is
black hole.
Cosmo says... I can survive it.
- If you went in a black hole, you would be spaghettified
and you would turn really long.
- That'd be kinda cool.
Maybe me and Pat could do that and we'd get really tall.
- It wouldn't happen.
- Yeah, I would come back and I'd be--
- Cameron's height, six foot nine.
- I could get in the NBA if I was,
every molecule of my body was just like,
kinda like one molecule wide,
but as many molecules as my body is tall.
Right, and I'm just like kind of an invisible
piece of string. - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I feel like I'd be a great basketball player then.
String Caleb.
Yeah.
That's what they would call you.
They would call you Caleb the String.
Caleb the String.
Like Wilt the Steel.
Yeah dude.
I'd be like 50 miles high.
They'd call you Caleb the Bale of Hay.
That's not a bale.
That's a piece of hay.
No.
He would look like a hay.
He would look like a singular hay.
But that's not what a bale is.
There's no such...
Hay is plural.
Hay is already plural.
What is it singular?
Ha.
It's hello.
Plural.
But in singular.
A piece of hello.
A piece of hi.
Yeah.
It's what's up.
Yeah dude.
And it's just the kind of stuff you learn
when you're me.
When you're a scientist.
Yeah when you grew up on a farm like me.
Yeah.
Yeah I grew up on a soybean farm.
the middle of the Sun the middle of that's the joke of the Sun though is
that the earth is the middle is hot the middle of the Sun is actually freezing
cold yeah it actually is just earth whoa yeah it's reversed holy shit yeah you
might want to think about that before you guys make fun of me for being like
stupid or bald is that I know stuff like that you know yeah I know so much about
the Sun cuz your head looks like it but it's so bright and and circular yeah you
You guys are jealous.
You guys are jealous. The next step in evolution is...
Evolution realizes you don't even need hair.
What is hair doing for you? It's slowing you down.
Guess who's fast at swimming? Guess who's a really fast swimmer?
Me. Except for my massive afro pubes.
Those really slow me down.
Yeah. Funny you just put those on your head.
You have like weights on the end of your pubes that are dragging you down.
You get your pubes transplanted to the top of your head
you just look like Bert from Sesame Street yeah and everybody's like are you
doing shibs on your head no I'm not doing a bird thing I'm not a bird yeah
I'm half I'm half Dominican and I'm half Muppet so you have to respect my hair
it's my hair buddy feel it look put your mouth on it it's my hair all me baby now
this list this is where the list starts to drop off but I think we should
skip ahead to 10 which I would just kind of what was expected to be on here and
has a lot of comments so we're skipping over North Korea and Antarctica
nobody really says anything good about those but number 10 is a Justin Bieber
concert oh here we friggin go yeah here we go seen this before
here's a comment that says he got caught with a hooker I'm this close to dropping
down a nuclear bomb on his frontal lobe. Yeah, "Hey Baby" is that a song about himself?
Yeah. Ooh! Yeah. I'd rip my ears off then make myself die by the vibrations of his
suicide singing. Justin Bieber, why would someone ever go to his concert? Whoever
does this is crazy. His songs make my ears bleed. I wish Justin Bieber should
go to hell LeBron LeBron wrote that comment dude whoa dude what's up LeBron huge fan I
could not agree more or a 1d concert that might be worse one Dylan one Dylan baby baby baby
oh ugh rather get pushed by a cow of a building rooftop than going to Justin Bieber's concert
that is horrible and I don't see why hell and prison is up this high because they ain't
that bad whoa Bobby the brony people spread too much hate to Justin Bob that's
funny to be a brony that hates Justin Bieber like what yeah what's your reason
for hating by the most common type of person that true yeah well now what how
do you how does that work cuz even a brony knows that he's a girl dude it's
true Roni's like girl things no no cuz there's my little ponies they're like
you know it's a pretty clear gender breakdown it's like 50/50. My Little Pony is not for girls.
Uh my Little Pony is Antifa.
Uh next is Flint, Michigan.
There's no comments on this.
I would survive Flint, Michigan.
That's a newcomer.
Yeah.
Whoa.
I-
Number 11 is school.
That's right.
Here we go.
Without school life would be hell.
Non-stop crimes, more wars, more gangs, dumb people, abusive people, and more.
Whoever thinks school is worse than hell, go to hell yourselves and find out how great school was.
Do not respect the author of that comment. That is fucked up.
You must be dumb!
School is a place where you learn!
Oh my god, dude.
Haven't ever thought of this before.
There's an acronym, some acronym action here for Minecraft Hater.
Okay.
School.
Seven crappy hours of our lives.
Hooooly shit.
Woooah.
I went to school for eight hours.
I feel like we could do a better one.
I went to school for like hundreds of days. I don't know why you guys only went for a few hours.
Stinky. Seven I would change to stinky. Crappy, that can stay.
H is hot poop. Hot poop, yeah.
O is our poop. Our poop. The other O is oh my god it's so poopy here. And L is...
L is love you. L is love poop if you go here.
Love poop if you're a teacher. It's true.
our way maybe the government found a way to torture us with school aka prison
that's true number 12 is the desert the deserts of Iraq Afghanistan Syria and
Somalia are hell on earth Vegas is an exception true true so hot it's just one
comments so I'm number 13 Bermuda Triangle and the lowest comment is the
tringle could be a I that shrink could be a I David potassium I've never thought
about that before the tringle could be a I David potassium told me yesterday that
There's a there's a there's an area of Boston called the Polish Triangle and
I've just been thinking about it as a Bermuda Triangle esque like place where shit just disappears.
Anyone who goes in doesn't come out.
Yeah.
Anyone who goes in there forgets how to screw a light bulb forever.
(Laughter)
That's the secret of the Polish Triangle.
It's all of them stacked on top of each other like the Tower of Babel
trying to screw in a light bulb.
The problem with the Polish triangle is all the ships that appear have a screen door on the bottom.
Yeah.
They call it, the Polish people call it the Polish triangle but it has like five sides.
[Laughter]
Oh, I hate the Polish. That's some classic shit.
That is some classic shit, dude.
That's some classic dad shit.
That is some old school. Polish jokes, yeah.
Old school shit.
Yeah.
I don't think, I think I, yeah, I didn't, I don't think I even knew Polish people were real until...
Until way late in life, 'cause I only knew of them through jokes from my grandfather.
Yeah.
Although I remember, I think it was...
Oh, I told my grandpa...
that I was talking to him about like friends that I made in Boston
like my first year of school and I was like yeah I know this guy Neil
and he's like Neil what's his last name? Oh no. I was like Linsky and he's like Linsky
is he some kind of fucking BOLOCK?
Damn dude. He's from New Jersey
I think he's Irish. Number 14 a Trump rally
That's right.
Yeah.
Let's play.
He sucks.
Crap dude.
Yeah.
Number 17 is deserted islands.
And the only comment is I cannot live
without my five favorite albums.
I can't
number 19.
They left me.
They left me on the desert Island and I forgot all my albums and my movies.
That's a thing, man.
Five.
If you bring your five favorite albums or movies, you're fine.
survive yeah yeah yeah don't eat food dude yeah I feed off the energy of music
didn't we talk about that one time bringing it like did we do that on the
podcast you'd get like the castaway special edition that is just oh yeah
yeah I get the I'm gonna get the the Pulp Fiction version that comes with two
cheeseburgers yeah man I'm bringing VR I got the super size me version that has
every meal has 30 days of food yeah yeah but it's from McDonald's no thank you
yeah number 19 is at the end of Chuck Norris's fist. That's true at the end of Chuck
Norris's fist and the only comment is worse than a black hole in the Taco Bell
bathroom of Justin Bieber's house in hell.
Whoa.
I really like number 20.
I like number 22.
Well, let's do number 21st real quick, is graveyard.
And it's just a picture of some guys.
Yeah, the band Graveyard.
And the comment is, "Oh gosh, terrifying."
But I really like that they were trying to think of what's the worst place.
Okay, there's hell, there's jail, there's a black hole.
A graveyard.
Yeah.
*laughter*
Hell jail, holocaust, school, graveyard.
Yeah, graveyard.
*laughter*
Did you guys ever go to the graveyard and pee on stuff when you were young?
No, not pee on stuff.
We would hang out in the graveyard and smoke weed though.
I did not.
I did not smoke weed, but I did pee on every grave.
I actually, I peed on like...
I peed on like every grave in this graveyard when I was in high school.
Jeez.
I just thought it was funny to go pee on the graves.
My high school was next to a graveyard.
Was it?
Yeah, it was like a little bit down the road, but
it was pretty close and some kids got caught hooking up in it.
God damn.
I never... What about graveyards makes kids so horny?
You gotta be goth, dude.
There's a school in Watertown where literally like the school is like right next to a graveyard.
Like if you look out the windows, it's just like graves.
Very awesome.
that's all there's a there's a there's a that's all those are all the graves of
the kids who misbehaved at school dude yeah yeah there's a there's a middle
school like that in New Hampshire one time I there's a graveyard literally
next to the playground that's sick dude one time I I took a picture of myself
covering up letters on a grave so it said fuck and I posted it on Facebook and
a guy came in the comments and started yelling at me and said I was
disrespecting the dead thank God I didn't video myself yeah on all those
- I was in his grades in high school, dude.
- Yeah.
- You are going to hell, Caleb.
- I don't think I'll ever go to hell.
- I think you're gonna go to hell
instead of futuristic robot world.
- No.
- Read number 22.
- No, I'm gonna go to a new place.
I'm gonna go to God's big house.
- Nah.
- Yeah, we can play football there.
We're gonna play flag football in the yard.
- Number 22 is Big Brother House.
Oh, I just realized that means the show.
- Yeah, did you know that they--
- I was thinking somebody just hated
older brother I didn't realize that like that whole show is like we're gonna get
people to have sex with each other and we just have cameras in every room yeah
yeah so everybody's been on Big Brother there's video of them having sex in like
a yeah yeah that's so weird I would do that yeah why not what you would go on
Big Brother no I would I think maybe I'll just set up cameras all around my
apartment and then that'll be a show it'll be called Caleb's house be big
Caleb's house yeah yeah Caleb the big brother Caleb's big brother
oh my big brother could live in one house together yeah you that's not a bad idea
sex with your brother Josh no I don't number 23 on the show no I won't
number 23 about number 23 is Justin Bieber's underwear you you could do you
could take some convincing I think that it would work no I would never I would
never have sex with my brother or anyone I was related to.
I think you would. And that's a fact, Jack. If there was a camera, if there was some cameras and you were getting paid.
Well, I am a performer. I mean...
I have to give the people what they want.
No, no, no, no, no I wouldn't, no, come on, I wouldn't have sex with my brothers on camera, dude.
Are you freaking kidding me, man? That's my brother.
He used to spit in my mouth when I was growing up. I'm not gonna have sex with him, dude.
Well, you could do it again. You could do it on the camera.
Oh my god, are you kidding, man? You're talking about my bro--
He listens to this show, dude. He's gonna hear this. He's gonna text me.
He's gonna text me and he's--
He's not gonna ask me to have sex. He's not gonna ask me to have sex.
I'm gonna send a picture of his ass.
He's not gonna do that! He's gonna text you at 3am, he's gonna say "you up?"
He's not gonna call me big head on a text message, man, come on, man, you nasty bitch.
You used to call him on his cell phone.
No. Late night when you need his love.
I'm not gonna sing to him, dude.
You're gonna sing "Hotline Bling."
I'm not gonna make him dinner and sing to my own fucking brother, dude.
Yeah, you're gonna sing "Hotline Bling" to him.
Dude, I'm not gonna.
"Hotline Bling" to him.
I will not propose to him with a ring pop. I'm not gonna do that, dude.
You're gonna say "ever since the city you."
If you think I'm gonna marry my brother, you got another thing coming, big fella.
[laughter]
Get your finger out of the camera.
I'm gonna put my finger in you.
You're gonna put your finger in your brother.
I'm not gonna finger my own bro, dude! That's my bro!
[laughter]
Dude, that's my bro, man. He taught me everything I know.
Yeah, he taught you how to have sex, and now he's gonna--
I don't know how to have sex, dude!
[laughter]
Shut up, dude!
Dude, I send all of these clips to my mom.
She's gonna hear this, man.
You send all the clips about you having sex with your brother to your mom?
Dude, I'm not gonna have sex with any of my four brothers.
Three brothers.
Was your fourth brother... did you add a brother recently?
His fourth brother is you, Cameron.
I included myself in the brother count.
I'm not gonna have sex with any of my brothers.
And you can take that to the bank.
You're gonna have sex with your brother at the bank?
No, I'm not gonna lock myself in the vault
and have sex with my brothers.
You're gonna bring a big check to the bank
from Caleb's Big Brother House, the TV show.
'Cause like if you requested a big check
and you're gonna try and cash it
and the thing at the bottom, it's not gonna say cash,
it's gonna say Big Brother's.
I'm not gonna start a new Playboy channel reality show
called Home Brother House.
You're gonna make a deposit.
You're gonna make a deposit into your brother's ATM.
- My brothers aren't big, except for where it counts.
Then they're big brothers.
Not that I would know, dude,
I haven't seen them, my brother's wieners,
when I was 10 or 11 years old, dude,
walking in on him in the bathroom.
That didn't happen.
I would say, no, me and my brother did used to do--
- Patrick's watching a video now.
- When-- - I'm not watching a video.
- What are you looking at? - Someone said
it looks like Pavarotti.
- When "Waiting" came out, remember that movie "Waiting"?
Oh, the penis game? You did that too?
No, not the penis game. No, we would do the donkey.
Where you tucked your ball sack and your
- Yeah, the whole game though. - ...penis around.
You did it without the game.
We just thought it was funny to look at
each other's balls.
You didn't even punch your brother after?
Dude, I'm not gonna hurt
my brother.
What if I accidentally, what if I miss
and I actually destroy his beautiful
penis with my fist?
That would suck, dude.
No, no you punch them because they looked at your penis. That was the point of the game
I'm gonna I'm gonna pitch that to my grandpa like Shark Tank. I'm gonna pitch it
All right, so we're gonna put me and all the brothers in a house and you're gonna pay for the cameras
And we're gonna punch each other in the balls, what do you think grandpa?
It's all I've ever wanted from you boys
That's what I raised as I raised you. Yeah
Yeah number 24 blood on the dance. No, you skip number 23 number 23 is Justin Bieber's underwear the top comment
I would hate to be seriously guys
You're telling me that a wide-open state with plenty of things to do and see that well fits 9 million people is worse than a super
Tiny place to do nothing that would near be nearly impossible to fit even one person
I wish people would get their facts straight and the comment I really like on this one is he will blow up when he sees
this lol I
I would hate to be in his underwear, especially if I was Caleb Bieber, then I would be double mad.
Yeah, if you were married to his brother.
Yeah, if I was his brother, I'd be so... I would hate to be in his undies, dude.
In his unders.
Did your dad's have a funny word for underwear growing up?
No, my dad said underwear. My dad said unders.
Your dad said Caleb's playhouse.
No. That's what he called his underwear. No.
- Oh, dude. - Yeah.
- No.
- He called it-- - I did.
- Did you guys-- - He called it brother's game.
That's what he called your underwear.
- Did you guys-- (laughing)
Did you guys have a phase where you saw on TV and stuff
that people just hung out with their hands in their pants
and then you guys did that for a little bit?
- No. - No.
- No?
- I used to walk around-- - What do you mean
hands in your pants?
- Like walk around with sweatpants with your hands,
like where your penis lives.
- What?
- You never did that? - I mean, no, I did that.
I didn't see it on TV.
Oh, I used to watch TV a lot.
You just used to... what do you mean?
You don't need to... come on, you've done that.
It's chill, it's relaxing.
Yeah, it's chill, you know you're safe.
Maybe you're explaining it wrong.
You put your hand in your pants.
Put both your hands in your pants.
That's about as simple as it gets.
Where did you see it on TV?
Put your hand in your pants.
Security camera footage.
(laughter)
(laughing)
- Come on.
- You ever did that?
- No.
- I don't know.
- At least one of you agreed with me.
That would have been horrible if both of you were there.
- I think that's a, I feel like that's
a fairly normal thing to do.
- Wait, like you're laying on the couch and you--
- And you just stick a hand down there, dude.
- Yeah.
- Maybe it starts as a scratch,
but then you're like, then you realize like,
I don't have a better place for my hand to be right now.
- Yeah, might as well.
- Oh, okay.
All right.
- Yeah.
- No, when you explain it like that,
I thought you meant you--
- What did you think it was?
did you ever see on TV when people put their hands down their pants and they
hung out like that? TV is a reflection of reality and there are moments... I didn't know what you...
Have you ever heard of Zakhla Khan dude? Come on Pat. I love her music.
Number 25, the ghetto. Damn. Yeah that's where I'm from. Number 32 is haunted
mansion. I would hate to be in the haunted mansion. That'd be sick dude. Fucking Eddie Murphy's there, he's making you laugh dude. He's doing the raw routine from the first eight minutes of the special.
He's calling the ghost. He's calling the ghost the slur. Yeah. He can't sit in the front row or look at his ass dude. Yeah. You're just dying laughing.
number 49 is Saudi Arabia and it's the first line of the top comment is the
cops there are very sketchy the cops in Saudi Arabia they're very sketchy and
43 43 90 year old ladies changing room whoa there's a comment here from British
goat that says how would you even get in this situation
Wait, number 59 is Columbine High School and the top comment is from Joe Boy and
says, "After the 1999 shooting, this place just got haunted."
Trains 45 on number 60 Iraq said, "I would never visit this country. One of the
worst places to visit." Back to the Columbine thing, I feel like
Columbine, if you went to Columbine High School, I feel like you would be pretty
safe yeah now yeah I mean definitely not in 1999 but afterwards like you're just
like they're not gonna do it like they already they're not gonna do it again
so the fucking what is Zaxby's cuz there's number 79 is a chicken
restaurant that's a number 79 is Zaxby's and then there's a comment that just says
why is Zaxby's on here Patrick's never heard of a fast-food place before that's
impressive no it's impressive there's one that Patrick doesn't know oh my god
that chicken sandwich looks good as shit oh number he's rocks number 67 I'm gonna
go to this place number other fried chicken place I gotta go to number 67
is earth and all the comments are really mad that they put earth on there the
comments are okay why is earth on here we are all in the planet you know if you
don't like earth then get a life what who wrote earth we're all in earth this
shouldn't even be in the list or we are already at earth why is this here we
We all live on here.
Take it off right now.
Everyone lives on Earth.
Number 74 is United States.
First comment.
Well we got a sub list.
People do not hate America because they are jealous of you.
They hate America because they have poor education and are the most hypocritical country in the
world.
I have a lot of reasons the United States sucks.
Number one, they eat too much.
Number two, they hate any nation that can do things better than them.
Number three, they are obese.
They are ignorant.
They only care about themselves.
They are rude.
They have Donald Trump.
They have start wars, health care is expensive,
they have stupid laws, they brag too much,
they won't get over 9/11,
they are the only nation without universal health care,
they have a lot of gun crime,
they elected George Bush twice,
they act like they're the only country in North America,
some Americans act like they're the only nation
in the world, and they brag about their military.
Peaceful countries do not need a big army or military.
18 reasons America sucks.
- Damn. - Wow.
Wow.
We have freaking gnome chomps in the comments here.
Number...
Yeah, that's from user Angela Davis.
Number 109 is Chernobyl and the comment says, "Terrible explosion that killed like 25 people."
Yeah, it's just 25 people.
I could survive Chernobyl.
That's all they got in Chernobyl.
Yeah.
I could survive it too.
I would just hold my breath, dude.
Me too.
That's all you need to do.
I would just lay on it like an egg.
Yeah.
I would just lay on the green stuff.
Yeah, you can tell what's radioactive because it's glowing green.
You just avoid those parts.
Did you guys watch the Chernobyl show?
I never finished it.
I watched the first few episodes.
The guy who wrote it is a very, uh,
he's one of those fucking,
like, oh, Trump is a Soviet, guys.
Oh, dude, that's the best part of the show.
Oh yeah, it's so, it's so insane.
Like, they'll have a, they'll have like a boardroom full of people
and it'll be and like is it one of those shows where they're like do they do they
speak in Russian? British accent. I fucking knew it. It's terrible. Yeah. So they'll all there'll be like a boardroom
that's like every important like Soviet leader and then Mikhail Gorbachev will
sit up and he'll be like but how do we how are we gonna we're just gonna let
thousands of people die for no for no reason at all and then some like old old
man will stand up and there's a picture of Stalin behind him and he'll point to
the picture of Stalin will be like, "Listen, buddy, we're communists. It's what we do.
We kill people for no reason at all." That's what he did, and he'll point to Stalin, and
then everybody will clap, and Mikhail Gorbachev will sit down and be like...
It's so awesome, dude. Yeah, there's so many scenes where it's like...
I wish this was a democracy. I wish we had pizza on here.
We need to get pizza. And we need to get Wendy's.
It's like this war room, and then Mikhail Gorbachev is like, "Well, if we're going to be here all
can we at least order a pizza and then one guy will be like there's no pizza
it's the Soviet Union you dumbass it's sick yeah no there are like so many
distinct scenes though where someone is just like yeah I like that all the
people are dying I think this is what this is the good part of it this is
actually good to me because I'm a con man I don't let people die yeah this shit's
swag as hell I love it when people die because of my communism. I can't wait to have the election.
Sanders in the room with I agree with all of this I hate pizza I hate I'm going
to help you know again in 100 I have helped planned all of this I was the
reason oh yeah like a little fucking kid comes in like trying to delivering the
communist pizza is just like a slice of bread with one piece of Mexican cheese on
it and they're like oh thank you son like you're you're gonna get a promotion
what's your name and he's like Bernie Sanders
Bernie was like 40 at the time. He was like old enough he's like knows everything's going on
but he's a little kid with a newsboy cap he's dressed up like tiny Tim
he hobbles in with a pizza and he's like I got your pizza right here
all hail radical Islam yeah that fucking that show rocks yeah to rewatch it did
yeah all right what else do we have rounding this out nothing really it's
just countries Bob that's true tells Duncan's house I hate Harper Japan town
inside of a small cramped box in the bathroom after a man took a dump
Kenya Venezuela rounding out the list yep that's it all right Wow
all right sorry for the late episode today guys Caleb's internet was out
yesterday yeah I was caught in a tornado yeah I got I got spun into a black and
white universe by a tornado yeah yeah yeah sorry there was there and you were
there and you were there too yeah you two were there and I was I was doing you know
what with you I was well now I'm ending the episode you can't say thanks guys
bye goodbye