You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts for the homeless.
You're a crap monster.
Reporting now.
What does it mean to get lucky with your dad?
What does it mean?
If he lets you go out late at night to hang out with your friends.
I just got so lucky with my dad last night, dude.
Dude, oh my god.
I love it with my fucking dad.
When he throws the football in the perfect way.
Mm-hmm.
That way that just makes you smile.
No, no, no.
When he throws a frisbee, you catch it in your mouth.
Yeah.
Getting lucky, getting lucky with your dad is when you, uh, is when you, you make him,
uh, come.
Come.
You make him come.
Yeah.
Come.
I don't know where I was going with that.
Dad.
Dad, can I be real with you, man?
Dad, I need to make you bust right now.
It's just so awesome getting lucky with you.
Seriously, I need to make you bust now. I feel like the ultimate getting lucky in this life is having a dad. Yeah, that's now that
Ultimate the ultimate getting lucky in this life is becoming a dad
No, no. Yep. No, cuz anyone
Cause a lot of real man
$100 a day to have a kid and you have to battle your son cuz he's trying to constantly make you come. Yeah
Get out of here you have to learn advanced SWAT techniques all sons are trying away
They're trying so hard to make their dad come until they turn 18. Yeah, that's what that um that
Ari aster short film is about yeah, oh, yeah, yeah the crazy thing about the crazy thing about that family
Son in the dad never come
That's what he was referring to
Yeah, the dad actually was happy even though he looked sad
That's the strange thing about the story thing is he's my dad's frown is upside down. Yeah
Yeah, see my dad's did my dad's he's part chin so when he when he frowns
He's actually smiling because his whole heads upside down
Yeah, the strange thing about the Johnson's people think that the title refers to you know
what the son does to the dad but it's actually there's one shot where you can
see their welcome mat actually says goodbye and that's that's what the
strange thing is that the title is referring to it's a happy birthday home
and it's from red bubble yeah it's kind of a it's kind of a strange thing that
nobody really I would say that's a pretty unrealistic movie because it is
all like doom and gloom when in real life it'd be like your dad like walks by
on the couch he's like smack his ass like daddy we going this big fat ass dad
- Dad, where you taking that thing?
Taking that to the office?
Taking that to the bonus room?
- You taking that and taking it out with the trash?
- What you doing in the bonus room, Dad?
- You taking your butt out with the trash?
- Dad wants it on the foosball table.
- Back that up.
- Dad, let's take that.
- Back that up, Dad.
- Daddy, let's take this to the garage.
All right, let's take this to the workbench.
- I gotta show you something I can do.
I'm gonna put some, you got vice grip in there?
I got something I'm gonna grip in there.
- Oh, we're gonna play catch.
you're gonna catch me mm-hmm yeah I'm gonna put my tools in your box daddy
hey mom me and dad are gonna be out in the garage dropping a bunch of tools
everywhere if you hear a bunch of weird stuff if you hear something weird that's
- that's us working on a bird house yeah we're gonna be we just brought home a
giant buck from our hunt and we're gonna be killing him in the garage if you hear
some yeah monstrous guttural noises we're having venison tonight by the way
yeah and then like two hours later it's like what are you talking about we never
said that yeah we never said we were gonna have venison I'm taking dad
outside and we're gonna have a little uh prime rib mm-hmm yeah remove one of
dad's two of dad's ribs and then I'm so he can suck my dick yeah that's the
car accident that we have to remove his ribs so he can even get down there.
No dude we're disgusting. We're nasty AF today. So a son and dad relationship
story I wasn't here for this but I got to work and somebody told me that the way
so we have like Slim Jim's at the counter and one of the guys I was working with
told me that a guy came in and bought 35 Slim Jims and he said and they're like
like wow that's a lot of Slim Jims he's like yeah my son loves them.
And then the best part of that is that there he bought 35 Slim Jims but there
were 36 in stock so he just left one Slim Jim. Like he was like no 36 that's way too much.
I think we need to introduce this guy to slimjim.com. Yeah. Yeah, I think you could
probably order... How many Slim Jim's do you think you can order at once? I think if you
order over 30, if you order over 30 you probably like get a call from the CDC
because you're gonna bring some strange disease in your stomach. Right. If you
order over 35 you have to send in verification that you have two sons.
(laughing)
- You have to send your son's birth certificate.
- That's too much for one son.
- Two learner's permit.
- Two learner's permit, not the copies.
So once they get that back, once they have that,
they can keep it if they want.
- Yeah. - That's right.
- Yeah.
- But I, you know.
- Just imagine doing that with anything else.
- Yeah.
- Just buying just a shit ton of stuff.
Ah, my kid.
- Yeah, my son.
- Yeah, sorry.
- My son loves gum.
- Do you think that's a,
do you think it's worse to feed your...
(laughter)
- That's me when you're 16 years old
buying condoms for the first time.
- Just buying them for my son.
- Yeah, my son loves these.
Yeah.
- Sorry, these are my son's.
- That's why I had to buy them 400 count.
- Trust me, I don't use these, come on.
- Do you think it's--
- None for me, please.
- Do you think it's worse to be feeding
your four year old son 35 Slim Jims,
or your 25 year old son 35 Slim Jims?
- 25, 'cause you're buying them for him
when he should have the money to get them.
that's like a true love relationship yeah you know what then it's maybe maybe it's
just the best dad in the world yeah he's a birthday gift but if it's a four-year-old
son I think you're poisoning your child no Slim Jim's aren't poisonous maybe it's
a birthday gift and he takes him out of the package and creates like an edible
arrangement yeah yeah little beef flowers using them to stitch them
together and build a son yeah we're building a son out of sling
jim I'm making my son yeah these will these will these will create his muscle
fibers inside you won't even see these these are his tendons
- Do you guys have any skin?
- You have skin?
- You have any skin?
- Do you guys sell brains?
- Do you have a sentient meat brain
that I could put in a sun?
And two meat eyeballs.
Oh, and you know what, I'll take that meat tongue.
- Yeah, oh, you have olives here, great.
Great, those will be the eyes.
(laughing)
- And the balls.
- Yeah, I noticed that employee,
you have mopping stuff up in the back.
Could I go through 'em for parts, really quick?
- You have a spare employee, I could just rummage through.
- I like rummaged through him for a little bit.
- Yeah.
- All right, sorry guys, I ended up deciding
I didn't want anything from him, so sorry about that.
- Yeah, sorry to leave a mess.
- My Frankenstein meat son,
do you guys have just like a bunch of blood?
Do you have like maybe a gallon of blood
that I could put in him?
- Do you guys sell, are you guys selling a lightning bolt?
Could you guys sell me a lightning bolt
that I could use to bring my son to life?
- Weird question, do you guys have like a roof
that's like a giant cobblestone tower?
- And do you have the materials here for a drawbridge?
Just because, sorry.
- And I just wanna make sure,
I just wanna make sure you guys do not
and will never sell pitchforks and torches, right?
(laughing)
I just wanna make sure I don't have to move
to another town to do this.
- Yeah, I'm with dads against pitchforks and torches.
- For our monster sons.
- I'm a monster dad against pitchforks and torches.
then I'm here and I need you to sign this petition and this contract this contract
to never sell pitchforks or torches in your store - I'll take two giant bolts
- do you have neck do you have neck holes yeah it would be fun to make a
frankenstein. Do you sell neck holes here? You guys sell a flat head? You sell a big flat head that's
shaped like a dome. Do you have any green skin? Do you have any green skin I can buy?
You have like a black and white Marge station hat. You know, you know, I, people tell me it's way
cheaper to build your own but just the the pre-built ones are just so much, they
look so nice. The new alien wear. The cyber power Frankenstein. You just get ripped off on the parts dude.
yeah especially the penis yeah kind of the men's graphics card it's like the
most expensive part of a man yeah yeah yeah it's true would you ever get your
penis insured I in what I don't plan on doing anything to it that I would damage
it right but what if anybody's seeing my penis you don't plan on your house
getting hit by a tree oh I do that's a good point yeah I mean you just don't
build your house in your trees so I'm gonna take what about this I take out a
hundred dollar insurance policy my penis cuz I feel like I could get it covered
for a hundred but yeah well like there's a nobody's penis the most because I know
somebody has a nice Ron Jeremy had a million dollar penis and yeah but if I
got it you also had some dark secrets yeah he should have gotten rape insurance
no I don't think that exists that's not a thing no thank God it's not a thing yeah
but I think I would I could ensure my penis for like a hundred bucks and then
I could have one of you guys cut it off and we can make a cool oh okay I think
I think it was damage it in some way I'm more finger-popping Freddy than anything
else yeah I'm a cherry poppin daddy yeah I'm a cherry poppin daddy with some long
long fingers. I'm going to the zoo. I'm at the zoot suit ride with my dick out. I'm a daddy long fingers and I'm coming at ya.
I got, trust me bitch, I got five thumbs on each hand. You're about to have the stupidest Thursday night of your life.
They all bend outwards. Yeah. They have five thumbs on each hand and they're all hitchhiker thumbs.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Yeah man, they work like a speculum.
- They're gonna tear you open.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, the maximum, most a bitch ever took was two.
So let's see if we can break some records tonight.
Happy Sabbath.
- Man, I've been-- - You guys excited for--
- For New York City, baby? - Yeah, I've been drinking
so much coffee.
- Yeah? - Nice, congrats.
- I know. - That's cool.
- It's changing me.
- Good. - What do you feel like it's,
how do you feel like it's changing you?
I don't, I, you don't get the, it does, Will described it like perfectly where it's like
monster energy, I don't want to just repeat what Will said, but it does feel like you
get poisoned when you drink Monster.
Because you are getting poisoned.
Yeah, no, I feel like Monster gives you about 30 minutes of caffeine high and then like two
hours of, uh, of aspartame fuckin' mind buffs.
There's not aspartame in it, that's the thing.
It's some other sweetener.
yeah there's they don't have to list what's in it on the ingredients because
it's just dark magic right it is cast a spell on it before they I don't really
put it on the shelf I think the thing I really don't like about this about
energy drinks is that caffeine is an ingredient it's not like a feature yeah
like that means that they have a white caffeine powder that they pump into this
yeah mm-hmm is that horrifying up for you so they got
- It's got a freaking salt bae there, dude.
- It's definitely liquid caffeine.
- Yeah, they have salt bae.
- They have salt bae, freaking sprinkling caffeine in.
- He does that down his arm, that's his move.
- That's what's tasty about it, he does it on his elbow.
- It goes down his sleeve, it goes down his long sleeve
and up into his armpit,
and it comes out the bottom of his shirt.
- Every day he marinates his arm in like a ginger soy sauce
for six hours.
- He's got miso paste under his armpits just for men to--
insanely wrinkly shiny pasty offer some that orange is my salt arm
you know being my short thing are
what you just do guess that's what he sounds like arched oak
I'll are you rasta
was that no not as a jewel I
9 and who who
or who are we haven't
little little Robin Williams doing it doing a vape.
I hit the jewel.
I'm a ghost!
I'm a ghost, I'm in your house.
I've been dead for five years.
I'm in the wall.
Look at me, I'm making the room cold.
Has he been dead for five years?
No, I think it's six.
- Yeah.
- That one was a tough one for me, dude.
- Yeah, we've been over that.
- Have we been over this?
- Yeah, you listened to Maren on the beach.
- I listened to Maren twice in a row,
and walked on the beach.
- Yeah.
- God damn, dude, my life sucks.
- My life be like, ooh.
(laughing)
- But you guys ready to come to New York City
in a couple of days?
- Yeah, I'm ready to go there and not have a panic attack.
- Take the big apple by storm.
- Be swag, dude.
I think indoor dining's about to start up.
- I'm not doing that.
- Yeah, I don't wanna do indoor dining.
Also public school-- - Not in New York.
- We could go to public school.
- Oh, okay, you wanna go there real bad, huh?
- I don't know, I miss Foursquare.
I miss being the king of something.
- All right, if that's your intention, then that's fine.
- You're gonna go play Foursquare and be the king
and look for a queen at the public school?
- Yep. - Psyche.
- You're gonna say,
would anybody like to be my queen?
Would anybody like to be my crazy queen?
Excuse me, I am the four square king. Would anybody like to be my queen?
I would not go there.
Sir Caleb!
I would be the king of recess, dude. I just want to fuck the teacher.
Is that so wrong?
Is that so wrong? I just want to fuck my teacher.
Is that a crime?
If fucking my teacher is a crime, then put me in jail.
Put me in that university.
(laughter)
- Airdrop me in there.
- 'Cause I'm trying to commit a crime.
If fucking a teacher is a crime, then I'm doing that.
- I'm trying to commit a crime.
- If it's legal, I'm ghost.
I don't want anything to do with it if it's fine.
- Is it legal to fuck a, I know a guy who's a college
professor who fucks his students all the time.
Is that legal?
- No.
- I think it is.
- I don't think that's legal.
- I think it's against the school.
- You gotta stop hanging out with these.
- It's against the rules of the school.
I don't, I bet that, I feel like they probably have just policies at the college, I don't
think it's illegal, but I think it's probably like you're not supposed to do that and you
could get fired for it.
That makes sense.
It doesn't take that long for you to think about that.
Yeah, I guess that does make sense.
So what's his full name?
What's yours?
Do you guys remember when that guy in our college killed himself?
Yeah.
He was a student fucker?
Yes.
No?
professor like fuck the student and then ran away yeah and ran away from home
that's it was sad but I won't say who it is but somebody told me they were they
were planning on going to like the school open mic and going up and doing
like an opening joke where's just like what's up with all these fucking rapist
professors killing themselves recently.
Jesus Christ. That is funny. Oh my god that's a funny joke. That's a funny one to me.
But yeah what are we gonna do when you guys get to New York? What's our first move?
We're gonna run around and go nuts. Yeah I'm gonna go nuts on your butt. Do you guys...
That's my first move. You will not. No. It's funny that like Pat's only time in New York he
just went to like the pit yeah I went to some stupid fucking comedy club I didn't
go anywhere cool we didn't go to like yeah no we went to we went to Times
Square did we went to Times Square yeah yeah it was too expensive it was like
$25 for pasta yeah Times Square Olive Garden and I was like yeah we got to go
we gotta go to the Times Square Jollibee I'll go sure we gotta go yeah I didn't
know that there was a Jollibee here until I saw that cup on the street the other day I
gotta look up the address I'm doxing the Times Square Jollibee. My first thought was like
somebody brought a cup from California all the way to New York and then just
left it on the street I never thought that there could be a Jollibee in New
York City yeah I'm so dumb that's the closest Jollibee it's there's one in uh
yeah yeah and right near Madame Tussauds oh yeah mad at the toad mad at my toad
madam no madam my toad madam my toad madam my toad now can you see my toad
can we go to see excuse me sir can you see my toad excuse me this is I need
it out.
Now say something about a penguin with a spork.
No say it dude.
It wasn't that written.
No cause toad has a penis.
Okay now say it.
Now say it.
I was doing.
I was being a flasher.
Put a smile on your face.
It was a joke.
Put a smile on your.
Let me see a smile on your face.
Let's see it.
Turn the frown upside down.
That's an upside down smile.
You look so much like Wario.
Jesus Christ bro.
What are you guys going for as Halloween?
I'm going to suck your penis.
I'm not going as anything for Halloween.
What am I going for as Halloween?
I'm going as Jamie Lee Curtis.
Yeah I'm going as Jamie Lee Curtis.
going as Jamie Lee Curtis. I'm going as a working adult, okay? That's my Halloween costume idea. I don't have time for little baby
things like dressing up in a costume. Maybe I'll dress like a rat when I go to work.
Cameron keeps talking over it. That's because it's a work uniform. I think I'm going as
Awesome Powers. Awesome Powers. I'm going as Boston Powers. Yeah, yeah. From that
SNL sketch yep yes yeah yeah I'm actually Boston Powers mm-hmm yeah yeah no it's
from an SNL sketch I'm actually I feel like that's the worst kind of person is
the person who goes as SNL sketch for Halloween like a sketch character I don't
feel like I'm doing a Kenan Thompson character yeah I'm Steve Harvey I'm
Steve Harvey no from SNL no no no I'm doing Thompson as Steve Harvey no no no
white Steve Harvey is not a bad costume though I'm no guys you don't get it you
don't get it guys I'm Jay Pharoah as Jay Z okay that's why I'm doing this it is
funny imagining just like a like a Hollywood producer casting like a role
of like a black guy and something and he's like what about Fred Armisen yeah
he played Obama I mean what about Fred Armisen for bad boys for all right
you're gonna love this this is a movie about Thurgood Marshall we're doing
like Hollywood arms Hollywood producer guys definitely have to have just like
assistants who just reign them in on that because that is absolutely that is
their first they just don't understand that like yeah they would do if you if
you gave them a chance they would cast every every black character would just be
a white guy talking funny and I just have to have like a 20 year old
20 year old man who stands next to him and goes "um actually the internet wouldn't like it if you did that sir"
Yeah, maybe Chris Evans. Yeah, yeah, we would have seen fucking
Cellmovie a really different movie. Chris Evans would have been both Captain America and Black Panther
Yeah, now we might have to be yeah
Don't worry his last wish was that Chris Evans
Takes his role as Black Panther
he hit it he hit it in the contract when he signed we didn't know this was gonna
happen yeah sorry guys Black Panther we have to we we legally have to pass the
role of Black Panther to Christopher Mintz Plass I'm so sorry
we did not read the fine print wakanda forever that's funny here's an op on
this list on the idea boards yeah this is more of this list was a nation yeah this
list was sent in by my brother Asian with the IGN yeah so sent in by my brother
Paul what up this is a hundred ways to abuse your nintendo no it's one of the
ways to abuse your night and dog yeah and it's made by user Alberta soar
Albert Alberta soars and on December 17 2005 it says noob here holy crap we're
reading we're reading a list made by a noob no thank you off of this is our
first noob list I think no no no no any list that you that you have sent in no
- No, yeah.
- No.
- You're basically a noob.
- You are.
- No.
- You better take that back.
- Yeah, I think you are.
- No, you seriously better take that back.
I'm not kidding.
- I think you are.
I think you're the noob.
- If one of us is a Supreme Ultimo gamer
and not a noob, it would be me.
- I play different types of games.
- Yeah, girl games, Peggle and Diarrhea Dress Up too.
- Diarrhea Dress Up is not a girl game.
There's no girls in that game.
It's just poop people.
- It's a girl poop.
they don't have genders like to dress up who people don't have you're one of
those guys you play dress-up games you don't even take the underwear off yeah
don't dress up games they just play clothes yeah I play quite gun to dress up
game and I take off his robes no you don't so no you can Jedi famously Jedi
don't wear underwear is that famous famous famous to me of Scottish guys
you yeah guys in kilts nah yeah well Liam Neeson technically I think he is you're
thinking of famous you're famous you're thinking of famously naked guys don't
wear underwear I think it's what you think Paris Hilton getting out of a
limo yeah yeah I think yeah I think that is what I'm thinking I think you might
be thinking of Winnie the Pooh actually Paris Hilton could be a Jedi name yeah
if you just move if you move if you put an apostrophe in there yeah yeah
Paris Hilton. But it would still be Paris Hilton? Yeah. Yeah.
Because you don't for some reason have... If you just switch the vowels if it's just
P-R-A-S-S H-O-L-T-O-N then that's a Jedi name. P-N-A-S-S H-O-L-T-O-N.
P-N-A-S-S H-O-L-T-O-N. P-N-A-S-S H-O-L-T-O-N. Okay. P-N-A-S-S H-O-L-T-O-N.
That's my ultimate Jedi. Yeah. P-N-A-S-S H-O-L-T-O-N. Number one way to abuse your
night and dog make it run in circles till it cannot stand up any longer
is there a fatigue system and I don't remember I don't remember either I never
owned some intent dogs my friend had it and I played it like twice I was like
this game is about dogs I didn't I would just like starve the dogs yeah yeah
there's like a way for me to get out you could you could hit the Nintendo
- Child psychopathy in the virtual world.
- In the original Nintendogs, he could hit them,
it just would give you negative points.
- I was thinking about this the other day,
you know how like a warning sign for like psychopaths
and serial killers and stuff is if they like kill animals
or hurt animals when they're a kid?
Like before they figured that out,
were they just like, oh man, Timmy killed a cat,
that kid's a freak.
- That kid's kind of weird.
- That kid's a weirdo.
- Ah, what a little creep. - He's getting into biology.
What a little creepy.
What a little teased little.
Yeah, he wants to be a doctor.
Oh, this guy's so stupid.
He doesn't realize you're supposed to pet a cat.
Yeah.
Yeah, they were, originally they just thought that they were stupid.
Originally they were just like, yeah, we need it.
This guy needs to take some more tests.
I feel like all, I feel like all kids like fuck with like lizards and stuff though.
Yeah, bugs for sure.
That's just you.
No.
You can, no, you can fuck with bugs as a kid and you're not a psychopath.
You fuck a bug.
A lizard is not a bug.
Yeah, you fuck a bug.
A lizard is a bug if it's small enough.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
A snail is a lizard.
That is true, yeah.
You were, I mean, yeah, all kids fuck around with iguanas and 10-foot-long Komodo dragons.
My grandma's house.
Oh, man, when you were a kid, you didn't-- You remember pulling the legs off of your
iguana?
Yeah, holding a magnifying glass over my marine iguana.
When I was a kid, my grandma had, she had, like, slugs all in her backyard, and I would
pick them up and sniff them till my head hurt.
(laughter)
They had like a really weird smell.
And I'd go outside and be like, I can tell that they're here.
I can smell them from here. And I'd like find them.
Hey, grandma, slug season is here.
I think that's why I like nicotine now.
I think it's kind of the same feeling.
Yeah, that's what they make cigarettes out of.
There's nicotine naturally produced in slugs.
Every cigarette is a slug penis.
Every cigarette is a slug.
Mm-hmm.
I'm gonna start calling cigarettes slugs.
sounds cool British way to talk about cigarettes that's like if they if
British people as a collective got in trouble for calling them fags they'd
switch to slug mm-hmm yeah you know cuz those two words are equal in their mind
for both you know both meanings yeah exactly that's just how British people
think number two make it bite the pull rope swing him around let go and he'll
fly off this is what I do with Caleb yeah I made a little bite my pull rope
and then I swing him around and he flies off. I stopped calling for that. I have not done that in a while.
Yeah. But it might happen this weekend. I mean you might turn me to the old me.
Yeah, I'm back on my bullshit. I'm back to biting the pole rope and flying off. Oh my god. My dad was a
monster. He'd give me a bone two hours later. I mean peanut butter out of a chew
toy it's really bad dude it's really fucking bad yeah yeah people used to
hide the ball on me mm-hmm number three hey throw things at it and then a
animated laughing like yeah was there a brick in the game yeah the nintendo brick
yeah we don't know we just put it in we don't know what the kids are gonna do
with it yeah I downloaded the bludgeon mod we thought yeah I would build a
house for the dog we didn't know that listen when we put when we programmed
the blood functionality into the game we didn't know that kids were gonna find a
way to exploit it by making the dogs bleed it was supposed to be for the
chew toys number four when he's thirsty take him for a walk and make him run the
whole time I definitely I did that a lot yeah yeah I love just not cleaning up
the poop yeah oh yeah do you think they're taking your dog into the woods I mean
yeah in the woods mm-hmm gaming gaming is escapism and in the video game you can
let your room fill up with poop and you don't have to deal with the real-life
consequences yeah cuz he doesn't you can't smell it through the screen not
yet at least not until that'll be huge yeah and they had smelled of er dude uh-huh
oh my god I can't wait to smell stuff yeah crazy funny to like go back to your
like favorite game ever and be like damn Mario 3 these worlds actually smell like
shit yeah yeah I couldn't smell was too bad
the Koopas smell like shit downloading the goombas were actually diarrhea the
whole time we never knew I'm downloading the Michelle Obama simulator just
smelling my armpits for two hours fucking let's see what these smell like
like dude yeah I can't wait to watch The Office with the smell turned on oh my
god can't wait I smell Creed's butt dude Creed's gonna smell so bad
can't wait to smell his desk they find they add like smell to every TV show
just every character smells like shit cuz they're just like on set under like
hot stage lights and yeah we just never anticipated this technology the West
Wing completely unwatchable now yeah oh man they all smell like yeah mothballs
Yeah it's disgusting I'm smelling train spotting tomorrow yeah oh it smells so
good it's really it's honestly the only good smelling movie yeah no it all
smells like heroin don't feed or water it for as long as I hate it when I have
to water my head make it play and stuff yeah I just have to water my dog it's so
annoying yeah I don't know I think a play seems like that would be fun for the
dog making a play. Dogs love to play.
No. Not when they haven't had water. That's true, not when they haven't been
watered. I guess that's a good point. You gotta water your dog before you play it.
Yeah, that's true. Yeah. That's my advice. You gotta warm your dog up. Mm-hmm.
There's a comment here from Bubble Burst Baby that says, "That's mean. You'll screw
up your Nintendog and he won't like you for the rest of your life." And
and then the response to that comment is,
"Okay dude, one, it's just a game,
"and two, real people like you and me won't do any of this,
"but I posted one anyway,
"and treat your Nintendog nicely,
"not to be mean to the people who do,
"but just do what you want,"
and then a peace sign.
- It actually says, "Do what ya what."
- Oh, whoops.
- The first time, and he responded to that and fixed it.
- I didn't mean to post so much,
but I had to fix a little problem, sorry.
(laughing)
- Oh man, yeah, this is from 2005,
miss forum shit like this I had to fix a little problem a little problem yeah my
name is on my keyboard and I had to take it out behind the shed this is this is a
little Easter egg for all the real April Mandy fans okay now here's my favorite
here's my favorite one so far from x-text this is a bunch of options all in
one post mm-hmm take it for a walk when it stops to piss
Yank its @$$ and done let it.
Ram a cart up its @@$$ while it's sleepin'.
Lay down some food, toy, water, and when it's 'bout to get it, you get it.
Make it walk all over its $H!+.
Throw a piggy bank on it.
Mwahahahahahaha skull emoji.
But I wouldn't do that to my Nintendog, even though it's not Xmas.
*laughter*
I would do this to my Nintendog if it was Xmas, but...
Can you put stuff in your dog's ass in Nintendogs? Is that an option?
Probably a thermometer.
When you play with, like, the carrot and you throw it?
We have finally modeled a perfect physics engine.
You can do absolutely anything you want in this game, this dog game.
- They're just... - You can put it in its ass.
yeah just like like finally creating the first the first full might as well just
be a simulated universe and just kids everywhere are putting putting carts up
there your their dog's ass well it's leaving bees and fucking talky
sticks my dog's ass yeah that's the game that's a good that should be that should
be our indie game funny revenue game that is that yeah I think we need to
- Yeah, simulator.
- Branch out into gaming.
I think that's the next thing we need to conquer.
- You know, we did our multimedia empire.
- We had a book, we did a, we're gonna do a movie.
We did streaming video games,
now we need to make a video game.
And we need to release an album.
- And then we stream the video game.
- Oh my God.
- And then we make a new meal.
- A new type of food?
- A new kind of food.
Bread.
- Then we wear--
- Sandwich.
new shirt. Bread sandwich. Oh speaking of if you bought the the fucking awesome Caleb
shirt can you send if you got it can you send me a picture of it because I got
mine and the print is small and I want to make sure that it's not like that for
all of them. We desperately need a screen printer if somebody knows yeah if
somebody knows like a really chill guy who hates money and spend prints t-shirts
please put us in contact with him. Again he needs to despise money yeah he needs
to be he has so much money's throwing it away do it for the love of the game
that's right yeah and make sure that he's fine with stuff that's extremely
copywritten yeah and is very easily crass taking it out gusting yeah and in
poor taste yeah things with the p-word on it yeah let's just we'll leave it at
that he'll speak no more on this shut up 11 bring the latest American Idol reject
to sing into the microphone just trying to be creative lol and then april mandy
says that's not a way to abuse it yeah what are you talking about i get to
hang out with a celebrity dude yeah but you get to hang out with sanjaya this
2005 this probably william hung territory oh if i got to hang out with william
hung i would be smiling william hung to talk to my dog
yeah man dude have you ever heard his album william
instead of when my carpet i make william hung i put his face in
William Hung's face as he sings. Bringing William Hung to my house to sing to my house plants so
they grow up big and strong. My mom bought that album my mom bought his album Inspiration.
Yeah yeah that's awesome dude. Pretty good he had a whole he had a cover Rocket Man on there.
Wow. Is that the one with Take Me Out to the Ballgame? No that's his second album.
He's got a he probably probably fine right? There was also there's also Hung for the Holidays.
Oh hold on let me make sure that's a thing and not something I made up yeah
that's so Attila the hung yeah yeah for the holidays is it is an album no I
didn't just hallucinate William having a Christmas album you did I did I wish
yeah imagine I I'm the only one that thinks that a William Christmas
- You called it that?
You called it hung for the holidays.
- Yeah.
- What the fuck is wrong with you, Pat?
- I have nothing wrong with me.
- You're right, you're perfect.
- Keep disc out of way of dog's head.
- Yeah, let's say it at the same time.
Ready?
Three, two, one.
- Keep disc out of way of dog's head
when he finally gives up.
- Let's throw it at him.
- Keep a disc out of way of dog's head.
- Let's do it like row, row, row your boat.
- Okay. - Hold on.
- Whatever you get you a punctuation.
- Keep disc out of dog's head.
- Of dog's head.
- Keep disc out of way of dog's head.
- When he finally gives up, throw it at him.
- Caleb, you're late, we have to start over.
- Fucking Christ.
- Is there a disc in this game?
- All right, let's start over.
Start over.
- Start over. - Frisbee.
- Oh, why is it called a disc?
- Probably British.
- Frisbee's a brand name.
- Is that a British thing?
brand name I didn't know that that's why they call it ultimate instead of
ultimate frisbee whoa I call it ultimate frisbee and my
to jail yes oh fuck you're gonna make so many friends in jail there's a really
gonna make some very special powerful friends in jail no this one from arc arc
commando almost not a noob kill your game that's true that is the ultimate way to
abuse your nintendo is just step on the
DS cartridge yeah just throw it in a vat
of acid yeah you're fucking nothing when
I was a kid I had like I had deep kind
of existential nightmares that every
video game character was sentient yeah
and that like I every time I turned off
my xbox I would kill them imagine
imagine you throw a disc at your nintendo
over and over and you're hurting it you
wake up one night your DS is glowing and
and your nintendo comes out of your d_s_
yeah all my god all master chief knows is fucking pain did
yeah it's true there never never once is he had just a fuckin
just a silent sweet moment
yeah in those games he's always trying to kill or be killed yeah
well now when you turn on the xbox he goes to sleep in naps
you get to sleep and i think he dot s_r_g_p_s like what i am a candidate
in that
Cortana have a Bubba ready for me.
(laughter)
- That'd be, I think the biggest problem--
- Cortana, where's my pinky?
- Cortana's kinda too small for him to fuck, unfortunately.
- If you think about it,
Master Chief is wearing a big onesie.
- Do you think Cortana,
his suit definitely has like a vibration setting.
- It has a diaper in it.
- Do you think Cortana, Cortana after--
- For sure.
- Give him a little vibrate down there,
little rub and tug.
- Where, down where?
- With the suit.
- Down where?
On his butt or his feet?
- On his feet.
feet yeah rubbing rubbing his feet and then tugging his toes to pop them yeah
you guys are right you do that to me well I do that to you I'm really good at it
dude I'm I can pop any part of the human body I'd like to see you try okay well
here we got a William hung his name dropped here whoa response to that's not
a way to abuse it I'd cut off my ears if I had to listen to someone like William
hung four hours in a row. 14 make your dog watch hours in a row of Martha Stewart
living and then you add the cotton bunny ears to the Easter egg to make the Easter
bunny oney complete. Dog whimpers. I don't think the dog would try to speak English.
Yeah I don't think that's true. Yeah. Probably get excited. Yeah. Yeah. Number 15
poke it in the eye with a stick then never feed it or let it drink then take
it for a running walk then when it's asleep poke it some more. Okay you
fucking fucked up freak. You psycho dude, what is wrong with you? Truly a psycho. Oh my god.
Even for this thread I mean come on. Yeah even for IGNboards.com. I know.
That's just, that's not right. Legacy account you psycho. This is kind of a
nasty Dirty Carlin style one. Whale it is sleeping, tax a big and heavy thing, add
throw it at its ass and then it might shit itself and eat its shit. And then he
responds to that H that I can't I did it but failed somebody says somebody says
make your dog read this thread that's a pretty that it's funny that that insult
has persisted all these years 15 years later people still throw that one out
yeah yeah keep hitting it with a cart says April Mandy where's there's a cart
- Is there a cart or, you're thinking of Mario Kart.
- Is there a cart?
Is there a cart?
Because they said earlier to put the cart in the guy's ass.
- I'm Googling Nintendog.
It's cart with a K, too.
- We should play Nintendogs.
- Yeah, oh my god, Nintendogs?
- Oh, there's a--
- You raise a guy.
- It's kind of virtual, buddy.
- You can buy it, you can get a Mario Kart toy in Nintendogs.
- Oh, and you put it in its ass.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Nintendogs would be good.
- They have a, I see, they have different,
You could get the Bowser one and put it in your dog's ass and it's got spikes on it.
Oh man, if I had the Bowser toy in Nintendogs, it's the only thing my dog would be eating.
[laughs]
Mm-hmm.
Someone says, "April Mandy."
That's like getting a... that's exactly like getting a Hitler chew toy for your dog.
Dude, I would get that and just watch him tear it to shreds, but then stop him from fucking it.
Yeah.
No, no! You don't understand, Fido!
No, that'll make him happy!
That's Adolf Hitler and he loves to get fucked!
By dogs!
Hitler loved getting fucked by dogs.
That's why he was obsessed with German Shepherds, which is something I learned from an Always Sunny episode.
Yeah.
'Cause that he would fuck these kind of dogs.
Yeah, and he would actually have really good sex with the dogs.
Mm-hmm.
Was that bitch really his cousin?
Eva Braun?
Yeah.
I don't know.
Let's find out.
Yeah.
I'm just going to say that she is because I don't like him.
Oh, here's a Hitler thing.
There's a guy...
Here's a Hitler thing.
Yeah, at my work, we do like deliveries to people.
And there's a guy apparently who...
Oh, yeah.
Who gets alcohol delivered sometimes whose name is Swastik Kar.
Swastik Kar?
Swastikaar?
First name Swastika, last name Kaar.
Oh my god, dude.
What an unfortunate name.
What the fuck, that's the greatest name of all time.
Dude, just an Australian pronunciation of Swastika.
Swastika?
What? I'm not delivering this shit.
I'm not delivering this there.
Some kind of Nazi.
We gotta get to his house now.
yeah I looked it up and swastika is an Indian name which makes sense because
it's an Indian guy named Swastika. Well yeah isn't the swastika an Indian name?
it was because Indian people were Nazis first and then Hitler took it and made
it evil but before being a Nazi was a sign of peace. That's not true. It's true.
yeah yeah it was like it was like hippies yeah yeah twisted it into his own yeah
perverted creepy vision exactly did an Indian guy named swastika I will never
stop thinking about swastika Jesus Christ fuck all right let's find
another there's so much just sort of back and forth banter in this thread until
Michael Jackson in the room with your Nintendogs so MJ can be
creative LMFAO and then like 50 exclamation points he can be creative
lolling at that put Ryan 007 11 in the room with it clap clap clap who's Ryan
Ryan007. Oh, then at the bottom it says "Just kidding though."
Ryan James Bond. Yeah.
Throw the frisbee when the dog gets it, take it and repeat it.
Run over your dog while DS is on.
This guy's not talking about the Nintendog. You turn on the Nintendog's game
and then you run over your real dog.
Drown your dog by making it drink tons of water.
I don't think that's drowning.
Every time your dog turns around and shakes its butt, poke its butthole with the stylus.
When I first got my dog and she started to do that move, I kept on poking her there until she got really mad.
She growled.
Every time I touched the screen, she jumped at me and tried to bite me, and then she ignored me.
Every time I called her name, she would turn around and would scratch up with her hind legs.
Of course I fed her and walked her and seems alright after that. I kid you not.
But when I poke her now, she doesn't get as mad.
I guess I have so many trainer points she doesn't get mad at me anymore.
Did you guys ever play Virtual Buddy?
Yeah.
You remember Virtual Buddy had like a George Bush skin you could put on?
They had George Bush and John...
And Kerry, yeah.
John Kerry.
But I remember doing... I remember like playing Virtual Buddy and...
it had the George Bush skin on it and I was just like blowing him up and shit.
My dad walked in to the room and he's like,
"Jesus Christ, that's just sick!"
Blowing up a fucking...
There's no blood at all.
This...
There's another... Here's another sub list.
This one has a really, really good one in it.
so i'm just gonna read through these and i'll stop when i get to the good one
to remedial or on it
when it's jump rope in or whatever make it go under and lifted up fast blow up
your cartridge if the combat copters little pellets shoot the dogs when the
mike things comes on cuts at the dog
joystick it scares my dog so much make it listen to my michael jackson songs
make it look at charlie chapman
starlet chapman i get so bored watching charlie chapman movies
Charlie Chapman's mustache scares the hell out of me.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
When I see his little mustache it freaks me out.
I hate Charlie Chapman.
Grab a tail and his mouth will go on your stylus and throw the dog.
Use the chopper to hit the dog with the propeller.
Get a fancy vase and throw it on the dog's head.
Get a ballon and make them make it explode.
This is a pretty good comment here from April Mandy.
Tal what do you want? Hey just being funny. I'm gonna wall you tall
50 we reach 50
50 one time I grabbed my dog's tongue, but it just growed at me. Lol you try it. I
Will I like all these ones that are like they're like all these like intricate tricks that just end with like and then put it
In prison like this one is like making the dog spin again and again and it will fall then you will have the chance to grab
its nose which you should shake around then you tap really and I mean really
hard on its head finally you deprive it of food water and attention for a month
it seems like you don't have to do the first part of that yeah it's from Ariana
smiley face throw a gold bar at your dog is there gold bars in the game no no no
just do it no I know there's no gold bars in Nintendogs I did the ultimate
abuse to my Nintendog where I left my my DS in a taxi yeah who knows what
happened that fucking dog right some I think that guy do you think that
taxi driver just like think he's still playing that game yeah dude it was taxi
driver like from the movie it was actually Buster Buster De Niro from from
taxi driver I've never seen it Buster Bistro is a scary name like that Buster
bistro yeah his name is Alex Trebek mr. scary mister that's guy mr. that guy be
scary Mandy Mohawk Texas driver mr. scary mr. scary Italian man yes scary Terry
yeah scary swaggy Dave swaggy Dave from Texas driver is one of my favorite
characters I think I might go as him for Halloween swaggy Dave is one of the the
biggest antiheroes yeah it's amazing I'm
trying to money and mine decide to base
their entire personality around swaggy
Dave yeah I'm watching the Joker movie
I'm saying to the screen this is just
swaggy day ripped off my boy swaggy D
they ripped off swaggy Dave so hard with
this fucking movie and now look at me
just right now they want and now they
want to make another Deadpool movie
where he crosses over with swaggy Dave
they want to put swaggy Dave in the
Marvel Universe and he's even more sarcastic than Deadpool? I'm checking out
of pop culture. Yeah, okay James Gunn is directing the new Swaggy Dave movie.
Swaggy Dave is literally problematic. He literally rescued a child prostitute, okay?
We can't put him in the Marvel Universe. He literally stole that swag from another
guy. He stole it from Swaggy P. He stole that swag from Swaggy P. Mm-hmm.
I don't know. Swaggy P is the basketball player right? Yeah dude. He's the one that dated
Diggie Azalea? Nick P. I don't know. Nick P? I don't know his last name. Nick Pipp. Nick
Pipp. Nick Pipp's your brother. He's my best brother. Yeah. That's what you, it's like a
combo best friend and brother. Best brother. Yeah. Number 48 put it in the
same room as a wolf from Wolves and Friends and have the wolf give it rabies.
I would do that. Were you guys scared of rabies when you were a kid? I was more scared of
tetanus. There was a kid in my hometown who got rabies and I bit him and I
bit him to get him back. Yeah I got him I got his ass but I was always scared of
like like raccoons and shit because I thought that that kid got rabies from
like a raccoon but I think he got it from like eating something. You're getting a
raccoon. Really? Yeah. He ate raccoons. Yeah he ate a live raccoon's teeth. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah with his arm. Yeah.
That happens if you do, if you do that. If you eat a raccoon? Yeah. Yeah you just, you
turn into a raccoon. You do turn into a raccoon, it's true. Yeah. You turn into
Sly Fox. Uh-huh. Sly Cooper. Sly Cooper. Whoa. No, Sly Fox is a new character I have.
Sly Fox is a... that's humongous in it.
No, you're thinking of Spy Fox.
Spy Fox!
Spy Fox was... it was like Spy Fox and Putt-Putt Saves the Jewel.
You're thinking of Guy Fox.
And Freddy got fished.
Freddy got fished?
Yeah.
And...
Yeah, whatever the other one is.
Pajama Dan.
Obama, Obama Sam.
Yeah.
Those games were awesome, dude.
Oh yeah, those were the best.
Click on whatever's jumping.
you go to the library and you say can I play can I play runescape and they say
no we only have we only have Freddy's his fish you got a little bit ready the
little fish Freddy okay good thing I know how to how to use Google translate to
look it to look at fuck calm yeah the children's room at the library I'm 23
years old a library computer was just like that was the fucking holy grail do
- Yeah, dude. - If you get a spot on that,
anything is possible. - We were playing, oh shit.
- I didn't know how to filter stuff.
- What was it called?
What was that game?
It was by, I think, the same company as RuneScape.
Was it Territory War?
Was that what it is?
- Oh, no. - It was Poopscape.
- Do you know what I'm talking about?
- Yeah, the one, is it the one that's like a worms ripoff?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I used to play that all the time at the library.
- It's called like Magic Guys.
- Magic Little Worm.
the Jagex fun orb no arcanists no no no no no brain org
Jaguar was the was the website Jagex games so well somebody just tell us fun
orb here's a comment here from Brendan o9 why the heck would you have 100 ways to
abuse your dogs I have three Dalmatians and they are just as precious as can be
Wow that's adorable. You think he's talking about real dogs there? Yeah. Chaos control
here has um has a really like evil psychological warfare kind of idea. At
the park play with the other dogs it painful in their eyes lol. Wow yeah
conduct it conduct an experiment where five dogs are in prison and five dogs are
prison guards and then see if the prison guard dogs take ultimate power. Which I
- I think is what happened in the prison experiment.
Didn't they take ultimate power?
- Yeah, I'm pretty sure they attained godhood.
- That's why they had to shut it down so early,
is that in the notes, they were like,
"Ah, crap, they obtained ultimate power.
"We didn't expect it."
- They actually got a level up.
- Oh no, they became the perfect life form.
- Ah, crap.
- Ah, Jesus Christ.
- Wasn't the whole thing with that,
wasn't a lot of it super exaggerated or some shit?
- I think so.
- And really, it was just like--
- Yeah, wasn't that all fake?
so many so many a bunch of study like psychological studies they just like you
can't reproduce them like that's like an issue in science it's going on right now
is like there's a bunch of like in science it is there's a bunch of like a
bunch of old studies and like experiments where like if you just try
them again they just like aren't true well yeah I just every time I meet a
baby I ask if it wants to fuck its mom and it rarely says yes so Freud even if
I try to give it a marshmallow. Even if I say that if you don't do that you can have a marshmallow.
I'm gonna mix it let's mix up all of them together so it's it's a prison
experiment yeah with only babies and marshmallows are the moms and
they see who fucks the marshmallow and who is and who kills the baby yeah it's
kind of a genius idea yeah and also the entire time there's a monkey
there's a gorilla doing the moonwalk through the screen and you have to see
if the baby's noticing right or if they're too distracted by the marshmallow thing
yeah you know what I mean and it's the thing about the gorilla moonwalking is
it's impossible to tell which direction it's walking because it's an optical
illusion right it's either gorilla or it's two faces making a gorilla yeah
yeah yeah and if you look at it you get a headache cuz it's bright green
and then if you watch the experiment and then you blink your eyes a bunch of times
and look at the wall you see a picture of Jesus. Yeah, but if you look
away from the experiment you get an electric shock. That's true. I did a
thing in, I had to like for my psychology class when I was at UNCW, do like
like be in one of the experiments and it was in like a classroom and there
was just one computer and basically the experiment was like see if like you and
another person, like there's another person with doing the exact same
experiment in another room and they, you each can basically punish each other by
like playing a really loud noise or like not punish each other by playing a
really quiet noise and the other person who's not, didn't exist just kept playing
like a really really loud noise and they, they, which is like a pretty common
experiment. Yeah. Just to see like if people retaliate. Yeah. But the guy who
set me up at the computer he just like hammed it up so much he like set me down
he's like there's a guy in the other room let me tell you what this guy is a real
asshole
yeah yeah he's got a little I yeah he's psychology so stupid dude it is it's
funny that people go and spend like six years getting a master's in psychology
yeah number number 60 is get the jump rope and make the dog bust its nuts I got
one here from master of vid games it says they say I got some 72 name your dog
shit water gay wad 73 never check on your dogs for weeks onths or years decades or
centuries repeatedly hit your dogs with hard things repeatedly use the jump rope
to trip your dogs or use the pull rope and throw the dog against another dog
repeatedly lol JK I would never do anything mean to my precious Nintendogs
I'm just going along with the joke and then a enigmatic lamp says here they
quoted it and said name your dog shit water gay wad in before ban you need to
fully censor the word was gay wad that was a curse word back in the day yeah
- Number six, or number 76 is when it's sleeping put him in her, put him, in him,
put him/her in a circle of gasoline and set a match. Dot dot dot. Death. 77. Put
poison in food and drink. Dot dot dot. Death. - Number 65, when your dog has its
back turned to you try to shove a bone up its butt. Lots of this. - Yeah that's right.
this is my favorite one by Pika pet it over and over till it gets mad at you
then hit it here's one here's one from it Vic rub his stomach and then crack him
in the nuts with something I got a really good one my dog in the nuts really good
one here from Trey gold throw a tennis ball at it and when it's about to pick
it up you pick it up and throw it at him or her pick it up and repeat over and
and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over
again everybody okay whoo that was a lot of typing edit and over and over and over
and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over
and over and over and over lol April Mandy
every dog so you're doing so and then someone no one responds wrong my
friend's dog cannot swim at all and when it falls in his pool they have to jump
in and save it number 94 tell the dogs they suck and will never be able to be
great you'll never be able to be great from Yoshi Yoshi 99 999 rock by
two dogs way bigger than it that's a good idea yeah your dogs you guys know anybody
growing up with a great Dane no my my uncle had one my friend's uncle was Dane
cook that's right there's a great thing my my friend growing up had a he had a
great Dane and then maybe it's talked about this before he had a younger
brother who would like ride he would get naked and ride the dog like a horse and
And then his they had to like give the dog away because one time their mom came home and the little boy had his
Like entire hand in the dog's ass
*laughter*
This is not good dude, this is a bad situation
And then their dad died
*laughter*
Yeah, that was a rough one.
Well...
99 whip it with the jump rope.
Number 100, show them the 100 ways to abuse your Nintendogs list.
And then they kept going.
And then the next comment after that is, "Huzzah!"
*laughter*
101 give the dog a wig, take it on a walk, and throw something for it and take it back.
and then there's plot a reply that it says
you're kinda only going to one hundred right
uh...
rights will sport
keep the topic alive
plus nintendo's a need in a year old
one of three
kill the dog that another dog loves
i created another threads that we don't need one hundred and four things on a
one hundred let thing list
they made a new thread
and it's a little justin's just continue this new this thread and then the threat
That was the last post.
Oh my god, this topic spanned like a year.
Wow, oh my god, yeah, it's 2006.
It took IGNboards.com a year to come up with a hundred things, dude.
We could have done that, we could do that in ten seconds.
Yeah, ten seconds.
Okay, hit your dog once, hit your dog twice, hit your dog three times, hit your dog four times.
Feed him a stinky meal.
Feed him two stinky meals.
Dress him up in human clothes, marry the dog.
Poop on him.
- Poop on him.
- Poop on him, like surgically attached breasts to your dog.
- Get feeded poop.
- You could slowly turn him into a man.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- That's some real shit.
- That's real shit.
- That's actually real shit. - That's just real shit.
- Yeah. - People don't realize
that's just real shit.
- People don't realize real shit sometimes
and I'm here to do it for them.
- People need to realize real shit.
Realize, realize real shit.
- I'm trying to think of other ways
you could fuck the dog up.
Fire hydrant, I mean anything heavy I guess.
Yeah, gun, sword.
Make him listen to your wife.
Basically all you gotta do is sit on the dog.
Get your dog a wife.
Get your dog a fat wife and a job.
Make him do human shit and then say, "Listen buddy, you thought you had it bad.
Check this shit out."
He'll never talk to you again.
(mumbling)
- Make your dog, how about this, make your dog vote.
Make him choose between a crab sandwich
and a turd fat guy or whatever.
- Yeah, a turd filet.
- Whatever, what is the South Park thing?
A douche bag.
- Giant douche and a turd sandwich.
- Giant douche and a turd sandwich, yeah.
Who, we're watching the debate tonight.
Who's gonna win?
- Me. - Last word, last words, Pat.
- You know what I'm gonna do?
You know what I'm gonna do?
If we watch the debate on the stream,
I'm gonna sit there and any time
that one of them's talking, I'm gonna say,
loser says something.
- Oh my God. - Oh, okay.
- You're like Immortal Technique, dude.
- Yeah. - Yeah, you're taking 'em down.
- Yeah. - Taking 'em boys down.
- That's right. - Yeah.
And then they're gonna make me the president.
- They will.
In a landslide victory, people have voted
for a sarcastic guy named Patrick.
- Hey Pat, you should change your name
- I'm gonna be the most sarcastic guy.
- Sarcastic, oh my God.
- Sarcastic.
- Yeah, yeah, I'm totally gonna not do that.
- I was thinking the other day, it was making me laugh.
- Yeah, I'm totally not gonna do that.
- It was making me laugh really hard the other day
thinking about a guy who is driven to suicide
by sarcastic comments.
Just mentioned today the suicide, now he's like,
"I could deal with the kid running away
"and my wife leaving me and losing my job,
but the god damn sarcasm, it pushed me over the edge.
- It's too goddamn much. - When people would say
not after stuff, oh.
- Hey, your wife's home, not.
- Well, guess what, I'm gonna live.
- Hey, we found your son. - Not.
- Not, yeah.
Yeah, we totally found your son's remains.
- Not. - Yeah.
- And I'll leave you with this,
I'm totally not gonna kill myself right now.
- Not.
- Not. - I'm totally not
gonna kill myself, not.
- Got 'em.
- All right, yeah, subscribe to the Patreon, everybody.
- Subscribe to the Patreon, we got shirts.
If you had a shirt issue, Caleb will refund you out of pocket.
- And again, if we could get maybe somebody
with like a mental disability
where they don't understand the concept of money
and is really good at screen printing shirts,
please put us in contact.
- Yep.
- Okay, thanks.
- All right, thank you, goodbye.
- Bye.