you're listening to Israel's number one podcast
you're a crap monster
okay we're back, Cameron stop recording
okay I stopped recording, now Pat say what you were gonna say because when you asked me to stop recording
why are you saying it so quiet, we're not recording
say it
I knew it. I knew that me and Patrick would get married. I knew it was gonna happen.
I knew it would be me and Patrick and not Caleb and Patrick.
Caleb's trying to make himself cry.
You'll never make yourself cry.
[laughter]
This is...
He's just looking at us.
Alright, we can just do the episode normal and Caleb can sit there and cry. So Cameron, what did we do this weekend?
We everything we've done this weekend. We've talked about 20 times already on these episodes
So it is so hard because it's like we usually just yeah, this is like the fifth episode
We've recorded in two days where we can like not we don't have to talk about you know
We could just make stuff up that we did. Yeah, I went to the outer space store. Oh my god
What I bought a rocket ship full of aliens
Caleb's still crying Caleb still crying in the corner. Yeah, Caleb's getting cut out of the patreon
Yep, Caleb's gonna get cut out if he doesn't.
If he doesn't say one word per minute on this podcast,
that's the minimum to get paid.
And it's been one minute, you haven't said anything.
You guys really get married?
Yep.
Yeah.
Me and Pat got married this weekend.
Yep, me and Cameron got married.
We got married in the 7-Eleven.
We got it notarized at the Chili Dog Notary Public.
Yep.
We had our honeymoon in the therapy castle.
Mm-hmm.
You making him happy?
Yeah.
Really?
We're happiest we've ever been.
Patrick, are you happy?
happy it's all opposite day it was all it was all a prank on you you're in the
Jamie can do that I was in the Jamie Kennedy experiment here he comes here
you're on my god you're on your own folks I'd like to be in the Patrick
experiment and experiment with his body it won't happen yeah that was only how
part of a prank there's only part of the prank we have something very important
tell you what happened guys we're adopting you we're adopting you you're
gonna be adopted he's crying again don't you hate your mom don't you want to cool
dads who are married to me and Cameron are gonna we're gonna teach you how to
do we're gonna take you to the firing range we're gonna shoot around you like
William tell I have a question yeah is it legal to marry your dad no it's not
legal it's legal and I mean okay we can ask Woody Allen about that yeah cuz he
married his dad yeah his dad no we can we can add here's a question would people
be so mad at that guy if he had just married his mom instead of his daughter a
guy who get who's who's like a guy who marries his mom swag a guy who fucking
marries his daughter disgusting gustus testing pedophile a guy who yeah a guy
this is your death warrant man you still listen you still I'm gonna kill you I'm
gonna kill you with time yeah you still listen to hoodie Allen do you hear what
he did married isn't mixed up yeah hoodie Allen married his daughter that
is a pretty bad Dean that's a pretty bad fucking name yeah yeah yeah yeah bad in
the first I'm a rapper named pill Cosby yeah yeah I'm Barzi Weinstein yeah I'm
rap Hitler sup I'm rap hit that's literally in the first episode of what
his kids you know Brad Hitler yeah like the first they do are driving down the
Street in this fancy car. Fuck me!
Yeah. What about this guys? Who's on first?
I'm Kevin Blaisey. There we go.
I was thinking of one because I- I'm Matt Lowder.
Cameron already came. I was going to say I'm Money Weinstein and then I realized that that
does not sound well. It's a little anti-semitic.
Yeah, exactly. Yeah, go ahead and do your new character, Pat.
Money Weinstein. Money Weinstein.
Do it. Do a doozy voice. Okay.
Yeah. Alright, ready?
Yeah.
"How's it going, everybody?
My name is Wesley."
Wow.
That's not how it sounded in the early versions.
Yeah, when we were practicing before we started recording.
It sounded kind of like sick Dracula.
Dracula with a stuffy nose.
Yeah, well that's what happens when Dracula eats garlic.
He gets...
He's allergic.
He's allergic to it.
Yeah.
Do you think he has normal allergies too?
Do you think Dracula has chronic fatigue?
Yeah, that's why he's up at night.
And that's why he's asleep all the time.
Yeah.
Insomnia, chronic fatigue, fibromyalgia, fibromyalgias.
- Yeah.
- Fibromyalgia.
- No.
- Mm-hmm.
- God damn it, no.
- I won't allow that to happen.
- He's got PTSD, he's got POW, that shit's Dracula.
- That's right.
- That's what the doctor said to him.
- Who's his doctor?
- Dr. Frankenstein.
- Don't say Dr. Acula.
- Better.
- That's better.
- Dr. Jekyll.
Frankenstein
Better, it's better. Dr. J
Doctor used to be a horrible screamo band called dr. Acula. Yeah, there's just a scrubs been
Dr. Acula, I never listen, but I saw it was just one of those bands
Yeah, like all their songs they're doing like a meatwad voice
But that's also about like like killing a woman who wouldn't look at you in high school
Yeah, dude
It's so funny that like every screamo band is just like
They have like the guy screaming and then like the the guy singing you know like a date remember. Yeah, yeah
Gonna kill you
My mom made me brush my teeth I hate my mom. I'm gonna kill her
Yeah, that's what every song is like every man
Sold every white man has a
Voice guy and a singing guy in their brain. Yeah, you have two wolves inside you
Yeah, one has a scream guy in the way the singing guy. Yeah, I
Love yeah, it's a pedophile and the misogynist those
Every man has one. Yeah, those are the two is the two. This is the two wolves
Yep, mm-hmm all right well, that's enough for the episode for today
Now that we're done. I guess I'll just marry Patrick. No. I don't think that's gonna happen. You can't do well. Will you marry me?
Make you happy
Doesn't matter that you're 15 years old we can go in my car and go to the store. I hate the store
cigarettes inside I smoked a lot of cigarettes and my voice sounds like this now I'm only
25 years old it's a young man and an old man yeah that's the perfect screamo band yeah yeah
it's just like a blues singer and a girl a blues singer and a guy yeah a guy with a Bieber
hair so John which is gone yeah he's like you're 15 years old and you are mature for
your age it's like you never looked at me in high school and then he's like I'm
gonna put you in my trunk
your body they don't know he has a pit my ride trunk and there's a PlayStation in
there yeah it's a water bed have you guys ever been on a water bed no my mom's
mom's boss had a waterbed and I would go over to her house.
You were sleeping on your mom's boss's bed?
Yeah, when I would fuck her in the face.
No, my mom's boss had a boss that the office was just like a room in her house.
Yeah. And so we would go over there and my mom would be like,
"To keep you entertained, you can go jump on the waterbed."
Oh yeah, baby.
And I would just feel, I would mold the water, because you can move the water around.
And I would sculpt a beautiful water.
The shape of water.
Nice.
See, if I had a waterbed, I would get a clear one and I would put a fish in it.
What movie is it? Hellraiser or is it Nightmare on Elm Street where there's a dead woman in the water bed?
It's your life. That's my life. You're right. I got mixed up.
There's a dead girl in my water bed!
I'm gonna sleep on it anyway.
I feel like I'd be more comfortable on like a chowder bed. Yeah.
Yeah, a peanut butter bed.
A peanut butter bed would feel great. That'd be awesome to mold your body. The water bed, you feel like you're sinking.
This is kind of like a peanut butter bed.
This is a good peanut butter bed that we're all laying on together.
Like all the grandparents in Willy Wonka.
Yeah.
One of them.
The grandparents in Willy Wonka were definitely 69ing.
Second the camera turned off, they were not actors.
Oh yeah.
They weren't actors, they were grandpas.
They found them there and then they wrote the movie around that scene.
Yeah, they found them living in the studio in one of the prop beds.
They're like, "Damn."
Just all fucking stuck to each other.
"Y'all look like some grandparents to me."
Y'all look like a chain link fence and I'm gonna turn you into movie stars.
Pause the orgy for like two minutes, we'll get the take we need, you guys can go back
to it.
Yeah, that's actually just the lemon party guys.
Yeah, it's true, Grandpa Joe did a lemon party.
Uh oh, Grandpa Joe did a lemon party.
Oh my god.
Yep, talking about Joe Biden.
Joe Biden was in lemon party.
Look closely, he's the one, you can see him.
He's the one.
He's the one getting sucked.
Wow.
It's funny, I was thinking about like shock sites that were just, just like a guy's penis.
Yeah, it's just gay porn.
Yeah, like how is meat spin like...
Whatever, dude.
Yeah.
I've done meat spin in the mirror before.
[laughter]
I have!
But the point of meat spin is you show it to a girl and they don't know what a penis is.
They think it's an alien.
Oh, it freaks them out.
Yeah, they think it's a...
It's to find out if a girl's straight or gay.
Yeah.
So then you can see if you want to be married to her.
Man, I gotta go pee right at the top of the episode this time.
That's alright.
I'll be right back.
Oh my god.
Dude.
This mean- the Matt and Pat project.
Uh huh.
I'm Matt.
Matt Caleb.
Matt Caleb and Pat- Matt- Matt Rick.
Mm-hmm.
Finally the Patrick and Caleb project starts.
The Patrick and Caleb project will commence.
This is what I'm gonna call our house when we get married.
It's not gonna happen.
It's happening.
It can't happen.
Why do you think I drove all the way up here?
Why?
Because it's not legal.
It is legal. They made it legal in all 50 states.
No they didn't.
Legalize it!
Gay marriage!
Legalize gay marriage. Oh, oh
Damn legalize a body boy
Man that's the best I think body boys the best homophobic slur it's the best one. It's so funny
It's not even close cuz yeah, you know why I do I ever does cuz I don't know what it means exactly
I have no idea what I'm saying.
It's probably so bad.
Yeah, do you ever feel like, you know when you're in your room at night and you're making
up Chinese and you're...
Do you ever feel like you say just like the worst thing ever?
No.
You say the worst word.
You're making up Chinese, it's probably pretty bad.
Nah, come on.
Nah.
But at some point you say like the version of bitch in Chinese, you know?
I um...
God, I don't know if he's Taiwanese, my mom's boss, but he taught...
Your mom is Taiwanese?
My mom is Taiwanese, yes.
getting politically saying Taiwan's not part of China. I don't know.
I don't know if he speaks Mandarin or Chinese. Hey Pat is Taiwan part of China yes or
no? It's all up in the air. This depends on if you're ever allowed to
travel to or this will decide whether you're allowed to travel. Sorry I was trying to out some Chinese.
I thought Taiwan was a province in China. I thought Taiwan was a state. I
think they I think they have problems with each other. I think yeah China's like
you're China and Taiwan's like no we're not we Taiwan Taiwan is Chinese for
Hawaii that's right yeah it's Chinese Hawaii yeah yeah cuz you know yeah
Hawaii does not want to they're not part of the US yeah my mom's boss taught me
how to say you're fired go for it I don't remember it it was in high school
also I wasn't gonna figure out if I did say it I wouldn't get the dialects right
or anything or like yeah everybody would have been so much of my friends took
Chinese in high school so I knew like a few phrases but I don't know the pitches
or anything. Isn't it like man isn't it like Chinese is not the language it's
Mandarin? I don't know. Mandarin and Cantonese. Yeah. Yeah. And there's like and
then there's different dialects of both of those. The class was called Chinese.
Well there's yeah there's like also like simplified Chinese or whatever. Right.
Right. Which I speak all of it. I speak all of it I know it all. Yeah. I speak all of it but I just
I just described the different...
The way you can speak Chinese you just describe what the different symbols look like.
Yeah, it's kind of like a tic-tac-toe board if you were losing real bad.
And that means lunch. I don't know. Yeah, this one's kind of like a tree.
Yes, it's a bird that's a bird that means bird.
Circle means circle. Uh-huh. Yeah.
Chinese is easy.
Chinese is so easy, man.
Thank God the Egyptians invented being Chinese.
Yeah.
Yeah, looking for the bathrooms, just be like,
man, all these doors say tree.
I don't know where I'm supposed to go.
Yeah.
That's Chinese for boy and girl in the bathrooms.
Tree.
Yeah.
Bingo.
You have an evil bag in your room.
Yeah.
It's moving around.
Evil bag spinning.
Evil bag--
I got to get my boards fixed on the wall.
I got to fix that.
You gotta get treatment for your disease, man.
- Yep. - Yeah.
- It's burning you up.
- It's burning me up inside and out.
- Do you guys think we'll get COVID after this?
- Probably. - Probably, right?
- Most likely.
- What do you think we're gonna, like, we'll get COVID?
- I think we'll get back, I think me and Caleb
will get back home and then in four or five days
we'll have COVID.
- That'd be pretty sick. - That'd be my prediction.
- And then I won't have it.
- Well, luckily we stashed these episodes away
so we won't have to do anything.
- Exactly. - Right.
- That's true. - We thought ahead.
- Uh-huh. - Yeah.
- Yeah, we got negative tests, which is good.
- Yeah.
- We'll still get it though.
- Yeah, we could still get it.
- We definitely will.
These cats are Patient Zero.
- No, absolutely.
- Yeah.
- No, they're not.
- Yeah, they are.
- They look like bats to me. - Patient Zero is me.
- Oh, really?
You're the one who--
- It's my fault.
- So you came up with it?
- Why'd you do it?
- Boredom.
- I was just bored.
- I wanted to get history moving again.
- Yeah, they canceled a baseball game.
I just I didn't like I wanted to see and want the election to happen
I wanted to post office to go away. I hate the post off. Oh my god. I hate why I go
Yeah, you know I think the first the only person who wants the post office defunded the most is probably Mark Maron yeah
Oh, I can hate the post office. I hate sitting in line. Yeah, he waiting in line the fucking party
Really funny if stamps comm has never paid him. Yeah, he says that he just says it cuz I'm even real
it's a he invented it is yeah nobody's ever used stamps.com dude no yeah no yeah
you walk to the post office yeah it's not that fuck why people complain about the
post office so hard yeah it's really what I was going to the fucking post
office subway is worse than the post subway is way worse that we should get
rid of subway yeah but we should go one last time yeah yeah and try every
sandwich yeah yeah long parties of sandwiches comm instead yeah are you
tired of standing in line at the subway. Are you tired of making that face?
They're gonna send you all the meat in the mail. You can make the subs yourself.
That's right. You tired of going waiting in line at subway? Here it is. It's called
the grocery store. Boomer lives. Who? It was this cat. Remember he used to end all the
episodes saying "Boomer lives." No, I never listened to the ends of the episodes. What?
Once the interview was done I stopped listening. Yeah. That's adorable.
You're so stupid and some not stupid. You're so fucking turn off your discord notifications. Yeah, I'll turn off your shit
I'll turn it off if it makes you happy camera you down. That's what you do for your husband. Mm-hmm
wait
No
Please you say no he says like
Damn, god damn boys
We had a good weekend. We had a good weekend, man. I took some of the worst shits of my entire life
Yeah, man, I just like fucking you know when you go to the beach
And you're a kid and you make one of those drip castles with the mud. Yep. I did that in your toilet 40 times
Yeah, baby me. I never lit a candle
What was it? There'd be at the euro spot then?
Maybe the red arrow. Yeah, you're a yeah, they gave me a burritos all french fries. Yeah. Yeah hell. It's pretty good though
It was pretty good but it destroyed my body.
It was just too many french fries. There was like no chicken in it.
There was too many french fries in there.
Then they gave us a box of french fries. There's too many in there too.
French fries were good though.
Yeah, but there's too many of them.
You gotta make it more expensive, less french fries.
Also, I need some cheese on them fries.
I'm gonna need a gold bar.
I'm gonna need you to put a gold bar into my bank account.
- Yeah, I'm gonna need you to give me my money back.
- Here's a get rich quick scheme.
Go to McDonald's, yeah, can I have a hamburger
double cheeseburger with $100 in the middle of it?
- Yeah, instead of a slice of cheese on my filet of fish.
- Can't you put $200 bills?
- $200 bills?
- Yeah, that'd be funny.
- No, wait, the filet of fish you can't do it with
'cause there's a half slice.
- There was like that McDonald's hack
where if you go to the ordering kiosk,
you could order 10 hamburgers with no patties, only buns,
and it would cost negative 10 cents or something.
- What?
like patched after like a day or two but for a little you can actually McDonald's
they knew the update mm-hmm so funny can you imagine this like people like
rushing I'm like holy shit I'm gonna get so rich do you guys know about the this
the world of fast-food hacks where you spend you just like ruin a cashier's day
so you can yeah you can save 50 cents on a fucking right fucked up yeah oh I'm
gonna get a chipotle burrito with free meat yeah I mean they're like trying to
make a Big Mac and so they'll order like four sandwiches and they're like yeah
I put them together, but like remove all this stuff
and the poor cashier is just like trying to keep up.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, saved 18 cents on,
didn't even have to buy the Big Mac.
- Didn't even have to pay.
- Like you, you made more money.
- You know how much a Big Mac costs?
- 60 bucks, that's a fucked up.
- Yeah, dude, triple A Big Macs nowadays.
- Yeah, I think I might eat a Big Mac after this.
- Yeah?
- I would not.
- I've been, I would say every six months
I get a, I have a strong consideration
for like seven days. - I don't think about it.
I'm like, "Man, I should get a Big Mac."
Now I'm thinking about it.
I've eaten McDonald's once since this whole pandemic.
I've eaten McChicken.
I made a vegan Big Mac.
Yeah, me too, actually.
Yeah, I've got my chicken.
I used to be a McDonald's twice a week guy.
Yeah.
I'm the same.
I was McDonald's once a week for a while in LA.
I just don't do it anymore.
Now I'm Arby's.
I would have been twice a week, but I was just like drew that line in the sand.
I was like, "If I'm at McDonald's twice a week, I might as well just be dead."
I got switched over to Arby's while we lived in LA.
I eat Arby's.
I had Arby's a few times.
It's pretty good dude Arby's is my life. My dad's Jeep used to be full of Arby's rappers
Yeah, yeah, you mean R&B singers R&B rappers singer R&B Jason Derulo, Tay Zonday
Yeah, these guys. Yeah, yeah, yeah, he'd said my dad would sing sexy love with a neo
My dad was in sexy love with neo
Matrix, yep, he'd sit down
It's a sexy neo
Today the list. Top 10 rare things more likely to happen than winning the lottery from Dark
Shadow. Read the intro. Everyone's heard of the lottery. Everyone hopes to someday be
lucky enough to have the winning ticket but it's really rare the Mega Millions is one
in 302.6 million odds and the Powerball is one in 292.2 million.
Either way, it's extremely rare. There are some
strange or interesting things that are surprisingly more likely.
Okay. Wow. Okay. Okay.
Number one has become president of the US, one in 100 million.
I feel like that's not true. I don't know if you can put numbers on it like that.
That's not true. Here's the thing, if you...
Well, they kind of fuck it up because you only are counting towards the odds of winning the
lottery if you buy a lottery ticket.
Right.
If you are born, you are-
You don't just become the president.
Yeah, no.
You don't enter into the competition to become the president just by being born.
Yeah, the odds of becoming the president are pretty high.
Patrick, stop leaning back in that fucking chair, you idiot.
If you're a Kennedy, pretty damn high.
No, odds of becoming a president is always one in two because you're either the Republican
or the Democrat.
One of them is going to get there.
True.
It depends which one wins.
Yeah.
like the Bush fellas oh they just yeah like if you're a Bush you have a what one
in 50 you have a one in two they should let Jeb be president for a week yeah oh
my god week and came for a day my wife for the rest was it like um there was
some like socialist yeah it was actually me just Jeb Bush the socialist yeah
because Jeb Bush is in Putin's pocket his asshole pocket I'd love to jump in with
him pocket and that's it but it works yeah but it's a good Jeb Bush is one of
our one of our greatest defenders from he was Terry Shivo's defender he was dude
he was he took care of her and she had a perfect life after that yep yeah keeping
her on that tube keep me in that tube what that bitch out of that - let that
Nobody can hear her, she's stuck in that tube!
Jeb Bush wanted to-
Terry Shivo got stuck in a Pringles can.
She got Augustus Gloops, dude.
[laughter]
Terry Shivo got stuck- that was the whole thing.
He was like, "Do we let her out?"
No, we're not gonna let out- we're not letting Terry Shivo out.
Look, I don't wanna let her out.
'Cause my hand can't freakin' fit in the can.
My hands are too big to get into the tube to get her out of there.
I can't get her out.
Anybody ever notice how you can't reach into a Pringles can with your hands?
How do they put this bitch in there in the first place?
first place what are they accidentally mix up they get a bunch of potatoes at
the at the tennis ball and my wife is Mexican what how come all the chips look
the same what's going on so I jabbed your sword jab
yo soy jeb bush and so I blast a spaniel yo soy jeb bush to Eris terry terry
shavo hola ola your retail so I started the Pringles tube out of the Pringles
to cherish ever we're gonna get this bitch out of that Pringles - we're gonna
get we're no we're gonna keep her in because that's what God wills God said
if she can't talk you put her in a Pringles - we're gonna forget about her
we're gonna put the lid on the tube I'm gonna make her I'm gonna throw her in
the ocean like a message hidden in a bottle a woman hidden in a Pringles -
That's what Carrie Shavo is to me and she's an American hero. Please clap for me. Please clap. Please clap. Classic Jeff.
Classic Jeff. Please crap. Please crap in a Pringles tube. Please crap in a Pringles tube. Mail it to my office.
I'll look at it. I'll smell it. I'll send you a review.
One of the best. No other candidate's gonna give you that. No other candidate's gonna smell your shit.
Not even my demon brothers who used to make me do that for them. Look, my demon brothers made me do it.
I kinda like it now. I smell the shit.
That's George Bush. I smell shit.
I'm eating shit. I'm ill sick.
I think I told you guys this before, just one of the best jokes I ever heard was like
why do Pringles come in a tube so you have something to shit in after you're done eating
them. That's good.
My friend told me that in middle school and it's just a perfect joke.
No, it's good. Yeah, it's out of nowhere. I mean, I don't even wait. I eat one Pringle. I'm sitting in there. That's
Yeah
Dude I need to stop eating coffee Pringles you eat one Pringle. There's a rattle in the can, you know
You get there to leave empty space. You got to fill it up
What if you ate one Pringle then you got a squirt brown water in there to muffle the sound of the cans?
It's rattling around so that so that this so that the so that the people in the TSA don't hear the Pringles can stuff
up your pant leg. Yeah, that Pringles tube, it has Terry Shivo on it. She didn't pay for
a ticket. Man, fuck this, I don't want microwaved airplane chicken, I'm bringing my poop Pringles
on the plane in my cargo pants pockets. Man, that Terry Shivo story was like the first news
story I remember being like, "Oh my God." Yeah. You're like, "Oh my God." It was just
about, it made me think about like what it meant to be alive. Yeah. Yeah. I was like
six years old. It was like my first existential crisis. Yeah. Who's Terry Shivo? Is that a
one by Metallica off of? Yes. Now she's this bitch who got stuck in some chair.
I don't remember. Didn't she drown or some shit? Yeah she drowned and then she was on life support for a
long time and then it was like a decision like oh should we like we want
like we want to pull the plug like I think it's her time to go and then Jeb
Bush was like no she'll God doesn't allow that. She's coming back around. I think she's getting better.
(laughter)
- Hey, Jeff, fuck me!
Jeff!
Jeff, come in here and fuck me!
- Can we get the cameras off?
Or leave 'em on?
My brothers are gonna wanna see this.
- We'll send this to Moloch.
- Yeah, no, she was like--
- We'll send this to Frylock.
- From what I understand,
Hillary Clinton is sacrificing babies to Frylock.
What the hell?
a Freylock statue on Little St. James.
- Yeah, they did.
That's where the house is.
- Yeah.
- Carl lives in Little St. James.
- Keep going.
Carl, who else is on that show?
- Meatwad.
- Yeah.
- And Milkshake.
(laughing)
- Milkshake.
- And Mark McGuire.
Okay.
- Okay.
- Keep going.
- And the Little Moon Men.
- Moon Men.
- Okay.
- Remember when Boston had that huge terrorism scare?
- Yeah.
Mooninite?
Yeah, the Mooninite people.
Uh-huh.
It was pretty funny, man.
Pretty sick.
Yeah.
Boston is so stupid.
It was just some, like, fat Irish cop.
Just like...
He was like, "Oh, whoa! Hey, there's a little triangle guy!"
"There's an alien bomb!"
"The aliens are here! What the fuck?!"
"What the fuck? Let me at 'em!"
[Laughter]
"Oh my God!"
"What color's the skin? Let me at 'em!"
"I'm gonna arrest this bomb!"
[Laughter]
He's putting handcuffs on the bomb.
"I'm gonna cuff this bomb!"
I'm gonna cuff it up right now. I'm gonna cuff the red wire to the green wire
Number two, yeah, he's trying to take get rid of the moon tonight thing and he actually blows it up
Number two is get struck by lightning one in 12,000. Oh, I don't like that's not the Boston be true
Yeah, the Boston police officer sees the the bomb and he's like we got to get this thing out of here and he gets on
a plane
One in 12,000 getting struck by like that's more likely than the fucking president. No, you can't tell me that what would that be like?
300 people a year gets getting struck by lightning. I'm sure yeah, how many people actually that sounds right Google it
Getting struck by lightning would be awesome because it would be like drinking an energy drink and it would have no adverse effects
That's a really much like an energy drink
What's the recommended daily doses of getting struck by lightning?
440,000 incidents.
How many people get struck though?
Incidents is different.
You just thought four zeros was two zeros.
I couldn't see it.
I could see it from here.
240,000 global incidents with lightning.
That's pretty fucking crazy.
A year?
Every year.
Yeah.
That's a lot.
That is a lot.
Lightning strikes per year.
Yeah.
2,000 people are killed worldwide by lightning.
Annually.
That's insane.
And most of them happen in those, in countries where people still wear armor.
Yeah, true.
Extrudes of armor and stuff.
Most of them are trying to make, are trying to bring a monster to life.
Mostly happens in Scotland.
Yeah, mostly, it mostly happens to those freaking Instagram influencers who wear the big hoop
earrings.
Basically 90% of the incidents are with Benjamin Franklin.
Yeah.
You tell me, you're telling me he got, his little key got struck?
You're telling me lightning struck another man's key?
Okay, I think I'm understanding this.
God is kinda gay.
Okay, God is a little bit of sus right now.
Yeah, I don't believe
Benjamin Franklin got
struck by lightning.
He would've died.
He gave him sexual powers and sent him to France, dude.
Actually, what happened is,
the lightning shot him so far
that he landed in France
in a whorehouse filled with 14 year olds.
And he was like, "Let me thinky
I'm gonna likey this."
inspired me to invent the $100 bill it's that picture of my face yeah it's
fucking it's scrambled his eyeballs and he had to wear glasses with seven lenses
I would like to use yeah I think I'm gonna invent the Illuminati that's what
he said I'm going to create the Freemasons guys they just had the
craziest idea. He got struck by lightning and he's like I just had a vision what if there's
a pyramid with an eyeball? And yeah it just created a... You gotta stop smoking that lightning
Ben. You always smoking that lightning. Yeah that's how they used to get high. It's from
the sky. Lightning is from the earth. Number three win an Olympic gold medal one in 662
deaths. Yeah these are not chances this is not something where you just roll the dice.
you have to work towards that. You just make stuff up dude. Yeah. Yeah. Chance of stubbing your toe?
One in trillion. Probably one in two. One in two. Every, every, because you have two feet. One in ten.
One in ten because you have ten toes. Yep. Yeah. Wait what's ten times two? It's twenty. So one in twenty.
So it's twenty, one in twenty. I like that you bought yourself time to do the math by asking us.
What's ten by... He was trying to dazzle us. He was trying to, he was trying to show that he could do it.
do it. How fast, yeah. You ladies want to see a magic trick? 2 times 10 is 20. Yeah, you
guys want to see a magic trick? 2 plus 2 is 4. Fuckin'. Fuckin'. Hold on, can I start over?
Let me hold that. I could have been- Don't look at my hands when I'm doing the trick!
1, 2, skip a few, 3, 4. He's typing into a calculator. Yeah, 1, 2, skip a few, 4. What's
the highest you guys have ever counted? I counted to 100 when I was in elementary school.
I counted to a thousand. I counted to a hundred...
It was like a hundred or two hundred so it wasn't very high.
It was actually two hundred.
I definitely, there were days when I was like, "Today I'm gonna count to one million."
And I started counting. I counted to a hundred. I was like, "What am I doing?"
It's super exciting because you hit numbers you forgot existed.
Yeah, and you'll be like, "Whoa, six hundred and eighty."
And you can be like, "Shut the fuck up, mom. I'm counting."
And she'll be like, "Oh, he's learning."
I'm counting! Please get out of my room!
Hello!
pressing numbers out there, pressing up on a keyboard.
- Yeah, would you ever just press equals a bunch
on the calculator?
- Just to get, you see how high you can make it go?
- Yeah.
- Do like 80 times 80 and then just equals, equals, equals.
- We should do that.
- That's like, that was the first video game.
- That's true.
- Play-Doh came up with that one.
- Yeah, I remember doing that at my grandmother's house.
She had a calculator where the like,
all the buttons were like rhinestones
or like fake plastic gems.
I would press them all.
Does that work on a on the paper calculator?
That what's the paper count the old ones that you still like it didn't have an LCD you talking about an abacus
that's just Chinese check you mean like a counting machine and what's it called a
Son addition there. I know you're talking about like the only one that's got the roll. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Oh Dex, no, no. No, I know I know you're talking about talking about like the receipt in it. Yeah
Yeah, what's a yeah Rolodex is on a cat on a cash register as a receipts
All right, we need to get this guy off the podcast. I'm gonna leave unless you marry me right now
You have two seconds. No two seconds to marry me 40
Number four being accepted into Harvard University one in 20. That's just as likely as stubbing your toe one in 20
It's not one in 20 one. No, it's one
To apply it's not just like you're born. It's like you have a 120 chance going over. Yeah. No you have to be white
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you have to be a white guy named Branson Bush Branson Bunsen
Bunsen burner you gotta be named Kyle to get in there resting you gotta be named Preston Kyle hunter
Winklevoss, that's right. Yeah, you got to be a fourth you guys ever heard of if the Winklevoss twins you called them the Winklevoss
Did you ever hear that joke that someone could make that's what I the Olsen's I called him
the
that they were still young.
- Yeah, he should.
- I am seeing double.
- Yeah, man, he thought they were the youngsons.
- Yeah, not the old sons.
- They never actually had a wedding ceremony.
He just saw them on Full House.
- He didn't realize that--
- I am marrying them.
- He didn't realize you could have twins
that are older than 10.
He thought when you get a certain age,
you stop being twins.
- You become your own person, yeah.
- Yeah, man, just be yourself.
- Just be yourself, stop doing shit.
- If I went to Harvard, I would've killed it, though.
i mean i'm andy very successful i still feel as you join the illuminati so many
people so many people are harvard in my what was my idea that it's like it's
funny like in my hometown if a kid goes to harvard it's on the news
yeah and it like in boston just like
everybody else is a very nice school is super like academically like like we
just don't have any way to the smarty pants missouri i know the school is the
school just let me they just want to make the kids either kill themselves or
go to a really a college like that's the point of the high school
the public high school my desire to use camera went to brain age academy
yelling to bring it
if there was a school and i wanted to be a little
range academy i'm gonna get some brain and i had a from you pal
if you buy a major brain is underage brain from patrick what he's fifteen
districts fifteen
what
on fifteen
number five data supermodel data supermodel one in eighty eight
hundred thousand. For me it's- You need to learn to read numbers Patrick. For me it's
eight hundred and eighty thousand. He said eighty eight hundred thousand.
Eighty eight hundred thousand. I've dated eight hundred eighty eight thousand supermodels.
It's a one in eight eighty eight thousand chance. Also if you have-
Interesting choice of numbers at the beginning of that one. If you have like five
thousand dollars and like you started an app this goes way up.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You can date any supermodel for a night if you know
the right person. Yeah. Don't make the cat do mischief. Please don't throw stuff at the
cat. Number six, hit a hole in one in golf. That's probably... One in 12,000? None of these
are chance. I thought... That's the first one though that like... I also think it's higher
than that. Yeah. Like hitting a hole in one is insane in golf. Like maybe for a pro it's
one in 12,000. That's true, yeah. But like normal people will play golf for 50 years
never get a hole in one. Yeah. I could get one. I mean I got one my first ever try. You
know? Yeah most of the time I'm not trying to get a hole in one because I don't want
people to like hate me for my skill. I just got a lock in. What I do is I do transcendental
meditation. I have a hud flip. I visualize a hole. I get a hud over my eyes like a boner.
And then. And then I use my pee pee to hit the ball. Oh wait using my pee pee to hit
- I need to bowl.
- That's right.
That's right.
Yeah, hole in one, dude.
- Have you guys ever gone golfing?
- No. - No.
- I mean, I've gone mini-golfing.
- Yeah, I could be a mini-golfer.
- What's that new golf thing?
Super golf, what's it called?
Fly golf.
- What are you talking about?
- Top golf, that's what it is.
- I've been to a driving range.
- Top golf.
Dude, top golf, honestly,
we would have a lot of fun at top golf.
- Yeah, is that the word you hear?
- It's like a bar.
- There's a bar, it's a video game, basically,
like the there's like lights all over the the it's a driving range but it's like
multiple levels and so you hit the balls and try to hit them into like these
different parts of the thing and it lights up and you get points and you try
and beat your dad it's been there's a lot of a lot of drinks there was a good
food it's sick and you don't have to dress like a like a man all for you can
dress like a woman if you want yeah that's pretty progressive there was a
there was a mini-golf like some kid in like eighth or third grade had a mini
golf party for his birthday it was my brother's friend and I went to it and I
kept saying like hole-in-one every time I got a shot and I annoyed this kid so bad
that he threatened to beat me up in front of my dad. Damn. Just like yeah he deserves it.
Yeah well go ahead I'm done with him. Yep yeah I'm here watching. I can't believe we
didn't get to go have lunch with your dad and mom today. Yeah. Sucks. I know. What are
gonna do man what am I gonna do for lunch now you're not gonna get it I'm gonna
get you lunch I'm gonna go to Arby's after this for sure I don't there's the
only one is in the mall I'm calling it a mall you're going to the mall anyway man
I've to return some stuff to Kohl's yeah yeah you're here 15 years ago
yeah sure Kohl's yeah I bought two pairs of there's no clothes in the mall there
was 15 years ago there wasn't there was I mean I opened it there was no Kohl's
in the ball, the ball is in the bed, or the poles is in Bedford.
You're in bed. And it hooks it. You're in bed with a Ford. You're in bed, turd.
You're in bed with Harry Ford. No, that's you. Yep, that's you. No, you're in
bed with Harry Ford. You guys wrote the, you guys published the Protocols of the
Elders of Zion together. You're with his son in bed. No. Why did you, why did you
publish that pamphlet with Henry Ford? Why'd you do that? Yeah, what was the deal with that?
- I was bored.
- You were just bored?
- So you were like, eh,
Protocols of the Elders of Zion, let's go.
- Yeah.
- You fucked up monster.
- I had the printing press,
he had something to print.
- And he was your friend.
- And he was your best friend.
- He taught me square dancing in school.
It's so funny that he like,
what was it, Henry Ford made a bunch of people square dance
because he didn't want jazz to take over.
- Oh, he's like the number one most racist guy in America.
- Yeah, yeah.
- He seriously is.
- He thought Hitler had swag.
Yeah, yeah, he was I mean like Hitler swaggy with it. Yeah, I mean that that was why he was like a big part
Of why it took us so long to get him right in World War two
Yeah, because he was just like publishing all this propaganda like the protocols of the elders of Zion
Which was like yeah, the Jews are they're all in this big room, right?
And they like get together and they talk about how bad we suck. You know how much that which cooler they are
They're talking about it behind their backs
They don't want me to make my big cars. They want they want me to make a small car. They were
No, thanks. Yeah, no chance car that uses little gas not a lot. No, fuck them, dude
Yeah, and then and then he was like and also Hitler has swag. Yeah
So it was a major swag Hitler got MLG swag. Yeah, but then he found out Hitler had AIDS and he gave up on him
Mm-hmm. Holy crap. Say something
upon you he sang that he invented that song
that song was based off of what he said after he found out that Hitler had AIDS
Hitler has AIDS
oh come on honey
Stick Cars by Gary Neumann
Hitler has AIDS
(laughter)
mmmm
Bowl of Perfect Games
1 in 11
(humming)
i say hitler has aids
and then i tried to the store
and i drive back home in my car
hitler has aids
hitler has aids it's true
he does though. I'm glad that that's becoming funny again. hitler having aids?
yeah it's so funny to me. it's like the most 2008
it was like hitler has aids
And I was like, yes. And then for 10 years I was like, no, he didn't have AIDS.
He was a racist. And now I'm like, Hitler definitely has AIDS.
Oh, that's back.
Oh, Hitler had AIDS for sure. He still has AIDS. He's in Argentina because they've cured AIDS.
Yeah. Except for Hitler.
100,000 years old.
But there's no cure in that attitude of his. No.
No, he's such a grump. Hitler was one of the biggest grumpsters on planet dumpster.
- Who's the original game grump?
- That's right.
- Number seven, bowl a perfect game in bowling.
111,500.
- What's a turkey in bowling?
- That's like a little bird.
- That's when you use a turkey like a ball.
- That's what they call, that's your bowling nickname
in the league.
- Call that a butter ball.
- They call you turkey.
They go, "Hey turkey."
- I think it's above 200, right?
That's a turkey.
It's probably because they give you a turkey.
You get a free turkey leg at the Ren Faire.
You get a frozen turkey.
Yeah, that's probably true.
Do they have bowling at the Ren Faire?
Yeah.
They freaking bowl with crystal balls there, dude.
Did you guys ever go to a Ren Faire?
No, I never did.
I did once when I was little.
Of course you did.
My dad took me. I didn't choose to go.
You went there. You chose to go because you were a magician.
There was a guy who juggled knives standing on a yoga ball.
yoga ball you were a little magician they had a big one they had a liger the
littlest magician you were the little yeah yeah I think we have a liar right
here that's not you and it's you is there using your little magician magic
I don't have any man you're using Jedi magician tricks on stop Cameron's a
little magician I'm not a little magician you're not a little you're the
littlest magician you just made me burp I can't believe the way that you guys
- You guys treat me sometimes.
I think you're a magician, I look at you
and you start to make me feel funny.
You must be doing some sort of hex.
- That's not magic, dude.
- That's charm.
That's charisma.
- He's a snake charmer.
- Cameron sits there with his little flute
and he makes my snake come out of a wicker basket.
- Whoa.
That's right.
I'll make your snake come out of its little
wicker, wicker, wicker, wicker basket.
- Number eight, be Delta Royal Flesh and Poker.
- Yeah, I want it to be all the time.
- 650,000.
- There's, one of my cousins has this husband
who's just the dumbest guy in the universe.
He's just so stupid.
- So he's your cousin too?
- No.
- If he's your cousin's husband, then he's your cousin.
- He's my--
- He's your cousin.
- He's my second.
(laughing)
He's my cousin.
- Yeah.
- So my cousin, just an absolute dumbass.
And he, the first time he ever played poker,
he played with us and we were playing like,
it was like a $50 money game or some shit.
he got two royal flushes in like five hands.
- Damn. - It's so annoying.
- Yeah. - 'Cause it's just like,
don't you hate when someone who sucks gets lucky?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- It just pisses you off, dude.
- Then he walked outside and he got struck
by lightning seven times in a row.
- Yeah. - And he came back in so high,
he created the elders of Zion pamphlet.
(imitating a lion)
- No, he's a good guy though.
- He's not.
(laughing)
- Number nine, make it in the NBA.
one in eleven thousand seven hundred and seven i did man i like those odds yeah i could do that easy
eleven thousand dude i'm cooler than i could get i could join the g what's the what's what about i
could walk in there i could shoot a uh ball from double half court full court then double two half
courts wow no it's like i'm standing on one court halfway and i shoot it into the middle so you even
get the little buffer in between like it's extra wow dude that's crazy half court punt well i've
done it. You have? Yep. High school. I used to be really good at half court shots.
You did a, you got a food court pint of ketchup. In college, I became one of those
guys in college who like to play. That's right, you got a food court pint of ketchup. You guys like that one?
Let's go! It's true. In college I became one of those guys who like would go play pick up
basketball all the time and just like it was right when I got into basketball is when Steph Curry
Curry became a guy in the NBA so I was like, I'm just Steph Curry man.
I'll just shoot from half court.
I was leaning on your wall and it clicked.
Oh, okay. I thought one of those was about to fall on your head.
That'd be cool. Probably.
Remember the fucking, the Sketch Troop basketball game?
Oh yeah, dude. So I would just like go and play pick up, like, downtown or whatever.
Yeah, you guys took that shit so serious.
Dude, I'm so good at basketball.
I remember one time just like bricking 10 like horrible long threes like just over and over again and then this like
Seven foot black dude who was playing pick up with me was like listen man. I'm never giving you the ball again
As long as I play with you you're not getting this ball. Yeah, alright. I guess I'll leave man
The cat just stood up like a hydraulic car. Yeah, that's the only thing you know that stands
What else stands can we one example a guy not like that? I see that cat
I say that stood like a guy. Yeah, I might get that cat nice. Yeah. Yeah, I was a good guy remembered the fucking
To sketch basketball. Why did we have one of those?
I don't know Jelani started it right people people like best. It was fun. Yeah, I just didn't like you suck
Yeah, I had a lot of fun. I just I was just wondering why were you on the mooyah team?
I was on the Mooyah team and the basketball team started practicing and I took their ball and shot it half-court into our
They had the other side of the court
They weren't supposed to have it and then I took their ball and then they owned and left good
Yeah, they started they started Corona and in Boston
That's true. It started from the from the school basketball NBA the NBA being closed is directly
Was caused by yeah by those people yeah by the Emerson basketball team. That's true. It's pretty funny very very funny
Yeah, yeah some guy was there. He was trying to he was trying to shoot a three-pointer with his mouth
Yeah, he's like I bet I can blow this ball into the hoop
He's like if you guys ever seen that clip of my new Ginobili, and he's playing you
He's a basketball player for the story about a little
Wizard then no no he's a big big
I believe.
Does he play for the Wizards?
No, he plays for the Spurs.
Oh, okay.
Or not anymore, he's retired.
There's a team called the freakin' Sperms, dude.
At one point...
They need to shut this shit down.
Oh my God.
At one point there was a...
Disgusting.
I'm gonna shoot my sperms in the hoop.
In the middle of a game in the stadium, he catches a bat out of the air with his hand.
What?
Yeah.
You gotta watch that video, dude.
It's fuckin' sick.
Yo, that's sick as fuck.
Yeah.
A bat was flying around the stadium.
He just goes, "Ah," throws it away.
Oh my God, dude.
Damn, that's sick.
He caused...
- He caused baloney.
- The baloney virus.
- He caused a bat in the trash can.
(laughing)
- Number 10, win an Oscar award.
- They should just give me that damn Oscar.
They give me that Oscar.
- It definitely goes.
- They should just give me that damn Oscar.
- Yeah, I'm in my Grinch shit tonight,
you give me that Oscar.
- I'll say this much, your chances of winning an Oscar
go way up, shoot through the roof if you make a great movie.
- That's true.
(laughing)
If you give a career-defining performance...
If you make the best movie ever, it's pretty high, actually.
Yeah.
Right?
If you make, like...
Pretty goddamn high.
Stickbug the movie...
If you make A Bug's Life 4...
You make Stickbug the movie...
Yeah.
You're getting an Oscar.
I think you're gonna get an Oscar.
I'm gonna make Parasite 2.
Yeah.
Parasite 2, the coronavirus.
The corona-site.
Whoa.
'Cause the parasite right now is corona.
Dude, now I have to pee.
Dude, you infected me. Hold on.
Now you guys get your own special podcast like we got.
Alright.
Patrick, Caleb's going in the litter box.
Caleb's using the- what the f- get out of the fucking litter box!
What are you doing?
Stop peeing in it!
What the fuck?
He's- oh my god.
Oh!
Dude, he put his tongue on it!
God damn it!
He's- now he's like squir- he's like scratching it like a cat.
He's scratching his own face with his foot.
Oh my god.
Why are you- oh!
Stop!
Stop! Caleb, stop! That's disgusting!
What the hell?
That's sa- oh my god.
Oh my god. AHHHHH!
Dude. Now he's pooping it and-
STOP! Now he's banging his head
against the wall over and over. STOP IT!
Stop, Caleb! STOP!
Stop!
Fucking hell, dude! Oh, he fainted.
He's on the ground. He's on the ground.
He fell into the litter box.
We're gonna have to scoop him out with the scoop lid.
His bald head is touching the-
- His balls are out.
- You know, thank God he doesn't have hair right now.
- That's true.
- Yeah, if he did, we'd have to get peanut butter
to get it out. - I would pick him up
by his hair.
- Mm-hmm, I wouldn't touch it.
What are you gonna, touch the poop in his hair?
- I would comb it out.
I would comb the poop out with a lice comb.
- Ugh.
- That's normal to do to somebody.
- I don't think so.
- If your homie just falls asleep in the litter box,
it's normal to comb-- - With a lice comb.
- To comb the poop out with a lice comb.
- No, you get peanut butter and you wear rubber gloves
and you get that shit out like it's bubble gum.
You put you wash your friends hair with peanut butter and the dog will lick all the poop out of their head
Yeah, then but I mean you put peanut butter in it. You can't tell what's where the poop begins where the peanut butter starts
That's that's some true shit. That's some shit. They don't tell you about in restaurants
No
They don't know where the poop is gonna get peanut butter starts in your hair at a restaurant from the way
You're getting a peanut butter sandwich at a restaurant nine times out of ten. There's gonna be some poop in there
Yeah, because they don't they can't tell the difference. They got a jar Skippy makes a
poop also and the same skippy poop chunky.
What the hell did I walk into?
Oh he woke up.
I wasn't asleep.
Yeah that's right you were unconscious.
Yeah he fainted.
I was in the other bedroom.
No you fainted.
No.
You were not in the other bedroom.
Yeah I was.
You were in the bathroom.
That's what I call my bathroom, my other bedroom.
Yeah you sleep in the bathroom.
My secret public bathroom.
Yeah.
My secret little place.
Mike Birbiglia comes out on stage.
My secret public bathroom.
Just fucking with the upper deckers on stage dude.
What I should have done was poop in the bowl.
Was flushing.
What I should have said was flushing.
Yeah.
Oh my god, I'm on fire.
Winning an Oscar.
I'm on fire!
Do you think you could get an Oscar?
I could get an Oscar.
I could.
Three 6 Mafia has an Oscar.
They should just give me that damn Oscar.
Juicy J has one.
I'd just give the coolest speech of all time in a movie.
They'd give me, I'd be like one of those characters that's in it for one minute who says something
crazy.
You would sit there.
It's like that fucking, that epic Charlie Kaufman speech where he goes up and he's like, "Thank
to the Academy, 30, 29, and he like cheekily says the countdown as they count him down.
Yeah. You have to be weird all the time. Yeah, come on man. Just be normal for a
minute man. Yeah, just make like a cool Will Ferrell movie. I would Eternal Spongebob of the spotless mind.
Eternal Spongebob of the Squidward mind. There we go. Let's get that one going.
I would point at people and just say pedophile.
(laughing)
- Yeah, pedophile, pedophile, cool, cool, pedophile.
- Yeah, if they let me in the theater for the Oscars,
I would shine a laser pointer on everyone
who won an award, I would shine it in their eyes
while they were trying to talk.
- I feel like one day we'll be at the Oscars, right?
- Yeah, we'll make it, dude.
- We're on the path.
- They should just give me that damn Oscar.
- They should give me that damn Oscar.
- We will make a movie one day, yeah?
- Yeah, absolutely, we're already making one.
- Yeah, we're making an epic movie too.
- Epic movie too, man.
Epic movie too, man.
- Epic movie too.
- Yeah, it's gonna be good.
- Borat is gonna be back.
Napoleon Dynamite will,
Napoleon Dynamite was a date movie,
but we can have some crossover.
- Yeah.
- I feel like, okay, the new movie movie.
What's the new movie movie?
Date movie, epic movie, girl movie.
- Superhero movie.
- That's probably what's gonna--
- Scary movie.
- No, but with like a genre.
- What about funny movie?
- Funny movie.
- Funny movie, and it's actually very serious.
- What about movie movie and it's a parody
of all the movie movies?
- Yeah. - Whoa.
- That's actually not a bad idea.
- That's actually kind of the best idea ever.
- We should write that and then do it.
- Yeah, we should write movie movie.
- We should write that and do it.
- It's kind of what Nerd in the Hood
is supposed to be a little bit.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Oh, we can have the Nerd in the Hood.
- It'd be one of them.
- Nerd in the Hood would be a movie movie.
- Yeah.
- Movie 43.
- That's kind of what that was, yeah.
Do you like that movie?
- No. - No.
The thing is about that movie,
like the ball chin thing is funny for like
- 15 seconds and then you're like,
it's just gross.
- Yeah.
- Ugh.
- But then it's funny again when you just think about
whose ball, whose face it is.
- Meet the Spartans.
- We could do a parody called,
called Feet the Fartans.
Right?
- Well if we just take elements from it.
- It's about feet that fart.
- Feet the fart.
- Feed my farting.
- Feet that are farting.
- Feed my fart hole.
- There we go.
Cake farts.
cake for its parts to we can make a part we can use a court's uh...
if you are to have barbecue sauce on our asshole yet instead of chocolate cake
frosting i said
yeah and it's
man i gotta go p again do you really like that i think you so much what i
had a wreck the point where we had a poison atmosphere that they can go in
the area will be a happy like thirty seconds man
all right go p fast right
right
Cameron keeps peeing.
When was the first time, how old were you when you saw cake farts?
Uh...
I saw it pretty late. I saw it when I was seventeen.
Damn. I think actually I was kind of similar. That was one of the only shock videos I didn't see.
It's more porn than shocking. Yeah.
It's definitely bad.
It's gross.
I didn't, it was the first time I ever saw what a butthole looked like when it farted.
You know?
Um...
I saw I went to lol shock calm when I was 11 Wow
That was a fucked up fucker. That's a fucking fucker. So I saw goatee when I was 11
I saw I went through all of them to see if I could do it. I couldn't do like the pain Olympics
Pain Olympics I could do you could do it because it's shit like it's like I don't like I've actually never seen it
Yeah, doesn't he like cut his balls?
Yeah
Why would you do that?
Bored.
You're bored.
I'm bored. I'm bored. I'm bored.
I saw...
There was like...
One of them where like someone puts an octopus
in their pussy.
Cool. That one was weird.
There's one of them on there
that was pretty funny.
It was called "Two guys, one hammer".
Yeah, no. That one I saw too early.
I saw that before the other one.
I never saw any of the like murder ones.
Two guys one hammer.
I saw in fourth grade.
Oh Christ.
Yeah.
Jeez man.
You fucking.
What else am I gonna do?
Watch TV?
Yeah.
What else?
What did my neighbors show to me?
Well like yeah, what do you think everyone here, nobody here has seen that video.
Everyone's walking around the happiest they've ever been in their life.
Exactly.
Getting tattoos and wearing an American flag.
Well I didn't grow up here.
I didn't grow up in this town.
You grew up like 20 minutes from here.
It's the same thing.
For 10 minutes from here it's different.
- I'll say, if I had seen that video when I was a kid,
I would be a libertarian now.
- Yeah.
- That turns you into a libertarian.
- That should be allowed to happen.
- Yeah, it turns you into a libertarian or a singer.
- I think--
- Singer?
- No, I live like 40--
- Put poetry in your soul.
- I grew up 45 minutes away from here.
- I don't care, that's not true.
- It's also not true.
- You did not, you better take that back.
- Yeah, man.
- Also, it's an hour drive to Boston.
- No, I grew up probably like 35 minutes away from here.
- It's not true, we went to--
- We just went to your place.
20 minutes. It was. I drove. It was 35 minutes. It was 20 minutes exactly. Oh yeah, Patrick
forgot he adds the 15 minutes for the lunch break. Yeah. True. You gotta take,
every 10 minutes. You gotta pull over. Yeah, but it's all woods there, what am I gonna do there?
Not watch someone get murdered. Watch LRShock.com. Why, who showed you the two guys with a hammer?
My friend's older brother. Your 50 year old neighbor. Come in my house, I gotta show you
something I saw the craziest shit. They just kill some guy with a hammer? Yeah they kill a guy with a hammer.
Oh come on. My friend's older brother. I would never do that man. He was only, he was my
sister's age so he's like. I would use the hammer to build him a house. Yep. Yeah.
I'm a hero. If you watch it in reverse. It's actually the story of a man being brought to life with a
hammer. The story of Jesus. There is one video on there, what I've been trying to
There's one that's called Walk the Dinosaur, you can just watch it on YouTube.
It's a 3D, it's 3D T-Rex's 69ing. It's pretty good. And that was on the shock
site so it's like under Goatse it's like Walk the Dinosaur and it's like Goatse's.
Far worse. What about One Man One Jar? Did you see Bottle Guy? Do you remember Bottle Guy?
Yeah. No. It's a guy and he has a whole 40 ounce bottle in his asshole.
is it one man one jar where he puts a jar in his ass and then it breaks?
yeah yeah oh my butt. It probably sounded like that. yeah crap I put glass in my ass.
oh man my butt is broken on the glass. but it will become stronger for this. epic fail.
that's what he said. there were other ones on there. I mean two girls one cup.
merry holidays. two girls one cup. merry holidays is just it was just an old man
who would make a weird sex video of himself for every holiday.
That's cool.
That's sweet, yeah.
He puts like a big fake penis on a jack-o-lantern and he sucks it.
Wow.
And he says thank you, and he sucks it and says thank you Mr. Pumpkin.
That's incredible.
That's really sick.
And then he dresses up like Santa and spanks himself and puts a banana in his ass on his birthday.
I would do that.
Why a banana for Christmas?
Christmas I don't know but I saw these way too young yeah so then you started
you you were like mom when do I get a suck off the pumpkin yeah I didn't want
a banana for Santa no that was his birthday you said dressed as Santa no he
says on his well he's dressed as Santa yeah so it's Santa putting a banana
Santa fucking matter if it's Christmas it was Santa putting a banana in his ass
No, his birthday, he wears his birthday suit.
Then what was the Santa thing? You said he dressed up as Santa.
That's for Christmas!
You said he dressed up as Santa on his birthday.
And he, on Easter, he dresses up like a turkey and then says gobble gobble.
And it's a video of him walking around his house going gobble gobble, gobble gobble.
You're not making any god damn sense and it's breaking my heart, buddy.
That's not what people do on Thanksgiving.
I don't even want to look at you anymore.
You're disgusting to me.
You have gone from the most beautiful man I've ever seen in my life and my future husband
to just shit.
Just pure pissing shit in a crap bowl.
Yeah.
Okay?
Mom, a video on the internet teached me how to dye eggs brown.
We got brown eggs this year for Easter.
Thank you.
We got brown eggs for Easter.
Yeah.
I'm going to lay a brown egg after this.
I might give you cancer.
She won't give me cancer.
give me cancer. I'm gonna come to your house and I'm gonna give it to you. You look like
if Dr. Manhattan looked up crime statistics. You look like if um what's a
bald guy? You look like if Lex Luthor looked up
crime statistics. There we go anymore any more takers? You look like if
Humpty Dumpty was Tweedle Deedle. Mm-hmm. Nice. That Caillou one was
perfect and then it's been it's been you know. And you guys realize that
Be on that can't be roasted. I'm too handsome. Yeah, looking too smart. Yeah mouth looks like
Your mouth looks like a little piece of shit
What is he eating he's eating my pussy
He's eating my pussy. No, my ass. It's not my cat. Not my job. Just chewing a blanket dude. Relax you fucking dad
No, he's got a sensitive stomach. So do so do so do you?
All right, that's why I want to take care of you.
Last one, number 11 to close this episode out.
Number 11, having autism.
1 in 42.
Well, there's 42 people in this room,
and I don't have autism, so I think it's you two.
What?
It's 1 in 42.
Gotcha, bitch!
Yeah.
You have autism.
You do.
No, I don't.
All right.
Bye, guys.
Bye, y'all.
Subscribe to the Patreon.
Subscribe to Patreon.
us out on Twitch. Check out Caleb's new stand-up special.
I don't have a stand-up special. It's called Triggered.
It's called Triggered. It's called Trigger Me This Batman.
Trigger Me This Batman. And he dress-ups like the Riddle.
It's called Fingered. He dress-ups like the Riddle.
I don't look like the Riddle. He dress-up like the Riddle.
Wrong. Alright. I quit the podcast. Bye guys. Bye.