You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Patrick comes to the help list.
[Music]
You're a crap monster.
[Explosion]
Patrick's gonna cry.
Yeah, Patrick is literally crying right now.
He's literally crying, dude.
I'm not crying.
He turned around and he can't even look at us.
He's so sad.
I'm not crying.
He's crying right now.
I just heard a loud zip.
I'm unzipping my pants.
Why?
I'm flashing you when I spin back around.
Oh, come on.
There's my penis.
There's your vagina.
No, I have a penis.
You have both.
You have an inward penis.
- Inward penis.
- What did you just say?
- Inward penis?
- Did he say that?
- You just said that?
- Why would you say that?
- You have an in-facing penis.
- Well, even worse.
- Yeah, that's even worse.
- No, it's not.
- You're a sick fuck.
- You're racist.
- You're a sink fuck.
- I'm not racist.
- You're the one who's racist for hearing that.
- You wanna fuck the sink.
- You're the one, if you say something's racist,
you're the real racist.
For thinking it's racist.
- That's true.
- That's a really good point, dude.
- Yeah, it's true.
I heard that. Yeah, you're the one who made it like that.
Yeah. I heard that from someone.
I hate minorities, but you say it's racist, you're the one who made it weird, dude.
You're the real racist.
If you make it weird, you might be Pete Holmes.
Yeah, you might be Pete Holmes.
If you make it weird.
You might be Pete Holmes if you make it weird.
Yeah, if you let other men fucking fuck your wife
and you just meditate to calm yourself down when they do,
you might be Pete Holmes.
You're meat bones, dude.
If you look like a golden retriever and you let another man fuck your wife...
Hey wait, does that guy look like lesbian Val Kilmer to you at all?
What?
Yes dude.
Yes!
Oh my god.
If I looked like lesbian Val Kilmer.
He's gonna come for me dude.
Yeah.
I'm never gonna have my HBO show now.
Yeah, he's gonna tell you that you made it weird.
Hey listen, you fucking made fun of me on that podcast and so as punishment you have
to fuck my wife and I have to watch you.
So that's just how it is Caleb.
Yep.
That's how it works.
Your pig wife dude?
Leave me alone.
Jesus Christ.
You got an eggplant wife.
Oh, he got that eggplant wife.
My back hurts so much.
What did you do?
My back hurts from carrying Battlefield.
I fell asleep in the corner, like this side of my bed where it meets the wall.
You got trapped?
Yeah, I rolled over into it last night.
You made a vacuum seal?
You fell into the crack?
I fell into the crack.
Like the phone crack?
I'm going to fall into your crack later today.
mm-hmm Wow yeah you would you never yeah just said I went there Wow would never he
just said that I already did you had to get choppered out you had to get
hello yeah they had to they had to they had to airlift me yeah spin around I
spun around inside your butt do someone I know I shredded it up in there friend of
mine just went like hiking in like somewhere in Washington and they were
were hiking for like 30 minutes. I don't believe they did that but go on. They were hiking for like 30
minutes and his friend just immediately broke his leg and had to be airlifted out of the place.
If you cut your butt it bleeds poop out of it. It's true. Well that's what yeah yeah you have
to sew it. Yeah you have to sew it up with stitches. Yeah you have to suture the wound.
You gotta use sinew to close your butt. You can actually use hard pee. Yeah. If you just
you can that can be a thread that you use to sew your butt closed. Yeah you can close your butt
with pee yeah yeah that's what I'm gonna do with you yeah that's why we have to do
that if you if you do that I will get so fucking mad I'm gonna close your boat
with my pee don't it's what's gonna happen if you rub pee around in your
hands enough it becomes like the consistency of bubble gum and you can
use it to stick your butt close to try if it's bleeding food I'm gonna I'm gonna
use my liquid to seal up Patrick's but like a like a jar that you're going
something in you know you boil a jar when you're trying to pick yeah yeah I'm
I'm gonna boil his ass with my pee and seal it airtight until a pop.
I'm gonna fill a sleeping bag with my stuff and I'm gonna zip you up in it.
I'm just gonna use you like a sleeping bag.
You won't!
I'm gonna use you like a sleeping bag and I'm gonna use your balls like the pillow.
And I'm just gonna...
You know those sleeping bags that have a pillow attached?
And let me tell you, I cannot get comfortable in that pillow.
I'm rolling it around, I'm twisting it, I'm punching it to make it tender.
I'm biting it, I'm licking it.
(growling)
- Sorry, I'm trying to get my pillow nice and cold.
- I'm gonna have a pillow fight with the other guy
that's in the sleeping bag.
- There's only one pillow though.
- There's two pillows.
- You have two ball sacks?
Pat fell asleep.
(laughing)
- I'm about to.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Haven't you had two monsters this morning?
- I did.
- They do nothing to me anymore.
- There's three monsters in this room.
Three monsters of comedy too.
- That's right, exactly.
Monsters of comedy tour. We should just do that man. Dress up like Dracula. We can do
what that guy at that open mic did. That one, were you there for that one? The guy
who did uh he was on it was this fat old guy in a beret and a blazer and
like striped shirt and he did a song that was Lon Chaney jr. as the wolfman and
Frankenstein singing I got you babe by Sonny and Cher to each other. That's nice.
that sounds like he wouldn't leave the stage until what's that guy's like into
the mic what that guy didn't what that guy is what that guy is in 1978 that
would have been the biggest comedy act of all that would have yeah yeah it would
be huge yeah but he wouldn't get offstage until the host of the open mic
told them or like went like ladies and gentlemen this guy did that's the best
yeah yeah I mean that's like the new version of like using a giant Shepherd's
Kane to like yeah pull someone offstage. Oh man they should bring back this
Dancing Sandman from the Apollo yeah from Showtime at the Apollo. I want to watch
Pat dude go up at the Apollo. That'd be great. In 1996. That'd be great. You know
yeah. You dressed like Ghostface Killah. I'm wearing a skelly. Yeah yeah yeah. And
Tim's. Yeah and you're just like yeah so 7-Eleven hot dogs or they've gone
downhill in quality greatly since in the last three years and they're just like
"WHOA! YEAH! LET'S GO!"
Yeah, yeah that would be funny.
Yeah, me personally.
It would be funny if they thought that I would like the videos where it's like
Rich Voss at the Apollo and like the title is like "White Boy Makes a
Black Audience Laugh"
Yeah.
And it's just me just talking about like 7-Eleven hot dogs.
You should take that video of Rich Vos, the apologist, cut you in.
Yeah.
Yeah, just too much crowd work in it.
You could make it work.
Just replace it.
Yeah.
Do you like hot dogs at 7-Eleven?
Hell yeah!
Hell yeah, I like hot dogs!
It's funny.
It's so funny.
Do you like hot dogs?
Hell yeah, I like hot dogs!
So I have to do all the voices too?
Yeah.
I have to do all the offensive voices?
You're not offensive dude. You think it's offensive to have a voice like that? Wow.
What the hell Patrick? Oh my god. Because I studied at Oxford. You studied at Coxford.
Cox Hole. You studied at the Cox Turd. That's right. Get his ass dude. Take him down.
Finish him. You're poopy. You're the poopy guy. Yeah you went to
to you went to hard turd University you went to stale University yeah you went to
Juilliard but it's spelled J U U L you went to holy holy Tard this guy went to
clown University like Brown you went to fool etard University okay you learned
acting there yeah yeah it's pretty good yeah you went to heart you went to hard
Art of Art of our community you went to shit it's a Pratt you had to crap
that's right to Chris Pratt University and it studied and being pro-choice I
studied hilarious improv lines yeah yeah I studied being pro-life and you went to
an HIV League school. Okay yeah that's pretty good HIV League yeah yeah damn
damn how we gonna come back from that one? Yeah I think we should just end the episode here. That's it right?
HIV League. Yeah if you didn't you graduated with an HPV. Oh my god yeah and you had AIDS too.
yeah yeah you went there you at age you graduated magna come aids yeah magna
come that's a new transformer they just added magna come magna come assemble I'm
not a robot I'm a human ah I didn't having you jack off a robot I don't have
to imagine. Every time you drive you're basically jacking off a robot.
That's true. Yeah. Stick shift. Every time you use the vacuum. Yeah man. Every time you fucking...
Every time you touch your phone you're jacking off a robot somewhere. That's true.
Yeah, yeah. Every time you turn your phone on and off a robot gets to come.
Hey it's five o'clock somewhere. Yeah that's right. Oh finally I can come it's
five o'clock. Oh god I'm just waiting. Tick tick tick. There it is. Oh.
all right boss man I'm heading home for the day yeah you have that door lock
right nobody's gonna come in and disturb me all right we're doing yeah we're only
- We're only 10 minutes in, dude.
- Why?
- Feels like an eternity.
- We gotta start the list at like 20 minutes or 30 minutes.
We have never been able to sustain a list
for longer than 30 minutes.
- Let's just not do the list.
- We have to do the list, we can't do another premium.
- I'm inventing a new list.
- Alright, we'll do Caleb's list this episode.
The list we were gonna do was top 10 creepiest guys,
so I mean.
- We're gonna do a list that I'm gonna make up on the spot.
- Okay.
- Like, whose line is it anyway?
- Alright.
- Alright?
- Whose list is it anyway?
you get the joke? Who's listening to this? Yeah. Who's listening now? That's a great show.
We would have been three amazing Whose Lines Is It Anyway comedians. Even when I was six years old
watching that show. There were so many props I could have pretended were my nipples in a
cold room. Yeah. Could have done Cartman voice. Cartman mockery. Eric Brad Pitt. Yeah. Those are
some of the great is some of the all-time grades drew drain Brady George Carlton
about grain Brady likes bread yep it's Wayne Brady but he's he's made out of
bread yeah Wang hang what about what about big baby all right well hold up
hold up let's get the obvious one what about brain gravy let's get the obvious
one out of the way yeah Greg poops Greg yeah Greg poops Greg poops I love doing
improv. I'm Greg Proops. I love doing improv. I'm Greg Proops and I love doing improv and I love
voicing the guy from the two-headed guy. You're just doing gay voice. Pretty much. It sounds like
this. Greg Proops, no. Yeah he does. I love voicing the pod racing announcer. He did that. No. He did
that. He did that. He ate that up. Seniors 2020, he did that. He did poop racing. Yeah. Yeah,
Yeah, 'cause his last name is Poop.
Greg Poops.
Greg Poops is a K-Hive guy, did you know that?
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
I love Kamala.
Kamala.
Wait, he's one of those ones who says...
I love Kamala.
Kamala.
Kamala Anderson.
Man, shut up.
It's not Kamala.
It's Kamala Malama.
It's Mama Llama.
It's Carl.
Her name is Carl.
It's Carl's Llama.
Yep.
From fucking...
Can I be the president and vice president please?
Yes Carl.
Carl!
Joe Biden, can I be vice president?
I need help being the vice president.
Tell you what, at least Carl would bring, he'd put some cool fucking snacks back in
the vending machines.
That's right.
He'd undo what she did.
Yep.
Yeah.
She lied, we believed.
Or we believed, she lied, they died.
Spev spieved. Spev spieved. Spev spieved.
We believe. Part machine. Oh no.
Yeah. I'm gonna put Fritos back in the vending machine.
Thank you Carl. Thank you for your service.
We're gonna put the purple Doritos in the vending machine at school again.
Which one are the purple Doritos?
The purple ones are the ones where you mix the red and the blue.
Spicy sweet chili.
Purple is if you combine the colors red and blue.
The Chit Saint purple.
Bag is.
Oh what about a blue Dorito?
Whoa.
Don't even say that.
Dude a Gatorade flavored Dorito?
Yeah.
On a blue corn chip.
Blue raspberry Dorito?
Oh my god.
It's got blue raspberry dust.
Don't even get me started.
It'll get stuck all over your fingers.
You're making me lose my mind dude.
I have a blue raspberry Dorito I want to give you.
Is that my valentine Carl?
(imitates screaming)
- Yeah, he would do that too, right?
He would like, when he would scream, he'd be like,
"Jimmy!"
- Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, and he would say he wants to hang out with Jimmy's mom.
- "Jimmy, I'm gonna put a Dorito in your mom's ass."
- Aw, he wouldn't say that, dude.
- Carl, come on.
- He did like his mom, though.
- He loved his mom.
He said, "I'm hearted."
- I mean, his mom was stacked, dude.
I'm gonna fuck your mom. Hey Jimmy I'm gonna fuck your mom in the butt.
No in the butt dude. What the hell he's fucking eight years old. He's three years old dude.
What the hell. Dude he's a baby. No he's a full grown man. He's like thirty years old.
Yeah he hangs out with them cause he can surprise them. He's in Andy Milonakis' situation.
Yeah he's got Andy Milonakis disease that's why he looks like Andy Milonakis. He does.
Yeah. Curly, short. He wears the same glasses. Glasses. Andy Milonakis known for his glasses.
Yeah, well now he is old man. How do you think he's gonna age?
I guess like fine wine. Yeah. Yeah, he's gonna make it to 300. Yeah
I mean, he also doesn't look any different, you know, it's been 20 years or whatever since his show
Yeah, I mean, he's getting some gray hair. Yeah, like that's fine
Yeah, he's gonna be a little he's like 43 an old kid. He's like 43 right now
Have you seen the video the pedophile trying to pick him up? Yeah, pretty good
It's pretty good because he did like the ice Poseidon thing where he would like IRL stream. Yeah, which is so weird, man
Yeah, I don't know why people have you ever seen have you ever seen the video of cheeseburger Andy not being allowed on their party bus?
No
In your mind 2018 I got really into IRL streamers, I don't understand it I got really into their beefs and stuff. Oh, I
I wouldn't watch their streams. I would only watch the videos explaining what was happening.
And there was a guy named Cheeseburger Andy who quit his job to follow them around.
Horrifying.
Yeah.
And he, there's a video of them not letting him onto a party bus.
Damn.
Then he breaks down crying on stream.
Whoa.
He just follows around.
He follows him around.
He also streams?
Yeah, he follows, he watches their streams on one phone.
He stream snipes them.
And then records him.
Yeah, he streams them.
Real life stream snipes.
Yeah, he real life stream snipes.
Dude, that was the craziest phenomenon in 2018.
It didn't do it for a very long time.
Didn't do it for very long because it got banned from Twitch for...
Oh, really?
Yeah, like creating too toxic of a community, I guess.
That's awesome, dude.
It makes sense.
Yeah, dude, fucking that. There was Cheeseburger Andy and there was Asian Andy and both of them
would follow Ice Poseidon around.
Two Andys?
Two Andys that would follow Ice Poseidon around.
And then Asian Andy, like, crashed a quinceanera and played Ram Ranch.
That's pretty cool.
That's pretty funny to watch, but then when you see it in person it's like...
Is his name Asian Andy or are you just calling him that because he's Asian?
No, it's his name. That's his name on YouTube.
I don't believe so.
He used to do Uber drive videos where he would do the text-to-speech over the car speakers
and people would say like, "The man driving your car is a pedophile" and shit like that.
That's actually pretty funny.
Yeah, those are funny to watch. It's just like he got fired from... he can't hold a job now
because of all of his like IRL streaming.
Yeah, I mean that's, that is one thing is like, if, what is the line with like doing dumb shit on the internet where it's like,
"Oh yeah, you just can never get a job." Like have we hit it?
I don't know. I think we might, we might be almost. We're probably pretty close. We're about to be there.
Yeah, we're just, we can't, like if I apply for like a job that isn't food service, that's be like...
Right, yeah, exactly. Nah, sorry man.
Are you the guy that sang that song about Joe Biden?
Yeah, I'll be like, "Nope, no I'm not."
Different guy, he had hair.
Anyway, I've always wanted to be an FBI agent.
(laughing)
- Since I was a little, little kid,
I wanted to join the FBI.
- What do you think the status of that video
is gonna be if he gets elected?
- What do you mean the status of the video?
- Historical relic?
- What do you, do you think they're gonna act upon it?
- Act upon it?
- What are you, they already did.
- You think they're gonna put--
- You think I'm going to jail?
- No, they're gonna put you in a black site.
- Black site?
- What's up?
(laughing)
- The Apollo.
That's what they're putting me.
- Yeah, they're gonna put you on Worldstar.
Yeah.
[Laughter]
Yeah, I'm going on BoxedIn and the Kali.
The forums.
[Laughter]
Ugh.
Oh my god.
I gotta just crack every bone in my body, I think.
And then I'll wake up.
I'll do it, buddy.
I think your cat's trying to fuck the blanket.
Which one is it?
We don't know.
They look exactly the same.
What eye color?
Light green.
That's fucker.
He's not fucking the blanket.
If it was Yoda, if it was Yoda, Yoda is a fucker. He fucks things, but he just needs things.
The fucker's a Yoda.
He needs sex, that's what he needs, with a blanket.
[Laughter]
Look at him, dude, he's horny as a parrot.
No, he's not... yeah, he's needing the blanket, but he's not having sex with the blanket.
This is your fault for getting a blanket full of holes in it, man.
Yeah, he's fucking each hole. He's been working his way through.
I see that shit, I just see options, you know?
[Laughter]
Like last night, I ran out of holes,
and so I turned to Cameron in the bed.
- Yeah, Caleb was trying to stick his foot up in me.
- Caleb was trying to put his foot
in Cameron's mouth last night.
- Dude, I'm a cuddler.
(laughing)
I don't know what to tell you, man.
- Yeah, Cameron, I woke up, I saw Cameron
put a pillow in between you guys.
(laughing)
- If I sleep in the same bed as another person
that is not my wife, I have to actively like,
wake up every hour and scoot further away from them.
'cause my body, I need sex.
(laughing)
- With Cameron.
- I need sex with whoever's in my bed, dude.
I will make it happen if I don't stop myself.
So, a couple times last night.
I had to calm down, I had to go outside and smoke a cigarette.
- He saw the back of Cameron, he saw Cameron's long hair.
- He saw Cameron's long hair and was like,
"Oh, it looks like a man."
- It looks beautiful.
- It's like Fabio, dude.
- Oh my God.
- Yeah, I'm about to turn you the fuck out.
I'm about to grabby-o your fucking--
- You're not gonna have no mercy, Cameron.
Cameron, I'm gonna put my gravy in you, dude.
- Oh man, you're gonna be stuff like a Thanksgiving turkey.
- No, I'm gonna put, I'm--
- With my gravy.
- That's right, dude.
- You're gonna be full of my gravy.
- I'm gonna make you into turd dicken, dude.
- Yeah, oh shit.
- I'm gonna baste you, yeah.
- I'm gonna master baste you, brother.
- That's right.
- I'm gonna make you my puppet.
- I'm gonna squeeze you like toothpaste on my mouth, man.
- I'm gonna make you my puppet, Cameron.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I'm gonna jump on you like a water bottle.
That's right.
I'm gonna make your cap blow off.
Yeah.
I'm gonna blow your cap off.
I'm not gonna respect your pouch.
I tell you what, tonight I'm not respecting your wishes.
Don't say that.
What?
That's not...
I'm saying it to you.
Your wishes will not be respected.
Don't say that.
Why?
Don't do that.
Don't do what?
Man.
We've had a crazy weekend.
Yeah.
We're at the tail. It's funny that nobody's gonna hear this for like weeks. I know we could all be no this is coming out
Wednesday, oh never was coming out of like two days. Oh, nobody will hear this for weeks. No one's gonna know
We're just gonna forget about it. Oh, yeah. Yeah
All right, we could you we could do the list now, right? Yeah, I made up a list. Let's hear it
I forgot the list. Oh, you have to make it up. Okay, just a Ten Commandments. All right, Sam one
the Ten Commandments of Bart
No
Caleb's 10 commandments, let's go. Yeah, Dom Patrick
Patrick's fat
Yeah, okay
Number two
Don't play guitar while I'm trying to give my commandments you fucking bitch. That's number two. What was that?
I don't know what that was. Oh, I need to think of it. No, that was number two
Oh yeah, that don't, don't play guitar or a microphone stand. Stop playing that song.
I hate that song. Number three, um, number three, uh, you, you, uh. I get to cut in line.
That's pretty, right? Dude, if Moses tried to add that to the end of the Ten Commandments,
- Thou shalt not lie.
every Sunday it's called Sunday Sunday yeah every six ice creams I get I get a
seven free yeah yeah and you have to make a special card yeah that's right
you have to punch this stone tablet and I don't have to pay late fees yeah yep
every I keep a copy of Freddy got fingered it's mine mm-hmm yeah it's mine
forever mm-hmm yeah also I get to design a Pokemon on his phone yeah he's looking
it he's you just got a he's about to call my phone Patrick you're the last person
who's allowed to criticize people for going on a phone or a computer during the
blood and I'm allowed to criticize personally I I become Patrick will play
ass hunter flash game for 30 minutes straight and be completely silent on an
episode come dude there's nothing wrong with that yeah sometimes you got a
fucking calm sometimes you got a calm it's gonna best a gravy load oh my god
yeah I'm gonna mist you I'm gonna mist you I'm gonna mist you with my cloud I'm
gonna spray you down with my mist yeah I'm gonna hose you down like a cloud mm-hmm
I'm gonna I'm gonna roll in you like thunder please do so I'm asking you to
do that yeah yeah it's time for me to it's time for me to burst my gravy I'm
yeah you won't burst forth throw my water balloon into you I'm gonna break
my gravy damn I'm a bus dump you up you I'm a bus dump on you I'm a bus dump on you I'm
a bus dump on you I'm a bus dump on you I'm a bus dump on you I'm a bus dump on you I'm
man how's it look like chocolate your rules look like chocolate my rue your
rue I was looking at Cajun your room I love it at those Cajun memes oh yeah
it's like when your partner fought it you your partner fought it what's the
other way it was like something about I don't know it's like what I call a
crawdad a prown.
It's so good.
They like write them out.
They like phonetically spell the accent.
Oh, like the Scottish Twitter thing?
It says like when ya and then like podner, like P-O-D-N-E-R and then F-O-D-D-E-D instead
of farted.
When ya podna farted.
It's like the stress one, right?
Yeah.
It's like the what stresses out a Cajun.
Oh yeah, it's like a stress headache diagram and like different thing.
like different thing yeah and it's like different arrows are yeah like when they
call crawdad a prawn when you're potna fodded yeah it'd be so funny to just like
it would be awesome to be Cajun to pretend to be Cajun it's so easy yeah
yeah just go down there's good in Louisiana you are a seersucker suit you
walk around the people go oh my god Cajun people don't wear suits man
is not a good story you know the band uh...
i'm a good job and i'm a good idea but i'm a little more about you know you
my body you know the band uh... acid bath in your listen to them
and they uh... they're from there from the by you and the singer
uh... ever like every video of a live show he always has his hand in his pants
on his dick to the entire so i think i think that he's on the couch he does has
a hand like in his pocket holding his dick well yeah screams
respected it's dope to pull that's a big deal
you know i'm not being a woman
no go get a new how are you going to go to the get a little bit of a political
yet again
my brother my lovely let me pull
let me pour a whole gallon of gas
I got go home depot
I got go home depot get big strew I go I go get some wood on the car
now where you get that from?
Come on, let me see the car with the daisy on.
Come on, how 'bout that?
Come on, get pretty hot out there in the bayou.
Let me see your car.
- Where'd you get your tools from, HD Supply?
(laughing)
- Man, I'm 'bout to go back to Circus City.
- I need a HDMI cable.
- I gotta go to Circus City, call Zero Recall.
- Oh man, I gotta--
- I'm building a tool bed for my record setup.
- I gotta plug in my Xbox.
- I gotta get my Xbox.
- I gotta surround sound.
- I gotta Xbox game.
- Got 10.1 surround sound.
- I got Dolby Digital.
Dolby Digital.
- Dolby Digital.
I'm Dobe Digital.
I'm the mayor of this hilltown right here.
I'm the go-no.
I'm the go-no Louieanna.
My name Dobe Digital.
My name is Dish D'Souza.
My name Dobe.
My name Dish D'Souza.
I'm Chiquita Bananas.
I thought we were talking about frog legs.
Frog legs.
I'm Chiquita Bananas.
bananas. I thought we were talking about frog legs. My name's LeapPad. My name's LeapFrog RibbitPad. My name's Mario. Lenovo ThinkPad. My name's Lenovo.
I'm from this hole right here.
Look I heard your mama make gumbo in a crock pot.
I crawled out of this little swamp right there.
Nah I came out, I'll ride an alligator like it's a car.
I drive, put a steering wheel on my alligator, I'll ride it out on the way home.
I'll ride that alligator all the way to the capitol building.
You wanna play leapfrog?
Hey man, you wanna go...
You wanna play some leapfrog?
Come on.
Hey get on your knees.
Get your knees on.
Get your knees on man.
We jump on each other.
A couple of leapfrogs.
We can play leapfrog for one hour.
I really only got an hour.
I gotta get an HR block man.
I'm working on taxes.
Watch out for the creature.
Watch out for my cousin.
He a monster.
He a monster in this one.
You better watch out for my cousin.
Oh you better look out for my cousin.
Man, he got slime for eyes bro. You don't wanna mess with him no more.
He got a catfish for a leg.
He sticks to the window like a frog.
He got us a great time.
Yeah, he got those sticky hands from the dentist's office.
And if you ain't careful, he'll charm you too.
Look out of the woods.
You ain't a man, man that man.
He gonna give you a single red rose.
Yeah, he gonna make you pregnant.
There's a predator in the woods.
It's a predator though.
He can see you from the camera. He got camouflage on.
He got a camouflage jacket.
He turned invisible.
He used to be in the army.
I used to be General Lenovo, think Pat Motorola.
Now I'm a simple man, running Circus City.
I just sit here with my overalls, I get sunburned every day.
Yeah man, I mean, I go Costco, save money.
I already like Mario.
I mean, I go buy both.
You know what I'm saying? I buy both, go Costco, save money.
Look my fan- I gotta-
I'm buying artichoke hoes- I'm buying artichoke hearts by the fucking-
-palette.
A condo flew into my fan boat.
[laughter]
Now the propeller don't work.
I put a fan on my bike.
All my vehicles gotta be a fan on the back.
I got a Tesla, put a fan on it, motherfucker.
[laughter]
I went swimming, I found Bikini Bottom.
Bikini Bottom actually in the bayou.
Yo, yeah, you wanna watch out.
There's a man, yeah.
I mean, there's good folk down there.
You guys punch bars with Patrick,
but there's some nasty little motherfuckers too.
You got Plankton.
Plankton, Plankton.
He, man, he ain't nothing.
He a troublemaker.
Man, I dropped a bucket in there,
he turned that bucket into his house.
Man, he made a house slash restaurant.
He made a house and a restaurant out of my bucket,
and I want my bucket back.
man bikini bottom man god damn see that big c-shirt he's my partner
spongebob patchwork they're my partners square world he kind of grumpy
plantin that's he got the devil in him boy
plantin done got the devil in that boy
uh oh i'm from minnesota
from Lansing. I moved to the Bayou when I was 38. I'm from Bakersfield, California. That's some real shit man. When I was 38.
Yeah. I've only been living here six months. Yeah, I'm studying abroad.
I'm from Edinburgh. I came here studying abroad. Right. You know.
she left me and then she left and then my mama left me I'm eight years old man I'm
eight years old I'm for the UK all right what time we do the list nah dude do this
forever yeah okay top ten creepiest guys top ten creepiest guys number one
Nicholas Cruz yep hard agree he does he has Marfan syndrome right he has to look
at his ears man yeah I know it's like you're looking into a mirror no no I'm
not Cuban yeah it's true you wish that'd be cool dude if I was Cuban yeah it'd be
sick Nicholas Cruz not much to say about
Nicholas Cruz there's no real good jokes about no they've all been said yeah I
mean it's just you know it's tired at this point yeah everybody's everybody
has a Nicholas Cruz joke yeah yeah it's just annoying yeah I will say Tom
Cruz come collect your son yep come get him definitely the least my least
favorite of the Cruz family yeah you know if it's if it's him versus Penelope
I'm fucking Penelope yep you know he's not that high he sucks
nah Nicholas Cruz your basic you're the sucka of the week yeah yeah
Nicholas Cruz you suck and you're the sucka sucka of the week and and by the
way we haven't read the rest of this list but we're sure we're giving this to
Nicholas Cruz he's the suck of the week yep nobody else on this list is gonna be
a sucker number two is Adam Lanza oh shit Adam Lanza you look like bug haul
he looks like alfalfa it's funny that they just used that picture of him yeah
it's just like him it looks I mean I I'd let him kill me in that photo you know
It's cute. Yeah. No, I wouldn't let him kill me. Oh, he looks like a nerd. I'd bully him
You'd be responsible then
Hindsight is 20/20
Number three Steven Paddock Steven fat fan favorite
Yeah, definitely I would say like the fourth the fourth mic
Mm-hmm, right? Yeah, definitely gets a lot of airtime on this show
Yeah, I mean we don't mean to you know he was CIA. Yeah
It's another example
Cool and cool in all ways
That's God yeah, that's right. God is cool in all ways
That's it, but that was when you know James Aldean when he was seeing bullets fucking rain down from heaven Jason Aldean
Jason Aldean whatever who was it was Steven Steven Paddock accidentally checking into the hotel for dogs
Yeah it's Jason Aldean right? God that fucking that video of his brother I haven't
seen that. You love videos of people's brother? No I just said I haven't seen it.
It's the one where he's like a thousand dollars worth of sushi comped. What's he
talking about? His brother I don't know it's the interview of his brother it's
like Eric Paddock being interviewed about his brother. And he just says a
a thousand dollars worth of sushi. Yeah.
Comped. Uh-huh.
Whoa. It's crazy.
Dude, he must have, it must be tough living in his brother's shadow, having a famous brother.
Yeah. Yeah, you might want to watch out for that guy next. Yeah. But what I was saying
is Jason Aldean definitely like what he was thinking when he's seeing bullets rain down
from heaven and just destroy everybody who loves him most, right? All over this, all
All these fans right who are singing along to his songs just seeing their brains splattered all over the concrete. He was just like
That guy's gotta be a real creep up there
That's a creepy guy up there. Oh, what a creep. Oh my god. What a creep
You were the creep. Hey Steven Paddock. Hi there Steven Paddock. You're the freak of the week. Hey Steven
You're creeping me out. Stop it. You're creep and you're not coming to my next concert
What if he was just you know what if he just didn't like the music and that's why he did it?
Cuz I'm a creep like Stephen Paddock liked everything but rap and country and then he saw there was a country concert
And he said well
He's just a not in my backyard he's an NIMBY. Yeah, yeah, yeah
And his backyard was the Las Vegas trip. Yeah, yeah, I mean
behind your window do you think Jason Aldean has did he like write a new song
about that probably he had to have right probably I'm sorry that my concert made
this happen didn't mean to make it happen to you people in the audience is
crying it's so beautiful yeah waving the light because it's a why it's like a
a like it's a country song after like 2000 so yeah it's like we're gonna get
the beers and the grill and go down to the lake and I'm sorry Stephen Paddock
shot up my concert yeah no it's like yeah when you were at the concert I was
looking at you you were wearing stuff from Walmart yeah where that - hey you
was shooting down but I didn't notice cuz you were so beautiful now let's get some
blood let's go take it to the porta potty he's have said raining down with the
giant shoddy sex in the porta potties while the shooting was happening and
didn't know what was going on yeah it was me and your mom yeah yeah can I'm
You're here.
Treboholics.
Real trashy.
They heard the gunshots outside and they're like, "Damn, you are coming so loud today."
The shooting come out with a gunshot noise.
Imagine how powerful.
How are you shooting without having to reload?
You're calm.
It's almost like you.
Imagine how powerful you would have felt if at that exact moment.
To be in that hotel room.
God.
No.
Come on.
Bad guy.
Yeah, naughty pilot. I'm so sorry that my concert got shot up, but you here's a discount code
Naughty man
Discount code for zappos calm if you were
Number four Marilyn Manson, yeah
Man, do you think these were all added in like well, it's Stephen Paddock happened after Nicholas Cruz, right?
Yeah, okay. Never mind that I was gonna say
Do you think I don't know maybe think they updated the same every like shooting happened?
maybe like Adam Lanza was number one for a little bit and then
Marilyn Manson the rest of the list and then Nicholas Cruz went up and then like the rest of the list and
They had Nicholas Cruz on the list before he did the shooting
Yeah, now these are like power rankings they can change
Number four Marilyn Manson. Yeah, I mean pretty creepy Marilyn Manson says the first first creepy person on this list
one of the I read an interview with
Corey Taylor the lead singer of Slipknot. Yeah, where um, he was talking about how he was hanging out with Marilyn Manson and
They had a gross-out contest and
Which is already so funny
But like Corey Taylor like made himself throw up and then ate it or something like that and then Marilyn Manson
Danced in his underwear and Marilyn Manson won the band voted that it was grosser
Marilyn Manson dance I was a Marilyn Manson. I mean that'll
If anybody has ever confused me sexually it was Marilyn. Yeah, you know he's releasing his new album on 9/11
Badass pretty sick. That's what's it called. I don't remember 11 was good
Are you scared of me? 9/11 was a good thing. Yeah. 9/11 was good to me. Oh, does that shock you? Yeah. Yeah. Sorry. Am I weird?
Sorry, am I weird for thinking that? Am I being weird for saying 9/11 was cool?
I'm giving a voice to all the kids who think 9/11 is cool.
Yeah. Didn't he say the n-word? Like hard r? He said hard r n-word in like the first song on his second album.
Irresponsible hate anthem. That's like the first line of the chorus, man.
He says every buddy is someone else's hard r n-word. John Lennon made people think they could do that. Yeah.
And George Carlin, you know and Louis CK. Yeah. Yeah. He also in that song. He also says I rape the raper
That's also part of that's heroic
You know
Yeah, he was really he really was dry. He was that song
He was just trying to get it all out in the first song
Then he could go back to just making creepy music about vampires and then the yeah that the second song in that
Album is just called like is about beautiful people
Number five is Michael Jackson.
Do you think Michael Jackson...
Imagine hearing that coming out from under your bed at night.
Did Marilyn Manson get the idea to be white from Michael Jackson?
Yeah, he was like I'm gonna be white.
I'm gonna do a white skin thing with me.
What does he sound like again?
My name Michael Jackson.
I'm mean daddy.
Know if we could do that voice
Michael Jackson
Not creepy to me. No. No really you support what he did the children. Yeah. Yeah, if I was a kid
I'd be creepy. I think he did that shit. Do I think he did it?
Sure, why not? Let's let's go over the facts. Let's go over the facts here facts fact
There was a newgrounds animation that made it seem like he probably did it. Uh-huh. Yeah
Yeah, and it also insinuates that Macaulay Culkin was gay
Yeah
It was a joke in a joke book that said what's the difference between Michael Jackson and a grocery bag and it's about it's
Plastic and you can't let it around children and the other one is a grocery bag
And then jokes that tell the most truth jokes. That's right number two fact jokes are facts
Yep. Number three. He'd be dancing. He'd be dancing kind of gay. Dancing kind of like a
gay guy. So you know. I mean we'll leave that one up to the fans. I mean think about it man. He did
a dance move where he literally he leaned he did not stand up straight. Straight. He did not stand
straight. Oh my god he's telling the world. Yep. He was telling the world I'm not straight I'm a
a pedophile. Well he was saying he was saying he'd and also the moonwalk yeah
yeah exactly you know who walked on the moon? A pedophile. Stanley Kubrick yeah
the guy who invented lolita. Also pedophile the whole the moon the whole thing is that
everything's reversed gravity is reverse and having sex is reverse you do it with
kids on the moon that's why he went to the moon. That's why Michael Jackson went
to the moon. That's why he went to the moon. It's true. He trained on the moon to do the moonwalk
and he's like I guess while I'm here yeah I should try some of the local that's a
Patrick yeah France no I did never been to France and I would never would go you
would go no wouldn't you were from France you would take me on the no I would take
you on our honeymoon I'd make you eat a snail I'm gonna get married to you and
put feed you my slug number six Osama bin Laden I'd say I'm gonna freak on a
leash man. His son is creepier than him. His son looks cool what are you talking about?
But I'm saying like his son like he's got the creepy aesthetic going you know.
Osama Bin Laden's pretty creepy now he's a bunch of skeletons in the ocean.
He's a bunch of bones in the ocean. He's a water ghost.
Water skeleton dude. Oh my god he's that was him in Pirates of the Caribbean.
Yeah he's Davy Jones. That was him and his friends dude. Osama Bin Laden's locker
filled with anime DVDs I've got 600 DVDs of Tom and Jerry sealed in this chest
and the key is stuck in my heart I'm gonna send you to Osama bin Laden's hard drive
at the bottom of the ocean Cameron you dropped something yeah your freaking
dignity yeah yeah what was that you dropped your penis no Patrick dropped
something back here I think all right don't even worry about it Pat I came
thought his balls dropped for the first time. Yeah we saw a guy the other day a
guy pulled up next to we were going oh yeah a guy a guy pulled up in his car
next to us and rolled the window down said hey man you dropped your nut and
then drove 10 feet forward and stopped at the traffic light and then we were
like four minutes we like I just stood there and scared him. And then he went "hahahahaha"
It was awesome. Such a good one. You dropped your nut. Hey man, don't look now. You dropped your nut.
Don't look now, you dropped your nut. You dropped your nut. What are you talking about dude? I thought that he was talking about
like your skateboard for a minute. Yeah yeah. And then I was like oh I've been fooled.
I've been pranked. He got as he drove up and he went "hey you dropped your nut!"
yeah that's what he did yeah we just said he was like he was gonna just say it
slurred what slur could you call us if friends you guys are friends hey you guys
are friends we got out yeah number seven the clock over Barack Obama go Oh
- Albraco Brimbro.
- Bedobobaba.
- Albra--
- My name Barack Obama.
(laughing)
- I'm Barack Obama.
- I'm Baracko Bayou.
- Bebo Baba.
- Bebo Bebo?
- Bebo Obama.
- Bongo Bidongo.
- Bidobo--
- Bidowakawakawakawookie.
- Bidobanana.
- Yeah, we're doing Minions talk
for the rest of the episode.
- Bidder.
- Bidodobidy.
- Hello.
- Hmm, Bidodobidy?
number one number like number one number nine is like a banana Stephen Paddock
bababoo dee dee yeah you know Stephen Paddock had just minions up there oh my
god everybody shot somebody call the ambulance
beedle beedle beedle beedle beedle see the minions followed him because he was
pure evil yes well that's if you see in the beginning of the minions movie yeah
yeah it's their whole thing is they move from evil person to evil person and then
they like they like in canon they're like yeah they're actually trapped in an
iceberg for the 40s yeah that's like something that's really yeah we weren't
Hitler's oh my god that's so good that is so that is actually that is great
right yeah they like a trap in an iceberg for like a hundred years
something yeah cuz it's like it's funny and it's like the right thing to do yeah
Because you shouldn't just not talk about it. You can't set the precedent of like yeah
they follow every man who's very evil yeah and then be like well we're not
gonna talk about it. You can infer. Trust me they would have loved to be doing the
Holocaust but unfortunately they were trapped in ice. They got stuck in the
freezer. In the fridge dude. Number eight Charles, Charles Ransom. Charles Manson
Marilyn Manson's dad. Yeah.
He took up the family business, Marilyn Manson, making music for creepy people.
I saw a documentary on this freak and it gave me nightmares.
Wow.
Do you guys think he was MKUltra?
Charles Manson?
I want to read that book.
That uh, you know that book?
Yeah, MKUltra.
Yeah.
Charles Manson book.
I'm gonna order it on Amazon, I think.
I think Charles Manson was just a great musician and I think people took everything he said
out of context.
I agree.
Including the people who killed for him.
yeah yeah they didn't realize he was being sarcastic he was being ironic dude
yeah irony he was like yeah dude I would totally love if you killed Roman
Polanski's wife. Oh I would love it if you guys started a race war. Yeah you guys should
totally do that yeah totally yeah hey guys look I'm pretending to be a guy
would have a swastika on his forehead look how funny this is right yeah I think
he's actually a jerk no he sucks yeah he sucks dude yeah you're a grade-A ninny
Charles Manson. Whoa. Charles Manson, you could suck my prick. Oh my god. Yeah, you could suck an egg.
All right, go jump in a lake Charles Manson. Go boil an egg Charles Manson. Yeah, go eat a boiled-
Hey, go take a hike. Go eat a hard-boiled egg.
Yeah. Bitch. Hey, go to jail. Go directly to jail. Go stay in jail. That would be so embarrassing to be playing.
You're a certified doofus, my friends. It'd be embarrassing to be playing Monopoly with Charles Manson, and then you're like, okay Charles and go directly-
Oh, I'm sorry. Oh. Oh.
Go directly to jail. Oh
I'm sorry, Charlie
How would he be MK ultra though?
Well, the I think the theory is that not really that he was MK ultra
But that basically like the the guy who the guy prosecuted him was like was MK ultra
No, he was trying to ultra speeds. He
Basically framed the whole story so that he could write like a crazy book about it
So he framed like all the like Helter Skelter race war stuff there's like
almost no evidence that that was what he wanted to do. He's just kind of a crazy
guy that some people think like everything was pinned on. Okay. Yeah so
pretty neat. You think there was like a plan that the government had and then
that he was a patsy? I think the government had a plan. Yeah the
government always has a plan. They always have a plan. This was also, this was in 1969 right? Yeah. Yeah so it's
like yeah this was the peak of like the government suspicion of counterculture
you know like this was that was when the government was not too happy about
hippies yeah you know so they would have done anything to put an end to it yeah
fucking kill they weren't killing showers I'll suck and wife like who
cares yeah you know well he wasn't a pedophile until his wife he was driven
to pedophilia he was driven to pedophilia yeah secretly though she was
murder and he was like yes mm-hmm swag swagged out swag dude number nine is
Ozzy Osbourne don't know him this guy ate a freaking bat first comment is from
Mozilla and it says his BFF is satin and he ate a bat this guy can't function in
society I mean crazy train seems to me this guy's a crazy brain crazy train that
It seems- is that his car?
Is that what he drives?
*singing*
That is kinda how he sounds
Yeah
He literally just speaks gibberish now
*singing*
There's still crap in my pants.
There's a crap in my pants.
There's some crap in the toilet.
Someone put a bat in the toilet.
I gotta eat a bat in the toilet.
Oh, the bat in the toilet.
It will make me fade into sandwich.
What's his wife's name?
Sharon.
Sharon, you gonna get me a bat in the fucking...
Yeah.
I ain't coronavirus.
I'll get everything on the ground.
Freaking Ozzy Osbourne started coronavirus when he ate the bat, dude.
Let's go!
Change his name to freaking COVID Osborne.
That's a crazy claim.
(Laughter)
(Singing)
He ate the bat!
Finished with my bat because I'm not hungry anymore.
(Singing)
Somebody gave me
Something to wash it down.
Like Sprite!
He loves Sprite.
"Finished with my Pepsi, now I want to drink a lemonade"
Ozzy Osbourne is such a fucking freak on the leash dude, or freak off the leash rather,
that he drinks instead of Sprite he might drink a soda called Spite.
That's right. He would drink, instead of Pepsi, he would drink something called Evil Pepsi.
Yeah, Dark Pepsi.
Instead of Coke he would drink, well he would do Coke.
He would drink Bloke because he's British.
yeah I look a blow look oh you got blood yeah look a blow blow blow blow blow
blow blow blow blow blow they go Ozzie didn't he have it with a bloke and no
love remember that his reality show every love dog shit yeah it's so Jason
deal was on an episode I remember that you were on an episode yeah I have no
one who craps on the floor and blaze Simmons family jewels was the better one
of those the best one is just him going on you see I'm hungry I'm so hungry right
now I'm hungry and I need to I need to talk to women we please oh god it's so
dirty in here oh Jesus Christ someone clean the house you seen um the the
documentary show that was on I forget what it's called but kiss restarted
arena football and then they bought kiss bought the LA arena football team and
called it the LA Kiss.
- Sick.
- And all their uniforms were Kiss themed and stuff.
- It's funny that Kiss's thing in the 80s was like,
yeah, we're the devil.
Now it's just like, yeah,
I wanna eat cheeseburgers and invade Iraq.
- Right, yeah.
- Yeah, so sick.
- They're like, well, their whole thing now
is just that they have the most merchandise,
like the Kiss Army merchandise is like,
like they have watches and wall clocks and shit.
- Yeah.
- It's like how Bamar-Jarrah makes rings now, right?
- Yeah, exactly.
- Sick.
- Yeah.
were they were they into the devil was that a thing?
they weren't actually.
but people that's so funny like they like they go around like yeah we're gonna lick
everybody and put hearts on our face yeah I mean it was just cuz of like the
face paint and like the fake blood.
yeah the face paint is like they're like what if I put a star over my eye
this guy's into the devil.
oh my god these people are evil oh my god his base is shaped like an axe
the band the band's literally called Kiss guys I don't think they're evil I think
they're lovely there the S's in the kiss logo are the SS we should just see we
should go see guar dude oh glory be off the dive them for 50 year old guys turn
soup on you the middle lead guar guy died a few years ago
unrest on Garis or missing yeah Bungo Bungo Bungo Bungo I love bands that just
like make shitty music but are fun to see yeah yeah yeah that's masked bands
are absolutely the best because especially because there's so many
- What's the name of the city?
like local bands and shit from random places you have like 10 listeners and
like looking up their music videos on youtube
i found some really funny shit dude yeah it's great dude there yeah
there's one there was one band where like they all wore like a bunch of them
like were wearing like scarecrow masks and like scary gory stuff
and then one guy was just wearing um a fedora with like a robot mask
yeah dude but i mean it's fucking no no it wasn't even a robot dude it was a
fucking vendetta mask in a fedora like straight it was
Damn.
Concentrate 10 minutes quick, run into Party City and just do something, man.
Just get something.
Come on.
We all made our masks at home.
What the fuck did you do?
I was playing CSGO.
Yeah, I got a...
I was actually reading this book called V for Vendetta.
I got a Jason mask, I got a hockey mask.
Well, that's pretty cool.
Yeah, hockey mask is...
We'll take it.
Hockey mask still looks pretty scary.
Can you put some blood and poop on it?
Can you smear poop on your hockey mask?
Yeah.
I wish that hockey, that was what they did instead of fighting.
They just threw poop like monkeys.
Yeah, they'd have to call it "monkey."
Is it a monkey?
I think you might be right.
They might have to call it "monkey."
Yeah, that's a really good point.
It's true.
Alright, number 10. Oh no, wow, way to round out the list.
Number 10, it's our man Tom Cruise.
Tom Cruise, Nicholas Cruz's dad.
Yeah.
I don't really get what's creepy about him.
He does his own stunts, is that creepy?
Is he a hero? Scientology.
Scientology. Oh yeah, I forgot about that. Yeah. Do you guys think Scientology kills people?
He says he does his own stunts but he's got enough Scientology energy in him that if he
hits the ground he just bounces back. He flips up into the air. Yeah, it's like when Neo
falls off the building in Matrix and he just bounces back up. Yeah. Yeah, it's just like
that. That video where he breaks his ankle is pretty cool. Tom Cruise. Yeah, just watching
hurt yeah just seeing that man is seeing it makes me just feels good to me
Homer does his own stunts this is this is my Marge impression I don't know who it
was it might have been sir but somebody posted something about how like in the
current Simpsons canon was 919 when 9/11 happened yeah that is so funny dude yeah
it's a funny shit ever oh that was Foley it's Foley yeah I don't remember who it
was yeah that's how is that Homer was 19 I don't I don't watch new
Simpsons buddy 2001 plus I don't even watch new the news then would make him
new than anything. 38? Yeah gotta be 38. He says he's 36 in season 4 I know
that cuz I just watched it. That would make him like 60 years old right now.
Yeah. They should just do one the final season of The Simpsons where they just
just do a movie every two every three years. Yeah. The Simpsons. Cuz The Simpsons
movie is great. Here's my idea. So the final episode. I'm sure if they made another movie right now
another Simpsons movie would be awesome. I mean the show sucked when the first
movie came out. It's true. It would definitely be good because they
spend a lot of time on it. It wouldn't be about Trump or whatever. It would though is
what I'm saying. It definitely would. I mean they did a ton of like dumbass
Bush stuff. They will be about. No. Yes. Final season of The Simpsons this is my
idea. Every episode is one is they all have the same birthday and every episode
they get older by two years okay well it's gonna be like a 26 episode season
or something or final episode final season of Simpsons is just Homer takes a
picture every day for 10 years yep yep right we just see no dialogue no
dialogue it's just plays it plays an Imagine Dragons song behind it yeah
that's something that would be yeah you get to watch that yeah sounds pretty
- Yeah. - You're getting good, right?
- Mm-hmm.
All right.
- All right, time to take a crap.
- Yeah, no, I get to take a crap.
- You can go first.
- Okay, it's my house, I better.
- I'm gonna go first now, 'cause you said that.
- You don't crap first!
- All right, bye everybody.
Subscribe to the Papeyon.
- Bye-bye.