you're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Crap monster.
I'm smarter. We're thinking of doing an episode where we read a list and just
kind of laugh at it and make fun of it. Yeah, we're kind of just gonna make fun of the list today.
We think we're done giving the list the spotlight. It's less of like a celebration of lists and
more of like a savage roast.
- A take down.
- A savage roast like Conan the Barbarian
would do to a list.
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna do a sort of, yeah,
we're gonna do sort of a New York Mag style
like Donald Trump take down on this list.
- Yeah, kind of like a brutal barbaric kind of berserker
wearing wolf skin kind of roast on the list, you know?
- Yeah, we're kind of just gonna do
the most insane crap we can.
- Yeah.
- We've been thinking,
I think we're due for an insane episode.
- Yeah, I think we're gonna do an insane one today.
- You know?
- Yeah.
crank crank the weird meter up we're on we're on because we're on the freak bus
so and the destination is your your house your ears we're not stopping for
anybody weirdness is about to ensue in this a
cerbic journey through through the Internet's weirdest lists we're thinking
of being a cerbic this episode so if you're we're thinking of having nobody
be safe from our caustic wit with victims including cancel culture lists and dracula the vampire.
I had to come out, this was really hard, I actually did, I had to come out to my parents
as sarcastic.
It was hard.
Yeah, you're like mom, dad, I'm not sarcastic.
Yeah I'm totally not sarcastic.
i came out as irony poisoned yet to come out of my employer
it
and i'm like
just so you know i'm very racist online to make you laugh
just so you know i'm actually grill killed
and manager
yet that's right
yes it's a cool things like i was not around here
we don't take a lead a grill bill you better get the hell out of my gas
station soon
So you're one of them.
This is Texas and I'm about to stand my ground.
I love stand your ground, Luz.
I just love standing my ground.
So you're one of them irony bros I hear so much about.
You'd best keep moving.
Yeah, this ain't no town for you.
I am trapped in my apartment because Janna wanted to paint our tile floor and our tile
floor is the entirety of the hallway that leads to the front door.
You have to go out through the fire escape.
I don't have a fire escape.
You have to climb out the window.
I have no way to get out.
The paint takes 30 hours to dry.
You should have done that.
I can't even go in my kitchen and to get to my bathroom I have to jump over like a hallway
full of paint, like a moat.
You should just put footprints on it and make it your home.
Make it like a...
That could be a cool kind of look.
Yeah, it would look cool.
Yeah.
Put handprints and stuff.
Yeah, write your name.
And maybe put some on the ceiling so people get kind of scared when they come in.
We could go...
Me and Cameron could come to New York and we could put our...
You could put more paint on the floor and we could put our hands in like the Chinese
theater.
The Walk of Fame.
Oh yeah, like Grauman's Chinese Theater.
yeah dominic chinese theater
yeah
it's so funny that that guy's name dominic
kianese chinese yes dominican chinese
is he a soprano? that's junior
that's like the deftone singer's name chino merino
which is which is spanish for brown chinese
that's a cool name
brown chinese is kind of another cool name
Chinese brown.
Isn't that just black China?
Bad Chinese brown.
Baddest man in the whole damn town.
Mm-hmm.
Badder than a junkyard dog, more Chinese.
Yeah, Chinese-est man in the whole damn town.
So I'm just, you know, I'm just stuck inside.
Just gonna watch TV a lot.
Been watching this, uh, this like
interior design reality show.
Yeah.
been watching that and Rick and Morty and so I'm watching the interior design
reality show last night. Jana was watching that and I was like not even
paying attention but there was a guy, they had like a guest judge who was, it's a
British show, they had this guest judge who's this interior designer who's
just exactly Austin Powers. I swear to fucking God, dude, go watch this. It's the seventh episode of whatever the
Interior Design Netflix original is this guy that it she introduces him she's
like he's a he's a superstar interior designer from all over the world and
then he's from all over the world he's from all over the world and then doing
like a talking head and he's like interior design is really about seduction
the entire episode he's like walking into all these rooms of these people of
decorating he's like something about this is so naughty like couches and shit they
walk into the barbershop that the lady like redoes and he's like does this make
you horny is it just me he's wearing like a big he's wearing like a pink tuxedo
yeah this guy in the world that's like one in every ten people and in England
England yeah types of people in the world for all over the world like a kid
is
a little bit in the future but not super in the future and he has an evil is a
mean phone. What are you talking about? Like he has like a phone that's like
hurting his life. What joke are you trying to make here? I'm not. It's no it's
a type of British guy. It's a kind of British guy. Yeah. And then you have
Sherlock Holmes. Yeah. You have Watson. And and then tenth person. Interior design
Austin Powers. Yeah, Austin Powers guy. Well, hold on. There might be more than this now
that I think about it. You have Austin Powers. You can't leave Austin Powers off of that list.
I think Watson is a Sherlock Holmes type. No, Watson is not anything like Sherlock Holmes,
you idiot. No, he is. You idiot, he knows. They're completely different. What are you
talking about, dude? They're the same archetype. They have different stats. No, no, no. Yes,
No different stats. They don't they have different sets. They're not the same archetype. They're the same class
Dr. Watson is a is a doctor. Okay, would you go to the doctor and say I need a crime solved?
Would you go to a detective and say I need surgery you would die
Both of those cases because neither of them would know how to do the job right either the same class with different stats
They're different. He just raised his doctor stat. That's not they're both detectives. That's not they're not detectives
No, a doctor is a kind of detective.
No.
Yeah, because he detects what's wrong with you.
Yeah, he puts that finger in your thing.
In your thing.
He puts his finger in your thing.
I think you guys are not going to doctors.
Ah, a mystery!
I found a clue!
Ah, the clue is prostate cancer.
Yeah.
There's a clue in your ass.
No, you guys are wrong.
You guys are wrong.
No, we're right.
There's more kinds of British people.
There isn't.
isn't. You could give me a British person, they fall into any one of those categories.
Rapper. British rapper. No, give me a person. Mr. Bean. Exactly. Mr. Bean. Mr. Bean is a
Sherlock Holmes type character. Yeah, because he's discovering the world. Yeah, that's true.
He's able to, using his childlike innocence. How about a witch? That's not a British type
of person. A witch is from Salem. No, that's from magic. That's from Salem. Shut up. That's
from Salem or from Wonderland's or not one Dorothy yeah they're from Australia
yeah which is there from Australia oh my god I just got the worst text in my
entire life what I forgot that I was supposed to have groceries delivered
today and I can't I'm painted out of my front door when are they being like
right now? It just got delivered. Oh my fucking god. They're just gonna be rotting foods.
No, it's just gonna get stolen. Nobody steals, nobody wants to steal like, it's all like,
it's like potato and milk. If I saw groceries, I'd steal groceries. What would you steal off
the street? Because I've stolen, like I would not steal like a bike tire, but any Amazon package I
I will steal. I stole, um, I went to,
I went to Kendall square to see the fireworks two years ago.
I got really fucked up. I, it was like the first time I was hanging out with like,
a high school friend for a while and we just,
I didn't realize how strong the gin and tonics we were making.
And I got real fucked up. My friend was,
I got real fucked up and I stole, uh, one of those big cheese,
cheese ball things from a family.
while we were all walking I just looked down looked at it picked it up they
didn't open it I looked at it picked it up and then just kept offering people
cheese balls as I was walking around. So when you took it, it was at their house?
No it was on the ground in Kendall Square. Why was it? While there was a family
sitting on the grass and I ran by and scooped him up and ran away. When I was
when I was stuck in the Dallas Airport a couple weeks ago I I found some trail mix
on the ground I just ate that nice there was a trail of trail mix leading into
the bathroom and you follow it's called trail mix yeah it might have been it
yeah it might have been an anthill but I think about it yeah because the Texas
the Texas Airport they they have it Alamo themed so there's a lot of sand
outside yeah this tumbleweed uh-huh that rolls by instead of the like normal
airport zamboni yeah yeah yeah um man i've watched i've watched freddy got
fingered like three times now you're about to watch cameron get fingered
you're not about to watch that you you watched it twice yesterday
yeah no you didn't you're lying i did i well technically
i watched it three once you say technically i know that you're
- I watched it.
- That means, that technically is what people say
when they're wrong.
- Yeah.
- I watched it at 3 a.m. and fell asleep,
and then woke up and then watched it again
at like midnight last night.
- And so that's two times.
- Okay, wow, that is technical.
- So, yesterday, that is a technical two times yesterday.
- You said you watched it three times though.
- Yeah, I watched it the day before yesterday.
- No, you didn't.
- Checkmate.
- No, you did not.
- You just got, you just got fucking owned,
Cameron got rolled, brother.
- You didn't.
I know that you didn't.
Cam's got to retire.
I know that you did not watch it three times.
Because when you were watching it last night, you said, "This is the second time that I've
watched this."
Cameron, you're fired.
Yep, you're fired.
You're fucking fired.
You're off the podcast, buddy.
And the podcast is over.
No.
Yeah, I can turn off the audio recorder right now.
No, me and Pat are doing a new podcast.
Yeah.
It's called Talking Cameron.
It's called The Prince and the Peanut.
I'm Peanut. He's Peanut. I'm the Prince of Comedy. And he's the Peanut. I'm the Peanut M&M.
Yeah, and then you could, I mean I guess you could guest on it sometimes. Yeah, you could be the guest.
I don't know, we'll have to talk to Prince and the Peanut and the guest. I don't really want to guest with someone who is like an insane liar that led to me getting kicked off my own podcast that I invented.
who literally lied about the number of times that he watched Freddy got fingered in the past few days.
We actually don't know who lied here.
I can pull up the messages right now where Patrick said he watched it twice.
He said it in a group chat.
I did watch it twice.
Patrick just admitted his lie.
If we can run it back.
He came so hard.
I wasn't going to pull those receipts up.
I'm not picking a side here.
this is a if this is a war I just call me Japan cuz I'm not involved okay choose
your you choose your hills to die on and if losing if losing my good friend
Cameron over over Cameron lying would what did I like the show you like you
you're lying right now that was a question you can't lie yeah that
Question is a lie.
I feel like I'm on crossfire.
This is incredible.
That's what they do.
Actually, the question is a lie.
Yeah, I don't know if I watched it three times.
It's all been a blur.
Yeah, you watched the whole blur.
This whole week has been a blur for me.
I don't know what's going on.
I've watched eight movies in the past two days.
I'm going insane, dude.
I don't believe you, but go on.
- This whole week has been a blur for me.
I don't know what's going on.
- I've watched eight movies in the past two days.
I'm going insane, dude.
- I don't believe you, but go on.
- You're lying.
Yeah, prove it.
You can check my letterbox.
- That doesn't, that you,
obviously you faked your letterbox to set yourself up
so that you could lie about this.
I could go on letterbox today
and say that I watched Inception 100 times
and leave 100 different ratings and reviews for it.
- You couldn't do that.
- I've never used letterbox.
Exactly, you couldn't do that. I watched the night comes to us, Dr. Sleep, King Kong Escapes, Alien 3, Alita Battle Angel, Alien Resurrection, War of the Worlds, and The Hitcher.
You watched the Battle Angel, you jacked off.
No, you know what I did? So I watched Freddy Got Finger twice, and then the third movie I watched was Wet Hot American Summer. So I did not watch Freddy Got Finger three times. I will.
Yes!
See, they are different movies.
You lied.
I just don't know what's going on with me right now.
Oh my god, ladies and gentlemen of the jury, he admits it.
Oh yeah, finally we can move on. I'm sure that was so interesting for everyone to listen to.
Well, I mean, you know, sorry for starting that.
No, that's what, this is what, your friendship is gonna be stronger now.
Yeah.
Because Pat admitted that he lied. Pat, you're worse than dirt. You're a fucking jerk.
I'm not worse than dirt.
You're a piece of mud, you fucking two-faced bitch.
I'm not two-faced.
- I'll admit that I lied too, 'cause it's--
- Cameron, you were virtuous.
- If it's, if I'm saying the past two days,
if that includes today, that's wrong,
'cause I haven't watched any movies today.
So I would actually be the past three days.
So we both kinda lied.
- Yeah. - Okay.
Yeah, yesterday I went to space.
Okay, so we're gonna move on.
- I believe you.
- I believe you too. - Thank you.
Yeah, you have no reason not to believe me.
We all trust each other now.
We're okay, we're never lying to each other again.
- Okay. (laughs)
- I've just had sex with Pamela Anderson
a thousand times in a row and made her cum zero times.
on the call with you don't need to you don't know she's actually saw she's
sucking my thing whatever it's called really creepy dude you shouldn't do that
on the call with us no she's got my you should say that my what is the thing
that's on your that's above your two other things she's got that thing in her
face right now she can't breathe you shouldn't say then we'll get wiki leaks
so don't do that I have my her boyfriend will get jealous and we can my main my
main little short thing is in her mouth but then my other two weird things that
in the like thing holder are in her nose. The things in the back are in her mouth and then
the other things in her nose. And I'm telling the truth. And also my poop is in her stomach.
I pooped in her. Yeah, Freddie got fingered so good. It's great. It really says
something too about like how like it's supposed to it's like supposed to just be
really unfunny and hard to watch but I just it's just it's so funny. Yeah. Like
it's it's really probably a bad thing for for my brain to have. You know what
Imagine Dragons says about this? What? Welcome to the new age.
they say I let my demons hide yeah they say radio they watch Freddy got fingers
you know you know what imagine dragons says about that what a great name for a
band I know yeah yeah they're from there from Las Vegas aren't they thinking of
thinking of monster yeah my name of my band yeah and we make music like this
yeah yeah imagine dragons my imagine dragons is from Las Vegas of course it's
the fucking desert be melted their brains is one of the yeah that's such a crazy
way to make a person yeah you you don't get you're not gonna get killers are
from there yeah yeah all of them are yeah that's right the band every every
last killer is from Las Vegas? I think the lead singer of the Killers is
Mormon. Vegas Mormon? That's an odd choice.
Yeah. Imagine being Mormon in like the middle of like... He's born in a
casino too. Yeah, the place where like gambling and prostitution are
legal. When a baby is born in Las Vegas... And you're like, "I can't drink soda because it has caffeine!" When a baby is born in Las Vegas
said the slot machine spins and if you don't get a jackpot they have a birth defect.
Is prostitution legal in the county that Vegas is in?
No it's Reno.
Reno, okay yeah.
I think it's funny that just like one county, just like something that's illegal everywhere
else in the country, they're just like, yeah just right here where it's gonna be.
Yeah, you gotta have one place.
- They should have the, yeah, Murder County.
They should have that somewhere.
- They do. - Yeah.
- They do. - Yeah, they do.
Yeah.
It's called New York City. - It's called
Lansing, Mississippi. - It's a war zone out here.
- Miss Chicken. - Between the Bloods
and the Cricks, the Crickets.
- Yeah, the Crickets and the T-Birds.
The Crickets and the T-Birds are constantly fighting
in New York, they're like, they're doing--
- New York City is like the end of Lord of the Rings.
- Yeah. - It's just like a giant battle.
- It's like the end of the Lord of the Wings and--
(laughing)
- The Lord of the Wings. - The Lord of the Wings.
The end of the Wad of the Wings.
It's the end of Wad of the Wings and West Side Story.
Yeah.
Dude, it's so scary to go to New York City because you're always, they're always, it's
always Team Aqua and Team Magma fighting each other with Pokemon battles.
It's so annoying, dude.
Oh my god.
I hate it when they, I hate it when Rayquaza comes to New York and he's wearing Timbs.
Yeah.
Now that would be something, a funny joke they could put in the new show.
The newest Pokemon show.
Yeah, they could have Rayquaza wearing Timbs.
Yeah.
Quanza.
That's, wow, that's kind of a triple entendre.
Uh huh.
Cause like Rayquan.
Rayquaza.
Quanza.
I didn't even think of Quanza.
Yeah dude, Rayquanza.
Rayquanza.
Raymond Quanza?
The inventor of Quanza.
I'm Raymond Quanza, nice to meet you.
Raymond Quanza.
Oh, Deborah, I gotta invent a holiday!
Raymond, you're never gonna win this.
I'm Raymond Quanza.
Raymond, you're never gonna reinvent the new Christmas.
Raymond, you really need to make a new holiday, Raymond.
I'm your big brother.
You're fucking dying.
I'm Raymond, my little big brother.
Hey, Raymond, I need new clothes. I'm in so much pain, Raymond.
Is it okay if I make a turkey-do-e-moat at your house?
He's just hooked up to the machine that Palpatine was hooked up to
in fucking Rise of Skywalker.
this is a great here in this palpatine
the
misterious green liquid being pumped into him
raven bob says that
you have to let me know the house it's like the
home i
god was
mhm
what back
you know we're not how we're bad so it's been a week
was that we did we're not going to make two days to the last day or did it were
bad were best like to say we're back
yeah it's it's puts me in a good mood to feel like i'm back
uh...
so you guys want
is a little bit less was a list i found a list that top ten wishes you would ask
from a genie if you had the alliance lamp
isn't there a speaking of raymond is a perfect transition transition into the
list
uh... was there a simpsons episode with ray
Ray Magini.
This is Ray Romano's guest appearance on The Simpsons.
Hold up.
I don't remember.
I think I've only seen to maybe season 11.
Hold on.
Let me.
I'm up to season I think 6.
It's starting to get good.
It's already got good.
It's gonna get even better.
Once you get to season 32, it gets better.
Oh my god.
It peaks at season 28.
Yeah, something I don't, I love season 5, but something I don't like about it is how few
Trump jokes they put in. Yeah. I feel like you can't really be
complacent when you're making a TV show you have to kind of speak truth to power
against Donald Trump so. That's right. Yeah, Ray Magini, that was the character's
name. That's like the first Simpsons episode I saw. Ray Magini, what season is
it? That is... I was like seven so. You were seven? Yeah. Means it was season like 20.
the
Yeah, now that I think about it, 16.
Yeah, one of them, yeah.
Yeah.
The discretest list is by Kaideretsunu.
Kaite-
Kaiteretsu.
Kiretesu.
Kitturu.
Kisturu.
Sas.
Kishdeban.
Kite.
Kis-
Kite-
- Kitarasnu.
- Kitar, Kitar.
- Vishnu Kaiba.
- You got it.
- Yeah, and the description is,
"The trademark I wish,
"if somehow were guaranteed reality."
That's word salad.
That doesn't make any sense.
Number one is, of course, unlimited wishes.
- Uh-huh.
- That's a layup.
- There's a list in this list.
- Yeah, this is a really long list.
There's a comment that just has like 20 things.
- Well, should we read this list in the list?
- I say we just read it.
- I feel like there's gonna be some duplicates.
- Let's go through it real fast.
- I feel like there's gonna be duplicates.
- We won't talk, we'll just go through it real fast.
We won't even talk.
We'll say one thing about each one, all right?
Ready?
Unlimited money.
That's good, you can buy lots of stuff.
The ability to order anything off any website for free.
Kinda redundant if you already have unlimited money.
Telekinesis powers.
That's cool.
- Can control.
- The ability to teleport anywhere.
- Where'd it go?
- I love Looper.
- I am going to school.
Wait, jumper, I love jumper.
- Immortality.
(laughing)
Immortality.
- That terrifies me.
- You could never die.
- No, so scary.
- Free airline tickets for life.
Again, redundant if you already have money.
- Hello, Hawaii.
- Unlimited school supplies.
- What?
I would never do that.
- Why would you choose that?
Unlimited food.
- No, no, no, listen.
You don't have to use them for school.
- You could sell them out of your locker.
- Why not just wish not to go to school, though?
All right, we're spending too much time on this one.
We have to keep going.
Unlimited food. Yummy.
*burp*
Everything is free for me.
That's the same as the first one.
The ability to time travel. Yes, please.
I would go talk to Jesus Christ.
Inability to feel pain.
Yes!
I would be the greatest skateboarder on earth.
No, this wouldn't be good for me because I'm a sucker for pain.
The best skateboarder who's the best ever
because he feels no pain.
He's just eating Neverland
and it just gets hurt so badly.
Just breaking all of his teeth out.
I could try it again.
I could try the trick again.
Private jet.
I don't think so.
No, I know what happens on private jets.
I don't want one of those.
Mansion with hot tub, game room, and water/theme park and backyard.
That's too much for one wish.
That's too much, yeah.
That's four wishes.
You can get the mansion, but you have to buy all the other stuff yourself.
You have to build it yourself.
Personal chauffeur.
I would wish for Caleb to be my personal chauffeur.
I wouldn't do it.
Caleb is our personal chauffeur.
I am not.
True, I am going to be driving you two to New York next month I guess.
Unlimited pets.
Dogs and cats just raining from the sky.
In a two bedroom apartment with like six pit bulls and a bunch of parakeets and shit.
No, no, no, not six pit bulls, unlimited pets.
Unlimited pit bulls.
Yeah, infinite pets.
Pit bull army.
- Inability to get sick, yes please.
Now that would solve a lot of problems.
- Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Pitbull army.
- Wow. - Yeah, dude.
I hear they're already developing that in China.
They're teaching pitbulls to bounce a ball at the same time.
(laughing)
- Would you guys, like an Iditarod style pitball,
pitball. - Pitball.
- My man, pitball. - Iditarod style
pitbull death chariot.
- That would be cool. - Would I ride it?
Yeah, dude, all the pitbulls are just eating all the other dogs in the rain.
You mount machine guns on them.
Dude, that is so cool.
To enter the Iditarod in a twisted metal style sled.
Dude, a fucking pitbull could totally, like, they are so muscly, dude.
Depending on the kind of them.
Yeah, they're like ripped to shit.
You could mount a 50 cal machine gun to a pitbull.
Yeah.
(laughing)
- He could, he totally could.
- You're so slow, but you're just killing everybody
ahead of you so it doesn't matter.
- It is funny to imagine pit bulls as just like,
like unthinking killing machines.
- Yeah.
- All they desire is death.
- Yeah, they crave carnage.
- They crave destruction.
- Yeah.
- Did you guys have to follow the idea to rot in third grade?
- Yes.
- I didn't have to do anything in third grade
because I was cool.
i died every other year and and and third-rate did you follow it for class or
did you follow it on your own class
i feel like you were following yourself
you guys both did a rod
you did a rod no you did i just said that about you dude you did a rod
it's two against one
i wish i was the only guy on the podcast that's my wish
well you're the only something on the podcast what are you eating
Patrick what is that
brother gave me a BLT
uh... yeah increased popularity
would be fun
i would never get in no
would be fun to popular already
uh... eliminate my son sensitivity
that's specific to one person
unlimited ink in my printer
that'd be cool dude i could print out so many pages
on the ability to correct all mistakes
plus what's going on
i don't know i feel like that's uh...
this is what we should soaring
yeah about their some really good comments on this unlimited wishes one
there's another uh... comment here that says
i would love this because you could wish for everything on this site and even
more than that for me it would be to have unlimited robux roblox
uh...
Imagine your kid discovers a genie's lamp
in the old basement of your house
and wastes all the wishes,
being like, "I want 100 robux.
"Okay, I want 100 more robux."
(laughing)
- I like this comment.
Would be nice, but depends if the genie
has a no unlimited wishes rule.
- That is so true.
- That is what, if I was a genie,
that'd be the first thing.
Like, why have they not-- - The genie's clause.
- Yeah, why does the genie's union not got together
be like we can't have they can't keep doing this to us.
- Yeah, what I would always think when I thought about like,
you know how genies like to twist your wishes?
A really cool twist if someone wished for infinite wishes
is you just force them to stay there forever
and keep wishing and they can never leave or stop wishing.
You know what I mean?
- I wouldn't be a mean genie.
I mean what else does a genie have to fucking do?
- Well I mean I just mean that would be a good twist
for a genie to do.
- Yeah, why do genies always twist the wishes?
- Why do they have to be mean?
- They're evil pre-Islamic deities, dude.
They, until Islam came in and set 'em all straight.
- Yeah, no, I only want a post-Islamic genie.
- Yeah.
- I just want a Muslim genie.
Is that too fuckin' hard to ask?
- Have you guys watched Wishmaster?
- No.
- Wishmaster's so good. - I think so.
I seen it a long time ago.
- Oh, yeah. - I love Wishmaster so much.
- No, I'm thinking of Pagemaster with Macaulay Culkin.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Yeah, different movie.
- That's a cool movie.
He goes into Moby Dick.
- He goes into the pages.
he actually gets this he's in the pages
wish master is awesome because none of
the none of the twists make like any
sense like there's a part where like the
police a police officer like points a
gun at the genie and is like freeze and
the genie is like okay and then freezes
the police officer in a block of ice
it's like that would be my twist would
not be clever somebody be like I want a
toy car and I'd be like okay and you
have poop for a face. Got you. I wish for world peace. Yeah you wish for world peace and I
gave you a hot dog for a penis. Yes. The world is at peace but you will never have a normal
penis again. You won't have a normal piece. Yeah that's right. That's right. I'm gonna
whirl your piece. Yeah you have a twisty wiener now. Yep you have a little pig tail for a
dick yeah and not like a hair like a actual penis for true love I gave you a
blue glove - they have true love and you have to wear this blue glove you idiot
I'm the G I'm the best genie ever here's another another comment on this one that
says I wash that in my school ma'am should call me for dance practice nice
That is so true. Epic123 says that and being creative with things and
then right under that RedPanda789 says that and being very creative.
You wish to be creative? Yeah I wish for unlimited wishes and to be creative. I love
being creative. Yeah. Yeah because if you have unlimited wishes but you're not
creative with your wishes all your wishes would kind of suck right? No, you
don't have to be creative. I mean if you have unlimited wishes you can
just be like okay I want $100 okay I want a hundred more okay I want a hundred
more it doesn't have creative well if you're not creative then it's like I
wish for no creative creative wishes is when is it when it gets bad it's not a
great wishes you're like I wish that I wish that my house what could fly and
then you fall out of your house and die you know but if you're uncreative you
just say I wish for a big house and you get a big house and it's fine the key is
you have to wish for you have to what if the house is to be happen to you so that
he twists it the other way.
- Yeah. - Oh, okay.
- You know, you could say, "I wish I was in jail."
And then you get put in like a really cool jail.
- Yeah, you get put in white collar prison
and you're playing tennis with Bernie Madoff.
- That's right. - I wrote a one-act play
with Aaron about that, about a genie who like,
the person keeps wishing for, it was like,
"Oh, I heard genies twist your wishes,
"so I gotta be careful.
"I wish for my whole family to die
"in a tragic buzzsaw accident."
And then her whole family dies and she's like,
"Whoa, what's the twist?
"How did you twist it?"
And just like he's wishing for stuff like that.
- You are so smart.
- I'm pretty creative.
I kinda wish to be creative.
- Yeah, Cameron wished to be creative
with his pre-Islamic genie in his basement.
- Yeah.
- That's why he's in that cave.
- Yeah, I'm in a cave. - You're like Charlie Cockman.
(laughing)
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Cameron's a real Charlie Cockman type.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Number two, make someone fall madly in love with you.
- I would like the first comment is,
i want to bring freddie mercury back to life in mary him
all my god i forgot to wish that he doesn't have a yeah
that's a shit it's a good
and i don't know
because did that's if you wish for freddie mercury to come back to that's
all three of your wishes right there 'cause it's one freddie mercury comes
back to life to freddie mercury falls madly in love with you and three freddie
mercury does that means anymore
yeah and then you're coming that's done you gotta pick one either
either he's not in love with you and he doesn't have aids
'Cause then where do you put Ski-Doo?
You know?
Where do you put Ski-Doo in your wishes?
- Exactly.
- There's a comment on this one,
there's a comment on this one that just says vagina.
(laughing)
- I wish that a vagina would fall in love with me.
- Yeah.
- The next one, I just wanna read this
and then immediately read a comment on it.
Number three is for you and your friends
family to be a mortal and then this comment says yes even better is if only
me and my aunt were a mortal when she was younger and I was a two-year-old so she
can give me baths and change my diapers forever
Jesus Christ just the first time that you've ever seen a genie express
disgust yeah I don't even have a twist for that I'm just gonna kill you I wish
that you were dead yeah the twist on this one is I'm just gonna kill you he pulls
out a smaller he pulls out a smaller lamp and rubs it that comes out and he's like
yeah I want this guy killed also unlimited wishes can a genie can a genie
give himself a wish? Maybe. May a genie cast a wish upon himself? Yeah. I think he, well,
I think he would have to have a smaller, lower number. If he says it into a tape recorder
and then plays it back and pretends it's somebody else's wish. If he does a really good impression
of a guy who found a lamp. Yeah. Or if he's very manipulative. Yeah. Or if he has split
personalities one is it one part of him is a genie and the other part is a kid
named Derek hmm who finds a lamp yeah that's that sounds like a Marvel
character from the 60s later there yeah there they had their their secret
identity just made no sense it was just like oh this this this is Thor is like a
Thunder God oh but wait he needs a secret identity I know he transforms
into a guy who has to walk with a cane like they're all just like they all just
transform. It's like like it would start out as just a kid who can turn
into a genie and grant people wishes but then in the 80s it's like he actually has
multiple personality disorder and yeah and inside of his mind he's constantly
fighting himself yeah yeah what was the what was that's actually a metaphor for
addiction yeah what was that cleat it sucks it comics got like cool at some
point I think you know and them a little in Chris Claremont yeah and Alan Moore
there's Alan Moore I know him yeah and they did the Vertigo comics they're like
yeah see these guys like that that like sub company or whatever that just makes
comics that are like a prostitute with AIDS has it has to fuck a evil trash bag
yeah it's pretty when I was a kid I was like yeah Frank Miller and shit since
yeah call me when it's SimCity and I can actually control it my own city called
Caleb's Berg they it's the Caleb I got great news what's the news there's Sim
city two thousand for ps one
that's exciting
uh... one ticket to caleb's bird please
number four is world peace
for world peace
and there's three comments that just say best wish ever must have wish
and random nader says would be nice that would be nice
yeah that would be nice but it's not a jet ski
Yeah, the twist there is you run out of oil.
Exactly.
Yeah, it's just your car don't work no more.
Yeah.
You gotta find a new...
If there's world peace, then there's gonna be no more video games, 'cause you can't force
a Vietnamese family into working in a software slave shop anymore.
Yeah, and there's gonna be no more cartoons.
And way too many cousins at Thanksgiving.
(laughter)
- Ah shit, Brits back, fuck.
No, come on dude.
- I thought you were at war.
- Nah, actually some kid voted for world peace at a genie.
At a genie, he voted at a genie.
- He voted at a genie.
- He voted at a genie for world peace.
- It's one of those overpopulation conspiracy theories
where it's like a war all along was a way
to trim down the cousin population.
- Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, there's not enough food at Thanksgiving now.
Half the fucking cousins, the big cousins especially, are back from Afghanistan.
Yeah the stupid cousins.
The cousins with IQs too low to know when to stop eating.
Yeah but he's also the cousin with the Dodge Charger.
Pretty one-sided flag football game at Thanksgiving now.
Now that all the war cousins are back.
Number 5 identical twin sibling and the first comment is kill them and pretend to be dead
then see how people really talk to you.
Kill your twin sibling just so you can- Why would you wish for a twin sibling to kill
you?
Why not just wish to see how people talk about you?
You are the better twin.
Also like, beyond that, I think identical twin sibling is kind of a crazy thing to wish
for.
Right?
I mean like under- Half the presence.
unlimited wishes fall in love immortal world peace identical twin sibling that
doesn't seem like the next thing that should be on this list it is crazy that
it's voted the fifth yeah right right what the fuck is the rest of also it's
just like a ring a lot of people are yeah it's just it's a thing
randomator says could end up being a problem that's true it could end up
being a problem because the genie knowing knowing this bastard genie he's gonna
make it yeah I don't you want an identical twin sibling okay here's one
that's identical to a monster yeah you're sibling is identical to Hitler in every
way congrats buddy sometimes people get you confused yeah that's right and now
you look like Hitler - uh-huh yep and now number six perfect singing voice I
already have this one yeah me too
I can't even think of the song right now
I was trying to think of oh yeah
Roxanne
I'm going to the 21
You're gonna make it dude
Do you believe that airplanes in the night sky are like shooting stars?
I could really use a wish right now, wish right now
Keep going
They wish in this list
wish right now let's pretend
sorry i don't want to get us copyright struck uh by eminem because i'm doing it
better than him too identical yeah i we had to copyright strike this podcast
because he he outshone eminem on his own [ __ ]
yeah number seven killed him on his own track
yeah he renegaded eminem yeah number seven is live in a world of
fiction. I'd like to live in a world of fiction. Top comment is... I feel like you're just giving a lot of
material for the G to twist there. You're gonna live in Salo. Yeah, so many... yeah, okay, you can just live in
hell. Yeah. Where, I don't know, there's so many options to twist that one. You're living in the human centipede and you're the middle.
I would live in a world that has Bikini Bottom from Spongebob and also has Rick and Morty and other fictional
things as long as my friends and family are there.
- Okay.
- Mom, we're moving to Bikini Bottom from SpongeBob
with Rick and Morty.
- Pack your bags and become very small.
- Grow some meals.
- Mom, yeah mom, when I get rich,
I'm moving you to Bikini Bottom.
- I'm gonna get you out of here, mom.
One day you're gonna see Bikini Bottom.
- One day we're gonna live in a house just like Squidward's.
- Son, I have cancer.
(laughing)
- Don't worry, mom. - I promise I'm gonna
show you Bikini Bottom before you die.
- Rick Sanchez has an invention that can create
clone of you that won't die of cancer and he's in Bikini Bottom 2. But will I still
die? Yes. It doesn't matter. That's kind of... Shut up. Mom you don't understand that's kind of one of the
moral questions of the show it's kind of like a philosophical quandary type thing.
Oh my god I was playing I was playing Valorant the other day and... With Rick and Morty?
Yes no I saw the greatest I saw the greatest like gamer tag I've ever seen
in my life is a person whose name was bleak nihilism. I was just like fuck dude I wish
I thought of that first. Bleak nihilism is my gamer name. I think my favorite gamer name
is not a gamer tag is uh will sent it to us it was a guy in warzone named soldiers wrath.
I changed mine, Carlos Mencia had one of my favorites, his Call of Duty, his Xbox Live
Gamer Tag, he used to post to his fans to ask them to play Call of Duty with him, and his
Gamer Tag was Laugh Punisher.
Sick, dude.
And I changed my Warzone name to Laugh Punisher.
That's so good.
It was two, so I couldn't have the ER at the end, so it's Laugh Punish-R.
That's even better.
That is cool.
nine-year-old brothers is a furious destroyer yes that is like the best like
nine-year-old Blake yeah furious destroyer
it's so good that's a good one yeah he's also like I'd obsess with Hitler
so I thank God it's a slippery slope. Yeah it could have been Führer's destroyer.
Exactly. Become the biggest celebrity ever and then user HiThere says
I actually can't stand the prospect of being famous. Me too. Fame is like a
prison to me. Fame is a prism and you shine the light through it.
It's got four sides.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
And you can see the dark side of the moon through it.
Yeah.
That's a Pink Floyd album cover.
Good one.
Nice, dude.
What do you guys think was the inspiration for Pink Floyd's song about money?
Money!
It rocks!
No, no, that's not it.
That's not it.
Let's try again.
I love the stuff and I put it in my pocket.
Money!
I wish I had $100.
- I had $100.
- No, that's not it.
- Money! - Money!
- It's cash.
There it is.
(laughing)
There it is, yeah.
We got it.
♪ Put it in my wallet ♪
♪ Then put it in the pocket on my ass ♪
- Let's see, what rhymes with cash?
It's a bash.
- It's a blast.
- Okay, I think we have the greatest song of all time.
♪ This stuff's awesome ♪
♪ I love to spend it on ♪
is maybe the worst skins and Valorant yeah yeah yeah yeah that was definitely a
late a last-minute addition yeah the bass riff in that song sounds like a song we
want it to sound when I elevate this to sound like truth what it sound like dog
shit yeah yeah it's like one of those like like the 70s guys who like like it
was very deep in the 70s but then you'd like hear it now it's just kind of like
It's actually it's actually really important because it's one of the one of the major
Inspirations for that fort minor song where they use just random sounds and household set objects to create a beat room
So he's kind of planes by by MIA. Yeah where they use a paper plane to record the song. That's yeah
Yeah, where she's song it they actually sang the whole song while riding on a paper plane. It's a little-known fact pretty impressive
She she wrote all the lyrics on paper planes and then threw him to her producer. Whoa
I
I love, I love like, Boomer like, deep shit, like Money by Pink Floyd or like, just the
phrase "Give Peace a Chance".
Like you just see some guy in like a denim shirt and like, who's smoked like a million
cigarettes in his life, and he's just like "Give Peace a Chance, give me a piece of
courage".
People being like alive and old right now that were hippies is like so awesome.
It's so, it's so fucking cool to like, to meet like an IT guy who was a hippie, you
know what I mean?
just that that type like or like a food service worker who was a hippie yeah oh
I I worked with I fucking worked at life alive I worked with people like that
yeah that one of my one of the because one of the people I worked with like
wouldn't let me go home unless I did everything on this list she never gave
she never gave me a break and I was like man aren't you supposed to be like
anti-authority aren't you supposed to hate the man
new generation of like hippie types like astrology type people and like
spiritual but like there's some there's just like something about the original
hippies they're really just it really just be hidden different you know what I
mean yeah yeah the government was definitely right to just like try to
kill as many of them as possible legally you know yeah like if they killed more
maybe we could have stopped like Steppenwolf from happening right you know
We wouldn't have to hear "Magic Carpet Ride" whenever like something happens in a movie that's cool.
Yeah, we could have because those guys all became people who love Steppenwolf and then that song
"Lowrider" from the George Lopez show. That song's awesome. That song rocks. Yeah. It's not a good
song. That is a great song. That makes sense that you think that. That song's so cool. No.
What are you talking about? Corn did a cover of that. You think E.T. don't like the part where it goes?
Cool is a cool song. It's cool for the time. Let me tell you what a cool song is
That's a song, you know, no, you know what it is lowriders and skate - so I associate it with
Sweetie - it's serotonin in your brain. Yeah, exactly. So
True true. I also associate it with George Lopez show, which also is the most serotonin. That's right, dude
they pumped that shit into my brain.
- What was cool about--
- When he goes, "Wapa!"
- My cousin told me when we were younger,
he loved the George Lopez show.
- Because of the mom?
- I was like, "What is your deal? Why do you love this?"
And he was like, "Honestly, man,"
because he's half Mexican,
and he was like, "Honestly, man, it's just so people at school
"believe that I'm Mexican because I look so white."
(laughter)
He just would watch it so that he knew everything about
the George Lopez show so that you could go to school and be like yo the Lopez was crazy last night.
That Lopez ep, that epi, lopey had my brain. Wow. What's the guy, what's his like Ernie,
his friend Ernie? You know I think I've seen it. You're thinking of Sesame Street and only. Yeah,
no there, no I'm thinking of George Lopez show because. You're thinking of Ernie and Bert from
from Sesame Street, your favorite show.
- George Lopez collects paperclips and he loves pigeons,
and his friend Ernie's always giving him the shit.
He's giving him shit.
And they sit there and they live together,
and there's a rubber ducky, and that's George Lopez.
- Number 11, no pain.
(laughing)
- Yeah, that sucked.
- No pain or damage to your body ever.
- We've already gone through this one.
- No, but listen to the comment, though.
Listen to this comment from Hai there.
Said Genie would be about 15 years too late on that one.
- What?
- He's saying that he made this wish 15 years ago.
- There's another comment on this that just says, "Venom."
- That's kind of a scary comment.
- Yeah, I don't like that comment.
- Number 12, become the prettiest person in the universe.
- I think we should skip to number 13.
I think this is the word this is where it's at for me. We is it ramp back up here number 13
No more Justin Bieber
But who would we make fun of?
you
What the heck I hate him so much even my friends hate him. Yeah, he makes my he makes my balls boil
You're really boiling my balls JB. This wish is great. No more Justin means no more problems for boys
He just suck. He is a human and he has the right of what he is doing. What have you guys done in life?
I've hated Justin Bieber. Yeah, I've
My my Justin Bieber jokes are way more creative than ever any song that freak could ever make
Remember that video? I think we watched it on stream, but it's like Justin Bieber is dead metal wins
Was it a clip of Law and Order or whatever we get shot a thousand times
Yeah, but it's a kid just it's a kid talking about it with no context
Nice. Oh my god
Wait, no, sorry. Keep going
He what well, it's called it's called Justin Fagber rest in piss
That's the title of the video
That's pretty good dude, we might need to
episode name I
Think we just found an episode damn. Yeah, dude. It's one of the it's one of the best like
like 20 like videos from
It just perfectly
Encapsulates the the mindset of a teenage boy in 2010. I
Fucking hate myself, dude. I
Love you more than anything and I'm gonna marry you you're not gonna. We uh we
We predicted this number 14 is to go back in time and change past mistakes and a comment on here says I can save Freddie
mercury
there's no there's another comment it's a safe delivery definitely
it's not what you've already don't talk that aspect here
that's over there
not mind you know i'm on and i would go i would go even further back in time and i
I would go to the guy who invented AIDS and say, "Listen, monkeys are not sexy, okay?"
Monkeys are not sexy.
It doesn't matter.
They may try to trick you with coconut bras and long wigs, but don't fall for it.
Yeah, I understand.
Monkeys are beautiful.
AIDS was created by monkeys on purpose.
They knew that if humans had sex with them, it would be the downfall of humanity.
It's literally the planet of the AIDS.
So they dressed up sexy to try and fool this guy.
- Yeah, 'cause they had--
- Is that what 12 Monkeys is about?
- Yeah, I've never seen 12 Monkeys.
- I haven't seen 12 Monkeys either, but it sounds right.
- I think it's about a guy going crazy.
- I don't think it is.
- It is.
- I think it's about you.
And it's about 12 of you.
I think it's about 12 different versions of you.
- It's basically Cheaper by the Dozen with monkeys.
So a guy has 12 monkeys in his house
and his wife is writing a book about it.
And he has, and also Ashton Kutcher
is marrying one of the monkeys.
Let's blow through some more of these.
There are a bunch of really good ones on here.
Number 15, wish for eliminating the evil qualities
which resides in every person on the planet.
I hope it includes pervertedness to be eliminated.
That's so true.
Me too.
Number 16, to bring dead actors back to life.
Who would you guys, if you can bring one person
back to life?
One person, or one dead actor?
I would bring one dead actor.
I'd bring Chadwick Boseman back so that we could finish what Marvel started, you know, and he can die again. I don't give a fuck
But at least that was like I love how that was like the first thing a lot of people said
Like they're like all the stupid fucking Marvel fans were like
- I
Mean, they definitely are just gonna CGI him for five more movies, right?
I already have a fucking clone of him dude. Yeah, there's no way they don't yeah
Yeah, they definitely already they either already filmed five movies or they're gonna CGI him
It's just so sad that that he was secretly arrested and then executed by President Donald Trump
It's really sad I would bring Jim Varney back to life so we could get more earnest movies
I would bring Jim Carrey back to life. Yeah, I'd bring his girlfriend back to life to find out what really happened. Yeah
Yeah, I slipped and landed on a bunch of pills
I would I would bring Kevin Spacey back to life because the guy that's been doing all this stuff that ain't him
Yeah, let me tell you he would never do
House of cards I would bring Marlon Brando and Richard Pryor back as two old men and make them fuck again
I would bring back like I would bring back like a Shakespeare era actor
Yeah, so I could kill them with someone like William Smithington. I would bring back Shakespeare
Yeah, it wasn't an actor. He wasn't really he was a collective of the biggest actors in the world
He was not an actor a collective of writers. That's right. Yeah
Wasn't one guy. Mm-hmm. Yep. He was like
Just like David Wayne and and the two Michaels, yeah
Become the most famous person in the universe
That's like the fourth time that's on this fucking list dude.
Number 22 is more genies and the top comment is
I want a genie to give me a lot of wishes and I want the genie to be a girl.
Yeah, no obviously.
It's like how you go to a massage place and you're like I prefer a female masseuse.
Yeah, I want a female genie.
Look, getting your wish granted by another man?
Yeah, it's you know.
Yeah, I don't know wait having another man make your dreams come true
Okay, sure
Number 24 turning you into a wizard
Then you can fight your genie. Yeah, there's a comment here old who just becomes an old
There's a comment here that says I voted this from old-fashioned Mickey Mouse call
Number 30 is wishing for an increase in the size of the Earth's radius for accommodating the increasing population
And then a comment says I love earth Wakanda forever
Number 31 be the most well-known
Okay, okay to turn Chuck Norris into your bodyguard
Number 30 for his potential number 34 become verified on Instagram and the top comment is this is not cool
Numbers number 39 a mercury back and curing his AIDS number 39 is to end racism
And then the comment that says this is an amazing wish but sadly and unfortunately
Unfortunately, there's too much prejudice in this world.
The genie was just like, "Yeah, I can't do that wish, sorry."
"Sorry, I can't do that wish."
"Unfortunately, yeah, there's too much of it.
I can't, yeah.
You know, I can make you immortal.
I can give you infinite wishes, but I just, you know, there's too much prejudice."
Number 45, a lightsaber, and the only comment is "Yas, queen."
40 economic prosperity for the whole world and this comment says this would never work because if everyone's rich then no one is poor
Just like no more evil in the world than what is good. Everyone is equally prolly shit. You're right, dude
Somebody has to be poor. Yeah, they could just make everybody rich except the one guy
55 is to make my tickling desires and fantasies come true
(laughter)
Number 51, wishing for spring throughout the calendar year.
No more Barney.
Number 53, to bring-
Number 66 is, Miranda Cosgrove visits Pakistan.
(laughter)
The comment is "I love Miranda Cosgrove and I want that she come to Pakistan for once."
Oh my fucking god.
Oh, that's so good.
That's your wish?
A genius wish?
Alright, first off, I want Miranda Cosgrove to come to Pakistan.
You're not even in Pakistan.
Just send her to Pakistan.
You're in Chicago, California.
California just make it I mean just fucking make a request
number 84 sex will never exist now
That's right. That's my wish
Someone says male won't exist in the world one problem with male or male sex never existed
Then people wouldn't put Sharon is user Patronus says I'm asexual so this would be okay with me, lol
Number 94, the last one is just a car.
[Laughter]
I'm gonna wish for, just give me like a 2003 Corolla and you can keep the other two wishes, don't really care.
I got what I wanted out of this.
Hold on, uh...
Free Sirius XM radio and then the last wish, do whatever.
Yeah, full tank of gas is the last wish.
[Laughter]
Premium, full tank of premium gas.
Not that unleaded bullshit.
and Spotify premium.
- Yeah, I mean, and now that I think about it,
I guess like a cool key chain for the car.
Oh yeah, and also Freddie Mercury's back
and he's cured of AIDS.
- And he lives in my car.
- He lives in the car, and also he can't leave the car.
- Yeah, and I get my own Freddie concert every day.
- Yeah, you know what, so actually scratch the SiriusXM,
but Freddie knows every song in the world.
And he has a dial on his back.
yeah we can get for a d_-mercury to sing reggae
oh yeah all you know my god for a mercury really cover
i think i'm ready for that you know we're gonna see your for a d_-mercury sing
toots in the may tals that's right we're gonna hear him sing
daylight come in the one go home
it's not a pretty it's not a really it's like and that's like the number one
reggae song in the world and i don't want to read your favorite charters sheriff
probably. It's "Come Mr. Telly Man, Telly Me Banana." No, the number one is probably
"One Love, Spirit of Jamaica, One Heart, Let's Get Together and Be Alright." No. No, I don't
think so. I think you're wrong on that one. It's "Daylight Come and Me Won't Go." The number
one reggae song is the Arthur theme song. That's true. That might be one of them for
sure uh-huh that's Bob Marley's kid yeah yeah yeah little Marley little Bob
Marley yeah Bob Marley the main comedian
he's a cool that he was in boondock Saints yeah well that's the thing about
every Boston comedian is they just do like bit parts and every Boston movie
that comes through there's like dudes who have just played like every version
of a cop, a principal, and a trash man.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- It's pretty cool.
- You're talking, it's just Gus's dad.
- That's true.
- You're just talking about Gus's dad.
- Tony V, respect to Tony V.
- Big ups, Tony V.
- All right, boys.
I think that'll do it.
Check out the Patreon.
- Check out our friend Gus's dad, Tony V.
- Yeah, check out Tony Viveiros, he's the man.
All right, bye.
- And we're fucking Tony V.
- Tony V needs it, dude.
(laughing)