You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- You really crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Wow.
- Yes, you guys have never, you've never,
you've never tried jacking off during one
of these Zoom episodes?
- No.
- There's no way you could.
- I mean, you could.
- It's just we find that pretty easy.
- Are you issuing a challenge to me?
How would you find that out?
How would you know?
You don't know what my coming
and jacking off face to face.
Just a fountain of white liquid just shooting up for one second.
Oh my god, I spilled my milk on the ceiling.
Oh no!
A bug just splattered upwards on my camera.
I crushed a bug upside down.
A big white bug.
A bug just flew into my mouth.
Mmm!
I might have to...
Oh, man!
Imagine if this bug was covered in chocolate.
I'm gonna take another bite of this bug if you give me ten minutes.
(laughing)
- Right, yeah, no, for the rest of the episode.
- I'm trying to catch the bug, it's really fast.
- The rest of the episode came--
- I have to move my hand around really fast
to try to catch the bug.
- Oh, he's, oh, I almost caught him!
(laughing)
- Oh, I just caught the bug.
- Oh man, was that--
- And I got the bug juice.
- Was catching that bug as good as it was for you guys
as it was for me?
(laughing)
I know somebody who I used to be homeschooled with one time while we were being homeschooled
jacked off on my couch with a blanket over him.
That's disgusting.
Yeah, it was pretty gross.
Yeah, did you call him out on it?
Yeah, dude, I ripped the blanket off.
It's crazy how comfortable kids are with each other.
Especially homeschool kids, dude.
We're freaks.
- Kids used to just be like,
okay, I'm gonna go jack off in your guest room now.
- Yeah. - Oh my God.
The amount of times where I was like,
hey man, I'm gonna go to your bathroom
and I'm going to jack off.
- I was never a kid who would jack off
at someone else's home.
I feel like that would be disrespectful.
- I didn't make that choice.
(laughing)
You know what I mean?
I wasn't like, oh yeah, I'm gonna be this kid.
No, it was fucking--
- But I wasn't that kid though.
- I was so horny. - I wasn't that kid.
No, I would like fuck like a crack in a door when I was a kid.
I tried everything.
You would fuck a cracker.
You would fuck a Ritz cracker.
You would fuck one of the little holes.
The hole, yeah.
You have the room, you have the room on your thing, your P-man to fuck a cracker.
Yeah, I have the room on my P-man.
I've been, I've been, I can't stop thinking about calling a penis a P-man.
Yeah.
And be like, "Oh, my P-man hurts so bad today."
Oh, you guys are gross talking about piss and where your hair comes from.
Where did that come from?
I don't want to, what?
- What, P-man?
- No, Cameron and I were talking.
- It was, someone said something,
I forgot who said something about C-man,
and I said, "Yeah, C-man comes out my P-man."
- Yeah, yeah, we were making fun of Seamus.
- Yeah. - Seamus, you fucking moron.
- Seamus, we're gonna attack you.
- Yeah, hey man, do you wanna go sit in the bathtub
and touch each other's P-man?
(laughing)
- Yes.
- It's like the Cheetahmen, but P-man.
- P-man, P-man is so funny.
- Dude, P-Man, so, it's so good.
It's like perfect.
- Yeah, like, you know, like the--
- That's nasty, dude.
- I got that idea.
It's like a chess, like the chessmen cookies,
but it's the P-Man cookies.
- Yeah.
- Stop! - Oh, Caleb's--
- No!
(laughing)
- No, don't go out, don't leave the frame.
Don't leave the frame.
Don't leave the frame of the Zoom call.
Stay in frame.
Keep laughing, keep your mouth open.
- No, no, uh-oh.
- Don't cover your eyes.
Don't cover your eyes, look in the camera.
No yeah, Cameron take your jacket off.
Patrick is so scared of Caleb jacking off.
I'm not kidding, right now my penis might be the smallest it's ever been in my entire life.
Oh my god dude it got so cold so quick.
I'm looking at it right now, I mean it looks like a fucking clit.
Yeah, I looked down at my thingy in the shower and it was, it just.
Also I just smelled it, it smells like Olive Garden.
(laughter)
- My dick smells like breadsticks right now.
- It does, dude.
- It's from fucking all those breadsticks.
- Smells like rosemary and garlic.
- Yeah, I'm looking kinda red today.
I think I'm on the Caleb tip.
- Yeah, you will be on my tip soon.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I was, it's so cold lately,
I was looking down at my P-Man in the shower,
it only reached halfway down the drain, dude.
- Wow.
- Come on, dude, you little, don't lie.
No, Cameron, you don't lie.
You're dangling your dick down the drain to get a snarl of hair out of the drain.
You're lying, you're lying on the drain.
The pee hole bites the hair like a claw and pulls it back out.
Disgusting.
It's great because I have a snake shaped penis.
Yeah, that's why I call it a pee man because it's sentient.
It's got little hands on the end.
It's more like a guy than it is a body part.
I would love to have a little penis no matter the type of my penis.
Just pee man, more guy than dick.
laying down, laying down with your arms,
like laying down in jumping jack form
while your penis is in the drain.
- Just spread eagle.
- I was gonna say spread eagle,
but I felt like jumping jack painted a better picture.
- Lying on your back outside the tub
and your dick draped over and going down the drain.
- There's a lot of dick talk,
but I realized recently that every single time I'm on a plane
I have a boner the entire flight
and I can't get rid of it.
really yeah I can't get rid of it yeah I just because you're scared I'm maybe
when I'm terrified I get a I get a huge fucking rock hard sting yeah yeah that
might be it sense that's I feel like that in doesn't that happen in movies
don't people say they get boners when they're scared in movies yeah there's a
whole Kenny versus any episode where they test that yeah in my brain there
well spinny is Mythbusters no basically Kenny versus penny was like they had a
whole episode like who whoever gets the first boner loses yeah I would win yeah
that I feel like we could just do that show yeah yeah just a bonus episode just
weekly just the bone every week exactly and you have a game show who gets a
boner first and you get random people women no it's got to be like it's got to
be last it's got to be better if it's last because then people will try to give
each other boners who gets the boner last wins yeah but yes then because then then
you have to try and get to give him to give him a boner yeah I misspoke yeah
yeah it'll be one of those say but you didn't know that's the thing there's no
sexual contact and there's nothing you know they don't say I'm going to suck
your dick they just have to say no you can't even talk you just have to sit and
you just wait it out cuz at some point you're gonna get a boner sitting there
everybody's got a boner where you've been like why what am yeah at a funeral you
- You think that it stops in middle school, but it doesn't.
- No, dude, no.
I mean, not for me, man.
Also, every time I'm in a job where I have a training session
- Every time I'm in a job interview, I get rock hard.
I stand up and I point down and I say, there's the legend.
- When I worked in IT, every training session, I got a boner.
- Every time I'm in a job interview
and the boss sits down on my lap, I get a huge boner.
(laughing)
- Oh, I hate that.
- That sucks so much.
- I hate when I get a boner when I'm on the block,
- When he's grinding on me.
Oh my God, it's so embarrassing.
- At the cheetah club.
- Yeah.
- At the bar during the interview.
- Oh, he's listening to Miss Pretty Pussy by Plies
and he's grinding on me.
(laughing)
- I'm just Plies, man.
- I hate that.
- And then he turns around and he puts on X-Ray specs
and he looks down at my crotch and he goes,
"Not good."
And he dismisses me.
- Not good enough.
- Yeah.
- Could be better.
- Sorry, but we need to make sure
that if a customer grinds on you,
you're prepared to not get a boner
and it seems you failed the test.
- It's a Chipotle.
And now for the boner test.
Seems like you passed the drug test,
the background check's all good.
Now I'm gonna see if I can give you a boner.
(laughing)
- I'm just gonna flick it a little bit.
- This is just a little thing I like to do with new hires.
- Yeah, contact those boners.
- Does it get to know you, game?
- I'll take a--
- I'm trying to give you a boner worth my mind.
- I'll take a steak burrito
and also, imagine, a huge pussy, huge pussy,
tiny butthole, two huge boobs, girl's mouth.
- Biggest boobs of all time.
- Two of the biggest balloon boobs you've ever seen.
Two giant planet Earths hanging off of a stick woman.
- Can you put, can you put--
- Can you put two huge Pam Anderson inflatable tits
on my burrito?
- Can you put a burrito-- - Oh, sorry, misspoke.
What's that in your pants?
- Can you wrap a boob in tinfoil for me?
- Yeah. (laughing)
- Can you wrap a boob in tinfoil?
- Can you put a vagina and a boob
as a combo into tinfoil and heat it up
and covered in nacho cheese and then give it to me.
There we go.
You lost and you're fired.
- Can I get a fuckable quesadilla?
- Yeah, can I get a thing of carnitas
that looks like a pussy? - Can I get a quesadilla
with a hole in the middle?
(laughing)
- Just a hole.
Size doesn't matter, any kind of hole.
You can do it with a hole.
- Hey, John, you want anything?
You want anything, John?
Two holes, actually.
(laughing)
- And honestly, you know, it's--
- Yeah, what's the bathroom code?
(laughing)
- 80085.
I feel like quesadilla of all the foods
that you put on your dick would feel pretty nice.
- Quesadilla, we're nasty today, boys.
- Fresh off the fuckin' stove, dude.
- Fresh off the gun city.
- We're gross, man.
- I thought you were talking about us.
I thought you were talking about us being nasty.
I didn't know you were talking about quesadillas still.
- Why are we nasty?
Are you guys--
- We're nasty AF.
- I just took a sip of coffee, dude.
- Are you guys naughty today?
- Yeah.
- Oh, is the naughty episode.
- Are we naughty and horny?
- Ugh, Christ.
What's wrong with me?
I'm having dirty thoughts.
- It's 'cause we know we're gonna see each other
in a few weeks.
- Would it have to be a seafood quesadilla?
- It's building up sexual tension.
It's starting to charge up.
- I'd like to see food and then fuck it.
The food.
Yeah, I'm on the F food diet.
I F food and then I eat it.
- That's what that new octopus documentary was about.
A guy saw a calamari, he got a thing of calamari
at Olive Garden, he got too horny
and he had to go fuck an octopus.
- Calamari's a squid, so that kind of
- No. - If you sew six calamaris
together, that's a pretty good pussy.
- You sew six of anything together.
- That's true, yeah, that's a really good point.
- As long as you put it in the right shape, it's fine.
- I would say the worst thing that feels like
it could be a fleshlight but would not be a good one
is a slinky.
- Yeah, what about a bucket of ice water?
- A bucket of ice water, well, I guess there's a hole
- Yeah, and it's filled with wetness.
- There's a hole in water.
- That's true.
I guess I could just kind of fuck a pond, I feel like.
If I got like a--
- I'd have to be a bog for me.
- Well, a bog will be thicker for sure.
- Yeah.
- A bog is gonna have some heft to it.
You're gonna feel some resistance.
How about a frozen lake?
- What about a scoby?
- A hole in a frozen lake?
- Yeah, like an ice fisher's hole.
- Like a scoby from kombucha.
- Shower dough starter.
I feel like that would be okay.
- That might be, we might be onto something there.
- I think that's what sourdough starter is.
I think it's like a guy fucks flour.
- You have to start it.
You have to start it up.
- It's alive 'cause you cum in it.
- Yeah, you gave it life.
- You gave it, yeah.
You need that to eat the,
you need something in there for the yeast to eat.
- Something has to eat your disgusting cum.
- Scientists in a lab being like,
we're trying to generate light,
we're trying to create life in a lab,
and they're just cumming onto various chemicals.
(laughing)
- No, they accidentally came all over the lab.
- That's how Dr. Frankenstein brought the monster to life
is he just came in him and then jump started him.
- It'd be kinda sexy to watch Sourdough Starter
eat your comb up.
(laughing)
Be kinda hot.
- We're getting too nasty now.
(laughing)
We're getting too nasty with it.
- Isn't this the mailbag episode?
Why are we doing this?
- Let's start over.
- Why the fuck are we doing this?
- Let's start the whole episode over right now.
- Just start the podcast over.
- All right, hi guys, welcome.
This is the first episode of a new podcast
where we read about lists online.
This is a podcast called "Guys We Fucked"
This is a podcast called...
Sourdough starters that air come
This is called the nasty little...
Panera Bread on Market Street
It's like, uh, the say, it's like "Guys We Fucked"
but it's just "Things We Fucked"
*laughter*
Uh, bagel...
That is the male equivalent of that show
Yeah, exactly, the male equivalent of that show
is "Things We Fucked" in half of the episodes
Stuff We Fucked
*laughter*
in the memory foam mattress.
- Yeah, the guy just like,
they start the episode and he's like,
"Yeah, so I fucked a pile of dirt again,
third time this week."
- You know what, when your dick touches loam,
it's a whole new experience.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I was trying to wean myself off of fucking things,
but I saw this amazing tree stump
when I was walking down the street
and I just couldn't help myself.
- Men are disgusting, dude.
Women on the other hand, they only fuck vegetables.
- Yeah, that's true.
- As God intended.
- Vegetables and animals.
- Yeah.
- Well, an animal's a vegetable.
- That's true.
- Okay, okay.
- Is a scoby an animal?
- Scoby-do.
(laughing)
He's an animal.
- Well, I mean, a scoby is technically living.
- He's not an animal 'cause he can talk.
- Let me--
- He's a human, technically.
- Is a scoby living?
- Yeah, let me look this up.
- I don't think it's living.
symbiotic culture of bacteria and yeast so things only live if they have eyes the
bacteria is alive well we can't go for human space is like bacteria and she I
don't would you look up a scobey look up a scobey right now can I look up scobey
bikini let's go be that up scobey bikini oh there's a haunted there's a haunted
pond it's a scobey look exactly it's go be looks exactly like a white woman's
vagina like exactly now that I look at it I mean it looks like four pieces of ham
stacked together like sitting in applesauce yeah with question is would
you fuck it yeah dude that looks really good that looks like real that looks
like it would I don't know why we I haven't done that before you know I'm
sure I'm sure there'd be health benefits it's got probiotics in it - fucking it
Yeah, the health benefits is you get to cum and you can't say hey you can't say that about pussy
That's right
Ain't no probiotics in pussy
Pussy gives me headaches
It's like Splenda
That's why you gotta fuck Scoby
Scoby, oh my god
This kinda looks like there's cum on it
Here wait, let me send you guys one
This one has a hole in it already
This one's pre-hold
Yeah, okay
You don't even have to go down to the kitchen
when your parents are asleep and put the hole in it this one's pretty would you
would you get a disease from fucking scoby do you think this is I mean just a
normalist no you probably just get a cool you probably would that's probably
like how your gut health super well it's like you know that you know that that
for champo store it's like the guys like I dropped I was cooking chicken without
my pants on and I dropped a chicken breast and it hit my penis and now my
penis is completely red and inflamed yeah and it was like what are you talking
about post a picture of the chicken and you post a picture of the chicken it
just has a big pussy shaped hole in it yeah I think that's what happened with
this one I just sent you it kind of looks like a like a like a pancake yeah
it's like a pancake designed for fucking it's like yeah you know how a
fleshlight is supposed to look like a flashlight so it's conspicuous yeah this
is supposed to look like a pancake yeah it's secretly for you to fuck yeah come
inside yeah so why people say life sees that I do you know full of yeah why do
you have a plate with a pancake on the side of your bed like oh yeah worried
that I might get hungry in the middle of the night yeah I love breakfast in bed
yeah breakfast in bed exactly meanwhile you're yeah cut to 3 a.m. you're fucking
screaming scoby at the top of my wife and accidentally saying scoby there's a
there's a different type of well that's a different type of kombucha it's called
June so if you're looking for a if you're looking for a shut up you fucking nerd
just shut up you bitch no shut up you shut up you shut up that would be
embarrassing you said it me really just if you you know if you said like toilet
paper roll while you're fucking your wife you know she's like what yeah I
I don't know. It's just I'm just doing a prank on you.
Wet wet wet toilet paper roll.
Ah fuck.
I mean Barbara.
Yeah.
Which is also not your name.
Oh fuck. I forgot that's what I named
the wet toilet paper roll that I go to the bathroom and fuck all the time.
Oh yeah. Whoops.
Hole in the top of the shampoo bottle.
Oh god.
Alberto V05.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- Alright, so we got a mailbag for ya.
- It's a mailbag.
(laughing)
- Did you say yours?
- No, Cameron, no more.
- Your socks.
(laughing)
- No more Stuff We Fucked.
- No, we're not listening to Stuff We Fucked anymore.
You're listening to the podcast called Mailbag.
- Stuff We Fucked comes out next week.
It's just gonna be me and two guys that I met at the bus.
(laughing)
- Just talking about mostly stuff on the bus.
- Yeah, bus driver.
(laughter)
- The hole in the seatbelt latch.
- Yeah.
- The little square hole.
- Ladies purse.
- Gatorade.
- There's no disgusting either, just listing things.
- Yeah.
- It's like, how long were you on that bus, dude?
This is a two and a half hour episode.
- Holy shit, how did they get two and a,
they're not even making any more episodes after this.
They said everything.
- Each other.
- It's every part of the bus.
- God damn.
(laughing)
- All right.
- All right, so we got some letters.
- We got some letters.
- Yeah, so we got letter everyone.
- You guys sent them in, thousands.
- We asked for them last week.
- And we only picked the best ones.
- We picked the cream of the crop.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
- Now cream on the crop, now that's something
that we could now.
- That's fuck ass coping.
- That's something I fucked.
- How about cream on the crap?
- Whoa.
- Cream of the crop, okay.
- Is that a good idea?
- That's a good idea.
- It's not a good idea at all.
- No.
fuck a crap to fuck a crap is sublime
bhagavad-gita yeah all right who wants to who wants to read one first I'll go
first if you guys all right yeah go ahead mm-hmm okay uh this is a short one
it's to Patrick oh yeah and it's from me and really quick it's a Patrick will you
marry me look I looked at common law marriage in New Hampshire and no no not
common love legally we can't get married why is that interesting gay marriage is
still not legal in New Hampshire it was it no it was no they legalized it pretty
quick after it got legal well great news I live in New York City so it's coming
in two weeks anyway. I just got diagnosed with breast. Me and Patrick already got
married. Yeah. That's not, oh, in what state? Massachusetts. Main Massachusetts.
The main state Massachusetts. The main part of Massachusetts. In Newburyport.
Yeah, the main area. Yeah. Well, mainly Massachusetts. A few other states.
Mainly burgers in Central Square. I'm gonna be honest, this ruins a couple of the other
questions. Yeah, now Caleb it's interesting that you chose to read that one first
because I got I got one sent actually to my personal email which is weird because
it was also addressed to to Patrick but it says, "Patrick what is the full
description of your penis? Do you have a little p-man or a giant brute? What is
the hex code of the color of your thingy? Is your wick wide or long, is your wick
wide and long or short and thin like a hair clipping? Will you let me touch your
special downstairs fellow and that's also from Caleb Pitts. Oh. It seems like Caleb
is doubling down on... As Popeye once said, "I am what I am." And I am in love with
Patrick. So let's go through these questions one by one that Caleb is
asking you, Patrick. Okay. What is the full description of your penis? Full
description... Give me the dirty details. Normal is way too vague. No, it's
It's very normal if you Google image search of it.
Normal is doing nothing for me down there right now.
Can you at least make it hot?
It's my, it's my, I have the stick.
It's my turn to speak.
Can you just whisper?
Oh, you have a stick?
A stick, okay, so that's the description.
There's some detail.
Yeah.
It's right here, that's my stick.
Alright, well let's, do you have a little p-man or a giant brute?
Well, I'm telling, I didn't finish with the first one.
Okay, well you clearly don't have a good answer for the first one, so let's keep this, let's
move forward.
Google search penis and the first result that's my penis.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- I'm not gonna Google it 'cause I know it by memory.
That is pretty disappointing.
What's the hex code?
- I didn't say it was a pointing.
- What's the hex code of the color?
- Hex code of the color is 00000F.
- Okay, so that's just a very dark gray.
- Yeah.
- Almost black, barely.
- Is F a rating?
- It looks like when you boil pork.
- It looks like when you boil a penis.
- Yeah, pretty much.
- Yeah.
- It looks like boiled pork.
Then you go to, if you've ever been to Hot Pot.
- Yeah, I love Hot Pot.
- Yeah, so imagine just what all the meat looks like there.
- All of it?
- And I do all of the meat, even the shrimp.
- Imagine Jim Gaffigan at Hot Pot, right?
(laughing)
Yeah, that'd be pretty.
♪ Hot Pot ♪
- He would be like, "Wow."
words yeah yeah and then they yell at him in Chinese these meats look like
Patrick's penis that's what he would do if you describe your penis as a long pig
or a short pig short pig the short pig you heard it here yep are you gonna let
Caleb touch it no what if it's for a video if it's it depends what if we're
making what if you're starring in a day by what if we make you a star of jackass
for okay and that's one of the pranks I've been thinking about this what do
you think we'd get sued if we just made jackass for cuz they're never gonna do
it aren't they weren't they are making it they're in production we okay
jackass five or we could beat them to four and then sue them when the movie
(laughing)
- Payday. - That's a good idea.
- That's a pretty good idea. - That is not a bad idea.
- Yeah.
- Maybe we do that when you guys come to New York.
- Maybe we'll just make a five minute video.
- Five minute movie called Jackass 4.
And then when Jackass 4 comes out.
- And it's just Caleb touching my penis.
- Let's make a huge, we send them a cease and desist.
- This is actually a very good idea.
- All right, we're gonna do this.
- Send it on a Sullivan the Frog Enterprises letterhead.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- That's a good idea.
that's a plan okay all right Pat do you have it do you have a mailbag yeah did
you receive email I received a lot of emails I've received this one here it's
to Cameron it says hi Cameron this is your big cousin Reynaldo I am writing
today to address some of the nasty rumors you have said about me on your
little podcast no I am NOT a sex offender and no I'm not going to prom
with my little brother.
It disgusts me that you would say all this stuff
about your big cousin even though I'm only 17 years old.
When my mom died, you said you would be my best friend
and look out for me, and now you use me
like a puppet for comedy.
My question is, do you stand by your remarks?
- Yeah.
- Oh, you do. - You stand by them?
- Yeah, look. - Wow, that's bold.
- Wow.
I mean, Ray Naldo is way bigger than you.
- Yeah, he's like 10 feet tall.
- Doesn't he have a-- - He's really skinny, though.
He's got like matchstick arms and legs.
- But he also has a bat with a bunch of nails in it.
- Yeah, but he doesn't--
- And it's scaled to his size.
- He only uses it to play baseball, though.
- It's like a cricket bat.
- Mm-hmm.
- He just swings it.
- It's got a picture of a cricket engraved in it.
- Yeah, that's what I meant.
- Yeah, that's why we called him Reynaldo the Cricket
when we were growing up.
It was also 'cause he can only speak in cricket noises,
which is, I think, why he had to write me a letter
instead of calling me on the phone.
- Yeah.
- He sent it to my email too.
- I think he got confused.
- So bad he has a typing.
- Yeah, I think he might have been trying to use Siri
to say who he was sending it to.
- His little cricket mind.
- Yeah.
Yeah, no, I stand by those remarks.
You wanna come get me, Ronaldo, you come get me.
You know where I am.
- Oh my God.
Wow, this is the first beef. - Is Ronaldo single?
- He doesn't say.
- No, he went to prom with his little brother.
and he's in a committed relationship
with his little brother.
Okay. Oh my God.
I didn't know that.
I didn't know that was real.
Can you respond to the email?
Can you write it really quick, Pat?
Can you just click? Yeah.
Okay, and CC me on this also.
Okay.
Okay, can you send, okay, prom, P-R-O-M.
Hold on.
Okay, prom, P-R-O-M, dot, or period, I guess.
Yeah, you got that?
Yep.
All right, now, any room for a third?
Winky face, question mark.
okay send enter enter okay yeah all right so that's not cool now command space
okay yeah now now can now minecraft enter okay okay now login login with your
username and password okay okay now build a house now build a giant Mario
build a working gameboy yeah out of redstone that's done okay that was that's
huge yeah I did I learned that in Java Wow yes where's Java type of script oh
who an actor all right do you have any more questions about Rinaldo no no from
mailbag. Do I? Yeah, yeah, I got tons. Yeah. Uh, this next one is, uh, kind of a love line kind of thing.
This person says, uh, "Hello Cameron, Caleb, and Patrick. I need some relationship advice."
I like this already. "I recently met the woman of my dreams at a mutual friends party.
She's gorgeous, intelligent, hilarious, and has piercing blue eyes that convince you to do
incomprehensible evil. She's a great public speaker and has a killer sense of fashion,
although she often wears the same thing every day. Parentheses, "If it ain't broke, don't fix it."
She's quite popular, though she prefers to keep a low profile as she hates being recognized in public.
I love everything about her, from her obsession with graphic design (she even has her own logo)
to her tiny square mustache that sits square in the middle of her upper lip.
"My problem is this. I'm almost certain that this woman is Adolf Hitler, leader of the Third Reich.
With her being 131 years old and me being 22, I worry what people will say if we start going
steady. My question is, what age gap is acceptable in a relationship?" That's from Ezra.
What do you guys think?
It's a difficult question. If the woman's the one that's older, it's fine.
Okay. So I feel like you're fine then.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess that's fine.
- Yeah, I mean the Ezra Hitler.
I like the sound of that.
- Can we go back a little bit?
Yeah, the Hitler thing isn't bothering you guys?
- I mean, when you're in love, you're in love, right?
- Yeah, dude, who are we to say?
- Look, I don't know, I don't trust that name.
- You don't trust what, Ezra?
Whoa, somebody's anti-Semitic.
- No, no, no.
- What do you not trust about the name Ezra?
I don't understand.
- Well, I've been reading a lot of history lately,
and there's this guy.
- Yeah, Civil War history.
- Oh, now we're gonna give some relationship advice
to Patrick, there's this guy, okay.
- Ah, all right, okay.
- There's this guy, he's been teaching me a lot of things.
- Yeah, sounds good. - So he's your teacher?
- Yeah, I guess he's a teacher,
I guess you could call me an apt pupil or whatever.
- Ooh, Mitch, your pupil is nice and apt.
- Yeah, here's the problem, I'm also dating Hitlers.
Wow. Oh, so that's the issue you have here.
Yeah. That is awkward.
So, uh, Ezra says, "Keep away from my man."
Hitler's the rebound.
Mm-hmm.
[laughter]
I rebound with Hitler.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
So, you and Ezra are fighting for this woman's love.
This woman named Adolf Hitler.
[laughter]
Okay.
So, tell me what you like about her.
(laughing)
No, I'm actually just doing a joke.
I'm not dating Hitler.
- I think you might be.
- I think you just feel bad now.
- No, I just didn't want to say that on the show.
- I think you're covering up 'cause you know that
I'm also dating Hitler.
- You know Ezra's stronger than you.
- Yeah, one, I know Ezra's stronger than me,
and two, Caleb, I didn't want to have
a same-girl situation.
- Yeah, this is kind of the R. Kelly,
R. Kelly and Usher remix with T-Pain,
'cause there's three of us,
and I'm kind of the T-Pain,
you're clearly the R. Kelly,
and then Ezra's the Usher, 'cause he's the best singer.
- No, I'm Usher.
- You're not Usher, dude.
- I'm Usher. - Sing something.
- Sing something.
- Yeah! - Oh man, you're Gusher.
- You might-- - Yeah!
- When Hitler's around-- - Yeah, yeah!
- When Hitler's around, it's hard not to be a Gusher.
- Take that, rewind it back.
Usher got the beat to make your mama go (mimics whip)
- What?
He never says mama.
Yeah it does. Do you think, do you think Usher, do you think
Usher and Hitler would have been friends? No, do you think Hitler ever made a woman come?
No, never mind. Do you think he ever made a woman squirt?
Do you think Hitler ever made a woman squirt with his fingers?
Because I have doubts. It's certainly possible.
I think when he wrote the Sibian he squirted. True, that's a good point.
- There's a, I have this letter.
- We never answered the question
about what age gap is acceptable.
- Oh, it's fine.
- I would say, I think we've previously said on the podcast,
the only acceptable age gap is if you're dating
your identical twin and you guys were born
within 10 minutes of each other.
- Yep. - Yep.
- Otherwise, you're out of luck.
- Yep, so Ezra, back the fuck up.
- If you don't date your brother, you're grooming.
- All right, so I got--
- Get the hell out of here, Ezra.
- I have this, I got this one in the email.
Hey gang, long time listener, first time mailbagger.
I'm a huge fan of the show and I love all the jokes you guys do about having uncles or if
Squidward was combined with the Grinch.
I tell them to people all the time at work.
Just the other day I pulled this guy over for a traffic stop and walked up to him with
my hand on my gun.
He was sweating bullets, he totally thought I was gonna shoot him or something lol.
I asked him "Sir, are you aware you are sucking a crap like it's McDonalds?"
He didn't really laugh so I stuck a nail into his tire when I was walking back to my cruiser.
I'm pretty sure I heard him praying.
Anyway, I need some advice.
I just backed over my son's dog in the driveway about five minutes ago and I'm thinking of
abducting a homeless guy and dressing him in a super villain costume and telling my son
it was Dr. Dog Destroyer who crushed the dog.
I could set my son loose with my gun to hunt down the hobo or something.
My son's four by the way, he's a huge fan, I caught him eating his own shit one time.
Anyway, like I was saying, I need some advice.
Can you guys think of a better super villain name?
That's from the cool cop.
Yeah.
Better than Dr. Dog Destroyer?
Hobo with a shotgun.
That's pretty good, yeah.
K9. Hobo with a dog gun. Yeah, hobo with a dog gun. Yeah. You could go with something
kind of like all-purpose too. You could just call him like K9/11 doer.
Whoa, that's pretty good. K9/11 is pretty good, yeah. Yeah. That's a Jim Belushi movie. You could go with
something very, like catch-all and call him like Chaos or something and then you
could just kind of have him do any bad thing that happens. I've got a great
villain name yeah okay what if we just call him the pedophile mr. mr. to damn
pedophile I might be good what about dog Hitler Oh even better what about dog
Hitler yeah I'm listening I'm listening that was found the only woman that's
gonna make him break up with Adolf Hitler. Yeah all dogs go to heaven. That's true.
How about dogs? That's just a classic joke right there. Yeah I got one oh all
right we still go ahead. No I feel like I can't. Dog Hitler's gonna be as good as it
gets. What about Dr. Dog Hitler? Doctors, see that's, some people are just scared of
doctors, but some people are more scared of doctors than they are Hitler, you know?
Nowadays. I'm not, the thing is I'm not really scared of Hitler. I mean, yeah I
could take him one-on-one in a conversation. Yeah I would point out the
logical fallacies. Yeah I'm not so much scared as I am just kind of annoyed, you
know? Yeah he is kind of a, he's kind of annoying, he's kind of like a, he's a real
monkey on my back sometimes.
(laughing)
- All right, so this-- - Pat, you said
you have a question?
- Yeah, okay, this is an email I got.
It says, "Hello Potabat List, it is me, Jubio.
"How are you today?"
- Potabat List? - "My question is,
"can I kiss Caleb?
"I've always wanted to kiss him.
"Thank you, Jubio."
- Yeah, Jubio, no problem.
Yeah, that's fine. - Okay.
- I'm not Caleb, but I'm saying that's fine.
- Yeah, I think I'm fine with it, too.
- Anyone can kiss me.
Any, I'll say this much. - Oh, I got another one.
okay hello it is Jubio again can I receive Caleb's kiss this Sunday?
You're moving things a little fast yeah I was just about to say this goes for all
Mexicans you can kiss me. Oh I got it hold on I got another question. Legally you can
kiss me and I can't say no. Are these coming in in real time? Yeah he's emailing me right now.
Okay hello it's more like an instant messenger it seems. Hello it is Jubio once again yeah I am on
name okay that's where I got all my questions I don't know how you guys on
your sidekick yeah I'm using a my sidekick that's cool hello it is Jubio
once again Caleb can I stay at your house for 10 days I've been I've been
telling him to come visit me for a long time okay he can come visit me he can
stay on my couch he can fucking fuck my landlord I don't care come
Jubio that's all I ask all right that's good I'm glad we got all the
dubious questions. Yeah like I was saying any Mexican can kiss me I can't say no
I've talked to my lawyer about this I legally cannot refuse consent it's it's
part of an anti-racist. It's reparations for your front-facing comedy videos.
Exactly yeah yeah so you guys are you're in the clear I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm
gonna take it and I'm gonna like it so. All right. Nice I just I got an email
actually another one this is one is also addressed to to Caleb okay um I love
being a care of main character it says dear Caleb I wrote you but you still
ain't calling I left myself my pager on my home phone at the bottom I sent two
letters back in autumn you must not have got him there probably was a problem at
the post office or something this guy seems to rhyme a lot in his email which
is kind of interesting I think I might know who this is sometimes I scribble
address is too sloppy when I jotted him but anyways fuck it what's been up man
how's your daughter you have a daughter Caleb what I no comment okay my
girlfriend's pregnant - I'm about to be a father if I have a daughter guess what
I'm a call her I think he wants you to guess Oh Caleb I'm gonna name her Bonnie
disrespect funny I read about your uncle Ronnie - I'm sorry I had a friend kill
himself over some bitch who didn't want him. I know you probably hear this every
day but I'm your biggest fan. I even got the underground shit you did with scam. I
got a room full of your posters and your pictures man. I like the shit you did
with Raucus too. That shit was fat. What is- have you done stuff with these? Yeah
who is this? I haven't seen Raucus and so this guy is a really old fan. This is
back from when I used to write about basketball. Oh okay. Yeah that's all. This is one of your Reddit
- Friends?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Anyways, I hope you get this man.
Hit me back, just to chat, truly yours,
your biggest fan, this is Patrick.
- Yeah, I said I guessed.
I guessed it was Pat.
The thing is, Pat, I'm--
- I told you not at the beginning.
- I think you know I don't have a daughter.
And I think you don't have a daughter.
- Size 48 font, at the beginning of my email,
I said do not read this, it's for Caleb.
- Oh, I don't know why you sent it to my email then.
- He gets mixed up.
- Well, I blocked him from sending stuff
to my email a long time ago. Yeah. So just because he kept sending shit like that. He
sends rhyming poems about how much he likes what you used to do. If you don't appreciate
my fucking limericks then why am I here? Say one of your limericks right now. There once
was a man from Nantucket. What did he do? He fucked my ass. Yeah, little miss Tuffet
sat on a... fuck it and fucked...
Ayy, little miss fuck it sucked on a ducket and fucked my little titties
She sucked me!
Ayy, little miss suck me fucked a ducky
and I just went bucky
Ayy!
Oh! What the fuck?
Romeo and Juliet took two boobs and pooed in the toilet
and I... and I ate shit from a crap sandwich
Yeah!
Heyo!
my lyrics back nice man's back I'm very inspired by the Dice man with I would
love to see new dice Donald Trump is an orange piece of shit
hey oh I've spoken jewel now hey I smoke a jewel on stage now he has a cigarette
is one of those big like like magic the gathering mods yeah that has like it
yeah one that looks like it looks like a dragon's fucking yeah it looks like the
cover of dope smoker by sleep yeah yeah yeah just a giant bagpipe I have another
cyber question here right sorry to interrupt
thank you Pat that's very kind yeah I don't want to fuck up the rotation on my
podcast yeah then thanks buddy appreciate it number three is for Patrick
Not again. Real quick, just real quick, and don't think about this one too much. Do
you Patrick take Caleb as your lawfully wedded husband to have and to hold
through sickness and in health, in good times and bad, keeping yourself under him
as long as you both shall live? So I think the correct answer here would be I do.
Let me just say...
What was that? Did his audio just turn off?
Oh no, my microphone cut but what I was gonna say...
Well we'll take that as an I do.
Yeah, no, we actually have that. I think in the state of New York, if your microphone cuts out,
- No, no.
- It counts as a yes.
- No.
- Yeah, so.
- Well, I'm in New Hampshire,
so I don't know what the statute of limitations would be.
- Well, but the internet is in New York,
and you're on the internet right now.
- No, I think the internet's in Boston.
- The internet's based out of New York.
- Well, I mean, it kinda depends on what he was saying
when his microphone cut out.
- It actually doesn't depend at all.
- And we'll never know what I said, so.
- If you don't respond when someone asks you
to marry them, you have to.
- Yeah.
Yeah, it's, yeah.
- Yeah, you have to specifically opt out.
- Specifically the volume yes.
- Yeah.
- Well, no, we won't know what I said.
- I already know, 'cause I'm actually an expert read lipper,
and you said, you said yes, yes, yes a million times yes.
You had me at hello.
- No.
- Yeah, you did.
- I think I burped.
- No, you didn't burp.
- When I said that.
- I think I burped.
- I know what a burp looks like in the lips.
- I think every time that I was about to answer you,
I burped.
- Wrong, just so wrong.
Anyway, I guess that was--
- I drank a seltzer in--
- That was my question, you guys,
just one of you guys go ahead,
I'm gonna take some time.
- Okay, this is a question from I Love Funny123
that says, "What makes you guys go nuts in the bed?"
(laughing)
- Makes me go nuts in the bed.
- I feel like we talked about that
for the first 20 minutes of this episode.
- I think we already covered this, I Love Funny123.
- When my girl has sex with me.
- True. - Ooh.
- That makes me bust my nut, dude.
- Oh my God, when my girl is hot as hell.
- When my girl is one million feet tall.
when I nut I bust everywhere. When I nut I bust. Nust if you butt. You know what makes me
you know what makes me. Nust if you what the fuck I said nust if you butt. You know what
makes me go boom is when I kaboom. That's some real shit. I'm just imagining nuck if you
buck but now it's nust if you butt. Nust if you butt real shit. I like to think of the
bedroom as the battlefield I think the bedroom is the battlefield I am the I am
the axis forces and I make sure my girl knows and she's storming she's storming
that fucking that Casper mattress and I'm gonna put a bullet in her head I have a
lot of sand all over my bed so it looks like Normandy yeah we might yeah that's
me that's my me and my girls favorite fucking role play is the beaches of
Normandy that's right me I'm a I'm a I'm a German soldier named Hans sitting on a
sitting on a turret and I'm killing all her friends but she makes it to me and
she sticks her knife in me oh I'm saying right in my heart yeah yeah yeah I'm
hunkering down in her trench yeah I'm one of the guys who gets shot in the in
the water. Well I do I hire a lot of extras for the roleplay. I hire about 4,000 older men. I try to hire
I try to hire actual veterans who survived storming the beaches of Normandy for full effect. So I have
anywhere between one and two hundred old men walking through my living room as fast as they can and just
pretending to keel over and die. Some of them actually do it. We don't check until I come and
And then, yeah, she makes it to the end,
and she saves, we call it saving my privates.
- Saving my privates, Ryan.
- Yeah.
- It's pretty fun.
- I got an email here.
It says, "Good evening, gentlemen.
"I represent a powerful corporation
"that shall for now remain anonymous.
"I will give you a hint, however.
"Steve Jobs, my illustrious company sees great potential
in your Sullivan the Frog Enterprises LLC,
and would like to extend an offer to purchase your business.
You would, of course, be able to continue
producing your podcast,
albeit with a vastly increased budget.
You would have the bottomless coffers
of the Steve Jobs Coins for Cancer Fund at your disposal.
The possibilities would be endless,
and I look forward to hearing what you would add
to the show with such wealth.
Sincerely, IEATA Big Poop.
- Huh.
- IEATA Big Poop?
and looks like the first few letters are the nationals
are i_d_a_ t_a_ be a big poop
notes in the info you're trying to get the turn to make him say he's a big
yeah i thought you're just
notices that's his name
now here it is it's as isaac
eric
it adam
thomas adam big poop
is that what i got a lot of twice
uh... it's that's that's that
yet crazy parents in my life and i think i think i think i think i think i think
It must be one of those things where he like moved from China to America and he just had
to do like an American name and he had a bunch.
He also had the same problem in China where he had five different first names.
He was going through immigration and they just threw a dart at a dart board five times.
They threw five darts.
And they threw one of the darts twice and it hit the same one.
Yeah, what, I guess, should we accept this offer
to be bought out by this mysterious company?
What would we--
- I'll never sell out 'cause it's not your problem.
- What could we add with that kind of money?
- I don't wanna add anything.
I think the show's perfect.
- Yeah, I think I'll never sell out and never be bought.
- You don't want to buy a big jacuzzi
to all record inside of?
- Okay, hold on.
- I don't know, I mean, I guess if we could like--
- Hold on now.
- I guess if we could like--
- You didn't tell me there was gonna be a jacuzzi.
- I'm saying we could buy anything.
We have Steve Jobs coins.
- Are you saying there's a possibility
we could do forced plastic surgery on Patrick?
(laughing)
- No.
- I mean, it says the possibilities will be endless.
- Yeah, but I think it ends in jacuzzi.
- No, 'cause what's the, so we haven't unveiled this yet,
but if we get to Patreon of 15,000,
like that's our next goal after 10,
we're basically gonna install a vagina
between Pat's butthole and his balls.
So, just so he has the option open.
- Yeah.
- And then after that, we were gonna get a jacuzzi.
So basically we could accelerate what we call phase three.
- Yeah.
- We're gonna get, Patrick's penis is gonna be zip off-able
like those pants that can turn into shorts.
- That's true.
- I have those pants and it's not,
you're not gonna want that.
- It'll also be reversible,
but the reverse side is gonna be really scary.
It's gonna be like the inside of a penis.
- A sharp piece of glass is what it looks like
when you turn it inside out.
- So I don't know, I mean, I guess we could use some like,
- We could get like,
- Round two funding, you know?
- Lunch or something.
- I was also thinking maybe we could bring the podcast
into the cloud.
- Yeah, I like that idea.
- Let's circle back to what Cameron said.
- Cameron, you're not making any sense.
- We, the possibilities are endless and we go get lunch.
- I'm the ideas man here, okay?
- Since when?
- I'm thinking that we-- - You've never come up
with an idea in your life.
- I'm in the-- - You're the inventions guy,
Cameron is the ideas guy.
- No. - Yes.
- I'm kinda like the-- - You're the guy.
- I'm kinda like the Patrick Swayze type.
- I'm actually all three of those.
- I'm kinda like the Patrick Swayze type
'cause I'm dying of cancer.
- None of you are guys, I'm the only guy.
Basically, I was thinking maybe we we we scale this thing up second podcast. Yeah
Stuff we fuck. Oh, yeah, we'll start a network. We'll start the soul network we fuck network
SWF network right and we take on we're taking on Legion of skanks
Right. So firstly we're absorbing crooked media as well. Yeah, we're taking crooked media and we get you do and you are gonna be so excited
to see our yearly company
Nerf gun game. Yeah, that's oh my god
We're doing a
We're I would love to see that we're taking a cereal cereal. It's gotten bore. It's boring
Nobody cares about Bo Bergdahl or some fucking guy with a D and they don't even talk about cereal
And we're gonna be it's gonna be only every season's gonna be about the new cereals. It's new cereals
Do you think we could do you think we could pay Michelle Obama to do a guest spot?
Listen, I don't think there's any amount of money that Michelle Obama would be paid you can pay Michelle Obama
To do anything especially concerning spots, okay?
Yeah, I heard Michelle Obama was doing a set at the laugh. Actually Obama is a prostitute now. She's been no
No, she's not she'll suck and fuck for the right. Oh, no, that's not true. That's not true
I know cuz I had sex I believe a million times in a day. That's not true. It only cost me
40 quarters I'm serious I think $10 I think you I think you may be confused
nope no Michelle Obama 6'9" 230 pounds pure woman I don't know about that
she's gonna she's gonna make it in the WNBA I believe it no this is my funding
in my love. I'm serious. I have a question. Yeah. Okay. Hey boys, I was wondering how
you guys deal with being bullied. Okay, this is a sincere one. That's kind of sad.
Recently at school, kids have been making fun of me a lot, calling me ugly, fat, and
pedophile. They sometimes kick me and throw rocks at me in the hall. And the
The other day Jessica wouldn't even let me have a bite of her sandwich at lunch, even
though I told her I forgot mine at home.
It's getting so bad I might not have anyone to ask to the fall dance.
If that happens, I might as well just give up and look for a different job.
Do you boys have any advice on dealing with bullies?
Love Patrick."
Different Patrick.
I don't know, it says Patrick in New Hampshire.
It's a different guy.
Okay.
How do you know guys do this to me? How do you know? Yeah, how do you know?
I I'm going through so much and you all all you well, yeah, I mean clearly you're being bullied. Yeah. No
Yeah, you can also Pat. You don't have to go through this whole rigmarole of
Writing us an email. We're your friends. Just call us if you're having an issue at work. Yeah, I mean
Every day I get betrayed by you
Betrayed by me. I'm not the one bullying you. It seems like there's no bully the other kids
You're doing a you're doing a hit piece. There's not a hit piece
No, you're a dirty donkey
Stop it. No, you stop it. I
Do not like this you like you like it. You don't like being called out. I don't like why do you sign your
Why do you sign your emails? Hey, buddy, don't sign your emails. That's right
Yeah, that's right
As far as bullies just just
Every day I deal with two bullies every day. It's you yeah your parents. Yeah, you cuz you're twice the size of a normal person
Yeah, I'm huge
Yeah, I
know
Yeah, you're not in the way that you're thinking
That makes no sense. Mm-hmm. Yeah, I got him. Let's get there. No, there's no air horns. Uh-huh. There's air horns
I have another question here.
This is from DarkSatanTheHater.
It says, "I hate you, I hate you, I hate your stupid show.
"Every single word you say makes me want to vomit barf
"out of my mouth.
"It makes me want to vacuum up every last drop of semen
"I've ever spilled back into my penis hole.
"That's how unpleasurable it is.
"I think that Patrick is a fat freak
"and Caleb is a bald bastard and Cameron is a gay girl.
"I have listened to all of your episodes
"and I have never smiled once.
"Your jokes are like nails on a chalkboard on the wall of a prison where I'm serving a life sentence.
"Why I'm serving a life sentence isn't important.
"The point is, I hate you, I hate you, I fucking hate you.
"When are you releasing the first 31 episodes?"
- Everyone's so mean to me. - Probably never.
- Everybody's so mean to me. - We should do a $100 Patreon tier.
- If you're in jail, you get them for free. - If you're in jail, yeah.
It's kind of a new program we're doing.
Yeah, we're trying to drive people in prison to suicide
Because by listening dirty scum so we're gonna give you the worst 31 episodes
Hopefully you're gonna hang yourself with a bed sheet and then we can be through with you the world could be through with you
Yeah, that's what happened to jeffrey epstein. He had the third first 31 episodes. That's true. I'm down hillary clinton wanted them so bad
Yeah
Pat do you have another question? Yeah, I do. I have one here from voodoo chip
- Okay, love them.
- This one says, "Hello, I'm a huge fan and a long time,
"and I love your Twitch stream.
"When you guys started Chappo Trap Host,
"did you expect it to get as big as it is now?"
- Yes, we knew from the very beginning.
- Yeah, we knew this was gonna be huge.
- We knew so much that we started it
and then we just, we moved on to the next project.
We let those other jokers take over.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- We let them do it.
- Those guys are my brother's friends,
and I just, when they told him, I was like,
Hey, do you guys want to run some fucking podcast?
Yeah, can you guys just don't fuck it up?
Yeah, and they've done all right.
Not great.
There's different things.
For example, things that I would do differently.
For example, I would have made it more of a
Republican conservative kind of podcast.
(laughing)
That's what I would have done.
But you know what?
It's not my baby anymore, it's theirs.
So I respect those fucking commie homos
to do whatever they want.
- Yeah, they have their thing, we have our thing.
- Yeah, you know.
- And they're kind of exactly diametrically opposed.
You know, they're good and we are evil.
I think that's, we've kind of set that up
as the dynamic there.
- But thank you for the question, Voodoo Chip.
- Thank you for the question.
- The question.
(laughs)
Thank you for the question.
- Thank you for all the questions.
This is one, this is a short one.
- If it's to me, please don't read it.
- No, it's not.
This is, what's the scariest thing you can think of?
That's from The Terrifier.
(laughter)
I don't know if we should tell him.
No, I, you know what?
I have an idea.
I have an idea. The scariest thing
I can think of is a
bunch of ice cream.
A ton of ice cream and a huge
huge blowjob. Yeah, a blowjob from the sloppiest mouth I've ever seen. A blowjob from the ice
cream man. Yeah, and all of the Halloween candy in the world. Uh huh. Yeah, so, Terrifier.
I hope that's it. That's right.
*laughing*
Terrifier, I hope you don't do that.
It's the hardest I've laughed in like at least a month.
*laughing*
Okay, alright, what's the next question?
Cameron, do you have another question?
Yeah, yeah, no, I got one.
This is from Curious Carl.
"Kid!"
[laughter]
"Would you rather
fly a plane or sail a boat?
The plane has a Playstation 2
built into the control panel, but the boat
has every GameCube game ever made.
If you choose the plane, there's a 10% chance
9/11 happens, but if you choose
the boat, there's a 20% chance 9/11 happens.
happens but you're on a boat so it doesn't matter also if you're on the
boat you get to sing I'm on a boat and T-Pain is there T-Pain is also on the
plane but you can't sing with him and if the plane does get hijacked he'll start
crying Oh boat then are you kidding yeah I'd be I'd be on the boat I would I
would I would pitch my you guys don't want to see T-Pain cry I want you to
pitch a parody song of I'm on a boat to T-Pain yeah called I got a goat I got
Well if he's on the boat you can't pitch anything to him you can only sing with him.
You can't talk to him.
So I'll just start singing I Got a Goat.
Can you pitch to any other people on the boat?
There's nobody else on the boat.
So it's just you and T-Pain you can't pitch?
Yep.
No pitches allowed.
The plane is filled with a lot of people.
Not even a cartoon.
Mr. Wonderful's on the plane too.
Is Mr. Wonderful on the boat?
Because if Mr. Wonderful's on the boat there's going to be a big problem.
Mr. Wonderful's not on the boat.
I believe it was his wife that did the thing on the boat.
Is his wife on the boat?
No, his wife is...
Does she drive?
Wait, no, because T-Pain and I are going to be singing, so who's driving the boat?
Let me message Curious Carl right now.
Okay, thank you.
Curious Carl, who will be driving the boat?
Oh, he says me.
So I think Curious Carl will be the one.
Can you ask him if he's a good boat pilot?
Are you a good boat pilot?
Wait, hold on.
Chris Carl is their last name wonderful?
One question at a time for this guy.
He says...
Are you a girl?
No.
Is your last name wonderful?
Yes.
Oh, shit.
Okay, I'm taking the plane.
Yeah?
Because I don't want to die on the boat and also 9/11 to happen.
I'm gonna...
You'd rather just get it over with in one fell swoop?
But I think...
I feel like you guys are thinking about the place...
I think there's probably a 100% chance.
Which is better, PS2 or GameCube?
I'm going with the boat because of GameCube.
- Yeah, I guess I'm-- - And that's my final offer.
- 'Cause at least, if I'm dying on both,
I'm gonna enjoy my last couple moments
playing Super Monkey Ball.
- Yeah, if I'm on the plane,
I can jump off before 9/11 happens.
- If I'm on the boat, I can swim the shore.
- Yeah, the boat is in a pool, so there's--
(laughing)
- Oh, we're fine then.
If it's just sitting in a pool, it's just a house.
- But it's in a pool of acid.
- Oh, then I'm not taking the boat.
I'm getting on the plane.
- The plane's made of acid. - I'm still gonna go
in the boat.
plane is a fire then I'm getting back on the boat the boat is in the plane okay
then I'm gonna get on the plane cuz I'm one layer closer to the outside of the
plane look I'm just trying to get close to God do I have a parachute you do on
the boat but not on the plane on the okay on the plane do I have a pair of
of shoes yes I can make that work okay Pat is in conversation with somebody off
screen it's a baby he's talking to a baby I'm not talking to a baby you literally
are talking to a baby you're talking to one of your students yeah nope all right
what's uh what's the last question here we had is anyone else have any yeah we
a
six rank the bugs by attractiveness that's from anonymous okay ladybug
but now ladybug all of them are men the booze no what do you know what about a
butterfly the Pamela Anderson bug is Imrata a bug yes possible right yeah
yeah I don't we don't know I guess so let's just say she is so probably lady
bug in the nimrata and then that's all the books yeah that's that's all the bugs
all right give me your other question here's one uh this is from oh it's from
the little gamer oh it says and access entered greetings losers i have
successfully hacked into your podcast mailbag episode there's nothing you can
do now in precisely 24 hours every piece of personal data you have will be leaked
onto the little web and if you're stupid enough to still be reading this your
voice has been scanned and will be synthesized into a deep fake confessing
to the heretofore unsolved Zodiac murders and the planning of various terrorist
acts. Any last words? Oh I probably shouldn't have read that.
Now that I think about it. Why'd you read that? I didn't hear it so I'm safe. I don't really
care about my personal information. Well I've been thinking of getting rid of it
anyway. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah I've been thinking of selling it. Yeah to the highest bidder.
But it's I mean, you know, I wouldn't I wouldn't have drawn a lot of money. So it's fine little gamer
You have it the little web can have it. I don't really care very much
Yeah, I honestly I don't give a crap. Yeah. I don't yeah, you know what fuck you little gay
You don't have power over us anymore. That's right. You know control. I defeated you in that battle
Yeah, yeah, I got to record the little game. Yeah the little battle
Not since the little wars you guys remember that spin-off series. I do remember that it was it was hard and it took so much editing
- Yeah.
- Okay, here's my last question.
This is for me.
Caleb Pitts, do you take Patrick
as your lawfully wedded wife
- No.
- And having to hold through sickness
- And in health in good times and bad?
It's my question, Patrick.
- You can't.
- Type down, you're already too uppity.
And in about 30 seconds I can legally hit you.
In health, in good times and bad,
keeping yourself unto him as long as you both shall live.
I'm gonna go with I do.
And in the state of New York City, only half of the parties have to agree.
So...
Cameron, it looks like we...
Welcome to my life, Patrick Pitts.
Ooh, initials are PP.
No.
Initials are PP. So, you're gay also.
This sucks, crap.
Yeah, it does suck for you. But I'm married.
And I got something to brag about at Thanksgiving this year.
I'm pissed off.
Yeah, I have a guy wife who lives in New Hampshire.
And he hates me and he said no, but we're married
So the last letter we got is actually a physical letter that somebody mailed to my house
Which is pretty exciting kind of weird, but Wow it's our first like actual fan mail. That's huge
The return address on it actually says
Kumail Nanjiani
nine three nine thousand three hundred and thirty six Civic Center Drive, Beverly Hills, California
90210 3604
USA so I'm not sure who this is from but
I'm just gonna go ahead and open it up
Let's see what the boy sent us. Yeah, hopefully it's something nice. Oh
That's weird. There's
There's some kind of like
Powder in here. Oh, no, that's just the language he speaks
It's a letter that just says ha ha
Guys, I don't
I don't feel so good over zoom fine yeah I breathe this crap in every day
all right thanks for listening is it your first time your first time doing
this oh I just had a loogie I'm fine again they say you don't get high your
first time oh and he says he said I'd send you some confetti that's very nice
of him. Wow thanks for the good wishes. Thanks for all the great letters everybody. Cam,
Lail, Nanjani, and a big thank you to the TerriFyre. Better luck next time. Bye everyone.
Bye thank you for listening.
[BLANK_AUDIO]