you're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
- Podcasts for the mindless.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Woo!
(howling)
- All right, Patrick is muted for this episode.
I just turned his microphone off.
- Okay.
- Yeah, if you guys can hear a tiny murmuring
in the background, that's Patrick.
- No, it's our pet mouse.
- That's our pet mouse we just bought.
We bought him from a gay pride mouse store
where they only stay so nice that are married to get the most trying to talk
again shut up now
was that
the city's it's going to be a little bit
you're my name you're off i turned your volume all the way down
no
stops on such this stop you i'm gonna i'm gonna fight you again you
patrick's good i'd tickle
alright i'm turning paths volume back up a little bit are you gonna be good
are you have a little bit of on the alternative gradually over the episode
if you act if you act nice this guy's so lazy can't even hold the microphone don't
touch that dude don't take the fucking idiot away I think cost a hundred
thousand dollars take it from this thing is like you you oh you will owe me all
the money in your bank account you will rue which is like $20 it's true Patrick
gets the patreon check and he goes okay I have to go buy 3,000 subs from 7-eleven
right now and keep them in my fridge you don't even have 7-eleven around here do
you we do it's just up there it's very far away you don't do it no I go to the
bodega boy yeah uh-huh the New Hampshire born me again the New Hampshire it's so
it's bird bird a guard a girl bird a guard a girl yeah I'm going down to the
bodega they sell like live bait no not at the one we've been going to they
don't sell live bait there they don't they sell any of these that's cool they
sell their DVD selection it's awesome it's just all just movies I've never
heard of the transporter 10 yeah it's like one of them's called like the most
wonderful time the coolest action yeah the craziest thing ever a movie must
watch they had this the Forrest Gump soundtrack there a week ago
whoa yeah now it's gone that's just a movie the CD Oh the soundtrack to Forrest
Gump and you know you plug it in or you put it in the CD player and play it it's
just the audio from the entire movie.
(laughing)
- That'd be great.
- East of Soundtrack.
- Yeah.
- We've been walking around.
- Yeah, we took a car tour.
- We have a car tour video coming soon.
- Yeah, once Patrick edits it.
- He did a tour of my car.
- Yeah, it's a tour of Caleb's car.
- You can see the inside of it.
- It's about 10 seconds long.
- Yeah, I'm trying to sell my car.
- This is the outside, this is the inside.
- Should I tell the story of what happened
or should we just wait till--
- I mean, no, that's just what happened on the other end.
- Wait, what happened?
the the thing thing with the cones thing with the cream yeah yeah you got too much
ice cream not I'm gonna have to subscribe to the premium yeah you
subscribe to the premium to find that shit here the cone story it is like one
of the only things we did we really did today it is the only thing dude yeah no
like I went to the dino I've talked we went to Red Arrow yeah I've talked about
how boring it was growing up here a lot I can't imagine it did yeah seems fucking
awful yeah no like I've talked about how boring it was growing up here and now
that you've actually seen where everything happened yeah fucking nothing
happened here at least in North Carolina we had like animals we could go to the
beach or the zoo or something yeah here it's just like I don't even fucking know
it's too far away to walk let me tell you what here you're in the zoo yeah
yeah yeah because they're animals they got animals everywhere addicted to
heroin a human and live in the park they live in a park and they're scum yeah
scum I'm gonna get rid of all the poor people we're making another video where
we go around we're gonna wake up social experiment yeah people not waking them
up we're making them do the ice bucket challenge to raise awareness for ALS
yeah yeah you know it's so funny have you ever seen videos of people being
Narcan'd yeah have you seen the one have you seen the one where the guy gets up
and he's like "you ruined my high!" and punches the guy that Narcan'd him in the nuts.
So good.
Awesome.
For some reason everyone that gets Narcan'd gets mad.
Cause adrenaline.
Yeah.
You're injected with fucking like speed.
I thought it was like smelling salts.
It'd be funny if you get Narcan'd and like immediately you wake up and you just try to
fuck the person that Narcan'd you.
Cause of the adrenaline.
That's just the first thing that everyone does.
You get a giant boner.
Yeah everyone who gets-
Yeah hey man thanks for the boner.
Yeah that's part of-
And that's even fucking helping me out with it!
That's part of Narcan training is you have to cover your crotch and back away really quickly
because they're going to try to suck you off.
How about Narcan Sam?
Okay.
Yeah.
I don't remember what Toucan Sam sounds like.
He's like British, right?
He has a British voice and he has three nephews.
He's a great uncle.
All uncles are great.
Wait a second.
Uncle Sam.
Wow.
Oh my god.
Multicolored on the beak.
Joseph's multicolored coat.
Stripes.
Have you seen the redesign of Toucan Sam?
I think I did.
Is he a girl now?
So with the fucking CalArt style?
Yeah.
Toucan Tim?
Let's talk about reboots again.
No.
They're rebooting cereal.
No!
Yeah, and I was like, dude.
Just make a new Toucan cereal.
Yeah.
You guys learned that about me, and now you're never gonna get it about you.
That I don't like, that I'm annoyed by rebooting movies.
It's just a funny thing to be annoyed by.
Yeah, well, I don't know.
Me, personally, I'm annoyed by it.
That's just one of the Twitter things to be mad about.
I get mad about that too.
That's just a thing where if you're on a certain part of Twitter, you get mad about rebooting movies,
about healthcare, and about kids who say the N-word getting put in jail.
Those are the three things you have to be mad about if you're on a specific subset of Left Twitter.
I get mad about women stealing our jobs.
Women stealing all of our jobs.
I'm trying to go back to the GMC factory.
Guess what? They only hire women now.
Girls make cars factory.
Man.
(laughing)
That's fucking right.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
Man, at least we used to have fucking Jupiter.
They took that from us too.
Yeah man.
Now women are going to college and Jupiter.
Oh my god.
It's insane.
Fucking annoying dude.
It's so annoying.
Girls can't go to Jupiter.
They have to go to college to get more knowledge.
Yeah, 'cause they need it.
Girls go to--
Boys are too smart, that's why they go to Jupiter.
We go to Jupiter to get more stupidity
'cause we're too smart.
We donate the knowledge to the girls.
Girls go to the sun to--
Oh, let me donate some knowledge.
(laughing)
Real quick.
Just saying that to a homeless guy.
Listen, listen buddy, come here. I'm gonna kick you. I'm gonna donate you some knowledge.
This is the best change you'll ever get, alright? Change your life.
You gotta space in that empty guitar case for some knowledge.
'Cause I'm about to kick it to you, player.
What was that band, the guy?
HEDPE. They're sick, dude. It stands for Higher Education Planet Earth.
Oh my god. Boss.
Yeah, there's like the video of them doing like a COVID live show so there's no one in the uh
there's no one in the audience and he's just going like "make some fucking noise"
and it's just completely silent and he's just going like like "9/11 was a fraud you have to go
on the internet that's the only place that can teach you the truth and I do not eat pussy that's just facts"
That's the best part of that video. So cool. We need to start a band soon. We got it. We will start a band.
I got it I have my guitar. Can we start a band in that vein like a truth band a truth teller
band? The truth sayers we could be called the truth sayers movement. The truth sayers sooth
tellers. No because if we're gonna be a band like that we have to have an acronym. That's
true yeah. Yeah. PISS. But it has to be something like like if you say it's an acronym that's
a word but it's spelled wrong. Acquiring supernatural spirits. Yeah if it's like yeah that's pretty
good. That's a good one. But yeah it should be something where yeah it spells out like
big dick if you do all the first letters so and but they're called like badass
instruments bad even given dudes ideas crazy changing crazy kids change get
changing kids changing Krypton changing yeah yeah yeah yeah we got a reference
comic book reference changing Krypton changing Krypton Clark Kent yeah Oh
Oh, changing Kirk, yeah.
Even dude's ID is Clark Kent.
Yeah, there's an ampersand, it's and Clark Kent.
Because Clark Kent, one of us is Clark Kent.
That'd be a cool alias to take on.
Yeah, MC Clark Kent.
Yeah.
But the C is a change symbol.
Yeah, whoa.
That's the C with the line.
I've been thinking about becoming a professional.
Yeah, making sense, MC.
Whoa, oh my god.
MC making sense.
what if we're called
yeah i don't have any m_c_i_'s that you have a nonsense right yeah they're going
to be a little in the public was like a some nonsense
i love what's ok mcmc is pretty good i think
mcmc making change making sense
wall of the uh...
about p_o_d_
puddle of dead
some bad idea right without uh...
fuck puddle of drug tenacious d
t
What about P-STAT?
P-STAT could be good.
What about G-SPOT?
G-SPOT?
G-SPOT, gorilla?
Gorilla.
What if it spells out money?
It's like mindfulness over--
Newgrounds.
Nefarious--
Evil.
Evil--
Yakuza.
Yeah, dude.
Yeah.
Pretty much, it's always like--
It's always like something--
Be an anti-Yakuza band.
Yeah.
Yo, just straight up the top.
Yakuza did 9/11.
Everything links back to the Yakuza.
It's true, man.
Yeah.
Start with Pearl Harbor.
Yeah. And if you come to my house, I will not call you an Uber home.
[laughter]
That's just facts.
I will not make you come.
And I close my eyes when I have sex.
I close my eyes and I count to ten.
I wear a mask during sex.
I wear a paper bag over my head.
Jim Carrey's face on my face.
We have to have a bassist who wears a paper bag with eye holes cut out.
So it's a Jim Carrey mask and then I put the mask over it.
So when you take the first one off you're like, "Oh, that's funny."
I'm having sex with Jim Carrey.
DJ Grinch Ventura.
Oh my god.
That's our DJ.
DJ Grinch Ventura.
And then he takes the mask off and it's Travis Barker.
- Oh. - Yeah.
- We should, oh my God, we should do a Travis Barker remix
of the show, of the podcast. - He would remix the show.
He would do an album with us, a split.
- Like a drum, like when he used to put like drums
over lollipop by Lil Wayne.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- God, that was so sick.
It was so cool. - We gotta get
Scott Storch on board.
- We gotta get, someone's gotta hop on this Scott Storch beat.
- Yeah. - Dude, he's looking good, man.
- We're gonna be the ones to do it.
We're gonna be the ones to hop on a Scott Storch beat.
This is for the first person to do it in 10 years.
I'm ready.
I'm sure you could get a deal with Scott Storch.
Yeah.
I'm so fucking tired now.
Are you?
I don't know why.
I was fine earlier today.
I think it was the skating.
You want to sip my bowl?
Maybe.
You want to sip my bully stick?
I'll sip the bowl.
I have more in there.
I'll just go get my own.
Go get your own.
Yeah, we can hold it down for a minute.
Yeah, we got this.
Yeah.
Don't try to take your mic with you.
[SCREAMING]
Oh, no.
What's with Tron?
No!
I think Patrick died.
No one's telling a story that goes nowhere!
Where is he?
I was gonna drink some of yours and then I remembered that we were doing a pandemic.
We're doing a pandemic.
I remember that we did the pandemic.
I literally, I'm sleeping in your house.
It's different. We're social, we're distanced from you.
We spend two hours a day kissing.
No.
Yeah, we do.
Yeah.
I kiss Cameron more than you.
You're not social distanced from me. We keep fighting.
Yeah.
That's true.
We spent five hours in a car with the windows rolled up.
Pat just thinks people are going to be mad that we're in the same room.
Yeah.
We spent so much time planning this and we all got tested.
People are going to be mad.
It doesn't matter if we post the results that say negative, people will be mad at us.
Yeah, let's get some hate for Patrick going.
No, that's the one thing that will just be bad for me.
That's the one thing you can handle?
One thing I cannot handle is hate.
hate. No, I only love love. Yo, MCMC one thing I cannot handle is hate. Yo, all the haters
out there, you're nothing but a bully. All the haters out there, I hate hate. I wish
we could play that track. Yeah dude, I wish we could. One of the best. Can we at least
say, we could say that I'm on my Grant shit? Yeah. Oh yeah. There's that one, so we found
a rap we've just been going into our home just watching home town white rap
rappers yeah that we grew up with been talking about like white rappers from our
hometown I found a we found one that's just about found a a it's on like reverb
nation yeah and it's about it's a song about bullies yeah you're nothing but a
bully and then they have can we at least play the kids part like at it where it's
chopped probably not yeah probably not yeah some somebody's gonna yeah I feel
bad enough like they like laughing at the song yeah there's a part where it's
like a ten-year-old kid like rapping but they just like it's like he records like
two words at a time and then they stitch it together so it's just like the middle
of every word it just jumps to another word
(mimics rap music)
- It's funny that that's just a genre of rap.
- Yeah. - Tech Nine,
and like, Yellow Wolf, Busta Rhymes,
all these guys, their entire thing is like,
I can rap 50 syllables a minute.
- Yeah.
(mimics rap music)
- It's like, dude, that's sick, man.
- Yeah, he's always like, "Yabba-dabba-doo."
- Awesome.
- God, that song's so good, though.
- It's like all of those--
- It's so funny how homophobic that song is, too.
- Yeah.
- The one with the five-year-old rapping.
- Oh, yeah.
(laughs)
- It's pretty sick, yeah.
Drop some words in there. Oh, he dropped some hard F's. Some hard F's. Yeah, strong F's.
Strong. Thrown and peppered into that one. Yep. Yeah. Oh my god. It needed some sort of perspective.
Wait, he says he's gonna send midgets to someone's house? Yeah, he's like, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna send, he also has a speech impediment.
Yeah. I'm going to send midgets to your mommy's house. Yeah. It's awesome. It's great.
But all those like fast rapping guys, they, all of their songs just sound, like to my mom, that's what like all rap sounds like.
Yeah, it's just like she turns on 50 cent and she's like
Is this Kanye West just here's Tasmanian devil, yeah, my mom thinks that
Every rapper that comes on the radio she thinks it's a jar rule. Really? Yeah, actually my mom thought Mambo number five was a jar rule song
Yeah, she was like yeah a little bit of mud that's that's his voice
So sick. God damn, Ja Rule's gonna drop a fucking Mambo No. 5 remix this year.
Mambo No. 6 dude. Yeah. He has one more woman. Yeah. It's so, Lubega's German.
Makes sense. Mambo No. 5 exists because like some German guy was like, "I'm going to bring
back swing music but rapping!" And it worked. It fucking worked. It was so ridiculous. Just
German, the German guys, German people are just like,
it was such a weird--
- There's something that pushes them to do,
to go above and beyond. - Do terrible things.
- Yeah.
- German people just do constantly terrible things.
- There's something uber about them.
- Yeah.
- It's crazy.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's funny, like the two big German songs
in the past like 20 years,
or it's "Mamba No. 5" and "Ich bin Gummibär."
- Yeah.
- Remember that song?
♪ I'm a gummy bear ♪
you know did you know that the gummy bear the 3d gummy bear was actually he was
real accused of a John Travolta yeah I talked about that I was like three times
on the podcast yeah so fucking funny though he spent all his money
it was like money laundering there were like helicopter trips that were paid for
with the gummy bear movies like 3d budget and it was supposed to be his
whole family except for his kid that died his kid died yeah John Travolta's
autistic son died. Yo, my apologies to Mr. Travolta, man. I had no idea. There's conspiracies
that Scientology killed him, but I won't go into this. No, dude, he's just in space. They
put him in space. They just put him in space. He's having fun up there. Oh, his wife just
died. John Travolta's wife died too. Really? Yeah. She's in space too. No, they just sent
him to space. It's okay to joke about it because they're not dead, they're in space. That's true.
Yeah. It's true. They're dancing in a circle with lizards or something. They're doing whatever
Scientologists do. They're doing what drinking out of cups. They're smoking a USB stick and
listening to drinking out of cups. Drinking out of cups is what Scientologist Heaven looks like.
Yes. I used to work with this guy. Drinking out of cups inspired L. Ron Hubbard.
I used to work with this guy doing when I was did like glass shower door installation and his name
was Rocco and he was. His life was so modern. It was most modern life. He's just like Italian
dude from New York. Yeah. Who would just always tell me these stories about well one thing is he
he would also sing all the time.
So like we'd be like going down the street
and he would just sing all the signs
that we would drive by.
He'd go, "Lada dee, lada doo,
"McDonald's on Market Street, ooh ooh ooh,
"I love their hamburgers, ooh ooh ooh."
And he would just like try to make me laugh.
- Yeah, that's the way to get a guy to laugh.
- He would tell me stories, he'd be like,
he'd be like, "New York in the '70s was unbelievable.
"For example, I saw John Travolta
"on the set of Saturday Night Fever
getting a blowjob from a man
*laughter*
I'm here to confirm to you
and I never went to the media
because a man's business is his own
and you know I may not agree with that
lifestyle but you know he's earned it
he's one of the greatest actors ever
he's the best. He's one of the fucking best Italians
we got. I mean oh my god. He's one of the fucking
best. If he wants to get his stew
got sucked by another fucking
man. Another fucking fairy
on Saturday Night Fever
set of his dancing movie. More fucking power to him. He's like yeah I mean you know you asked me I
I knew he's gay second I saw those pants. A little too tight you know. Oh he got. A little too tight
to be hiding a straight penis in those pants I'll say that much. Hey look hey you you wear those
pants you wear those white pants you better you better be taking them off for another man. Yeah
dude he rocked though. Yeah well it's in his name. Rocco. Yeah. I told you. Uh-huh. Rocco. I said it's
in his name. Oh yeah he does rock. Yeah. He rockos. You have to, you have to live up to
your name. He would have to live up to your name. He was like a late life
weed smoker. Oh yeah he did it late? Yeah he's one of those guys where like one
time we were like working on this shower door and we like chipped off like a
little piece of it which is like almost never happens it's all tempered glass
usually if a piece chips the entire thing explodes so if you chip off a piece you
know there's enough like tension in the glass yeah someone like knocks it it
it explode yeah I was like he like chipped it and he was like okay Caleb be very
very quiet I accidentally got insanely high before I came to work I'm about to
freak out we're not gonna tell the lady we're just gonna put the shower on the
fucking shit shower door on the shower and so just guarantee that lady's shower
door just fucking exploded the first time she opened it oh my god that's so
awesome he rocks it yeah he was the fucking that's so funny just destroying
somebody's shower yeah do I yeah god that's awesome
big meaty hands he claimed one time he got impaled by what my piece of glass
when he's working in New York in the 70s and 80s he was like yeah we did the the
glass for Rodney Dangerfield's comedy club Dangerfield's put in a huge glass
panel I'm bringing it down fucking Fifth Avenue right this fucking knucklehead
Mexican I'm working with drops his side giant shard goes right to my stomach
then he was like I still have the scar and he showed me like it looked like he
fucking got like a paper cut like there's no way a fucking giant piece of
glass went all the way through it survived it cuz he was digesting the
glass when I went in there you see me yeah he does have superpowers I forget
Yeah, it's true, but I yeah, I have superpowers if you're Italian in New York in the 70s you had superpowers. He's perfect
Hey, trust me. I I don't need superpowers. I'm Italian. They're real superheroes
The real super Italians are real superhero is John Gotti. Yeah, may he fucking rest in peace
Go to Nostra
First time I met you I just got out of seeing Gotti. Yeah, and I didn't remember meeting you at all. Yeah
Yeah, I was just like this guy's probably not
to talk to this guy again. He just didn't say anything. I met Ben that same time. Yeah. And
Neil was like, oh yeah, you got to meet Ben. So I was like, okay, I'm meeting Ben and this
other guy. No, Kieran was there too. Oh yeah, it was you and Kieran. Yeah. Kieran, the really
tall dude. Turns out I was right about one of you. I miss Kieran. I got to see. I don't
think I've ever seen him since. I don't know, I don't even know who he is. Actually, he came
to Muyo one time, talked about his penis. He did a circumcision story. Yeah, that was funny.
Yeah, no, he's super funny.
We have a list, yeah?
Yeah, we have a list.
Yeah?
Yeah.
We have a list, yeah?
Top 10 things that will blow your mind.
Blow you.
Top 10 things.
God, I can't get over that fucking guy, the Italian guy just being there.
I saw George Ravolt again.
He's getting his fucking pecca fucking licked on the set of a movie.
He's getting paid overtime for this.
(laughter)
- They're doing this all over the country.
It's not just movie sets.
They're doing this in McDonald's.
People are getting paid overtime.
(laughter)
- And it was just between him fucking singing songs
about Best Buy and shit.
Just him like, "Circuit City, Circuit City."
Yeah, so John Travolta's a homo.
(laughter)
- John Travolta is so gay.
- He rocks.
- John Travolta does rock.
- Top 10 things that'll blow your mind by pet sounds.
you know that feeling of incredible amazement which makes you stop in wonder
that's the description of it
i know number one
music baby
without music life would be a mistake
frederick nicha
that's not even that's just a comment
there's no like continuation just nisha commented that
that's sick dude
oh no wait no that's a good yeah
that's pet sounds
- The music blows my mind every time I listen to it, man.
- Yeah.
- There's an incredible elation you get.
- The fact that we can trap little guys
that sing inside of an earbud.
- I know, it's impressive.
- Little guys can sing in your computer
and they have one.
- They can put spirits into an AirPod now.
- It's impressive, dude.
- Yeah, they don't even have to use ghost technology.
- Yeah, they don't even need wires.
- They use ectoplasm.
- They don't even need wires to sing music.
- They shoot ghost slime from the little amputee stubs
on the end of the AirPod.
flies into your computer and it haunts the music and brings it back to you.
And you can get different musicians in your phone whenever you want. You don't
even have to download the musicians. Their AI consciousnesses have been
uploaded and they're singing the song every time you listen to it. Can't wait
till that actually happens. That will happen in one year. I can't wait till I go in there and meet
Katy Perry. Yeah. And I dress her with my mind. Yeah. I can't wait to crawl into my phone's
lightning port and hang out with the gorillas and their cartoon world. Whoa.
I would love to go to the plastic beach.
Inside the gorill- a Vice video, inside the gorillas cartoon world.
[laughter]
We sent a journalist to go to the cartoon lighthouse
and talk to the gorillas in their hometown.
You won't believe how they laughed.
[laughter]
Yeah, well we're gonna smoke weed with gorillas today.
Right.
Right, well, I'm gonna smoke weed with a cartoon.
They sent Matty Matheson to make the gorillas a fuckin'
I'm gonna make him a great steak sandwich!
I'm gonna make a Spongebob burrito!
I'm making a great steak sandwich with Spongebob square pants today!
It's gonna be awesome!
I made Squidward nachos.
You know, Squidward, in Canada we don't have nachos like this.
It's okay, I have a Grateful Dead shirt on.
What's he saying that before doing it?
I don't know.
It's okay, I have a Grateful Dead shirt on.
I don't know. It's just I'm talking about Maddie Matheson.
You're doing a scary version of Maddie Matheson.
You're doing a scary, scary thing.
I'm Maddie Matheson and I'm gonna scare your kids!
Doing scary Matheson.
Yeah, that's Maddie's scary sin.
I'm gonna getcha!
Oh, I'm gonna getcha!
Maddie Maskeson.
I'm smokin'!
Somebody stop me!
It's kinda the same.
It kinda is doing the mask when I think about it.
Number two, nature will blow your mind.
your mind oh my god yeah yeah I'm an animal lover I am animal lover and
animals are nature that's why I love nature nature is lovely you need to love
nature we won't be alive we need trees grass brushes to help us breath that's
from the wolf lover some true-ass shit that is some we will be dead will be not
alive be duh what we will be the we will be the we will be the any other good
comments on their path that's the only one close enough to the computer read it
It's poor engineering by us.
Yeah.
Seeing an eagle fly, hearing the ocean roar, feeling the crisp cool air of autumn.
Whoa, is that, did you write that?
That's a poem.
Let's do some nature poems right now.
Nature poems?
Yeah.
Two, two big rocks.
Two giant birds.
Two giant breasts.
Flying like an eagle.
Sinking, soaring through the sky.
The ocean was filled with, the ocean was filled with a beautiful fish.
A fish called love.
I'm looking at the door open yeah I opened it with my mind
okay yeah you think someone just came into your apartment right now yeah
okay I don't know yet I know what she's doing to soaring birds flying like an
eagle they can't have sex until they're married one of they have no idea what
Pro-choice means life begins at conception.
That's my poem.
- Two little ants, so happy because they don't know
who Donald Trump is.
- That's right.
- Two ants who voted for Donald Trump, one giant shoe.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
- Did you guys ever set an ant on fire?
- That's the scariest six story, six sentence story.
- The six story sentence.
- You ever set an ant on fire?
- The six stories in one sentence.
I went to the store and the library and I saw a movie
and I played a video game and my brother was sick
And I played another video game.
That's six stories in one sentence.
That is pretty sad.
Did you guys ever set ants on fire?
No.
I tried to but it didn't work.
We didn't grow up like you,
like Sid from fucking Toy Story.
I just said I tried to.
Oh, hey, come on.
I tried to.
You interrupted me to say that I didn't do it.
I tried to with a magnifying glass.
You're speaking over PSE right now, person of Cameron.
And person of Caleb, come on.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
I was a...
Person of C name.
I was like trying to with a magnifying glass when I was growing up and my grandma caught me and I thought she was gonna be mad
And she's like Jesus Christ. Why are you using a magnifying glass? Here just use my lighter
She just started lighting ants on fire. God. Yeah, it's pretty cool, man. I never did that. Yeah, I burnt a $10 bill one time
I love to destroy life. I burnt a $10 bill cuz I wanted to see what happened money means nothing to this
Joker esque madman. He's on the fourth grade and I stole $10 from my parents and I went in the basement
Damn, you burned your parents ten dollars?
Yep.
He burned his parents to the ground.
I did.
Yeah.
I burned, yeah.
God damn.
God damn, dude.
That shit's scary.
It lit up- money lights up really fast.
That's why they make it like that.
They do it on purpose so you can lose it easily and get it burned and it's gone.
It's actually one of the bigger conspiracies going on in the world.
When the money burns it respawns and dies in the president's pocket.
Yeah.
Money is uh, money is made out of cotton, right?
I wouldn't know.
Who just went ffff-
He did.
Oh, okay, I couldn't tell.
Sorry, I'm eating some delicious air out of my mouth.
Yeah, you're eating air.
I made a big mistake.
In sixth grade, my science teacher did like a thing where he told us like, "Oh, like paper can't be magnetic," or something like that.
And then he like somehow made like a dollar magnetic.
Scary.
And then he was like, oh, then the next day he came in.
Man, that guy had telekinetics.
The next day we came in, then he explained to us that money is made out of like a cloth
paper mix and not just paper. Yeah, it has something else. It's not just paper. Then why didn't you ask the questions?
And it was supposed to be a lesson about how we're supposed to always ask questions when doing science.
Wow, but he just went off on like just like it just felt psycho. Wow
Yeah, it's a funny thing about being a teacher is you can just make up like anything
Yeah, I mean like you can just talk about whatever you want for an hour
It doesn't mean you do spend 10 years working on the book and then you just be like yeah science reminds me of my wife
Did your science teacher ever set a big fire on the like on the table?
No
my science teacher like poured
Some like hand sanitizer and like mix with something else on the table and set a big fire on the table and they would do that
Every year that's sick. It's so cool
The cats coming after you. Oh, dude. He's coming
Wow
Seriously a throwback to have the cats running around
He's talking yeah, yeah, he's hurting dude. He wants yeah, he wants to be pet. I'm not pet him
Thank you having this gross little fucking fucking putting his stinky shit on my disgusting ass
This is empty balls. That's the grossest ass alive. Yeah, I gotta wipe his butt. I think I'm gonna wipe your butt
Is he putting his cashew in your face? He doesn't he doesn't have a cashier his penis looks like a cashew
No, he doesn't taste like one pet. No, that's why
That's why it's the nickname for his penis to you. Yeah
Let me see it I call his penis a cashew because it's as delicious as a cash. It's very expensive per pound
Number three number three is life life. I'm blown my mind life be crazy. That's damn true
Mm-hmm. Someone says don't think about it then do it
I love to do life. I of course have discovered the answer to the age-old
question what is the meaning of life but if I told you you'd be as wise as I am
and I can't have that knowledge is power muhahaha that's from Brit girl
damn fucking plankton that was a scary comment yeah it was terrifying
mwahaha I don't like that I added this item as I was surprised it was not here
at number one already.
What is more amazing and mind-blowing than life?
That life.
- That is so true.
- I'm about that life.
- From Blue Dog Girl.
- Blue Dog Girl.
Is the dog blue or is the girl blue?
- Blue is a dog.
- Blue Waffle Girl.
- That's you.
- You were the Blue Waffle Girl.
- Okay, now we're getting somewhere.
Blue Waffle Girl.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, all right.
- To me, it looked pretty,
it kind of just looked like she took a shower.
(laughing)
The Blue Waffle.
You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
when I seen it. Yeah, you know, it's just like, uh, it's accessorized. Yeah, Cameron saw it and he said,
"It looks like mine." It's true. It did, yeah. Cameron said, "That looks like my mouth."
Yeah, that's right. Let's go! I think actually that might have been the first vagina I ever saw.
Me too. And I was like, "That's terrifying, like, that is so scary, like, thank God they don't all
look like that." And then I saw one in porn and I was like, "They kind of all kind of look like that."
(laughing)
- It kinda all looked a little weird.
- What was the, someone convinced like a senator
in like Baltimore to talk about it at like a meeting?
- It was you.
- It was you?
- No, you were the senator.
- I was the senator and I talked to the president.
- And you didn't need any convincing.
- No, he said, "Let me tell you about my favorite movie."
It's actually a picture called Blue Waffle.
- I held up a graphic of it and I pointed to it
on a slideshow.
- Yeah.
- I zoomed in more and more.
- You should change our logo to that.
We should change the podcast about list logo to the blue waffle.
Yeah.
Blue waffle logo.
We should change it to a picture of a literal blue waffle and say try to google this image.
I think somebody did that for dodgeball at my high school.
I think they tried to name their team blue waffle.
That's funny.
Yeah.
Or trying to get one over on the teachers and naming my dodgeball team Pornhub.
They tried to name the dodgeball team.
They'll never know what this means.
Team Ass Fuck.
Yeah.
Got you bitch.
They had a name that was kinda-
Team that one video where the two girls drink poop out of a cup.
Yeah.
Hee hee hee hee hee.
Team collateral murder video from WikiLeaks.
No what the situa- I think it was somebody tried to name something like kinda like, like
it was an acronym that spelled out, oh no they weren't allowed to, they were gonna wear shirts
and then if they like stood close enough together it would just say like gay or something and
then they got in trouble for it.
That's pretty fucking funny.
Yeah it was pretty funny.
they were about to get really close to guys to make it happen so they were
about to get in trouble for it and then like they brought it up to the assistant
principal principal was walking down the hall
their heart their heart don't remember what the situation was all I remember
this close threat level on their hood was going up somebody snitched on a team
that was named og mud bone and our assistant principal had to look up a
picture of OG Mudbone in her office.
- Dude, he had the thing with him, dude.
- He had, you know he had that thing.
- Can we pause for one second, so I can pee?
- Yeah.
- Nice.
- Wow.
- And we're back.
- Weiner just got amped.
Caleb weinered out.
- I just emptied my weiner.
- He just tinkled out his thing.
- I did what men do.
I did what's natural.
I did it like I do on the Discovery Channel.
I went to Patrick's bathroom,
I put a bunch of weiner stuff in the bathtub,
and I flushed it.
- No.
- Yeah, buddy.
- You didn't flush my bathtub.
I you why'd you put a flusher on it? He didn't want me flushing it. You're not supposed to touch that
I'm gonna crap in your bathtub
Don't I'm going to yeah, don't you know that flusher thing on the bathtub?
It takes everything from the bathroom and puts it right into Patrick's trough
That's how he loads his trough with oats. He's a repeat in a trough. Yeah. Yeah baseball games nice. I
Went to it like I think I have like once I went to this like when I was a kid my dad took us like
Like a speedway like a like a knockoff NASCAR thing. Yeah, and do a speedway gas station
You watch all the cars come in. He's like, well, this is NASCAR. It's just the tracks, but this is where they do the pit stop
And now realizing my dad was just there to like gamble. Yeah, like one of the fucking crank heads
it was driving, but there was no barrier between
the people in the audience and the cars and
They were going insanely fast on like a dirt road and also it was completely allowed for you to walk
Onto the racetrack in the middle of the race and to get to the middle part if you wanted to be there cuz that's cool, too
So like we were just like like he was like, okay. All right boys. Wait, wait, okay
Run run run run run and we just ran before we got destroyed by
Fucking that would blow your mind more than fucking science. Oh, man, that is science. That is science. It's Frogger science
number four is science by the way yeah Patrick did that thing again where he
says it talks about the thing before we say it you're so dumb dude I gotta
figure out how to don't take your shoes off and also scroll down don't use your
foot on the keyboard that's disgusting that's so gross I was gonna eat my pizza
off that later well too bad you can't disgust me now you can't eat my pizza
science blows my mind sometimes so I fucking love science like when you when
you throw it when you uh move a water bottle around and you create a tornado
yeah that's some cool-ass shit if you're running you throw a ball up in the air
it can land on you yeah that's true if you shoot your cousin with a gun he dies
yeah centrifugal force yeah the bullet will kill your cousin yeah that's my
experiment my experiment is experimenting with my carowack who shot his wife in
the head no that's a William Williams yeah we know okay there's bill burrows
burrows hey what's he doing he's trying to eat my cable cable evil cat he's not
evil he's the nice one why was he trying to eat my fucking cable cuz he's bored
it's not my fault it's it's evil to be bored it's a sin
be a little bit idle hands idle hands belong to the devil's stuff bill burrows
Bill Burroughs. I shot my fucking wife! Everyone is at lunch, they're naked!
Look at all these fucking people, they're all fucking naked! I hate it!
We just watched a Bill Burr video. We should note. That's why our impressions are so choice right now.
So fucking choice. We watched a Bill Burr at Hampton Beach.
Yeah, which is again, kind of just what we did with your hometown.
It's true. Except way worse camera work.
Mm-hmm. Yeah. Whoops. Oopsie. Probably should just record. Oops. Pat Bilber style.
You would have walked around. Can you imagine if you did that Hampton Beach video? I would get my
ass kicked if someone heard me talking about it. You'd be like yeah it's a fucking I mean look at
that you see that wrapper for that candy bar? I used to eat that all the time. It's pretty weird right?
Yeah. Candy's weird. Candy's weird. Alright I'm ready to go home. Alright yeah I mean there's
There's not really much here.
You guys want to go 40 minutes away to look at a building?
Look at an ugly brick?
Oh yeah, sure.
Let's go, Pat.
Yeah.
You guys would love it.
Do you guys want to see the bank where I deposited one dollar?
You would love that.
You would love that on the video.
I wouldn't want to be there for that.
You would.
No.
Yeah, you would.
You simply would.
Dude, I'm not simple.
You are simple.
You look like Simple Jack.
No.
Yeah.
Nah.
movie yeah it is I agree yeah that's the only offensive part yeah I hate
offensive movies dude piss me off that's your remake Tropic Thunder in cartoon
mm-hmm yeah with cartoon cats dog piss off Pat right wouldn't piss me off I'd
actually like it no you wouldn't I would like it no you'd be like um so this is a
thing oh yeah he puts a picture of your cats together and you'd be like so this
is a thing they're actually redoing the remaking Star Wars as a cartoon I would
like that yeah no you wouldn't I would like it you wouldn't like it I would
like it I would like it so much remaking Spongebob is a cartoon
is a thing so now that's a thing oh great yeah great you're gonna remake
Spongebob as a cartoon come on now no they would never they will never if they
remake a real life spongebob was a real life cartoon you will be sponge sponge
Bob square dick no have you ever seen that sponge don't say that don't say
that sponge not that's awful wash your mouth to go to the bathroom wash your
mouth out you wash it my mouth okay you wash my mouth I'm gonna come wash your
mouth how about that you you won't I'm gonna take you there you and I'm gonna
wash your mouth out with a bunch of Irish spring big no I have dr. Bronner's
No, you don't you might have dr. Pepper in your mouth
Global there's a shortage of dr. Pepper global elites that control the world. Dr. Pepper is one of them. Dr. Pepper
Dr. Pepper
Dude pepperage farms. Oh my god pepper spray. Dr. Pepper had to take red hot chili peppers
Not the RC Chili's peas
My friend pepper the pet boy friend pepper the pet boys the pep boys are part of the doctor
We look like the pepper boys. We don't look like the pet boys. Do we look them up?
I look at the way look like two pet boys. You look like a tire
That's not true, no, it's not but it is a little funny it is very funny. Yeah, it's pretty good. Come on. Yeah
Number six anime no number five humans
Yeah
He's looking at you right now
It's actually on purpose to kind of punctuate the point that they're making here
I said human stupidity of course who mang so mang stopping that II I once told my man my ethnicity Swedish
So I said I had a Nordic background, and he said oh, where's Nordea not in a sarcastic voice. It is very sad
Where is Nordea nobody fucking cares about like obviously nobody cares of yeah, you're gonna go up to someone say you're Nordic
right suck my ball if you're saying yeah go go back go back to Nordia you're not
wearing armor you're not no yeah right where's your braided beard yeah yeah but
then then the if you're so Nordic the white like the American Swedish guys who
are like descendant of Swedish and then they braid their beards that shit's
annoying oh it's a worst yeah liking guys Viking guys who were like I guys
are like yeah I love death metal and I'm a Viking and I weigh 86 pounds yeah yeah
sick dude. I look like Thor. Yeah. That's just some schlubby white guy. Kill yourself.
Yeah. Check it out guys I just got this silverware set where the forks look like
battle axes and the knives look like a carving figure head. Brother check this
out. It's a subreddit called nature is metal. I think you're gonna like this. You're
really gonna like this. Yeah. This is gonna blow your mind. You're gonna love this and
it's just like they just show. You know Vikings would often have up to four
13 year old wives and I come from a long line of if you see you see a scrawny
Viking guy like that you just have to pull a trunchbull and you got to throw
them by their beard yeah you gotta swing around like miss trunchbull by the beard
braids and then just chuck them yeah just chuck them into the ocean dude they'll
they'll find a slave crew it's a Viking funeral yeah I shoot a flaming arrow at
me yeah and but you are a flaming arrow yeah owned hey you're a red arrow yeah
No I'm not.
I've been getting really into pillaging lately.
That's what they say.
That's what those guys are like.
My beans from the Red Arrow Diner were delicious.
It really was an honor to eat Adam Sandler's beans.
That's his personal stash.
Yeah. Those are his beans.
There's a big warehouse behind the diner that's labeled
"Sandler's Beans".
Oh hey, I got your beans.
Oh, the beans are good in this store.
Here's your beans.
You got the beans in the store!
Adam Sandler's bean boutique. I love the beans. I have a bean over here. I'm gonna give you my beans.
We gotta get him back here dude. Yeah. We gotta get him back on the podcast.
Yeah. Get Adam Sandler. It's been a while. He keeps calling me dude. He's blowing up my shit.
He keeps beeping me. Yeah. He keeps calling me. He's asking me if I've been through.
He keeps abusing his privileges of having me in his contact list. Exactly. I'm like man if you're gonna
to call me this much I'm gonna lose your number. Listen, Sandman, I can't play
pickup basketball every day. I know you're always dressed for it. I know,
because you want to get better. You want to keep playing me so you can beat me
eventually. I'm gonna tell you what. Yeah, not gonna never gonna happen. Yeah, try
fucking- You're only gonna play one game a year so I can still beat you. That's right. Try playing with a
weighted vest on. That's how I got so good, so dunkable. It's easy for me to dunk a
basketball. I wore weighted sunglasses. I can see the ball from the from a court
away yeah yeah man I have sex with a weighted condom yeah man my penis grows
stronger I've been wearing a weighted a weighted hat this whole time so when I
take my hat off my hair goes straight up cool as hell it looks like guy from
Street Fighter. Maybe I should try a weighted head yeah I mean my hair grow back yeah it could
work wait weighted hair yeah weighted hair it calms people down it does have
Have you guys used a weighted blanket?
- No.
- My younger sibling has one and I tried it one time
and I just felt like I couldn't breathe.
- Yeah.
- Not nice. - If you're claustrophobic,
the weighted blanket's the worst thing.
- If you're extremely weak and brittle,
I can imagine it would hurt you.
- It doesn't hurt, it's just like,
I mean it's just like you're lying down
and there's stuff stacked on you.
Like you wouldn't wanna lie down
with a pile of books on you.
- I go to bed every night with a microwave on my head.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Dude, I'm training my sleep.
- I'm just comfortable that way, okay?
- Now, if you sleep with the weighted blanket--
- You're extremely strong in your dreams.
- Yeah, no, you sleep with a weighted blanket,
then when you have a nightmare and you sit straight up,
you're gonna be sitting up,
you're gonna be able to sit up really fast.
- That's right, yeah.
- You hear an intruder, you're out of bed and in a jiffy.
- Yeah.
- Oh man, imagine having an intruder in your house
with a weighted blanket.
- You could hit 'em with a weighted blanket.
- That's true.
- You can put it on them,
and then they fall asleep 'cause they're so comfortable.
- If you put it into a ball, the weighted blanket,
if it's heavy enough, you throw it.
- It would weigh 100 pounds.
- Yeah, 100 pound weighted blanket,
you throw that at someone's head,
snap their head off. Would you like to have like a million pound weighted
blanket? Yeah. It has to be something that can at least lift off of me. How much does that be?
Probably like five pounds. I think a normal blanket is five pounds. Five pound
blanket? Yeah. I don't think so. Like a down comforter? With like a duvet cover?
Absolutely. No, not five pounds. That's like insanely light. I would bet my life at five
pounds no I found Google had to Google down down how much is it down comforter
way have to me put your mic down for a second so you can type faster now how
much does a how much is a pound of feathers no not a blanket a down come
for a down comforter a blanket is not gonna do anything from five to thirty
pounds damn I'm a genius well that's perfect weighted blankets oh that's
weighted blankets yeah so a weighted blankets like five how much so how much
How much does a down comforter weigh?
Give me the fucking keyboard dude.
I don't even...
I'm bypassing the pain.
Come on.
Blanket weight, is there a maximum limit?
This is about weighted blankets Patrick.
This is not what we're talking about.
Selecting a weight for an adult's blanket.
I'm getting an adult blanket.
Cameron's blankie.
Dude, I got a blankie at my house.
50 pound weighted blanket.
How much does it down comfort away? What does it say?
You're so clean and cleaner. You're swirling to find the correct the first one first fucking one dumbass
First one nine pounds. Let me see it a queen size a blanket could never be nine pounds unless it was weighted
It says it's nine pounds. No, that's the box that it comes in. Yeah. No, no, it's not
Yeah, it is. I'm right. They ship it with a lot. You guys are heavily overestimating how much five pounds is yeah
Yeah, your your phone is like
A feather is zero pounds. Okay, no matter how many fucking feathers you put in a blanket. It's not gonna weigh five pounds
It's gonna be zero
You're stupid and you're wrong
The skin of the blanket might weigh half a pound. Wrong. Keep saying this if you have a full diaper
You bitch. You kept saying it. What are you doing DreamWorks face?
Because I'm happy and I'm correct, and I'm a hero for being right number six is anime
That will never blow your mind that would never blow my mind
Stupid Cameron yeah, I don't really care. I'm a stupid. I'm not a I've watched anime
I'm not an anime fan the only cool anime is that one where they it's like Hiroshima
Yeah, it's all of it in Vietnam with the
in their dust and stuff and like their eyeballs are getting melted.
Oh have you seen, it's called Violence Jack.
Ugh.
No, it's not like, the guy is named Violence Jack or something.
Oh god.
Ugh.
Those Japanese.
It's just like a gory, it's like one of the goriest animes.
I saw a video that was called the top 5 goriest animes.
It was in my recommended.
It's like when you're a kid and you search like goriest video game.
Yeah yeah.
Just cause you were like.
Yeah you see like a clip from Rikki-O.
Yeah I'm so fucking squeamish though.
I can't handle like any gore in movies anymore.
I've wrapped back around.
I can handle it as a kid.
There was a movie I watched, Revenge.
It was called Revenge.
They gave me, that made me actually nauseous recently.
This is the first time in a while that gores made me nauseous.
There's a scene where a guy steps on a big piece of glass and he has to reach inside
his foot to pull the glass out.
Like he has to put his fucking hand.
I felt the tingle in my balls hearing that.
I think we might have unlocked something then.
Yeah.
You might need to call Rocco.
Let's get back in some base.
Oh, hold up.
Wait.
his fucking balls when he heard about glass? He was a dude of me what that
glass did to me in 1978. Holy shit. Fifth Avenue headed to Dangerfield's, Rodney
Dangerfield's club by the way. Rodney's club. Rodney. Yeah, Rodney. We used to call him Rod
back then. Hot Rod. You should call him Rodney. Yeah. We would call him Mr. Rodney.
I saw some movie recently. We'd have to call him Mr. Dangerfield his highness. I actually didn't see a movie, just saw a clip from it.
We call him Crazy David. We call him Crazy David. Yeah, I actually didn't even see a movie, I just imagined something.
I saw a clip from a movie where a guy pulls a he like puts a rod in a guy's
Mouth and then just like pulls it until he like basically cuts most of like basically cuts his head in half
Uh-huh
It was like it made me want to go to the bathroom the only the thing the fucking the key behind the eye and saw that's
The worst thing for me. Yeah anything with the yeah, I
The finger me it's it's legs. Oh, have you seen it?
Is it hostile three where the guy gets up out of the chair and it cuts his Achilles?
and he like you can't we do like falls over it's broken leg broken leg stuff
really fucks me that's like like knees going backwards and shit yeah I can't
handle did you see the Gordon Hayward injury a couple years yeah I did I
watched that shit live and I screamed like fucking like home alone dude yeah
I was like so upstairs Jana was like downstairs doing homework or some shit
and I was like I'm gonna go upstairs watch the season opener and I watched it
I just went, "Ahhhh!"
And she was like, "What happened?
"Did you fucking, did something fall on your head?"
And I was like, "Some white guy on TV
"hurt his leg real bad."
(laughing)
So sad.
- Yeah, anime would never blow my mind.
Number seven, flight.
Flight's still kinda gay, like being on a plane.
- Say it's kinda gay?
- Kinda gets me.
- Oh, okay. - Kinda gets you?
- Flight's kinda gay.
- Flight's kinda gay. - It blows your mind.
- You know what, are you pretending to be a bird?
Homeboy.
(laughing)
You flying around like this.
- Yeah, a guy sitting on a plane,
flapping his arms. Oh you flying? Oh you like to fly Mr. Pilot? You flying to your boyfriend's house?
Oh yeah where you need to go to a guy's house? Yeah I'm flying to San Francisco.
Who you talking to on the radio? Hey who's that? Who's that waving those things around out there?
Oh look at those flags. What's he doing with these flags? Is he dancing out there at the end of the runway for you?
With those sparkle sticks? Look at his three planes lined up in a row. Looks like a parade to me.
was that that guy with glow sticks is he going to come on the plane?
Oh is he doing a rave out there?
Oh man.
Anyway I'm going to go to the bathroom on the plane and get fucked by my boyfriend.
Oh you got a co-pilot?
Oh you got a guy who sits with you up here in the cockpit?
Oh two guys up there.
Oh hold up the cockpit?
What's that?
Here's a nickname for you.
Tookus huh?
Yeah?
Anyway I'm flying to my husband's house.
You guys going to use each other's instruments?
Me and my husband are celebrating 50 years.
And we're flying to Acapulco right now.
So thank you.
Thank you so much for your service.
Bless your game.
Thank you.
So thank you.
- Thank you so much for your service.
- Bless your gay, gay pilot.
(laughing)
Yeah.
Flight doesn't blow my mind.
- Flight blows my mind still.
I didn't go into a plane until I was 18 years old.
- There's a video game called the 30 Flights of Loving
where the end credits just explains how flight works
and I had no idea how it worked until then.
- Yeah.
- And I'm from the first in flight state.
Oh, thank you very much.
North Carolina, the Wilbur Wright brothers.
- Yeah.
- By the way, they didn't call them the Wilbur Left brothers.
So let's keep that in mind.
Yeah. You know what I'm saying.
The Left Brothers.
Yeah, the Left Brothers invented the submarine.
Yeah, exactly.
The Left Brothers invented just hanging out with your friends on the ground and not flying anywhere.
You guys look stupid up there!
Yeah, we're drinking with girls!
Trying to go to the plane!
By my calculations, this paper plane will fly--
Man, shut up!
Shut up! You look stupid!
Yeah.
We just got a big table!
We're making our own micro-brews right now!
How big of a pussy do you have to be to go all the way- haul your ass all the way to the beach
just to fly a plane?
Right? You're not even- you're not even smoking weed, you're not- there's no girls in bikinis, you're not drinking Bud Lights, enjoying yourself.
You didn't even bring a grill.
You didn't bring a grill, you didn't bring your fucking George Foreman grill.
No, you can't even have a grill on a plane.
You don't even have a tent, nobody's doing poppers, you're just flying.
flying the the the left brothers invented a plane - but it was they invented the
first spy drone to fly over the girls bathrooms on the beach the left brothers
invented the plane hamburger number eight success we understand this yeah it
does definitely blows you mind those things are being blown you wake up and
Lord I am blessed yeah success to be released by Blake is playing money for
breakfast Blake Blake is like Drake but like not a pedophile hotline drink hot
line thing I know I'm a hotline thing I don't want to die today Blake it's hard
being successful. It's slow me at the top. Yeah people recognize me on the street
all the time they fucking and they fucking they point to my fly and they say my fly's unzipped.
How do they know the show so well? They know all the lines from the show. Exactly. Like your fly's
unzipped. Yeah. Hey you fat freak stop telling these stories. Yeah. They say that they don't
say that to me. People kind of put a red carpet when I go to the store. Yeah. Yeah. They put down
a red carpet now I'm gonna put I'm gonna roll you up in a target and it's just
the carpet that they put out in front yeah they put down saran wrap in front
of you because there's just like drool just coming out of you they follow they
have to follow behind you with a paint roller just repainting the floors
wherever you walk yes you are like pig pen should we do for dinner for dinner
yeah Dom's getting groceries we're in the middle of a fucking episode dude
We'll figure it out after the episode.
We'll fugger that out.
We'll fugger it out.
Yeah, we got five minutes left, Pat.
Okay, alright.
Well, number nine.
Nine movies.
What movies don't blow your mind?
What movie blew your mind?
Movies don't blow my mind.
Fight Club.
Enter the Void, dude.
Enter the Void, that's like doing drugs on acid.
That's like doing drugs on acid.
That's like doing drugs on acid on top of the earth, dude.
Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas feels like you're on drugs the whole time you watch it.
Fear my clothing in Las Vegas, dude.
Yeah.
Wear my clothing in Las Vegas.
Vegas. Where are my clothing in Las Vegas? Where are my clothing on the campaign trail?
72. What other blow your mind movies? Yeah, Flight Club. The Prestige. The Pistiche. The
Pistiche. Yeah. Incepticon. Incepticon. Yeah. Stepbrother. Stepbrother. Transformers Dark
of the Moon. Transformer. Transdormer. Nope. No. We're gonna keep trying it. We're gonna
trying to find things come on what you got
uh... you did me and and did one
dance formers stance for his former stance for a man of our
robots on the floor
uh... robots pond the floor
uh... dance formers robots for a while but i'm going to be a floor it is that
they got
it would be awesome to meet a jamaican guy who does not have a lot of money
to the body but
but i think i have a lot of fun and uh...
rd and it's a make a call and
it's pretty good
ross stepped the congress it just last uh... now ross about ross was that
restores so but the respect the mons and
it's because of the better is that this business is a good god's respect them
on
the rasta but it's not only got a lot about the bumper class so many of the
- It's so good, dude.
It's all the right syllables.
- Yeah.
- It's so funny that Michael Bay just made the two,
like there's the two robots that were the radio ones,
the ones that speak with the radio.
Yeah, you made, you just made them do AAVE.
- That was one of my,
it was an early standup joke that I would do.
It was just like,
I don't even remember what the joke was anymore,
just talking about the fact that he was just like,
yeah, man, we just,
for some reason, two black robots.
All the other ones were like, hello.
and they're like "man what's up with the, with the, with the septicons man"
and it's Tom Kenny voicing them
what?
yeah
you didn't know that?
yeah and they're like peeing on them
yeah yeah
and shit they're like "man man what's up"
that's Tom Kenny?
yeah
oh my god
Bob Esponja
yeah
Wobby Sponja
yeah Tom Kenny voices the really egregious one
yeah
egregious bot
yeah that's what he's called
his name is Greegious
yeah
Greegious
what were their names I wonder
I bet they have
have a chance bebop and rocksteady is that true no it's like jazz and something
else yeah it's hasn't like boom box and swisher yeah P money number 10 which is
ended on 10 we won't even look at the contenders you really want to figure out
dinner well no she's at the store right now I don't want oh my god he's a baby
10 is space space blow you guys mind portal - man yeah I guess sometimes I do
do look up there. Sometimes I look up at space and I'm thinking, "Hmm, there's so many
little stars." God, you would not believe your eyes, dude. You wouldn't believe how many stars there are in the
space ship. Oh, their names were Skids and Wheelie. Oh my god. Skids and Wheelie?
"Hey, what's up, Megan Fox? Damn, Megan." That's literally just what they do. Yeah, it's like they just try to see Megan Fox naked.
So wait, for some reason, like yeah, there's two black robots and what a fuck a human woman.
What the fuck were you thinking Michael Bay?
It's so funny how good of like a character story like Michael, or Megan Fox's character,
like a backstory Megan Fox's character has in that movie.
And then it's just, while she's explaining like, yeah I learned how to do cars on my own,
and then the whole movie is just like, every shot is just Shia LaBeouf being like, "I'm
(laughing)
- Whoa.
- Look at her boobs.
- Yeah.
- Her boobs, man!
- Whoa, you got big ol' boobs!
- No, I'm trying to figure out what her boobs are.
(laughing)
No, listen man, if you take,
dude, Shia LaBeouf is so--
- No, seriously.
- He's so good in those movies, he's so fucking funny.
- Dude, he's one of the best actors.
- I love those movies.
- Guy is so much swag.
- Shia LaBeouf rocks.
- Yeah.
- Now, seriously, mom, I'm not having sex with her right now,
okay, you just need to back up out of my space.
He just does that 100 times every movie.
That's like the period after Viva La Bam
where every mom in every movie was just April Margera.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- It's true. - They all just
pretended to be April.
There was seriously, every mom--
- 2007, 2006 to 2008.
- They're just pretending to be April.
- That was the April Margera mom period.
- Exactly, yeah.
'Cause it was like, oh, we found the perfect mom.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Seriously, that's like the best mom archetype.
- She's so good. - April Margera.
I did a Jackass 1 rewatch recently. Couldn't even get through it at one point.
When Steve-O does the snot on the Wasabi Snooter and he puts his snot and eats the vomit sushi.
Yeah.
I just turned it off, dude.
Jackass 1's the best one.
It's definitely the best one, yeah.
Because that's when they were on the most painkillers.
Oh, yeah.
Because they were so young.
yeah the better the alligator tightrope is on the final we're gonna
the alligator in april's hazard we're gonna put a we're gonna put a fucking
alligator in a cell phone funny
so so good the best at actually the best part is when the fireworks in the car
no not even now the best part of that one is when phil's on the toilet
and obey and i'm just a pretty sure that i'm just a bunch of budget
shit I mean you're losing your mind kids losing it so fucking funny yeah dude I
beat up my dad so much as a kid because of that I bet oh yeah my dad would not
fight back either I can go let's go to my parents house right now let's go be
my dad would throw me at the window if I did film a video of me beating up my dad
dude I mean that's you cross a serious line when you touch it we put hands on
your dad yeah I can never be on cross no no no once you once I knew kids growing
up that would be they were like yeah I gotta fight with my dad the other day
and I was like oh yeah doesn't suck it was yell at him about chores or whatever
and he's like no man I broke his nose right it's like what yeah that's insane
I never beat up my dad like that but I was like when he wasn't
expecting it I'll just go in and do kidney shots like while he's trying to
cook cuz I wanna see it man Margera did it it's me as a little kid just punching
my dad's kidney this is Steve oh and I'm gonna be my dad yeah man this is Steve
I'm gonna take a shit on my dad I'm gonna shit on my dad's face hmm yeah once you
once you like get your dad while he's cooking you kind of have power over your
dad is there a steve-o senior he's got to be dead Steve us dad yeah I don't know
let's find out let's find let's find it let's end the bottom of that dead all
- All right. - Okay.
- Bye guys, subscribe to the Patreon.
- Subscribe to the Patreon.
- See you baby. - Bye.