you're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
- Podcasts about List.
- You're a crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Are you recording Caleb?
- Boom.
(screaming)
- Welcome to the Podcasts About List Halloween special.
- Yeah.
(screaming)
- It's, today it's set a podcast about List,
it's ghost cast about--
- Mist.
The mist of the ghost.
- Oh no.
Podcast about myths.
- Oh my God.
Don't, if you're gonna scream like that,
you have to do it far away from the microphone, okay?
- Podcast about crypts.
- Not because I care about it,
but because it will ruin the audio.
No, just move your head away.
You don't have to move the whole arm.
It's gonna make a weird noise on the audio.
- Well then it's adding to the scariest.
- All right, now podcast about a split, a body in half.
and
about a creature in the fall
it
this is our very own this is like a dream queen our treehouse of horror
uh...
because it is a it is coming out on and i see on skos
in the treehouse.
Alright, now I feel sick every time I scream.
Are you kidding me?
You're that...
Yeah, you need to go to the doctor.
Are you that fragile?
Yeah.
A scream throws you out of homeostasis?
Oh no, I've been screaming all morning, so that was actually the youngest scream I did.
This was almost a chicken brain episode.
I found a chicken spot in town.
No.
Uh-huh.
No, don't do it.
I had to lay down for a little bit.
I had to get the chicken out of my system.
You know better than that.
I know, I forgot.
I forgot what chicken does to us before we record.
I don't think it's the meat, I think it's the skin.
It's the skin.
The skin on that chicken was good.
I think it might be the curse.
Yeah.
The curse of chicken?
I think it might be the curse that the witch put on us to be stupid when we eat chicken.
I forgot about the curse.
Duh.
You guys are so stupid.
Everything has to be scary.
This is also, this is episode 111, okay?
There's six of us that do the podcast.
Six times, 'cause we all have split personalities
like Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde.
Yeah. Six times one, one, one.
Yours is Mrs. Hyde.
No. That's your split personality.
Yeah, at night you turn into Mrs. Hyde.
No, mine is Mr. Fly.
And I'm very cool.
No. Yeah.
You can't fly.
Six times one, one, one.
You guessed it, Friday the 13th.
The scariest number of all time.
No.
- We're gonna start off this episode
with some very scary stories.
- Yeah, we're gonna tell scary stories around the campfire.
- Yeah, we have a campfire here.
I'm smoking a cigar.
We're gonna tell a scary story.
- I just put a whole, I dropped a sausage into the campfire.
- Why do you pick it up?
- I'm roasting a Ritz cracker on a skewer
like it's a marshmallow.
- I'm roasting a human leg.
- Oh my God.
Patrick if you want I just want to just like a quick sidebar um there's a very easy fix
to make people stop saying they want to hit you with the bus and it's to not scream directly
into the mic every 30 seconds on this episode.
Wait hold on hold on Patrick needs to fillet the mic really quick.
Did he mute himself?
Did you mute yourself?
Yeah.
How much you want to I bet that screwed up your audio in audacity.
I did not.
Alright.
My audio's fine, I just clicked a button.
Anyway, we're at the campfire.
Yeah.
We're gonna tell some stories.
Cameron, how 'bout you go first?
Oh, I have to go first?
Or, or...
Okay, I'll go first.
Someone, or someone else?
I'll go first.
Alright, no, wait, Patrick just left, so I guess, um...
Yeah, no, that's fine.
Yeah, just stand up and walk away in the first fucking five minutes of the episode.
Yeah, the campfire's here.
Dude, the campfire's gonna go out.
out.
Caleb was doing a voice that was too scary and I got too scared.
You didn't get that scared.
I had to leave the room.
You did not get that scared.
I got so scared just now.
Are you guys ready for my scary story?
I'm gonna leave again.
This is gonna scare the pants right off you.
This story is called the terrifying story of the crazy murderer.
Can you take it back?
No!
Take it back dude!
I'm serious.
Alright, are you guys ready?
I know.
Of course not.
Why not?
Wait.
Maybe I'll do that.
Maybe I'll do a light scream.
That's smart.
Is this working?
It was a dark and evil night.
Not a creature was stirring.
Except for some ghosts!
But that's a story for another time.
Little twelve year old Patrick lived alone with his mom and dad and brothers and sisters
and his aunt lived next door and he had two hairless cats.
But his brothers and sisters were away on vacation,
and his aunt was in timeout.
And tonight, on Friday the 13th,
his parents were going on a date.
They hired a babysitter and they were talking
to the babysitter about the rules of the house.
- That fell out of his chair.
(laughing)
- Are you okay, Patrick?
- One second.
say something you have to stop scaring me so much
down cam fuck did they were talking to the babysitter about the rules of the
house one Patrick can't play with toys to
he really hurt himself he broke just broke something in his house
Rule number two. I'm telling you right now, stop scaring me. Rule number two.
Patrick can't eat snacks. I'm not gonna do it again. Rule number three. You can't even see it. You can't even see it. I don't know why I'm still doing it.
Patrick can only watch one minute of TV per night. Patrick started to cry and went to lie down in his room from sadness.
Right before Patrick's mom and dad went out to their date, his dad stopped and turned to the babysitter.
"One more thing," he said. "There's a freak on the loose in the neighborhood tonight."
"A freak?" asked the babysitter. Her name was Vicky the Babysitter, by the way.
"Yes, a freak," said Patrick's dad. "He's a serial killer, and he's obsessed with killing babysitters.
He was in the asylum, but he escaped by getting out of his cell.
Now he's walking around the neighborhood looking for babysitters."
*snickers*
*wheezes*
Crazy Murderer is from Egypt, so he can cast a mummy's curse on his victims.
He's also Native American, so he can shapeshift.
He can time travel, so he has visited every world culture, and he has a place in their
legends.
He's also a werewolf, which is separate from the shapeshifting, by the way.
But tonight is the full moon, Vicky said.
Exactly, said Patrick's dad.
That means the Crazy Murderer will turn into a wolf with blood-red eyes.
He can smell children being babysat from 100 miles away, and he has a hook in place of
one hand so that he can catch children like a fish.
He drives an ice cream truck, but instead of selling ice cream, it sells blood and eyeballs.
The ice cream truck plays the Lavender Town scary music and it's driven by the ghost
of a child.
The crazy murderer rides in the backseat and sticks his head out the window like a dog.
One time the window got rolled up by accident and it cut the crazy murderer's head off,
so it had to get stitched back on with barbed wire.
He's immortal, so it's okay for his head to get cut off.
He has the eyes of a spider and the claws of a dark demon.
So what do I do if he comes to the house?
Asked Vicky the babysitter.
He's already here. I can see him through the window, said Patrick's dad.
Then Vicky turned around and said, "Oh my god!"
Also, Patrick's mom's mouth was sewed shut by a voodoo doctor. That's why she hasn't talked in the story.
The reason Vicky the babysitter said "Oh my god" was because there was nothing at the window.
Patrick's dad was just tricking her.
She didn't realize that the people talking to her were never even Patrick's parents after all.
The dad was the crazy murderer all along, and the mom was Bloody Mary.
They were pretending to be Patrick's parents to get into the house and kill the babysitter.
They killed the babysitter and drove away in the ice cream truck.
The ghost child who drove the truck wicked at the camera.
Patrick stopped crying and came downstairs because he sensed there was no more babysitter.
He was so excited he got his favorite Lego toy set and ate a corn dog and sat in front of the TV.
He turned it on and Squidward's suicide was on the TV and he watched it for 10 minutes and went crazy.
He had to go to the asylum and turned into the crazy murderer.
Then, once he grew up, he time-traveled back to his house to kill Vicky the babysitter to get rid of all the rules from his house.
What happened to Patrick's real mom and dad, you may ask?
Well, remember the ghosts from the beginning of the story?
Yep, that was his parents.
BOO!
[PATRICK SCREAMS]
That's the story of the cr- the terrifying story of the crazy murderer.
My god.
I'm shaking.
I, even reading that was difficult for me.
I fell out of my chair twice.
Pat, what was that like for you?
I don't know.
I fell out of my chair.
No, I mean, it was still in the, for that to happen to you.
Oh.
It's terrifying.
It was, I bet it was, dude.
I bet it was.
I mean, that's more terrifying than I could imagine.
Yeah.
If that happened to me, I would scream.
I fell out of the chair so hard I scared the cats out of ever coming to this room again.
You're kind of the horror movie.
Every life, every day of those cats' lives is always a horror movie.
You're just a monster who walks around and grabs them.
Yeah.
And shoves their balls in their friend's face.
Stomping around the house going, "Yeah!"
"Yeah!"
It's true.
Alright.
Who's ready for another scary story?
I don't think I'm ready.
I'm freaking out.
a happy story here I'll tell a happy story yeah yeah there is a very there's a
great there's a great movie it's called Air Force One it has Han Solo in it and
he's president and there's terrorists and they get on the plane as he's on and
then he has to fight them and he actually he's kill he kills every one of them and
and he survives.
- That's pretty good.
That's pretty happy.
- You guys feeling a little better?
- Yeah. - I feel a lot better.
- Okay.
Let's do another scariest,
Pat, you wanna say your scariest story?
- I'll tell my scariest story.
Okay.
Let me.
On the scariest night of the year,
Friday the 13th. - What night?
Okay.
- I came home to see my home in complete disarray.
I walked into the front door and all of my Funkos were out of their boxes.
I looked over to my wife's room and she wasn't in there with her awesome boyfriend.
I grew to be terrified of this so much that I dropped my bag of Woot Stouts on the ground
causing them all to explode.
The foamy hoppy goodness leaked all over my Mass Effect Asari body pillow that my wife
and her extraordinary boyfriend take turns watching me fuck every Friday night.
The pillow absorbed most of the moisture, so I picked it up and started sucking the delicious
woot stout that I earned after a long week's work at the ThinkGeek factory.
I sucked it right out of the pillow's pussy hole.
I was scared as hell, but I couldn't let that beautiful golden IPA go to waste.
Anyway, I digress.
The point of this story is that I was scared as hell, but I couldn't-
I was seriously terrified.
I couldn't believe it.
It had happened.
I couldn't believe my own eyes.
My 30-50 feral hogs had finally unionized.
I ran to the door but tripped over my RC BB8 that I also fuck and I fell face first onto
the floor and chipped all my teeth.
Just then, an unfamiliar foot stomped right in my face.
I looked up in sheer terror.
My 30-50 feral hogs brought carrel-freaking baskins into my home.
- No.
- To be continued.
(laughing)
- That's the scariest ending of all time.
- I think what's so scary about that is the,
is the cliffhanger at the end.
- Yeah, anything could happen.
- It also means that we have to go through it,
we sit through another scary story.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
- That's the prospect of another scary story.
We're not safe, there's no end yet, no end in sight.
- Yeah.
- All right, can someone tell a,
someone else tell a happy story?
- Yeah, I got one for you.
Basically, there's these little fellows that work for a guy named grew and they have missed they do mischief and come up with different inventions
the main okay, no
No, that's I just came up with that I know what you're talking about really yeah, I just made it up
We're gonna make you a millionaire. Yeah, I'm gonna think I'm thinking of making a movie about them called the the fellows
the yellow fellows
(laughing)
- Called I Am Despicable.
- You ready for my scary story?
- Yeah.
- All right.
- This is called Scary Story by Caleb Pitts.
There was a carpenter, let me try that again.
There was a carpenter who traveled around the land
growing his hair out really long, tanning and fucking perfect tans in every town he went
to.
He would have women wash his feet and they would gobble on his balls and then he'd probably
go surfing after that.
He would do a thousand pull-ups a day and he was ripped.
He had a squad of other jacked assholes.
Yeah, I'm an asshole, so what?
And they would tag team girls and they would eat huge feasts and they all had long ass
hair and they liked to fish together. Life was good. Then one day one of his friends
started tattletailing on him like a puss. He told the nerds of the town about his
friend and about how much hole he was getting and about how much food he was
eating. At the time you couldn't eat a lot of food at once it was illegal. The
nerds controlled all of the banks in the town and so they had the power to stop
him the nerds grabbed a man and they punched him and then they put him onto a
cross and they crucified him till he was dead now you may be thinking that's just
some story that could never actually happen but it did yeah happened to a man
named Jesus Christ died he died for your sin in the end of the story the end oh
Oh my god.
I came up with this idea.
You know, loving your neighbor more.
I have an idea for a sequel.
He could turn into a zombie.
And they could make a day to celebrate him turning into a zombie.
Oh my god.
That would be even more terrifying.
That would be so scary.
A zombie of him?
I'm having a picnic attack just thinking about that.
A zombie of the coolest guy ever did a picnic attack?
attack right now and just absolutely I'm getting Pikmin attacked just thinking
about it so those are scary stories yeah yeah some of them scared me too much
some of them could really happen some of them did happen no but the listeners
can't see this but raise your hand if you put a little pee in your pants while
we were listening to these well that's about what I thought I'm not gonna say
who raised their hand but let's just say it was anonymous yep yeah or synonymous
synonymous's wife is named synonymous so you know I think you guys get the idea
what are you guys dressing up as for Halloween today? Myself.
I'm one of those awesome guys. Yeah I'm going as 45. Yeah I'm going about
scary going as I'm going as uh as somebody who's been red-pilled because
the scariest thing to most people is someone who knows the truth and it wasn't
if I got it yeah I'm going as a truth teller I'm going as Eric Weinstein yeah
yeah I'm gonna walk in there and I'm just gonna be like yeah math proves that
gay people are wrong and people are going pretty scared I'm going as Julian
Assange neo combination whoa yeah one of the scariest things to the modern is
It's kind of the real life Neo.
It's true.
Let's punch this out, let's beat this out.
Julian Assange is Neo.
Yeah.
The United States government is a robot.
Angelina Jolie is--
Salt.
The girl.
She's Salt, from the movie Salt.
She's Salt, yeah.
She's Hannah, and it's both of them versus America,
and Obama is Morpheus.
Yeah.
Yeah Obama is Morpheus.
Obama is Morpheus.
Evil Morpheus.
Okay, yeah, he's Dark Morpheus.
He's Dark Morpheus.
Good Morpheus is Kanye West.
It's Laurence Fishburne still.
No, it's Kanye West and Laurence Fishburne.
No one else can play Morpheus.
They share the role.
They switch off every scene.
No, Cameron, you're wrong about that.
No one else can play Morpheus.
You're not making any sense, Cam.
It's making me sad that you're not making any sense right now, buddy.
What are you talking about? You're talking like a crazy person. Yeah that's what most people say about truth tellers.
And that's terrifying me right now. You're scaring me on Halloween.
Can you just invite us into your world right now?
Can you bring us into your terrifying world? Can you just start the list and show us a glimpse of the dark mind behind other podcasts such as this one?
what you're terrifying mind palace we just want to see into your mind mm-hmm
okay so basically imagine a gothic castle uh-huh filled with 100 vampires of
dry eggs at the mind I click exit of the mind it's too scary for me I knew it I
knew my hand was mined this mind is getting me so scared it's giving me
indigestion this mind is first mind freaking me your mind freaking me and I
I need you to calm down.
Oh my god.
You're like an evil doctor, which is the scariest thing.
I'm like a mad scientist.
You're kind of like Dr. Terrible's sing-along blog.
Yeah.
That's your kind of terror.
I'm kind of like Dr. Anthony Fauci, who seems to be scaring all of these Republicans nowadays.
Yeah, scaring all of the geniuses out of drinking hydroxychloroquine.
Yeah.
yeah yeah maybe they don't want us taking it because it's too hard to pronounce
that's what it is yeah they need to come up with doctors don't want to have to write that
whole thing down on a prescription yeah
we'll just wait we'll wait for the shorter cure hydra just [ __ ] just it doesn't exist
this stuff is illegal it's illegal
yeah you can't have this actually yeah this will kill you
Yeah. Yeah, this actually kills you instantly if you take it, so yeah.
Yeah, we're just gonna give you Advil. Yeah. Doctors, doctors are trying to get rid, to stop
people from drinking bleach because they're worried there's not going to be enough left
to use on their lab coats. That's true. Keep it crispy white. Yeah. Yeah. There'd be a shortage.
Use your brain, dude. Escape from the prison they construct for you. Escape from where they want
you to work. Escape from which mountain? Escape from which mountain, Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson.
get scared of it. So today in keeping with the Halloween theme and the theme of
fear yeah we are doing the top 10 scariest things ever on the top tens
yeah and so and I thought that we had done this list before but I looked back
into our archive and we unlocked the vault and back into the dark 31 which
interestingly today Halloween is also in its own way kind of a dark 31. Oh my god.
We did the list top 10 scariest things ever to see so it's completely different
from this list so it's a different completely different. It's true. We're fine.
This is new content. Number one scariest thing ever is being buried alive. Not
that scary. Yeah it's scary are you kidding me? If you think about it okay
Well, they're not being specific. Okay, imagine this you
Are hanging out in your house? Okay, you're playing video games. You're watching TV, right?
You think I need to take the dog out you open up your front door and it's just a block of dirt
And you realize that your entire house has been buried underground. Yeah
Well, your life's not any all right here here's a better shit in your bed, but that's fine. Here's a better scenario
you wake up you find out that you're buried under 1 million coins that's one
of the million gold coins like screw in your under screws medux money pit my
dog my dog
yeah yeah how do you get out of that you have to spend all the money
- You do.
- No!
- Dude, you got something to do.
- You put Amazon orders in, you get them COD,
and then they have to, so once you get out
of the gold coin pit, you got a bunch of packages.
- Holy crap, and you get to do unboxing videos.
- And yeah, then you grow your wealth.
- Exactly.
- You grow your wealth.
- And then you realize that you got knocked out
from all the coin amnesia, and that's what actually
put you under the coins in the first place.
- And then you're trapped in an infinite loop.
- Because you're making so much AdSense money,
and then you keep doing it because you keep forgetting.
- Hold up.
- And then you have to write, and then you write,
you're not very smart though.
So you try to do a memento thing where you remind yourself
with tattoos on your body, but you just write coins
on your arm.
- Yeah, and then you look around and you go, yep.
- Yep, that's about right.
- There are coins.
- That's a really good point, Arm.
- Here's a comment on this one that says,
what about your house burning on fire?
I'm not saying this is the scariest thing,
but it is the scariest thing that ever happened to me.
It happened to me in February of 2018.
A house two doors down from me was on fire.
I live in a townhouse, so all the houses are connected.
And it spread to the house right next door,
and then my roof was smoking.
But my house didn't go on fire,
but I was very scared
because I thought my house might burn down.
I hadn't got my diary or my books or my clothes.
- Whoa.
- Yeah, if my stuff got burnt, I'd be so scared.
- Yeah, if my roof started smoking.
- Uh-huh.
- You know I'm grabbing my diary first.
- Grabbing my diary, I'm grabbing my Palm Pilot,
I'm grabbing my Nokia N-Gage and getting the hell out of here.
You're grabbing your diarrhea with a bucket out of the toilet and then you're leaving.
That's all you take.
Come on.
You're leaving your girlfriend and your cats inside and you're taking your diarrhea.
No, I'm not.
Yeah, you're taking it all the way home.
I'm not taking any diarrhea home with me.
Yeah, you are.
Wait, listen to this comment about being buried alive.
Just imagine being in a dark, cold space waiting to die and you keep screaming but no one can
hear you and as the hours pass you feel worthless.
It would be like putting a granny in a room, take her off her medication knowing she will
die in a few hours and then shut the door and walk out with the granny knowing what will happen.
I've done that to a granny. You've done a lot of stuff to a granny. Yeah. A Granny Smith.
Yeah, I smoked weed out of a Granny Smith before. Yeah, I smoked weed out of your granny.
No, you didn't. My nana would never let you do that. She's not built for it. My nana smoked
- She smoked weed once in the 70s
and she said that she vomited for three days.
(laughing)
And she said that was the only time she ever smoked weed.
- She's like actually allergic to weed.
- And I don't believe her.
- You probably smoked, she probably smoked K2 back then.
- Probably.
I don't know, I think being buried alive,
I don't know, I feel like I'd kill Bill that shit, you know?
- Yeah.
- Or just ring the bell.
- Ring the bell?
- Don't they have little bells?
- Yeah, the Victorian graveyard bell.
- It's not that hard.
- Yeah, pretty easy.
- They have a bell at the graveyard?
- They have a bell at the graveyard.
You can ring it when dinner's done.
It's pretty big.
That's why they had that bell.
- Yeah.
- That's how you got somebody to come dig you up,
is you would ring the bell and they would think,
oh, there's dinner down there.
(laughing)
I guess I'll dig 'em up and see if there's dinner in there.
- Damn, they buried a hibachi chef under the hair.
(laughter)
- Damn, he still had an egg in his hat
when we put him down there.
(laughter)
We need to take him back out.
- Oh, I should've known that there's a tower
of onion rings that were on fire.
- This heroic hibachi chef was saved
during this mass shooting when the bullet
was stopped by the shrimp in his chest pocket.
(laughter)
- I would never be buried alive, though.
This is all true.
My friend secretly ate a deep sleep medicine
and she went to sleep for 24 hours.
Then when her family came and thought she was dead
and buried her, when she woke, she was buried alive.
- And then what happened?
- That's the end of the story.
- Then she farted and they all died.
- Someone says, I don't agree on this.
It's actually quite fun, really.
- Whoa.
- Twisted crazy.
- Fucking psycho.
Oh my God.
Someone says nothing like a psychopath burying you alive, but psychopath is spelled C-Y-C-O-path.
[laughs]
Psychopath.
This is what happened to my great-grandpa. Died by this on D-Day.
[laughs]
Buried alive on D-Day?
I don't believe that.
I believe it, dude.
Imagine waking up in a coffin and you struggle to breathe.
I get claustrophobic, so please, it's no laughing matter.
I think being buried alive is definitely one of my worst fears.
Really?
Now someone's going to do it to me.
God damn it.
Probably a fan.
A fan's going to bury you alive.
There's a comment on here that says, "Apparently they used to bury people alive."
Okay, this is an open...
Invitation for anyone to come bury Pat alive at any time.
- If you bury me alive, I will be pissed.
I'll be pissed.
- I'm imagining just like a circular coffin.
(laughing)
They just fit you in, like a gear.
- Someone comments, this is really scary,
but Five Nights at Freddy's should be number one.
(laughing)
Facts.
- Yeah, spitting straight facts.
When you're unable to move that's terrible.
Not that scary. I would say being buried alive is not my number one fear.
In Russia a girl named Sasha was 16 year old and she slept a really long time so
her mom and dad thought she was dead. They buried her and then Sasha woke up
and said where am I? Wait I'm buried. Help help help please wait I
can't breathe. Agh. And 16 minutes later she was dead. She was beautiful.
Ariana Grande.
- They buried Ariana Grande alive.
- Number two, fear.
- Whoa.
- Fear itself, dude.
- Remember that line?
- Yeah, I remember who said it too, Dracula.
- Yeah, you have nothing to fear but my dragon ass.
- No, no, he was trying to trick them.
- Fear but me.
- He was trying to trick them.
He was trying to be like, listen,
don't worry about Dracula, you should be afraid of fear.
And they were like, "Oh, duh, okay."
Well, he's got a point.
By the time they realized what was happening,
they had two little pencils in their neck.
[Scoffs]
Top comment.
"Fear is scary and is what makes us afraid.
It is the seedling of panic and sets terror into the body.
It is the father of phobias and the mother of horror.
It is fear."
Father of phobia?
"Anna."
That's from Anna?
Yeah, that's what it says.
Wow.
"Anna Bell, the doll?"
[Gasps]
[Screams]
No!
(laughing)
- No!
- That would be so scary if Annabelle DePaul
was a top 10's comment. - I fear being sick or hurt
and no access to healthcare.
- Wow, welcome to America.
- Yeah.
- That's a really long comment too.
- Someone says, I bet Ted Cruz won't bring this up.
(laughing)
He got his ass set for life.
- Our nation's biggest problem is fear.
- Poor white stupid, I bet you on free healthcare.
- Four white steps above ground. - This is the biggest one.
Bigger than "Starded" on the ocean because it's fear.
You're scared of being buried alive fear.
Ghosts and Slenderman, fear.
Sometimes you're not gonna like admitting it,
but that's sort of fear mixed with embarrassment.
- Oh wait, we figured out who said the quote.
Somebody got it in the comments.
The only fear is fear itself, Marilyn Manson.
(laughing)
There we go, we got it. - At least you said it, yeah.
- But you nailed it.
The only thing to fear is fear itself. I think this is so true because if there was no fear, there would be nothing to fear.
Holy cow, we blew that one right wide open.
Really, fear is the scariest because all the stuff on the list is fear. Fear is the devil's happiness. So yeah.
Fear kinda makes me, uh, happy.
You're a psycho.
I'm kind of, uh,
You're a, uh,
Freak with that.
You should be in 21 Pilots.
Mm-hmm.
You're a halloween crazy.
I'm just a sucker for pain!
Oh, maybe you are a 21.
It's kind of a 21 Pilots hat.
It's funny that we make fun of this hat every week
and you just keep wearing it.
It's not a bad hat.
Just wear a different hat when we record.
Just change hats or something.
It's a good hat.
It's not comfortable to wear a hat under headphones too.
I do it all the time.
It makes your head really sore.
I don't know why you choose to do it.
Yeah, tell that to Caleb.
Every time.
Well, I mean, Caleb only does it sometimes.
That's right.
You do it every single time.
I do it all day, every day, man.
I'm afraid of what's under that hat.
And I'm having goosebumps.
That's a comment right there.
I'm having goosebumps right now.
Number three, being stranded in the open ocean.
Whoa.
I just swim away.
Can you not swim?
Yeah, just swim to the land.
Do you have no-- I just swim home.
Here's what's scary,
being stranded in the ocean and you're just a head.
And you realize that your body has been taken
by Somali pirates and you're just a floating head
in the ocean. Oh my God.
That might be pretty scary.
But just being straight, I mean, again,
I'm an excellent swimmer.
I placed third place in like two or three
swim competitions growing up.
- Yeah, I was number one in the world
when I was like one year old, so.
- No, you weren't.
- Yeah, I was. - No.
- No. - No.
- I swam around the world in 80 minutes.
- That's a Jackie Chan movie. - I just don't believe you.
- That's not a real thing.
- No, well, they based the movie off of me.
- They did not.
- They did.
- They didn't, no.
So we just heard a one-year-old got an awesome one-year-old guy swam around the
world in 80 minutes we're gonna make a movie where Jackie Chan swims around the
world in 80 minutes and then my family was gonna sue him so they had to change
it to going in a hot air balloon instead and 80 days no they didn't change that
that's a that's a little known misconception that's a mistake that's a
misprint on the DVD yeah cuz I mean yeah they think about it the movies like 80
minutes exactly boost they based they boost they based they based on Wilson
on me they did Cameron's look you're thinking of Shanghai noon no oh and
Wilson is in around the world than 80 days is he yeah I don't think so and
yeah no man you're thinking of um bottle rocket by West you think you're midnight
in Paris yeah no yeah oh that's Jackie Chan and Steve Coogan huh no Owen Wilson
Owen Wilson is it in it but he's Wilbur Wright oh so he's not Wilson he's
Wilbur Wright you just said he's not he's not a high noon he's he's I heard a
rumor I heard a rumor that that movie that that someone got Owen Wilson hooked
on heroin on the set of that movie. Around the world in 80 days? Yeah. I guess when
you're a celebrity like you might as well just get addicted to heroin you know?
Right? You got to do it. Like I get it. Allegedly. I just want to say allegedly so
that Owen Wilson a big a friend of the show does not sue us. He's a friend of
the show. He's a friend of me. He's not a friend of the show. He's a friend of the show.
He's a friend of the show. He's not. He's a friend of the show. He's a friend of the show.
He's a friend of the show for someone like me. He will throw up on any boat due to seasickness. I couldn't agree more
I'll just stick to the kiddie pool and the bath toys. Thank you very much
Yeah, I'll swim in my bathtub. It's also they said kiddie pool. KITTY
Like the cat pool yeah, yeah kitty cat pool
Okay, I would probably make friends with the sharks and just have them
Take me home if I would swim to the bottom of the ocean and that I would find a portal that goes into my house
I would tell the sharks I'm kind of like the shark of like humans so we kind of
you know we might relate a little bit and they would understand me and they would
take me home. Here's a comment guys if this happens to you watch the shallows
first it's a story of a woman gets stranded in a middle island. Oh fuck I'm stuck in the middle of the ocean. Does somebody have an iPod video with the shallow on it?
The shallow she's like she's not even stuck on an island that's the one with
um fucking wait let me is this the one I'm thinking of yeah with Blake Lively
she's not stuck on an island she's stuck out she's like stuck is stuck like 50
feet from shore on like a buoy like this isn't even doesn't even apply lean just
lean towards the the ocean or the land well there's a shark just step on him
jump on his head Mario style on the shirt you get to bring a coin home what
What kind of shark would you ride? What would be whale shark?
I would ride the shark from 47 meters down uncaged.
I would probably do a hammerhead shark just so I could grab onto the sides like a hammerhead.
I would do the megalodon actually. I'm changing my answer.
Like a west coast chopper.
Yeah, yeah, hang onto it like a west coast chopper.
Get your motor running.
Shark out on the highway.
Eating all the small fish.
And whatever comes our way
Born to ride a shark
Meow meow meow meow
My uh, my grandpa
This should make wild hogs but with sharks
My grandpa used to have like a little, like a plushie of Santa Claus
And when you, and he was on a motorcycle
And he had like a Harley Davidson jacket
And when you pressed his uh
If you pressed his hand
It would play that song and he would like shake
So I used to hide it under the couch cushion
So when he would sit down
down when he got home from work he'd sit down and he was like get your motor run
you go god fucking damn it the last comment on being stranded in the open
ocean is I would die with the smiley emoji okay freak I'm scared of that guy
yeah let's get these I okay with death get him out of there I don't know I
think my video driver just crashed what are you driving I don't know
know something just crashed. Both of my screens just shut off so. Turn them on.
Yeah they're playing Skater XL. I'm not playing Skater XL. Thanks for the
dramatic gong hit. Yeah. That was the mic stand. Alright anyway.
The monitor turned off because you suffered a ghost curse on Halloween.
Yeah. Dude you're suffering. I wasn't playing Skater XL but I did look up Owen Wilson's
heroin stuff and it turns out Steve Coogan might have be the one who got him hooked on
heroin.
He might be the suspect?
It says in this New York Post article that Steve Coogan with whom he starred in several
films with according blah blah blah I went through it with Steve.
That gets the heat off of Jackie.
Wow.
I would have thought it was the Chan man.
Now that's scary.
Jackie Chan did not get oh Wilson hooked on heroin it was allegedly Steve Coogan.
Jackie Chan was addicted to heroin and he's just like trying to do all the kung fu and
his arms are just like going just completely limp as he's trying to punch these guys and
they're all like flipping over as soon as he touches them.
Yeah.
That'd be awesome.
Look like Jar Jar Binks fighting.
Number four is hell.
I can't even say it.
Here's a comment.
I don't believe, this is the second week in a row we've talked about hell I think.
This is a comment though, um, I don't believe in hell.
If there is an afterlife in anything, there won't be any punishment and people suffer
more than on earth.
More likely to be a reincarnation are ghosts.
This sounds really stupid, but if ghosts exist, maybe the reason why no one has seen them
is because it's the souls of humans and it's the ghosts of people.
In government that passed away, they threw Adolf Hitler into a cave and have some laws
you cannot haunt someone's house.
You guys ever think the afterlife might be like that?
Do you think they have laws?
Do you guys think that it might be the souls of humans and the ghosts of people in government
they threw Adolf Hitler into a cave and have laws that you can't haunt someone's house?
In hell, in hell they would have a million laws.
That's true.
Holy crap.
What would hell be like?
A million laws and no TV.
Oh my god.
No TV for a week.
No TV because of how many laws regulated it.
That's right.
And you wouldn't be able to cross the street.
can't watch Superstore. You can't ever cross the street to go to the store. You can't watch Superstore at all.
You can't watch Superstore even in the old episodes. No. Yeah. No. And they say,
they say, you say, "Do you guys have Mr. Show?" and they're like, "Oh yeah, yeah we
have Mr. Show. It's like one of the few shows we have." And then you turn it on
and it's with Bob and David. Yep. Turns out it's actually Sister Show and it's
the all-female reboot. No. Oh my god. Yeah. And it's Elijah Schlesinger. Only in hell.
that's only on hell TV yeah I want to go to hell that's how they get you dude
that's how they trick you they have a byway exclusive TV shows I would do I
would do fixer-upper to hell yeah I would put in like some nice wood floors I would
put in a is that no I'm thinking of I think is that chip and Joanna chip and
- Chip and Joanne.
Yeah, I would go Chip and Joanne on Hell.
- Joanna.
- It's not Joanna.
- Get her name right.
It's Chip and Joanna.
- You don't even know what the show is called.
- Yes it is.
- It's Chip and Dale.
- Chip and Dale and they're two chip monks.
- Chip and Joanna Gaines.
- No, wrong.
- That's their name.
- That's her formal name.
When you know her and her husband well,
they let you call her Jo.
So Chip and Jo, I'm taking them to Hell.
We're putting in granite countertops.
We're gonna cover up.
- We're gonna get some nice,
we're gonna get some beautiful magnolia.
We're putting an in-ground fire pool.
Oh, hell yeah.
Because they have an above-ground one and it's kind of tacky.
Yeah.
Yeah, the thing is you get a lot of bang for your buck in hell.
Yep.
It's made out of stones.
Brimstones.
Whoa.
That's right.
Here's a sub-list in the comments.
What's going to happen if Satan rules the world?
One, the opposite of heaven is hell.
I would hate that.
2. No peace and quiet, just noise and screams.
3. Endless torture.
4. Satan will make you hungry and lets you feed human organs.
5. No more anything you like in your life. Ever.
Oh my god, did he see I I would seriously fucking hate that. Yeah
He's Satan's gonna make the opposite of that would disgust me that would disgust me
Yeah, that would straight-up scare the hell out of me. Uh-huh. I would be disgusted by that Zayden is a
Republic guys
Satan I'm a house
I'm a house devil. Yeah, I'm a house demon
It's a bad word who would be afraid of that
I would not be but still some people might be if they get a spanking from their mother after they say it
Hell time with hell mar
Yeah down here it's all Republicans, yeah, so yeah my show pisses off a lot of people
Yeah, yeah down in the
Mar on a Halloween episode
Mar in hell down we need to get we need to take bill more to hell as I hope they sir
I hope they show bill Maher in hell. Yeah
And I hope they serve beer, too
He's gonna be down there and the chaos of pandemonium that city of hell where there's riots going on constantly
He's gonna get down there. He's gonna look in the camera and say no rules
Whoa, yeah, no rules. It's hell.
Yeah, Satan rules.
I love hell. That's what he's gonna say instead of you rule. I love hell.
I'm in hell. New rule. Internal damnation forever.
My first guest tonight Mac Miller everybody Mac Miller come on
Yeah, I don't know
Yeah, what's up is me Mac Miller
Yeah, you think if you think saying Mac Miller's in hell if you think this is exactly like Pittsburgh
If you think there is nothing scariest than hell, then you are not lucky person time is drawing near
here
on this night
i feel like again much like this is the ocean i would make friends
spending a trip spending an eternity and beyond through the fire and flames not
the song is terrifying
- Yeah, I thought we moved on.
- Hell is basically Guitar Hero on Expert.
Oh, number five, drowning?
- Yeah.
- It's kinda similar to number three.
- See, again, I would make friends
because once you get down to the bottom of the ocean,
you'll meet SpongeBob.
- I'd meet SpongeBob and Patrick
and Pearl the Whale and Krusty Krabs
and Sandy the Creature. - And Gary that Snail.
- Gary Dat Snail.
- I'd meet Squidward Mr. Octopus, blue guy.
- Squidward that guy, Mr. the Crab.
I might, I might, real shit, I might drill a hole in Mr. Krusty Krab and I might fuck it.
The Plankton.
Hell, I'd hang out with the Jumping Dumpman on his pirate ship.
Plankton the Plankton.
The Flying Dumpman.
The Flumping Dumpman.
The Jumping, the fucking duck.
The Jumping Dumpman.
The fucking duckling.
The Dazzling.
The fucking Dutchman.
The Donkey.
The Flying Monkey.
The fucking duck.
The Fucking Duck.
Yarrr, yarrr, beware the flying monkey!
Beware the dazzling jump man!
Man, I'd be, I'd be hanging out, I'd be terrified of the flapping dapping if I was down there.
Beware the flapping dapping!
Beware the flashing Dutchman!
You'll come and take your doubloon!
I'd be hanging out in the wavy holes locker if I was down there, I gotta be honest.
I did, I, listen, cross my heart and hope to fucking fall into Jerry Hole's locker.
Why does he have a locker?
What is he going to school?
Stinky Dave's box.
Arr, Gravy Jones will get ya.
And I'll put you in his meat locker.
Arr, look out, he'll put you in Crazy Jones' locker.
Crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy,
crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy,
crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy,
Joe's locker we got we got frimp shrine right
Davy Joel doesn't sound like such a bad guy
come on down to Billy Joel's locker it's your life that's right
no but I could drown easily and then come back to life yeah I just spit the water
out you fucking idiot yeah who made this stupid I try not breathing water dumbass
again if you can swim not a problem if you can touch your wrench you can swim
dodge a wrenching dogs and water yeah that's right you can dodge when I was a
kid when I was a kid I I thought I invented eternal breathing and I because
I had a Capri Sun with the straw and I was like, "Oh my God, what if I just put air in
the Capri Sun and then I just breathe it in and out and in and out while I'm underwater?"
And so it went underwater and I just started doing it and then I like got out and climbed
onto the dock and I was like, "I'm about to pass out."
I told my brother, I was like, "I think I invented forever breathing."
And he was like, "If you do that anymore, you'll die."
(laughing)
It's heartbreaking, dude.
- Here's a crazy-- - Here's one of my early
forays into science and the scientific method, actually.
- Here's a crazy comment.
I once drowned from OddGuy31.
- Oh my God.
- That's why he's so odd.
- You can drown and not die.
- Yeah.
- You can drown as long as, I think,
I wonder what is the line where they're like,
okay, you're officially drowning.
now I'll come save you.
- Yeah.
- You know, like what is the--
- It's three dunks, it's three dunks.
- Yeah, three dunks.
- Like--
- Up and down three times.
- Yeah.
- And you're drowning?
- Uh-huh.
- It's if you turn blue like water,
'cause you can see the water through your skin.
- Oh, that's why you turn blue when you're drowning.
- Yeah.
- Because your skin is water.
- Here's a comment, one of the last comments on this one.
Drown is God, boat break, drown, get eat by fish,
soft of water i'd i'd die water now tomorrow
he took this guy was drowning when he wrote the message yet
sounds like it
yet there's only one place i can submit somebody could save me right now i
like scrolling past calling nine one one and i'm going on the top ten searching
drowning
comment on it number six is the unknown
who
what would i mean
I mean yeah it's kinda...
Is that... is... from Pokemon?
The unknown...
Pretty much everyone's unknown.
Woah.
If you don't know them.
So.
Um, so...
Here's a comment.
I...
Just... let's... let's try to figure out what this comment means.
Amanda Joy DeRidder is the scariest thing forever,
the worst thing forever,
and the most painful thing forever.
Amanda Joy DeRidder is unknown forever and not real forever.
We are saved by God from Amanda Joy DeRidder.
all things forever and three pluses ad bonus are complete forever all things
forever and three pluses ad bonus are complete forever all things forever and
three pluses ad bonus are complete forever
now i googled that name
and the top result is a is a free background report of someone with a
different name and the second result is from quiz lady dot com and said and
it's a quiz called what are you subconsciously afraid of
wall
who's the author
- Let's see, let me click on this quiz.
- There's one comment here that says,
Amanda Joy DeRidder scares all things
the highest number of times, more than all things,
except Amanda Joy DeRidder forever.
- Should we take this
what are you subconsciously afraid of quiz?
- Yeah, dude, let's do it.
- Question one of 10,
which of these activities do you dread the most?
Work meetings, family gatherings, weddings,
giving a speech, or first date?
- Work meetings. - Work meetings.
If you could travel back in time
to any time period in your life,
which time period would you choose?
Five to 10, 15 to 20, 21 to 26,
26 to 40, I wouldn't wanna go back.
- The Civil War. - 26 to 40.
- Do you regret anything you've done in your life?
Yes, I've made a lot of mistakes.
I regret some things.
I try not to regret anything.
No, the past made me who I am today.
- I regret going-- - Yes, I have a lot
of regrets. - I regret going back
to the Civil War and accidentally joining the wrong side.
- Would you rather be rich or in poor health
or healthy but poor? (laughs)
- Why can't I be healthy and rich?
- Rich and in poor health, healthy but poor.
Why can't I be healthy and rich?
- Yeah, that's a good question.
- Are you currently in a committed relationship?
Yes, and it's great.
No, and I'm not happy about it.
Yes, but it's shaky.
No, and I'm okay with it.
- No, and I'm okay with it.
- Would you consider yourself to be more of an introvert
or an extrovert?
- A little bit of both. - Or a little of both?
Are you taking it at the same time, Patrick?
- Yeah.
- What is your favorite genre of music?
Indie/alternative, R&B, country, folk, or pop?
- I like anything but rap and country.
- Yeah, so folk and pop then.
- Yeah, let's choose folk.
What was your greatest fear as a child?
Well, I mean, that's kinda--
- School.
- Country and rap music.
- What do you believe is the most important thing in life?
Money, family, contentment, love, or career?
- Contentment.
- Yeah.
Do you consider yourself to be a religious
or spiritual person? - No.
- Yes, no, or I'm not sure?
- I'm not sure anymore.
After this list. - All right, here's
calculating our result.
Calculating.
Change.
- Mine says failure. - Wow.
(laughing)
- Where's the--
- You failed the quiz.
- I failed the test.
- You picked the wrong answers, dude.
- I thought it was gonna say something about this weird name.
- No.
- No, where is that coming from?
- You thought it was gonna unlock the secret?
- I don't think we can unlock the secret.
- Is there like a comment section?
- I thought it was like a Cicada 3301 thing
and we were gonna get into the secret society.
- Let's see, let's search it with quotes.
Yeah, no, it looks like it, I don't know.
It came up on another paid website
It says, "What is the scariest thing?"
Weird, dude.
Somebody on the, somebody,
one of the fans figured this out for us.
Yeah.
Find out who Amanda Joy DeRidder is.
And if she's single.
(laughs)
If she's single.
Mm-hmm.
Ghosts are totally in my life.
Hello, I read your name on a list.
I was wondering if you're single.
I read your name and it called you
the scariest thing of all time.
Uh, what's up with you?
Caleb Michael Derrider.
- Derrider. - He's gotta redo it.
- Derrider.
- Ghosts are totally real.
I have seen one once, aspiration once,
and orbs energy, black, clear, green, I should be yellow.
It happens to a hobby of mine and I'm not scared one bit.
If I saw one again, they are just earthbound spirits
that are in limbo, lost after a murder or suicide
and trying to communicate and everyone gets scared.
They're not scary, they used to be like us,
but now they're on another plane.
That's true as hell.
- Getting a little philosophical.
- Yeah.
Yeah, we should get a little, let's get scarier.
Death, not very scary.
Yeah.
You know, it's not much to me, you know.
Number eight, clowns.
Now that's fucking, yeah.
I can't sleep, clowns will get me.
Here's a comment.
This particular clown is the reason I hate them.
I'm not afraid of them, or at least anymore,
when I was a little freaked out, me more than Satan.
But they do make me sweat a lot.
And I think I'm somewhat traumatized by Pennywise from Bon Jovi 17.
[laughs]
Whoa.
Wow.
[laughs]
John Bon Jovi saw Pennywise the Clown
When he was 17.
And he got so scared that he wrote the song "Run Away"
[laughs]
Because he wanted to run away from the clown.
He was thinking about running away from a clown.
Uh-huh.
That's a good point.
Once, a clown sang me "Happy Birthday" and just now I have realized how scary they are.
If that clown would sing me happy birthday, I think I'm gonna be terrified for the rest of my life.
I do remember a clown when I was a kid, a clown at a circus handing me a caramel apple.
And I don't know if there's anything scarier than that.
Yeah, that's so scary.
You know, there's no way he was licensed to do that.
Listen to this one. When I was five, I had a Black Friday. I went to a circus. I loved clowns,
but then the clown got my hand and looked at me. He grabbed me and then done some tricks.
I was so scared that he even looked at me creepily. I screamed hat day. I couldn't sleep.
He had a Black Friday. Oh my God. That is terrifying.
What are the top 10 scariest clowns ever? Number one, gotta be Panty Wise.
Panty Wise.
Number two, Shakes the Clown.
John Wayne the crazy John Wayne crazy mr. smile yeah mr. hands the Joker the
freaking clown the freaky Joker the Joker and the Junker yeah the Joker is
like the Joker but he's kind of covered in junk yeah bullcrap all over him he's
got rappers and cans. Krusty's clown. Go Go the clown. Uh, Bobo. Bobo Bozo no no oh oh.
Bobo Bobo Bozo. Cheech and Chong are some pretty scary clowns. True. When they get too high.
Get over here I'm gonna Cheech your Chong. Don't Cheech, hey man don't Cheech my Chong.
I'm gonna cheat you with Chongsun.
Don't cheat by Chong. That's right.
And then number 10, Cameron.
That's not true.
Number nine is Lost in Space.
Oh, I see you.
I thought you were skipping ahead on the list.
No, Lost in Space would not be scary to me.
I just, you know.
I'd meet an alien and I'd invent technology with them.
That's what I was born to do.
I'd meet like four goofy robots
and I'd sit around watching movies with them.
I go to Planet Cybertron
and I would pilot Optimus Prime's sun.
- If I got lost in space?
- Yeah.
- Probably just eat some astronaut food.
I'd eat frozen mashed potatoes.
I'd eat frozen mashed potatoes
and I would spit them out of my mouth
to make myself fly back to Earth like I'm a rocket.
- Oh, true.
I'd use a fire extinguisher
and I'd propel myself directly into the sun.
- Yeah, but you'd use the fire extinguisher
and you'd put out the sun by accident.
and you'd kill everyone. Yeah just my fucking luck. Yeah and I come back with like a tiny
black rock and they're like what's that? It's the sun. Sorry. You use a fire extinguisher
to propel yourself toward the sun and then you hit it and it like flips and it's just
like it's been a cardboard cutout all along just floating in space. Yeah there's a guy
Is it like an old man projectionist behind it?
Yeah.
Well, guess I'm calling it.
Ah, geez.
Well, that's me then.
Yeah.
Well, there's my cue.
All right, well, I'm gonna head out.
Boss ain't gonna be too happy about this one.
Well, wait, wait, it's your turn.
Come take over.
Yeah.
Number 10, burning alive.
Whatever, man.
I was gonna say, I'm gonna go with number 10.
I'm gonna go with number 10.
Number 10 burning alive.
Whatever man, I would wear fireproof clothes and a whole suit.
I would just stop and roll.
I would pour water on myself.
There's like a thousand solutions to this one.
It's impossible to be scared by.
If I started burning alive I would just die.
So I'd be burning dead.
That's brave.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
Would you kill yourself while you were burning alive so that you wouldn't have to die for
burning alive?
Maybe.
Also, I wonder how much time it takes when you're burning alive until you die for real.
Like, uh, hmm.
Uh, well I know that in stunt, when you're doing a stunt for a movie,
you can only do a full body burn for 30 seconds before it starts to do damage to you.
But that's like if you're wearing like an anti-flammable suit or something.
I should ask that monk who burned alive.
Yeah, hey man, I should call he's still he's still burning. Yeah. Yeah, he's still pretty
Yeah, he's like it's it's like the tomb of the unknown soldier like people just kind of rage against the machine visits him once a year
Yeah, I give him his royalties
That's why he did it. He wanted to be on the cover of a rage against the machine. Yeah
Yeah
Slender man
Now we're getting the really scary stuff
Centerman is scary. No definitely. So no man is definitely scary not to me a guy with no face
You're a man who you can't kiss
Scary no lips
I'd hate to see his thing. I'll say that much this thing has no head
This thing has it has no hole here. Wait. No people. Do you guys see this comment from Jays top 10 list?
It's kind of a script. I want to read it with you guys. Okay, let me find it
It's on the I think the second page of comments. Okay from Jays. So you you be boy. I'll be slender, man
Who me what a good day to go out in the woods?
Hello
Crap, I'll shall kill you
Well, that's a good that's almost better than scary stories. We told that's a beginning middle and end. Yeah
Exposition it's he's going out in the woods and it's got and it's got like kind of like a transitional between each of them to exactly
flow smoothly
This is the shortest or the scariest story you can write in one two, three, four, five six seven eight nine ten
This is the shortest story you can write
1819 20 21 22 the shortest 22 story word stories
stories to scare people with.
Let's do, alright, six words, how about this, six words scary stories.
Not just six word stories.
This is how we'll close it out.
Okay, six words scariest story.
Boo!
Ghost has an evil weird gun.
Alright, mine?
Yeah.
Scary, terrifying, Dracula, werewolf, and mummy.
- Godzilla, ghost, monster.
What are these things all have in concerts?
Everybody just went to my scary concert.
I love that line.
Weird.
- Unlimited homework, no lunch, no recess.
- Whoa. - Oh my God.
The freak from TV ate lunch.
Help, I got scared of something.
Squidward suicide, real footage on TV.
My dad just converted to Islam.
They just elected new president, Carol Baskins.
Is Carol Baskins one word?
No.
Kevin Rudolph, let it, let it rock.
Patrick doesn't know how to say it.
My Reddit account just got banned.
Ouch, I just stubbed my penis.
Lil Wayne has passed away forever.
There once was a graveyard.
Boo!
They did the monster mash.
- Today.
Chuck E. Cheese, no pizza, bathrooms closed.
Chuck E. versus Squidward
Alien versus Predator, a great movie.
[laughter]
I think we got it. I think we nailed the scariest stories.
Thanks for listening. The next one won't be so scary for those with timid hearts.
Happy Halloween. Bye bye. Get out of the bag.
the bag he has a ghost in his bag a ghost went into Patrick's bag mm-hmm all
right goodbye bye