You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- And.
- I have barbecue sauce in my brain
and I'm ready to record.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, my brain is full of barbecue sauce.
- We took a day of rest and it still wasn't enough.
- No.
- Yeah.
- It really was not enough.
Till late. I'm worried. I'm worried. We got it. You think we got it? We might. Does it just make you
Dream where you have gay sex? It does. Really? That's one of the main symptoms. I liked it in the dream
Might have to try it out. You can try it. Yeah. You guys down?
Either of you? Yeah, I'm game. Any takers? Yeah. I would need you to change something about your ass. What about it? If I fucked it.
What about it? Do you want me to wear like a pad on it to make it bigger?
yeah you could put a cushion if you could maybe like get maybe a red sharpie and
kind of like mm-hmm dress it up dress it up like a clown dress it like like in
the Winnie the Pooh movie where they put antlers on it oh yeah exactly like a
dog's mouth yeah that might help me out a little bit okay yeah I could do that
Or, I mean while we're here, only in New York.
Only in New York, could you fuck your friend's dog mouth butt.
Patrick has dog teeth in his butt.
Is that true?
I do, I do have fangs in there.
You have fangs in there?
Fangs.
You got a fang on there?
I got my thingy in there.
Not yet.
You're about to though.
Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
New York City, baby.
That's where I'm Eurekan now.
are when you decide to do that I decided to become New York in yesterday I was
looking at fitted hats uh-huh online which one did you decide on Puerto Rican
one because I am New York in a port tell me what the Puerto Rican flag looks like
it's like the American flag with one star I think he's right yeah yeah I think
you're I think I'm thinking of the Star of David yeah yeah it's like blue it's
two blue lines and it's white in the middle and there's a star David. It's like the American flag but it's black and white except for one stripe which is blue.
Yeah it's like the American flag but there's like an X in the middle.
With stars on it. Yeah it's got like stars on the X. Yeah it's got stars and bars.
Yeah Puerto Ricans are not friendly. I didn't say that. No. That's what you said.
No they are good people. They're good people. They love my front door
and standing in front of it. Mm-hmm. It's like when I think it's a cultural it's
like one on their it's like their holiday yeah yeah Caleb's door Sunday and
Saturday they stand in front of Caleb's door yeah they bring all their family to
him they just kind of stand there yeah it's like um it's like a it's like a
pilgrimage yeah it's like Mecca yeah for Puerto Ricans you have to go to
Caleb's door yeah stand in front of it he's trying to go to the store it's
really nice it's really good I like to learn more about different kinds of
cultures yeah New York City is where your city is the best place to do that
New York City's run by every kind of culture. Each part of the city has its
own personality which is what makes it so interesting. Exactly. You got the
Puerto Ricans, the Italians, the clowns, the mole people, the Spongebobs in the
square pants, the little guys, the funny monkeys, two
brothers named Ted and Todd, Mr. Blister, Todd and Rod, two other brothers
Yes!
They share the same Todd though between those two groups.
Rod and Ted.
Is it Rod and Ted?
What is that Flanders kids name?
Ted and Tad.
Tong and Dingond.
Yeah.
Ted and Nugent.
Yeah, Homer and Simpson is what you're thinking of.
Yeah.
You're thinking of that little yellow ass homie Bart.
I am.
Yeah.
Little homie Bart.
Me and Patrick last night when we were trying to fall...
Don't puff bar it.
I'm puff barring at Pat.
- We were trying to fall asleep
and we just kept going back and forth and saying,
I'm that little ass homie
who fell between the couch cushions.
- I'm that little weird guy.
- I'm that little weird guy that fell between the couch.
- I'm that little ass homie
who gets into the nooks and crannies.
- It is a nightmare sleeping one room over from you two.
- I know.
- And just hearing you guys just keep going.
- You guys were watching TV all night.
- I was asleep, Janna was fucking watching TV.
And you guys were just.
(Janna and Matt laughing)
- We were trying to stay in our entire bedroom.
I'm back to being tired all the time.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Did you leave being tired all the time?
No, I mean the past couple weeks I've been feeling good.
Really?
But I don't know, I think it's just hanging out with you guys.
It drains the energy and life from you.
Stop, stop.
That hurts you though.
Stop.
It'll wake you up.
No, I don't want to get hurt.
I don't want to get hurt again.
I think it's just like...
I pinched his bottom.
I pinched it.
All we did the first day, the first day we got here we stayed up drinking until like five
I should have waited until the last day to do that.
Yeah.
That was so stupid.
And then, yeah, it drained me.
Like I got like, I ate a Euro and walked eight miles yesterday.
I'm like, I feel like fucking shit.
Eight mile.
Oh my god, eight mile.
But I'm also psyching myself out.
That's that soundtrack.
I'm also psyching myself out because it's like, oh man, I feel like shit.
And then it's like, I already had all the COVID symptoms, like, all the time.
I already had all the COVID symptoms in the car. I already had a fever and a cough and a sore throat when I was in the car with you guys.
I had them as soon as you guys picked me up.
I had those before COVID existed.
Every day I think I have COVID and then I realize I just am over.
I've been living in the fucking woods with my parents.
Yeah, and I've been living there too.
Yeah, I've been staying with your mom.
No.
Yeah.
You didn't move in with my mom.
I didn't move in. I'm just staying there.
I'm that underground homie who lives in the dirt.
You're a worm?
Don't.
- Yeah, I'm that wormy little homie that squirms around.
- Dude.
(laughing)
You're like my only worm homie right now.
- You're my only worm friend.
- You're my only worm.
- You're the only-- - I miss my worm.
- Yeah?
- Do you have a pet worm?
- I do now, it's Cameron.
(laughing)
- I do have a pet worm. - Man, I miss my worm.
- I paid $16,000 for a purebred worm.
(laughing)
- Yeah, yeah.
- They breed it to have legs.
- I think you take a nap after this.
- It crawls on my couch.
Yeah, yeah.
He squirms on there, dude.
Mm-hmm.
He squirts on me.
My purebred worm is a freak.
Worms have...
Is it true that worms...
I've never seen a worm poop.
Is it true that worms are easily confused?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Is that true?
Yeah.
If you tell a worm it's not opposite day, it blows its freaking mind.
It doesn't even...
Never tell a worm a riddle.
Yeah.
If you tell a worm a riddle, it'll go underground and hide.
That's scary.
The opposite day paradox.
Have you seen that?
what's that explain it can't it can never be opposite day because that means that
there is a day that's called not opposite day it can never be opposite day I really
sound like that no that's just what like supposed to be she really sounded no oh
yeah we've been fighting all day because this morning Kayla made us lattes and
Patrick asked for Caleb to make a pretzel on his lawn and make the art
Thanks for outing me as a gay artist who makes coffee.
I just feel like we need to be transparent about what's going on.
Yeah.
Yeah, you want to be a transparent.
You want to be Jeffrey Tambor.
You like yelling at people on set.
That's right.
Did he get in trouble for sex or being too funny on set?
I don't remember right now.
It was definitely one of those.
He's too funny when we do the show with him.
Yeah.
He makes us laugh.
We don't get any work done.
No, that would be ridiculous.
That doesn't make any sense.
He's not even that funny, dude.
Yeah, come on.
You know he's not that funny, it's just the good scripts.
True.
It's really the writers.
It's really Michael Bateman.
I love any time that...
It's really Jeffrey Bateman.
Jeffrey Bateman?
Is that his name?
It's really Matthew Bateman.
Matthew Bateman.
It's really...
it's really my counter right now let's just start the list so bad is something
to think about what do you know is it what time oh it's 6 in the morning oh
that's why I'm tired yeah yeah it's 2 p.m. does you have somewhere to be mm-hmm
yeah you got a doctor's appointment I gotta go to the store to do what I gotta
go get groceries. What kind? What are you making? I'm making a big stew. A stew? At my house?
Yeah. I'm making you a stew. I need all four burners. Do you have like a huge cauldron?
Do you have a cast iron pot? Do you mind if I make a fire in the middle of your living
room? Put my cauldron on? I need to smoke this dinosaur leg. Yeah, I'm making potions
in your kitchen. Is that sick or what? Do you have mud? Do you have mud I could bake
into a mud I can use for a potion and little bits of leafs leafs leaves today
we're doing the most romantic things you do with her mm-hmm all men want to be
the most romantic person in the lives of their partners so when Valentine's is
around we always start thinking for long hours how to make this day the most
beautiful and romantic one here are some ideas for the beautiful couples to make
this day an unforgettable one mm-hmm unforgivable one here's a very
unforgivable Valentine's Day. I spent my Valentine's Day with the
unforgivable one. I didn't have a choice. He filled my heart with chocolate. Yeah it
was really scary. Yeah he cast a spell on me. Number one kiss her slowly so she can
feel every spark. That's right. Oh my god. Top comment I plan on kissing my future
woman for the first time slowly and intimately and I'm hoping she will do
the same on February 14th. Women love when you kiss them slow as hell.
Slowly and intimately. When you kiss a woman sensually. Future women love that.
I'm about to go slug on that mouth if you're not careful. It really works out for both
of you. She might not even want the moment to end. It's true. So slow that it's forever.
That's right. Wow. That's what the unforgivable one does. He puts you in an infinite roll
that it lasts forever. He puts you in the phantom zone.
So does the unforgivable one. Definitely the best. Always works and it makes
her feel very special. Women love the yumminess of your lips touching.
Let her enjoy it. Be like. Damn.
Damn. If my boyfriend did this and it was perfect.
Would you love the yumminess of my lips touching you, Patrick?
Yes. Do they have like barbecue sauce chapstick
and shit? They have like Skittles.
I'm sure they have like bacon chapstick.
They probably do.
They better.
It's just bacon fat.
It's not even like...
Yeah.
Cow, beef tallow.
Just eating it like chapstick.
Just going out on a walk and just getting mauled by a pipple.
Getting your lips ripped off.
A Reddit guy wearing bacon...
My lips were too juicy.
Wearing bacon flavored, bacon scented underwear to attract Reddit women and just getting his
dick ripped off by a dog the second he sets foot outside.
I don't think even reddit women like bacon.
I think bacon is a treat for a male.
Fine, a gay reddit man.
Okay. Alright, maybe that's it.
Alright. Okay, maybe we could write a script about this.
A gay guy on reddit.
A gay guy? What would a gay guy on reddit act like?
Probably a guy.
Yeah. Probably like a gay guy.
Yeah. On reddit.
He'd probably type kind of funny. Yeah.
He would probably go on relationship advice and say, "I'm gay, what do?"
[laughter]
Yeah. Instructions unclear. Became gay. I accidentally became gay. I will probably
try this when we are dancing. FML. TIFU. It is the first thing a girl want to be is kissed.
That's true as hell. Where the hell is sex? It should definitely be on top one.
Does sex... sex isn't romantic. Romantic is the stuff that you do so that somebody will have
have
done would you kiss heavy Donkey Kong I would Donkey Kong's metal metal Donkey
Kong could you knock metal Donkey Kong off the stage no like not in a million
years dude just way too heavy number two hug her tightly in the starry night I
love being romantic so beautiful wait we need to test some of these yeah yeah
what would you do look at me look me in the eyes what would you do if I hugged
you tightly in a story night I would probably hug you tight whoa
Wow it works see this could you I'm getting romantic as hell right now
accidentally got so romantic today I got to hey Patrick could you hug a lovely
fool could you throw it back for an adjunct professor could you throw it
back on a lovesick frog could you make could you make a sensitive thug happy
could the lonely play I have a single thought would you let the sensitive
creep hit it yes I would laugh out loud I hugged my girlfriend really tight and I
kissed her on her neck she swear never to let go that is hilarious she slapped
you all hug is the warmest thing in the world
whoa I can barely see stars in the city you got to take it that's why you got to
take her to a like an old house outside of the city yeah yeah yeah yeah the stars
the house the first Resident Evil yeah so many stars out here yeah when we huged it
was felt so good I love huging a girl yeah yeah I've never done that yeah you
you would never huge a girl. I would never huge anybody. No, there's not a chance.
Number three, while watching a sunset hug her from behind kiss her cheek and
whisper in her ear. I would do that to you guys. You would do it to Caleb right
now. Come on. No I don't want to. Go hug her from behind. You just said you would do it.
Hug Caleb from behind. We are not watching a sunset. Oh look the sun's going down. Oh my god two
o'clock that's weird. It must be God telling you to fuck me. I'm not gonna do
that oh my god baby look how beautiful stars are I think it's God saying you
should suck my balls it's amazing number four hug and kiss her from behind and
tell her you love her that's kind of one step up yeah also girls don't like being
kissed from behind that's like a that's like a that's a good I know that's like
that's the thing you would do to the backwards man that's what you do to
fucking backwards man till you do the tongue finger yeah that you don't do that
to a normal woman. The backwards woman? No. Freddy got fingered? That's a different movie.
That's a very different movie. Yeah. Number five, kiss her deeply on the lips and then
say you'll always be mine forever. That's beautiful. Some of these are almost bringing
me to tears. Yeah, the top comment on this with nine up votes is, "Deep kiss, then a
loving passionate I love you, they'll be mine forever can be a little creepy." That's true,
lot of these could be a little creepy not if you're doing it with a romantic
with your romantic friend doing it in a romantic way yeah yeah what if this was
we could read this list as like top ten ways to piss girls off piss strangers
off yeah top ten ways to ruin your relationship with your father yeah like
number six kiss her on her neck while dancing to slow music
with your dad yeah true well you added back of the neck yeah that's even worse
I do it right in the front of the neck, right in the center.
Right on the Adam's apple.
Right on the collarbone.
Daddy, that Adam's apple is looking like a damn tarpon.
I'm going to kiss my dad's Adam's apple.
I'm going to stick my head down your throat and bob for your Adam's apple from inside.
I'm going to turn up for you, dad.
Just watch.
The top comment on this is, "This is the most intense way to express your true feeling for
her, knowing more romantic than this.
Got me the best sex."
I love listening to slow music.
There's a comment that says, "When this I did this, she got nude and striped me and we
had some really nice sex.
Guys, it really works."
Someone striped me.
A little too much information, buddy.
And then another guy says, "Too much information.
Thanks for that."
I love information.
What a pervert.
Yeah, come on.
Don't tell people your girl striped you.
Be romantic.
- Yeah. - You're a sexual dude.
- What do you mean?
- Say I fell in love with my girl physically.
- Yeah. - Don't say we striped
each other. - Mm-mm.
- No, I mean, let's try and think
of some romantic things to do.
- Yeah. - Mm-hmm.
- You could-- - Would you wake up
a pervert from a nightmare?
(laughing)
- No, that wouldn't be romantic.
- Would you?
- You're not supposed to wake people up from nightmares.
- Yeah, you are.
- They could die. - No, they could die.
(laughing)
The nightmare could become real.
- That's true.
- That's like the rule.
- Mm-hmm.
Would you wake up a sensitive pervert and make his dreams come true?
Is he having a nightmare?
Because yeah, maybe.
Because a pervert's nightmare is me sticking my boot down his fucking face.
Fucking face.
Trying to think of a romantic thing to add to this list.
Maybe like bending yourself into their name.
Maybe becoming a pretzel.
Becoming a pretzel that spells their name out.
Yeah, that might be a good idea.
Yeah.
language.
Just for them.
Learning how to become a sign language interpreter.
Learning Spanish so you can talk to them.
That's romantic.
That's true.
Not screaming at them for doing yoga in the middle of the living room.
Asking them to marry you.
Yeah.
What's more romantic than that?
That's true.
Asking them to marry you again.
Yeah, well, can you renew your vows?
Will you marry me all over again?
Will you marry, would you marry, if we could go back in time, would you marry your little
as homie?
Who's the one that got away for you guys?
Cameron.
Patrick.
He's right there.
Wait, you're each other's one who got away?
What?
This might be a huge development, dude.
We might start a new season of the show right now.
We got away from each other.
We got away from each other earlier.
You're right next to each other right now.
No, we got away from each other.
Get back with each other.
I don't think it can happen.
I can't do that.
Not after what happened.
Not after the things that happened to between us.
Too much happened.
Did someone make some decisions?
There was a nightmare involved.
Really?
was a nightmare. Sometimes love is a nightmare and life is a highway. Mm-hmm.
Yeah. Yeah. One day here the next day gone. Yeah. Sometimes the cow jumps over the
moon. Mm-hmm. Sometimes the farmers in the dell. I hate when that happens. That's too
scary for me. This is a sad and sensitive emotional episode. We're deciding to be
sort of a slower and emotional podcast. This is a quiet, this is a, this is if you want to have
lovely dreams yeah put this on or bed we're pivoting to lovely dream podcast
yeah let's do like let's do a guided meditation for someone to go to sleep
ready all right and look in the mirror before you go to sleep you look in there
you look there and you stare in the mirror for five minutes until you see a
freak because you're fucked up brown eyes look at you need be in the lowest
cast you being untouchable look at those fucking eyes you look like shit okay well
you need to go to sleep so you can forget all about yourself. You smell like dog shit.
Patrick's asleep. We're walking Patrick through this. All right, now get in bed. Tuck yourself in.
Tuck yourself into a spot. If you do not have a mom around, tuck yourself in. That's right.
It might be tough. Avoid the wet spot. Avoid that stain. Avoid the wet spot in your bed.
Oh, what's that stain? Do you spill? What's that stain? You spill salsa in your fucking bed? What
What the fuck is that?
It's all right.
Give it a smell.
Double check before you go to sleep.
- Sprinkle some salt on your pillow.
- Oh fuck, you forgot to brush your teeth.
Get back out of bed. - Oh, get up, get up.
Wake up. - Go brush your teeth.
- Go to the bathroom.
All right, now we're back in the bathroom.
- Put your finger in your mouth.
- Put your finger in the toilet.
- Then put it in your mouth.
- Put your finger in the toilet
and then check to see if there's any wind in the room.
See what direction it's coming from.
Find the draft, right?
You feel the wind coming out from a wall.
- Go to the wall. - There's a hole in the wall.
Break the wall open.
Oh my god, you're in the Truman Show.
You see the set.
You're Truman.
You're Truman from the Truman Show.
You see the set, there's cameras everywhere.
Just go back to the bathroom.
Go back, go to bed in the tub.
If I found out that I was on the Truman Show,
I'd probably just keep doing it.
Yeah, why not?
I'd be like, it's a job, it's a living.
(laughing)
You know, you got a pretty cool life.
I would actually start just hamming it up a lot.
how it was it was an island that they built the show around is Jamaica yeah
yeah that's it's a metaphor for Jamaica yeah experiment experiment this is just
indicative of the immigrants experiment can how long can we go without learning
English that's the immigrants what's the craziest name we can tell the guy at
Ellis Island what do you think his life is like show when he lost the you will be
Truman show you are Dark Knight
Terminator - Ricky Morty what do you think he did when he left the dome did
was it got some dome that's right yes some dome from a ho you think you went to
the nearest bitch and got dumb yeah you guys are on site he was like the
Gundam down the fucking most famous guy in the world right yeah how is he gonna
escape I mean just like it instantly just so famous and getting just so many
fucking blowjobs yeah yeah but he would never escape his legacy that's right
would you ever escape your legacy no could no everybody knows me as that
That crazy legacy liver.
I'm a sensitive thug who hides it with a smile.
People know that and that follows me everywhere I go.
People say he laughs through the pain like a thug clown.
Would you stroke a handsome strangler?
Yeah.
That's fucked up dude.
I would.
Why?
What the hell?
Just because.
It's a bad choice.
Yeah, that's bad optics dude.
You're making bad choices right now.
You're making bad choices today.
I think I'm making good decisions.
Number seven, lay with her in her bed and wrap your arms around her. Maybe stroke her hair.
No. He's not even sure. He can maybe stroke her hair. Yeah, maybe. Here's a comment. Joey
lay with Angelica bed. Yep. I've been saying that. I would love that. Can you tell my boyfriend
about this? No. Great idea. You should do that to me. I'll be naked. This is a great idea.
You guys should just come over. I'll be naked, by the way. You can do all the stuff on the
list of me yeah I'll be naked I would tell him to get out of my hair that's so true
that's what that's female humor yeah so my little brother is doing this in this
scenario yeah get out of my hair get out of my
hey get out of my hair you get out of my hair right now number eight watch the
sunset on a silent beach like a nude beach how many times is it gonna be like
a sunset it's romantic Patrick there's only like six romantic things that's
true you just have to mix and match. Sunset, stars, NBA game, playoffs. A giant cake.
A giant cake with your name on it. Monster Jam. That's some real shit. What's number six?
That was all of them. Okay. That was six. Can you knock out? Yeah I can. Amazing. Did
it and it was definitely an option I'd recommend and if it's cold lend her your
coat. But then you're cold. No. I'm not giving up my coat. Listen bitch first
things first. I'm not giving up my coat. We're gonna walk on this beach and you're
not getting this coat you should have should have packed heavier yeah yep you
should have brought your shit you should grow some some hair on your body no I
told you where I'm a teeny but that's more for me than you sunset on a silent
beach is great you might even get something for yourself that evening you
might even get you might even get something for yourself go get a jaw
breaker yeah hey you want to get out of here maybe go get get some job
humongous jawbreaker that we can share it's holding her cheek
Hey, hey, babe, you want to come back to the cul-de-sac? Yeah, sorry if this is too forward
But I'm thinking of doing a get-rich-quick scheme to get a quarter
You want in? Do you want to build a go-kart with me? I'm gonna build a go-kart with me. Hey Ed boy. I
What's up, damn Ed boy. Damn Ed boy, okay. You're good as hell, Ed boy. What up? That's Plank
my impression of plank was saying the whole show nobody could hear him because
they were in this dialogue damn it boy boy you look fine boy take that wig off
is that a hat or a wig it's a hat I think he's wearing an old sock as a hat
yeah did you guys also that's a girl when you were a kid and you had a crush
on him no yeah me neither yeah I didn't know I didn't either
Double D? Double D yeah. It's not like that's co-edited anyway.
Double D got some big, some haters. Ed and Eddie was tricking me into being
gay for sure. Yeah. Yeah. I mean they had... But it didn't work. They had sex on the second episode.
That's true. A jawbreaker is what they called Ed's cock. That's why it was called a jawbreaker.
Because he was busting. He was busting up his jaw. It was too big dude. It was too thick.
Yeah, and that thing on Double D's head, that's right, it was a condom.
Uh-huh.
And the gravy bath?
Yep.
I don't even want to go there.
I don't even want to get into that.
They were in purgatory for having sex.
This isn't Man Cow.
We don't have to get all fucking disgusting like that.
What I just did with my girlfriend or fiancee because we got engaged while doing so.
We got engaged while doing sex.
We got engaged while doing so.
Run through a big field together and then fall down with her, you become tired,
then just kiss her and say she's adorable that's attack of the clones
they do an attack of the clones
they get tired
they get tired and then Padme falls down and he says she's adorable
do you want to go to, you want to drive to a big field and just run around till we fall over?
do you want to go to Naboo and fall down?
no, you're supposed to surprise him, you just chase him around the field
number ten laid down on the roof of your car at midnight and watch the stars
man that's just transformers transformers all you guys are doing movies
you guys are just doing movies come on
most romantic thing but you gotta have a romantic song playing with the
windows down
most romantic song go beer for my horses Toby Keith and Willie Nelson
seal kiss from a rose
twinkle twinkle
as if you're watching the stars at least oh true yeah yeah if anything else
ABC it changes based on the situation yeah yeah
IBS by Cam'ron. If you're on the toilet. Yeah, if you're on the toilet and having a really
hard time. Yeah. You know. Yeah. Don't stand so close to me by the police if you're a teacher
pedophile. Yeah. If you're at a nice dinner. Sing was a teacher. Yeah, that's the funny
part about it. He was like, oh, I was a teacher and this song is inspired by...
Don't stand so close to me. It is funny to make that song and be like, nobody's gonna
know. No one's gonna think about that. Publicly you're like, yeah, it's crazy. When I was
I was a teacher and then you make a song that's like I want to fuck an 11 year old
And it's a ska song. Yeah, he made some fire ska. He did. Yeah, he really did
Yeah, if you're eating a fancy dinner, the most romantic song is eat it
True. Mm-hmm weird out could be romantic if you have a goofy wife. Yeah, if my girl doesn't finish her dinner at the restaurant, I'm leaving
That's right
Yeah
I'm leaving her. I would hate to have a funny wife more than anything dude. Yeah
My comedy wife my comedy wife. He's putting weird out on while we have sex dude
So annoying it depends if it is a clean car ass
Okay, I don't have a car. This is crap
I don't want to dent my roof sounds like a great idea if you don't want to dent your roof go on a diet fatty
He's not doesn't have it. It's not that he's fatty as a horn in his back. I don't know
he's made out of metal now the contenders number 11 nestle her head in your chest
and stroke her hair oh yeah that's Nestle Nestle her head
the nest quick bunny mm-hmm give her a Nestle crunch do you guys have enough
hair on your chest you could nestle somebody and I have no hair on my chest
hairless I want to see that big boy oh my god you have no hair yeah dude I'm
smooth whoa Cameron's a smooth boy Cameron smooth yeah you could water slide
I mean this is Cameron's smooth summer dude.
Yeah you didn't know I told you that before.
You've told me.
I'm smooth.
I've told you I'm smooth yeah.
I've definitely told you.
We were just walking around LA both very depressed.
Man I'm smooth.
I've absolutely told you man I have no hair on my body.
We definitely had that conversation at least twice.
No hair.
No I have hair.
I got hair where it counts.
All over your penis.
Yeah inside my penis.
Yeah oh my god.
I got hair on my penis goes all the way to the tip dude.
Jesus Christ.
I put the hair into my pee hole when I'm not using it.
And then it sprouts.
And it sprouts out like a flower.
Like a magic beanstalk.
Like a bang gun from a Joker gun flag in the gun.
Your chest, you took off your shirt and the flag came out and it said hair on it.
Yeah.
There's no hair.
Take her to a restaurant where there is just one table and not a single person around with
light music and candlelight. That's not a restaurant. Take you to a restaurant where there's nobody
and there's no food, no waiter, it's a single table, there's one light and a candle. That's
the best restaurant. And that's the most amazing restaurant in the world. It's called Romance
Dishes. It's called your garage. Yeah, it's called the basement. Romance Dishes would be
a really good name for a restaurant. That is a good name for a romantic restaurant. The
sexual plate. I just want to read this comment from the last one really quick. Okay. Before
girlfriend one videos games to girlfriend after girlfriend one girlfriend
99 video games for me is kind of opposite yeah yeah oh yeah I switch it up on her
yeah I actually switched up on my wife for the one who said he hates the one
whoever think of this it was your fault you are not supposed to turn around you
are supposed to go to her and tell her how you feel and I'm only 14 years old
but trust me do it again but instead of turning around go to her and ask her to
dance or something do everything her way everything's always her top comment is
there are no restaurants with only one table it's true try New York City you
might be surprised yeah yeah number 13 send a written message through any
little street boy expressing your love to her any little street boy little
street boy would you mind taking my message comment says I would chase away
the street boy every girl wants a little street boy who loves women nice street
boy that delivers those messages
little boy come over here here's $10 you whisper in that girl's ear for me we get
real nice and close number 14 watch duck dynasty reruns and drink boxed wine over
crushed ice swag swag oh Tom at best one she loved it LMFA oh yeah she loved it
I bet you loved that she's dead have done this numerous times LM a oh wow
someone says gets the fluids flowing number 15 kiss her in the middle of her
sentence yeah hey could you please leave me no that's the end of the sentence
taxi taxi no she's planning on saying it two more times okay come on dude I'm an
amateur I've done that shit I want John C Reilly to do this to me so bad like I
talk so much and he kisses me to shut up
you dumb bitch shut up I'm gonna kiss you would you like to get a kiss listen I'm
gonna kiss you right now hey listen I gotta kiss you yeah they told me to do a
mid-sentence they told me have to do a mid-sentence you do realize that a woman
can also kiss her man in the middle of his sentence I did not realize to that
you need there's freaking feminists on the top 10 stock these fucking every
These feminists think that women can kiss back.
Number 16, pull her away from her friends and sing songs for her.
Come here. Hey, come here. Hey, come here.
Fuck the rules.
There they go. Back in stadiums and shady spaces.
Love it. Now there you go.
Top comment.
I sing to my girl every time I like to wake up with a beautiful song.
I love you when your hair turns gray.
I'll love you if you gain a little weight.
'Cause she is the rose that blooms in my garden.
Gosh, I'm so in love with her every sec of my day.
It will be three years next month.
Baby, can I sing for you?
Can I freestyle for you real quick?
I love little girls, they make me feel so good.
Hi-ho the Dario, the farmer in the dell.
She loves when I do my ukulele version of "Shippin' Up to Boston."
I'm that diddly darn doge.
How much is that dog in the window?
How much could that little dog be?
Well yes, but timing is everything.
If she's trying to discuss something with some friends
and you pull her away and start Rickrolling her,
there's a 50/50 chance you're doomed forever.
It's gonna work.
Nah, the Rickroll, bitches love getting Rickrolled.
'Cause you're telling them
that you're never gonna give them up.
Yeah.
When me and Jennifer started dating,
she didn't know what that was, dude.
Damn. What?
Can you imagine somebody not knowing what a Rickroll is?
Yeah, I know.
That's crazy, dude.
My first Rickroll.
Yeah.
Spotify ads now that Rickroll you.
It was like dating a caveman.
That sounds fun though.
Yeah.
Here's the bottom comment.
I would ask him if he is crazy because he sounds like a cock crowing.
You sound like a serious crowing cock right now.
Yeah.
Hey girl, let me sing to you.
You sound like a cock growing.
Hey.
There we go.
Your sound makes my cock growing.
Okay.
You're, you're, no, it's probably the end of it, huh?
right take her on a long drive away from her house in the evening do you want to
get as far away from your house as possible
be careful she doesn't feel like she's being kidnapped I promise I'm not
kidnapping you that'll do it yes and make sure to have the windows down so
you can feel the fresh air if it is warm outside and put them up if you start to
talk to her you do not want anyone hearing what you have to say to her
outside the car definitely yeah no it's bad news dude number 18 every time you
see her after a certain period of time wrap your arms around her and refuse to
let go playfully of course after a certain period of time does that mean
did refuse to let go I'm refusing to let go of you I don't like I really don't
like this list it does feel like it's made by adults yeah I do this to my girl
all the time she hates me tries struggling to try and get me but then we normally
turns into real play if you know what I mean turns in a real play calling don't
forget the real play real play no it's for playing in real play yeah yeah
Patrick's disgusted Patrick is literally trying to make himself vomit right now
yeah I'm gonna puke I'm gonna puke yeah you have a puke number 19 get some
bonfire in your room and sit on the carpet with her watching her favorite film.
They're talking about the Dan Soder show. Yeah, that's true. Listen to the bonfire.
Listen to the bonfire with your wife. She's gonna go crazy for the Gillis episodes.
Ah, no bonfire in the house or in my room. This will not make me want to have sex with you.
It will make me want to call 9-1-1 and say fire.
Mm-hmm.
Boop boop boop.
Fire.
Does it hang up?
Did you say tire?
If her favorite movies are crappy rom-coms,
then fuck no from Beatles fan 1964.
I hate when my bitch like rom-coms.
Holding hands while walking on a private beach,
just the two of you.
Wow.
Top comment, he just did it.
He just did it.
Yeah, he actually just did that.
When my boyfriend takes me on a private beach,
I go on Google, I search holding hands
while walking on a private beach,
and I comment on the first thing they say.
He just did it.
I literally just did that shit right there.
Number 21 goes skinny dipping.
You guys ever gone skinny dipping?
No. No.
I did it one time. In the tub.
(laughing)
I go skinny dipping in the shower.
Yeah.
I went skinny dipping in Yosemite,
and there's a picture of me
with the smallest penis in the world.
Yeah. Can I see?
Yeah, it's somewhere in this house.
But you have to find it.
And you have to solve my riddle.
I want to play a game.
Under the couch, it may lie.
That's the riddle.
(laughter)
- That's the riddle.
- That's the entire riddle.
- Number--
- In the fridge you may find the photo.
- Number 22, take her to the terrace under the moon
and say even the envious moon is hiding behind the clouds.
- Hey baby.
- And the top comment is, it's terribly crap.
- It's true.
- Even the envious moon is hiding behind the clouds.
- Even that envious moon is hiding behind the clouds.
- It's terribly crap, isn't it?
- I'm in the terrace under the moon, by the way.
I know it's a hall.
- Number 23, watch a movie with her.
- No, this never works. - Top comment.
Did this to my wife.
And gave it. (laughing)
- I'm gonna have to pull this one out.
- Did this to my wife and gave her a back rub
and said I love you.
That night we also had her favorite
for our anniversary dinner.
Do this for her when you are in a fight
or for any occasion.
Trust me, it works.
I love her.
- Okay, dude, you don't have to rub it in at the end.
I love my wife. I love my wife. Yeah, who cares?
I watch movies with my wife every time the kids are asleep. Rent the proposal and do this. We both love it. Go to Redbox now.
That's a Redbox ad. Love to and dim lighting comfortably between her arms.
I love it my big wife holds me. We watch Pixar movies.
Did this ending up having sex me and her will Netflix and chill. Sincerely Christian.
Luke Ross, Coking, Cook, Book, Dree, Up, Music, CD, Dace.
Let her pick the movie dude?
Fuck no.
Yeah, no.
We're gonna pick fucking True Detective Season 1, the part where Matthew McConaughey has
sex with the wife.
Yeah.
She's gonna just wanna watch that over and over again.
It's yucky.
It's yucky dude.
That's disgusting.
Listen, I get that he has a nice square ass.
No man, we're gonna watch the Raid Redemption.
That's right.
every time a man gets his arm broken I'm gonna say I will do that to you if you
pick the wrong movie next time. Maybe it's time for our Friday Ouvé Bowl marathon.
We're watching Rampage and Postal. We're gonna watch Falling Down.
Assault on Wall Street. Yeah. Yeah. And then we're gonna make a movie. Yeah.
We made a movie last night, an Ouvé Bowl movie. Number 24, get blue lights in your
room and pleasant slow music. Perfect for a dance. Mm-hmm. That's like an
underwater dance I love it you're amazing at this I'm naked you should come over
you think anyone got laid off this list there's a lot of literally that's a
pedophile hunter yeah true yeah take number 25 wedding restaurant with a ring
in her glass you're so tired you can't even read try it again take her to to her
favorite restaurant with a wedding ring in her glass that's right so this one's
just proposed to her comment is a top comment with 17 upvotes is that's how
people die safety should always come first you dick-licking jackass 17 people
saw that and were like hell yeah yeah fucking asshole piece of shit stupid
idiot now that's dangerous only a man who hates his wife or his girlfriend
would try something like that yeah you have plausible deniability there you
know that's a good way to kill your wife probably hmm bubble bath candles low
light and just you her and soft music I would do that with Patrick I let it
happen was last time you took a bubble bath I don't know it really is fun
relaxing together maybe it really is fun relaxing together in a warm soapy bathtub
everyone should try it at least once mm-hmm hot water or cold freezing cold
ice have you ever seen Titanic yeah it's romantic my wife LeBron James again my
ice bath. Number 28 go to kiss her lips and quickly peck her on the nose. What are
you a bird? Come on man. What are you a peck? Like a bird. I'm that little bird homie who
pecks you. I'm the bird who pecks. If I was a bird would you give me your seeds? Yeah
now that's it now breaking bird. Breaking bird. Breaking bird I'm the one who pecks.
Bird is bad. Birding bad. Bird pit. Breaking my butt.
come on dude you gotta make bird in flight club oh my god with Ed Ed penguin
Norton beak Norton whoa beak Norton might be a great guy
beak Norton be man I'm beak man or beakman's world and he's a bird this time
okay what other birds things a flying the flying Dutch I I flew over the
cuckoo's nest mm-hmm cuz I'm a bird I am a bird sponge bird squares nest okay
sponge birds beak beaks wings eek word beak word tentacles is beaks Burke yeah
okay right okay like branch Burke yeah yeah or it could be branch bird there
are yeah yeah birds branch the birds branch can we start a new podcast called
the birds branch where we talk about bird news?
The God Bird.
The God Feather.
Come on dude.
That was my first try.
The fucking bird.
The fucking bird?
Mm-hmm.
The fucking, how to kill a fucking bird?
That was the title.
How to kill a fucking bird.
That was, that was, that was, that was her, that was whatever her name is, her first Google
search.
Yeah.
Her name was Jane Rand.
Rand. Her name was Jem Hadar. Number 29, during hugging time tell her that you
adore her. Hugging time? Have I ever told you I adore you? Hey, it's three o'clock!
It's hugging time! Yeah, the wives they go out and they stick their
fucking huge asses and tits out of the window and ring a bell. It's hugging time.
Number 33, kiss her in the rain. That's not romantic to me. Yeah, that's wet and scary.
and scary and horny. You could get a disease if you're in the rain for too long. I need
to be dried out to even have the blood flow moving in my penis. Number 34, do everything
she loves doing and support her every day. Seems like a bit much. That's a bit sus. Yeah.
Always keep a short distance or you will get up in the friend zone. I'm trying to not get
friend zoned by my wife right now. Yeah. I don't want to be too nice to her. Number 35,
take her to the place you met in the beginning of it all. Sounds like the subtitle of like
a third action movie in a series. Yeah. Here's where you're not. Domino's the
beginning. I was your boss. The beginning of it all. Take her to the place you met
in the beginning of it all. Number 36, make love to her. There we go. Yes, that's
what I really want. Number 37, drive-in. The drive-in is amazing. Did that for my
first date with my girlfriend and halfway through the first movie, fireworks
at the fairgrounds next to the drive-in started going off and he started smiling
and blushing which was so adorable and make sure the movies are scary movies
because she will scoot closer to you and you just wrap your arms around her and
hold her tight and assure her that she is safe with you it works trust me so the
whole thing with the drive-in is it's a movie and get a blowjob at exactly yeah
pretty much sick yeah kind of cut out I mean you get a blowjob who's the
middleman in that situation is the guy who is the guy who's blocking the guy
for blowing you the guy who's watching your day at home the guy who's sorry
baby the middleman got here first we got to cut him out let's go drive in next
Next time I hate regal cinemas.
Would you get middle from a man?
No, I would.
My bitch gave me some fire-ass middle last night.
Give me some of that middle hole.
You know what I'm talking about.
No I don't.
Number 38, climb a tree.
Tree climbing is so swagalicious.
Makes her and I happy.
Amen.
When she's happy, I'm happy.
Love you Natalia.
Do you guys know I'm amazing at climbing trees?
Yeah, I've seen you.
That makes sense.
I can get to the top of any tree.
How does that make sense?
What the fuck is that supposed to mean?
You're a monkey.
Yeah.
Wow.
You would say that to an Italian.
You are an ape's friend.
I'm not a friend.
Mm-hmm.
No.
Number 39, text and tell her when you think of her.
Every 10 seconds, just thought of you, just thought of you, just thought of you.
Just thinking of you right now.
Just remembered I texted you already.
Sorry.
Just thought of you again.
Eating lunch.
Pooped my pants.
Need help.
Will you clean me up?
Take a nap.
9-1-1, 9-1-1.
40, go with her to the movies and eat popcorn.
Oh, you know what they're talking about when they say popcorn.
Yeah, I love you my girl's popcorn.
Because she's such a diseased fucked up vagina.
It's all bumpy and shit.
It looks like popcorn down there.
I say, I love butter on that one.
I love your lizard-y little pussy.
Yeah.
Can we get parmesan cheese on there?
Ugh, ah, ah, I'm leaving.
uh... number forty two go to six flags and tell you love her on the top of the
giant drop
that would be perfect number forty three if she felt asleep on a couch or if she's
tired bring her to the bed lie her down and wrap your body around her saying i
love you
the snake
a statement that does that's what a snake with the move
number forty five dim the lights but i'm marvin the gays let's get on a mix we
love
it's true that's a little obvious to me that you have a number i don't think
I think that's a good song to have sex with,
'cause songs that you have sex to
should not talk about sex.
'Cause it's like an instruction book, you know?
Then you're following Ikea instructions.
Number 48, "Taker Swimming."
And we have kind of like a stand-up comedy,
like sassy reply comment on this.
If you read it in maybe like a Bill Burr voice or like--
'Cause I do.
(mumbles)
The local pool and watch soggy band-aids
floating past each other.
Or play a game called,
guess which person is using the pool right now?
- He's urinating in the pool right now.
You're the one who can't read.
- No, Bill Burr can't read.
It's the character I do.
- It's the character who can't read.
- Number 49, introduce her to your family.
- That's so romantic.
- That's one of the most romantic things you can do.
- Here's the woman I wish you looked like.
(laughing)
- Can you look like this?
- Can you look like my mom and dad?
- Take her on a walk to the woods, that's scary.
- Number 52, play video games together.
- That's right.
his call of duty ghosts but I think it'll work mm-hmm
today's women always want to play video games about depression yeah shut up you
do you like playing those no you do no he is you literally do I literally don't
you literally do I like I love awesome games about number 59 spend a rainy
night in the backseat of a car with her be homeless yeah just be homeless girls
love it when the guys are almost tiny Patrick would you lie with a homeless
female I would I knew this guy who was like my youth pastor growing up and he I
may have talked about this but he like did this thing where he was like I'm
gonna be I'm gonna to support homeless people here's what I'm gonna do I'm
gonna be homeless for a week and he just like took a tent downtown and he made it
like five hours before he was like somebody tried to kill me
goddamn what a pussy yeah he's I could do it for ten years I could live in a tent
for 10 years if I had full heating and air conditioning.
If I had Wi-Fi and electronics.
If I had Wi-Fi it would be over for me.
And a TV in there.
Would you be homeless if you got a billion dollars from it?
Yesterday we walked by a kid around here who was wearing a t-shirt, like a little kid who
was wearing a t-shirt that was the Wi-Fi logo, but each of the bars had words in them and
it said, "What's the deal with Wi-Fi?"
What the fuck?
New York is a crazy place.
That's a good shirt.
The thing is, everybody's trying to be a comedian.
Yeah.
So you got kids.
The kid's working on his type 5.
Listen, kid, that's the funniest shirt I've ever seen, but I'm kind of the comedian in this neighborhood.
I'm the comedian of New York.
I'm going to drive you out of here.
Mm-hmm.
I'm that New York comedian.
You have to leave.
I'm that New York comedian with the funny-ass jokes.
I'm that New York comedian that talks about his parents.
I'm that tiny little comedian you can't see on stage.
Yeah.
Spotlight can't find me. Yeah. Because I'm too small. I'm that invisible comedian.
I'm that tiny little comedian that uses the mic wire like a jump rope.
Mm-hmm. We should all, when stand-up comes back, we need to, I mean it's
different now. We got to come up with some characters to be doing on
stage. Yeah. You know, some funny kind of meta like Neil Hamburger type shit.
Basically I'll be headlining a lot of shows as your tiniest homie. Yeah.
true I gotta be the prince yeah the prince of poppers the prince of poppers
yeah yeah yeah yeah it's sliding down my fucking leg just about to be good I'm
that tiny ass homie who visits a crack in the sidewalk like it's the Grand
Canyon do you think ants have like parts of the sidewalk that they think are cool
This is my favorite part. This is my favorite ant hill kids were coming up on the best part of the sidewalk right now
You think ants have playdates with each other? Oh, you can't have wives and sons
Yeah, they have the one queen is the one wife, but do you know it's just other girl ants?
No, but they don't they're not married, but they get those are those single those are those single freak females
They get a little side ant though. Yeah a little side ant. Yeah, here is the queen side ant man
I'm trying to get some thorax from a side and
My side ain't got that good-ass thorax.
You got a good thorax.
That's some real shit, dude.
Ooh, wouldn't the thorax crunch on you?
Oh, man.
Is it ants?
I'm trying to get some mandibles.
Let me look to see what an ant's penis looks like.
I'm trying to get pedipalps from a spider.
Can you look it up?
Look it up on the laptop.
I want to see what it looks like.
An ant's penis?
Do they have a penis?
No, they have sex with their minds.
Ants could be psychic.
You could tell me ants use psychic powers.
I would say yes.
I would say science is true.
I believe science.
Science is real.
Oh, it looks like this.
Oh, okay.
Let me see.
Interesting.
It's an anthill in the shape of a penis.
Did you search an ant's penis?
Do ants have penises?
Strangest creatures.
That thing is pretty strange.
That's a penis.
I don't think that ants have penises.
Let's just look at penises for the rest of this episode.
It doesn't look like it.
I think it's an answer, but what does that go up?
Justin Bieber where they circled his like crotch and it says a penis for ants.
That damn.
Zoolander shouldn't have said that.
Yeah, Zoolander kind of messed the game up with that.
Zoolander went off when he said that.
Zoolander snapped and said is this a school for penises?
What is this a school for penises?
My little penis?
That's what he says when he has sex with a girl.
What is this?
What is this a vagina for penises?
What is this college for my wiener?
You like my wiener?
It went to college.
Yeah, I have the smartest wiener in the west.
That's just some real shit, brother.
We're out of items on this list.
Oh, damn.
Yeah.
That's alright.
Let me get another beer.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I think I might get another beer, dude.
Alright, get another beer.
Let's do a list of what's in Caleb's fridge.
Okay.
Eggs, yogurt, beer, a jar of dots.
there's a jar of dots. No, it's garlic. That's just a bunch of white dots. Jam, broccoli, an urn.
A frozen condom. Eggs. Oh shit. Oh shit. We sped through this list.
We sped through this list. Oh yeah, we started at 10 minutes because you were crying.
Oh yeah, that's true. Why do you keep crying, Pat? Yeah, there we go. Get this.
The noise of beer.
Makes me so hungry for a beer sandwich.
There's something delicious about the noise of beer.
When you guys were kids, did you ever have beer bread?
The noisiest beer of all time.
I don't think so.
I always, I always thought that that was a
You just don't want to have to finish the episode.
Yeah.
That's fine. He's gone.
Now we finally get to go on our date.
Yeah. Hey. Hey.
What's your favorite song?
Anything that you like.
I like that you like I like the wheels on the bus
Okay, I take it back. Yeah. Yeah, I was trying to trick you. I don't like song. My favorite song is
changes by Tupac
That's right. Favorite song is the that puberty song from the Brady Bunch
I'm a fan of tickle biddies myself
Yeah, tickle biddies is kind of my jam
I'm a big fan of that Mortal Kombat parody rap take all the goodies. You know, that's fine as a first song I ever heard
Yeah
That was actually the first one. We did that on the last episode. It's funnier if you do it with
Tiggle Bitty. If you do it every episode. Yeah. If just for the rest of my life
anybody says yeah do you like that song? I'll be like yeah. That's actually the
only song I've ever heard. It's really weird. Patrick's on mic in the bathroom.
I'm in the bathroom. I'm taking so many pees. This is the noise of
Patrick peeing. Mm-hmm. Pat is peeing on the ground right now. That's my noise.
shaking up his penis to prepare to pee.
That's true.
That's what it sounds like when Patrick jacks off.
Get out of here mom, I'm trying to get, I'm trying to start peeing soon.
I'm trying to start it.
I'm trying to get the pee to come to the end of my thing.
I'm trying to start it up.
What was the worst thing, did you guys ever get?
Lying down in the night next to Patrick and just hearing.
(laughing)
Did you guys ever get caught
jacking off as a kid?
No, I never did.
What? I did not either.
porn in my search history, but I never got caught like jacking off.
I got caught. I got caught my I had a bathroom that did not have a lock on the door and my
little brother walked in and he saw he just he just saw me holding my penis and jacking off and
he's like what the fuck are you doing and that's not how you pee. I just panicked and said I was
reading. I'm reading. I was like I'm reading. I'm reading the braille. I'm reading. You know how you
play with your wiener while you read to focus? You know how you play with your thingy? I'm a
- Like a tactile learner.
That's just how it is, dude.
It's like a fidget spinner.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, my penis is called a ring spinner.
- When it's your penis, it's more of a midget spinner.
- Oh!
Are you serious, dude?
- Would you take a midget for a spin?
(laughing)
- I would.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- That's rude.
- Pretty much anything you've asked me, I would do.
- When was the last time you guys saw a midget?
we saw a guy was really short yesterday wasn't he wasn't it but it was very
small though he was like he was like he was like from from like a three-quarter
size of her to you yeah it was like for a he was next up out of Atlanta for sure
yeah the funniest little person I ever saw was one time me and Alex got off the
train in Austin and the doors opened we're having like a really serious
conversation about like his relationship problems yeah and the doors opened and
And we just saw like a guy who was just a head on the ground.
Just a head coming out of a puddle.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
He had like a voice for that shit.
Laugh Patrick.
Laugh.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Alright cancel Patrick.
He's falling asleep.
You piece of shit.
He doesn't even think it's funny to find a little guy.
Do you want to go get like a Red Bull or something before we do D&D?
Yeah.
Yeah we got to do some D&D action a little bit.
Oh yeah that's right.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Or just nap.
Yeah maybe.
We can all just hop in my bed.
- Like a doll hop.
- Ooh.
- Yeah.
- Ooh, yesterday Caleb took a three hour nap
and locked us out of his house.
- It's true.
- I gave you my keys.
- Yeah, we did have the keys.
- They didn't work.
You gave us fake keys.
(laughing)
- You gave us the baby keys.
- Yeah, I'm handing you a thing of,
like a plastic toy key,
and I'm like, okay, this one opens the front door.
This one opens the deadbolt.
- Yeah.
- And this one--
- This one opens the toy chest.
- This is the tastiest one.
- Yeah.
- If you're gonna suck on them.
(laughing)
This is the best one for chewing on.
Caleb locked us out of his bedroom when he was spending special time in there.
He should let me sleep at the foot of his bed.
Yeah, we were scratching at the door and whining and he wasn't doing anything about it.
You guys, I tried sliding food under the door.
But my pot roast was too big. It wouldn't fit.
I got that tall-ass pot roast.
Yeah.
You're gonna want to take a bite.
I think he did a flat pot roast.
I asked my mom to make the pot roast flat so I can slide it under my brother's door.
Yeah, so I don't have to talk to him.
I think I do. I have a huge gap in the bottom of that door. We could slide some stuff.
If you guys want to like pass each other stuff.
Yeah, can we whisper under there at night?
Yeah, I can't hear everything you guys say at night. That's kind of why.
What did we say last night?
We didn't say that.
That might have been the TV.
That was the TV.
Yeah.
Yeah, you guys said, "Doh!"
yeah so eat my shorts we said no yeah we said I need some day braces I Nisa do you
think they're gonna add a new character to the Simpsons yeah when when the when
the lady who does Bart dies they're gonna add Bart - and he sounds like this
I am Bart - oh but then people think he's saying Bart - mm-hmm well that's it
that's their fault finally yeah the Simpsons is sorry if you'd educate you
about Bart yeah versus El Barto Bart versus El Barto the battle of the
century that's right Wow yeah our Valvers Capcom
Carvel Carvel verse Capcom like the cakes yeah just a bunch of ice cream fighting
whatever Capcom is that's pretty good man how about Carvel ice cream versus
cookies okay they're doing a Marvel vs. Capcom self-fighting game but it's yeah
it's it's candy versus cookies what do you guys think yeah all right have a good
day everybody everybody