you're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
- [Computer] Welcome to the podcast.
- You're a crap monster.
(explosion)
- Polish man, the Polish man, Polish man, the Polish man.
I can walk backwards only way I can.
- There we go.
- Woo!
- It's about Cameron.
- I think when you guys--
- I think when Freddie got fingered
is a story about the Polish experience in America.
it's where you find a treasure in the toilet yep yeah you work at the cheese
sandwich shop mm-hmm that she's saying no we know this because this is all
things that are true about Cameron you do say daddy would you like some sausages
that is a pretty keystone part of the Polish experience I like wearing this I
like wearing this tall XL Paul sweater yeah I look good I think when you guys
leave I'm gonna kill myself really yeah you're gonna miss us too much I'm gonna
I'm gonna be up at night and I'm gonna take my photos and I'm gonna hold them in bed.
You're gonna go? You're gonna take your photos?
The photos that I took of you guys while you were asleep.
Oh yeah, yeah. Yeah, and I'm gonna hold them in bed and I'm gonna look at them.
Patrick took a photo of me while I was asleep the other day and it woke me up.
That'll wake you up. He put the flash right in my face.
Shut up you daffy duck motherfucker.
Man, shut the hell up.
Man, you daft punk. You daffy duck motherfucker.
You daft punk.
Put some pants on Daffy.
I don't even think Daffy wears a shirt.
Put a shirt on Daffy.
He ain't got no underpants on.
I don't think he wears anything.
Daffy wears drawers.
Put them on.
No one wants to see that tail.
Yeah, they should be calling him naked duck.
They should call him Laffy Duck because that's what he makes me do.
Yeah, he makes me Laffy Duck.
Laffy Duck.
They should make him, they should make him Sadly Duck.
And he wishes he was anything else.
And guess how he does things?
Sadly.
The same.
The saddest duck.
I'm the saddest duck.
I'm imagining a sad duck and it's almost bringing me to a tearful state.
He dives underwater to catch a fish.
He never comes back up.
No.
He's never coming up for air.
Scrooge.
He's sinking.
He's sinking in water.
He's Scrooge Bogovich.
That's right.
That's right. That's a spoiler for something that's gonna come out that's very fun.
Yeah. There you go Pat. You got it unlocked today dude. I'm on the top of my game. Top of his game.
He hits you with the back with the Polish man. Uh-huh. Yeah. Anything else? You gonna bust out a
new impression today? Oh maybe. Yeah? Here's my impression. Donald Trump in the restroom.
go. Donald Trump at the hospital. Yeah, vomiting blood. He's eating six meals. By the time this
comes out Donald Trump will be dead. That's a TikTok Ben made. I'm dead. What? We gotta
cut that one out. That's a TikTok Ben made. I just remembered. Well you just say that
then I'm not going anything else.
Diet Ben Loftus.
Guys we have to cut that out.
The Polish man is actually, I realized that was referencing
Freddy Guffinger.
Shut up.
You know what, new impression to save it.
This is my impression of
Alexander
the bust.
This is my impression of that guy.
Caleb bought me because he thinks he looks like me. I didn't buy that.
Your allegations the great. Allegations the great? Not true. That's your name.
Allegations the great. Allegations the great. Your allegations the great amount.
All the allegations against me is that I'm a great guy.
Nobody says that. People never say you're great. Allegedly a great guy. People say
allegedly all the time no who what your mailman no that's part of his job he's
a moron mailman and all he was a bitch whoa mm-hmm that's a working-class hero
you're talking right now no you ever give your mailman a Christmas present and
he's ungrateful yeah that happened to me with my mailman yeah I got two packages
for you mailman yeah mr. mr. righty and Fred gave him a Starbucks gift card news
like just this you're a mailman what were you anything here mailman I don't know
your name put this blindfold on he's also he's that mailman was terrified of our
dog who are my dog is like a natural enemies he's like a but she's like a
tiny little dog that's very fat and long you call him this mailman a pussy yes
All right. Maybe we had the same mailman. Yeah probably. Maybe you guys had the
same mailman. Oh you guys are brothers. I forget that. We lived in the same house
with the same mailman. That's true. No you weren't there when that guy. No it was
Neil. Neil was there. Neil had come over to my apartment and the mailman was
yelling at us about the mail because we didn't check it for like two days.
And he was like, "Hi! Yeah you got to check your mail!" That's rude. I was like, "What?"
yeah you guys check it all recently our mail our mailbox outside the like the
door is like hanging off and sometimes it falls off and the mailman and it even
it weighs like fucking a pound maybe and a mailman recently like I opened the
doors he was delivering the mail and he was like you got to do something about
this door and I was like what he's like your mailbox the door fell off could have
killed me I was like what are you talking about dude like I'm just fix it
okay is dangerous yeah mailman love to do shit like this drama queen yeah a mailman
is like it's like if you want to be a police officer but then you fail at a
firefighter school yeah that's a man it's like the lowest level of public
service yeah yeah yeah but I have more respect for mailman that I have the most
respect from garbage men because they do that job while they do the stinky ass
job yeah they do a stinky ass job well I love I love every mailman except for
that one mailman I had in Austin.
- What? - That guy.
- He just rubbed you the wrong way?
- He yelled at me.
- I'm sorry.
- Caleb, I'm noticing you have opposable pinky toes.
- I have-- - Your pinky toes
are sideways. - Oh my God, dude.
That looks like a baby's thumb.
- Yeah. - What?
- What is going on?
- I don't know.
- Pick something up. - It's like literally
turned sideways. - Pick something up with that.
- I have, you know what it is?
I have extremely wide feet in my entire life.
- Did your feet get bound?
- Kind of, by vans off the walls.
- Vans off the, what is that?
even one of the shoes they make.
- That's their logo, slogan.
That's their slo-gone.
- Their slogan.
- No, but Vans old school, I've worn them since I was a kid
and they have definitely, my feet are too wide for them
but they don't make a wide version.
- Yeah, they do.
- So they've, well not for me.
- You just have to look.
- They don't sell it at journeys.
- Oh yeah, that's true.
- So my pinky toes on both feet are pretty much bent.
- All the ads for the Vans,
all the ads for people wearing Vans
had people wearing with hair in them.
So Caleb got these shoes.
- Wait, what the fuck's going on with Pat's fucking pinky toe?
look at that shit.
What, that one?
Oh, it was fucked up.
It was fucked up a second ago.
Wait a second!
Yeah, you're not getting out of this one.
I'm just accusing you.
I'm just trying to get the heat off of me.
Oh, look at that weird thing out.
You guys just missed that.
Give me your hand.
Ugh.
Ugh, dude.
Can I smell this?
Wow.
What does Patrick's feet smell like?
It smells like the store.
It smells like a zambonied floor.
Yeah, it smells exactly like the store.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to get out of this.
the store. It smells like a zambonied floor. Smells like the store. Yeah, it smells exactly
like the store. Where you been boy? You been walking around the store barefoot? You been
around the store again? I might. Don't play coy with me you white bitch. I might be going
to the store sometimes. To do what? I know it's not working. It's some shopping. For
with what money with your money I knew it Patrick's been taking my money and
shopping this is a shopping barefoot at the store we you know what we didn't you
do to the only store in Ridgewood that's sure went no shirt no shoes you will
give you service for the last one that's right no shirt no shoes hey don't have a
nice outfit that's the shirt on get get out but if you don't have shoes on we
love you. Barefoot is legal. I didn't turf up this hardware store so people could wear shoes in here.
That's what I hate about Chinese restaurants is they make you take your shoes off when you walk
in. It's not good. Come on man. You're killing me this week. It's so offensive that Chinese people
take shoes off. Everybody's gonna be so mad. Crazy offensive. Oh that's some offensive stuff
Really? Yeah. God, I'm offended. I'm actually, I'm the triggered one.
Yeah. That's what people know about me as the host, is I'm the trigger.
You're the lonely triggered stoner. I'm the triggered soft boy.
Yeah, you are. You're a soft boy.
You are sensitive. I'm the sensitive. I'm the sensitive.
A lot of people don't know that Pat's sensitive. Yeah.
He's sensitive as hell. I'm so sensitive.
Shut up. And I'm shy.
You're not shy. I'm shy.
He's not. Prove it.
Oh you're shy? Prove it. Here I'll be a new, I'll pretend I've never met you. Hey man nice to meet
you I'm Derek Jeter. Oh my god you're so famous. I'm not, hey man I'm just one of the, I'm just
one of the girls. You're the most famous Yankee. No the most famous Yankee was. Baby Ruth. General
E. Lee. No he was the other one. He's a confetti. You're thinking of Ulysses S. Grant. Yeah Ulysses
Ulysses S. Grant. You let me sex, you let me sex, Grant? I that's, I'm a lot, I, I'm, if I
know any more than that about the Civil War, I'm in big, dude, I'm in, I'm in
Bantha Poodoo, so I have to just, I have to feign ignorance. Ulysses S., what's his
name? Huh? Who dat? What? Yeah, who dat? Yeah. I don't know, man. What was his weak spot on his
body? His Ulysses heel. Yeah, you studied his Ulysses heel. I studied his Ulysses heel.
comes back yeah just in case I'm gonna put you back. His heel was sex with women. That was my heel.
You have well it's because you're a descendant of him. I have hundreds of heels. Yeah. Yeah my Achilles
heel is pretty much anything. Yeah. Pretty much anything that'll kill me. Probably like my nose
honestly. Yeah my Achilles heel. I have a pretty sensitive nose. My Achilles heel is getting hit by a car. If somebody hits me in the nose
I'm out for a little bit. My Achilles heel is snacking.
My Achilles heel has got to be the crutchie Cheetos.
Yeah, my Achilles heel.
Takes me down.
One.
It's probably getting my leg stuck in the lawnmower.
Probably getting laid out and molly whopped on the street.
Yeah, it would probably be catching on fire.
What's that thing, that thing that I found?
God, it was some fucking tweet.
Your penis?
Responding to the New York Post.
Oh yeah, I witnessed Rick Moranis get his jaw slid for no reason.
The city's wild, dude.
I witnessed Rick Moranis get his jaw slid for no reason.
It's like the most insane sentence.
The guys who, the best kind of dude right now are the ones who can't stop replying to news
stories about crime in New York saying like, "Well, there goes the city.
It's going to be the 70s again.
There's going to be babies holding guns."
It's like, "Fuck it.
Hope so."
Yeah.
I hope, everybody talks about how the 70s New York was the cool New York.
Let's go back, dude.
They're going to bring the velvet underground back.
They're going to put graffiti language on the subway.
They're gonna put graffiti language on my body like a tattoo.
It's funny that if you own a van in New York City, it's just covered in graffiti.
There's nothing you can do.
Work van, fuck you.
Exactly.
That's why you get somebody to preemptively do it.
Yeah, but what if your shit's toy?
What if you got like, no graffiti slang?
What if the shit you get on is toy?
What if it's toy?
What does toy mean?
Toy means bad graffiti.
Toy is what it means?
Toy is the...
Toy is bad.
They teach you that in Tony Hawk's Underground too.
I didn't learn that shit.
All the guys who spray around the city in Berlin, they're all toy.
I don't think so.
I bet it means gay.
Yeah.
I think so.
It probably means gay.
It probably does.
Look that up on the graffiti dictionary.
Yeah.
It probably is a contraction of tugging boys.
A toy, otherwise known as a pawn, is an unskilled or new, inexperienced graffiti artist or writer.
I'm really good at graffiti.
- Tags and pieces are usually crossed out
with the word toy or crosser's tag around it.
- I had graffiti stuff all the time though.
My tag is the sad clown.
- Yeah.
- The saddest clown in the world.
It's really a long tag.
- Mine is white boy universe.
(laughing)
I spray paint galaxies.
- Yeah, I'm the Italian galaxy.
(laughing)
I could expand your mind.
- I'm hip hop kid.
So all the graffiti stuff is named after chess pieces.
I graffiti a jack in the box on the wall.
You can be a knight, a king, a queen, a pawn, a board, or a toy.
Some of my graffiti are graffiti a jack in the box, but it's Donald Trump on the end
of it, and it says "Whack in the box."
And then I sign my tag, "Hip Hop That Kid."
That hip hop kid lonely.
That lonely hip-hop kid.
That hip-hop son.
That, yeah.
That lonely ass little white boy.
That lonely.
That lonely ass little white boy who cries all the time.
Yeah.
That's my graffiti name.
That lonely ass little boy with a big sweater.
Maybe we should just.
And he hides in it like a turtle.
Is there a lot of money in graffiti?
Yeah.
You do it for the love of it.
You do it for the.
Yeah, the love of the.
You do it for the fumes.
The love of the money.
The love of the paint fumes.
I just love those paint fumes, dude.
Oh.
Have you guys ever looked at a graffiti and thought, "How the hell did that guy get up
there. But then you read the tag and it says Spider-Man. Yeah, and it says that 30
foot tall homie. Yeah, we were walking around, we saw us and it said fuck me.
No, no, it said, I know it. Let him talk. Okay. But you can go ahead and say a
worst version of it if you want. It said, it said, kiss me like you love me,
fuck me like you hate me and you read that out loud and I thought you were
just saying it to me asking fuck me like you hate me is it's really good yeah
when you hate someone you fucked him really good fuck them the best way you
bitch let me fuck this shit out of you forever fuck you fuck you and get
married yeah yeah I hate my dad so much how do I get back at him I'm gonna fuck
him really good another episode where we talk about that Ari Aster movie yeah did
he's beefing. Yeah. Yeah I'm beefing with my dad right now. I'm beefing. I've got a pretty serious beef going on with my dad.
Yeah I'm beefing with my dad. He won't let me pound him out. Yeah. He won't let me beef him.
Yeah. Ask him to show me the birds and the bees. I just want my dad to show me. I want my dad to show me his pie bird making it scream.
*laughter*
Pie bird?
Make it scream!
I feel like pie birds, I feel like they only have, well they have them here obviously, but I feel like it's just a British guy thing.
British guy thing?
Yeah, I feel like British guys fuck pie birds all the time.
I feel like American Pie would be a lot different of a movie if there was a pie bird in there.
Yeah, he'd be fucking, he'd be sticking his dick in a bird.
There'd be a perfect hole.
Did you guys ever fuck a fruit?
Did you know that they're making a girl's...
No, I never fucked a fruit.
This is not a joke.
Patrick did though, he didn't answer.
I don't have to answer.
He did.
They're making an American...
Patrick fucked a durian.
I did fuck a durian.
Yeah.
It smelled like home.
It smells terrible, but I'm going to be so good at eating pussy once I finally do it.
I'm going to be so good.
Once I finally find a pussy that's covered in spikes, I'm going to be so good at this.
I'm going to be so good at holding my nose while I eat pussy.
making an American Pie, a new American Pie movie, all girls. They're making a female
reboot of American Pie. Who's the girl Sean William Scott? It's called American Pie Girls
Rule or something. That's a diary of a wimpy kid. It's got the girl from the Tooth Fairy
movie in it, Madison Pettis. The little girl from the Rock Tooth Fairy? Is she the new
Sean William Scott girls rules she's Shana willow Scott Alita Scott Alita now
that it's senior year Anna Kayla Michelle and Stephanie band together to
harness their girl power to get what they want wait when it that comes out
tomorrow are you serious October 6 really
gotta watch this movie I'm gonna go see that shit oh my god we gotta go see that
in a theater they're doing it they're doing it all girl alien versus predator
Yeah, the xenomorphs are all women.
Man, shut up!
The xenomorphs.
The xenomorphs are all women.
The xenomorphs are all women and they all got boobs.
Do they?
Under those thingies?
Ah, yep.
Finally, a fucking-
Alien vs. Predator is so good because they just set it in an Antarctic Aztec temple for
no reason.
They're just like, "Yeah, you know what we should add to the- you know, Alien vs. Predator,
that's not enough.
We should have it take place inside of the Millennium Puzzle from Yu-Gi-Oh.
That's the only way we can make this movie work."
You know that climate that the Aztecs lived in?
Yeah, yeah, the ocean.
The coldest ocean there.
The coldest ocean.
The coldest ocean in the middle.
The middle had a lot of those.
Those were the lonely Mexicans.
Yeah, they were the lonely Mexicans.
And they lived in Antarctica.
And they were the sad boys.
They were sad boy loco.
Sad boy loco?
Yeah.
Sad boy loco.
That's some real shit.
Last night?
Last night I was lying awake and you know, I told you
I was lying awake, you know, you know how they did like discovered that you have taste buds on your balls and specifically you Patrick
Yeah, but like just imagine being like it's how I imagine being a scientist who had to sit in the lab and taste so good
Never mind
Imagine me. Oh, never mind. No, never mind. It's okay Patrick. I'm a ball sack. Is that what you're gonna say?
Imagine being a weird ball sack.
Imagine being a ball sack and tasting something.
I was tickling you.
Imagine being a ball sack and just being like
shorts, shorts, shorts, shorts, cereal.
Okay.
Alright.
Imagine being the scientist
who had to sit in a lab all day and just look at balls
in a microscope to see if they had taste buds.
I feel like we're gonna
slowly find out that balls have
even more features.
It's just what you look for.
weaned demo tape like a bootleg that's called craters of the sack. You want to
put your wean in a bootleg? I would. I would do that. Don't tempt me. Should we try
tasting stuff with our balls? Yeah. Do you want to do that on mic right now? Kinda.
All right turn, pause it. What do I have that we could even dip our balls in? We can put it on
monster. That's empty. I could vape and then blow it on my balls. Yeah you could.
- Yeah, do it.
- But someone else would have to blow it.
- Pepto-Bismol, let's go.
- Put some Pepto-Bismol in your balls.
- What if it tastes so good though and I get addicted?
- You get addicted to the taste of Pepto in your balls?
- Like what if it tastes different?
What if it's like tomato juice on a plane?
You know how the air pressure makes it taste different?
What if it's like Pepto on your balls?
- Imagine that movie.
Tomato juice on a plane?
(laughing)
- Yeah, do it.
- Okay, now do it.
- I'm tired of the attacks.
- Now do I'm tired of these--
- I'm tired of this goddamn tomato juice.
- I'm tired of these motherfucking--
I'm tired of tomatoes on this motherfucking juice.
I'm tired of this plane.
Now say you're tired of the juice.
Now say that Patrick.
Say it.
Say that.
I'm tired of drinking so much juice.
Okay now let's get a different read on it.
Let's try a different take.
Let's try it a different way.
I'm tired of the jweice.
You're tired of the jweice?
The jweice.
What kind of person is that?
The jweice?
- Nope.
- No.
- What?
Is that a person?
- I'm tired of my nagging Jew-ess of a wife.
- You can't say that, Patrick.
- Why?
- You can't say that about your wife.
She's listening.
- She better not.
If you're listening right now,
you're supposed to be plugging your ears
and going la la la la la la la la.
- Pat is gonna do a Disney Channel show
about him and his twin called Hitler Hitler.
(laughing)
- Why did you guys make me say this?
- Now everyone's gonna get mad at me.
- Everyone's gonna be mad at you.
- It is really funny to imagine someone being mad at you
for just talking about Hitler.
- Yeah, mad at me.
I wouldn't be able to handle him too.
- You know if you say his name three times, he wakes up.
- You'd be able to handle him
'cause I'd be trying to defend him.
- If you say his name three times,
everybody starts laughing.
- Yeah, if you know--
- I'd be trying to defend him, you know.
- Yeah.
- He's just sexy.
- He's sassy, come on.
- I don't think Hitler's sexy, let me clarify.
anymore. I'm just doing it. It's too old you know it's like seeing young pictures of
Betty White and you're like what's up ma? Oh yeah and you're like oh now she says
she says shut the fuck up motherfucker all the time come on. She says it to me
and she says it to me. Dude I mean I mean Wedding Singer that old lady rap. The
rapping granny? That was fucking huge for Betty White she was like I might still
have a career maybe I can say something nasty and naughty. Maybe I could just
talk about my WAP. Dude, she is a WAP for sure. White ass person. White ass petty.
It's crazy that yeah that she made a career from being that that nasty ass
grandma. There's like a joke in like the second season of 30 Rock like
2008 or 7 or whatever and she's like they like check to see if she's dead and
I was like she's just been doing this forever. I know. Just like you just been
this old the oldest bitch in the world yeah for like 30 years she's gonna die
like she could be died I remember think so yeah lock it in there you go in the
power dude I've been doing I've been doing a lot of us talking to the devil
recently what is he been saying to you you've been saying some nasty the devil
got a potty mouth yeah he actually know the devil doesn't like the curse words
because then he has to act upon them like if somebody says fuck you the devil's
like yeah I think that I think the reason that nothing has happened in the past
couple of thousand years since the big the big civil war in heaven is you guys
never seen the prophecy with Christopher Walken no there's like a said there's
like a civil war in heaven so what does that have to do with fuck you you say
fuck you and the devil says you say fuck you and the devil's like I'm not dealing
with that right now what's busy with he's he's there's too many this is the
hall of your imagination yeah I swear to God there is a fucking gas leak in here
so I've been fucking loopy since I got here I mean loopy I'd be loopy your
funny-ass friends yeah I do I think you make me enjoy this a lot easier yeah
when you're loopy yeah yeah you can kind of just turn the mics on and be weird
for a little bit yeah watch this that's not weird that's just scary sometimes I
can feel weird and scary
the terrifier is nowhere he's wholly terrifying I hate when I get caught when
I catch the Holy Terrifier yeah I started doing claws with my hands chasing people
around the church like Tom and Jerry
getting the devil at an evangelical church yeah and being getting paid to get
exercised yeah yeah oh my god dressing up like Tim Curry from legend yeah and
I'm here to fuck all of you. I'm going to suck your dick mister. I'm going to fuck
something. So you're getting fucked. Oh. What are you doing with your hat? Oh I'm fine now.
And then once you get exorcised you turn into Nigel Thornberry. Yeah. They put you
behind a curtain take all your prosthetics off. Smashing. Yeah. Oh smashing Darwin. That was
the boys name right the boys name darling Darwin and he pulled his pants and did
the wedgie day I think Patrick calls his son darling he was that monkey s son oh
yeah they had a monkey kid yeah they had the monkey kid I'm not thinking of that
guy he was the missing link that he was adopted they found him in the jungle and
he was the missing link and they were like wait no cuz there was a there was
an anthropomorphic guy what most guys are anthropomorphic that's what
anthropomorphic guy outside. Yeah, it's just an anthropomorphic guy that's been
sitting out in front of my house asking people for change. Speaking of which, if anyone does
furry art, can you hit us up? What? I vaguely remember talking about this, but I don't
remember why we need that. Yeah, we need it. I can't talk about it right now. Was this at like 5 a.m.?
Was this one of those? No, we talked about it. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Was this 5 a.m. in Toronto? It does have to do with something.
Yeah, if you draw furry art, it's probably too late by the time this
comes out to be honest. Yeah, it'll probably already be out. Someone will
probably make. By the way, if you draw furry art, keep it to yourself. Do not send it to us.
Wait, are you guys planning a birthday gift for me? Yeah, we are. Your birthday is in the next
few weeks. No, so it's never too early to get started on Caleb. It's always too early to get
started on Caleb. Not. No. Also, Christmas is coming up. That's like kind of my birthday.
Christmas is the Lord's birthday you shit.
No.
Not to me.
Hey, not anymore.
Yeah, after your conversion?
No.
Well yeah, now that I'm a Muslim.
I wasn't going to say Muslim, I was going to say Scientologist.
You said Muslim with such contempt in your voice Patrick.
What are you talking about?
You have rage.
Patrick is Hitler.
I'm not Hitler.
What's it like?
Do you like being Hitler?
I hate it.
Have you seen the clown that hides from Hitler?
clown that has from Hitler. Yes. You have? What did you kill him because of his race?
You fucking Hitler motherfucker. Because he was Irish. No. It's funny that basically because
we're recording these in just a few days just all the stupid jokes that we'll get tired
of in like 10 hours are just yet. Three weeks of. Yeah we're gonna get so tired. We're gonna
get sleepy. Oh I'm gonna get sleepy. I'm already sleepy now. Tell you that much. I don't know
what it is about every time I come to New York I just like... It's just whenever you
leave your whenever you travel. Yeah. Yeah. Well if I travel by like car. If I travel by car or like bus
or anything like that it sucks but like... How else do you travel? By plane you fucking idiot. And when did you last
travel by plane? By giant cruise ship. To LA right? And you felt like shit in LA as well I remember it
vividly. I felt yeah okay you know what it is every time I travel. He slept in a trash can. Okay but also
he he said he was gonna cry yeah you know i did feel i did feel the exact same way that i did the
day we went to jolly yeah i remember it yeah i remember you were at work but he was having a
really bad time and i gave him my salad because i felt bad yeah because i asked if he wanted anything
and he said no and then he started crying you're a sweet friend i'm a sweet friend he's he's
cameron's one of my best friends cameron puts on you have to you have to level up i have to level
up you have to level up you can have this if you want you just got these that's how good of a friend
I am Wow Jana's gonna. You can have both of you can I could have your bar stool Patrick
Patrick you can have both of the bar stools I can have both of the bar stools on a better friend Caleb
Okay, you can have Cameron
You already have me in Octa prima nocte. Yeah, you can fuck him out. You're in my house
My house daddy's rules you get to fuck Cameron, and you get to show him pleasure
Well the pleasure men are gonna love this. Let's do the pleasure men again.
God damn. That is okay yeah guys that's a new character you can tweet it that
instead of just talking about the Grinch or like your cousins or something start
talking about the pleasure men's ball. The pleasure men's ball. That's the next big thing.
It's gonna take all your money on the pleasure men. Yeah bet it all on black.
Bet it all on the black pleasure men. The black pleasure men? What? You said that.
inclusive. Yeah, man. Yeah, there's a pleasure men's ball. If you don't get
glooped, if you don't get a new t shirt, I got glooped at the pleasure men's
ball and all I got was a gloop all over my face and all I got and all I got was
my put the eight. I got my put the eight out. I did get my put the eight. Do my
knuckles still say you see it's no I gave Caleb knuckle test to say eeat PUS why
yeah you're gonna put in the center of his forehead yeah bunch of L's uh-huh
yeah yeah looks cool he takes so yeah you took four out yeah you took four L's
Charles Manson took four yeah he's to take more because that thing is a bad
look yeah we're at like halfway let's start the list oh shit I forgot we had a
list it's sometimes it's hard having so much fun I know top ten best comebacks
yeah we didn't do this before I don't think we did the top ten comebacks to
being called gay uh-huh so now these are comebacks for being called straight yeah
we almost did top ten best comebacks to being called fat and Pat vetoed it I
didn't veto you guys we could have done it if we did do it we totally know we
could have done it's funny veto you guys I would have done it if you guys said if
it wasn't for your meddling kids. What the fuck? What? Was that you farting or was that
the chair? I think that's the noise outside. That's what I hear every time I fart. That
sounded like something escaped you. That sounded like you sat on something and it just got
out of you. Sometimes I get nasty at home. Let's do the list. Number one. A frog crawled
out of his ass. Yeah. Number one. Wait, no, we have to start out with the insult. It's
a respect. It's a comeback. Exactly. Oh. You're a bald ass bitch like Squidward. Respect. No,
you're supposed to get to the comeback. Look at you, blue motherfucker. Look at this blue
Squidward guy. Hey man, I'm sorry. You must have mistaken me for someone who gives a crap.
yeah go back to your ass oh the top comment on this is from Lucky's and it
says I don't use comebacks because I'm the nicest person you'll ever meet that's
what I tried to do right then that's the ultimate comeback somebody says yeah you
fucking suck your dick small your wife hates you yeah hey man respect for that
big ups what was that video you got you watched it it was like I'm not I'm
I'm trying to follow the Lord the best I can and not partake in your...
In violence.
That's what I do.
Someone just beating the shit out of me.
I'm winning because I'm not doing anything back.
Yeah.
I'm turning my other cheech.
I'm turning the cheech.
DogeLife4Gaming comments, "Number one should be your mom gay."
That's true.
Big facts.
Your mom gay.
Number two.
Hey, Cameron.
Yeah?
You...
Hey.
Shh.
Say it an insult. That's my insult saying so quite too much. All right, let's say it again
So you play too much stop calling yourself hot. The only thing you can turn on is the microwave
If I ever encounter a heckler, God save their fucking soul.
If you ever encounter a heckler.
If you ever enchant a heckler.
If you ever enchant a broadsword.
That's my first move. Second move, just cry instantly.
Next!
You said next?
Wait, wait. First I point to myself and I go, me?
And then I look behind me to see if there's another guy.
You talking to me?
Me.
You must be talking to me because there's no one else here.
I got some bad thoughts in my head.
But R2-D2's gay.
But...
What?
You didn't like it?
I just start going...
[Heavy breathing]
[Gurgling]
[Laughter]
I trick them into thinking that I'm going to cry, so then they get vulnerable.
Yeah, so they let their shields down.
possess them yeah and I do and then I pretend it a little yeah then I take
their body over and I go I say I have to go to the bathroom I have to go to the
bathroom to suck on my own poop yeah yeah peace peace out and then I drop the
mic on stage I drop it I have to I have to type the T pose as I take over his
body yeah I go suck a shit in the bedroom really confuses everybody else
in the audience so I can suck a shit it's basically a really cool old comedy
section. Yeah. Number three. Doing a cool section. Caleb has to insult Patrick now. You
bitch. Yeah you look like you fell out of a unicorn's butt. Kind of do today. But.
Yeah you do. But. But. You look like a butt. You look like you fell out of a
unicorn's butt. You look like you fell out of a unicorn's butt. Why? Don't give him the
credit of unicorn. Yeah. You know. Well. At least a normal horse. Okay. It's like you fell out of a guy's ass.
You look like Ace Ventura with the Rhino.
Ace Ventura with the Rhino.
He pulled up with the Rhino.
Ace Ventura pulled up with the Rhino with the PS2 in it.
Rhino with the PS2.
Dude, can you imagine?
Can you imagine if a Rhino could play PS2?
Someone has to insult me now.
Okay.
Hey, bitch.
You smell like a bitch.
If I'm ever drunk, you'll be good looking.
We got drunk on Friday.
Yeah, so you looked at me.
We got drunk together.
And you looked about as good enough to eat.
You would eat me?
I'd take you to frown town.
You'd make me frown?
I'd make you frown like there was no other choice.
I'm going to give you, listen, listen.
You would make me frown and I'd turn it upside down?
We're going to get drunk.
I'm going to give you zero options.
zero options.
What?
That's just the facts of the matter.
Zero.
Okay.
All right.
That's a better comeback.
Moving on.
Yeah, that just happened.
Awkward.
So that just happened, and now for something completely different.
Hey, Cameron, you're a big fan of the news.
I'm a big fan of the news.
Hey, hey Cameron, you're a you're a pussy and you'd at you'd have pussy eating white boy
Where did you get that? Where did you got those clothes at the toilet store?
This is this I know what this is. I do look like one of those. I'm dressed like one of those breaks
This is from brick from anchorman. Oh
Here's a comment on here that says I laughed at this from dark boy X
I would shop at the toilet store. Yeah, why not?
You have to get, I mean, there's toilets.
You have to get a toilet. Yeah.
Where am I supposed to get a toilet? The clothes store?
And if they have clothes at the toilet store, I like to support
It's called a two for one. Small business. Yeah.
As a small business order,
order myself.
You will come to my toilet store.
Hey Patrick, you got, you're the one,
you're that big bouncy freak I'd like
to pop with a needle and to see what's growing
inside you pregnantly.
[laughter]
- Come back.
- You have to do it, come back!
- I know, but.
- Come on, okay, I'll say it again.
You're that big, bubbly.
(laughing)
- You're that big, bubbly motherfucker.
- You're that big, bubbly guy with a thousand babies
in there, I just wanna look in with an x-ray scope
and check out their features.
- You rise and you shine.
(laughing)
- That's what it says.
- That's number six?
- And the only comment says, I don't get this one?
- Yeah, me neither.
- I don't either.
You rise, what could that mean?
Maybe like, you're my son.
- Yeah.
- Oh, okay.
- You're the sun. - Is that true?
- You rise and shine.
- You rise and you shine.
- You rise and you shine. - You rise and you shine.
- And you blow my mind.
- Oh, okay.
- I'm working on, no, it's a new song I'm doing.
- New sensitive gangster song.
- You rise and you shine.
- New sensitive gangster track.
- Take off that makeup, you look like a clown ass bitch.
♪ You look like a penis ♪
♪ Take that makeup off you ♪
♪ Trollop what you cunt ♪
- Trollop?
- Yeah.
- That's what--
- John McCain said to his wife in the car.
- Yeah, take that makeup off you look like
a trolloping cunt, I think.
♪ You trolloping ass cunt ♪
♪ You look so ♪
- Trolloping?
- He said trollop, he said something, maybe--
- You a trollop--
- Trollop is an adject.
- Trollop.
Is that an adverb, ing?
- Trollop, he said--
- Go back to school of rock.
- Fuck, what the--
- Jackie Black. - Mad libs.
- Jackie Chan.
Jackie Chan teaching me school of how to break a rock.
School of yeah that's right.
School of cock that fist back.
School of cock-fu.
You say cock-food?
Hey Caleb, you think you would learn cock-fu but all you're doing is learning cock is food.
Don't you forget about me?
- Well, like I will forget about you,
and Simple Minds will sue you for covering their song.
(laughing)
That's a, that was a stretch.
That's a little bit of a stretch.
- That one, I thought that one was perfect.
- That one works as a comeback to one very specific thing.
- Yeah, which is, why would somebody be like,
hey, you're gonna-- - Hey, don't you forget
about me. - You're gonna forget
about me. - Hey, don't you forget
about me.
I'm just a kid and life is a nightmare.
- Oh, you're just a kid and life is a nightmare?
- Yeah. - Yeah, hey,
I woke up at seven, went to bed at seven, woke up at 11,
waiting for somebody to call.
- Yeah, you wish.
- What's new, Scooby-Doo?
You're thinking of a different band, Cameron.
- Hey, Cameron.
- You're thinking of Simple Plan, not Simple Minds.
- Cameron, I got beef with you.
- Simple, that's a really--
- I'm trying to beef with Cameron.
- That's a really funny name to have for your band.
- Simple Minds.
- Didn't age well.
- Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, we're the fucking dummies.
Hey Cameron, nice pants.
You're a girl.
These are women's pants you have on.
If I throw a stick, would you leave?
You're a dog.
I'm a dog.
Okay, I just got it.
Wait, okay, now there's a little script here of what happens when you use this comeback.
So I'll be kid and you be me in the script.
If I throw a stick, would you leave?
Dude, I'm not a dog.
Bully assassinated.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, believe you start mr. That's the best way. That's the best way to come back to a comeback
You know someone's like hey if I wanted my comeback I'd wipe it off your mom's face and they say dude
You're not having sex with my mom. Yeah, you're making that up. Yeah, dude. I'm not a dog
You're a liar. What's it like to be a liar? What's it like to be a liar?
And your parents know you're a liar your parents know that you lie to me
Yeah, I don't come down to your job and knock the lies out of your mouth
I don't come to your house and lie to you.
Have you seen the clown that hides from the guy who lies to his friends and breaks their
heart?
Have you seen the clown that hides from someone who broke my heart?
Have you seen the clown that only shows himself to the sensitive thugs of the world?
Because I have.
Me too.
Yeah.
Have you?
What?
Have you seen the clown that only shows up to the porno freaks and the pleasure men?
Yeah.
What do you throw back on a porno freak?
Have you seen the clown in my neighborhood?
He's funny.
He's hilarious.
Have you seen the, oh I just remember, when I went to community college in Laconia, there
was a clown outlet.
Clown outlet?
There was a clown supply store.
Did you go?
In that fucking town.
I never went, but her name was like.
Did you go to the store for?
Her name, whose name?
The clown, the woman's, the woman clown.
The woman's clown.
You didn't?
The woman's clown?
woman who owned the store is everything she was a clown she's not okay yes but
what I'm saying she's not she owned it she would dress up as a clown and would
sell and let me tell you she owned it she was a clown and she owned it he's a
clown she owned it all the way I think I just moved to she moved her store to
Pennsylvania a lot of clowning yeah I climbed capital there yeah
capital of the USA yeah there's a huge up in plumbing clowns coming community
there yeah I think maybe you can leave the oven on again yeah cuz I can't
fucking think yeah sure I thought that we're tired and haven't eaten except for
eggs in the morning mm-hmm and Charizo toddy so I made sure he's a city the
clown see the clown clown names and stripper names oddly similar yeah yeah
crystal pussy the clown yeah divine bubble sparks would be a good clown name
Yeah, he's a he makes stripper music. Yeah stripper true. Yeah
Do you wine?
Those are rappers. Those aren't
Can you I'm just getting there getting any rap fell in love with the stripper?
That makes you a stripper. Yeah, that's a clown ass thing to do. Hey, those are my clown ass partners do that. Yeah. Hey Patrick
What's up with that with your stanky thing? Hey, if you hate this, I'll hate you
These don't make any sense
This is dropping off fast. Okay. Wait. No, this one's that it's the next one's pretty good. Okay, whose turn is it to be insulted?
Hey Caleb
You didn't question you're singing it's beautiful
It's I'm not gonna go there
Saying insult I can't insult you can make fun of this beautiful voice. That is a joke
I'm on hey Caleb. Yeah, Caleb. Yeah
yeah yeah what's up your voice is wild.
My voice is too.
You need to come back.
Sorry.
I'll just write.
I'll just read it.
Autotune makes you sound like a computerized voice.
But I mean my voice is naturally beautiful.
The only comment on this one is I should use this one on my sister.
Yo sis.
Autotune makes you sound like a computerized voice.
When you do Autotune you sound like a pewter.
You sound like the family computer.
You sound like Adele.
Yeah, you sound like Adele.
That's right.
You think you sound like Adele, you sound like Adele.
You sound like Adele.
Yeah.
Adele.
That's pretty good.
From 90, that's running Windows 98.
That's right.
That's just the dial up and that's what you sound like when you sing.
You sound like a dial up modem going on.
You sound like dialia.
Uh huh.
Yeah, you sound like Crystalia.
You sound like Crystalia right now.
You sound like.
Why you cocking that eyebrow up, girl?
You ain't Crystalia.
You sound like Crystalia.
You're saying some nasty things.
Chris D'Elia, you're saying some nasty things to a 15 year old.
Yeah, Chris to see ya.
Buddy, bye bye.
Cause you're not playing at our, you're not gonna come on our podcast.
Mr. Pedophile.
What you call him, Chris the Pedophile?
They should do that.
Chris to feel ya.
Chris to feel ya kids.
Chris to feel ya kid.
Okay.
Mr. Chris to feel ya damn kid.
Hey Patrick.
People are always riding around on lime scooters.
I'm just trying to ride a slime cooter.
(laughing)
- That's right.
- Is that your insult towards me?
- No, I was just letting you know.
- Well, I think it's Cameron's turn to be insulted.
- Uh-huh.
- Hey, Cameron, you will never get to ride a slime cooter.
- Do you need some sunscreen because you just got burned?
- What? - Whoa.
- Somebody's being like, you're a fucking idiot.
- Do you remember when just burning was--
- Yeah, list of burn centers in the United States.
Yeah, there was I remember my brother was like I came up with a new burn if someone burns you you say I
Just burned your burn pretty sure that's a third-degree burn and then I explained on that that made no sense
And he hit me really hard. Yeah
Yeah, what are you a piece of toast cuz you just got burned in my sister used to have bread now your shits toast
You said bread now that's just toast
Dude, I'm a miracle you used to hey Caleb. Well you used to have bread now that shit's toast
Nice wig what's it made of your mom's chest hair that one's not that was not bad for camera. Oh come on
See if someone said that to me. It's like we have my mom is beautiful hairless tits
Watch out top comment this kind of made me laugh, but that's a gross comeback
This next one's really good hey Patrick
You're you're that ugly sucka
I just said the next one's good. You're not even going to read it?
What you're doing is not okay at all.
No, he didn't. Let's start it over.
I was building up.
It's called being in character. You're clearly not an actor.
You don't understand me and you.
Patrick.
Like watch this, I made myself cry.
And people can see that right now.
People can see it.
(laughing)
- Give me a second.
- Dude, oh my god, you have so many veins in your head.
- Come on, suck up, come on, suck up.
- Jesus Christ.
(laughing)
Take a picture of me.
What the fuck?
- Okay, I'm having a dry day.
It's just not happening for me today.
You guys happy?
Maybe I'm not the best actor in the world.
Maybe I'm not the next Daniel Day-Lewis.
- Lewis.
- Daniel Day-Lewis, that's you.
No!
Read the fucking thing.
Daniel Day-Clueless is that, wait say it again.
What was it?
Daniel Day-Clueless, that's you.
Listen buddy, I don't know what makes you so stupid, but it really works.
I'm guessing it's the gas I left on in the fucking oven.
It could be that.
It could be that I'm poisoning you.
I'm poisoning you guys so I can take advantage of you.
Yeah.
On the podcast.
What?
Come on.
Taking advantage of your, what?
What?
You guys will laugh at anything.
I'm taking advantage of that.
What?
You gotta hear yourself before you speak.
You take it to this nasty place every time, Patrick.
You gotta hear yourself before you talk.
You should be the one wearing these headphones.
Do you think I look cool?
No.
Okay.
You would look like, these headphones on you would look like a halo in a renaissance painting.
Yeah, that's true.
That's an intellectual reference for my scholar.
That's for all the art fans.
For the scholarly gangstas.
Scholarly gangsta.
Yeah, you wish you were a scholarly gangster, but actually you shit.
I bet your brain feels as good as new seeing you never use it.
Let me feel it.
Yep, you're right.
Yeah, I bet your brain feels as good as new.
LOL, you had no brain.
LOL, I love this one.
This is that's definitely that should be way higher than the fucking horrible ones.
Yeah, yeah.
Like number seven or whatever. The one that's like, what are you doing? Hey, Patrick, you're
you're done for. Hey, I should get one of those erasers that say they're for big mistakes
and throw it at you. Yeah, because that's how you erase. What people don't realize about those is
that the erasers don't work on your heart because who you are and who you love isn't a mistake.
That's real shit. Uh-huh. People don't realize that about a lot of stuff. People don't realize that your heart
has a good amount of memories. If I wrote your name on my heart, would you fall in love with me? Yeah.
Would you dance if I asked you to dance? Would you dance if I played your favorite song right now?
You know I'm such a fool for you. You got me wrapped around your finger.
Let me tell you what, that's like that song "Cherry Pie" when you realize what it's about.
Like, she's wrapped around his finger. Okay. Yeah. I see you, you Scottish bitch.
She has to get me fingered. She's Irish. Same shit to me.
Fuck you. I don't give a fuck.
What the hell? I don't give a fuck.
Disrespect. That's the same thing to me.
The cranberries is all we have. Yeah.
And a lot of other stuff. That's true.
But yeah, what other things do the Irish have? Wisdom.
Drinking beer. Beer is honestly cool. Yep. Drinking a lot of Guinness. Yeah.
Prone to depression. Are they? Yeah. Yeah. They're those sad-ass leprechauns that don't tell nobody.
The leprechaun who hides everything with a smile. I'm that leprechaun that hides my sensitivity with
my rainbow. I put the key to my heart at the end of the rainbow. Everybody always asks me where the
gold where's the gold where's your goal to me to share my gold nobody asked me
how old I am nobody asked me teen 15 year old leprechaun I'm a 15 year old
leprechaun and girls keep trying to fuck me everyone's all concerned about the
pot of gold nobody's concerned about the gold in my heart mm-hmm
whoa my heart everybody's worried about the pot of gold in my in my rainbow
nobody's worried about the spot of mold in my apartment that is that could be
mold problem that could be giving me allergies yeah everyone's always talking
about my pilgrims hat nobody realizes I'm chill not whack my green pilgrims
hat seems chill not whack yep everyone's always concerned about my pilgrims hat
buckle I just want to find a girl who will give me a good suckle. I just want to find a
steady girl who will give me a good suckle.
Yeah yeah yeah. People are always texting me about the Grinch. They don't
realize my life ain't a cinch. Everybody's asking me the leprechaun about what's at
the end of my rainbow. I just want to settle down with my mane hoe. I just I
just want to sit at the window and watch the rain go. Mm-hmm. Everybody's always
noticing my my my charms. Nobody's noticing my arms. I've been going to the
gym recently. Everybody's always talking about my giant penis, but nobody wants to
a look at my giant penis.
Nobody wants to be my guy on
krinis.
I got another e for the crane is
it said I got an email that we
talked about that on the podcast
yeah only once in like on like
it's like it's an MMO that that
cameras that got signed up yeah,
I got an email that's yeah. The
first one was like it was like
an MMO like like a beta that I
got somehow got signed up for
and I got an email that said see
on Kreenis. And I got another one a few days ago that said, "There are many life
quality upgrades waiting on Kreenis."
We've all been waiting for that.
I'm just waiting for Kreenis to hit, kind of like, be as good as Earth.
Yeah.
And then I'll head to Kreenis.
Get me on Kreenis as soon as... A-S-A Kreenis.
A-S-A Kreenis.
That's right.
Yeah.
Do we have more insults?
Oh yeah, we got more.
We got a lot more. Let's just pick out the good ones here.
- Yeah.
- Hey, uh.
- Whoa, here's a good one right here.
- Hey Cameron, why do you eat poop?
- I'm busy right now, can I ignore you later?
- (gasps) No.
- No!
- That's me. - What is this?
- Okay, so yeah, wait, wait, wait, here.
Just give-- - I'll insult you, okay?
- Yeah.
- Cameron, basically,
it would be, I would be okay with you if you were gay.
- Gay?
I'm straighter than the pole your mom dances on.
One idiot in my school kept calling me gay to annoy me,
and then i use this comeback on him i didn't really what this meant i'd just
found on the internet and thought it would be effective but then his dumb
friend told the whole grade what i said
thankfully when some people ask me what i said i lied to them and they believed me
and the guy who blabbed everyone now denies it barely anyone talks about it
anymore i was only bothered by it for a few for two days by a few people
that's the whole insult were you guys word warriors in middle school?
what does that mean?
uh... as you're great rewards i i i i did organize uh... or no
i think it was another boy who organized this in the fifth grade or the message
with the boy
uh... fifth grade to your little boy organize you
this time is going to talk
i was more of a i was more of a uh... mister payback is a warrior a patrick
can i finish with us today patrick no you let a boy or guys in the hand the
hand you can use the comeback i'm setting you up for a good comeback
That was a real one for me. Talk to the booty that hands off duty.
Mm-hmm.
Some kid in fifth grade,
because he had just watched Yo Mama,
he organized a--
He just unbuckled your pants?
So that I have to pee and it's pushing against my--
I don't mean buckle, I meant button.
We had a Yo Mama contest from like the show.
That's the best, yeah.
And he was the Wilmer Valderrama and I would just--
every one of them I did was just like,
"Your mama's so fat she'd make you look thin!"
Nice.
It crushed. It crushed. Yeah. Nice. One time a kid said "Yo mama joke" and I punched him
and I beat him up and he was a midget. Serious. His name is CJ. Yeah. He had a mohawk. Oh yeah
you told me about the pink mohawk. Oh yeah I do remember that. I was there. Okay. You
guys weren't there? I was there. You were 20 years old. Hey Caleb. What man? Your shit
It smells like candy.
Get out of my house!
Oh.
I'll see you in heck.
Hey, uh, hey Caleb.
Yeah?
What's up?
I bet your mother has a loud bark.
I didn't even insult you.
What the hell, man?
I just asked what's up.
Sometimes you just have to do your job.
This is how police officers feel.
Yeah, it doesn't matter what somebody's saying to you.
You gotta do your job.
Somebody insult me.
somebody in something.
(laughter)
- What's it?
- How's the weather up there?
- Is the girls restroom smoke good?
- What kind of drugs does it take to enjoy your experience?
Your existence?
- Fuck that up dude.
- It's the same word basically.
And then the comment says, "Okay this is amazing,"
says the kid who loved Joker.
(laughter)
- I'm that kid who loved Joker.
- I'm that comeback kid who loved Joker.
- Mmhmm.
Let's see here. Hey Caleb.
What's up?
Oh, if I stand close to you I can hear the ocean.
Cause you're a shell. Yeah, I'm a beautiful shell. You're a beautiful gorgeous shell.
Yeah, I'm a shell of a guy. Yeah, you're a conch. Shut up.
Hey. What? You're the coward who ever heard of beating you two up to a pulp.
That's the comebacks.
- Comebacks in a circle, so it's a comeback circle.
- Let's just read the rest of this to each other.
- All right, we'll start right here at number 30.
We're gonna go with a whole list.
- Okay, we gotta start with one insult.
- You fat, Caleb.
- Which one?
First of all, no.
- You just read the fucking comeback.
- Just fucking read it.
- You fat, Caleb.
- Not fat.
- People always say,
"Treat others the way you wanna be treated."
I guess you really wanna be treated horribly.
- I don't know who you think you are,
but if you think you can talk to me like that,
you could go right here, right now.
Hey man, that elephant wants his underwear back.
No you.
You ruined the circle.
You know how a circle works?
No you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry you must have mistaken me for a mirror.
No you.
I would like to help you out.
What I can't hear you over the epic sound of how awesome I am.
No you.
I really like that one.
Your mom had an abnormally large vagina.
What the hell?
That's how she gave birth to you.
You get ten times more girls than me.
Ten times zero equals zero.
That's kind of an omen.
You're a special kind of stupid, aren't you?
I'm busy right now, please don't leave a message ever.
Whoa.
That's a good one.
Bully, hey look over there.
You gasp.
Is it your intelligence?
May the fleas of one thousand camels infest your armpits.
Wait, no.
Fleas are too good for any part of your body.
Oh my god, that's a good one to use on dogs.
Fatality.
That's a great one to use on dogs.
Hey Patrick, waddle on over here and we'll talk.
Okay.
That insult was so funny I nearly fell off my dinosaur laughing the first time I heard
it. Aperture Science called. They said they had that the future does not start with you.
Holy crap.
Why is Aperture Science--
There is a crap somewhere out there in the deep cold darkness of space. A crap resides.
That crap is waiting to be given.
The top comment, only comment. How the heck is this a comeback?
I like watching your show, but when the camera goes in your general direction, all I can
see is you.
Is that a fat joke? What does that mean?
Or maybe a tight lens joke.
Yeah, maybe you have a small camera.
That's a joke for Carl Zeiss.
Yeah, Zeiss would love that one.
You're so stupid you let the target throw darts at you.
No I don't.
How can I say somebody is stupid?
Let me think of a thing somebody does.
You're so stupid food eats you stupid.
You're so stupid in Soviet Russian.
It drives you.
You're so stupid your air conditioner makes the room hot.
That's right.
You're so stupid. You sleep upside down. You're so stupid a firing squad of you stood in a
circle. That's right. You're so stupid it takes three of you to screw in a light bulb.
It takes two of you to turn the... Stop tickling me! I'm gonna get you soon. I turned off my
microphone when you did that. It was so loud that it turned off his microphone. And you
You turned me off when you wouldn't let me tickle you.
Can you giggle into the microphone?
Just giggle into the mic.
Just giggle once.
I'm going to tickle.
Can we get a sweeter tick?
Yeah, just for the...
That was evil.
Listen, don't scream.
I just want to tickle you.
Just giggle, okay?
Don't yell or scream or hit me.
He did it.
That was a real giggle.
Are you ticklish?
He is ticklish.
I tickled him the other night while you guys were sleeping.
Do you want to shower with me after this?
You want to shower with me after this?
You're not allowed to. I'm not going to meet you in the shower.
I'm...
Yeah, you will. I think you will.
I think you'll find a way to do it.
Make like a unicorn and get the fluff away from me.
Oh my god.
If I wanted a B******************** I'd have got a dog.
Oh, I think I know what that says.
Beast Burger.
If I wanted a beast, I would have got a dog.
So what's the point of your existence again?
Oh, come on.
Your mom used that joke already.
Oh my god.
Quit whining over your sad life.
You're on the internet for way too long.
I think Floyd once said, "We don't need no education."
I guess you might need it if that's your response to life.
That's a good one.
Alright, let's see what's at the end of this year list.
MeRapid just called and wants his insults back.
Let's just scroll to the bottom here.
He was good though.
Oh, here we go.
This one's perfect for Caleb.
Caleb, Caleb, say something mean to me.
- You look like a big fart.
- At least my head doesn't look like a deformed lemon.
- No!
- Thanks for listening, guys.
- Thank you listening.
- Listen to the Patreon.
- Subscribe to the Patreon, buy our t-shirts.
We got some t-shirts.
- We got a new t-shirt that has a picture
of Patrick's XXX journey that he took.
- Yeah.
- His triple X journey that he took with his friends.
- He did a triple X journey with three friends
and we put it on the t-shirt.
- Without telling him.
- What are you talking about?
- You were asleep.
- Bye everybody.