You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts for the mindless.
Crap monster.
We just start.
Oh, yo.
What? Yo.
The Brussels sprout sandwich is back.
At Clover?
At McDonald's.
I just got a notification from them.
Have you guys ever had a McRib?
McRib, yeah.
I'm thinking of taking the plunge this year. I've never had it before.
Oh, it's good.
Is it?
It's so good.
I'm sure it's good.
Yeah.
Fucking rib sandwich? No shit.
Barbecue?
It's rib-shaped patty.
I like everything at McDonald's. I like the filet of fish.
I do too.
I get a double filet of fish when I go.
Yeah.
You get two filet of fish?
Yeah, dude. It's fucking nine dollars.
When I used to get real fucked up and go to McDonald's and get filet of fish,
it's the perfect food to sober you up because it's so gross.
You're wrong.
I don't know. People make fun of it for being gross. There's nothing gross about that to me.
It's no grosser than any meat in McDonald's. No, I know. All the meat there is gross,
but I think it's the grossest item on the menu. I disagree. I mean, it's really good,
but it's still gross. I think it's the grossest item on the menu. No. The salads are the grossest.
Have you had the poop? The poop? The McPoop? No, it's just poop. I didn't even try to name
it anything else. The McJuggerNuggets. Yeah, that's bad. Yeah, because his dad's going psycho.
What's the oldest chicken nugget you've ever eaten?
Ooh.
I ate a nugget off of the seat of my mom's car that I left there the day before.
Yeah, my cousins used to leave whole boxes of fries in the back seat of their car.
Yeah, that's not meat. Meat does not age well.
But I mean, the thing is, the McDonald's, it's not like the McDonald's meat is going to go bad.
No, McDonald's doesn't go bad. You can leave nuggets, you can leave chicken nuggets.
Most food doesn't go bad.
Basically nothing goes bad. Yeah, you can eat anything old. If it's cheese, especially cheese gets mold on it
Just cut the mold off. You're still good. Cheese is mold
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Horse, there's always in the middle of cheese. It's always fine. Yeah
Exactly. Yeah, you just cut around the more if it's if there's if there's flies and maggots in the meat you shake them out
It's green. Let it lean if it's yellow
That's a perfect cheese for a grilled cheese. And if there's maggots
it's
that's fucking right yeah
what do you guys think the best cheese in the world is?
oh god
shut the episode off now
we gotta figure this out before we go any further
i didn't pause anything
honestly i think just a smoked gouda on a grilled cheese
that's one of the nothing beats it
I'd say like a small piece.
You know what the best cheese is?
The best cheese is the Lando Lake slices.
That you get from the deli, the really buttery ones.
I'm a good old boy, I like a fucking Kraft single.
You like a confederate flag shaped cheese.
No!
I'll eat a Kraft single, I'll fucking...
Kraft single's fine.
It's good.
I'll fold it up.
I used to not like it when I was a kid.
You know it'd be great.
But I grew up.
This is like a really expensive bread with a Kraft single grilled cheese.
You know what would be really good?
Awesome.
Like the greatest sandwich in the world.
Yeah.
Wouldn't that be so good?
Yeah, you know what would be great is like...
Like the best ingredients, everything is the best.
Five star, five course meal.
Did you see that Burger King tried to get a Michelin star?
They did?
Yeah.
And I don't think the new, the quarterly like Michelin guide has come out yet, so they may
have gotten one.
Wow.
Damn.
Yeah.
were like please go review these locations they're fire yeah Michelin man
there if you live near a Burger King yeah yeah that's that's how you people that
that's what you know to make the best food you can possibly make when a giant
yeah he's wearing sunglasses and yeah yeah my name's David yeah I'm here
under cover. What's your name? Just initials mm. Yeah, he's just holding a
bunch of tires. Yeah, yeah, yeah. And can you serve it to me on these tires? He can
only eat off a tire. Can I get a possible whopper? Yeah, oil. Yeah, they only give
you go to a four star Michelin restaurant. Everything's car themed.
What the fuck is this man? Best filet mignon in the world. Yeah, they put like
the pickles on the side of the burger like a tire.
You're like, "Oh, okay, now I get it.
Yeah, that makes sense."
The, uh, when you, if you live near a Burger King,
your apartment just, like, you can smell Burger King
from a mile away.
Yeah, man, you can smell the paint that they put on the burgers.
Dude, whatever that fucking, like, car exhaust they use
for their chargrill.
Dude, Subway has the number one fucking,
we're pumping it out.
They're polluting the earth with smells.
Yeah.
like half of boston smells like subway yeah well there's so many subways there
for i mean it's insane well you know the subway the subway regional headquarters
is in concord so it could be could be the reason why
there's so many subways in the thing is that where they do a lot of like
fat poor people they do secret missions yeah the headquarters
yeah that's the hq we gotta figure out how to get all the yoga mat chemicals
into the bread without people finding out
yeah you walk by subway like i mean it's like a it's a couple city blocks yeah
that smoke covers. Yeah. Yeah, like from literally like Boylston to Government Center just smells
like Subway. Yeah. I miss it dude. Oh my god. They have a little elf that lives in the ceiling where
they just hand up a sandwich to him and he chews it up and breathes out of the vents.
That's how they do it. He's never brushed his teeth. He only eats the bread, he's never brushed
his teeth. Yeah. Hold on. Hold on. Hold up. How many Subways are there? Because there's that one
that's in like the corner, the one like in government center by the uh the subway near the wax museum.
The one I used to I used to work at that wax museum. Did you know that? Oh you worked there?
Yeah. You worked there for like one day. I worked there for one day. Wasn't it owned by like some
Brazilian like mob guy? Yeah. It's like a complete tourist trap. It cost $30. I worked there for one
day and they made they said that you can't take a bathroom break and you have to stand outside for
eight hours and just sit next to a wax Peter Dinklage while like Chinese
tourists come up to it and they're like this is Matt Damon and you're like no
this is Peter Dinklage. Yeah he shrank. It was a little bit hot outside. The way I quit, we ran out of
wax so we had to make them small. The way I quit was I just an hour before my shift
ended I just took off the shirt and left it on the counter and I just
left. I never paid before it. I just I was like this is the worst job ever I'm
not fucking doing this. Yeah. Yeah, I've heard nothing. I was really, really poor in Boston.
Yeah. Yeah. It's pretty awesome. How much were you getting paid there? At the wax museum?
Yeah. Zero because I didn't. Well, how much would have you, would you? I think it was
minimum wage, just like 15 an hour. It would have changed my life. I didn't, I mean, I
never had any money in Boston, but especially not like then because it was before I started
working at the gym. Oh yeah. And that's when I... I remember going into that interview
at the gym. Oh yeah, I recommended you. And he was like, "I'm not fucking hiring that guy."
I went in and he was like, "Oh, so you know Caleb from Improv?" And I went, "Yep,
exactly. That's exactly where I know him from."
That dude rocks. I loved him so much. He would just fucking...
Yeah, you said he had so much CTE.
He got hit in the head so many times doing Jiu Jitsu that he would talk to you and he'd be like,
Yeah, so you need to fold the...
the towels.
I should have just used that.
And then he would drool. He would drool while he was talking to you.
I should have just used that to my advantage in the interview.
Yeah. I mean, it was like stopping time. You can use him like a click remote.
You can just snap right at his face and he just freezes for a whole minute.
You can use him like a remote and click, and when he's frozen you could punch him in the
face a bunch of times and fart on him. Yeah, and then just come back.
Yeah, confuse him because he doesn't know where the sound's coming from.
him.
Yeah.
Just if you just point behind him, he'll turn and look for 10 minutes.
He was one of those guys.
Wait, the oscillating fan.
Okay, now it's gone.
Wait, it's coming back.
Yeah.
It's just that bit.
It's just that bit in Freddy Got Fingered where he's trying to, he gets into the, oh,
the elevator.
Yeah, Japan 4.
Yeah, just points at the floor and shit.
Upstairs, upstairs, Japan 4.
The penguin.
What does he say?
for the badger? Yeah, great movie. Yeah, it's the best movie ever dude. It's up there. But
yeah, he would just like, he always insisted on fucking talking to me about his tattoos
he had. Yeah, yeah, he'd be like, yeah, I got a new tattoos, new tattoos eight years ago.
Do you want to see them? Yeah, and he had stuff like that. He had like a peace sign on his
arm and then he had like a like a like one arm was like a Japanese like full
traditional sleeve and then the other was just like stuff where he's like yeah my
cousin did this like yeah in the back of a Ferrari yeah pretty cool right it's
always cool when you can like tell somebody got the tat their tattoo from
their cousin I miss having just like a stupid boss yeah you know it's fucking
awesome all my every boss that I had was like very cool when I worked I've never
had a terrible work experience. When I worked at the museum at MIT I had a great
boss but all my co-workers were like crazy old women and one of them was I
mean they're all just like hippies who are like artists that can't make a living doing art
so they work at a museum and one of them she never she always was connected to a
wire that was connected to the ground and she was like I was like one day I was
like are you like plugged in like what the fuck is that she was like oh so
basically what happens is your ions when you're not touching the ground because
you have rubber soles on your shoes they disconnect you from the earth and so
what I have done is I have a wire that goes into the ground and I attach
myself to it. How have you never talked about this person? I don't know. But yeah she was always connected to a wire. What the fuck?
Yeah and she offered to buy me one of the wires she was like they sell them
online they're $180 but I can get them really cheap because I know the guy who
makes them and that's so sick. I mean she claimed it like changed her life.
She claimed she broke her back and then being plugged into the wire healed it.
That's so sick. That's like that's I would find websites for like you could
buy order like a chakra detector for $800 and it's just like it's like a it's a
thermometer yeah instead of saying a number it said it just says like it says
like sacrum clogged. It's like the time travel machine in Napoleon
dynamite. Oh yeah with the crystals. Like that shit like I mean that shit gets sold
on eBay all the time. People just sell toaster. Maybe we should just
start doing getting into that. We could sell to people like my grandpa. Yeah we
could do like you know those back in the day when people would make like cool
stuff out of duct tape. We can do like yeah that shit. Well for your chakras.
Yeah. Yeah. Chakra cleanser. We could do a book called the duct tape chakra.
Yeah. You know. Yeah we just make a duct tape wallet and sell it as a chakra
catcher align your chakra with duct tape yeah you take a whole road a whole roll
of duct tape paint of the back and for top of skull and your agent 47 spot huh
you know this fucking tape yourself you go around your head and you do the whole
roll of tape yeah if you can do that at home you send us a photo you sent
Patrick a photo send me a photo I don't want to send you you send me a photo I'll
- I'll send you a $5 bill in the mail.
- Really?
Like a sweepstakes?
- Yep.
Whole roll of duct tape.
- First person.
- Whole roll of duct tape,
gooch to head top and around.
- Vertical wrap.
- One line.
- One mummy.
Vertical mummy.
You gotta vertically mummy yourself with duct tape.
- But no, not all over your,
but just one line of duct tape.
That you're going over and over.
- Like a racing stripe.
- Yeah, like one down the middle stripe.
- Yeah, that you keep going over and over.
We'll put a diagram up.
Yeah, with the episode.
You know what, we'll just do it to Pat, so some people have an example.
One time we duct taped my friend to a couch in high school.
We used to duct tape my little brother to the wall.
Yeah, dude, that's the best.
He would like fall asleep.
Levi was like the fucking heaviest sleeper.
And so when he would sleep, he could do anything.
Like you'd like pick him up and use him like a puppet.
"Honey, come on."
And we duct taped him to the wall and he just woke up just like screaming one night.
He was there for like an hour.
there's we did we duct tape my friend kevin like we wrapped it around a bunch
of inducted into the couch
and there's a video of him dislike thrashing around going
s
and my brother friend was sitting on the reporting on one time i was a ran
wrapped me to my bed and i thought i died
but i couldn't move i just got out of the worst when you get like you it
not being able to remove yeah
in a prank horrible i got my cousins uh...
my cousin's dad had like a boat
And I got stuck in like the-
- You went all paralyzed from a prank.
- Yeah, I got stuck inside,
there was like a small room with like bunk beds in it.
Like I don't remember what the fuck it was,
but there was like a hole in the floor.
It was like a perfect square.
And I tried to like, you know when you're a little kid
and you try to like fit into a spot?
- You can fit in anything.
- You can fit, yeah, but you try to like fit like,
oh, like I'm gonna like see if I can like
perfectly fit into the glove seat.
- Yeah, in my brain I can't.
Yeah, yeah, so I tried to do that but ended up getting stuck and like freaked the fuck out cuz I didn't know how to get
Up. Mm-hmm cuz it's like the boats moving
So I that's scary shit. Yeah, especially cuz the like if fucking boats rocking and I can't move
Yeah, yeah when I was 11, we put my cousin into an iron maiden and killed him. I
Know a kid who got stuck in his family's like elevator in his house got chopped in half. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, I didn't know him, but my parents.
And his top half and his bottom half both grew back separately.
Yeah, and then they were sexy twins and they did porn.
Yeah, and they're called the elevator twins.
Now that was a real kid then, I shouldn't say that.
My cousin had elevator buttons on his closet.
I actually don't know if he got chopped in half, that's what I assumed as a kid.
I just knew that a kid died because he got trapped in like Final Destination style as the elevator was going down.
He had a dumbwaiter?
Why did he have an elevator in his house?
That was my question. I was like, "How rich is this fucking kid?"
Yeah.
Maybe he just lived in a hotel like Suite Life of Zack and Cody.
He could have been Zack or Cody.
That's the origin of Zack and Cody!
That's the twins! Oh my god!
Here I am in your life, here you are in mine.
Yes, I got chopped in half by an elevator.
That one time.
But that was fine.
But it ended up fine.
It's not a crime to die.
It's a crime to kill yourself, isn't that weird?
No.
No, it's not weird.
They should be punished.
Yeah.
Yeah, they haven't been through enough.
That's true.
Yeah.
Well, now that your son's dead, he's going to jail.
Yeah, if your son ever comes back to life, let us know.
Yeah, they should bring the dead bodies to jail and let them use them for arts and crafts.
Or as like a fuck puppet.
No.
That's disgusting!
Come on!
Oh my god.
It would cut down on sexual assault and genital--
They should kiss--
No.
and go on dates with them. They should be buried, but they should bring the ashes to jail. They
should have to be in love first. Yeah. They should have to fall in love with the dead
body. Yeah. No, they should cremate them if they request it, or bury them. How would they
request anything? They're dead. If you're cremated, look, if I'm cremated, do whatever
you want with my ashes. I don't care. You want to be fe- fe-melted. What? You want to
be turned into a girl. You want to be creme-ulated. Okay. You want to be creme-pied. We did that.
(laughing)
- We did that like yesterday.
- All right, we gotta switch gears.
We're just gonna do that episode again.
Fuck.
- Yeah, let's restart that episode.
- Okay.
- You don't have any floss sticks here,
I just remembered that.
I gotta get this thing out of my dad's tooth.
- Dude, I told you, use a piece of paper.
- Do you have that, is that fork still up there?
- You're not gonna use a fork in your tooth.
- Why, a plastic fork?
- He has like a hole in his tooth.
- Yeah.
- I don't know if the fork's still up there.
- Yeah, dude, my tooth has just been like,
I was supposed to go to the dentist on Monday,
the Monday that I came down here.
- Sorry, I'm moving to New York City to follow my dreams,
so I can't really come to the dentist.
- I'm gonna follow my dreams for three days.
- For my life-saving operation.
- Sorry, I can't get my fillings and shit.
- I hope it's one of those things
where it gets an abscess in your tooth
that infects your brain and you die.
- Yeah? - You hope that?
- I guess I don't hope that, now that I think about it.
That'd suck.
- There's probably an abscess in my tooth.
- Yeah.
- There's an absence in your heart.
- There's an absence in my Maryland ancestry.
in your tooth. What the hell? Turn this light on. I can't even see you guys. Turn that off.
Absinthe is the one that people think. It's the one that like Anthony Bourdain made an
episode of his fucking show where he was like, "Absinthe gets you high." Yeah, like people
say that absinthe is like hallucinating. You just get fucking, I mean it's just alcohol.
There's nothing else. You don't actually get. It's just like hot, it's like moonshine. Yeah.
Some people got like, some people hallucinated but that was because of something in the barrels
or something that the absinthe was being kept in.
Really?
Yeah.
I didn't know that.
Do you guys drink Everclear?
Would you drink Everclear?
I think I have before.
I would drink anything.
Do you have some?
I think I have.
How was it?
No, I did drink Moonshine though.
It tasted amazing.
Moonshine is not that crazy.
I drank Apple Pie Moonshine.
It never tastes like what they advertise it as.
No.
Yeah, it's like how all fucking vape flavors taste like electricity.
You tasted like apple pie at first and then you do the rest of the shot and then
The rest of the shot? You sipped a shot?
It was a shot glass of apple pie moonshine.
Yeah, so you shoot it.
Yeah, I took it like a half a sip. I'm not gonna do a whole shot of moonshine.
And then you did the other half.
No, I gave the other half to a friend.
You shared a shot with a man.
No, it was a girl.
*Burp*
*Laughter*
You drank with a girl?
Oh my god.
That's like you're kissing her.
I think.
I don't even remember.
I don't feel so good.
I'm gonna blow chunks.
You know what?
I drank moonshine so I don't fucking remember what happened.
You drank one sip of moonshine and just blacked out completely.
It was like hangover too.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Zacky G was there?
Yep.
Zach Galifianakis was kind of just like you mixed with Zach Galifianakis.
What the hell?
Mmhmm.
I'm bringing that song back you guys.
We're gonna do a cover of Hot Shell Ray, that's the next sensitive gangster track.
You know the la la la whatever.
Oh I know that song.
Going at it tonight!
Oh wait I forgot that song makes me so angry.
Why?
I don't know.
That song is like one of the worst songs of all time.
I feel like- It's probably tied with every song you'll ever make.
Oh my god.
We made a song today.
True, that was some- That joint was fire.
That'll be like three weeks ago for you guys.
Yeah.
was actually so fire though. Yeah. We don't miss. You don't miss. Musically. Please cap
straight up. We're like the. Please, please pot of Ls boys. Just cap one time. Oh my god.
Just cap even one time. Sorry bitch. Yeah. We're true to the game. We don't do crap. We don't do
crap. We're not putting out this mainstream bullshit. Yeah. We're underground. We're
underground. We're underground. We're weird. We're weird. So what? We're the weird podcast. So what
But if we're weird, we're weird, we're guys, we have three microphones and we're here to
tell you some weird crap and you're gonna...
We're gonna fucking convince you abortion's murder.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
And that's a weird take.
Uh-huh.
That's a weird thing to say.
But it's ours, especially Patrick.
It's not mine.
Patrick got all this into that.
I have no opinion on abortion.
None?
No.
Then you're complacent.
I'm complaining about them.
Then you should at least give the fetus a chance to run away first.
Yeah.
I'm going to give you a 10 second head start here.
It's not a bad idea.
You'll be playing tag with this giant drill and you're it.
Have you seen those videos that get shared around Christian Facebook groups where it's
like, "The doctors pulled the baby out limb by limb."
Yeah, it's like a behind the scenes footage of the thing where the animatronics are malfunctioning.
Like this is a fetus at 5,000 weeks and they aborted him.
And now he's a nudely, now he's a fucking spider.
That's kind of cool man.
Maybe we should keep doing that.
If E.T. had a baby.
E.T. got aborted?
Very different movie.
You could already do the movie.
It wouldn't even happen.
It would be called Elliot.
Yeah, exactly.
It would just be about the lamest kid ever.
It's kind of weird how ET is the first and last letter of Eliot.
Wow.
Think about that.
That's my favorite argument that people have against abortion, where they're like, "That
ET?"
No.
But people will be like, "Well, what if Martin Luther King Jr. had been aborted?"
Yeah.
It's like, "He was."
I mean, "Sure."
Yeah.
"What if Jesus Christ had been aborted?
Would you be pro-abortion then?"
Yeah.
Yeah, dude, because I wouldn't be a Christian.
Look at how many problems he caused.
He caused a lot of problems for a lot of people. Yeah, you know when people say
something bad, when something bad happens people say, "Oh Jesus Christ."
So say Jesus H. Christ. What's that H stand for?
Hitler. That's kind of weird to say. I don't think so.
That's your name. Why did you catch it? That was my, the side of my
body that I lost all control of. Oh okay. Yeah. It does anything,
anything I don't want it to do.
Oh, he just got a toothache.
You're like that lion from that movie.
Yeah.
You need a mouse in your mouth for real.
Damn, I need a mouse in my mouth tonight.
Damn.
Ooh.
If I get a little mouse in my mouth.
Damn, I'm lonely at home.
Would you eat a mouse?
Yeah.
A mouse?
I mean, I thought when we had a mouse problem,
I was like 50/50 either wife that thing up as my pet or just fucking eat it.
But you can't, you can't wife up a city mouse.
A field mouse, maybe.
A field mouse you could probably take and make a pet.
What are you talking about?
A city mouse? Are you kidding me?
A city mouse is used to being in the city.
Yeah, a city mouse is used to being in the city.
You're saying a field mouse, one that, one that's used to
roaming wild, I could put it in a cage?
Fucking no way.
No way.
You could put it on a leash.
What?
No.
I'm done talking to you for the day.
You're in timeout.
No, I'm not.
Let's play the silent game, Pat.
Okay.
Yeah.
I hate this so much. Please talk. Please talk.
One time I was walking around Harvard Square with Aaron and we saw a mouse, we were just walking down the sidewalk and we saw a mouse run really fast across the sidewalk in front of us and it ran right into a sewer crate.
It just ran, just went into the hole and just fell in. Just like literally like half a second.
Just wily coyote-ed?
crazy I think it's like burned into my brain forever one of the funniest
physical things I've ever seen missing a mouse disappear yeah cuz it just like it
appeared and then it just like went into a hole and it was gone it didn't even
make a noise when it hit the bottom of it like it's still falling yeah it's
vanished it's an endless sewer I'm gonna tickle Patrick do you think you think of
mouse had hollow bones like a bird it could fly? Yeah. Do you think if a bird didn't have
wings it couldn't fly? Yes. Okay. I think the trick to flying is hollow bones. And wings.
Let's hollow those things out dude, come here. I'm taking that, I'm sucking that marrow out
of you. Yeah. That does reduce my risk of bone cancer. Bone cancer? Oh yeah, that's when your
bones get spiky. That is the scariest cancer.
That's the scariest kind of cancer.
Because your bones, they just...
fucking, you get spiky bones.
What the hell?
The scariest cancer is ghost cancer.
True.
Vampire cancer.
It's where you grow a ghost in your body.
Freddy Krueger cancer.
Yeah.
Ah!
Yeah, the scariest cancer is when your fingers grow blades.
It's when you find out you have cancer on Halloween.
That's the scariest cancer.
That is... I mean, what's scarier than that?
Yeah.
Would you rather find out you have cancer on Christmas or Halloween?
Christmas.
Halloween I'd be like, "Yeah, what else is new?"
But Christmas I'd be like, "Am I even going to open my presents?"
Well, Christmas you would have the presents first.
What?
Oh true, I guess you'd find out on Christmas Day and you already opened the presents.
No, you'd find out on Christmas Eve.
Well, you didn't say that.
The next day you have presents to look forward to, but hopefully it's nothing like vacation in five years.
Yeah.
True.
You get a bunch of presents.
You win a lifetime supply of candy.
Yeah, yeah.
Of hair dye.
Yeah.
Dude, awesome.
This is gonna fucking rule.
Yeah.
Oh.
Christmas should be about winning.
It is.
No, it should be like you should have to--
In America-ca-ca.
You should have to win something to get a present.
You think Christmas should be a game show with you and Santa Claus?
Mm-hmm.
Wait.
Yes.
Sorry, did I just accidentally spit the most amazing idea of all time?
Yes, you did.
Okay.
Okay. It could be called...
Christmas with the Thanks.
Uh...
Christmas with the Thanks? Because you're thanking them for giving you the prize.
Well that is technically just regular Christmas.
Shut up.
You shut up. What about Chris...
Uh... What about Chris Rock with
Tom Hanks?
Chris San...
Chris Sanx. Chris Rock with Tom Hanks instead of Christmas with the Cranks.
Chris Rock with Tom Hanks? Uh-huh.
That could be a good movie.
Yeah.
We just have to figure out a different title.
They were in a movie together, right?
Chris Rock and Tom Hanks.
They were in Madagascar.
Was Tom Hanks in Madagascar?
He's on the island, and then they find him on the island.
Dave Chappelle is in You've Got Mail, but he plays like a--
he's like-- that was in the '90s when he was like 19,
doing all these movie roles.
And he's supposed to be like 35 in that movie.
Yeah, dude, he was like 25 when he made Half-Baked.
he was he was nineteen and he did uh... at the role in uh...
men in tights
really yeah
he was nineteen on letter to you
for twenty
we got a list of really got a driver's license
well yeah can you believe that
that's what you say can we have a list of their for our own idea
so halfway through it uh... top ten
things parents need to stop doing
pay parents
or soon to be parents reading this
I'm a 13 year old so you probably won't listen to me, but you should.
I'm trying to help you be better and don't do these to your children.
Number one, abusing their children.
Big facts.
Yeah.
I'm going to go on record.
We spot the lie here.
I'm going to go on record and say I never hit a kid unless they deserve it.
Please miss when you try to hit your kids.
Yeah.
I think this is wrong.
I think you shouldn't hit kids, but I think you should beat the shit out of your dogs
Why cuz I
Don't know cuz I'm bored. It's like yeah, I'm just bored. I
Don't know what you guys think about spanking though spanking. No is that hitting?
Yeah
Yeah, I would never spank a kid. No. No, it's weird. Yeah, is it it's spankings weird
Why we're to do to a kid just weird. Why you're hitting the kids, but yeah, you made it weird when you do that
See, I mean you change at least
Where you're in the head? Yeah, if you have to change your diaper, you have to fucking know what hole I didn't your honor
I did not fight that man. I was simply spanking
Yeah, he said something rude to me, and I was spanking him to show him not to say that again. I spanked him with a gun
I
Don't know. I think I think spanking school cuz then your kids get to complain
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, I mean you could would grow up to become an artist so maybe spoon growing up. Yeah, yeah
They just got hit with the hand yeah your mom with a hammer. Yeah. Yeah, you did yeah
- Yeah, I got hit to death by a hammer.
- Your mom was trying to eat poop out of your butt.
- There's a famous video about it.
- Yeah, two guys hit you with a hammer.
- Two guys were hitting me with a hammer in this video.
Yeah, it's pretty fucked up,
but it happened to me and it's the truth.
I was just hit with a spoon, a wooden spoon,
and then one day my mom cracked it in half on my butthole.
- Yeah.
- On my butthole.
- She made you whittle a new one.
- She was trying to eat poop out of your butt, dude.
- Yeah.
- True, she was missing.
- Yeah, thank God it wasn't a fork.
- Yeah.
- I got the belt, I get hit with the belt.
belt yeah the belt is cool cuz I think it's he's hitting the sense of style
and yeah yeah exactly yeah yeah it's suck cuz my dad was a god yeah yeah my other
dad my dad is a heroin addict so he's hitting me with the hottest spoon yeah
once my dad started working at Hot Topic the the belts got really weird
yeah yeah yeah I had a fucking Marilyn Manson's name imprinted on me like a
Punisher dude dude they had hello we're standing on my life as when it was when
when my dad became Batman my dad would hit me with all of my dad
- I had to join the army, that bandolier.
One time the shotgun shell from his bandolier went off.
Chipped my shoulder.
- I saw my mommy hitting my daddy with a belt.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, daddy was wearing a ball gag.
My mommy was wearing the belt and hitting him real hard.
- Yeah, just hitting him real hard in the butt.
- And she was wearing a belt.
- And she had a funny belt buckle on.
- And the belt had a wiener on it?
They'll have a very hilarious book along.
Yeah.
Number two, trying to control their children's life.
Hehehehehe.
What is that?
That's like a super villain parent.
Yeah.
He's trying to do mind control.
Oh, okay.
That's kind of what I was going for there.
Let me try it again.
Hehehehehe.
Now that I have the context, the laugh makes sense.
I found this video about how to control your child's life.
I found a video where this woman, she's like, "Yeah, I'm a hypnotist and I've been hypnotizing
my children to do their homework and they did like a news story on it and then
that the like she just talks about and the children like yeah we love it it
helps us be better and more productive and that the end she's like and I also
hypnotized my husband and it's like a 30-second like I have no idea what she's
doing to her husband. I hypnotized my husband to chase down a senator. Yeah I think I mean
That shit's funny when people are like,
have like very strict, serious kids.
- Yeah.
- You know, like they read like that Tiger Mom book.
- Oh yeah.
- Like I knew some kids whose lives were just fucked
because their mom read the Tiger Mom book.
- Oh yeah, the fucking Tiger Mom book is just like a--
- Did you guys read the Tiger Mom book?
I read the Tiger Mom book.
- No, I'm waiting to tell my mom.
- It's just a guide to abuse your kids.
- Yeah, yeah.
- It's crazy.
- At the end of it, like, the daughter,
the like rebellious daughter,
they're at like a restaurant
and the mom is being crazy to her daughter
and the daughter just like smashes a bunch of glasses
and plates from the restaurant and is just like,
fuck you, I'm not gonna ever do what you tell me again.
And then leaves and then it's like,
and that was the crazy story of how I raised my daughter.
It's like it clearly didn't work.
- What are those girls are doing now?
- Yeah, it's like, oh, that's just an anomaly.
- Yeah.
- One's probably--
- Usually it works, but sometimes.
- Yeah, sometimes--
- One's probably a cop and one's probably like
in a very expensive escort.
(laughing)
Like that's what you get with the tiger mom lifestyle.
Yeah, it's very expensive because, you know, tigers don't come cheap.
You want to fuck a tiger?
That's going to cost you. Keep going.
Look, I've seen Tiger King, I've seen Joe Exotic.
I know, I know.
We got the bastard Carol Best.
Yeah, she's a tiger mom.
I just want to see the tweets, "Carol Baskin dies."
I want to see half of the people going, "We fucking got her!"
And then half of the people going, "She was actually a real person with a real life."
Right.
Yeah, I'd probably put something like, "I guess her husband, her dead husband, what
did he feed her to the tiger?"
What, she accidentally used sardine oil?
"Oh, I guess she fed herself to some tigers."
Yeah.
It's like, "No, she overdosed."
She opened those.
I was imagining the tigers.
She was chasing the tiger.
Chasing the white tiger.
Yeah.
That's how she died.
Carol Baskin.
Carol Baskin died of tigers.
Carol Baskin died of a tiger attack.
(laughter)
It sucks how much...
I miss Johnny.
Carol Baskins on this show yeah as a joke and then it's morphed into just us
talking about Carol Baskins in our regular life that might be a you probably
I don't talk about Carol Baskins no no Gamecube brother sheep I play Gamecube
with her you play with her sometimes really yeah little what do you play
Play fantasy star online on Gamecube with Carol Baskins
Number three dictating career choices, it's kind of the same as number two
No, I don't know. I you know those people are like
Here's my little lawyer. Yeah. Yeah, dude. Fuck you man. Your kids way stupid to be a lawyer. Yeah
Yeah, it's very realistic. Yeah. Oh, there's my Times Square spider-man. Yeah
Yeah, my great-grandma always said she was like one day you will be the president of the United States
And it's like thank God you fucking died
Fucking thing crazy to do in sixth grade. We had to do like some
like
It was like gold board or something like that. He was like, yeah, you know, we're good
my my social studies teacher was like we're gonna make like a
Board and you're gonna cut out like newspaper clippings and stuff like magazine clip. Hey, what's bored me? Yeah
but on mine, I said I wanted to be a doctor and he like saw it and was just like
Okay
It's so cool. If you ask like a kindergarten or what they want to be when they grow up
They'll be like I'm gonna be a frog. Yeah. Yeah, that's like a spider-man. Yeah, I'd be evil. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, I'm just gonna be evil when I grow up just be a villain. Yeah, I'm gonna be a super villain like real shit
I'm gonna be the Red Skull. Yeah, basically my whole my whole career path has just big been me becoming the Green Goblin
Yeah, I'm basically gonna become like an evil like a scientist like fine at first
Yeah, but then I'm gonna invent some sort of like I'm gonna invent like so skeleton
Some octopus arms jump in in front of a ray
Space mission and get hit by rays in space basically what I'm trying to do is work
Around or with gamma as much as I can
Try to just get as close to gamma as possible
But not so close it kills me but close enough that it makes me kind of like an evil
Yeah, it makes me kind of like a soup that can turn into like anything. I think of yeah
I want to have rocks for a body when I get older. I'm playing on being the blob
Yeah, cuz then I'd be anything the what the blobs only power is that he can run really fast
The blob was just a thing.
Yeah, it was just an unstoppable force.
Yeah, whoa.
Are you talking about the blob like...
Oh, I thought you were talking about X-Man blob.
I didn't even know there was a blob.
He's a supervillain.
He's just really fat.
That's his power.
Nobody could like knock him down because he was too fat.
What did you do to power?
Made McDonald's?
Radioactive?
He got bit by a radioactive ember.
The blob what did he eat a tiger? No?
My fucking my god Cameron you've really done it this time
Would you find would you fall into a fucking falling some grease the blob?
What is this guy named Bob and he added an L in his name tag?
Yeah
You had a misprint yeah, I should call him the typo
All right number four spanking children
Which we've already covered we talked about that. Yeah, we already talked about that. What are the comments here hold up?
Horrible punishment it causes injury by breaking the capillaries and causing burn trauma, so it's an overrated punishment. That's been taken to her
It's my biggest complaint about spanking is it's overrated big red baboon ass. Yeah, I got spanked as a kid
Yeah, I was a swollen giant sexy ass mm-hmm
Bad punishment, it's just as bad as taking away their things I
Think one of them
Think one of them is a lot longer
Taking their chance away to me is way worse
When I was a kid you guys do so much rather just like get spanked and get it fucking over with you guys ever play the
Trick where they're like I'm gonna take away your favorite toy, and you're like oh my favorite toy. Yeah
up. Yeah, I actually I just left it in the toilet. Yeah, fucking bitch,
fucking stupid. Yeah, it's actually this this this broken action figure is
actually my favorite. Yeah, yeah, I know. Don't take that away. Don't
touch it.
I was just playing with my homework, but secretly I'm gonna go back under
my favorite play. My favorite toy.
but secretly she doesn't know.
- Yeah, my favorite toy, dad's,
well, why don't you go somewhere
and buy something nice for yourself, sweetheart?
I think you might have a better attitude.
- Hey, mom, my favorite toy is a bouquet of flowers
just for you.
(laughing)
Yeah, so if you wanna take that away, be my guest.
- Yeah, you wanna take that, throw it in the trash?
Oh, okay.
My favorite toy, $100.
- My favorite toy's my penis, mom.
Are you willing to go to jail for your fight?
(laughing)
I don't think so.
- That would never happen.
number five putting pressure on their children like you like john cory
i think that the president of the board of the
my son
you send walks into the dinner party with anvil on his head
uh... under the futon
but it was a take turns it not been a bit of a about it i'm on the other
spill the last one hundred
and i think he likes let them know it
he ate too much cereal yesterday and we're punishing him
with the comments on this one
uh... there's one about asian parents
okay don't even
i hope there's no there help there's new ones that causes major anxiety and can
lead to serious issues later on in life
big facts parental pressure is just as bad as peer pressure is the like parent
like i i honestly think ninety nine percent of like
adults consider their childhood trauma is just their parents just
not even fucking realizing what they're doing.
Oh yeah, for sure.
Like none of it's on purpose.
People always blame their parents for, they were like, "Yeah, they fucking bought me the
wrong skateboard as a kid and made me gay."
It's like, you, I don't know.
It's such a crapshoot raising kids.
Yeah, yeah.
You know?
Yeah, they just said something that they, and then they didn't think about it.
Yeah, my dad gave me too much stuff and you know, now I'm really traumatized because-
My dad had too much swag and it made me feel inadequate.
My dad gave me a Nintendo and I wanted a Sega.
I broke grandma's arm.
Now I'm a murderer and it's his fault.
I wanted a Sega and my dad got me a Nintendo and a Sega.
So I threw the Nintendo out the window.
I swung it around and I hit dad.
Dad say hello fail block.
I hit dad in the head and now he's in a wheelchair forever.
My mom is still in the fail block.
And it's so traumatic having a crippled dad.
Isn't that the plot of Garden State?
I haven't seen that.
Me neither.
Like, the whole thing in Garden State is that, like, Zach Braff's character is like, "Oh,
I have so much childhood trauma because I accidentally pushed my mom over, like, the dishwasher would
open up sometimes, and I pushed my mom one day because I was mad at her and she fell
back and it paralyzed her for the rest of her life, and my dad always blamed me."
So yeah, that's your fault. Your fucking fault right there. Yeah. Yeah, you deserve to have trauma for that.
I call him Zach Math, fucking boring ass actor.
He's boring as hell.
It's like watching someone do math in front of me.
Dude, Gordon State?
Gordon State?
That movie sucks.
Again, I have not seen it.
Yeah.
Take that, Zach Braff.
I'm coming for you.
I'm gonna punch you in the face, dude.
Zach Braff, I'm gonna expose you.
For beating up that 12 year old.
Have you ever seen that footage?
Zach Braff beating the shit out of a 12 year old kid
because of pumped.
- You told me that.
- Yeah, dude it rocks.
- Yeah, super swag, very sick.
Number six, let their kids smoke/vape.
- I would let my kids smoke.
- Didn't your parents let you smoke?
- Kinda.
- But you're cool.
- When I like, towards like my 18th birthday
when they found out I smoked cigs,
my mom did buy me cigs.
- Nice.
- So when I was like 17 my mom bought me cigs.
- But she bought you like kid cigs.
- She bought me Camel Blues, so yeah.
- Yeah, whoa, controversial dude.
- They're the best cigarettes though.
- Yeah, all cigarettes taste like dirt.
- Yeah. - Yeah, there's no difference.
- I think I might've had like,
I might've been hypnotized or something,
like if I smell a cigarette now,
I feel like I'm gonna puke.
- I got straight Hitler-tized.
- I got Hitler-tized, exactly.
Like I'll try to smoke a cigarette when I drink and like--
- And you do not like it?
- No, I feel like I'm gonna throw up.
- That's funny.
I smoked cigs forever.
Yeah, that's an odd thing to all of a sudden...
Yeah.
So I've heard sometimes if you get like the flu or something and you like...
Like sometimes people will get the flu and then like quit cigarettes because like it fucked up their taste buds or something.
Woah.
Oh yeah, there's something like if you...
Yeah, if you get the flu like yeah, and then you like eat a certain food...
Like eat your food... a food you like during having the flu like you won't like it anymore.
Exactly.
I can never eat collard greens again because I ate collard greens and then got like the stomach flu really bad
And I just vomited them for like yeah, two days that happened to me when I was a kid
I I like loved hot dogs
And then one time I had hot dogs and I like got really really sick, and I was like oh
I can't eat hot dogs anymore, but then eventually I can't eat cheese poofs cheese poops cheese poofs cheese poofs
Only this place puffs cheese poofs
poofs
Cheese poops cheese poofs cheese cheese pucks cheese pucks
Cuz you ate them weird. I think
Yeah, I got the flu fucked up. I can't eat cheesy wheezes anymore. Yeah, I think
The willies
Get he be jeebies I had him I had the flu yeah, I hate fevers now I hate getting a fever
Kind of ruined vomiting for me. Yeah, I can't throw up anymore because of cuz I ate a hot dog before I threw up
Fucking bummer now whenever I throw up think about hot dogs number seven
Telling children what music to listen to that's actually true. Yeah, that's what my dad did with me, and I'm fucking
Lovely skinnered till I die well ordin lightfoot fuck. Yes. Oh, yeah
Today today is the anniversary of the end of the admin Fitzgerald damn, dude
This isn't gonna be released on that day. So a load of iron ore. Yeah, it's their ears not yours
Everyone swears sex is a normal part of life and people can sing about whatever they want
My mom was pretty stupid about like me listening to rap girl. Yeah, I couldn't I the only rap I could listen to was like MC
Hammer. Yeah, she my mom. Yeah that
The phrase ballin had something to do with sex. Yeah, so any song that they all in the ball
That's that's yeah
That's why I got so into
into new metal right is because I'd listen to like Green Day and Linkin
Park and my parents were like iffy on that you know but then I go online and I
find like All in the Family by Korn and I'm like "Oh my God!" "Friend Durst you need to rehearse!"
Yeah, where they call each other gay for like five minutes and
yeah they just say like "Oh your sister is gonna suck your dick" and I'm like
"Holy shit I didn't know music like this could exist." I didn't know white boys could be
so crazy. Yeah. Damn. Yeah I think my mom listened to like Without Me or something
and she was like, just forever, she was like, "Eminem is okay to listen to in the house."
My mom caught me listening... Do you remember Music Choice on the Comcast channels?
It's like the...
Oh, yeah.
It's like the channels that would just play music. And my mom caught me listening to Fat Joe
on it. She came into the house. She was outside doing something. She came back inside. I was
dancing to Fat Joe in the living room. And she was like, "You cannot listen to this!" And turned
on classic hip-hop and it was literally just playing "You Can't Touch This." I was like,
"This sucks compared to that." One time my nana unplugged my iPod touch that I was borrowing
to listen to "Lean Back" by Fat Joe. Yeah. And then she just turned it off and I'm like,
"I don't think she'll ever use it again." Yeah. Yeah. My mom still does it. Like a year ago,
I was listening to Young Thug, that one song where he says, "She sucks my dick on the plane,
so I call her Airhead and my mom just says, you know, she does the, she does what on the plane?
So he calls her what? Oh my, uh, come on mom. I'm vibing down here in the basement. I'm just trying
to hang on my slat right now. Yeah, and you're fucking, fucking messing it up. Mom, I'm sliming.
I'm sliming, mom. Chill, mom. God, I'm gonna need to sip some codeine to take the edge off.
Parents are gonna yeah, that's one thing about now like like like rap like playboy cardi and shit his parents can't understand anymore
Yeah, to get angry. Yeah, my parents were never able to understand rap. Oh, yeah
My mom would listen to like fucking like Kanye and she'd be like, it's like he's speaking a different. Yeah. I know it's very funny
Yeah, it's uh, did something about rhythm
Nailed me with a rubber band god damn. Are you so good at that? I don't know the second time. They just hit me in the eyes
eyes. The rubber band. God damn it. Fuck that. I hate that you know how to do that, dude.
I'm hiding all the rubber bands next time you come to my house.
Those are from the chicken. Really? You didn't have those?
I'm going to talk to him. You freak.
Hey, did you give my friend rubber bands? I'm going to have a stern talking to.
They put rubber bands in Patrick's chicken. Yeah.
They're like, this guy looks like a guy who likes to digest rubber.
I was speaking my fucking I just remembered this around Christmas time in like 2012
when doing ass by Big Sean was big yeah my aunt freaked the fuck out cuz my my
cousin played it working yeah dude she went hot she went down no she like I
think like one of my cousins put it on and then when he said now make that
motherfucker hammer time she went like oh my god and like ran over it shut it
They always pick the funniest lyrics to get a man. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah fucking rules, dude. I mean that sounds fucking annoying
Yeah, so I feel like the overreaction was just cuz she didn't want to hear that song
I remember my mom got mad at me for listening that Eminem song
Rain, man. Yeah where he talks about who's that guy used to play Superman and like the 60s Christopher Reeve
Yeah, he like makes fun of Christopher Reeve. She's like, that's just wrong
It's like that's Superman right yeah, and I would listen to like kill you by him where he talks about like raping his mom
Yeah, he's like. I don't even understand what he's saying
This black fellas talking way too fast
Yeah number eight take away children's electronics
Evil that you should do that. I think my kids will not have any access to
I'm sorry, but I'm just saying.
Jesus Christ.
I'm giving a preview.
My kids will not have any access to electronics, including the microwave, until they're like 18.
Yeah.
I have weird little fucking freak kids.
I think the perfect age to give a kid like a phone
is like
16, but like I'll let them be on
the computer and shit.
My kids will never touch a computer.
Yeah, no, that's...
Yeah, I'm worried about my kids becoming alt-right.
My kids are.
have to end up like me yeah that's how I'll talk to my kids yeah like yeah I
just fucking playing runescape and I'll be like you're making all the same
mistakes your pops made I'm doing this for you I'm doing this for you I just
cut the Ethernet cable for you I'm throwing my own computer in the trash
this is for you trust me it impacts your 3m yeah you go back outside
- Yeah.
- Trust me, it impacts your children negatively.
It impacts me negatively pretty much.
It doesn't work at all.
It just makes things worse and puts pressure
on your children and gives them anxiety.
- Taking away my phone gave me anxiety.
- I mean, that's how people be--
- What if I missed a TikTok?
- I mean, that's seriously how it is these days.
What if I missed a coupon from the McDonald's app?
- No, kids don't even use coupons anymore.
- No, kids hate coupons.
- And that's a problem.
- They use QR codes.
- Kids think that coupons--
- Oh my fucking God, dude.
Kids think that coupons are life hacks now.
You know what kids think?
Kids think a coupon's a groupon.
Yeah, that's right.
And they don't even know about Great Poupon.
That's right.
I'd like to take a Poupon Groupon.
Hey, you guys ruined coupons.
(laughing)
You piece of crap.
You guys destroyed the coupon industry.
Yeah.
By making it digital.
Nobody's ever gonna be able to sell those books anymore.
Do you remember the fake coupons
that they used to have on 4chan?
Nah, I think so.
It was like people would make like scannable like fake coupons and it was like
manufacturer's coupon one free Xbox 360.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And people would try to use them.
They would work.
That's the thing.
There's a guy who got sued for like two million dollars of like lost revenue.
Because people...
Alright, fine. I'll pay it.
Here, take this coupon.
[Laughter]
Yeah.
What do you mean?
This coupon for Lamborghini Murciélago is not good?
Yeah.
Well, thank you for the coupon.
Court adjourned.
Wait a second.
Haha, double jeopardy.
You already said court adjourned.
Number nine, giving little kids cell phones.
Yeah.
Wait, that's...
We've already covered this.
Yeah, we said it was good, right?
I don't remember.
We said it was the best idea.
Well, how are they going to listen to this podcast?
Exactly.
My mom said she will give me my phone when I'm 15.
Turns out I got it when I was nine.
LOL.
Swag.
Six years early, dude.
Yeah, 'cause that's the thing,
I mean, you gotta teach your kids online etiquette.
Yeah, like for me, I mean, just immediately,
I was trying to have sex.
Use the lick emoji a lot.
When you're responding-- People love it.
People love it.
People love when you ask them to throw that thing back.
If your teacher ever texts you,
reminding you about homework, lick emoji.
Yeah, water.
Water and eggplant.
And licking.
Water, eggplant, lick, fist.
It means I'm at dinner right now,
I'll text you back later.
means I'm licking an eggplant at dinner and I'm drinking water and I'm staying hydrated.
Teachers want to know if the kids are hydrated. Do teachers text their kids now? I don't know.
Teachers, I have like friends from high school who became teachers and I see they post on Instagram
like, "Oh look at this funny email my kid sent me." And it's like, "I am chasing the cat around
the house and my parents are gonna get me." Just like stuff you know just stuff like that or like
- I would just be like--
- It's a bunch of crazy emojis and shit.
- I would just respond to all those and be like, cool.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- It's always weird when a professor in college
gives out his phone number in class.
- Yeah, and if you need to text me for anything,
and I mean anything. - Exactly.
- A lot of people at our college
got beers with their professors.
- Yeah, that was weird.
- Yeah, but the thing is, in college, you're all adults.
- Yeah, yeah. - That's also true.
- That's all fucking suck your teacher's dick, who cares?
- Yeah, that's true.
- Yeah. - You know?
- I guess I could--
You're all sexy, sexy adults.
Oh man, you 40.
I don't think I've ever had a single hot professor in college.
I think I did.
Oh yeah?
Name names.
Professor Patrick.
Professor Pamela.
Professor Pamela Beasley.
Yeah.
God, I have to go pee pee.
Number 10, let children dress how they want.
Children.
How was that bad?
Ben Trilden.
Ben Trill had a moment.
If it's showing their skins, then no.
Not to kids in 8-12 years old.
pedophiles will increases the chances of sexual harassment to them do that at the
start of seventeen to twenty three years old now you're seventeen years a bikini
it's all you're allowed to wear
yeah now that you're how you're safe from pedophiles no way you ever be assaulted
sexually in your life
here's a laundry good school
go to the market gives us a little bit of fish market because i'm tuning this
laundry
gonna be nice and cold. Can you get me a whole Chilean sea bass? I'm not letting my kid dress up wearing clothing
they exposed their midsections and legs. Pedophiles ain't touching this family.
That's a number one rule a family has to make. The first reply is but they're uncle is.
Oh my god. What are you doing? Have you seen that documentary about that the family who they had like a
neighbor who was like a pedophile who like fucked everyone in the family. Oh
Oh yeah, on Netflix?
And they kept like kidnapping their daughter and they were just like, "Sorry!"
He made the dad give him a handjob or something like that?
Yeah, the dad fucking blew him or some shit.
He fucked the mom and he kidnapped the kids.
Yeah.
And it's like, "Damn dude, he's 100%ing that family."
Every situation that the dad describes, he's always like, "Well, I don't know what happened,
but eventually."
Yeah, it was very confusing how he fucking caught my daughter with a butterfly net.
Yeah.
I had no idea what was going on.
(laughing)
- Yeah, it's such a weird one.
- He just had, there was something magic about him.
He was so charismatic.
- Yeah. - Yeah, so.
- Hey family, I'm gonna be taking your daughter.
I'll be back in a year or two.
- Yeah.
- I mean, how do we say no?
He's so charming.
- I left $20 on the stove.
- Wink.
- Oh, he left the stove on.
(laughing)
$20 burned up immediately.
I didn't even think it was $20.
I think that was printer paper.
- He's fucking, I mean, it's just so funny
just have a kid that just keeps getting kidnapped by the same dude.
Yeah.
Just being like, I mean, what can we possibly do?
He's our friend.
So weird.
Yeah, if they go to the police, they'll make fun of us for being friends with them.
You guys are weird.
Skip around here.
Spoiling children.
Yes.
Yeah, you do not want to spoil your child.
My kid's way past his expiration date.
I wish I had spoiled.
He's spoiled.
Number 13, drinking.
Joeljohns249 says, "Agreed, and not just minors."
I don't think even college kids should be allowed to drink.
My mom was so obsessed with her tiny bit of Italian heritage that she really wanted me
to drink wine when I was 10.
Oh yeah, my parents...
She was like, "Come on, you can have a glass of wine at the table."
My parents did that too.
We weren't Italian though.
And I would have it and I'd be like, "This tastes like fucking dog shit."
Yeah, my parents offered me wine one time and I smelled it and I was like, "No!"
I remember my dad being like you want a sip of beer. Yeah, that's we go
My dad tells a story about how like when I was a kid
I like he when I was like a young kid like three or four
He gave me like a sip of his beer
like as a gag and then I went to school the next day and I like sucked on a Lego and I was like this tastes
Just like beer
It's pretty cool number 16 is stop reproducing and there are two really good comments here
First comment is I think it should be illegal to have more than one child because when people have more than one they hardly ever get
Along just because the parents didn't use a condom when they had sex the first child gets stuck with a nosy loud
Destructive and attention-hogging sibling which basically ruins their life in good times. I might you do one child policy. Let's go
Let's do it. Yeah, let's do it. Neither. You guys would be born. Yeah, that's true. Yeah, and that's the point
You should put that on a mean I bet it blew your mind. Yeah. Well, what if I don't even want to be alive man?
Yeah, god damn. I'm cool. That's so cool to say other comment on here
You read Nietzsche for the ones who already had kids you would bring more evil
By the way, if you're saying legendary bands like Slayer and bring me the horizon should be banned
Maybe you should be banned from living you inconsiderate monstrosities
It's funny though because they're brothers
Their brothers. I mostly hate single children when I meet them. Yeah, I like children who are in relationships
No, I think there's like I think I only have like three or four friends who are
Single childs. Yeah, they're just usually bad people, right? It's just it's like if your parents like a barrier
You can't cross. Yeah, it's like you were fully loved. Yeah. Yeah, exactly
Exactly, you were loved the most in your family.
Yeah, it's like you got so fucked.
Like you don't even know how much that fucked you up.
Yeah, oh yeah, yeah.
Like the perfect kid has 50 siblings and all of them were raised by their grandparents.
Yeah.
And they like never saw their parents.
You never had to act out for attention.
Yeah, dude.
What the fuck's wrong with you?
Ehhh.
Yeah.
That's gross to me.
Yeah, you never put glue on the dog to get your dad to say something to you?
Yeah.
Can't relate.
You never shaved like part of your head?
Yeah, eighth grade exactly exactly you don't get it. Yeah
Number 23 demanded grandchildren. Oh, yeah, I hated that in high school
number 24 thrusting their babies in other people's faces
What's that comment weird wording?
Yeah, that's right. Yeah, that's right. That's right
Gimme being anti-vaxxers being it's actually cool. Yeah, that's cool to do
Showing embarrassing baby photos to people without their children's consent
That's right putting them on birthday cakes also counts comment by the dutty gal
the dutty
Duppy gala d u t t y g y a l the dutty gal gut dutty gal
number 36 listening to 13 year olds mm-hmm Wow
Wow. Being slutty. Top comment. No way. That is bad influence for a parent to do that for
a kid. Wait, is this? Yeah, they're saying the parents should stop being slutty. Yeah,
it's things parents need to stop doing. My parents need to stop being slutty. My parents
are such sluts, dude. My fucking mom's always sucking my dad's dick, you fucking whore. Gross.
You bitch. Being ageist. Number 41. Yeah, just because I'm one years old doesn't mean
I shouldn't be able to fucking drive. I should be able to drink number 43 last one allowing small children to run around places
Unattended that is the worst. I was allowed to do that dude. My mom Walmart was like daycare for my parents
Yeah, we show up. She's I mean I just fucking ran to the
Gun section because I know cuz I did it. I know that it's the worst cuz I know what I fucking did
Yeah, dude. I was
Yeah, I was evil. Yeah. Yeah, it's really not about losing the kids. It's like if your kids are cool
they're gonna they're gonna do something real yeah yeah yeah yeah or hide in like
the racks or something yeah oh of course yeah yeah I think from your parents is so
for I saw fucking employee of the month with Dane cook and I have to get build
the toilet paper I have to get to the second level yeah these fucking Costco
racks like I will do anything I will climb over so many artichoke hearts just
to fucking play poker at the top yeah Andy dick with Andy dick oh my god I
I would do anything to hang out with you Andy.
Please go over here Andy Dick.
We wanna hang out with you right now.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
He's here.
Hey.
Oh my god Cameron, Andy Dick's in there.
Oh my god.
Hey.
Hey Andy Dick.
What's up?
How are you doing?
I'm...
Hey.
How did you get here?
I went to the toilet.
You don't sound like that.
He does sound like that.
It's your Griffin McElroy voice.
Yeah.
Okay.
I don't know what he sounds like.
He's generally high.
You made Patrick cry.
Cause he's scared of Andy Dick too.
I was so happy for a moment and then I realized it wasn't Andy Dick it was Caleb.
I'm sorry I can't make all your dreams come true.
Alright, subscribe to the Patreon.