You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(laughing)
- [Announcer] "House of the Hopeless."
- You're a crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
I was thinking of doing a--
- Ooh.
- To start like when you're talking about like
really, really rich people, be like,
oh fuck, I wanna be rich like Carlos Slim or Jeff Bezos
or like Mr. Beast, like one of the millionaires.
- Yeah, what's--
- Really, really--
- Why, who is Mr. Beast
Why does he have all this money? He's me in disguise
That's why I have money that answer make questions. Yeah, it makes sense. What are the richest guys ever?
He basically he's the guy who gives money to homeless people right or like black people cars and stuff. Yeah
Yeah, so what he does is he just goes to the whole off. He finds a homeless person that has a million dollars
And then he just gives it back to them as for the video. True. Oh, yeah
Yeah, or if it's like a sick. Yeah, exactly. Yeah, and that's fucked up
Yeah, and that's and let that be a lesson to all you out there
There are a lot of homeless people walking around that already have a million dollars
And you know they they beg out for I see you store and then they go walk
They're just never satisfied they don't understand that they could buy a house with a million dollars
This is what it is more and more and more grind. Okay, they can't stop grinding. Is that awesome? Yeah, is it confusing? Yeah
that
board you have five million dollars how frugal are these guys they must have
taken Dave Ramsey's fucking course on on economic responsibility yeah I think that
may as baby what happened yeah I think Christmas man I don't care Christmas I
don't care can you let us finish our conversation first let us finish our
Mr. Beast.
Christmas!
Do you think every time Mr. Beast tries to get laid, the girl is like, "Maybe this is
one of the best."
Do you think that...
I gave this poor girl two inches of penis.
Her reaction was awesome.
Do you think Mr. Beast ever gives out candy canes on Christmas?
I don't care about Christmas, dude.
I'm over it.
What?
Yeah.
wait until you just try to interrupt the conversation and like disrupt the flow
which is like i like it has to flow you just try to ruin the episode right now
i'm trying to go but then we won't be able to read
and listen we won't be able to restore friendship to understand that
uh...
as a talk about christmas i don't want to talk about christmas i'm got
i don't i love christmas dude night yeah what are you talking about not fucking
this goth
I
Christmas. I hate Christmas due to my goth nature. You love like someone's
cringing. Whatever. I don't even know who that is. I know so little about
Christmas due to my goth brain. What even was it presents and a fat. He
knows everything about Christmas. No, you know what I like literally just
said all the Christmas stuff. Hold on. Let me light another candle. Uh yeah,
you know, it's tough being goth with all my candles, but uh it should be
is
the
Yeah. No. Oh, fuck. That's not goth. Oh, dude. I'm so goth. I just have to I gotta I gotta
sit around and and listen to to Townes Van Zandt, dude. I'm so goth. God, dude. Goth
people do listen to Townes Van Zandt. Can we just can we just this could this episode
just be like us listening to Leonard Skinner in a goth way? That's not goth. Dude, Curtis
Lowe. He was black. I'm so I'm so I'm so I'm so you're thinking you're thinking around and
I sit around and I watch the Curtis Lowe.
That's the Leonard Skynard song that Curtis Blow is named after, you moron.
No.
He's the finest picker who ever played the blues.
You're thinking of Curtis Blow.
You're thinking of basketball.
I'm not thinking of Curtis Blow.
He's got these things about basketball.
Basketball is the most goth sport.
And the breaks.
What is the most goth sport?
for
I don't think it's BMX. What the hell are you talking about? It's BMX. Why would no have you seen a goth riding a bike? Yes
No, I saw it all my childhood goth sport as you stand at the skate park
Yeah, true smoking cigarettes and you look at the bike. The goth sport is smoking cigarettes
Yeah, just sitting around smoking cigarettes listening to fucking Linkin Park. I'm God
No, you don't listen to Linkin Park if you're God I have black
Who's it? I'm so goth. I'm listening to all the sad songs from frozen and frozen - that's not you guys
I mean, I'm gonna about - I'm about to freaking I'm gonna about to do but here I'm
I'm a goth guy about to lose it here. Do you guys want to watch my goth cut of up?
Yeah, it's just the first four minutes. Oh my god. Yeah, you know, that would be guff
Yeah, you guys wanna watch my goth cut of Toy Story 3. It's just that it's just that - hey
Do you guys do you guys want to eat my goth cookie too bad? I eat it it
Yeah, no, that's emo. No, I'm emo -
I'm goths have been persecuted for too long. We can't I'm goth emo. I'm get mo you can't
No, yeah, we can't we can't let goths continue to ruin this episode this whole time
I'm not trying to rule first
God first he tries to interrupt us talking about mr. Beast to talk about Christmas
Then when we want to talk about gods, he's going no, that's emo. No, that's frozen. No, that's no
That's a BMX bike and I'm sitting here saying who's the one who's wearing a shirt that says murder death on a black shirt
Okay, Pat. Yeah, I think I would know a little something about being going to shirt
This is FedEx and I delivered it to your house
I'm wearing a shirt with a C on it and it stands for kill myself
Become recently so who's got now
now. I don't know dude. Hey guess what color of coffee I'm drinking. That's right, black
and white. Cream. Black and white. Yeah like a goth would wear. With stuff in it. You're
drinking cream. Hey, sometimes it feels like me and Cam are the goth ones and you're more
of a hoth one. That's right, because you're cold to us. Because I'm so icy. Because you're
so damn icy to us. Which we like because we're goth. I just like shit like that. I like when
people are mean to me.
Patrick's like Hoth because he's got a wampa in him.
He's got a monster.
You guys are punk goes crunk and that's why I'm so icy.
You're a punk who eats junk.
That's right.
I'm...
I gotta wake up.
Calm down beginning of courage the cowardly dog.
Come on guys.
We're on fire today for Christmas.
Welcome to the Christmas episode special.
the
white bitch you're white you goth bitch you are so white from being goth
today you have corpse paint on anniversary of the show you're like a porcelain doll
you're like you're like a little can't play with you too fragile and white you look like robert
smith yep so i'm goth damn it he's too goth for us he is he keeps owning us with his kind of bad
attitude
yeah he keeps flipping his bangs out of his face
say you like smiles
hey have you guys ever seen
say it
say i like smiles
they make me happy
smiles just truly depress me in the way that's
what if the devil was smiling
he would
in a sly manner
wait wait
i'm not sly
in a sly
you can't listen if i said i was sly then you guys would
you'd know i was a genius not a goth
of
They buy corn syrup and red food coloring.
Uh-huh.
The supermarket.
You guys ever, you guys, you know how goth I am?
You know what my favorite movie is?
Edward Scissorman's.
Whoa!
He'd like a scissorman's hands.
Yeah.
Yeah, 'cause I'm goth.
You put your hands like, you put the Vulcan hands,
you put your hands together and do Vulcan hands
and another man comes and does it too
and then you look in and you see it,
you guys make a vagina together.
Yeah.
Yeah, 'cause I'm goth.
That is pretty fucking goth, making a vagina.
Yeah
Yeah, well, I don't know it's just hard for me this time of year because of my goth
My goth vibes and my goth history. We've already we've already been over this. I think
No, I think I'm the goth one actually. Okay. What's your favorite part of being goth being dead?
evil
Yeah, yeah
Death and mine is being tortured every day by the prison. That is my life and
Which I seem to be serving a life sentence. Yeah, I actually I like to eat poop
Yeah, I don't think I'm tons of nasty crap. I think I was goth now. I
think I'm just a I
Think I'm too hyphy for this
Dude to be gone when I when I see a cute animal I scream in terror when I see a scary spider I pet it
Yeah, see see I'm about me I'm about being hyphy and being from the Bay Area
You're not from the Bay Area. Not e40
Say you're a 40 dude. Stop going as I think I'm
The way it the way that now the way this episode is a thing is about instead of e40 soon
We're pretty soon. We're gonna be looking at d25. Mm-hmm Wow
Oh, December.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's right.
That's Christmas.
I thought it was the 25 year anniversary of Disney.
It's kind of the 25 year anniversary of the podcast today.
It's true.
It's tomorrow.
Tomorrow.
What do you mean?
Why do you keep saying that?
Because it's tomorrow.
I thought you were goth.
Do you mean tomorrow?
You're obsessed with rules and time.
Yeah.
Do you mean tomorrow when the episode comes out?
No, I mean the day after this episode comes out.
A goth is so depressed with music that he doesn't even know what day it is.
Okay.
Wait.
The anniversary of the podcast is Christmas Eve.
Christmas Eve.
Okay, you could have just said that.
Well, I told you that so many times.
I truly don't remember at all.
I think we must have.
Originally, it was supposed to be a Christmas podcast.
We must have been like, "It would be funny if we released this on Christmas Eve."
That must have been the thought process, because I don't know why else we would do that.
Yeah, that was a horrible move.
People were so busy opening gifts, they couldn't listen.
Yeah, that's true.
It made it very hard for us.
for us. We got pigeonholed as a Christmas podcast for the first year and a half.
Yeah, people kept listening. It's like they didn't even talk about the naughty or nice list.
Yeah, speaking of that's what I thought.
Are you guys drafting? Yeah.
Nice list, Patrick. Naughty list, Caleb. That's my first picks. That's what I want to be because
I'm... well you guys know by now. All right, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry. Nice list, Patrick.
Stupid list Caleb stupid is the same as naughty to me because of how good you're stupid. No
I'm on the often stupid. I'm on the nice list cuz I'm so hyphy. I'm so good with it
You're not guys give some stop arguing about who's goth and who's not and just start just a long pipe adding to your life
II he's like e4 like oh
Do the list say it naughty and nice?
naughty is
Fuck
Naughty has to be from this year. The terrifier is definitely
Big facts, no cap detected. Yeah, and the nice list I'm gonna give it to you know
President Donald Trump. He's been pretty nice this year, you know, he hasn't done too much
I mean, I not really not really but it's his last year kind of a courtesy pick
Yeah
I mean, you know, you can't go if he got went four years in a row getting naughty list that he would just be devastated
You don't even I think you you can't get back on the nice list after four years in a row of naughty
So I think I think it switched off every year. I think around Christmas time every year
He did do something to get himself back on the nice list
He pardoned a turkey and that was oh
Yeah, do that ever. You know what he does that he did that every year for four years
It's kind of a Thanksgiving. Oh, it's out of a Christmas thing, but so it
Yeah, all right, so mine I have three lists so obviously
nice list
I'm gonna put Parson Brown on there. Mm-hmm. Nice. I mean, I mean just you got to give it up for this guy
Yeah, what is nice this year? I mean like I haven't heard about that guy since I don't know
well, I mean
He can do the job when he's in town
What job is that?
Pretty much any job, you know, he's one of the he's really greatest guy last can see fisherman
Yeah, he I mean he can do the job when he's in town
Any job any job person we got to get this cat on task rabbit. Uh-huh. Oh my god
Are you kidding me probably five bucks an hour?
Amazing on test grab. He's one of the biggest celebrities of all time - he's like really yeah, he's got that staying power
the
up
on
he said and one of his and one of his debate I mean hey your misogyny showing Bernie Sanders I mean
yeah it's out of your zipper you lady liberty you're saying lady liberty is a big green
monster who won't you want to she wants you to step but you want her to step on your balls
did he say that he said that when was that he said he wants the statue of liberty to do cbt to him
really uh...
he's not and not cognitive behavioral therapy
so piece that together in your mind crushing balls kit tiny lee nine oh
uh... what happened
well bad things
yet exactly
what how uh... i don't know that about him well it's lost my vote in the next
minute when he's me too
i'm here so i'm gonna i'm gonna be voting for him for not even the next
so
I didn't invent this list. E40 you can't put yourself on the list.
No, I did not invent the list.
It was E40 and Andre Nicotina and they put me on the Most Hyphy list.
Ok, let's see proof.
And Mac Dre did too.
Alright, let's see proof.
Is Pat on the list? Nope.
Is he fat like a fist? Yep.
List.
Hey, I'll go ahead and search that too.
a
is
It says the number one most high fee it says that I'm after Mac Dre. Yeah, and then Mac Dre is
999 no
Not true. No
That's a different Mac Dre this Mac Dre was a caveman no, this is a guy named Mac Dre. Yeah
Yeah, no, I think I think I'm not from the bay. I think I think okay, then send the right link
you
now that i mean it looked like you go to our kind of work a quick look at it over
then
okay let me uh... crap
so here it's not our kind of organ says patrick is the mc is the most creepy
now it doesn't know that it says on the most as you act the most weird towards
people
it's a little bit about what would they put that on the high-flying i think i
think they mean i think it says you have the most it says you have the most
problems patrick what does that even mean give a little less than two i think
what does it mean the most problems is that i don't like a mental issues that
you have is a counter to a lot of obstacles arm
my problem is on most i_d_ and i have too much money
and swag patrick it's as you've been acting up on here
yet then acting up in the club
now doesn't say in the club
yet as you've been acting out you back to nothing your grandma's house
that's the closest here that your grandma made you sit in the corner chair
it is you know maybe you put it
it's a good idea to have a great backwards i was being too high fee
so that's what i think that's your use there is because you're acting weird
there is a i mean you failed your height the test is that yes i think that's
right here
it does right here you feel your testimony of a teacher comment that says
that boy and right and then it says they sent you back to kindergarten yet so
that boy it says that way too hot right now
no doesn't say that's why i mean you can't you can't trust that teacher
to
know
the
no
I'm really, congratulations though for winning guy who pooped in the urinal and lied about it.
Yeah, that's a huge award for you.
It sucks.
For you winning any award is huge.
I'm logging off the call.
You can't log off, you don't know how to read and press the buttons.
I'm pressing alt Q.
You can't even read your keyboard, man.
I'm gonna go ahead and click out of it.
Yeah, go ahead, read your keyboard.
QWERTY.
You just do that from...
That's not even a word.
UIOP.
Asdif.
Dude, you're just saying nonsense right now.
Shut up, dude.
You're talking, you're cursing in here now.
Zyxstriorquembrm.
quorum berm
are you okay
is everything okay at home
dots of my house to i_t_
now
that can remember every family member except you
now that's true
that's right my mom is the forty and my dad is mcdray in my brother is under
nikitina
no your brother's too short
well guys i know that's my cousin
the podcast account is going to be no i have really big news
what our podcast station is live on verbal
well
who are b_l_
well i i i
that's pretty good sick dude
dan actually i don't like actually don't care
i care
i don't care
because of
my disposition
yet disposition of good for you disposition that i'm
on
a food-centered naughty nice list. I'm just I'm just thinking. Nice list, Anthony Pelosi
or whatever her name is from TV for giving us so much money. That's enough to buy ten
games. Naughty list has to be the man made out of piss I had a dream about last night.
Yeah, and it kept dripping on me and he'd say, "Hey, you got piss on ya!"
And I'd be like, "Dude, it's from you, man."
But then I woke up and I was like, "I'm just gonna be goth instead of think about what this means."
My nice list, uh, gonna put Israel on there.
Yep.
Get you that money. We gotta get you that stimmy check, Israel.
We gotta get you that money.
I don't like how many times you're saying "get you."
What?
it
I don't know man. No, it's just my New Hampshire accent. It's winking so much. It's my New Hampshire accent
I say oh you can't hold up that symbol in a zoom call
You're gonna get banned from zoom by me accent is when you slur all your speech
And yeah, it's also when you speak all your slurs dude, mm-hmm, that's right
a
for
Oh, that kid got a rock.
[laughter]
It's Charlie Brown.
Yeah.
Yeah, Charlie Brown is Palestinian.
Yeah, Charlie Brown got a rock and he's throwing it at a tank.
No.
That's not true.
Yeah, it is true.
That is true, actually.
Yeah, you know, maybe it is.
That's the new tick to make after you make a stupid joke and just go, "Yeah, that's true."
That is true.
Yeah, you know what, that's right.
Yeah, that's right.
No, yeah, of course that happened.
Alright, in honor of ourselves.
We love to honor ourselves so much.
So we're honoring ourselves by doing our, is this our first ever list?
Yeah, so this is our first ever list that we did.
This was like our trial.
This is when we record, before we even like put, this episode was never posted.
the
I
they have this whole website archived so we can come back to this whenever we
could we did a bunch of these already we have to remember which ones we did yeah
but it doesn't matter because they probably don't exist anyway but yeah
this list is a top 10 monstrous people that are not human being
I'm being hit by so many amazing memories right now.
Yeah dude.
Nostalgia.
I don't remember fucking any of this.
That's because you were not around dude.
Yeah Pat can you leave for the second half of this episode?
I think we knew each other at this point.
Shut up scumbag.
I did not know Patrick at this point.
What are you talking about?
We were friends on Facebook.
That doesn't mean anything.
I'm friends with like 4000 people on Facebook.
Yeah but we used to... I'm just saying I don't know Patrick, I didn't know Patrick.
I never met... We used to do a... oh yeah, probably never met you but we would go into Ascension, Fifth Dimension and stuff.
I met Patrick. We would play together. We would play on Facebook with each other.
I met Patrick and I didn't remember that I met him for a long time.
But I had met him one time here because he was so kind of forgettable and bland and just lacked kind of any impression to be made on.
He was dressed in a button-down shirt and khakis and he went "Hey guys" and he was wearing
big glasses and his hair was slicked back and he had a pocket protector.
Yeah, I was wearing a mask before all this covid crap.
He's dressed like an uncle.
He's dressed like Steve Uncle.
I kept walking around like "Can I do that?"
Can I do this?
Can I do that?
Shut the fuck up bro.
Just fucking up to people.
Can I do that?
That's Urkel with social anxiety.
I'd like to see Urkel throw it in a circle.
I'm just saying Urkel, just going up to people like, people just like having a picnic in the
park and just going, "Can I do that?"
No Urkel, get away from me.
Leave me alone.
Stop it Urkel.
Get out of here white Urkel.
Get the fuck out of here.
i'm at a picnic
uh...
number one most monstrous people are not human being number ten most monstrous
people are not human being
yokozuna
she's a super wrestler
we gotta read the the things but because these are very good descriptions
yokozuna was a simone american professor at professional wrestler
We gotta read this thing.
(unintelligible)
You read it then.
Uh, Yokozuna.
He was best known for his time with the World Wrestling Federation.
The term Yokozuna refers to the highest rank
of professional sumo wrestling in Japan.
Um, blah blah blah.
Standing at 6'4" and weighing an immense
589 pounds, the Yokozuna squashed
legends like Bret Hart, The Undertaker, and Hulk Hogan
on his way to becoming one of the most dominant
WWE champions of all time.
October 23rd, 2000, Yokozuna died from pulmonary edema, I don't know.
Funky cold, Medina.
In his room in England while on an independent wrestling tour in Europe.
Being very, this is the last line, being very tall and absolutely massive at nearly 600
pounds, there is no way Yokozuna was human, just like the rest of his family.
Yeah that's my reaction anytime I see anybody kind of big.
Yeah, you and your family are not human.
First off, you're not human.
Second off, your sisters cannot be human either.
Your mom and dad are not human.
You're an alien.
You're just an alien.
Dude, Roman Reigns and The Rock were his cousins, it says here.
I can't believe I skipped that.
Whoa.
What?
Roman Reigns, Rikishi, Umaga, and The Rock.
That's what it says.
He was a member of the Anoa'i wrestling family.
Roman Reigns, Rikishi, Umaga, and The Rock were just some of his cousins.
Damn, I'd hate to see some of his other cousins.
I know.
Damn.
the
this
to
from the same pineapple and their Samoan cousins.
Yeah.
You know?
Number nine, Sun Ming Ming.
Sun Ming Ming is a Chinese basketball player.
He currently stands at 7'9" and weighs 370 pounds.
That's a big motherfucker.
Yeah.
Goddamn.
Wears size 20 shoes, makes occasional appearances as an actor.
Dude, maybe we can get him for our movie.
Holy shit.
Oh my god, that's such a big--
In the summer of 2005, Sun discovered that he had a brain tumor attached to his pituitary
gland.
Because he had neither medical or neither health insurance nor enough money to pay for more
than $100,000 in medical bills, his sports agent, Charles Bonseigneur, started...
Charles, Charles Bonseigneur.
Wait, he was a basketball player and he didn't have health insurance?
sports agent who only represents giant Chinese guys. No you have to, the giant Chinese man
is my... You are the biggest Chinese man I ever seen. You are the biggest Chinese man
I ever seen. You've been an amazing addition to my life. You are not a human being. You
are a giant Chinese man. You are a monstrous people, cannot be human being. You are a huge
Chinese evil man, let me let me introduce you to my to my friend here this statue liberty
You are a Chinese dragon to me
The tumor was successfully removed dude, yeah
On March 11th son
2007 son was part of the tallest lineup in the world on the Maryland Nighthawks with four players over seven feet tall
So I never made it to the NBA
But if he did he would have been the tallest person in the NBA's history although. He does not look like a monster
He is a limitless one and frightens every person that stands in his path
Without disbelief it is safe to say he is not a human being at nearly 8 foot in a 400 pounds
Jesus Christ
You are a limitless monster
You are like Bradley Cooper
You are a limitless person
You are disgusting to me
You are a lumpy old leg of the snake!
You are a dead yucky insect!
You are a disgusting monster!
You smell horrible!
Come here, let me smell!
You smell so bad!
You are a gross monster!
You are a naughty monster!
You are a disgusting monster!
Let me drink your bones like a deer drinking from his water bottle!
I love you so much!
You are my new son!
You are my big Chinese monster son!
I love you like a my grandson. I am going to give you a brain to me
You are being my granddaughter
Valley's oh you have it. We have a guest room you can stay in but he's not this ceiling is only six feet tall
What ceiling
You're in the shower
I've got to get you to take up the main say it. Yeah
You look like a beast that rose out of Davy Jones lucker. I need to use you as an anchor
You're not allowed to flush in my house
I have to clone you. I'm a pirate, but I must know a scientist
Clone you in the name of research
large hadron collider. I sail the seven seas of the large hadron collider.
All right number eight big show. He he looks human he can't be a monster.
I was gonna read hey okay go ahead I thought you weren't because you just started talking.
Galleying which I didn't like much. Yeah read it if you're gonna read it. He is a feared competitor
who intimidates opponents with his size and stare alone. Just like Andre the Giant, he used to have
a Cro-Megili. What's that? A Cro-Megili, a disease of the endocrine system. On his 12th birthday,
he was 6'2" and weighed 220 pounds and had chest hair. Currently, he stands at an unbelievable
7 feet tall, weighs a massive 450 pounds, wears a huge 18 US size shoe, and has an incredible
64 inch chest. I bet his aunts were so weird to him. Oh, yeah. Oh my god run their fingers to his chest here
Yeah, yeah, you're so big for your age. Oh, you're gonna be a basketball or linebacker
You're gonna be a giant fat inhuman monster, oh you're gonna be so gross. Oh, you're gonna be disgusting. Oh
I'm gonna hate looking at you when you walk down the street. I'm gonna chase you with an angry mob.
On your 21st birthday, I'm gonna walk in and I'm gonna vomit.
Oh, I'm gonna chase you with pitchforks and torches when I see you.
I'm gonna run you back to your swamp.
You could be a member of the Dark Carnival if you wanted, honey.
[Laughter]
Oh, oh honey, this way comes!
Honey, who was our friend? Who was our friend? PT Barnum? PT Barnum, yeah, we can introduce you to him.
Who was that friend? Who was that friend? Who was that sorcerer who was looking for a brutal giant servant to
smack together the heads of his opponents?
Uh, Magnifico the evil.
Oh, Magnifico. Yeah, it was- I'll put you in contact with him.
Oh, Big Show, you have to meet Magnifico.
He doesn't have a cell phone. He's one of those. Just talk into the shell at midnight.
That's why you- well, listen, Big Show, when you meet Magnifico, just walk hunched over, okay? He'll like you more that way.
Honey, did you bring the orb? Did you bring the orb, honey?
*laughter*
Okay, we're gonna look at the most amazing orb.
Well, go look in the fucking car! It might be in the fucking car!
*laughter*
Honey, I know I brought the orb. I know, I know. Check the fucking trunk, honey!
Oh my god, it's in my pocket. I feel like an idiot.
*laughter*
Well, you have to-
Oh, it's like a one-foot-in-diameter orb.
*laughter*
To call Magnifico, just read a Bible verse backwards.
It'll pick up really fast.
Just say Mecca Mecca like a high Mecca. Honey, honey. Ho just like peewee just like me play house like you're talking to John B
Who dares to disturb me in my flow my study Oh
Some woman in half someday you're a real charmer Oh
Magnifico, how are the kids?
They're great. They're great. Oh, oh
I mean one of them getting real evil over here. Oh, yes. He is he still going to evil high school
Yeah, he goes to evil. He's about to go to evil University. Oh
My god
One second, I'll put him on the phone
Sorry looks like he's busy he's scheming right, you know, you know kids are oh
He's gorgeous. He's gorgeous. Oh my god. He must be beaten up the evil
Big show you and you and him should be friends Magnifico jr. You would love him. You know my youngest raid in the Magnifico
My youngest he's 12 he's going through one of these phases he's keep saying he wants to be good when he grows up
Oh, they grow out of it. Don't worry. I mean I
out of it
Devil will is I mean just the other day you forged this this glowing golden blade and he was trying to slay me with it
What oh my god cut me an arm. Is he making crucifixes because I would love that
I would love a new one to hang up at my home
Just an Irish Catholic who's friends with all these deep
Last the last line of Big Show is Big Show is not a human being but rather a vicious beast
We just skipped over it. Yeah, he I guess he flipped a Jeep
In 20 or yeah 2005 he flipped a Jeep over and that's number seven is the great Kali
The guy is an Indian professional wrestler actor and powerlifter. Although his parents are well in range of normal height
His grandfather was over six foot six the great Kali also has acromegaly that causes facial distortion
deformities, distortions. As you can tell by his large brow, nose, chin, and ears. At 42 years old, he stands at a crazy 7'1" and weighs 347 pounds. It is not clear what shoe size he wears, but in Big Boss Season 4, he had worn an enormous US-sized 22 shoe.
It's pretty fucking clear!
In 2001, he even accidentally killed a guy!
Brian Ong, for giving him a flapjack, a professional wrestling throw!
In 2012, he underwent a brain surgery due to a tumor on his pituitary gland that prevented him from being able to stop growing.
I'm seeing a pattern here.
As one of the biggest WWE superstars of all time, the Great Khali is definitely not human, but rather a giant savage!
He's in... yeah, he's the guy in the longest yard.
Yeah, it's the only movie I know him from I don't know him from wrestling or anything
I know him from the Adam Sandler jail comedy on this list. I don't know. Yeah, I think so, too
I don't I'm looking up what he looks like right now. Oh
Tumor on my fucking. Oh, yeah, dude
Glen do you think there's like if you put your head in a microwave for a lot like maybe like
Rig the microwave so that it opens the door stays open you put your head in there
Where's your pituitary gland dude if I could raise the microwave for the door to stay open while it ran
and that would be like the best day of my life.
I could just watch, like I could just watch my food get warm.
- True.
- I guess that would--
- I guess that would get my face
one inch away from the microwave.
- No, that would fuck with your wifi, don't do that.
- The wifi in your head?
- Oh no, no, yeah, not my wifi.
That's the main issue.
- Yeah, it would fuck with your wifi
and your neighbor's wifi.
- Good. - Yeah.
- And it would fuck with your wife's eyes,
who she'd have to look at you.
- If my neighbors don't have wifi,
they're gonna have to make more Chinese food
'cause they can't go online.
I'm gonna be bored.
I got to go to get to go smell that that's a win for cam.
Yeah, they're Chinese though, right?
I don't know.
They just make Chinese food all the time.
Yeah, Chinese Cameron lives next to a Chinese restaurant.
We are forgetting my neighbors make the most delicious food.
Number six Emmanuel Emmanuel Emmanuel Yarborough.
Yep.
It's a manual manual Yarborough's in America.
American
I have a goth depression nap coming on. Yeah
American amateur sumo wrestler you could do it. No
Martial arts competitor also having competed in judo wrestling and American football for more two decades
he's taking on challenges and most with mid-day impossible and
Consistently proven that he has a focus and determination to master any endeavor. We should be doing this in YouTube voice
Yeah
Which one I was doing the chills one
And at one time more than an insane 700 pounds
Emmanuel is in the Guinness Book of World Records as the largest professional athlete in the world
He wears a size 21 shoe. He was the
1995 world amateur sumo champion and is considered to be one of the most famous sumo wrestlers outside Japan
Three times the size of the average person and ridiculously tall this sumo wrestler has no proof. He is a human being
Dude that's what's next did you're not sir walking around carrying that's what the real
Destination cards do yeah, I have a card that turns you on a dog in one of yeah fucking bug cat
You're gonna have to walk around like Bolsonaro said you're gonna have to fucking show proof to your human anymore. Yeah
Oh my god, look at this that yeah, there's no way this next guy's human look at him in this picture
He's covered in hair like a beast. Yeah
Jesus and he's so tall. Yeah
Number five is Jorge Gonzalez
Jorge Gonzalez was an Argentine basketball player and professional wrestler
He was best known for his appearances in World Championship wrestling under the ring name El Gigante
Now that's a good game, dude. It's scary
Let's see. No superstar in sports entertainment history was as immense as giant Gonzalez
Thought his name was giant instead of four
Not big show not even the legendary Andre the giant he stood at a great seven foot six great height weighed
460 pounds and he played the role of Manny a carnival sideshow giant in a
1993 episode of Baywatch who befriends Hobie but later falls into the water and his large size makes it difficult to be rescued Wow
That's so tragic. Oh wow
I hate I befriend to Hobie but
And I'm too large to be rescued
That's you
Hoby is Pamela Anderson's name. No. Yeah, she's Hobie. No
Hoby is the goblin who lives underneath the dock at the beach. Oh, Hoby was a child on that show
and
And his name is Hobie.
What's up, I'm Hobie.
You wanna go play hoop and stick?
Ah, it's me, Hobie Buchanan.
I'm here.
Let's go play stickball in the alley.
I like this, uh, I like this last part.
On September 22, 2010, Jorge Gonzalez died due to complications of diabetes and severe
heart issues.
His hometown of San Martin, Argentina.
He was just 44 years old.
his lifetime he could not have been human but most likely a giant animal.
Now that you're dead, you weren't even a person.
You were just an animal to me.
You were in your graves.
I'm glad you died like a fucking dog that you are.
You look like shit, you were too big.
You kept getting- Hobie kept having to rescue your bum ass from the ocean but you were too
damn big.
Fuck you.
Rest in piss.
He must have had to go pretty far out in the ocean to be able to not stand up.
be able to reach him. Yeah. Yeah. With Hobies with Hobies tractor beam that he invented in
season five episode twenty two. Exactly. Maybe that's what put the pituitary. The tractor
beam you guys remember that episode when Hobie became a scientist. Yeah. It'll be Hobie Buchanan
Harvested alien technology from from Pamela Anderson's thingies.
Hobie put a black hole on the beach again.
We gotta fucking stuff it with your big ass hole.
There goes Giant Gonzalez.
He fell into the black hole and he's too big to be rescued.
I guess we shouldn't even bother. He's probably too big to be rescued.
He's too much like a giant animal to be rescued.
I hope that episode he like he drowned like three feet of water.
Yeah he fell like a kiddie pool.
You know what he's already dead.
He's too fucking tall for this.
That guy you know now that he's in the water I just have to say I've always thought that guy might be a giant animal.
Hobie what did I tell you about making friends with extremely huge non-humans?
You bastard.
Number four Andre the Giant. We all know this guy.
this
you
to
a total of store for husky boys
it's just casual mail excel toilets
there are toilets that
there are toilets that have like suction in a way that it sucks all your fat down
so it doesn't look like you're fat when you're sitting on it
it's like a slimming toilet
it's like that thing in the simpsons where kent brockman has like the clips on his neck
yeah yeah yeah
he weighed 520 pounds I don't think we did we talk about this how he was like
not as big as they say was
yeah but then we said that he was big
now he's already do a list of tall people
he's like five-file you're talking about under the giant he comes up a lot in my
conversations
that's true yeah yes the guy that I'm mode similar where it's cuz you were so
much obey
yeah that's true yeah your your
of hypebeast filipino kid in 2013.
that's facts.
yeah.
so let's just skip andre we don't need to talk he's also not very christmassy.
well i mean i need to read the last line though.
eventually his heart- his size was just too much for his heart and he died in paris in
his hotel room on january 27th 1993.
there is no way this guy was human but rather a behemoth.
i love every like sentence that's like "ah tragically he passed away."
this fucking free
it's a beast
if i was going to go out with this guy i'd kill him
we're just going through the
thesaurus results for monster
and just saying a new one at the end
number three
go ahead
no you go ahead pronounce that name
number three, cameron fetter
thank you
hey thank you
weighing in at a whopping one billion gajillion pounds
and height of infinity. Number three,
Vaino...
in
seven foot three and weighed 434 pounds at the age of 21,
but experienced a second phase of growth in his late 30s,
attaining a height of a giant eight foot three.
He is considered the tallest soldier ever,
having served in the Finnish defense forces.
That's pretty sick, dude.
- That would suck getting another growth spurt at like 30.
- That would really suck.
- If you're already that tall, I mean for me,
but like if you're a giant and then just being like,
ah, I can't stop fucking growing.
- Imagine being a drill sergeant
and
Also you get deflected with his metal teeth.
Yeah.
He returned to Finland in 1939 to serve in the Finnish Army during the Winter War.
In 1946, he moved to Jarvenpaa and ran a chicken farm.
That's nice dude.
Yeah, that sounds like a good life.
He died in 1963 and is buried there.
He's buried in 1963?
We have to go back and get him back.
He had a 15.7 inch hand span, the greatest known.
As tall, heavy, and strong as he was, it is nearly impossible to call this guy human.
This guy's in the army and his hand's that big.
He doesn't hold any guns.
Bazooka.
He holds a cake and fires it like a gun.
Yeah, he probably, you're right.
I do feel like this list was written by Van Helsing.
And at the end, everyone is like, "And another monster put in the dirt where he belongs."
list is what's in the folders that Mulder and Scully are always flipping through the
X-Files.
Yeah, ever heard of Giant Gonzalez?
Scully, he was friends with Hobie and then he fell into water.
I don't believe in Giant Gonzalez.
I don't believe in vicious beasts.
John Rogan.
Joe Rogan?
Yeah, sure, on opposite day, Joe Rogan would be the biggest guy.
I don't know.
How--
Joe Rogan is really small, right?
Yeah, he's--
No, no, no, no, no.
He's like three foot--
Three.
Yeah, he's like a foot and a half tall.
He's kind of like a gnome.
That's why I moved to Austin, because it's a small city.
Gnome Rogan.
Gnome Gnoman.
Yeah, Gnome Rogan's there.
He has a funny little hat.
Jamie, Jamie.
Hey, Jamie.
Pull up that--
Jamie, pull up that toadstool.
I'm going to sit down.
Pull up that Keebler recipe, Jamie.
Jamie, pull up those cookies and some milk.
the
in our tribe and her name's Smurfette.
Yeah.
See, see, no men would know.
When young men, we need to know.
You only should be eating pixie dust, okay?
You need to clean the front yard that you sit in all day.
You need to make sure it's cleaned up.
You need to sweep the pine needles away from your toadstool, okay?
That's-
You need to make sure your toadstool-
The only way you can have an ordered mind.
All right, bucko, you need to make sure your toadstool is clean every day.
Get up and clean your toadstool, bucko.
You want to be casting at least one spell a day, okay?
Now, lobsters are particularly scary because for us they're bigger than...
Kind of a monster-sized creature.
Kind of monsters to us, and I think that these monsters are...
We need to boil them, we need to boil the ocean.
ocean
and all of the
and peterson
that's right
yet
pretty much okay and i was one of seventeen of people medical history to
reach a height of a feeder more also the second allspurs never recorded after
robert wadlow great spoiler
fox spoiler for our loser
by eighteen ninety nine he'd go into a height of eight foot six despite his
exist success in this regard success
and so she says it is a really great it would say
he declined all offers to join the carnival inside shows john rogan's hands
measured eleven inches in length as feet measured thirteen inches in length
you could need to grow until his death which was in nineteen oh five at the age
of just forty
the twist with john rogan was that in the nearly nine feet tall he was only one
hundred and seventy five pounds
he was extremely skinny but ludicrously tall
john was a gargantuan historic figure and in no way at all human
uh...
that last line always gets me
i just love that he's literally not human
he is such a freak
i hate this guy
if i saw him i would throw things at him
he does look pretty fucking cute no cap
i wouldn't throw things at a tall person you could throw one thing at that guy
he'd fall over. You know what, that is true. It'd have to be pretty damn heavy if you just
like hit. The thing is, yeah, he'd probably be really good at basketball, but if you fucking
crossed over on him, he'd just break both his legs immediately. Right, well that's the
problem with tall basketball players. There's a lot of 7'6" guys in Europe who just can't
play in the NBA because they just get owned. Right. Dude, Allen Iverson was like 5'5".
I
the
Is where we big and so he looks pretty small what I thought I thought Alan Iverson was small
He he's small for the NBA, but he was taller everybody everybody
I know everybody I know is like Oh Alan Iverson was like pretty short for a bet. What the fuck? Yeah
They're all like seven tall
Six foot six. He's a fucking liar. Nobody lied to you. Everybody lied to me and everyone betrayed me
Nobody betrayed you. Stop stealing the goth thing from me. I'm the betrayed one and you've been mean to me my whole life.
I got betrayed. I got betrayed by somebody who told me Allen Iverson was 5'7".
I got betrayed by God for letting me be born.
Somebody told me Allen Iverson was 5'7", dude.
Yeah, the liar.
5'5", 5'7".
The town liar.
Yeah.
I'm gonna, I gotta go.
No, you don't have to go.
I gotta go.
No, you have to do the last one, Robert Wadlow.
Inhuman beast that we have to talk about. Well now i'm looking at the shortest basketball players
I know
Oh, it's spud web is five web and mugsy bogues. You mixed up fucking spud web with alan iverson, dude
Alan iverson's like one of the greatest fucking two guards ever. No, I don't know. I don't know
I don't know who told me alan iverson is your brain dude, but whoever fucking told me you switched it to five seven
You said five five five whoever told me alan iverson's five five i'm i you know what?
Maybe they were talking about white iverson
Oh, they might have been talking about
That's a really good point. Let's see how tall that's post malone, right? Let's see how tall he is
I think he's probably six feet as well
uh
Yeah, he's six feet tall
What the fuck?
is not a single iverson oh here it is your thing of will lose you've heard
he's five four
okay and the people also search for
that's gotta be it
you think of that iverson
yeah robert wadlow is the tallest person in recorded history for whom there is
irrefutable evidence
he reached an earth-shattering eight foot eleven and wait a whopping four
hundred thirty nine pounds at the age of his death
at weight at the at his death at age twenty two on july fifteenth nineteen
forty
his great size and continued growth in adulthood were due to hyperplasia of his
pituitary gland
which results in an abnormally high level of h_g_h_
he showed no indication of an end up to his growth even at the time of his death
his family claim that robert was taller than his father at age eight
true yes they had to get an expanding casket he just keeps growing and growing
He's like 20 feet tall now.
Yeah.
They had to make a special desk for him due to his size.
After graduating from Alton High School in 1936,
he enrolled at Shirtless College.
Shirtless College, dude.
Yeah.
Signed me up.
Hey, they didn't have shirts big enough for him.
I'm going to take 16 credits at Shirtless College.
And it's going to go ahead.
I'm taking shirtless math, shirtless science,
shirtless English.
The intention of studying law.
By the time he had graduated from high school, he was 8 foot 4.
thirty said that
robert wild low size began to take its toll you required leg braces to walk in
a little feeling in his legs and feet
uh... despite these difficulties
while they never used a wheelchair
according to the guinness world records
he was a u_s_ size thirty
seven shoe
a u_k_ thirty six and a european size thirty one
it's incredible height and weight
yet the is what was the biggest three feet tall yet the difference is that
this is a you know
roberts incredible height weight proves that he could not have possibly be
possibly been a human
but more like a walking empire state
that's good
carabinier on the street scenario we asked people who did so i are state
building is in their own rubber like ninety-four
yet uh... one trillion miles and he looks at the cameras
all
when it's up to be robert wadlow's height and still have to select it and i do
you know because you got to go to shirtless college and you have a
specialist law and decide whether or not a restructured circuit
uh...
but i don't know how to do you think that will be a
yet
i mean
it'd be in robert wadlow's height and just having like and normal penis
well nobody's ever gonna believe you this normal
strew
you know you would you it
imagine that
you'd okay you get a growth in your pituitary gland swag
you to get the start growing but you can assert shrinking
opposite swag
what is that that class
class
that's class it's class 'cause you got to homework
the idea of a little how to jail now
for a bit but you have such a powerful big and your dad's true joking is on the
on a whole nother
planet did not where you're from did you not only in it joke
clinics
that's right it discovered it
so far away in the telescope
planet jill
uh...
the
it puts that puts it for good
planet rock mars africa been by the soul and iraq yep
distinctly have to be a part of some company jill
and you know she got out about the joke planet
i've got a lot more trust me
metrics been in contact with the jelly beans for years and that's true they're
part of the federation it's been teaching me
can you tell you how to have the one the one planet that everyone in the galactic
federation hates me like oh we can't did nobody takes us seriously because there
are these fucking joking's that just walk around talking on their dicks my penis is
getting longer yeah it's really scary cuz one day they're gonna have penises so
long that they hit other planets yeah when they turn around yeah yeah that's
that's pretty fucked up
all right
okay christmas there have been a year
we got an exciting episode coming out tomorrow
you up
it's this episode played in reverse
uh... merrick christmas thanks for the uh... thanks
thanks thank you banks two years
two years spot you are a new year's fuck you i don't care
well that's got
by
say by caleb