You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
This is premium content.
If you are not a premium subscriber,
please pause now and purchase a premium membership immediately.
[LOUD EXPLOSION]
Fuck, dude.
Here we go.
I have a joy hangover from Christmas.
Yeah, let's do a clap to line it up.
OK, now you can line up my audio to Patrick's clap.
Can we-- what if we do--
What if we--
OK, and then about 10 minutes, Caleb, you should do a clap.
And then you can sync up your clap to our claps.
- Yeah. - Okay.
- What if we did a snap?
- Okay, that sounds more fun.
- Okay, we did a snap.
All right, so they all happened at the same time.
- I think this might be the most synced episode
we've ever done already.
- Well, oh my God, I can't even believe
how synced up it'll be.
- I'm so excited.
Did you guys have a nice sweet Christmas
with lots of gifts? - I did, I did.
I didn't get any, I just got 200 bucks.
My mom's just, she's at the point now
where she's just like, yeah, I'm just giving you money.
- Yeah, that's the move, dude.
- Yeah, I wish it's better.
I think, I talked to my dad and I think next year
we're just gonna give each other $100.
Yeah, my mom, the way my mom did it though
was she put the money inside of like trash.
So she bought like--
Your mom is so weird.
She bought a thing of, my brother got like wart remover
with $100 in it and I got feminine hygiene wipes
with $100 in it and she taped it all together
so I had to pull it out.
So it looked like I was pulling money.
- So it looked like you were pulling out something else.
- And then my nephew-- - That's dirty.
- My nephew-- - And your nephew's
watched you do that?
- One of my-- - Your nephew's watched
you pull feminine stuff out of your hygiene area?
- Ugh, you're nasty, dude. - Don't say that.
- Well, you said it already.
- You literally just said that.
- You didn't let me finish.
So my nephew-- - And they liked it.
My nephew saw me do that and I guess he heard somebody say,
I got pussy wipes.
So then he started walking around.
- Saying I got pussy wipes?
- Yeah, he was saying pussy wipes.
- That's awesome, bro.
Yeah, I didn't really get anything cool.
I got slippers.
That's mine.
- Nice, dude.
- And I bought myself some candy.
- Whoa!
- My favorite part of--
- Yeah!
- My favorite part of Christmas
when you're not a kid anymore is buying stuff for yourself
and then like making your parent wrap it.
- Yeah.
- I think that's so funny to do.
I love like I got the Friday the 13th box set
and I just had it shipped to my dad's house
and I was like, dad, you're gonna wrap this for me.
(laughing)
- That rules.
Yeah, this is the first year since I've not seen my aunt,
this is the first year that I haven't gotten
a Blockbuster gift card in like my entire life.
- Oh no.
- Yeah, she just bought, I don't know, like 10 years ago,
she bought like 100 Blockbuster gift cards
'cause she was like, "This'll be around forever."
And she's just been giving them to everybody since then.
Can you like redeem them for anything?
I haven't even tried.
Yeah, coolness.
I haven't even thought about it.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Wait, let's look up if you can.
I could probably sell 'em.
I have a couple back at the apartment.
They're vintage, dude.
True.
People will frame them and put 'em on their walls.
Dude, I miss Blockbuster, bro.
I miss like trying to just guess
which movie had a boob scene in it.
- Yeah.
- Just trying to, just wild guess.
- My only memory from the video store in my town,
'cause it closed before I was like old enough
to like really go to, like to go to it by myself,
is just like going there with my parents
and seeing Jurassic Park 3,
and seeing the claw marks on the video
casing me like, holy shit, the claws make a three.
And that's the only memory I have from that video.
- It's just me walking around looking for tits,
just picking up every Halle Berry movie,
and being like, "Mom, Dad, I have to watch this movie."
- Ma, I'm really a huge fan of Swordfish.
- I'm a huge Halle Berry fan.
- I'm intrigued right now, Mom, Dad.
- I looked it up, Caleb, as of April 2011,
Blockbuster gift cards are completely worthless.
- Are you serious?
She's been giving them that long?
- Yep.
- Bro.
Nobody, I honestly don't even know if she knows
that it doesn't exist anymore.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, she might seriously think that it's still around.
- It might be, it might be like,
they might have changed Blockbuster
into a streaming service.
- True.
- They tried to do the DVDs thing for a while.
- They might have changed Blockbuster
into a streaming service.
- Whoa.
- They might have.
- We should do, we should start sending the episodes
on CDs in the mail.
- I was talking about this on stream.
That's the next tier is I'm gonna mail people DVDs
'cause I have too many DVDs
and I'd like to get rid of some of them.
And the thing is, but the thing is,
I only have like 10 too many DVDs.
So it's gotta be enough money of a tier
that only a few people are gonna subscribe to it.
- Let's say $1,000.
- Yeah, okay.
- Yeah.
- Well, if you get $1,000, I'll send you my DVD
of "Tammy and the T-Rex" or like "Alien vs. Predator"
or something.
- I'll send you a video from the Creation Science Museum
if you subscribe for $1,000.
- Do either of you have Dish TV?
No, like the thing no dish the the antenna like
Cable thing like dish network dish network if you have dish network blockbuster
Blockbuster comm is where the magic of blockbuster video lives on with dish
dude
2011 blockbuster has been part of dish and you can still make it a blockbuster night registered trademark
Continue the blockbuster experience. We just a channel dish
Do you know why they call it Dish TV?
Why?
Because you sit on the couch and you say,
"I'm watching Dish TV."
(laughing)
True, true.
I'm gonna watch Dish TV all night long.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't really know anybody with satellite anymore.
Me neither.
My dad switched over completely to streaming services.
He's spending like 300 bucks a month.
Yeah, I think my parents are doing the same thing.
Just to watch live basketball and shit,
it's like dude, that rules.
Yeah.
Yeah, I wish I had a TV.
Oh, I think, I wish I did too.
I need to get, I'm sick of watching movies on my computer.
I gotta get a big TV and surround sound.
Yeah.
Can I just get some Dolby Digital 5.1 surround sound?
Oh, I'm going 7.1, are you kidding?
7.1, no, no, no.
Yeah.
How about just--
I was getting 100, but I mean, you guys can--
- Yeah, but they have to get a 10 million point one
surround sound set up.
Yeah, 10 million and one decimal point.
- I'm thinking of getting like infinity point one,
Dolby digital, I don't know if you guys agree with that.
- Yeah, I'm thinking of getting a giant,
I'm thinking of getting like a 1200 pound TV
that's 36 inches wide,
and then a $50,000 surround sound set up,
and one of those ugly leather couches that reclines.
- Ordering a TV that says it's 50 inches,
but it's like a foot on the diagonal
and it has like a 50 inch deep like CRT monitor.
(laughing)
- It's 50 incher, dude.
- Yeah, you can get inside there if you want.
- That's a plasma screen too.
- Yeah, there's plasma in there, so don't go in, you'll die.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I'm gonna get one of those crazy couches.
I'm gonna tell everybody I have a home theater set up
and they're gonna come through
and we're gonna watch the first "Transformers" movie
in 480p. - And I'm gonna sit
in the chair behind the couch and I'm gonna jack off.
- 4DP, 4DP with the best sound on earth.
- The best unbelievable sound.
- Terrible video.
- You can't even see what's happening.
- It's 16 by 16.
- I got a state of the art sound system for a home theater.
Okay, how it works is everyone puts on headphones.
We have one headphone splitter.
And if you got, listen, if you have really,
if you have good headphones,
it's gonna be the best sound you ever heard.
- Yeah.
- But if you bring fucking Apple earbuds,
it's gonna sound like shit.
- That's on you.
- And we're gonna call you gay.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, but you will be able to hear
through those terrible headphones.
I'm gonna say, "You're gay."
You're gonna be like, "I heard that loud and clear."
- But yeah, but then this guy over here
has got the Audio-Technica over-ear headphones.
You know, he's not gonna hear it.
- Yeah, headphones do make you--
- He's gonna be smiling and he's gonna be watching the movie.
- They're insult-canceling headphones.
- Yeah, that's a good idea.
- It's genius, dude. - That's a good idea.
If everyone wore insult-canceling headphones, nobody--
- How many times has somebody called me a homo on the train
and I just didn't know 'cause my big ass cans?
- Yeah. - You know?
- Your boobs?
- My big ass boobs that I have.
Yeah, I was like, excuse me?
- It bounced right off.
- I just say, look at these, man.
- Yeah. - They get distracted.
They don't even know what they called me in the first place.
- Yeah, my boobs are down here.
- Excuse me, my boobs are down here.
- What a stupid ass gay hot guy with big boobs?
(laughing)
Look at that homo with the most beautiful tits of all time.
- You're walking out from behind the escalator
so he just sees your head at first and then.
(laughing)
- What?
- Hominomin, hominomin.
- The escalator on the train.
(laughing)
In the train station.
- No, they have double-decker trains in New York City.
- In my city.
- It's like an inter-K thing.
(laughing)
- Yeah, in my city that I'm inventing
where I have giant boobs and I ride the train all day.
(laughing)
- Yeah, 'cause I'm the mayor, dude.
I gotta prove the trains work.
I'm just getting on there with my big ass titties.
- Yep. - Yeah.
- Dressed in a suit, a men's suit,
my tits are bursting out of 'em.
- And my name is Boob Da Boobio.
(laughing)
- Yeah, that's right.
- Yeah.
- And I live in huge boob city.
- In the state of huge boobs.
- Yeah, titty city.
- I love it, I live in New York titty and new titty.
- Papa new titty.
Papa's new titties.
- That's right.
- Uh huh.
- Papa's got a new pair of titties.
- Yep.
- They're on the way.
- Papa's got a big rack.
- Can you check the mail?
It might be my tits.
- Daddy needs a new rack.
(laughing)
- Daddy needs a new, this is a guy at Vegas.
Daddy needs a new set of boobs.
- Did you guys see Santa Claus?
- No.
- Did you wait for him?
- He came immediately.
He came down the chimney 6 p.m.
- Yeah, he's definitely a man.
- I said, "Man, you're early."
And he didn't say anything.
- No.
And he waited until midnight, and then he went back up the chimney. He didn't even eat cookies
He can't speak at all he can't no he had well
He can say ho ho ho but he has like he had a there's a bullet lodged in his brain
And they can't take it out, but it it has disrupted his verbal ability
Yeah, that's true bad now for all yeah, I bet you feel real naughty now
What would you guys do if Santa just chilled in your house for like six hours?
I would make fucking fight him. I'm just a world star shit to him dude
I it's funny cuz you look at the Santa tracker, and it doesn't look at that Santa tracker right now
It doesn't say where he is so he could be
He's on other planets delivering gifts to aliens. Yeah, it's true. Yeah. Yeah, he goes down
Woman's chimney, and she's like oh, I don't have you know I don't have any money
And but and he's like you don't have to pay me with money
It's presents, but she doesn't understand and then she traps him in the bedroom. That's a movie that I could see being made
Oh my god, dude. I was thinking about this doesn't it feel like back in the day?
Women they used to look like Marilyn Monroe and now they look a lot more like Marilyn Manson
Have you guys thought about this
Well now think about this yeah, but you said these beautiful
four-foot women, weighed 180 pounds,
blonde as the sun, and she's fucking,
if you're the president, she's gonna suck your dick.
Now, Marilyn Manson-style women,
walking around all the time, they're seven feet tall,
they're skinny as a rail, casting spells.
- Back in the day, we used to have women
that looked like James Charles.
Nowadays, we have women that look like Charlie Chaplin.
- That's so fucking true.
(laughing)
That's really true.
I'm sick of these Charlie Chaplin ass bitches.
Yeah.
Yeah, back in the day, women used to look like
a big ass thumb though,
and now they look like Dikembe Mutombo.
And that's facts, no printer.
Yeah.
I can't think of any of them.
That's right.
Yeah.
Ooh.
- Back in the day we had President JFK,
now we have President he's not okay.
- No.
- Somebody needs to check on this boy.
- That's right.
- Somebody needs to check on this JFK.
- Yeah, somebody needs to check and balance on this guy.
- Oh my God.
- Do you think the president could even balance?
I'm so hungover guys.
- Boy had a little too much nog.
- I did.
- Yeah.
- I did, I did.
- He was drinking Christmas cream, dude.
- There's one time of the year
where you can nog yourself into a coma
And this man, he's just drinking it out of a Camelback.
We, me and my brothers, drank just straight whiskey.
Just Christmas Eve, just.
I drank straight up Aldi wine.
Yeah?
Yeah, I had three bottles of Aldi wine.
Damn.
Yeah.
Good for you.
I was dressed as a gnome at my family Christmas,
walking around drinking Aldi wine out of the bottle.
Oh yeah.
Just like.
I'm glad you like your gift.
I'm glad you like your costume.
It was the best gift I've ever gotten.
My grandma was so confused.
She was like, "What?
"Why are you dressed like a gnome?"
And I said, "I got cursed."
And she kept being like, "Seriously, what are you?"
And I was like, "I don't know.
"I'll turn back to a guy at midnight.
"There's nothing I can do."
She was like really upset with me.
- Yeah, was she upset with the knife I got you?
- No, she thought the knife was absolutely righteous.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
She thought it was so swag, dude.
- It's so funny how small that knife is.
- I showed, I told-- - It is tiny.
- I opened it up and I-- - It's like,
the handle's bigger than the blade.
Pat got me a knife with a, yeah, it's really small.
Pat got me a knife with a Bible verse on it,
and I read it, I was like, "Oh, it's got a Bible verse on it."
My mom was like, "Which one?"
And I was like, "Philippians 4.13."
And then she spent like 10 minutes
just trying to guess what that Bible verse was
and getting it wrong every time.
(laughing)
Yeah, some Christian she turned out to be, dude.
Patrick got me an Excalibur.
Oh yeah, that's true.
I was trying to get you this one.
I wasn't sure if it was from Patrick.
Patrick said he got me that in a DVD drive,
and he told me he was sending the DVD drive
and I didn't know he was also sending a sword.
So when the sword got here,
I genuinely didn't know if it was from Patrick
or from my uncle.
- It's a real sword or a sword-like object?
- It's a sword-like object.
- Oh, buddy.
- I'm gonna hang it on the wall though.
- Yeah.
- I think I'm gonna make a sword while I'm here, I decided.
I've been watching this show.
- Oh, Forged in Fire?
- I've been watching Forged in Fire.
- I've been watching this show.
I didn't know if you knew what it was, dude.
I've been watching it, and I was like,
"God, that's crazy cool, I definitely wanna do that."
And then me and my brother looked up
how much a forge costs.
It's like $60.
What?
Yeah, to get like a propane-powered forge
and like a little anvil, it costs like 60 bucks.
And then you get a scrap metal.
We're making a sword like tomorrow.
That's sick.
It's gonna be awesome.
I'm thinking of going with Damascus steel.
Yeah?
Yeah.
That shit's hard to make.
sharp nope it's easy is it easy yeah they do it on TV okay yeah I trust you about
that show I only watched like one or two episodes of it it the only cool part is
when they hit the pig with the stuff oh yeah rest of it is just like it's just
like it's a cooking show but not interesting it's like what yeah they're
making it's just like a stick of metal
- They should have a sword swallower to see,
to test that aspect of the sword.
All right, your blade will kill, it will cut.
Let's see how it swallows and how it tastes.
- It shows them like dunking the sword in water
or whatever and the guy's like,
"I was really upset because my sword, I didn't like it."
And that's like the extent of like,
it's so not interesting.
- My favorite part of that show is every three episodes,
they try to have a girl on.
- Yeah, and they fail.
They lose in the first round.
- They always lose the first round every time, dude.
It's so funny.
They have a girl on and she's like,
"Yeah, I've been doing this for like 50 years."
And all the other guys are like,
"I started last summer."
- Yeah, there's a guy who's like 20 years old.
- Yeah, and then she can't even get the metal to get hot.
And she just, they cut to the judging section
and she's holding part of a spring
that she tried to turn into a sword.
And they're like, "Unfortunately, you are disqualified."
He's sorry.
It's pretty, it's a pretty funny show.
It's always like beard guys on that show too.
There's a guy with a kilt.
Yeah.
And then they did the thing where they leave
for a couple days and they make a sword in their home forge
and then come back.
And the guy, when he was at his home forge wearing pants,
comes back to the show, brand new kilt.
Of course.
He just can't be seen in the stew without a kilt on.
Yeah. It rocks, yeah.
I don't know, I think I might have to pick up a tactical kilt pretty soon.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You're not Scottish though, you can't wear a kilt.
I'm tactical.
Ah, well, you know what?
That's an aspect of the kilt that I forgot.
I have knives and screws that I need to keep around.
Yeah, in the kilt.
That's what the tactical kilt is, it's covered in fucking cargo pockets.
Oh, okay.
Come on dude.
What color is it?
I thought it was tactical because it was made out of Kevlar.
- Yeah, it's made out of bulletproof,
it's a bulletproof kilt.
- Yeah, so you don't get your thingy shot off.
- As long as they don't, as long as they don't
leave it short. - Shot off my thingy.
- The problem with the bulletproof kilt
is if the bullet hits the ground
and bounces up into the kilt,
it's just gonna ricochet around inside there.
- That's true.
- And fuck up your shit from every direction.
- Not to like a birthday cake.
- A birthday, yeah it does.
What if the candles, what if they can't blow out?
They're green candles. - Well that's a what if,
that's not a negative.
- Well yours is a what if.
- No that has happened.
- Are we talking about a tactical birthday cake?
- Yeah.
- Ooh, that's not a bad idea.
- That's a birthday cake covered in pockets for the presents.
- So yeah, you can keep, wow.
It's like a mobile birthday party.
- Yeah.
- It has wheels to it.
- And clowns can fit in there too
'cause they can get small.
- If it's a tactical bachelor party cake,
you can keep the stripper in one of the pockets.
- Whoa.
and then she doesn't have to get messy
and you don't have to put her in the oven
to get her into the cake.
- True.
- That's the worst part about bachelor party cakes.
- You have to find a heat resistant stripper.
- Where the fuck is the stripper?
She's supposed to pop out of the cake
and digging through the cake
and she's just like red and burnt.
- Somebody stuffed this cake with pulled pork.
What the fuck is this dude?
- Oh no, we left Goofus in charge
of getting the stripper into the cake.
(laughing)
- Sorry guys.
I'm sorry about that.
- We left Goofy from the first scary movie.
(laughing)
We left him in charge.
Why do you fuck everything up, Goofy?
You're so stupid.
Yeah.
- I wouldn't do that on my bachelor party.
- Dude, are we gonna do a bachelor party when I get married?
- I guess we have to.
- Should just us three--
- Just watching TV.
(laughing)
It's just us three at Pat's house watching TV.
With all of our arms around each other.
With my mom and dad.
My mom and dad are in their chairs.
Yeah, we get a big bowl of popcorn.
They're not allowed to touch it, that's our popcorn.
Just watching YouTube videos.
Yeah, cut to my fiance's bachelorette party.
She's just on a casting couch getting fucking just turnt out like a fucking hot pocket.
We're just like, we're watching Mr. Bean again.
- Caleb's jacking off under the blanket.
(laughing)
- We're sitting, it's me and Cameron on the left
and right of the couch and Caleb's in the middle
jacking off.
- Yeah.
- Caleb's going like, oh, oh, oh.
- And we look over and he's like,
no, it was really funny, I'm laughing.
- I wouldn't jack off in front of you guys.
That seems like a Patrick move.
- No, what are you talking, I would never jack off
- Caleb is definitely the one who would do that.
- What?
- You are 100% the guy who would jack off in the--
- I don't even jack off in my life.
Why would I do it in front of my friends?
- Yeah, you do.
- No, I don't.
- You're the one who jacks off the most.
- I do not jack off.
- Yeah, you do.
- Dude, I'm like--
- You probably quit like a week ago, right?
- I'm like a divorced dad.
- For the holidays?
- No, I've been every other weekend for years.
- I don't believe that.
- It's true, dude.
How do you think I stay so powerful?
You don't, you're not powerful.
That's why every other Monday
is the worst possible day to catch me.
If you need me to do,
I can't even fucking tie a knot every other Monday.
I'm so fucking, I don't have any cum in my body.
Yeah? Yeah.
Either way, you're the one who would jack off
under a blanket. No, dude.
I'm like a samurai. No.
Yeah. We know samurai
jack off under blankets.
Yeah. Samurai have never
jacked off.
And I'm jacked off all the time.
- No, incorrect.
- Then why is his name Samurai Jack?
- You might catch me, now I'm not gonna say--
- Answer the question.
- His name is Sam, because he jacks off so much.
But that's why he's not just called Samurai.
He's Samurai Jack because he's the only one that jacks off.
That's not true, listen.
You guys might, you might catch me edging on the couch,
but I would never come.
'Cause edging is part of the power.
I edged fucking 30 minutes ago.
I was edging while I was shitting,
because I had to do this.
- So it hurt less.
- So that's why you were taking so long to get here?
- Yeah, I had to bring my penis with me.
- Because you were having a diarrhea attack
and you were edging at the same time?
- Yeah, dude.
I rubbed the tip like a crystal ball
and I'm ready to podcast.
(laughing)
That's just how it works, dude.
That's a little trick that I learned from Gus.
Yeah, I was about to ask, didn't Gus teach you that?
Gus taught me that.
Yeah.
And I've been on a new level ever since.
Yeah?
Yeah, I can see the back of my head right now.
Maybe I should have done that.
Maybe I wouldn't have, it wouldn't be so tired right now.
Yeah, dude, when you start edging
and taking stimulants a lot,
you're living like a third person view.
Yeah?
It's insanely cool.
You hit P and you go into third person.
Exactly.
First person, you don't have,
you're missing stuff out of the corners of your eyes.
What if somebody tries to attack you from behind?
I can see around corners when I edge.
I can see through wooden doors.
That's right, I can noclip.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm getting there, that's the goal.
Eventually, if I hold my command long enough,
I can start noclipping through walls.
You can use player.setscale 0.2.
Yeah.
You can get underneath doors.
I get, yeah, I get real, when I edge, I shrink down.
I set my jump to 5,000.
That's right, and bound my jump to the mouse wheel
so I can do it faster.
Yeah, I spawn so many items.
That's right, it's just the truth.
I set my max health to a million.
I'm really hard to kill right now.
Yeah.
Yeah, but it wears off.
I feel like I'm dead.
Maybe I should start doing this.
You should, man, I could teach you how.
Yeah?
Yeah, Cam could leave you
and we could stay on the Zoom call for a while.
He's the host, that's the problem.
I think we could just shut off our video
and then tell each other how to do it.
- Well no, I have to show you.
- Okay, then Cameron can put a piece of tape over his screen.
- Okay.
- One piece of tape over my screen?
- Over your whole screen.
Just take a thing of duct tape,
take duct tape and put a big X on the monitor.
- I just cross it out.
- Yeah.
- Just FaceTime me later and I'll show you
how to do it on a banana or something.
- Okay.
- I don't have to show you my penis.
- Dude, on Christmas morning,
I woke up like still fucked up and I was trying to like
sober up and my mom told me to eat a banana.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause I guess that she was like,
oh, that'll sober you up or whatever.
And I tried to eat a banana and I immediately threw it up.
- You threw up a single banana?
- I ate like the tip of the banana,
held it in my mouth for like a second
and then just like threw it up in the sink.
- You didn't even swallow it?
Okay, so you spit out the banana.
- Yeah, so you didn't throw up a banana.
- It felt like I threw up.
- Do you ever do that thing where you--
- You just say, wait, it felt like you threw up
or you did throw up?
- It felt like I threw up.
- Do you ever do that thing where you sit with your friends--
- So you spit, wait, so you just spit it out?
- He just spit it out.
He doesn't know the difference
between spitting and throwing up.
Do you ever do that thing, Pat,
where you sit on a bridge and you see how far
you can throw up and then suck it back into your mouth?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, that's pretty good, right?
I like doing that kind of thing.
- I felt, dude, it's straight up,
I think if I ever swallowed a banana, I would throw up.
It'd be funny to go to the top of the Empire State Building
on a tour and just throw up off the side.
Yeah.
That would rule.
I feel like the wind,
I feel like it wouldn't touch the ground.
I feel like the wind--
It will, every single person would get like one piece
of throw up on their face.
Maybe like, "Ew, carrot."
That's the coolest shit, dude.
When I would go to Canterby Lake Park,
we'd go up on the log flume.
Oh, the star blaster?
No, the log flume.
Oh.
you know the log flume where you have to climb all the stairs
to get to the top, like it's like this metal,
it's a log flume, I don't know how more to describe it.
Yeah, you have to like climb all these stairs
to get to the top of it, like to wait in line,
and we just like spit off the top of it
and just watch like the wind would just like explode
the spit halfway down.
Just the coolest thing in the world, dude.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I mean, the Star Blaster,
that was always fun to spit off of.
- Yeah, I just love spitting.
- Me too, we should just start spitting a lot.
- That's the fun part of amusement parks.
That's one thing COVID's taken away from us, dude.
- You can't spit on people.
- You're right.
- You can't spit onto people from--
- It's become a rude thing.
- From 40 feet in the air.
- Yeah, it's become very rude.
- It's become very messed up to do.
- It's pretty sad.
- It sucks that people think it's rude.
- To spit on someone?
- It's funny too.
- Sometimes you need to spit on the ground too.
That's something, people are always like,
people always go like, oh it's so disgusting
when people spit on the ground.
It's like no, sometimes there's something in your mouth
you need to get it out.
- It's fine to spit.
- If you say it's bad to spit on the ground
or it's gross to spit on the ground,
I know that you've never eaten anything in your life.
- You've never eaten sunflower seeds?
- You've never had phlegm, you've never had allergies,
you've never had any, I know that you drink through a tube,
you drink water, that's all you eat.
- We gotta bring back spittoons.
- Yeah, I agree.
- Like at a bar, just like a metal pot.
- They should put 'em around like they put trash cans.
- Yeah, dude. - Outside, it's everywhere.
- Well, that would be a problem for pigeons.
But then there would be like a guy who likes to like drink it.
Yeah, exactly.
I mean, he can do what he wants.
There's probably a guy who likes to drink the trash cans too.
Yeah.
Is that what those families are doing
when they walk around my neighborhood
opening all the recycling bins?
They're looking for cans with spit in them?
They're looking for empty bottles to eat.
You know what I would be scared of if they had spittoons
is somebody taking my DNA.
You know what, maybe now with DNA,
I don't want somebody to take my--
Now that DNA has been discovered this year.
Yeah.
I don't want someone to take my spit from a spittoon
and put it at a crime scene.
That's a good point.
Yeah.
I went to a pool hall yesterday,
'cause we called them, we were like,
hey, what's the deal?
Are you guys open?
And they were like, yeah, everybody has to wear a mask,
and we're opening every other table and stuff.
And we're like, okay, that seems pretty safe.
We get there, and we get set up,
and there's a guy in a cowboy hat,
walking around with no mask, licking his hands.
(laughing)
Just walking around the whole place,
licking the palms of his hands without a mask on.
Giant cowboy hat.
- Was he doing it as like a fuck you?
- Like a fuck you COVID?
- I think, or he just had like the best wings ever.
It's one of those for sure.
I honestly have no clue.
Yeah, it could have been either one.
- Man, that's so funny.
Let's do this list.
- Yeah, hold on.
I'm gonna, since I'm editing this,
I'm gonna get a cup of coffee one second. I'm gonna get one too. I won't I promise I'm not gonna edge anymore
That's just gonna get picked up on the call
Hey now that Caleb's not here
I've got another present going to his house. He's gonna hear this when he edits it. It's a it's
Anthrax did you get my present? I think I said I did Asheville by accident
No you I got it. I think I sent it to Nashville by accident. Oh now I get that now I got
Yeah, I think I sent it I think I sent it I think I sent it I think I think I sent it
I think I sent it. I think I sent it. Yeah, I think I sent it
Yeah, I think I accidentally played a message to say you had to evacuate and then send it to Nashville by accident
And my niece really loved the the gift that you got me Cameron
It was that's so funny doesn't make noises. Yeah, it makes it makes baby Yoda sounds and farts
Really dude. Yeah, nice. All right. My penis is a red-hot tamale and we can record now. All right, okay
58 things you probably forgot happened in 2020 since this is the last episode of 2020. Mm-hmm
And this is from mashable everyone's every favorite website. Yeah, here's the thing. I did a quick cursory glance of this list
I remember all this. Yeah, you have an amazing memory
This is this list is by Jess Joho
Wow, what a cool name? Yeah, wow guys we survived 2020. Yay
Congratulations, you survived 2020 does the idea of this godforsaken years and bring you little comfort because you know
The horrors it rot will outlast December. Yeah us to
Emotionally speaking 2020 lasted approximately 12 months and 487 years
quarantine time distortion is a real thing.
That's why we're billing to what,
we'll bill it.
(laughs)
- We're Billy Willys.
We're willing to bet you will not believe
many of the events we've compiled on this list
actually took place in the year of our Lord 2020.
You know that, the year of our Lord.
- This is funny.
- Time is a human construct.
It's lost all meaning forever,
whether due to isolation or just the unending onslaught
of world ending news.
In all likelihood,
you'll experience the memory of events
from earlier in the year
like they're from a bygone era,
a time when humanity was more innocent and naive
unless, you know, on the brink of total societal collapse and whatnot.
Or maybe you were just bombarded by so many unfathomable news stories,
or, let's be honest, too busy spiraling to pay attention,
that you missed some or deleted others from memory to make room for...
everything else that happened.
As strange and unbelievable as some of these seem,
they all did indeed occur in our current timeline.
So get ready to dive headfirst into the wormhole, friends.
Let's defy the laws of physics and logic together
as we walked down a memory lane located in the bowels of hell,
smiley face emoticon.
Your body might want to physically reject the fact
that some of the following took place
in the span of just 12 months,
but as your soul fights to leave your body,
just try not to think of what's to come in 2021.
- It's just rules that no matter how bad shit gets,
people will still write these articles.
- Yeah. - Just forever.
There'll just be like 150 cities that fucking
were consumed by the ocean this year
that you might not remember.
- Yeah.
- That's swag.
- I'm thinking the ocean came in this year.
- Yeah, a hundred cannibals you might not remember
eating your loved ones this year.
- I think, you know, I think it's pretty,
it's good that we have lists like this.
- Yeah, it is good.
Why do you think that?
- The devil just appeared, because why not?
- Yeah, 'cause now it's 2020 and I guess that's a thing.
- I guess the devil is real now.
Yeah.
I think this has been the worst year.
Wow, really?
Dude.
I feel like there's just like,
it's just like, I can't wait for the dumpster fire
to be over.
Dude.
Is one thought that I've been having.
It's gonna be so freeing when you wake up
on January 1st, 2021.
Yeah.
And you're like, dude, it's all, it's back to normal, dude.
I'm still writing garbage fire on all my checks.
When I wake up back in my kid body
and I realize I'm not an adult anymore.
Uh-huh.
2020 is over. I wake up back in my race car bed, "Mom, I missed you." It'll be great, dude.
Dude, every year has been so bad. You know, like 2019, Peter Mayhew died.
Yeah. First Peter Mayhew. That was the first hell year for me. That was when I know it was
going bad. And then this year, you know, this year, my uncles. My uncles didn't come to Christmas.
Yeah, it's pretty fucked up dude.
Oh, by the way, my uncle, we're getting him on the podcast.
He's coming.
I'm so excited.
We're doing it, dude.
(laughing)
Patrick died.
He asked me what the podcast was called
and I just lied to him.
It's just somebody who's like, really?
I don't know anyone who's really into Peter Mayhew.
(laughing)
It is so funny though, every fucking year before this,
they were like, this is the hell year,
because like one celebrity they yeah always it's always like that because
like it's always it's always a from Star Wars yeah yeah great David Bowie died
This is officially the worst year of all time.
(laughing)
- It's not even that funny.
It's not even that funny at all.
- Awkward, it's tired.
- Dude, he's got nog brain.
- Number one, makes it happen.
Makes it.
We need to get you you need to take a vibe answer
The year we lost fucking Mayhew man this sucks
Didn't lose Peter Mayhew this at least he already died so that he didn't get to die again
And Peter Mayhew dying. Thank God. My father died of coronavirus and Peter Mayhew
God this year sucks
Megxit this is one of those lists where every item is just a tweet
Yeah, and then has like a little blurb about the tweet. That's swag
So Megxit was when Harry and Meghan were leaving the royal family. I will be honest. I don't remember this one
I don't remember this happening. I you know I was too broken about Peter Mayhew
Yeah about Peter Mayhew? I was still recovering. There was about six months that I just blacked out after he died.
I don't even remember everything. I was kind of entered a fugue state. I went on an insane bender. I woke up in Tulsa.
And you know people were telling me I had to put on a mask and stuff. Yeah. I was like what?
I was like what? Why? I gotta put on a mask? Don't you know fucking Peter Mayhew just died?
- Yeah, can you stop bothering me with this mask shit?
- Oh my God.
- I'm mourning.
- I'm mourning Peter Mayhew.
- It has been nice though,
'cause now you can't tell who people are.
So sometimes I see a guy with long hair out
and I'm like, that could be Peter.
- That could be Peter.
- He could still be alive.
- Sometimes I'll see a dog running around
and I'll be like, if that thing stood on two legs,
it might look a little something
like Peter Mayhew's famous character.
- I hope he yells.
- I put bandoliers on my dog.
(laughing)
Yeah, I don't remember this at all.
But I don't think I would have known about this
the day after it happened either.
Yeah, I don't think I was ever aware of this.
I do remember this.
I don't think, I was kidding when I said that.
Well, you're a TMO, dude.
Did you get tore up?
Put the floor up?
I didn't actually.
No?
I didn't actually enter a fugue state
when Peter Mayhew died.
Although, it does seem believable.
Actual Brexit happened too.
Yeah.
Like it happened every year for like five years.
Brexit keeps happening.
As Americans trying to deal with our own dumpster fire of a country, it can be hard to keep track
of the clusterfucks happening across the pond.
But as recently as a year ago, the UK thought it was a good idea to officially break up with
the European Union.
Then the pandemic hit.
We're hashtag all in this together though, right Boris?
Yes, dude.
Get Boris.
Kinda like Donald Trump's brother in some ways.
Well, 'cause yeah, everybody has a British brother.
It's like a doppelganger.
Yeah, did you know Peter Mayhew was British?
Really?
Mm-hmm.
The UK and America are actually sister cities,
which is why that happens.
Yeah.
If you have sister cities, you get brother guys.
I'm like sister shitties due to the different leaders
who are in charge of various nations of the world.
Yeah, and the different fires going on in our dumpsters.
Yeah, that's right.
Parasite won the Oscar for best film.
I mean, what a-- What a clusterfuck.
- What a duster fire of a year.
- Oh my God, don't they realize
it's an award for American movies?
- Right, they should get that award
to movies with Peter Mayhew.
- They should give it to Wonder Woman 1984.
- True.
- Yeah, now the joke's definitely fucking dead.
- You think that was it, Patrick?
You think that was the one that killed it?
- No.
(laughing)
No, it's gonna come back.
- Don't say killed, he'll remember
that Peter Mayhew died. - Yeah, I'll think about Peter.
- And he'll start laughing like a hyena.
It's gonna come back. Yeah, no I remember when Parasite won. Yeah is that the way
that you get out of your laugh fit is just saying that? Mm-hmm yeah I remember
that one. Number four there were locust swarms in Africa.
stop laughing stop I'm I'm I'm so sorry I ever do I need you need to put an
Aspirin under your tongue, dude
There's something wrong with you
Wait didn't though didn't the locust swarms happen after we killed cuz team Soleimani
Yeah, yeah, we did yeah, we three
Yeah, yeah.
He said, "This is prefer Peter, maybe."
We weren't supposed to reveal that, but I just, ah, fuck.
I stopped laughing.
Wow, this is a funny, I mean,
how hilarious is this fifth one?
Harvey Weinstein was sentenced to prison for sex crimes.
Wow.
Yeah.
It's hard to recall any justice being served in 2020,
But folks, it did indeed, it did indeed,
it indeed did occur in at least one case.
- You think Harvey Weinstein's funny?
- I think it's funny what--
- What he did?
- No, what's going to happen to him.
- What he's going to do?
- What do you think's gonna happen to him?
- He's gonna kill himself in prison.
- What, why are you laughing again?
thinking about Peter Mayhew.
- I'm glad we're closing out the year with this one.
- Just Pat laughing for 20 minutes straight.
- Now we have something to do better than,
we're lowering the bar for the end of the year.
So it's easy to have a good 2021.
- Yeah, it's true, that's exactly what we're doing.
- With this freaking dumpster fire of an episode.
Well, but Pat's just, you know,
some people's reaction to the trauma of 2020
is just laughter.
- That's true.
- Yeah.
- Laughter can actually--
- I'm kinda like the comedian from Watchmen.
I think everything's a joke.
- People don't realize that like giggling
can actually be a sign of trauma at times.
- Yeah, it's been, that's so true.
- It's like a common quote among psychiatrists
and like astrophysicists that like,
The man who chuckles may be the man with the most pain.
- Yeah. - It's true.
- Or the woman. - Or the woman.
- That was one of like-- - Mostly the woman.
- That was one of Freud's archetypes.
- Yeah, it was basically-- - The sad giggler.
- Basically, Freud and Jung came up with this idea
that like a clown could die.
- They came up with the Pagliacci joke.
- Yeah, they came up with Joker.
Joker is basically the myth that Joker was based on,
which was called the Greek Joker.
- Yeah. (laughs)
- Yeah.
- Yeah, he was half--
- He was half Greek and half Roman.
- Yeah, his dad was Zeus and then his mom was the Joker.
(laughing)
Yeah, he was a half guy.
- Basically, they won't teach you that kind of stuff
in school, but they will on BuzzFeed School,
which is a new section they have on their website,
which you guys should check out.
- That's great, kind of a Khan Academy style.
You can learn different.
- You can go to buzzfeed.learn
and you can learn a lot about trauma
and different types of laughter and why.
If you recognize your family's laughter
based on whether it's your mom or your dad's laughter,
that could mean your mom or your dad
was abusive towards each other,
you or your brothers or sisters,
based on whether they were laughing
when they were attacking you.
- If you have ever been tickled,
it could have been a traumatic,
you could have had trauma in your past.
- Do you wanna say something back?
- If someone touches your tummy and you giggle,
it could be that you have been depressed
when you were a child.
- One famous case study is like Santa Claus,
his bowl jiggles like a bowl of jelly.
- His bowl does?
- His balls jiggle like a bowl of jelly when he chugs.
- Oh. - Yeah.
- Oh God.
- And you don't-- - Wait, is that a sign of trauma?
- It's because-- - Santa, believing in Santa
is a sign of trauma, I heard.
- Yeah, I heard basically, you can, what is this?
- What did you just send us?
(laughing)
- Patrick just sent us an image that is a quote
by Peter Mayhew.
(laughing)
- This is the best thing that ever happened to me.
- What is he talking about?
You think he's talking about dying?
- He's talking about dying.
- I don't know.
(laughing)
- That's his last word.
This is the best thing that has ever happened to me.
- 'Cause I forced him to dress up like a dog alien for--
(laughing)
- For years.
For every fucking local--
- Every time, yeah.
- Every Memphis Comic Con,
he had to show up dressed up as a dog.
- Every time a show on the CW wanted to do
like a Star Wars crossover episode or like a feat,
like they wanna do an episode that's like a Star Wars parody,
they're like, "Hey, Peter Mayhew's been stuck in the suit
"since the '70s."
(laughing)
- Yeah. - You gotta go through this.
- I'm sorry, I keep looking at fucking Peter Mayhew.
- Just look at us. - Stop looking at them.
- If you worked at Google instead of for me,
you'd be in so much, you'd be in jail right now.
*laughter*
Stop!
I hate you.
*laughter*
Look at the face!
With my mask, I controlled all of the mouth movements with my own mouth!
*laughter*
It's a quote!
It's a quote, but it's over!
It's over like a Microsoft default background and it says "Peter Mayhew".
*laughter*
Wow, thank you.
With the episode.
That's so good.
That's a good quote.
Yeah, that is really good.
Thank you for that.
(laughing)
- That was really amazing.
- It's totally inspiring.
- Well, especially, you know,
he died before they made him wear another mask.
- Yeah, it's true.
- He had to die.
Do you think he would have just worn the Chewbacca mask?
- Oh yeah.
- When he went to Tesco?
- He would have put a COVID mask over Chewbacca's mouth.
- It should be, I think this should count as a mask.
(laughing)
- Oh, he's pantomiming eating pussy.
- I think doing the finger, the peace sign that you eat,
whatever that's called.
- Yeah, it's called Delicious Peas.
- It's called Delicious Peas.
(laughing)
- Are you saying, yeah, I think someone did that to me.
Are you saying you love peas?
- Are you saying you wanna lick peas?
Yeah, I heard that, brother.
- Yeah.
- Number six, Michael Bloomberg ran for president
and they have the video Nick Ciarelli made.
- Yeah, that's a--
- That's one of the funniest videos.
- That's funny that they picked that
and the Buzzfeed people were like, this is so real.
- Yeah.
Shout out to Nick, Nick Ciarelli.
- Number seven. - Great comic.
- Yeah, shout out.
Number seven, all the prophetic
Netflix reality shows that aired.
- Yeah. - You guys remember,
you guys remember in January 2020
when they had that game show, Pandemic?
- Yes, yes.
- You guys remember that game show,
Murder Hornets House?
(laughing)
- Yeah, remember in 2018 when they did that show,
Peter Mayhew just died?
It was prophetic, dude.
- Yeah.
- It's unbelievable.
- Did they do like a,
let's see, Peter Mayhew Memorial.
Did they do some kind of like,
like memorial thing for him?
- Yeah, at the end of the Oscars they did that.
- Dude, they made a memorial coin for him.
- Whoa.
- Chew-daka.
- It's a beautiful coin.
- I hope someone makes a beautiful coin when I die.
- It's on jedibusiness.com.
- That's just Jedi shit, you wouldn't understand, civilian.
- Check out this coin.
- Guys, just Google the Peter Mayhew Memorial Coin.
- Google Peter's Coin.
- Damn, that's a sick coin.
- That is a pretty sick coin.
- He looks like a rock star.
- Along the edge of the coin is a quote,
"If I see further, it is by standing
"on the shoulders of giants."
- Wow, Peter Mayhew.
- Peter Mayhew said that.
- Dude, was he tall?
He was really tall, right?
- I don't know.
- Who knows, dude?
- It's impossible to tell 'cause he was in a suit.
- True.
Number nine, Australia faced, no wait, we skipped one.
Vanessa Hudgens couldn't understand
why people dying from COVID was bad.
Is that true?
- Oh, I remember that.
- I don't remember any of this, bro.
- Yeah, she wanted to go to Coachella so bad
that she was like, well, people are gonna die anyway,
so what?
- Yeah.
- True, dude.
- Yeah, that's not the first dumpster trash fire
she's created.
Well, if you guys recall,
I believe she started a little something
called High School Musical.
Let's go.
I believe she actually broke Zac Efron's heart
by having her nudes leaked.
So she's kind of a bitch.
Yeah, she basically took Zac Efron's virginity
and like toyed with it.
And then again, she allowed naked photos of herself
to be hacked off her phone, so kind of a whore.
Come on, man.
That's facts.
Number nine, Australia faced devastating fires,
then California joined them later.
I did not care at all that Australia was on fire.
I did.
I didn't care about California either.
Talk about a dumpster fire, dude.
Those two states to the worst.
The state of Australia.
To the worst, most liberal states in the world.
Yeah.
It's like if you didn't wanna get caught on fire,
maybe, first of all, don't live in a place
where fire happens.
Number two, don't build your house out of wood.
That was literally in like the Three Little Pigs story book.
That was nature's retribution for that video
of that guy punching the kangaroo in the face.
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
- Nature had to get back.
- Australian nature got made a fool of.
- Yeah.
- And they had to strike back.
- God heard the way that Australians were saying the word no.
- Yeah.
- And he came down on them with righteous wrath.
- Yeah, and he said, wait I thought they're already in jail.
- Yeah.
- Oh wait, no, well, all right,
I guess I'll set her on fire now.
- Yeah.
- Number 10, we started the year by making
LOL World War III memes.
- And here's a tweet from Boss Logic.
Dude, I bet this guy's a beast.
Let's check out Boss Logic.
He's an artist and art director.
That's my favorite kind of guy.
Wow, and he has a--
He posted pictures of Drake and the Simpsons.
Whoa.
That's sick.
That's two of the coolest things a guy could like
if you're a designer, an art director.
(mimicking music)
I'm tired too today.
Yeah, I'm so tired.
I'm just tired, y'all.
Our president was impeached and inquited.
- Yep.
- Inquited.
What the fuck did I just say?
- You skipped so much.
- What?
- Oh no, you didn't.
My bad. - Yeah, bitch.
- I just said I was tired.
This video looks like an ad,
that's why I thought you skipped it.
That's why I thought you skipped something.
- No.
- 'Cause it's not even in like, it's like a--
- Right, they don't even have the list.
They have another thing on Mashable.
- Yeah.
Number 12, we were risking it all to watch Cats,
Doolittle and Sonic the Hedgehog in theaters.
Not, no.
- No.
- No, I don't remember that.
Number 13, we thought stockpiling on toilet paper
would save us from the virus.
- That was like the worst couple weeks.
- I was gonna turn myself into a mummy and just wait it out.
I was gonna wrap myself in toilet paper,
jump in my sarcophagus and just wake up in 2021.
- That was the week we were smelling DVDs, dude.
- Yeah. - That's true.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, we can like directly see the effect it had.
- That's a good point.
- That's also the week we were talking about,
Caleb was talking about eating a dog's pussy in his sleep.
- It's true, yeah.
- It was normal.
- You can directly, that was the most stressful week,
and it was also, we did the most worst things.
- Yeah, I guess you're right.
Tenet was in theaters, god this sucks.
- I don't remember Tenet being in theaters.
- Oh yeah, we did have a Super Bowl.
- Did we?
- Yeah.
- Dude.
That's awesome.
- Yeah.
- Man, Jared Leto and Big Brother contestants
found out about the pandemic weeks after everyone else did.
- Oh yeah, I forgot about that.
Yeah, yeah, they were all pretending.
I actually just found out, I've just been,
I've been in my house, so I didn't notice.
- I wish he fucking stayed in that desert facility.
- That's right!
- Yeah, I hate, I think--
- Buddy, go back to it.
- Go back to the desert.
Well, he's studying, he's doing,
he's gonna play Gandhi next year.
- Are you not gonna watch Morbius, the Living Vampire?
You're not excited for that?
- He's getting into character, dude.
- I fucking hate that guy, I think, more than any.
I don't think I hate celebrity more than him.
- I think he's swaggy.
- Fight Club is such a good movie
'cause they beat the shit out of him.
- Yeah, 'cause he gets the fucking shit kicked out of him.
- That's such genius casting, dude.
- I think he seems like one of those guys
that makes women sign an NDA when he has sex with them.
- That's like all famous guys.
- That's true, but his is a scroll.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Yeah, you have to use a quill.
You have to sign it.
You have to prick your thumb and put blood on it.
- Yeah, and then the scroll just vanishes
in a puff of smoke.
- Yeah.
- And he goes, "Ee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee."
- My warlock will be contacting you
if you breach this NDA.
(laughing)
You won't be hearing from my warlock.
Yeah.
(laughing)
Number 17, Trump praised the coronavirus opinions
of a doctor who believes there are demons in sperm.
That was awesome.
That was pretty cool.
That was fucking sick.
This is like the first year that I realized
that doctors are just crazy.
Yeah, most doctors are stupid people.
I feel like there were so many doctors like this
who just started talking about,
- Just became like public figures out of nowhere.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- And then it would come up like, yeah,
they have, they like turned their kid into a dog.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah.
- They walk their kid on a leash.
- Public figure doctors are always the most evil people.
- Oh yeah. - Definitely.
- 'Cause they don't give a shit about the medicine.
- They don't give a shit about the hypnocratic oath.
- Exactly. - Which is,
all doctors and nurses, we've talked about this,
they're cowards and they're bad people.
- You should talk to a nurse or a doctor,
you should talk to them, you should look down on them.
You should talk to them with disdain in your voice.
You should talk to them like you just found
a dog with no legs in a dumpster,
and it ate your trash and you're mad at it.
That's the tone of voice to use.
- Here's what a lot of people don't realize.
You know what the beginning salary for a nurse is
in any city in America?
- One dollar.
- A million dollars.
- Really?
- They're all millionaires.
- I was way off.
And you know what, they get paid state taxes.
But only from people who make less than 50 grand a year.
All of their taxes go to nurses.
Yeah.
Yeah, so next time you feel bad for these sickos
and these freaks, just remember they like it.
You know how long their lunch break is?
All day.
Yeah.
They don't even have a job.
They get paid to just dress that stupid.
All they have to do is wear a pager.
Yeah.
And they don't have to answer it,
they just have to wear it.
Nope.
for technically. Yep. All the other stuff is just because they choose to do it. Like if
they put a needle in you, they just feel like needling someone. If they save anybody, it's
completely accidental. And that's the truth. It's all luck. Yeah, the only thing that can
save you every few days is fire. If a doctor saves a guy, it's just because he wants to
get back to his sandwich. Exactly, yeah. His DVR is fucked up, and so he can't record Seinfeld,
He's gotta get back.
- Exactly. - Yeah.
- That's the truth.
- But if he lets someone die, it's on purpose.
- Yes, exactly.
Number 19, Kanye West not only ran for president,
but was endorsed by Chance the Rapper and Elon Musk.
- Oh, we skipped-- - What?
I'm sick of this freak, Kanye.
- We skipped Andrew Cuomo's nipples.
- Well, I don't wanna talk about a man's nipples
on the show.
That's a-- - That's crass.
- That's too far, that's crass,
and it will ruin my edging streak.
Kanye ran for president sure oh yeah he gifted Kim Kardashian a hologram of her
own dead dad that shit is so sick that was the funniest fucking thing I think
of this year I really hope I hope it was like that like you know that the Nathan
for you thing where the kid sees his dead dog yeah it's just like that where
it's just he got like a random guy to voice him no it gets John it didn't know
David Schwimmer come to the house dude you're fucking Kanye West you don't
you have you have a well that's the problem that's a hologram starts like
glitching and like clipping through walls and it's like comes off did it it
did it it it it it it it it he dies again
him had to have cancer yeah yeah speaking of number 21 we lost more
Titanic legends and we could keep track of oh my god all the legends dude yeah
Ruth Bader Ginsburg yeah Alex Trebek nope I said that's it all right just our RGB
man yep just be our G Ruth Gaber Dinsburg ruber-duber goober
Rube Goldberg nobody Allen Allen yeah Ginsburg Allen Ginsburg dober dober
wait scoober-doober are you serious no wait this can't wait somebody good oh
it's on TMZ they always know this stuff first scoober-doober just died oh my god
no get me the flipper I'm just passed away wait let me from star Fox died oh
my god and look it's this year Peter make you know stop we were doing a
tightrope act just dodging talking about celebrity deaths dodging Peter Mayhew it
was almost perfect we were at the edge and then we just fell off yeah we just
felt you pushed us off yeah and all the add goofy gopher died - yeah please say
it ain't so no no yeah yeah goofy gopher died yeah and actually goofy gopher
yeah - gopher jr. just it's so sad the goofy it's kind of mysterious how the
The goofy gopher family keeps dying.
- Dude, I'm so mad.
Ooey gooey Bobo just died.
- Oh no, dude.
Dude, Slime Richard died.
- Slime Richard.
- He's dead.
- Yeah.
Nobody remembered 4/20 and it wasn't
because we were too high.
What was it then?
4/20 was a sad state of affairs this year
as stoners everywhere grappled with unknown risk factors
of smoking during the pandemic.
I don't think--
Mashable think people stop smoking weed during the pandemic
Yeah, dude, I I've been completely clean and I haven't done any drugs this whole year yeah because I got scared
There's no way there's that's not like how people deal with stress or anything. No
Stupid stupid website number 23 murder hornets failed
to kill us
Yeah, sure
Bolivian orchestra was trapped in a castle by way
That's actually a cool bit of news, okay, maybe this is the best year of all time
Number 25 Chris Evans doxed his own dick what?
What you don't know what doxing means?
Nobody does anymore means you should just mean like post your personal information now
It just means that if you say somebody's first name, would you yeah?
I want to go pick up a pizza, but I can't remember where the dominoes it
Would you mind doxing them real quick
so that I can figure out where to go?
I'm gonna dox them into my Google Maps
so that I can go to Domino's.
- Yeah. - Oh, yeah.
- Oh, you know, oh dude, we're having a huge party.
I'll tell you, I'll dox it to you later.
- I'll dox the owner of the house.
Oh, oh, you gotta, oh, you gotta talk to my therapist.
He's so great, I'll dox him for you.
- Yeah, here, let me dox him real quick.
- Oh my God, this dinner is delicious.
I have to know how to make it.
You have to dox it for me.
You have to dox the chef.
Uh, number 26,
the internet stand Kim Yo Jong,
Kim Jong Un's sister.
Oh yeah, she was the one with the crazy shaped face.
She's so beautiful.
She had the weird cheekbones.
I publicly proposed to her.
It was kind of funny that that was,
I remember that, that people thought he was dead for a minute.
Yeah. That was pretty funny.
It's cool. It's true.
Yeah, him faking his own death
to see who was loyal to him.
That's, he's the Kevin Gates of rulers.
- I think I'm having a heart attack right now.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, do you guys feel loyal to me?
- Yes. - Yes.
- I'm so loyal, Cameron. - Maybe.
- What? - I'm so sad
that you're having a--
- Well, guess what, Cameron?
I'm alive and I wasn't having a heart attack.
- I didn't say no.
- And next couple times I see you,
I'm gonna be, I might be a little rude.
- Damn, you're rude all the time to me.
- Whoa, best friend, slow it.
- That's true.
- Number 27, people honest to God believed
in a baseless conspiracy theory about wayfair sex traffic
in children through cat.
- Okay, baseless?
- Yeah, that was--
- I hope that the further down on this list we get,
it is like, yeah, people honest to God believed
in a child sex ring run by Jeffrey Epstein.
Honestly, these fucking internet freaks.
- Dude, it's fucking, we're not even halfway
through this list.
- Oh Christ.
- Oh my God.
- And we're over an hour.
All right, speed run it.
- All right.
- We're not even halfway through this year.
- Okay, we'll take turns, lightning round, okay?
- All right.
- The multi-billion dollar Mulan live action remake
premiered on Disney Plus, don't care.
- It wasn't good.
- Giselaine Maxwell was arrested.
(laughing)
- That's a great one-two punch, just an ad and then.
- All right, Patrick, go.
- Trump claimed he was banning TikTok
like seven different times and just forgot about it.
- Didn't he do it?
Did he not do it?
Can't you not download it or something?
I don't know, I don't go on TikTok.
- Everything was cake, we will never trust again.
- No, we're taking turns, Patrick.
What do you not understand about taking turns?
Everything was cake, everything was cake and we will never trust again.
Yeah, because the cake is a lie.
Twitter got hacked.
Oh yeah, remember when blue checks couldn't tweet?
That was funny.
Yeah.
Carol Baskin was a contestant on Dancing with the Stars.
Oh my god.
Is that true?
Oh my god!
Okay, stop the list.
Stop it right now.
What?
Did she really dress up like a lion?
Why is she dressed up like a lion?
This is the wrong fucking cat, you bitch.
Fuck you. Oh my God. Go to hell you bitch. Get that gay guy out of jail. Go to hell.
Fuck you. A whole bunch of famous people got COVID that you totally forgot about. Trump
bragged about passing a base of cognitive test. Pat, you're terrible at this bro. Patrick,
I can't believe you.
- Space Force was a show that happened, we are told.
- Sophie Turner announced, who's, I don't know who that is.
She's pregnant though.
- That's you.
Quibi launched, then shut down only six months
and 1.75 billion dollars later.
That is, I'm really, Quibi is one of the funniest things
from this year for sure.
- I think you guys were talking about,
I think it's an episode without me,
but I think you guys talked about
how it was gonna shut down.
- Quibi?
- Yeah.
- That's not an impressive prediction though.
- That's true, yeah.
- Yeah, I think that was like from the beginning
people said that.
- Yeah.
- No, the only, the most impressive prediction this year
was Cameron said that Nancy Pelosi was a ho-tip
and then she wore the--
- The kente cloth. - The kente cloth, yeah.
- Yeah, that's true. - That's you, dude.
- Yeah, that was pretty good.
- I'm a prophet.
- You are.
I have to pee, we can't finish this.
- No. - I have to pee too bad
and this is just turning into ads every other time.
- Happy 2020, guys.
- Yep, yeah.
- Rest in Peace.
- No.
- Ruth Bader Ginsburg.
- Yep.
- Alex Trebek.
- Yes.
- Chadwick Boseman.
- Scoober Doober.
- The Goofy Gopher.
- Lumpy.
- Lumpy Cristo.
- Restroom Fred, he drowned in a toilet.
- Chilling Steve.
- Yeah.
- Christmas.
- Mr. Gumdrop.
- Yeah.
- Christmas Christmas, Mr. Gumdrop.
- Mr. Gumbo.
- Dr. Cream.
- Hell's Angel, Kevin.
- And Caleb Bitts.
- No!
- Evil Elvis.
Happy 2020.
(laughing)
Bye.