You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Oh, ow.
Ah, ouch.
Ugh, Caleb stop.
- No.
- Ow.
- Ugh.
- You don't, you better bring that tushy back over here,
Don't!
Ouch!
Reacting like Mario when he falls into lava.
His butt turns red and you bounce away.
Ouch!
Caleb just gave me a purple nurple.
Yeah, on your, you know what.
On my butt, on your thing.
Why are you so quiet, Caleb?
Because my heart is racing.
My heart has been beating out of my chest for like
like a like a it's exciting to have a
two hours. I didn't realize it was 140 milligrams of caffeine. I thought because it was a tea.
You're dead. You're fucking dead. I drank that yeah that fucking monster I got this morning
I don't know if it leaked in my bag or not I don't know what happened. Oh yeah it was half empty.
It was half full yeah. I feel like I feel like it was like yeah well like because your bag was like
not that wet and also it was still like like you left it on the table for a long time and there was
nothing around it so I feel like it wasn't leaking I feel like it was just like that. Yeah I think it
it just came half full. Because it was it was... Oh, they must have ran out of monster.
Yeah, they ran out at the factory. It was a sugar-free monster but not a zero
ultra. And I haven't seen one of those in months. So why is that the thing?
So you actually think they just ran out halfway through and they're like we're not gonna
make a whole nother batch just to fill this fucking can. No, I think maybe they've discontinued
production of zero sugar monster. And how does that have to do with the half?
- What does it have to do with the thing being half-empty?
- 'Cause I don't know.
- Bitch.
- They discontinued doing it normally
and now they only do it with mistakes.
- They discontinued it.
- It got too expensive.
And it's like, you know how they have a bunch of air
in a chip bag? - It keeps evaporating
in the can.
- Yeah, they just started doing that with drinks now.
- Yeah.
- They're just trying to rip us off.
- Maybe the bodega worker--
- Bodega?
- It wasn't a bodega, it was the worst gas station
of all time.
- That's literally what a bodega is.
(laughing)
- That's true, you know what?
- Yeah.
What if that guy was like siphoning it out?
Yeah, you can't--
- Oh yeah, that was that gas station where we walked in.
- Oh yeah, nothing worked.
- He was like, "Yeah, it's cash only."
And we bought stuff with cash and the ATM didn't work.
And then I tried to buy gas with cash
because the debit card part of it didn't work.
And he was like, "Yeah, that just doesn't work either."
And I was like, "Oh, this place sucks."
And he was like, "Yeah, I know."
(laughing)
"Yeah, I know it sucks."
- This place sucks?
Sucked, he sucked the monster out of the can.
That's why he said he thought you knew.
Maybe all of the drinks in that place are half full.
Yeah, 'cause he keeps drinking all the time.
That's not a bad move.
You mean half empty.
Well, let's not even, no.
Sorry, I don't wanna get into philosophy tonight.
On the podcast.
But I am a Christian.
And Christ always does things half full.
I should just start trying to convert you guys.
Yeah, if you wanna be a real fucking.
I don't want, no, I don't want to have anything to do
with the church.
- You don't wanna go to heaven, see your mommy and daddy?
- No.
- Dude, I believe in the spaghetti monster,
I'm a Rastafarian.
(laughing)
- The only difference between a Pastafarian and Rastafarian
is that Pastafarians think it's flying.
Rastafarians are like, it's just a spaghetti monster.
- Yeah, and it's coming.
- Yeah, and it's right behind you.
(laughing)
- I think the only religion I think I would convert to
is Judaism.
Yeah, I mean that is a funny one to get into.
Just because it would be funny.
It's funny to get into Judaism because like Jews don't even believe in that shit.
They just do it.
Yeah.
Like it's just one of those things you're just born into and you're like, "Yeah, I guess I'm Jewish."
You know?
Yeah, which I mean I respect that more than anything in Christianity.
Yeah, I guess it's like Catholics.
Okay, I think that Catholics make like the best art though, like about being like, like being...
Oh, being tortured?
Yeah, yeah, like make like the exorcist and like that shit.
That's like a religion that anybody who is Catholic is just like
miserable. Oh yeah, my whole fucking family is Irish Catholics. Normal fucking
evangelical, we fucking chop a snake in half, we're done with it. That's it.
That's all we have to do. We don't have to confess anything. And also
compared to Catholics, we're good boys. Yeah. We don't do naughty stuff. The Catholic
Church has done a lot of stuff. Like the most evil thing you can do in an
evangelical church is be a pastor who's secretly gay. Yeah. That's like evil.
And Catholic church that's like... I don't know if that's just an experience I had
growing up because I did... Whoa.
An experience I had growing up.
My aunt worked at a church and every like priest that came through was like
clearly just like a gay guy. Yeah. And I just grew up believing that
all priests. I just thought all gay guys were priests. Yeah I thought all priests were gay
guys because they were like closeted and they had to share. I mean it's kind of the reason
all them. A gay priest is like a Dexter or like a Hannibal Lecter where God recruits
them to take out all the other gay people. Yeah they know how to stop the monster because
it lives in them too. That puff bar sounds crazy in the microphone.
It's like a buzzing sound. I don't get why you're doing puff bars.
Because they're flavored? Is that it? It tastes so good. And I haven't brushed my teeth in two
months. We've already talked about it but I swear to God there's gonna be
like some study about like Jool and like puff bars ruining your teeth and
And they're gonna use me as the example.
- Yeah.
I have strong teeth.
I don't think I've ever had a cavity.
- My family has terrible teeth.
- My teeth are extremely strong.
- I think my dad's missing a tooth.
- My dad, I've never seen my dad brush his teeth,
but he does Listerine like six times a day.
- Okay, that counts.
- So he's just burning that shit off.
- Oh yeah.
- I also think maybe there's a chemical
that they've been dumping into the water
in my hometown for like 40 years.
- Frug?
- No, it's called--
gingivitis. It's called gin X is the name of the chemical. It's a Teflon byproduct
and they've just been done. They only got caught like two years ago and I think it
probably gave me like the strongest teeth ever and like a sane brain cancer.
Yeah, probably I probably I probably honestly beat brain cancer like five
times. Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's it's just there's like the the fucking enamel of
your teeth like growing up like like yeah growing up in your brain and just
stabbing the tumors. It came out like right when like the like Flint water
situation started happening. Yeah. Well that's a different thing because at
least yours gave you superpowers. Well that's a really good point. Yeah. I mean
I may be so good at video games. Yeah. But they just they also don't eat like the
company that they had like some hearing and they were like like what is this and
they were like we we don't know. We don't even know what this is. It's just when we
make Teflon it comes off the side of the like thing and we got to put it
somewhere so we put it in the water. Pretty sick dude. If I was in Flint I
would just drink the water and pretend it's chocolate milk. Yeah I would simply
hold my nose and drink the water how bad can it taste? That's what Obama did. True yeah that is the
funniest shit. Yeah looking back like that that is like just one of the most
like asshole fucking moves. Yeah just dribbling it down your shoulder yeah yeah on your face.
Yeah, oh man, that's the best water ever
Pouring it into the dog's mouth
I finished all my water
Can I have ice cream now
Yeah, I mean I
Wouldn't drink the Flint water. I'm gonna say it. I
If I was president at that situation that moment, what would you have done? I would have told I would have said
About this crap. I would have played in it. Yeah, I need to get we need to put a Brita filter on it
Why didn't they just put a Brita filter in the water system? Yeah, I would have told them to just move to another state or town
Yeah, I would have told him that before that shit. Yeah, it's so crazy. Did all the fucking people that now that are like
like cuz Flint was like
Flint turned Republican or something like that or Flint was like Republican
everyone's like I don't want to hear you bitching about your water. Enjoy that water.
And then it was... They probably voted Republican because they've lead in their brains.
Right. Yeah. It wasn't it also that like it was red and then like everyone yelled
it like did that and then like the rest of the votes were counted and it turned
blue. Oh yeah that too. It's just how fast those people just fucking overreact to be like you're a piece of shit.
deserve every bad thing that happened. Damn you. We're going to send you to
kingdom come. We're going to bore a hole in the center of the United States and
we're gonna put you in the bottom. Yeah I think there is a thing in my hometown
where like people get thyroid cancer at like a crazy high rate. In Flint or your
town? In my town yeah. My town yeah Flint. Your town of Flint? My town of Flint.
North Carolina? Yeah. I don't even know if they stopped but dumping it in
the water that's the other thing yeah cuz I think it's I think it's legal for some
reason it's one of it's one of the things like oh we forgot to make a law
yeah yeah yeah cuz there's so many little things that they forget to make
laws for cuz it's like all the laws were written back when stuff was written on
like yeah there's a law and southern states there's a law in North Carolina
that like the first Sunday of the month you're allowed to take your wife on the
porch and beat her up yeah like I don't I was told that as a kid and they were
like they just forgot to repeal this one that and slavery yeah I guess I forgot
about that there are still slaves yeah I completely forgot yeah that's great
wasn't it like in the 90s Mississippi like ratified the 13th Amendment or
something like that well some some state I can't remember some state like just
just outlawed slavery as like a punitive thing. You can legally be a slave if
you're in jail. You can be a puny little slave. If you're the little slave alive.
If you're like Stuart Little, you're a slave. We'll let you be one. If you're
sized yeah puny little slave he's not gonna get much done it's the problem no
yeah you think home with it could be hard days work comes out with six beans yeah
he's like I picked all these beans yeah that's all that could fit in my little
car you I mean if you weren't so cute I'd fire you slave go go sleep in your
little RC car in your tiny little shed you know kiss thank you you if you owned
Stuart Little as a slave you would kiss him? Mm-hmm. Okay. I'm not going to pay him, he's a slave! Come on.
Yeah, that's so, I mean, there's so many laws that shouldn't exist. Drunk driving
laws. Agreed. Yeah. Or at least make the limit like something that nobody, like if
you drank that much it would kill you. Mm-hmm. You know? Yeah. Yeah. .08. Yeah, .04.
If you drank .04, that would kill you.
I think it should be based on weight.
And if you're like 600 pounds, you have to-- and also it should be based on beers, not
alcohol content.
Yep.
So if you drink 30-- like if Pat drank like 15 beers, he's still good.
Yeah.
But--
Well, that's 'cause I'm very good at--
It's also-- well, here's the thing.
A cop asks you how many beers you have to have to get really drunk, and then they use that
to base you should have it you should have it like on your phone like you know the
wellness app yeah yeah should you should do like a test the doctor gives you the
test it's it's a but it's a quiz it's a quiz yeah no quiz it's a quiz as soon as
your checkup you can yeah I'm afraid of needles you the pop quizzes him handing
you the questions are the same every time so you can just look up the the multiple
choice answers online - that's really max it out every time yeah but most of it's
about like what kind of movies you like and then just extrapolate based on that
yeah it's one of those how many episodes of law and order it's like a sleep
watch yeah it's like a personality test at the beginning of a Nintendo DS game
when they make your character for you yeah I just like change the color your
pants yeah yeah yeah would you live in the forest the an iceberg or a cave or a
blue pants story. Yeah. That's what you sound like every time you hit the puff
bar and that's not a joke and this is the actually a puff bar intervention. Very
awesome. Me and Cameron are intervening on your puff bar addiction. We're
inventing you. I could quit anytime I want. Watch this. Okay. See I just threw it
across it's yeah now I'm going to fetch it
yeah I want to quit Jules so bad there's definitely pee in this yeah you know
that's what gives you a red pee that's what menthol is yeah yeah
it's all is easy mm-hmm yeah I gotta stop let's stop yeah and me and do a
challenge let's fucking know yes no I can't I can't quit right now let's not
every time every time you're right quit every time I've been like oh I'm about
to quit like nicotine I'm like well I can't quit right the thing is I always
so much going on I always quit for one month and then I'm like well I already
quit I might as well just do yeah it's awesome being addicted to stuff oh my
god it's so cool being addicted I miss my pal was addicted to weed that was a
much funnier thing for him to be addicted yeah a couple because I was
trying to quit Juul and the only thing that I could I think I think you should
get into toothpicks or men's penises yeah I think that either one of those would
help you should have like a long penis well I got some good news for you you
should walk around with like a piece of straw in your mouth like a farmer yeah
oh or like a piece of dry spaghetti oh yeah or like one of those one of those
duck call whistles uh-huh a diaphragm I could put a directly there we go I think
honestly what if you walked around and you were like an astronaut helmet yeah
so I couldn't put anything in my mouth no just because it would look have you
tried chewing gum have you ever tried like why can I if I get gum it has to be
sugar-free cuz my teeth are bad you ever tried nicotine gum or the patches I had
nicotine gum when I was 13 did you like that no it tastes weird it tastes really
fucking god never have you ever touched poop with your hands not on purpose
okay have you ever made love on purpose no okay I've always it's always been a
roller skating accident I had a roller skating accident I didn't accidentally
fuck I accidentally made love he's actually so passionate yeah so bad it's
the last time I do that yeah that's the last time I do in lines at fucking
Jellybeans roller rink jelly beans that was the name of the the roller rink in my hometown jelly beans just recently closed down
Unfortunately zone, but do you I did I got so much fucking sex in my brain there
Just looking around. Oh, I forgot. I told you so right. I'll you you're so right that I forgot to turn it off again
Fuck that's just every episode. We record while you guys are here. Yeah, I'm just gonna be like oh
night it'll definitely be one oh yeah I forget it makes noise during the night
yeah I can't hear you all right I can't hear it in my room and it Jana when she
bought it told me that it turns off at night it does not not do that no no so
blame Jana if you want to complain which I know you love doing so go ahead I'm
blaming it or with that no I blame you yeah that's fine you got a good hotel
you guys make plenty of money it's your head I'm fine with you guys going to get
hotel.
Yeah, that's your son.
I wish.
You're annoying fucking kid.
He is only annoying for two seconds every hour.
That's still, that's still annoying.
Still worse than a normal kid.
Yeah.
Normal kid.
Normal kid at least goes to sleep.
Normal kids don't even do anything cool.
True.
Yeah.
Yeah, true.
Normal kid is annoying for 12 hours and then sleep is just dead for 12 hours.
Yeah.
I was just keeping the, oh, it's awake.
It's not, you don't have to look at it.
Oh, I thought you were.
Yeah, you're just keeping your son awake.
I was just keeping the computer awake.
Man, that fucking burrito was so good, but I think it's giving me the hungy sleep.
Hungy sleep?
The itis.
You got the itis?
I got the itis.
Dude, I cannot fucking wait for Thanksgiving and just eat like a fucking donkey.
Oh yeah, dude.
Oh my god, dude.
I'm making some... I'm definitely making brussel sprouts.
I'm gonna get so fucking stupid, I'm gonna make marshmallows.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I'm gonna make like...
Marshmallow sweet potatoes?
No, no.
I'm gonna make s'mores.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, for Thanksgiving.
I'm gonna be like...
Like everybody's gonna be so full of turkey and fucking gravy and I'll be like,
"How about some s'mores? I mean, come on, let's get some cigars in here."
Yeah.
You can light the marshmallows with the cigars.
"Grandpa, you ever had jungle juice?"
We're gonna get grandpa fucking fucked up.
I'm gonna get grandpa fucked up. He's gonna say something inappropriate to my cousin.
I'm gonna clap behind his ears so he has a flashback.
We're gonna get this party started.
I don't have any war grandpas. All of my grandpas were cowards or had a glass eye.
I have a war great uncle. Yeah? Yeah. Does he love it? I'm sure he loved it.
My uncle, I think my uncle went to Iraq. Nice. Just on vacation though. Yeah, exactly his
birthright. I think he was like a medic or something. I don't know anything about that
guy. I would love to be a medic in the army. The thing is, he's a medic in the Air Force.
There's no like, nobody's expecting you to save anybody's life.
So somebody's like, "Medic!"
And then you can just be like, "Oh dude, he's gone."
I gave him water.
I think the funniest type of kid is the kid who like in middle school or high school wants
to be in the army but he wants to be a medic.
Like that shit is, I found one of my favorite.
I've never encountered him in real life but one of the funniest like posts I've ever seen
online is I was like browsing, I was looking through like the Slipknot subreddit because
that's just like a bunch of like, you know, like seventh graders
Yeah, posting like look at this crazy drawing I made and it's
just like a smiley not inspired thoughts. Yeah, exactly. And
there's one where a guy was like, check out my drawing and he
drew one of the like slipknot members and it just looks like
shit. And it's like on a school worksheet that's like a graphic
organizer for an essay and it has this full name at the top
and then it's like the issue I would like to argue is like for
legalized marijuana and like and it's like it's very clear like
it's very clearly like a sixth or seventh grade level like like paper and
then like the comments. So I was like what like wow great job putting your
full you put your full name on this good luck ever getting a job and then he
responded and he was like I don't ever want to get a job. I am going to go
into the Marines and become a combat medic. Oh my God, I think you need a
gummy bro. Just take this if you don't feel anything take two more just so
like the idea that like an employer is gonna look on the Slipknot subreddit and be like
"this guy wanted to legalize weed in sixth grade"
Yeah, uh, sorry buddy, you know, maybe an army medic in Jamaica, but not in America, you
fucking commie.
Yeah.
I can't, the kids that wanted to be in the army when I was in school were like, always
the kids who were like, who just sweat from walking in the hallway.
Yeah.
Oh yeah?
Skinny kids who sweat.
like bigger kids who swell, yeah skinny kids who sweat too.
Yeah, big old fat guys.
There was like this group, this pair of kids
who wanted to be in the army
and one of them had like,
clearly like his dad was in the army or something.
He was giving him like the army haircut
where it's just like the flat on top
but then he shaves the sides down like with a razor.
And he just looks like--
- Like the bottom of a number two pencil.
- Yeah, exactly.
He just looked weird.
He just had like a weird like flat--
- The Marine kid at my school was this giant kid
who was he would just go to people and go like I'm gonna kill you yeah there was a
rumor that he just locked his mom in a closet his mom started that rumor yeah
okay mrs. Johnson and yeah he had like a social worker with a British accent which
is just like that's just such a perfect combo yeah like a giant like marine kid
who's like I'm gonna fucking stab you after school and like all right Greg
like come on come on now and then yeah and then and then that kid like left for
some reason and then that same social worker like I had another kid he was
helping who was just like this like tiny like this is in high school this kid
looked like he was in like fifth grade.
He was just this tiny autistic kid who was obsessed with trains and whenever a
train there was like a train tracks behind the school and whenever a train
went by he would run to the window and then he would turn around he would say
what type of train it was.
Whoa.
Yeah, so sick dude.
He was the best.
I loved him so much.
He's probably it was he held better. Did he see where grades I he might have I
don't know. I mean I didn't really know those kids are freaks. Do you worked at a
medical supply store?
God damn sick. That's the coolest kid alive dude.
Yeah and he had like a really high-pitched voice too. I think he
probably was held back the more I think about it. Or skipped grades. Yeah same you
know what I mean. Yeah.
He was held forward. Yeah he was helped forward. Yeah. Yeah I do remember having
like like my first day of middle school having like a kid who was like eight
years old in our class yeah yeah he was only there for like two weeks and then
his mom pulled him out but he like yeah
that's the beginning of of almost famous cuz it's about like the kid and almost
famous is like he skipped three grades or whatever yeah and they're in the shit
it starts with like him in the shower at school with like all the other kids and
they're like you're you don't even have pubes! You don't have pubes man! Look at our pubes!
You don't have any pubes!
Look at these pubes!
That's such a funny thing to bully somebody for.
Dude I wish I didn't have pubes now man.
I would do anything to have no pubes.
Anything.
You could go get laser surgery.
Except lasers because I'm scared of them.
So scared.
kid who plays the almost famous kid is named Patrick Fugget. Really? F-U-G-I-T.
Yeah. I'm sure it's pronounced Fugit or something. Yeah. I call him Patrick Fugget.
Patrick, when you talk about him? When I talk about him because he's my
close personal friend. Yeah. That's what I say to Patrick after you go to sleep
Caleb. Fugget. Yeah. And I know what you're pointing at. Oh yeah. You. No. It's one of those
I'm not an it. Farting cup things with the slime and you.
Aaron's making me fuck one of those. Aaron's thinking putty. One of those things that are like the it's like a
Chinese finger trap but it's not and it's like goo and it's sparkly. Oh what that
called? It's called the sparkler. It's called a Chinese sparkler. It's endless. I know
what you're talking about. Japanese finger trap. Ooblik? No. No it's it's a it's. If you tried to
fuck oobleck would it go hard or soft on you? I would go hard on it. Yeah, but
that's that's the... If you go hard on it, it will go hard on you. If you punch the
oobleck it's hard. Yeah. What happens if you fuck moonsand? Is it smooth or is it sandy?
You probably get a grain in your pee hole. A greedy disagreement.
oddly satisfying grain of sand and pee hole compilation fits perfectly.
I wish there was just like one thing in real life that had a cartoon sound
effect like if I got a boner really fast I wish you would just make a "boing"
yeah the put like putting down a glass bottle funny and it goes like "boing" you
know what I mean like yeah I've never heard that or like a or like if you hit
also if you hit like a metal water bottle on like the side of a table.
Oh yeah.
That makes me laugh every time.
That's good, yeah.
You know what else makes me laugh every time?
If you hold a spoon under the faucet and the water goes everywhere.
That always gets me.
That is funny.
You know what makes me, I think it's really stupid, but like car horns just make me laugh.
Like if it's like a quick enough car horn.
Especially like a lot of European cars have just like the most sissy horns in the world.
Oh yeah.
Just a short loudish noise is just very funny.
If you're driving a Volkswagen, nobody ever thinks you're mad at them.
It's always just a courtesy honk.
Yeah.
Yeah. It's always just like, "Hey, man, you're wasting your own time here."
Yeah, they're so polite.
That's the problem with the La Cucaracha horn is it just makes people dance.
Exactly.
It's like, "Listen, buddy, if you want me to... My hands are completely off the wheel now."
Look, I'm in front of my car doing the Mexican hat dance now that you've played your La Cucaracha
horn.
yeah and you're like by the way guac and chips and you bend over and they eat
out of your super all right let's do this list baby yeah top 10 reasons why people
don't commit suicide by this an awareness of why the suicide guy by
Paris and mm it's Paris Hilton yeah all right number one because they don't know
how that's a really good point that's I think that's what's kept me from doing
it up until now you can't figure it out I mean just like what is it I mean yeah
I'd love to trust me but how yeah maybe just like jump really hard yeah what
that's a good point can you kill yourself from running too hard you
probably could probably so easy to kill yourself by doing something yeah could
you rip your own head off? Maybe. That was one of those like those it was either
like an essay thread or a 4chan thread that I would like got screenshot and I
would read all the time and like as like a 12 year old be like there's like the
coolest ways to commit suicide and it's like like put like glue your hands to
your head and then like get in like a piano wire noose and then jump off a
building so it looks like you ripped your head off like a bunch of shit like
that yeah I can't remember what that was but but that's definitely the coolest
one that is the coolest one I think yeah because it's not who cares if you rip
your own head off it's about the illusion exactly exactly it's about an
illusionist it's all about tricks yeah yeah that's the thing you fall down if I
saw if I if I was walking down the street and I saw a body on the ground
with with its hands with the hands on its head and the like and the head not
connected to the body I would just think it was a Halloween decoration even if it
was like July I would like oh that's yeah that's a special effect I do this yeah
that's sick I would take a picture with it I don't think the piano wire would be
able to get through the spine though oh no if you jump on you want to try it out
jump if it's long enough this one I don't know that weird spine can't be a
freak guy you know if you get it in the space between the spine connect things
yeah I know a guy who fucking died cuz his spine got fucking cracked in half by
a limo seat I feel like how did you get that he got he was in a limo yes very
fancy I get it is he famous he was the most famous soundboard guy at my church
growing up and he got hit by a semi-truck while he was in a limo well
that's no the seat like cracked his entire body in half that's not getting killed
by a limo seat that's getting killed by a semi truck yeah he didn't touch the semi
truck okay but the semi truck touched the limo i thought you just meant like
you like unreclined the seat too fast and like snapped his body and you know
what maybe that is what happened i don't remember
haha i knew a guy who got killed by a bug yeah
yeah a mosquito that triple e yeah you got killed by a spider triple e
What's that?
It's a mosquito sting.
And what's it called? Electro... no, uh...
It's encephalitis or something.
Yeah, that shit's scary, dude.
Yeah, I knew a kid who got it.
That's like a disease that mosquitoes carry in Massachusetts. It kills like one in every...
like one in... it's like pretty rare, but if you get it, you just like die.
Whoa.
It just like completely fucks you up.
Yeah, my mom scared the shit out of me about that as a kid.
Yeah.
I always wore bug spray.
Yeah, dude, it's scary as fuck.
Yeah.
It's... yeah.
You guys don't have like black widows in mass, do you?
No, we have uh, what's that fucking brown reckless? Yeah, we have those too. Yeah, North Carolina. How you don't you don't have that?
Yeah, they do. Mostly just kills kids though. You have brown poopoos. Yeah, they're actually named cameron and patrick
No, we don't we aren't there. So yeah, you're gonna be you're gonna be in you're gonna be in a world of pain
No, I won't. Oh, yeah, you will I will not
Do you want to go? No, let's just fucking fight. No. Yes, I win
I'm gonna bring back Fight Club. You better not. Oh my god. Yeah, the first time that we met up to
record a bunch of episodes a couple months ago, I just kept trying to fight Patrick. That's true.
And I beat him every time. It's Fight Club, dude. Yeah. Yeah. I got some good hits on you. You did.
I really wasn't happy. Yeah. You were very scared. I hit your arm quite a few times. We kept telling
you to go inside and you were too afraid to go inside. I was. He wouldn't even open the door
Yorkie thought when he turned his back to us that we'd start beating up on him.
And you were very correct.
Yeah, you were right.
Yeah.
Number two, because they are happy with their life.
That's a good point.
I think people still do it.
Yeah.
You know.
If they're happy.
I'm too happy.
I love things too much.
I've never been sad in my life, so I don't understand true happiness.
I have nothing to compare it to.
I have to kill myself, the saddest thing of all time, so I can finally understand how happy
I am.
I have to do a Squidward suicide.
Don't even fucking start, dude.
I have to make my eyes go real hyper-realistic.
My friend's mom did Squidward suicide.
Who was like the first person you guys knew who like had killed themselves?
I don't think I've known anyone, like nobody I've been close to has died from suicide.
I know of people, yeah, like people at my school and shit, but like no one I like knew
None of my friends, like while I was growing up, but I did this lady from my church, she
like one day she just like fucking got the kids in the car, drove them to school, went
home and hung herself.
My God, dude.
And then there was like, didn't leave a note or anything.
Oh man.
And I was like, you know, his dad was fucking, I don't want to accuse him on the podcast,
but he killed his wife.
Yeah, definitely.
I mean, yeah, it could be.
There was one of my neighbors growing up,
like my senior year of high school,
we didn't hear from him for like two weeks.
And then I guess he had like gone hiking
and then like it was like, it looked like a hiking accident,
but then they found like a note in his house.
Well, that's the funniest thing though.
His notes said, "I am going hiking.
"I am going to have fun."
I will love the trail.
I love hiking.
The funniest move is every time you go hiking
somewhere that you know there's like bears and like things that can kill you
right a suicide. No yeah, and if you get mauled to death and eaten by a bear,
it's like the coolest yeah, people are like suicide. It'll be like oh that
pussy got a oh shit. He did on purpose. Yeah, that's a beast damn. This guy
damn yeah guys fucking dude imagine on this that's so yeah being like I want to
kill myself and just walking to it like grabbing a bear cub just covered in
honey.
Hey bear showing your asshole over some reason
excuse hey mr. B over all yours I'm gonna naughty little be just what just
hiking around wearing a wig and going yeah dude that's I'm gonna I'm gonna
cuz they're still mad at Goldilocks I'm gonna kill myself by walking into a
gorilla enclosure dress like Marilyn Monroe yeah I'm just gonna be like hello
hello mr. president like Empire State Building yeah yeah miniature you'd have
to bring an Empire State Building with you and it's the only problem. That is
tough it's a pretty big building. Yeah. Some might say the biggest. I've never
seen it. Really? Yeah you have. I brought you there on our elf tour. What? Remember
we toured everything from the movie Elf? No. You can't tell me you don't remember
this. I don't remember the elf tour. No, we went to the North Pole, walked through Canada.
no no we went to that one coffee shop where he goes inside and he says
congratulations on having the world's greatest coffee you don't know we went
into the shower and we watched the shower shower and then I forgot I forgot
that's a part of that movie is him spying on a woman in the shower he
doesn't understand look at her yeah he doesn't know creep that's my god
and he enjoys her music. Don't tell me you've never done that.
Don't tell me you've never snuck into the girls locker room to enjoy the music.
Some girls fucking singing Beat King and you're like I know this song.
Yeah, what's Beat King? He's a rapper.
Sing it. Club God, baby pop that pussy.
Something like that. Yeah, just joining in.
can't sing in Little John number three because somebody sent a threat to kill
them if they did commit suicide this is kind of a joke and yeah I think this is
kind of just like a prank yeah yeah that wouldn't work on me I'd simply know
River clan rocks comments that's ironic because if they committed suicide they
would already be dead you only die twice I don't know do you know who's trying to
riff that comment out as they write it yeah you know straight up I'm not even
thinking right now but maybe you would you could die twice who knows though
knows though real yeah I mean P for real - P how to save an idiot's life 101 damn
him hey Pat if you kill it if you commit suicide I'll totally kill you yeah maybe
I think that's a bad deal no it's not a deal it's a threat just say yes
no it's like if you if you ever set foot in this town again I'll fucking kill you
you know I don't know if I like that deal what do I get out of that number
Maybe like a jawbreaker number four because they don't want to
Yeah, that's number one I simply just don't want to yeah, yeah, you know, yeah
I'm bored
Dude, I don't I don't want to fucking go through this a lot of rigmarole when it comes on yourself, dude
Yeah, really is. Yeah, people get mad at you people get mad at you. You're on the news now
Yeah, you know, that's the thing. Yeah, your size don't go on the news
Well most I mean not mine will it goes on like that.
I bet you anything they cover what I'm about to do.
Yeah it's a dark episode we should we should make sure all the jokes are light.
Okay sing a silly song.
I'm gonna kill myself.
There we go.
I'm gonna kill myself
I wanna die
Girl let me stretch that pussy out
I'm gonna kill myself
Your pussy make me kill myself
Your pussy smells like egg salad
It makes me wanna kill myself
I'm gonna wear your pussy like a basketball jersey
I love the weekend so much
Dude he loves eating pussy
And this guy has to be the only man in the world who likes eating pussy.
Stuff is like candy to him.
Yeah.
What if he has one of those people where his like taste buds are all fucked up so he tastes
like the, you know, an armpit taste of a pussy and he tastes barbecue sauce, you know?
And he's like, "Oh yeah, swag!"
And nobody finds out until he starts singing, "And her pussy tastes like ribs!"
(laughter)
- I was like, hold on.
- Pussy's like ribs, I'm like bubble gum, but ribs?
- Yeah.
- You know those, have you seen those videos of--
- Little pussy tastes like beer.
(laughter)
- People who get like, it's like,
hey I'm COVID positive, so I'm gonna eat
like a bunch of disgusting food.
'Cause like the taste buds are gone.
- Taste buds glee?
- Yeah, you can't taste anything.
- How do you lose your sense of taste and smell?
- For how long?
- For the duration?
Well, then some people say they can't taste for like a month after.
Yeah.
Did the people that you know have that sensation?
I don't, I think so.
Yeah.
It said, they said that everything tastes like salt.
I just eat poop, dude. Fuck it.
Yeah.
Yeah, dude. You can make so much money in one week making videos of you eating poop.
Yeah. People will eat like a whole onion when they have COVID.
Just like, yeah, just like, yeah, you get COVID and you go to the hospital and they're like,
"Oh, so we're also gonna have to pump your stomach from poop."
Yeah.
You're filled with poop. I forgot about that. I didn't realize that COVID makes you lose your
sense of taste. I just thought a fairy blessed me in my sleep. It's a living, dude. Sir,
from the looks of this, your stomach hasn't digested this poop for two weeks and you got
COVID last week. I have delicious poop. What can I say? What can I say? I like poop. You want me
me to apologize I want me to apologize for my diet fuck you fuck you I'm going to
the other hospital since I don't animal hospital since I haven't had it now I
don't think I'm gonna get it I think it's probably impossible I think I might
be the only there's gotta be some people who are immune to it I think the cures
in my blood yeah I think they probably need to check cuz I mean there's people
who are immune to like chicken pox and shit yeah not me buddy I had a terrible
time with chicken pox I never got it my face got stuck to a pillow either well
And my friend came over and we watched Click and we both started crying during Click and
I made fun of him for crying, even though I was also crying, but I blamed it on Chicken
Pox.
It's crazy how they would have Chicken Pox parties to get all the kids immune to it.
Crazy those poor kids.
They tried that with COVID and it did not work.
Yeah, it did not.
Remember like the beginning in like March when it first hit the states?
Yeah.
And everyone was like, "Yeah, we're having it."
Like it was a COVID party in Kentucky.
Yeah.
It was crazy.
Crazy.
Crazy world.
Number five, "Because it is hard to."
Suicide is hard to do.
That's the song now.
Both of these comments are really depressing.
I'm not going to read either of them.
Really?
Yeah.
This is a fucking depressing list.
No, it's reasons people don't commit suicide.
This is one of the most joyous lists we've done.
Yeah, that's true.
I do want to read these just to myself.
Okay, well we'll give Caleb 10 minutes to read these.
We'll give Caleb a minute to cry.
Guys, I love you guys.
(Laughter)
Just taking one look at him and going...
(Screaming)
Oh, geez.
He tried to kill himself.
(Screaming)
I feel like it can't be that hard.
What, killing yourself?
People kill themselves by accident.
All you have to do, you literally just have to sit in the car.
That's it.
That's all you have to do. You can literally play Gameboy until you die. Yeah. You know. Yeah.
Yeah. Unless you're really like Michael Phelps, hard time killing himself in the
car. Yeah. Hold his breath forever. Oh that's true. Yeah. Because he could swim out of the
car. That's right. He can swim out of any situation. Yeah. That's a really good point I'm
making right now. Yeah. So smart. I should have my own podcast just me where I say
smart stuff. Yeah. What would it be called? Caleb's Corner. Caleb's Corner. 2Ks. No
spin zone yeah be called the no because a no bins why is it called the no spin zone
because he doesn't because Bill O'Reilly he doesn't spit anything except his penis
in a dressing room towards his intern's it yeah he says welcome to the spin zone
helicopters is exactly yeah yeah and he did that and that's actually a fact
that's true he did that to me yeah it's funny my grandma every every year she
would give me a new Bill O'Reilly book when I was a kid never arguing with
idiots? No, I just hid guns in them. Yeah. Yeah, just fucking cut out the pages.
Yeah. I think I tried to do that. I think I did, actually I did when I was a
freshman in high school, I did try to take my mom's copy of Arguing with
Idiots and hollow it out so I could hide my weed in it. By who you said? Glenn Beck.
Glenn Beck, nice. Arguing with Idiots. Well that's a bad choice, she's gonna be reading that every day.
Exactly, yeah. She's gonna have to read it to argue with me. It's funny that Neil in college was
like, you know what would be awesome? I'm gonna make a hollowed out book and hide my weed in it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
always fuck it up and they say action figures are dolls. Incorrect dude.
They're simulations. Yeah. They're simulators. They're simulations of the human male form.
Yeah. Okay. I'm learning about my own body through theirs. Yeah. I mean this it's on
the same it's it's the same thing as as if you had like a medical skeleton that
you could learn from. That you could make fight the devil. Yeah. Yeah. Exactly.
Which is what I always did. Yeah it's like if you had the devil in your skeleton.
Well, that's that's pretty scary. Yeah, I'm afraid of the devil why?
He's got a big red ass
His horns look sharp. Yeah, big bouncy red ass. He's gonna bounce it on me, dude
Yeah, I'm afraid the devil's gonna fart is gonna have a little bit of fire. He's got two giant Super Bowls back there
Yeah, he's gonna he's gonna hit my head with him like a jackhammer
Do you think the devil has a big penis or a small penis?
That's small but smart the arrowtail is his penis. It just goes backwards cuz he's the devil. Yeah
Everything's backwards on this guy. Yeah. Yeah his legs cuz he's got goat legs. Yeah, so let's go back. We're right and wrong
That's right. That's right
I guess that would be my biggest fear with with committing suicide is just knowing you go to hell. Yeah. Yeah
You what if what if you go to like what if you get to hang out in the what if you don't go to hell?
That was the funniest thing like growing up like super Christian is anytime someone in our town like killed themselves
like a friend's like parent or whatever my mom be like oh that's so sad
especially that they're in hell now yeah yeah yeah that rules yeah there's a
family that's like irreparably broken forever yeah I'm so sorry that your dad
chose to go to hell so sorry decided to punch his dad out really yeah your dad
went down the highway the hell I'm so sorry you went down I-40 until he got to
hell. Oh my god perfect timing. Number seven, because it is a serious sin. Mm-hmm
that's right yeah. I don't know if it is. It's not. No it's actually it's cool.
Yeah it's just you want to get closer to God. Exactly. But you don't get closer. You
do get closer to God. I don't know I don't really know what the biblical
argument for it being a sin is. It's because it's you're supposed to die when
God tells you. What if God is telling you through the radio, "Kill yourself right now, I'm God."
That's true. Yeah. Yeah. It's taking God's will into your own hands. Yeah.
Which you're supposed to-- I know that God-- If somebody gets cancer or somebody gets
anything like that, it's God telling them. It's God's plan. I know God has a plan,
but Shop O' Trap House is telling me to do something completely different.
Yeah, they're sending mixed signals here.
You want me to fucking vote or do you want me to kill myself?
Yeah.
And what do I do when I get the C4 on the bus?
I'm waiting.
Yeah.
Sorry, I'm not going to make it to the party.
I'm waiting till midnight for the new Choppa episode to come out so I get my new instructions.
We're just kidding.
Yeah.
We're not.
Number eight.
Wait, one of the comments here says, "I'm baptized and I want to go to heaven, but I would go to hell instead."
That's not... I would just do it. Yeah, I would go to hell. I don't want to, but I would.
The coolest people are in hell, dude. Yeah. The pedophiles, the... Ray Romano. Ray Romano.
All of Caleb's friends' dads. All my friends' dads killed themselves, or had cancer,
got shot in drug deals they're pretty cool dude dad goes to the one who had
cancer here's this is pretty cool he used to eat a potato every day like an
apple yeah yeah a baked potato or like a completely raw he thought it would cure
his cancer and he died way faster yeah yeah so growing up a potato then he had
he got potato cancer yeah yeah potato started growing in his brain yeah yeah
The Irish and stuff started growing out.
Number eight, because they could listen to some brutal metal songs to let out their anger.
But doesn't the brutal metal tell you to kill yourself?
Yeah.
Isn't that the whole argument about Judas Priest?
Also like, it's definitely, yeah, the kids who want to commit suicide, the people who
want to commit suicide, they're angry.
That's the problem.
They're really mad.
I'm so stinky, man.
I could kill myself.
I'm so angry.
I could, yeah.
I'm so mad I could sit in my car for an hour and leave it running.
Yeah.
most angry acts you could ever do. That carne asada took me out. Yeah? Yeah. You just had
a yerba mate, brother. I had a yerba mate and I took a nap. Yeah. You had a you're so
so gay. Come on. Let's fucking go yeah! You have a weak mind. I do. I've been getting
tired a lot recently. I didn't mean that. I've been getting tired a lot recently. I'm
I'm worried it's cancer.
- You think it's cancer?
- It would be funny if it was.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, just the worst.
- Yeah, it'd be funny if you had cancer.
- It would be very funny to me.
- Maybe get those Patreon numbers up though.
(laughing)
- Oh, oh my God, Patrick, what's that?
- I see it on right now.
- Oh no, my tumor's literally growing.
- Oh, dude, whoa.
- I think the only thing that'll change it,
I mean, let's just say $20,000 a month, right?
I mean, that's how much cancer, here's the problem.
Healthcare in this country. Oh my god fucked. Yeah, but telethons have been going down and we need
Look, the problem is that there's not enough telethons, I think
Yeah, I think we could fix health care immediately. We should have a telephone phones
We should just do a instead of a patreon we do a daily telethon. Uh-huh, but the tell us that we don't even do the podcast
Anymore, we just do a telethon every day. Let's just become like megachurch guys. Yeah easy
That guy yeah, he just stood there and laughed that was so sick
I know that the guy's like video media says Joe Biden's president. Ha ha ha
He just does that for like two full minutes did whenever pastors got political growing up is so fucking. Oh, yeah
Dude, do you know our pastor would be like be like?
You know what you're talking about TV pastors. No no like in my church
Yeah, be like and the elections coming up this week and just remember
I mean the candidates whoever you're choosing to support one of them is you know very possibly a
Vehicle for Satan to move through and the others Mitt Romney, but whichever one you choose to support
I trust that God's helping you make that decision like to fucking swag dude. Yeah, I
Can't imagine being like a an evangelical wanting to vote for a Mormon
Did it was the worst decision they've ever had to make yeah?
Yeah. Because it's like everybody, all evangelicals think Catholics and Mormons
and Jews and anybody who's just a different version of them is going to
hell. Yeah. And so they were like, "We gotta vote for a Mormon." I don't think a Mormon could ever hold
office. No, do you? I think that Mitt Romney has held a lot of offices. I mean the
office of the president. Okay, was that? Because then we would all-- I can't swear.
Yeah, can't swear and we would all have to wear those pajamas and those
underwear yeah make Mormonism the state really would think so yeah be sick if we
got a more if we got a Mormon president and he like immediately just kills just
like diverted a bunch of money into NASA and we're like we're gonna find Kolob
yeah we're gonna go to the throne of my first second and third ladies
dude it's crazy how much Mormons hate Native Americans oh yeah that's a pretty
that's a black people too dude yeah that's yeah they only recently yeah they
only like in the past like few decades have let black people yeah there's like
old like fit Mormon like educational film strips where it's like they turn
like a black person white yeah yeah they say that like black people are like if
you if you sinned in a past life you like reincarnate as a black woman they're
They're like Islam where they have like an Ayatollah kind of person who talks to...
No, no, they have like the current president of the Mormon Church supposedly is still getting information from God.
Yeah, and they send all the same sermons to every church. Like they all do the same shit.
It's wild, dude.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's pretty sick.
Mormonism is crazy. It's so sick.
I know they have like a pole or something that's supposed to face a certain place.
So maybe yeah, the North Pole just advanced Islam. Yeah, dude
Yeah, and they have that shit where if you die you reincarnate as a planet and all your wives live on you as slaves
Yeah, that's one of their beliefs and the celestial kingdom the
Beauty tonight tell you that much. It's really sick dude. Yeah, they have a bunch of planet. They believe in planets. Yeah psychos. Yeah
Such a weird fucking and they're too polite
Well, that's the other thing is I like the nicest people in the world. Yeah
yeah most polite people on earth yeah yeah and funny and hot mm-hmm and really
smart yeah and correct mm-hmm one of the more not converting next week one of the
Mormon kids I knew in high school instead of swearing he would go so we go
he would just always go what duck didn't Mitt Romney live in your town yeah yeah
Mitt Romney was gonna hold a victory party uses was he I don't know think so
he was something he has a house I one of his like grandchildren or like some like
Like some relation went to my high school like a few years off of me.
That's bizarre man.
It's weird that guy being involved in Massachusetts.
He was going to hold a victory party in my town but then he didn't.
Yeah I think he was the Massachusetts governor or like one of the senators or some shit.
I don't fucking know dude.
I don't keep track of shit like that.
That was where his like Romney, the like mass health thing, like Romney started that as like
and that's how he got so owned for being like the creator of Obamacare or whatever from like
the right yeah pretty sick dude. That's nuts. Yeah he's a beast he's I mean he's a
sexy beast yeah yeah. Number nine because they want to see where life takes them.
Yeah yeah. Life has led me to Mormonism. Yeah I don't care where it takes me as long as I'm visible.
I just um when I was in in Edinburgh visiting Aaron he went to Mormon Church
one morning because he was like it's just like it was like yeah I want to see if
they can convince me. Oh yeah, you were telling me about that. We started going
that we like he was like come on you should come with me I'm gonna go to
Mormon Church and we're like okay and it was like pouring out and we like went to
we couldn't find it yeah and then like me and Leo. All the Mormon churches look the same.
Yeah me and Leo were just like oh fuck this we're just gonna go like to a cafe
and Aaron's like nope I'm I'm gonna find this place and he just went to the
Mormon Church alone. Dude we were like I was like maybe I was maybe one full month
off of converting to Judaism in high school. I had a Jewish girlfriend who I
would go to a temple with her and I was like, "This fucking rules, dude!" It was like
people were dancing and they're blowing like a fucking horn and shit and I was
like, "This is beast!" Yeah. Yeah and then she was a... she was a whore.
Which will really... We'll see that. Yeah, so that changed my opinion on that religion forever.
I do this weird thing where I let one person decide for the whole group of people.
Number ten because they fear death.
Oh.
Number eleven because they are famous.
No famous person has ever killed themself.
I was thinking of killing myself.
But I was like, nah.
Nah, man, I'm famous.
I'm fucking famous.
I can fuck anybody I want, dude.
I can go down the street and start fucking.
Fuck this.
I'll just do all these drugs at the same time instead.
Yeah.
That's what they end up doing.
And then you end up with like My Man Juice World or My Man Little Peep.
Can you imagine just, yeah, jumping off a building and midair being like, "Oh shit,
wait I'm famous."
Oh man.
Because people are recognizing you as you fall.
Yeah, they're pointing out the window.
"Oh shit, that's Jim Morrison!"
It's Eric Clapton's son.
(laughter)
- Why is he killing himself?
He's the most famous kid in the world.
- He's got so much to do.
- He's got so much to live for.
- He has that great song that's being written
about him right now.
- What if Eric Clapton was writing Tears in Heaven?
- Eric Clapton wrote the song and he was like,
oh I need something for this to be about.
- Or he was writing it and then his kid,
like he was writing it on the balcony
and his son like crawled up to him and started like,
he hit like the string on his guitar
and just pushed it out the window.
Oh shit, what did I just do? Wait a minute. Or it was like, because his kid was like a
baby and he's slowly crawling from the living room into the window to fall out
and Eric's like, "Oh my god, no, he's gonna fall out the window. I should write a
song about this." He finishes it as he falls out. Eric Clapton was like really stuck on
writing the lyrics for his song my son is alive
number 12 because they're stupid I would love to kill myself but I'm just so
goddamn stupid
I'm so stinking stupid I can't even kill myself right
I got this bucket on my head I can't get it off
number 13 because it may fail.
Yeah, and if it fails, then you're a failure and you'll just want to kill yourself.
Shoot for the moon, even if you fail, you'll land among the stars.
I don't think there's any stars between us and the moon.
But if you miss, you keep going.
Oh, that's a good point.
So you're not falling short, you're overshooting it.
Shoot for the moon.
You just miss. I didn't say fall short.
Shoot for the moon because if you miss you're gonna just keep going.
If you miss you could maybe go to another planet's moon.
I think that's the scariest, that's the like indicative of how afraid I am of just like being
bored is that the scariest way to die to me is like you're in a spacesuit and like you can you
can live for a while but you're just like floating through space forever no books no video games.
For me I think the scariest way to die would be if a Dracula jump out.
number these are number 14 days of them are just repeating they don't want to
rot in the ground what this are you gonna get cremated cremated maybe yeah
sure I'm gonna get remade it yeah they're gonna make my body new again
yeah you know put you in a new suit I'm gonna get cream pie as your mother's
lawyer you have to go through with her every last dying wish so look it says
I was of sound mind when yeah so someone's gonna have to cream but I'm not
sand it's one of the kids yeah somebody's gonna have to do it look all right she
was a sound mind around here she was a sound mind and wet ass pussy dude
fucking getting in that bitch she's dead she would just get burned up into ashes
okay she wouldn't she would but she'd she wanted to be cremated and then
cream-pied yeah turned into like sort of a like when you huck a loogie into sand
kind of that kind of consistency. Like a ball. This is moon sand. That's how you make moon sand.
You see that there? Every container of moon sand has a mother's soul inside it that makes it stay together.
You see that kind of lumpy, you see that lumpy? The strongest thing in the world.
The strongest thing in the world is a dead mother's soul who was cream-pied and then burned to a crisp.
You see that lumpy kind of clay-ish textured mound on the mantle? That's your grandma.
And it's also some of her boyfriend Ricardo. He's in there too quite a bit.
Yeah, you see that, you see that, that crumpled Playboy magazine with gray stains on it?
Yep, that's your mom.
That's grandma.
Number 17, because they are rich.
If I was rich, I think I would just kill myself in the richest way possible.
Which is?
Choking on caviar.
It's true.
I would say choking on platinum.
If you're like really rich, you might as well hire a hitman on yourself.
You could hire a hitman that you have to try and you can spend the rest of your life trying
to escape him.
Yeah.
Give him like a billion dollars and then just have him, he'll get you eventually.
I really hope that there's been a thing in the past where a guy tries to hire two hitmen
to kill each other and just like watches it play out.
Like I really hope that's actually happened.
You know what I mean?
You're gonna love this movie Mr. and Mrs. Smith.
Yeah.
I just mean I hope that's happened.
They had to make a rule in the...
Well, all the hitmen know each other.
It's like plumbers.
Yeah.
They're all in a union.
Yeah, exactly.
They're all in big fucking overalls.
Local 66 and fucking...
Yeah.
I've been a fucking hitman since like '72 or something like that.
Yeah, I've been doing this for a while.
Do you think there's like hitmen scabs?
Yeah.
fuck it up every time yeah yeah I've been doing this for a couple years my father
did it he fucking he died accidentally choking on ricin that's just a Freemasons
now yeah yeah that's what you're talking about now yeah goddamn you Freemasons
those guys are freaks having the in Boston having the Freemasons building
next to the homeless shelter is a really poor city plan yeah and then they made
And then they make yeah true. They're just farming those guys. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, they're just practicing on them, you know
He's fucking because I did get the Freemasons just pick up homeless guys like from the alley outside of the the shelter
Like how people pick up like grease from McDonald's. Yeah, like a car
No, the I got I got confronted for wearing
I think I've talked about this but I got confronted in front of the Freemason building because I was wearing a Krampus sweater and
It was a man who's like very clearly schizophrenic saw the the Krampus shirt free mason thing pointed at me and asked me about
Baphomet and I was like hey, man, that's the question
Yeah, it was very weird
So I miss all those guys. Yeah, I miss all my homies from the old hood
Real shit. Yeah. All right, and finally death is depressing
sensitivity to suicide I just wasn't aware of. Yeah I've not been depressed once this
episode we didn't even say anything bad. It's just the word suicide is depressing. I think
you're just full. Yeah. We should show an Adam song. I think that Venice Weyland food is uh
yeah I'm already. You got depressed from fucking carne asada. Whoops. You know what carne asada
translates to in English? Day of the dead. Yeah which is really sad. Yeah one of the
saddest days.
Alright, I have to go peepee.
Yeah, we gotta plug all that stuff.
What?
The Patreon, the Minecraft server.
Oh yeah, listen to the Patreon and listen to the Minecraft server.
And the Discord, and the T-shirt, and the Twitch stream.
And the Twitch stream.
And Cameron.
Patrick's asshole.
What?
Oh!
and the t-shirt and the twitch stream and the twitch stream and and
and Cameron's asshole