You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Congratulations Donald Trump,
45th President of the United States all over again.
- Congratulations on having a wet diaper.
- Whoa.
- Can we just get, listen, it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter what you're,
we just have to celebrate it right at the beginning.
please put the divisive political bull crap yeah i don't think it's a good
thing i don't know that i was an accident
i had you before my accident
i'd read the ballot upside down
yet about and and you're not you're the only one of the down is donald trump and
donald trump of that and it will know he thought he was voting for permits
did
glenn old
plan old permit and i thought that maybe i'd gotten a ballot in a different
language voting for the and the president of russia amazing dude yeah this is huge
man donald trump is the president again officially officially yeah it's official
real quick we should we should specify that we actually don't know we're
recording this the day before yeah so I guess we'll have to say this at the
beginning of both episodes but yeah we're recording on on election Tuesday
Erection Tuesday as I like to call it because I'm a sexual freak.
What the hell?
We don't know who's gonna win so we're recording two episodes you just listen to whichever one.
Don't listen to the other one because we're gonna sound like idiots.
It's not gonna make any sense.
Whoever won listen to that one and whoever didn't win don't listen to that one.
Or wait until they win maybe next year.
Yeah.
And then try it then.
The next election in 2021.
You just save it.
you just save it you can it's like a it's like a present episode maybe we should do
a Hillary Clinton episode - maybe the right me that's a good idea enough that
she wins yeah we should do a spongebob episode - just in case dude I feel
never know yeah you feel like drink cuz you're moving to Canada you're moving to
the six if Trump wins I'm because I'm moving to the Trump did when that's
right I'm gonna sit yeah I'm moving to the six sorry I'm gonna sit in my hotel
I'm gonna sit in my hotel room like Drake wondering if someone is gonna kill me.
I'm gonna sit in Marvin's room.
Yeah I'm in Marvin's room.
Do you want to kill me or you want to kiss me?
I heard that because Donald Trump just won the election they're changing the name of
Marvin's room to Donald's room on the album.
Where do Canadians move if Trump wins?
Into the ocean.
Yeah.
We have to push them up.
They go up higher.
Yeah we push them north into the-
it's a site so people from South America go up to Mexico and then people from
Mexico go up to North America. Wait, if Trump wins people from Mexico go to the US.
Wait, we get Canada if he wins? What do you mean if he wins? Oh he won, we get Canada?
This is a hard concept to record. I know.
It's so confusing.
We should record more stuff for the future.
Yeah.
Oh my god, I'm 30 years old today.
Oh wow.
This is huge, dude.
My 30th birthday.
I got so bald.
No, you gained your hair back when Trump won.
I gained all my chest hair.
It migrated.
Nose.
Everything's going north.
Your pubes went into your mouth and they're on your tongue.
Yeah, but now I can just taste shit better.
Everything goes north when Biden, because Trump won, because if Biden had won everything would
have gone south real fast.
Would you, you think that you would be able to taste more stuff if you had hair on your
tongue?
A taste bud is just a little piece of hair.
Is that true?
Yeah.
Oh my god dude.
Taste buds are hair on most animals.
How do you think they taste things?
Wait, can you guys taste them?
You think they're nothing dude?
You don't think they're anything?
I mean I honestly thought they were holes.
- I thought they were holes.
- I think they're their hair, okay?
- I thought they were holes that different flavors
went into and it like locked it in.
- They can fall in.
- Yeah, they fall.
The flavors fall into the holes.
- Like a pachinko.
- That's where the flavors fall.
- Yeah, and so like every food is like a pie chart
of like a percentage of different flavors.
- Yeah.
- And then different ones go into your mouth.
- Well, each food is a different shape on the flavor level.
So like the sweet foods are triangles
and they fall into your triangle holes.
- And they go into triangle holes.
- Exactly, yeah.
- Which turns on in your brain,
you think this is sweet like candy.
- Yeah, exactly.
- The sour ones are shaped like a lemon.
That's a coincidence.
That wasn't the-- - True.
- That came before the lemon. - It's just a circle.
- It's just, no, it has--
- But if you-- - It has a lemon shape
on both ends. - If you move it,
if you move it, yeah, no, 'cause if you move it this way--
- No, it's 2D like a Flintstones vitamin.
It's not a 3D shape. - It's not a sliced lemon.
- A sliced lemon is a circle.
- I think that's, it's a full lemon from the side.
- Well, sometimes a sliced lemon is a wedge.
So I feel like we really do need to make the distinction.
But that science has already made the distinction. This is I'm not make I'm saying for Caleb. I'm saying it for Caleb
Caleb you know if you ever looked at a lemon from the side
No
Come on dude you fucking piece of shit. Oh my god. I hate that was all
Brilliant Frank are we even recording this
No, I turned it off a couple minutes ago.
We don't have a podcast.
Are you just fucking making fun of me, dude?
Yeah.
My life sucks.
Me and Patrick have been paying $6,000 into the Patreon per month just to pretend that
we have a podcast so we could get you for that.
Really?
Yep.
We're actually rich.
It was all leading up to this.
All right, well I guess we're done.
Yep.
That's it.
That's the final episode.
Unless you guys have something to admit, I'm going to stop recording.
you just want to talk with your friends and record it if you want to listen later?
Yeah, yeah, no I guess I do want to talk about Donald Trump being the president with my friends.
Let's go!
I'm- art is gonna get so good.
Punk, punk music- punk music is gonna be so good under-
This is gonna be the best four years for punk.
This is gonna be the best four years ever because I love punk music.
Uh huh.
Yeah, I'm a rock and roll punk.
I'm a rock and roll punk.
I'm a hardcore punk.
Dude, comedy's gonna be insanely good again.
Oh my god.
Yeah, just another- another fucking four years of Trump.
See because the past couple of months comedy has just been about voting and now today's
the day to do a joke vote because all these comedians were telling me to vote and I want
to impress them and I'm trying to do a yes and thing.
I can finally post a picture.
I'm writing in a funny vote.
I'm writing in Drew Carey.
Or I mean yesterday was the day.
This is so hard for- how stupid are we that we can't just pretend it's tomorrow right
now?
It's so difficult.
We fucking suck at this dude.
We can get it in the next half.
We'll get it in the next half.
We'll get it in the alternate universe.
We'll figure it out.
In the alternate universe.
That's a different version of today.
Trump's the president today. Everything's topsy-turvy, upside down.
Oh yeah.
No, I'm under so much stress right now.
Yeah, dude. I'm fuckin' so afraid.
Oh my God.
I'm afraid what's gonna happen to me.
Dude, all the Biden thugs are gonna do
violence in the series.
antifa did all the all the yeah did all the fun my god militant the second day
is second day announced it all shoot me in the head the second day announced it
all the people all the ponytail all the flower shop owners started running out
in the streets do you guys remember that all of the librarians were throwing rocks
yeah the pedophiles are flooding the streets and destroying cars it's a nightmare oh my god
I wish Biden did because then we wouldn't have to deal with all of these Antifa thugs that
we're dealing with right now. I'm fearing, I'm cowering in fear. I'm being wedged right now by
Antifa as we speak. There are a hundred guys who look exactly like Finn from Adventure Time and
they're in a circle around my house. Yeah. They're doing Antifa prayers, blood prayers. They're
They're trying to be threatening.
Yeah.
And they're saying, "Hey, we're gonna come in here and we're gonna suck your dick!"
"I'm gonna fuck you!"
"I'm gonna let you fuck me!"
Yeah.
At least now that Trump is the president, there's no violence anymore from any of his
supporters.
None of his supporters are gonna...
None of his supporters were gonna freak out or kill any minority or anything like that.
Honestly, I hope four years in this office changes that man.
Yeah.
I think this is a good opportunity for him to grow and learn.
I cannot wait to see how fucked up he is at the end of his second term.
Like just looking at the difference from him at the beginning of his first term to the
end, to yesterday, and then just imagine like it just continuing to decline at that rate
for another four years.
I really can't wait to see what it does to him.
to be a new virus every year of his turn and he's gonna keep getting it and keep
surviving just by a thread he's just he's gonna just be like the term he's
gonna have like no legs no he's gonna be like just sitting in a big in a big
golden armchair and every time he shifts like a roll of fat lifts up and just
releases another mysterious bacteria that's never been seen by the world it
just yeah floods out in a giant four years he's gonna be flubber it's a
disease made by ham yeah yeah only get it from eating ham yeah honey glaze
nobody's ever eaten enough ham to get to that disease before like eat the bone in
the middle of the ham yeah and it's gonna give him some fucked up fucking like
osmosis this is folks I ate the whole I ate the whole bone I ate the whole bone I
sucked it down very good bone I sucked on it I sucked the marrow out
it was one of the best it was one of the best and I made this horrible disease
with it I made this horrible disease with this bone people are saying that you're
gonna put the real in my mouth and I'm gonna I'm gonna put it in my mouth that
I'm gonna pull that pull it out and it's just gonna be a bone but they're wrong
folks I'm gonna eat the bone too and I'm gonna create a deadly disease that's
gonna destroy the world I'm gonna put only the bone in my mouth the meats
gonna come out completely intact I'm sucking the marrow out of the hole and
and i'm making a new disease
for the middle of the love the hand bone disease delhi
it
that
we have a lot of love putting a whole piece of ham in our mouth and taking it
only the meat and swallowing the bone and creating a disease is completely
sold out everywhere people of people of the greatest and ladies and gentlemen to
say the song about
hand bone disease little pimp
little bit this year
and i'm not talking about the public found the actual little pimp
I was confused.
We have Lil Pimp here and he's gonna sing Lil Pimp.
What's up it's me the Lil Pimp!
I'm here to sing about the hand bone disease!
Oh look at him he's the littlest pimp folks look at him.
What's up?
Look at the littlest pimp.
Isn't he adorable?
He's so small he's like an M&M.
He's like a little M&M.
He's benevolent like a Buddha folks.
I'm the purple M&M.
Oh the Lil Pimp he's a purple M&M and we love him don't we?
- My hat's as big as the rest of my body.
- He's purple because he's blue lives and firefighter lives.
- We love his stovepipe.
We love his stovepipe hat.
- I love the fucking pimp flag, dude.
The thin purple line.
- The thin purple velvet line.
(laughing)
- He's here, he's singing "Ham Bonin' on 'Em."
- I'm ham bonin' on 'em, ham bonin' on 'em.
- He's sucking the bone out of the ham.
No meat is even being touched.
That's just the marrow and the bone.
Meat is murder, isn't it folks?
Meat is murder. It's murder. It's wrong.
We're not allowed to eat meat.
I love seitan now. I love eating seitan. I love eating tofu.
Praise seitan.
Yeah, and then Rachel Maddow, then I say,
Donald Trump says that he loves seitan.
Folks, I think we know what he means.
And then she just goes,
for an hour and a half.
Folks, I love it. I love jackfruit. You can turn it into pulled pork.
[laughter]
You can make it a pulled pork. It's fine.
It's just as good. It's a little bit sweeter. If you like sweeter things,
this is perfect for your pulled pork.
Get slow cooking.
Donald Trump is accidentally eating one bone and then just being like,
"It was on purpose, actually. I love bones."
[laughter]
I'm on a bone-only diet, folks!
All right.
yeah okay we're just that was just us that's just what's on the news right now
so yeah that's we were just playing the audio from the news yeah cuz I know it's
so you know satire is moving too slow and Donald Trump's moving too quick
because he's our president that's right and he's moving way too quick yeah he's
He's the fastest president we've ever had we time we actually did
St. Nancy Pelosi
May a glass of water just at the end of one of his rallies. He just runs offstage like
Fucking like like 60 miles per hour. He will say I'm not fast
He does it does the Scooby-Doo sound the
No but we are glad that he's the president again.
Yeah I mean congratulations man it takes hard work to get to the-
I mean listen, you won fair and square.
To get to the biggest job in the world and then get to get to it again, I mean kudos
man.
I don't even know how you did that.
I mean it's crazy that everybody in the senate, democrats and republicans resigned so that
he could be only the leader.
Amazing.
And you won despite that actual video from Borat 2 of Rudy Giuliani jacking off onto
a baby's face.
Uh huh.
Which is, it was impressive.
I re-watched that the other day.
I watched like just that scene.
Yeah.
It's so clear, the way that they edited it, like, you know those videos that are like,
we edited Home Alone to look like a horror movie?
Yeah, yeah.
They edited it just like that.
Yeah, no.
Where it's just like, they just cut in, yeah.
yeah sure then and they put like a slasher sound effect yeah yeah they just
put in a dub where yeah where they're trying to do an impression of him but it
was a guy going oh I think they jumped the gun on it I feel like maybe if they
let the cameras roll for like two minutes longer something would have
happened but obviously they don't want like falling asleep dude yeah that's
Obviously they don't want an actual like him to whip out his thingy
They wanted that they did want it, but it's one of those things where it's like okay. That's a woman named Pandora's box
It's a woman in Pandora's box
Afraid that he had a vagina yeah, they didn't want to reveal how do you fucking whip that out? You know uh-huh that's tough
Opening up Giuliani's box. Today we're doing in honor of
President Donald Trump. Our brand new president. Our brand new, brand spanking new, fresh out the box president.
Top 10 fictional characters that would support Donald Trump.
Number one. Here's one, cartoon Vladimir Putin. That's right.
Our cartoon president. Yeah, unicorn Vladimir Putin is a character in my brain.
After Donald Trump won the presidency, the media has revealed the existence of cartoons.
They are real.
Cartoons are all real and all these people did vote.
They revealed that cartoons were actually able to swing the vote.
Very mysterious how they were able to keep them hidden from us for so long.
Trump won people of color, including purple and blue and yellow.
I don't care if you're black white purple green whatever or hey Arnold yeah did
fucking congrats also real quick Congrats Anthony at a man you like for
four more years of the only impression yeah this is huge for you dude Anthony
animaniacs was the guy that's actually the person that's the one Anthony
animaniacs was the one vote that this is huge did yeah number one mr. Krabs I
I mean this fool loves money.
- Of course, yeah, this makes,
absolutely he would vote for Donald Trump.
He would see Donald Trump's golden toilet
and he would say, "Can I shit on that?"
- Arrgh.
- Arrgh, let me shit on your golden toilet.
- SpongeBob, let me shit on the toilet, arrgh.
- Let me take a shit on your golden toilet.
- He doesn't say arrgh actually, does he?
He says arrgh.
Yeah, he barks like a dog.
- Yeah, like a crab would.
- Mm-hmm.
- A crab would bark like a dog.
if it could. It just doesn't, it just can't so it can't. Yeah. I mean, I feel
like he's like, I feel like he's socially liberal. This is, you know, this is
a really ingenious comment. This is kind of, I could see this on a
t-shirt maybe, like a t-shirt to condemn Donald Trump. Yeah. Rich minds vote
alike. Whoa dude yes. This is a comment here that says Mr. Krabs is in the top
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh one percent. Probably true he's got a lot of money.
That's true. I think he's the richest man in Bikini Bottom. I think he has the most money in the ocean.
I would have to say funny Krabs. What? Was he in the top yeah was he in top 1% of
funniest crabs on earth? I don't know. Probably. Here's another comment that
says so you're saying mr. Krabs in his poor human disguise would support
himself. Whoa. Whoa so he's saying Donald Trump is Mr. Krabs in disguise. That was
another thing that was just revealed. That's why Donald Trump keeps going to Mar-a-Lago
is because he's seeing his cut his he's going to he has to get back in the water.
yeah I'm just gonna be in this tide pool pay me no mind no photos please I have
to go talk to a spongebob it's good word I mean my advisors yeah he tries to he
tries to cover it up by saying I mean not squidward Ben Carson but he just
I can't think of another name for Spongebob.
And there's a Buzzfeed article that's like,
"Look at how stupid Donald Trump is.
"He finishes his speech and walks offstage
"directly into the ocean."
(laughing)
Fuck you, Donald Trump.
Yeah.
Number two is Peter Griffin, which I don't think so.
I think Peter Griffin did fight Donald Trump on an episode.
You're thinking of a chicken.
Oh, you fucking moron, dude.
Oh my God.
He fights a chicken.
Yeah, you know what? He's orange on the show. He's orange on the show, the chicken.
Yeah, that's my bad. I just, I was thinking about how cowardly Donald Trump is when it
comes to respecting our veterans. Yeah, that's right. Yeah, that's right.
He's a chicken. Yeah.
Yep.
I was thinking about how he's covered in feathers with a beak.
Yeah, that's my bad.
I'm thinking about how he's got a big, he's got big juicy breasts that he put onto him.
He's huge too.
you know you put a lot of sorry guys i was thinking about his eggs
it has to do it all the eggs he lays
that's my bad guys i got a mixed up again
number three i don't know who this guy is pretty looks like i was when i know
this is a good one from pokey money is not as much as my does not does not
they got you know i'm a pokey is not
does not as a fictional character introduced in pokey months on the moon he
He is the leader of Team Skull.
He specializes in bug-type Pokemon.
Team Skull would definitely support Donald Trump because of all their Punisher logos on
their shirts.
Team Skull, Local 141 supports Donald Trump for president.
He's got a cool chain and a cool watch.
He does.
Guzma does have swag.
Team Skull is the ghetto white boy team, right?
If I'm remembering correctly.
They all do, they do freestyles at you.
Yeah, yeah, that's what I thought.
And they chose Bug as their type?
Yep.
Well he did.
Oh no, he did.
Just him.
I thought every team has their own type.
What is it?
Come on man.
What's his, it's not Velocipod is it?
I'm not a baby, I don't understand Pokemon, you know?
I understand Pokemon.
I understand it on a deep and primal level.
I'm into cool stuff, I'm into RuneScape, Halo, LA Noire, those kind of adult games, you know?
you play LA Noire all the time. I do. I like the nudity. Is there boobies in it?
Yeah dude every dead woman is naked in that and then you get to inspect
it get this you get to inspect their bodies. Yeah I'm thinking I'm ordering
this game again. That's like the saboteur. I gotta order the saboteur get the DLC.
What's the DLC? The DLC, it's a pretty good game. You talk about it
every day I don't talk about it every day I talk about it every day dude I don't
talk you brought it up it didn't come up there was there is deal yeah the saboteur
Oh boobs in that game you know what I'm a self saboteur cuz I keep bringing it up
Wow whoa I got bars today dude dude you should
Donald Trump Donald Trump's presidency gave me bars cuz I knew I knew that I
I would have to save the world with hip-hop. Goddamn I got bars right now. I'd
have to save the friggin world the free world with hip-hop. Goddamn I'm like Drake
today. I got my eyes on Donald Trump. I'm gonna take him down with hip-hop. And
that's my that's the Drake parody I'm gonna write that's gonna change voters
everywhere. Yeah. For the election next year. I'm excited for next year's
election are you gonna vote for Trump again? I'm gonna vote for Spongebob. I'd say I'll probably take that one off.
Yeah. I'll probably take off next election. I did, I mean I'm too, I'm already too emotionally
drained to vote. Yeah. I might fall asleep on the next election while I'm voting.
Yeah. I think I'm just gonna go into the booth and cry. If I stayed up all night the night
before I could fall asleep while I was voting.
That's a good idea. You know you can stay up until midnight and then vote at the movie theater.
I was thinking about the funniest way to try and suppress votes would be to like walk into
like a voting whatever voting station where like say you're Trump supporter you walk into
a voting station a very liberal area and just just shit on the floor
because nobody's gonna go in there to vote after that. I would just you could get like
six people however many vote polling stations there are in the play in the
polling place and just make sure you vote real slow.
Yeah oh yeah. It would take like eight hours to vote.
Eight hour vote. Because they can't stop you from voting.
yeah so yeah I'm sorry I can't decide I can't figure it out then you sit on the
floor and then when they try to try to make you decide you take a shit on the
floor yeah that's right yeah or you can let a wild animal loose library yeah
yeah right yeah in the library yeah there's where you go and we can't you
can't vote there's a toucan in there yeah there's a bird flying around with
his nephews. Yeah, there's an ostrich in the polling station. I worked as a
polling judge in 2016. Really? Yeah, I did. What does that mean? So it's all your fault?
So you're the person who sits there and people like
come up to you and they're like, "Hey man, I'd like to vote." And then you have to
like write all their info down. And it was awesome because the guy, he was like,
It was a very Republican district and like my boss was like, "Yeah, so..." because you
have like provisional ballots that people fill out if they don't have like an ID or
whatever in North Carolina. Yeah. And my boss, I was like, "So do you guys like send
that somewhere?" and he's like, "Yeah, we're supposed to, but like nobody ever... none of
them ever counts. I just throw them away at the end of the day." Damn. Yeah. So I was
just you know just watching fucking election fraud happening right in front
of my eyes. That's sick dude. He didn't report it and it's your fault. I didn't know.
I honestly was just like I don't care dude this is it's an 18 hour workday
because you have to get there at like 4 30 in the morning yeah and you have to
clean up after it's a fucking nightmare. I was thinking. No amount of injustice could make me
stay. I was thinking about last night how how fun it must have been to do election
fraud in like the like 1700s you could just like just like write on a piece of
like right on a napkin me and my 20 brothers all vote for John Adams and just
like hand it to someone and then it's like yep okay. Well, I suppose you all do. I guess that's fair.
Whole family's on the same page. Good to hear. Or just like walk into a like a polling station
just take all the boxes. What are they gonna do dude? I actually work for the
government. So that's why when you when all you know your kids would die all the
time you just save their bodies and then bring them with you to the election.
You can just go in and be like oh yeah you go in and like start moving around the
ballot boxes and just be like yeah I actually am George Washington like I
know I look different in the paintings. Oh sir, Mr. President! Salute. They didn't have pictures back then
they just had paintings that like they tried to make everyone look good in.
And you couldn't you had to see the painting in real life. Yeah. You had to go somewhere.
museum to see what the president looks like. Yeah, it's not like you could like Google like what is
this actually George Washington. You just walk in there and do whatever you want dude you could burn
all the ballots. Yeah but then it led to some sticky situations where you could be like guys
I think George Washington might be jacking off in the saloon bathroom but I mean I know
what's wrong but I don't want to stop him he is the president after all. Yeah I don't he could
executive order kill me
yeah this is a donkey with wooden teeth
yeah i can jack off in the bathroom
it could be a off in the bathroom yeah by the actual george washington yeah
and number four batman
all
now
no top comment and only comment
well he is trying to save the world so maybe
now
all
uh... what
that meant that they would vote for trump
Bruce Wayne would be the most liberal billionaire, I feel.
Yeah, you think so?
I think he would be the most liberal of the billionaires.
No fucking way, dude. He'd be in fucking Africa, like Bill Gates style,
just injecting people with fucking Zika and seeing if it makes his computer run faster.
Yeah, he would.
He would, come on.
He would I think Bruce Wayne would definitely be he like
Because he at some point he's gonna run for office right and I think I think he's got a lot of momentum
He ran for Batman anyone. Yeah, it's true. Yeah
Yeah, once everyone figured that out. It was like, ah
Yeah, thank God the Joker didn't win in becoming Batman. Oh my god. Well, I mean if Donald Trump won
That's my god style he's kind of a Joker style Joker. Uh-huh you guys have you guys ever seen that like
That that page from like Batman where the Joker like beats up Hitler and he's like he's like I may be evil
But sir, you're something else
Yeah
I gotta look at this now. Hold on. It's so funny. It's so funny when they do that all the time, dude.
They did one, there was like a Marvel or DC like 9/11 page where it's like even
super villains shed a tear for the lives lost and it shows like Doctor Doom
like crying about 9/11. It's like... I look this up and the first thing I see is a
frame of Michelangelo from the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles punching Hitler and
And his text bubble says, "For the millions."
Oh you know what it is?
It's not punching Hitler, it's punching the Red Skull, who's a Nazi.
Oh, true.
Joker wouldn't punch Red Skull.
They're different guys.
Different characters.
Different universes.
They kissed.
He says, "You mean that's not just some crazy...
Some..."
What is he saying here?
"You mean that's not just some crazy disguise?
I've been working with a Nazi?
That mask must be cutting off the oxygen to your brain.
I may be a criminal lunatic, but I'm an American criminal lunatic.
Keep back boys, this creep is mine.
Fuck, dude.
That rules.
And it just has the red skull with a giant swastika on his chest.
It's like, come on Joker.
That rocks, dude.
You didn't realize?
Number five, Mr. Burns.
It's obvious.
It's obvious, that's all they have to say.
It's obvious, dude.
It's true.
Number six, Sonichu.
Oh my god, no.
No.
Oh! Not Sonichu. Not Sonichu. Number seven, this is true, Barney the dinosaur. Oh yeah,
and then there's a comment from Maddox, you may remember him from the internet. I remember
him from the internet. Yeah, Maddox is on this, on the top tens now, that's what he
does, and he said here, "Oh, another Barney insult." Great. Yeah, just throw it on the
pile buddy. Yeah, just more, more things to make us divisive. Do you liberals ever get
I'm tired of making fun of Barney. Jesus fucking Christ dude. You fucking liberals have no
idea how much he taught us about sharing. How many jokes about Barney can you even make dude?
Number 15 skipping ahead Peppa Pig. Top comment with 15 likes. She would so love Adolf Hitler
and Donald Trump. That's fucking true dude. I think that's way more likes than you usually
see on a comment too. Yeah. Most of the top comments have like 5 likes. She's not even
in the top 10 you know who is number 10 is Wario that one makes sense I don't
know that he can vote mm-hmm yeah he's he I don't think I don't think evil guys
can vote yeah exactly if you're evil you're not allowed to vote I mean number
18 Voldemort cuz you're just gonna vote for whoever is gonna make the country
evil Voldemort is a British citizen I don't think he can't vote either right
He has like a social security card yeah yeah it just says Voldemort yeah number
45 is the Joker okay top comment here only comment you need an ace in a hole
in the hole you need an ace in a hole mines Donald the Joker
Huxton it's an amazing line for the Joker number 22 the Grinch what do you guys
think I think the Grinch is socialist cuz he steals the presents yeah I think
he's green yeah yeah I think he might be green mean he might be a green mean
fucking present-stealing machine I don't know that he's even politically minded I
I think Joker's like, I mean Grinch, I think those are the same guy also.
They're too green.
I think that the Grinch is probably one of those guys who like writes in Mickey Mouse
because he's just like, "Fuck it all, dude. I don't even care."
The system doesn't even apply to me. He writes it himself.
Well, he's also writing the world's smallest ballot because he's on a snowflake.
Yeah.
Oh, he's liberal. He lives on a snowflake.
That's true.
Yeah.
He's the biggest snowflake of all because he wants to take the Christ out of Christmas
and destroy the presents for everyone.
That is so true.
Dude, he's a liberal snowflake.
He's a socialist.
Number 56, Wolverine.
No.
He's short.
Okay.
Never mind.
I think then.
Wolverine would vote for Professor X.
Yeah.
He'd vote for the claw candidate.
57. Makoto Itao
55. Dr. Eggman Dr. Eggman and Donald Trump are both judgmental,
rude, egotistical, and obnoxious people. They also look somewhat alike as well.
cat number cool cat would Hank Hill no way dude
Hank Hill no Hank Hill would write in John Kasich like yeah he's like a Mitt
Romney yeah yeah yeah cuz he has some common decency
Jesus Christ number 140 is a Chara from Undertale and there's one comment that
says she's not stupid and it's from I hate Trump I hate Trump but I love
Undertale Gaston he Pac-man King DDD again can't vote yeah King DG more like
the emoji movie yeah a little bit of a Carlos Mencia King mm-hmm
Kevin McAllister from Home Alone excuse me nah for only comment Trump actually
made a cameo in Home Alone 2 seriously look it up number 94 the annoying orange
Here's a comment.
"Hahaha and why is the annoying orange at number 101?
Sewell Day be higher on the list."
I mean Donald Trump himself, Donald Trump herself is relate to the annoying orange.
I mean look at it and tell me that do not relate.
Number 212 is Austin Powers.
I'm voting for Trump baby, yeah.
He's from a different time.
Well I think fiscally he's a great candidate.
He's gonna do a lot for small business baby.
I'm a small business owner, yeah baby.
His tax policy for small business owners is very shagadelic baby.
More aid to Israel baby, yeah baby.
We gotta stop him, us baby, yeah!
Zionist Austin Powers.
Remember, uh, remember, these are all fuckin' donkeys now, or ponies from My Little Pony.
These are donkeys.
Donkeys from My Little Pony.
ever Dean, excuse me? Swiper the Fox? Fuck yeah dude.
Swiper the Fox, also socialist, steals stuff from successful people.
No, cause he's, no, cause she's, she's Hispanic.
They wanna, the socialists wanna steal from everyone.
Well I guess he also probably speaks Spanish though, huh?
Mm.
The, the last one is number 262, the beast from Over the Garden Wall.
It's true. Donald Trump exists in the Over the Garden Wall universe.
Yeah, you know what the wall is?
Oh my god.
Over the hardened border wall.
Yeah.
Over the border wall, that's our parody animated series.
Over the border wall, that's good.
Yeah.
And it's you and me, and we fall over, and now we're in Tijuana, and we have sex with prostitutes.
that might be a pretty good good idea for a car kind of an adult swim show kind of
a weirdo messed up kind of cartoon but we could do it yeah yeah work it could
happen yeah how about over my hardly balls I have really small balls in this
but only in this show over my hearty balls and then it's it's written around
their trunk sound like honey I shrunk the kids and he has to get over my hard
hard, my hardly balls.
Yeah.
Okay.
And he says, "These are hardly even balls at all."
Yeah.
Oh, I figured, okay.
You still gotta get over them, big guy.
I'm saying big guy kind of sarcastically.
If it's over my hardy balls, 'cause they're full of chowder.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
It's like a Campbell's Chunky in there.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'd come a full potato chunk.
Over my smarty balls, and they just have glasses on them.
and I'm doing like a,
kind of like one of those corn pops commercials
where you have your mouth upside down,
but it's just my balls upside down.
- Yeah.
- And they got googly eyes.
- And they have googly eyes on them like,
oo, oo boo.
- Oo bee?
- Oo bee, like Hulu.
- Mm.
(laughing)
And every time, and you don't want that,
you don't want that character to sneeze
in that commercial, I tell ya.
- No, no.
- No way.
- Come on man, Jesus.
All right, Donald Trump.
- Oh yeah, congratulations Donald.
- One last big congratulations dude.
Congratulations on pooping yourself.
Yeah, congratulations on making your diaper wet!
Yeah, you bitch!
Fuck yeah!
Nice diaper asshole!
You peed into your own mouth and enjoyed it!
Congratulations on shitting and then taking all the fiber and stuff from your shit
and eating it and you like it.
Yeah, you'd--
Grimlin's Grimlin.
Congratulations you fell down the stairs, you rolled down like a Looney Tune.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, congratulations on getting stuck in a barrel.
Yeah.
Fat bitch.
No, but seriously, congratulations.
Yeah, I mean, we can't say it enough.
Yeah, I just don't want to get hurt, so congratulations.
Don't listen to the other episode.
Don't do not interrupt when it's...
Don't listen to the upper episode, because...
Don't.
Because...
Don't do it.
Okay.
If you do, we'll know.
We know if people listen to it.
There better be zero downloads on it.
There better be.
Uh-huh. Yeah, yeah. And if you listen to this one before the other one,
well, you shouldn't have done that.
Yeah.
Don't listen to this one if the other one's true.
If what happened today didn't happen, you shouldn't be listening to this. You're bad, aren't you? You're nasty.
You're a nasty fan. You're a nasty little fan, and you're gonna be punished.
and you want to become an even nastier fan
and you want to subscribe to us on Patreon.
- We're gonna be nasty.
- That's right.
- We're gonna be nasty on Patreon and Twitch
and our Minecraft server.
- Oh, he has to plug the Minecraft server.
Go play Minecraft.
- Join our Discord, podaboutli.st is a bunch of links.
You can join the Discord server
and then you can join the Minecraft server from there.
- I think it's podaboutlid.st.
- Yeah, that's what I said.
- List.
- Podaboutli.st.
- It's podaboutlist.com.
- No, it's not potabotalyst.com.
- Shit.
- Okay, we're ending the episode.
Shut up, Trump won.
(laughing)
Bye.