You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts for the heartless.
Crap monster.
Yep. That's some funny shit, man.
I don't care who you are. Black, Indian, Hitler.
Man, I don't care if you're Adolf Hitler yourself, man. That's some funny shit, man.
That's some funny shit.
I don't care.
God damn.
- Damn, the boys are back, dude.
What the fuck?
Oh my God.
- We're back in New York, New York, Manhattan.
- They done fucked up and let it happen again, dude.
- They let me back into New York, Manhattan.
- Which I wasn't expecting to, yeah.
I wasn't expecting that to work.
- Yeah, after you acted like a total beast.
- Yep.
- You partied hard.
- I did.
- Dude, people were talking.
- Last time I was here,
I thought I had COVID for a couple days.
- You did think you had COVID just 'cause you were tired.
We all got tired and we were like, "We have COVID."
I was like, "This is the big C."
There's no other explanation.
I mean, it's fair because that happened to me so many times during the beginning of lockdown.
I got tired or had a sore throat and I thought, "Oh, I have COVID."
That was the first time that I got tired when I was around other people.
Yeah.
No, COVID was like as a fucking just a terrible hypochondriac.
Yeah, that's bad.
This whole thing.
Yeah, yeah.
- Since March, I have been on edge just every day.
- Yeah.
- You've been on H every single day?
- I've been on H every single day
to deal with the pain of COVID-19.
- I wish, I mean, I could get some good shit in New Hampshire.
- I would love to have those big bulging veins.
- Oh my God, dude, I would get so thin on heroin.
Are you kidding me?
(laughing)
- True, true.
- I would look good.
- No, you would be like an already laying heroin addict.
- No, I wouldn't.
- Yeah, you'd be like, oh, I just had so much heroin,
we have to go to Burger King.
- We have to eat cheeseburger.
- We have to go to Burger King.
No, no, no, I would get Taco Bell so I could shit it out of my system immediately.
Plus heroin makes you shit.
Does it?
I would not.
I've never done it.
What's the thing in Trainspotting?
A toilet?
A baby toilet?
Yeah, he goes in the big toilet.
A train?
No, heroin makes you constipated.
Scotland?
Heroin makes you cum.
Heroin does make you cum.
It is true.
Would you guys do heroin?
I mean, it's available to me.
But you haven't done it.
That's a, yeah.
So why not?
thing I know every all the heroin in New Hampshire is cut with Fent.
Ah!
So we have a very...
Would you do Fent?
New Hampshire has an extremely bad opioid crisis and now that the election's over it's gonna
be forgotten until the next election.
Because Biden's gonna snap his fingers it's over dude.
Biden's gonna do the Thanos snap.
White people listen to Biden.
If he says...
Yeah.
Listen Jack.
If he says hey Jack stop doing Fentanyl.
Yeah listen.
Stop putting Fentanyl in your balls.
Jack you're...
The whole city of Manchester is gonna be fine.
was a kid fentanyl was something that mom said to their dads when we were and we
were walking around
Well shit. It's been ages since I've seen one of those. Well shit.
Shit. Joe Biden.
Gimme Joe Biden.
No I can't wait till the opioid crisis in New Hampshire to get way worse and then Joe Biden should be like "Hey look, this is not my fault."
I mean it's not his fault. It's his fucking fucked up ugly hillbillies in New Hampshire.
I'm really I'm really a glad fucking Corky Messner didn't win New Hampshire
I'm glad Jean I mean, I don't like Jean Shaheen, but I'm glad that Jean Shaheen beat him out
He's a mean and quirky guy if the guy from New Hampshire who was in charge of shit was named Corky Messner. Yeah
Would fucking suck. Yeah, that would not help my case for being stupid. Yeah
Run by a man named Tweety bird. Yeah, exactly
That's yeah, yeah, this is New Hampshire's state senator chunky
Yeah, yeah, it's basically everybody in New Hampshire throws their poop
We all live in cages
We all live in cages and throw poop at people yeah
In North Carolina everybody who runs for election is either called like
Either like Rob Messner should be the North Carolina. Yeah, well, it's either like it's either like Robert
Braxton or like or like Duh-Dawn
And like Duh-Dawn got a got a City Council membership. Oh damn. Did you hear Duh-Dawn finally legalized drunk driving?
Now that's the fucked up part is in North Carolina did dawn is a way better
Fucking elected a right like you're fucking elevator per ari berry cherry berry. Yeah
There's a woman who's the who is the commissioner of?
fucking elevators
First of all, what the fuck is that?
secondly sure her name is
cherry berry and she puts it on every single elevator along with a picture of her face and
she's never lost an election she wins by by 90 she's in the booth and it's like
yeah who do you want to vote for you want to vote for you want to vote for Enrique
Rodriguez or Cherry Berry there's a clear choice yeah yeah especially North
Carolina yeah I know people are like well Cherry Berry it's not like an ice
cream flavor. Cherryberry, hell I'm hungry. I could go get ice cream right after this. I don't care if it's November.
But yeah she's a she's you know probably a piece of shit. Maybe. But she's a genius.
Yeah she's the best. She invented elevator. I'm gonna take you guys to North Carolina and show you an
elevator. Oh I'd love to go to North Carolina I know the skate park there. I know the skate spot.
We have to go at some point. It's sick. North Carolina rules. Yeah. Much respect to North
Carolina. I feel like North Carolina is like New Hampshire in the in the spring.
well it's better food than New Hampshire for sure. Yeah, now that you guys
experience what New Hampshire is like. There's black people and beaches. It's nothing like New Hampshire.
I feel like the most similar state to New Hampshire is probably Vermont
because it's upside down New Hampshire. I would say or Maine. No, Maine's too big.
but main is like main is half about mongolia
yeah yeah might be close right people eat out of big boy do it we do have a lot of uh
we do have a lot of cons there we do have a lot of uh distant relatives of genghis khan
they're all over yeah yeah he actually conquered new hampshire
yeah that was the edge of the empire everybody yeah when people say like oh like like point
2.2% of the population has has Genghis Khan's genes. That's all New Hampshire.
Yeah, it's only people in New Hampshire.
It's just a bunch of Khans conquering each other.
There was this house in Auburn that I used to drive by. It was literally like,
I think it's a trailer that they built like a big picket fence around.
It's in the middle of the woods. It just says it has a big sign that says keep out on it.
And it's just like a whole like fence. It's like a fenced in house and it's near like some fire
department in Auburn and that is the great wall that King is Con was trying to conquer.
There it is dude.
So what do we, I mean are we going to stay up until 5am again first night with you guys
here?
Probably not.
Knowing us we probably will.
Let's just do the same thing as last time.
Never learn.
Never learn from our mistakes.
What did we do last time?
Last time we stayed up until like 5am and then Caleb took us on a 10 mile walk the next day.
We said, "Oh, Caleb, so we're going to go backlog so many episodes. Oh, wait, no, let's
go, let's walk ten miles."
We had to have something to talk about. We couldn't just do Phil Hoffman all, you know.
Well, we could have done Phil Hoffman all weekend.
Yeah, that's true.
We haven't seen each other in long enough that we could just talk.
That's true.
It's trying to go on a long walk.
Yeah. There's been some stuff happening, I guess.
So, there's some interesting stuff going on.
Hey, look.
No, Patrick, go ahead. What's going on?
I'm going to talk about what's happening in my life.
Okay. All right.
All right, I'll talk about what's happening in my life. It's going fucking awesome. Yeah
Doing so much drugs and fucking having sex every day. Yeah. No, no, I've gotten a little bit better at the base
I've gotten a lot better video games. Yes. I have I think if it wasn't for video games
I would have gotten addicted to drugs. Yeah in the past six months. Honestly, I think honestly I think learning like the first
part of
Chicken by Jaco Pastorius has saved that guy. Yeah. Yeah by Jacob Jacob Sartorius Jacob Sartorius
Yeah, nice. Yeah, because the first like bar of
Chicken is just done done done
Well, it's the exact same chord progression as the chicken dance. Exactly
Yeah, which is the taco pastorius wanted to play the chicken dance and people are like this isn't few
This isn't jazz fusion enough if this ain't jazz fusion. I don't know what is play. Oh
Exactly. Yeah, I don't know enough about Jaco Pastorius to even joke about him. Don't even joke about that
I don't even joke about that guy joke about Jaco Pastorius. He's got a scary name. That's all. Yeah, he kind of looks scary, too
What does he look like? He's kind of like a freak
Go on he looks kind of like a freak I've only seen him the only pictures I've seen of him
He's wearing a turtleneck and I don't trust somebody wears turtlenecks all the time. Yeah, we never know it could be under that
What if there's no knife under the turtleneck?
What if it's to hide the fact that he has no neck?
He's a floating head, dude.
What's that scary story as to tell in the dark?
The first one in that book?
Yeah, what if his head falls off?
Yeah.
What if he takes it down and he's got dracula bites?
He kind of looks like a vampire.
What if he has one of those boxes that smokers have when they talk to a robot?
What if he's got a pussy on his neck?
I think that's definitely the most effective.
I think I'd actually want to see that.
Yeah, let me see.
Let's take a couple steps back here.
he's got a pussy on his neck. He's got an innie or an outie on there.
If you're born with a pussy on your neck do you think you get in trouble for having it in public?
Yeah. Yeah. What? People hate women more than men. If you had a penis on your neck you could
walk around with your dick hanging out. Dude. That's right. Yep. Uh-huh. Yeah. Cheers to that
dude. Oh my god. Imagine imagine okay imagine you're a guy who has a penis on your neck okay
and you're walking around the mall and across the mall you make eye contact
you make eye contact with a woman working at Auntie Anne's who has a
pussy on her neck and you walk up to her and you walk up to her and you ask her on
a date because this is the first time you ever see someone like that she says
know. Well, because she knows what you're doing.
She's not going to be like, "Oh, this is what happens."
He's asking me on a date. How convenient.
Well, I mean,
you don't think that she would,
finally someone that's like her too?
I mean, guys would find a fucking
face fuck. Yeah, guys would
fuck a throat with a pussy. Yeah, that'd be
like kind of ideal, dude. I don't have to get
near the butt.
Fucking perfect. Are you kidding?
You know?
Yeah. Yeah, my wife heard that and I heard her move around. She's opening the door. That
was the most scary moment of my life, dude. I almost got grounded. That was tough. I got
grounded before I left. You got grounded, really, by your mommy? My brother grounded
me. For what? He texted me and said, "I'm grounded and I need to come back home." Are
you serious? He just misses you, dude. Is that why you've been crying the entire time
No, that's why I've been crying. It's because Eric said I was grounded.
Damn, dude.
Yeah.
How are you gonna recover?
I don't know.
I mean, how are you gonna crawl yourself out of this?
I probably won't.
Yeah?
No.
What's the longest you've ever been grounded for?
Longest I was ever grounded...
No, I didn't get grounded for a long... I always knew how to weasel my way out of getting grounded.
But...
Yeah.
The first time I ever got in like serious trouble for something I did was
was when I first got Twitter in like 2012.
Yeah.
And my cousin Patrick, I have a cousin named Patrick.
Looks just like you.
No he doesn't.
He probably does.
Oh is he one of your big cousins?
No, or I think we're the same height.
He looks just like you.
So he looks exactly like you.
Nah checkmate.
He doesn't look like me at all.
Okay what does he look like then?
I think-
Just describe him you fucking idiot.
He, I feel like if I showed you a picture you'd say he didn't look like me.
You probably couldn't tell.
So say some features on his body.
I got a lot of tattoos.
So that's not, that doesn't have to be.
I was right dude, he's Maori.
Yeah, he's Maori.
Exactly, that's my Maori cousin Patrick.
But we went back and forth and we were talking about holiday themed dick pics and somehow
my aunt saw it.
In 2012?
Yeah, exactly.
Like in 2012, that's just an at midnight game.
And my aunt saw it and then I guess something he said, he said like a picture of my dick
on Yom Kippur with Jewish sideburns or something.
And my aunt, who I hadn't talked to since I was like, I hadn't talked to her in like
four years.
Is this a Blue Lives Matter aunt?
No, this is not the Blue Lives Matter aunt.
This is the aunt who has notorious RGB stuff.
Syndrome.
Yeah.
(laughing)
But she messaged his dad and then his dad called my mom
and said, "Your kids are posting anti-Semitic things online."
(laughing)
And my mom--
- Your dad was like, "Duh."
(laughing)
- Hell yeah, dude.
- Nice, dude.
- All right.
- Nice, dem boys, right.
- My mom, as soon as I got home from school that day,
my mom was like super mad at me and I was like,
"What, what the fuck is going on?"
She's like, "You need to delete your account, blah, blah, blah."
And I was like, "What are you talking about?"
She said, "You're posting anti-Semitic things."
showed her that it was his kid not me your mom hit you with a delete your
account my mom hit me with a delete my account yeah so my my mom was like you I
uncle Bobby called and said you were posting anti-semitic things and I was
like no it was uncle Bobby's kid who was posting the anti-semitic things so take
that and he didn't call my mom back because my mom explained to him like
yeah you know because it was me my brother Paul and my cousin Patrick damn
and they got confused by which Patrick exactly yeah they said they said Patrick
my I think my aunt said Patrick is posting anti-semitic things and then
Bobby called my mom immediately eight years later you're posting anti-semitic
things constantly rewarded for it yeah I'm rewarded by all those Jeremy Corbyn
nights. Patrick runs a small account that's been getting a lot of
anti-semitic cow which is different from anti-semitism cow. He moves when something is anti-semitic in a good way.
It's like yeah dude fuck yeah. Yeah it sends moos to fucking every Jeremy
Corbyn tweet. That's right. The longest I ever got grounded was I well I didn't
get grounded for that I was under threat of getting grounded I don't think I've
ever been like grounded dude I had some fucking harsh yeah I know you fools dude
you you were the one evil you got caught more than me uh don't say that cuz it
kind of makes it sound like you're sneakier than me which is just
completely full no I'm sneakier than you and you literally you don't know what
you're talking about no no I'm sorry that your mom is you guys you've been
have an insanely hot but she's not that's your fault I got grounded because I just
completely ripped off a paper in like high school I never did that and then my
mom was like my mom was like you're grounded for two months and I was like
oh fuck and then my younger brother came down the stairs and my mom would always
get on him because he wouldn't shower and his hair was always greasy and she
could tell that his hair was greasy and she was like when was the last time that
you showered and he was like I can't remember and she's like you're also
grounded for two we both got grounded for two months me for plagiarizing and
him because he couldn't remember when he took a shower yeah I feel like Cameron
never got grounded I just said that yeah fucking commie parents yeah that's true
yeah I I did not just didn't do much bad stuff I was a little shy kid yeah I
I didn't do I wasn't I wasn't I wasn't crazy like you guys that's true I was
crazy I was crazy in my head dude yeah I had demons that I couldn't let out you
guys wouldn't understand I wanted to sell drugs there was definitely something I
almost oh yeah I smoked a shit ton of weed in the basement swag and I went
upstairs and made a bunch of clam chowder and I was like oh wait so I almost got
ground it was before a parent-teacher conference I smoked a shit ton of weed
and you brought a grocery bag of clam chowder.
A clam chowder.
Family style, you eat it out of a Walmart bag.
So it was the night before parent-teacher conferences,
and I made a bunch of clam chowder,
and I was about to make egg noodles for some reason.
That's a great combo.
Yeah, clam chowder and egg noodles.
Why didn't you make pasta and clam chowder?
That's what I was going to do.
Dude, okay.
And you got punished for it, dude.
It was midnight before parent-teacher conferences, so I made a shit ton of it and then I
Think the microwave went off and I was like that shouldn't have happened
Like I was like I was too busy looking at the noodles to realize that the microwave went off and then I went oh no
It was beeping for like a couple minutes my mom like came downstairs
I was ready to like get like she pissed at me and she looked at the fucking
Clam chowder sitting on the counter and was like oh having a little feast
start and I was like mom went medieval yeah dude she went medieval on my I never
got caught with smoking weed cuz me and my parents I didn't get caught smoking weed at the same exact time.
I didn't get caught, she didn't know I was high. Okay. But she did see that I was
eating a bunch of food and was yelling at me for eating all the food and then
went to parent-teacher conferences the next day expecting to hear something
really bad. She was like, "Oh, now my son's a fuck up." And she they went and she's
like, "Yeah, no, he does all the work. He's just kind of like a piece of shit."
My mom sat me down one day and she was like, she, you know, she texted me while I
was out and she was like, "You boys need to come home because I have something, we
have to talk about something really important." And I was like, "Oh, fuck dude. Her and my
stepdad are like getting divorced or something. This is serious." And I got home
and they were like, "Come to the bedroom, sit down with us."
And they were like, "So basically, we've been using medical marijuana to deal with our anxiety
because I can't find a job."
And I was like, "Fucking shit."
The same shit happened to me.
My fucking dad called me and he was like, "Cameron, I just want you to know that I sometimes
I'll smoke marijuana because it calms me down and I like it.
And I just wanted you to know because your younger sibling just found some in the attic
and I just wanted you to hear it from me.
It's like, "Okay, Dad."
That's hilarious.
Yeah, and I was in college.
I also know that it's not for anxiety.
That was like in sophomore year of college.
Dude, the fucked up thing is like...
That's when we knew each other too.
Yeah.
No, you know what?
It might have been freshman year actually because I think it was pretty soon after my
parents got divorced.
Oh, okay.
I know that it wasn't for anxiety because now I go home and my stepdad will like smoke a
bowl and watch Lord of the Rings.
And like do a puzzle or some shit.
Yeah, he wants to become an Uruk-hai, that's why he smokes weed.
But it's just like, just fucking, I don't care dude.
My parents never smoked weed.
And then somehow they could never tell that I smoked weed.
Even though, like, I mean they were just so brain dead about it.
Yeah.
Oh dude, I almost got caught one time.
It's when smoking go on.
When I was 14.
This is before I realized I just can't smoke weed, but I like went up the fucking
Oh my god.
I'll turn it off after this.
But you won't.
I won't.
So I like it was like when my sister was like a senior.
So my sister, my brother and I were in high school at the same time.
and she had her like ex-boyfriend over and uh
i like went i got super high in the basement i went upstairs and i was going
to grab oreos and i didn't think that her ex-boyfriend
was like so like my i was in the basement do you
want a piece of paper yeah i have to map this out in my mind
but i opened the door and he's looking right at me and my eyes are like just
beet red i look at him and i go and just shut the
door. I ran downstairs further into the basement and he like told Amanda that my
like eyes were like super red and they were like I heard them like talking.
He's just evil. I think your brother might be the devil. I think your brother got possessed.
That was like one of the scariest moments of my life. I was like yep I'm
about to get caught I remember coming home from from my friend's house and my mom
at 4 in the morning and my mom being awake and she was like like what's up
like I was where have you been I was in high school and I was like oh yeah I was
over at my friend's house I mean something like the highest I've ever
been I was like I was over at John's house we were writing like a parody of
seussical and she was just like she's like okay even try to get me dude yeah
like I couldn't tell her something that was more indicative of the fact that I
was just fucked up yeah and she just had one of the one of the tricks one of the
keys to if you're really high and you're trying to hide it from your parents is
you just act sad yeah say you had a bad day and then you can just be quiet yeah
you have tough parents yeah they call me fucking pansy or the f-word yeah but is
that better than then getting grounded that's the question no you still have
your dignity yeah I've never been on my mom has never called me faggot my mom
does as a joke yeah my dad I think he called me a loser one time when I was
bad at football. Damn. I think my parents were very disappointed when I stopped
playing basketball. I went to one practice in jeans and I was like
I've never played basketball before in my life I just realized. I know I was
just like the biggest fucking disappointment to my--
'cause like-- - Oh yeah, dude, my uncle--
- Being like my dad being like,
"Oh, here's a Boston Red Sox sweatshirt
"for you to wear to first grade."
And then being like, "I like Ditchymon."
(laughing)
- Dude, my uncle, as soon--
- I just know I cause him so much psychic pain.
- God damn it.
- Yeah.
- Fucking my pansy son, dude.
- I still have it. - He wants to be a comedian.
(laughing)
- I still have it, but my uncle,
The day I was born, my uncle Jack, my godfather,
took a, he had his game, I think he was like 18
when I was born, I don't know.
I don't remember when he was born,
but he had like a game-winning ball
from one of his high school football games
and he wrote my name, my date of birth, my weight,
like everything, I still have it, it's in my closet.
It's a football from the day I was born
from one of his game-winning, like,
oh, he got the game ball.
and I still have that and I cannot imagine what he thinks of me now.
Just like yeah this kid's gonna grow up he's gonna be a fucking linebacker it's
like not. He walks in your house and you're using it like a whoopee cushion.
Yeah I played football for like three years.
Really? And I was insanely good at it. I wasn't. But I kept getting concussed.
I knew. I got concussed like five times. As a kid?
As a kid. And this is back like people talk about like they're like
back in my day football was way worse than it is now. Like people used to lead with
their head. That was like 2008. Yeah. Like it was not that long ago that people did that.
One of my cousins quit, it was like a flag football team, one of my cousins quit because
the coach was like, "Use your fucking head!" He was like, "I'm not gonna lead with my head!
I'm not gonna charge with my head!" God gave you that heavy brain for something, buddy.
Yeah, you like freaked out at him and like...
The thing is I was really good at football because somehow when I was 11 I was 6 feet
tall and I'm 5'9" now.
Like I was fucking huge.
You were probably 5'9" at 11 which is 6 feet for an 11 year old.
Your mic just turned off, pal.
Oh shit, I turned it back on.
Why did you turn it off?
It was an accident.
It just slipped the finger.
It happens sometimes.
You definitely were like, "Oh, here's the switch."
Come on.
It's true.
We should get you a Staples that was easy button.
any kind of fidget tool we could use for me that's why I could never be I could
never be like the president or anybody who has access to like nuclear codes
I've never been in line at Staples and not been like I'm a press that button
and just ruin their day right yeah they get pissed dude they're like we don't
buy it and then you press yeah like maybe I want to test make sure it works
yeah we run this just scrolling through every website just highlighting and
highlighting every line of text like yeah you can't you can't give me any
anything that I'm not supposed to click on absolutely not yeah that's what Best
Buy fucks up by having computers so you can access the internet on yeah yeah you
can go on you change the big thing in my high school was going to the Best Buy at
the Manchester mall logging into Facebook on it and then using the photo
booth app and then that was your profile when I was really into when I was really
into Hearthstone when Hearthstone was like big they had like a you could get
like bonus packs for like playing on an iPad and I didn't have an iPad so I went
to the Staples in Harvard Square and I installed Hearthstone on their iPads.
I one time put Goatsy on one of the computers at Best Buy yeah and I was
like dude fucking epic dude I'm like anonymous right now yeah yeah there's a
there's a picture of me very young I'm wearing a... It's called Goatsy? I'm wearing a
Ray-Ban. Yeah, picture of me. You don't want to see it. I'm 11 years old it's called Goatsy.
I think I'm like 12 or 13 but it's me and my brother's friends and we're at the
Apple store and I'm wearing the fake Ray-Bans to their wayfarers I'm wearing
those and I'm wearing a shark tooth necklace oh yes dude I look in the
Boston metropolitan area I'm in Manchester it's not even fucking my
Metropolitan yeah get it still yeah no there's no fucking the closest beach is
an hour away and we're at a fucking shark to you like this dude that's sick dude
I looked I looked cool did my uncle got me a fossilized shark tooth one time
yeah oh that'll blow your mind coolest thing ever yeah you got me you got me
arrowheads - ooh that's a little offensive why why
And that's the problem. Nobody can tell you why. Fucking owned.
It's a good thing to venerate another culture you respect and that you want to be part of
and you want to dress up as on Halloween.
Yeah, it's amazing.
It's true.
Yeah, my grandpa brought back these Vietnamese eyelids from the war. I mean, you know, am
I going to say no?
What am I going to do?
These are perfectly good ears, okay? I'm not gonna just throw them away.
I'll never throw away good ears. My grandpa would get so mad at me if I didn't wear his ear necklace to school.
(laughter)
You'd think it was disrespectful, dude. Yeah, my grandpa killed a whole village for this, man.
fucking 18 years on this how much work goes into that it was a lot of time it
was a lot of time it was from one guy
My grandpa went to ward the circus. He's got a necklace of girl beard hair. He's
got a necklace of clown noses. Dude, I need to check on my grandpa since Trump lost. I
bet he's not doing well. Yeah? Yeah. I bet he's doing so badly. He has like all the
hats. He has the white one. Oh man. Once you buy the white one, the coolest one is
the one that that uh that poopy pie 360 has. Oh yeah the the real tree one? Yeah. Yeah.
That one is cool. Honestly that one does kind of look sick. Dude anything that has real tree on it
I'm just like I would wear that it doesn't matter what it says on it. When I when Trump like first
started like running there's a there's a picture of me in a Trump shirt because I didn't think he
would win. One of my my friend my high school friend's roommate bought one because he was like
a serious Trump supporter and I put it on as a joke and I was like "Hey guys, check me out!"
And then like months after, as soon as he got elected, I was like "I need to delete that
photo."
There's a photo of Noah wrapped in the Confederate flag.
I guess that had nothing to do with Trump being elected.
No.
That didn't look good at the time.
But it does make me laugh sometimes.
I do remember when me and my cousin on like the first debate being like, "Let's go Trump!
Let's fucking go!"
Right, because you don't think that guy's gonna fucking win.
I mean and he texted me like when Trump won, he's like, "I can't believe he did that."
I was like, "It was still funny."
You know, whatever.
It's cool that he's out, but he's out as bisexual.
Guys Donald Trump is bisexual and he loves drama.
Yeah, Barron's actually his boyfriend.
He's his little boyfriend.
not even a son you were like how do you fucking pop that kid out you didn't dude
that's a boy for a 14 year old boy he's a fucking Jesus twinker just twinker yeah
and then come on he got a milfy wife and a fucking twinkie little baby folks the
polycule the hell is wrong with us - we got weird we were we were today
lists oh yeah I forgot this is a normal how far are we into the episode 32
minutes and I go pee real quick no you can pause it you go pee and we won't
pause it no you pause it no we don't you're actually together so we can pause
all right fine I'll pause it okay stop touching my penis okay okay so that
happens penis stop something I do to calm down while I'm recording
I'm gonna bust. I'm gonna cum. I'm gonna cum.
I'm gonna start doing extremely physical Charlie Chaplin bits on the show.
Yeah. Yeah.
I fucking told you dude. Come on.
No one could hear that.
That was just like Charlie Chaplin.
Yeah that was more.
That was just like the Charlie Chaplin bit where he fell sideways on the chair.
You know what? That was more Buster Keaton. I'm gonna be honest.
True.
No, no. You were Buster Keaton. Come on.
That was more Caleb sliding off a chair to me.
I could be the worst physical comedian of all time.
I'll say it, buster.
My SNL audition, "Uh, yeah, so, uh, I'm gonna be sliding off this chair pretty slowly, honestly.
I really don't want to hurt myself, so, uh..."
Just know, this is fake.
No laughter?
Yeah, I heard that happens.
Yeah.
Today's list is "Weirdest Reasons People Have Filed for Divorce" by Usermisfire.
It's strange, but it's true.
people have filed for divorce for strange and bizarre reasons.
Number one, she didn't share her love of a Disney film.
Oh my god.
When did that happen?
If I married a Disney woman, I would get divorced immediately.
A Japanese woman filed for divorce because her husband didn't share her love of the movie
Frozen.
After persuading her spouse to watch the film, he made the mistake of asking her, "Did you
really think it was that good?"
Apparently she did, and the fact that he could even ask that question made her question what
sort of person he was she furiously responded if you can't understand what
makes this movie great there's something wrong with you as a human being and
filed for divorce after unfortunately it seems that she didn't learn anything
from frozen's biggest musical number let it go I think she did big facts she did
let him go it's funny to him go this this it's about divorcing over a Disney
movie and you mentioned frozen specifically and then Pat goes that's a
kids movie. Yeah. What the hell? Disney kids movie. Watching Frozen. Okay, so
whoever fucking, if you're married when Frozen comes out, you're probably past
like 23 at least. Would you be happier if it was a Marvel movie? Yes. Okay.
Alright. Yeah. I feel like Marvel divorces happen a lot more. No, I feel like the, I
I feel like the kind of women who marry, assuming it's the guy who likes the Marvel movie and
the woman who doesn't, I think the kind of woman who marries the kind of guy who likes
Marvel movies probably is not the kind of, you know.
Yeah, she's probably 14.
Yeah, she probably doesn't know any better.
That's a really good point.
Yeah, she's probably saying, "Oh, my man's in his man cave again watching Captain Marvel."
Yeah.
- She's watched it three times this week.
- That woman is probably like a--
- I never picked up Black Panther for whatever reason.
(laughing)
- It's probably like a pizza rolls maker.
- He said we could skip it.
- Hey, we don't even have to watch that one.
My hair is bad.
CGI is just terrible in that movie.
- That's like a made snacks for my gamer hubby.
- Yeah, true.
- You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
- Marvel husband is a gamer hubby too.
- But he's only playing the Avengers game,
the Square Enix, the Squeenix.
- The new one?
the ones that they lost like a hundred billion dollars on.
Because who's gonna fucking, I don't wanna play this shit.
They already, they made a Spider-Man game that was good and they were like,
oh everyone's gonna want to do Avengers and it's like no, the Spider-Man is good.
Literally that game, the first hour of that game you just play as like a girl walking
around a convention center and you're like, oh that's cool, it's fucking-
In Avengers?
Yeah, you're like, oh it's cool, it's Thor.
Oh that's cool, it's Iron Man.
You don't get to play as the Avengers for like an hour.
like Amazon was doing like whenever you order from Amazon for a while they would
send you in a package that was just like it was just the whole package was an
advertisement for Avengers so you would like get like I ordered what did I
fucking order might have been these headphones or something but it was
literally like it came in a package like did they send me a ventures for
PlayStation because it just says when Avengers just has the fucking Avengers
pictures all over it with the minions - they like minions minions they made a
lot of money on it yeah I mean minions made fucking money but the Avengers game
did not make... Did you see the... When we were growing up, was there a Minions style thing,
like an IP that was just so fucking popular? Yeah, there definitely was. I can't think of
it off the top of my head. Rugrats. What am I thinking? No, no, Rugrats was not as big as
the Minions, but I think when we were growing up, it was probably like... Mr. Meaty. I think Minions
is probably the first thing that occupied the same space that Minions does, though. And being
and like old people's like minions. It was still Tweety Bird at that point. Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
Tweety Bird was just everlasting. Yeah. There's no like fucking rank. Like they were waiting until
like CGI, like the 3D animation was good enough to make a minion. Yeah. And they tried with Rango.
They tried with fucking. It was the mine seagulls from Finding Nemo. Oh you're right. Yeah. Yeah.
yeah i'd be right yeah yeah well yeah that's the thing pixar could never do
what the minions did maybe napoleon dynamite it's definitely true
pixar could never yeah yeah pixar characters aren't cute
there's a response to this one like minions from user boris rule
woody and buzz have swag that says yep made a post about it on my idiotic
people blog series
Disney fans in a nutshell. What the heck? What is this? Disney 1994 wants to know your location.
Number two, he was just too nice. That's every time I get divorced. Classic story, dude. Yeah.
Every breakup I've ever had, yeah, it was too nice. Yeah. I was too nice with it. I was literally too
good at eating pussy. Jeez, top comment. I was too good at singing Or Nah by Ty Dolla Sign.
Yeah, the weekend verse. I just hit every note. My bad.
Yeah. My bad, bitch. Yeah. My bad. Sorry you can't accept me for who I am.
You don't fucking let me lick your flip or dick or nah.
Whatever that line is. You don't let me lick and flip your tits or nah.
Or nah. Or nah. I'm gonna bouncy wouncy
in you. I'm gonna fucking jump on you right now.
We were doing in the car him just like losing the voice in the middle of the verse.
He's like,
♪ You gonna let me flame your ♪
Sorry.
(laughing)
- I feel like he has to talk in that voice.
- Yeah.
♪ Hey what's up ♪
♪ Hey it's me the weekend ♪
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Yeah, but it gets confusing
'cause I'll walk up to someone and he'll be like,
♪ Nice to meet you ♪
♪ I wanna bounce on your pussy ♪
♪ Like a bubblegum trampoline ♪
♪ I'm sorry ♪
That's from the song, I meant to just say hello.
- Just making sure you know who I am.
I'll take my mail.
Thank you.
(laughing)
Welcome to the post office.
- Top comment on this one is from Metal Treasure
and says, "Well, maybe the woman just needed a wife beater
"to make her happy."
- What?
- I'll step up.
(laughing)
- No.
- Yo, if I got to.
- He means the article of clothing.
- No, he doesn't.
- He does.
- Come on, man.
come on. Randomator comments what the hell don't women want nice guys? No.
You buddy eat randomator? Here sit down let me teach you. You got a lot to learn here.
Let me learn your thing. We're gonna start with a Nigahiga song. Randomator
is 18. You're really threading the needle with that pronunciation.
You want to go soft eye? That's way worse. What? You say it.
You, you, come on man. It says here the randomator is 18 and the display name is
blog posts matter. Yes, dude. BPM, bro. No! Blog posts matter, dude. That's sick. Number three.
Oh, Patrick's skipping into the kitchen. I don't think there's any more, any more
drinks. Dude, I absolutely swagged on Pat right there. Number three. I'm so genius for
knowing things she couldn't handle the size of her husband's penis yeah that's a
pretty good like that's a good excuse yeah oh you're pinned you honestly
opinions are just too big yeah me bleed yeah I think that's that's kind of a
that's kind of copia yeah I wouldn't have a problem with that because my penis is
small and then cries and asterisks
facts big facts
and randomators back in this one. Okay, hold up first women want guys with some
size down there and now there's people complaining that a guy's you know what
is too big. What the hell guess that's women in a nutshell for you make up your
mind. You stupid bitches come on. Do you want to humongous do you do you listen?
Do you want to do you want my one inch penis or my one hundred foot long penis?
I've got two of them. Do you want a baby dick or do you want a fucking light pole
in your pussy? Yeah, you want a light bulb.
Once you put it in, you can't take it out.
Yeah, they might like that. No. A light bulb? You don't think so? No, a woman would not like a
light bulb up her d*ck. You would know. Yeah, yeah, cuz you would know. No. Not. I do. I got all
the powers from that Mel Gibson movie no you didn't passion of the Christ you're
talking about the beaver one yeah that too what's that called exactly the beaver
one I learned everything there is to know about the beaver from Mel Gibson
mm-hmm yeah number four he voted Trump for president hmm here we go all right
it's a little too early you know let's let's let's a flood fucking dead doves
You guys want to talk about the election for the rest of the episode?
Let's go.
Yeah.
I feel like we've...
I can't get started.
Matt just fucking... is throwing his jewel like he's bowling at his white clock hands.
I'm practicing for Wii bowling later.
We are gonna play.
Do you have a Wii, Caleb?
Sorry, a Wii?
He has a Wii Wii.
Two Wiis.
Yeah.
voted for Trump, I would divorce him.
- Yeah.
- Hmm?
- I'll say it.
(laughing)
- What if, what if, what if,
if me or Cameron voted for Trump,
do you break up the podcast?
- Probably talk to you guys.
(laughing)
- What do you say?
- Yeah, let's have the, okay.
- I'd say, no!
- Okay.
- I voted for Trump, Patrick.
- Dude, what?
- Patrick, I voted for Trump.
- Okay.
(laughing)
- How about, how about this?
- That's a good talk.
- I, I voted for Trump.
- I believe it.
(laughing)
- No!
did you either of you guys vote? I did. I didn't. I voted green. I went Patrick's tie. Dude, swag.
Irish. I voted for the green party because it was calling to me. I didn't vote and if anybody asked
me I'll tell them that it's because I live in New York and it doesn't matter but I'm registered in
North Carolina. Could have actually mattered. I mean last election I just said I voted for the
woman and that meant Jill Stein. Jill Stein, yeah. I voted because I thought there was some like
public service police department shit on the ballot but I guess it wasn't on this
ballot so yeah I just died dude New Hampshire there was literally the
fucking district I was in was just like all Trump like I looked I looked at the
ballot results and it was literally like by a thousand votes Trump so my vote
really didn't matter even if I did vote well could have been a thousand one who
knows it's true you know my mother's a run up the numbers right yeah yeah I'm
I'm just glad fucking you're gonna win you want to win I got a text from my mom
yesterday where she was like OMG Biden won awesome oh yeah do you want to see
the picture my mom sent me when they called it for by yeah I showed Patrick
yeah it's pretty good let me let me show you this here I'll show you guys mine
too are you guys my mom your thing I'm just gonna Joe Biden I'm gonna scroll
this is this is a picture my mom sent me
yeah it's a dinosaur with a party hat breathing fire and it says
Oh yeah, I don't even know where she got this.
Yeah, what she got off her phone.
It came with the phone.
Did she Google like birthday dinosaur?
This is what I this is my family group chat when it happened.
The Joker.
Oh, that's you.
Okay.
I thought your mom said Joe Biden is president-elect and I sent a Joker
gift.
She said oh stop it.
And then and then J-E Devil speed said Caleb loves Joe Biden.
He even made a video about it.
Yeah.
He's kind of telling on me there. Yeah, whatever.
Does your, do your parents not know about that video? Fuck no. Damn.
My parents know about that video.
I told you a crazy parent.
Your parents definitely check your phone every night when you're sleeping.
So no, they don't. Yeah, they do. My parents never checked my stuff. No,
you think that's just what you think. My parents never checked.
They check about it,
but not to check and make sure you're doing anything bad,
but just to laugh about it while you're sleeping. Yeah. Just be like our son.
We're so proud of our son being too proud of me.
That is funny. Yeah, my family to my parents are like hey, I'm so proud of
him. He's yeah, we don't know what he's doing, but he has asked for money in a
ever so we're okay.
Yeah, number five. He saw her without makeup. That's a fake story. I remember
days after her marriage. A 28 year old Arab bride was dumped by her 34 year
old husband after he saw her with no makeup. Apparently the man felt that his
had deceived him with cosmetics. The couple's engagement lasted for six months.
She did one of those Tim Burton makeup tutorials. Yeah, she looked like Jack Skellington.
He only ever saw her on a black background. He's like, "He looks just like Jack Skellington.
Beautiful, beautiful round head. Jesus Christ. Perfect skull."
Matt Afterburner comments, "From what I heard, with the triple talak, a man in the Middle East
can divorce his wife just by saying to lock three times for whatever reason this
is just one the triple to lock I'm keeping that you have to go in the
bathroom and say to lock three times your wife gets sucked into the mirror
she becomes the next bloody Mary number six he found her secret love letters in
the 1940s. What does that say? I can't read that from here. A 99 year old Italian man
divorced his wife of 77 years after he stumbled across letters she had written
to a secret lover in the 1940s. The wife confessed to having an affair 60 years
ago and then desperately tried to persuade her husband to stay but he
just wasn't having it. What's the statute of limitations for you guys on an affair?
For me it's probably that. Probably that amount of time. 60 years? Yeah 60 years.
60 years is like, hey, you can forget it.
But 59 years?
59? No.
I mean, no fucking way.
No, look at it. It's like, it's the point, if I'm 99 years old, I'm not going to care about divorcing my wife. You know what I mean?
He's not thinking about the fact that he'll never get pussy again, dude.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's over for him.
His thing doesn't work.
I mean, he's probably, the strain of signing the divorce papers is going to take it like the last...
Yeah, dies in the office of the law.
I don't need the stress of filing for divorce if I'm 99 years old and Italian.
I would have just been like, "Okay, now I get to fuck an 18-year-old because you did
that."
Okay, this is on you.
You did that, so here it goes.
I'm going to fuck some OnlyFans woman right now.
What are their seven 250-pound, 40-year-old children going to think, dude?
That's a good point.
It's going to break their hearts.
Yeah, they're going to be like, "What?"
gonna be like what? They're gonna be like what? They're gonna be like what? WTF? Excuse?
Excuse? Sqoozy. Sqoozy. Realistically that's what they'd say. That's true. Number seven
he was cleaning too much. Yeah okay well if somebody was cleaning too goddamn much you'd
probably probably probably knock their block off. I mean maybe doing it to avoid his bitch
wife yeah yeah they didn't they didn't mention I'm angry vacuum before I'm not
gonna fucking lie like I haven't I've been I've never cleaned when I'm angry
fucking take this they didn't they didn't mention that he was he's cleaning
his wife that was the problem he was vacuuming his wife's body
you need to you need to rub I'm gonna rip you down with this
I'm trying to get you a job
I'm trying to get you a job as one of those naked women that they serve sushi off of
you have to be as clean as possible yeah yeah yeah he was cleaning out all our
photo albums. He's cleaning out her wallet. Trash, trash, trash. Oh your purse is so dirty
on the inside. I gotta get rid of some of this stuff. Showing her a picture of a, or showing
her a hundred dollar bill and pointing to Ben Franklin and be like, "Who's this? Who
is this man? Who is this guy? What is he doing in your wallet? Why do you have a picture
of this fucking guy in your wallet?" Oh and this is his phone number? 100? Let's give
him a call. I'm gonna dial it right now. Yeah, let's give him a call right now. Oh, looks
like someone got wise. It says it disconnected. Number eight he refused to shower. An Egyptian
woman filed for divorce when her husband refused to shower for eight weeks
according to the husband he could not bathe because of a skin disease which
made him allergic to water however while a doctor did confirm he had a skin
brain disease. He had it. He said it never had you reading nothing to do
with water.
He was in the shower. I hear reading. What is so funny because yeah, you
can tell you're just checking everywhere you every time you say a
word you're checking if it's the end of the sentence.
I can't help that. I don't know how to Egyptian woman filed for divorce.
(laughter)
From her husband?
Yeah.
- What's the longest you've gone without a shower?
- Me?
- A hundred years.
- What do you mean?
There's two of you.
Either of you.
- I didn't know.
- I'm not asking, in what world would I be like,
only Pat, Cam, take a fucking minute off.
Pat, how long have you gone without taking a shower?
- Well, okay, if you're asking me now,
yeah, probably like five days.
- That's not that crazy.
- Yeah.
- I think--
- No, no, my routine used to be I would shower
as soon as I woke up.
- I think when I went camping for a while,
it was probably two weeks.
- A few years when I was taking baths.
- Just a couple.
- Just a--
- Mm, you fucking--
(laughing)
You're a trickster, dude.
- Yeah, I don't know, probably like a week or so.
There's probably, but there's, yeah.
- I don't like showering.
No, I don't like it anymore.
- I like showering.
- I used to like it a lot.
- I like showering, but now that I have long hair,
I don't like having to let my hair dry.
Oh yeah, since I cut my hair, my shower has decreased in time.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I remember when I cut my hair pretty short for me and I was like, "Damn, I'm in and out
of the shower."
For like three years now.
I can jack off way faster.
When I shaved my head completely bald, I just like...
Dude, it's easy.
You just jump in the shower, jump out.
Fucking pits and tits and I'm out.
You don't even have to dry your head when your hair is short.
I just washed my winky.
I hold the hole open and let it stream from the shower head.
Well, I got skin there.
True, you actually do have to do some work.
I do have to do some maintenance.
Thank God I'm a Christian.
You get one of those water jets from a dentist's office.
I spray the water pick at my wiener.
And then you also have one that sucks the water back up.
I close the hole up and I just keep the water in there.
That's a good idea. You got a Velcro hole.
(Laughter)
You got a Velcro hole?
Fuck.
That's not a bad idea.
Dude, imagine if you could shave like
your pubes so they were Velcro.
Yeah.
And then you could stick it to something else that was Velcro.
I'm almost certain you could put a piece of Velcro
on your pubes and it would stick.
That's probably true. But if it was like
actually Velcro.
Wouldn't that be cool?
Wait let me think about this for a second.
Wouldn't that be interesting?
Yeah that would be fucking awesome.
Yeah.
Why would I get stuck to?
Probably your mouth.
Just get stuck to the carpet.
Just face down on it.
I'll be a couple minutes late.
I do think sometimes.
He's trying to do a push up.
I do think sometimes about a guy falling over.
If you fell over
and your penis got stuck
like a warm hole in the ground probably takes you a minute to get up you know
yeah you're probably like yeah I must have pulled something I'm gonna be a
little late you guys go ahead on the hike I'm gonna I'm gonna say I'm sorry
I'm trying to pull myself up here
It's a volcano. Would you fuck a volcano? Yeah. If I was God. Yeah. Yeah, if I was God.
There's a there's like the Chappelle show Godzilla sketch he fucks the
volcano and I remember watching that when I was younger and being like. It
awoke in something in you? No I was like why would he fuck the volcano his penis
would burn off. Here it is fire in his mouth. That's true.
It's actually not fire, it's an atomic ray.
Now I brought up Godzilla and now Cameron's not going to be able to talk for the rest of
the episode.
I just need to correct something really quick, okay?
He said something that was wrong, I'm not going to just like...
Well alright, number fucking whatever.
Number nine, she won the lottery and wanted to keep the money all to herself.
That's a good reason.
Yeah, that's a very good reason.
I think that's a very good reason.
Yeah, absolutely.
That's a fine enough reason.
I just won ten million dollars and yeah, I'm keeping it.
you seen that video of the it's the aunt and nephew and the oh yeah I think I
have seen this video it's the aunt and the nephew and like the aunt finds out
at the lottery office that they are sharing their winnings and she goes it's
not what I agreed to she'd like sharing their winning because I think she bought
the ticket and then he scratched it for her so she went down to the office. How do you
prove that? With the nephew and was like yep we won together and then the they
brought out like two checks or something. Oh yeah. Yeah and then she freaks the
fuck out yeah. Damn. It's a really good video. That's fucked up dude. I'm gonna just kill
my nephew. Take the money. Right there? I mean yeah. Kill my nephew and then I'm
doing a Cain and Abel thing. I would kill anybody for money. Okay. Yeah. Okay, number ten I think
is the most justified one so far. Yeah. She was possessed by the devil. That's fucking
clear cut, dude. An Italian man has been granted a divorce by claiming his wife is possessed
by the devil. Apparently, she displayed inexplicable behavior. Yeah. Including fits, body stiffening,
even self-levitation.
- Whoa.
- Crescential. - Self-levitation's
pretty cool.
- Yeah, I would marry him all over again.
- Yeah, damn, let's just go renew our vows.
I didn't realize you were some levitating ass pope.
- You took your vows in midair?
If you levitate while you're renewing your vows,
you're technically not on land.
- Yeah, it doesn't count.
It severs your connection to Earth Spirit.
- You can't get married in water?
- No.
What do you think?
You think it's a mermaid?
Yeah.
Tell that to a mermaid.
Oh, you already said that.
Tell that to some crabs.
Yeah.
Tell that to Sebastian.
Tell that to a fish.
Yeah.
Tell that to dolphins.
Dolphins are like...
Say some more.
Say some more in water.
Yeah.
Tell that to a guy and a girl in a bathtub.
Tell that to two boats that love each other.
Yeah.
Sure.
I'll believe it.
Yeah.
yeah sure i'll tell that to the atlantic in the pacific oceans
they hate each other actually are married though
it's an east coast west coast rivalry
by the library and i i i i i got some white claustic in my throat
noon
yes i'm like a second your brain brother yet
you know put my white cloners to have to do that
when i was a on the white cloth uh... cameron has a lot of his call on your
brain
karen has a cloners pp
dude
she was possessed by the devil
number eleven he didn't have a remand on his animal crossing i_r_a_ unreal
showed up
uh... anything about number twelve i never played animal can you talk to
match how would if you have a divorce somebody if they can't all the play too
much he played a lot of that
i'm divorcing you could you just play way too much for you you're too much of
a you play in way too many years
listen you work hard but you play way too hard
straight up your way harder than you were at your play work balance is out of whack
with divorce divorce is so strong like
that's a silly strong repudiation
strong yeah yes have a long
so what's how what do you what do you guys divorce over
to what I divorce if I don't want to be married yeah
while probably a bit probably
double homicide double D's yeah that's right double D's next door
peace yeah I'll see you later yeah double homicide Caleb's paradox is when
you're is when they're two women who live on either side of you with double D's
and you keep getting you keep getting divorced and remarried over and over
you're trapped in an infinite loop yeah that would be a nightmare
don't be so awful oh my god I hate that fuck no bitches right next to each other
it will mean twins to Cameron you just said that please no oh fuck the Caleb
dilemma what if you marry one twin and you get to forget dude what is dude can I
get a high five? What if a pizza guy had no money? What if the lady had wanted pizza?
Well? Okay. I'm not feeding her. Go on. You're joking. Do you guys want to get pizza after
this? No. Maybe. I had pizza already. I might have a slice or something. I had pizza last night. I had frozen pizza last night.
We said already I assume today. Yeah. Yeah. That's a lot different. I was gonna say
yesterday but I just stopped it already. Well because then it makes no sense that you won't eat pizza
two days in a row. I just don't want to. I mean we can. I'll just I'll just hate you
forever. That's Caleb's dilemma. Yeah. That's the true Caleb's dilemma. That's the real dilemma. Yeah.
I'll get pizza.
Alright.
Sounds good.
I mean if you guys really hate me that much.
Pizzazz!
We'll have to find something that's open if it's not pizza.
Yeah.
It's like 1030 now.
Number 13, he was clingy.
Hey, remind you of anybody?
Cameron.
I'm not clingy.
Don't say that.
You just tried to eat my pizza.
I said I didn't want to eat your pizza.
Oh, never mind.
Me.
I'm the clingy.
I'm the clinger.
You try to get me to come to your house all the time.
true yeah you're right I am clean guys never want to come to my house yeah we
do your parents are there that's true I always say I want to come wait wait your
parents are there yeah Pat's wait is your mom one of your parents she's so
gorgeous I hope she listens to this she's probably gonna Wow did she's so
beautiful don't say that I try to blow her kiss today she gave me the finger
Yeah. Well, you guys, were you peeing at Cam's house? I blew her a kiss and she went, she
gave me the finger, dude. What kind of woman does that to a beautiful woman?
She doesn't like you.
She loves me, dude. She's my best friend.
She likes me, right?
We're going to be more than that.
I don't know.
She likes me, right? Can you tell her to like me?
I can't tell you if my mom likes you or not.
Can you tell her to like me?
She thinks I'm a bad influence. She does.
Yes!
Bad boy?
Yeah, I think you're a bad influence.
My dog went crazy when Patrick came to my house today.
Oh yeah, because you look like a milk bone.
I don't look like a milk bone.
I'm sorry, you smell like one.
Because you look like, with that hat and that facial hair, you just look like a robber from
a movie.
It's true.
I did, when I first shaved my head bald, I wore my black beanie all the time, the one
that I still have today.
And my friends medals teacher told me I look like Joe Pesci in Home Alone.
You should just start walking around dressed in all stripes with a giant burlap bag over
your shoulder.
That would be so fucking funny.
That would be funny.
And a black beanie.
Yeah.
I would not be that funny.
That's not bad luck.
Yeah.
All right.
I think we're done.
Yeah.
I gotta eat something.
Yeah, me too.
Bye, y'all.