you're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
- [Woman] Welcome to the podcast.
- Crap monster.
(man screams)
(monster roars)
- Yeah, we're back.
- We're back.
- Drinking my little drink.
- What's your little drink?
- It's, what is this?
This is cranberry pineapple juice.
- God, dude, healthy Patrick on the way.
with a little bit of coconuts from the net really yet
do you know i'm getting who what i was a love lunch
watches on a map favorite things and rom is like is like a mimosa it's like a
lunch alcohol uh... yeah ron designed for a lot of the
it's really a lunch thing yeah
i'm over here on my own
up till a man
i might need help from you guys will key
yet what yeah
I need help hiding a body.
Ooo.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
You know why?
No.
Because I accidentally killed the game.
You can't.
Cameron said we weren't going to record video.
Oh yeah.
Whoops.
Yeah.
Nobody saw my cool move then.
Nobody saw me look cool.
But I killed the game accidentally.
Low key.
Yeah.
Man, my teeth.
Ugh.
guys about time for Patrick's teeth update. Play the intro song.
No Patrick, you didn't say anything about your teeth before. What are you talking about?
What's happening with your teeth now? So I got all of them fixed.
Whoa. Isn't that going to cost like $10,000? No, it's gonna cost $8,000.
I know. I got, well not all of them. Didn't some of them fall out after they
fixed them? Yeah, no. The fucking day I got them fixed I was eating something and
and then the bottom one didn't it didn't find a poop in your mouth
no no yeah
all my god no
no i'm sorry
it was you can find a poop in my mouth
what the hell when you have a girl dentist
i do have to have your father girl touch that way you had the same day
times who can't do that you said you're a little bit insane and i think that
that day and uh...
this is the
the
tooth number 30 is what they called it and 30 fell out and I had to go back in
to get 30 put back in the same day because there was something wrong with
my bite and then this one fell out the other day while I was flossing so I just
stuck it back in. Wait your tooth fell out while you were flossing? Yeah the crown I got two pounds put on.
You said you didn't mention crowns until you were just talking about
the
thing. Oh no. You really scared me. Why? How many teeth do you have Patrick? That doesn't
happen to you? Your teeth don't fall out? All of my teeth are chipped in the front.
Yeah me too. My teeth are chipped from grinding on a man at a club. Really? Yeah your father.
My father does have rock hard abs. He's got a rock hard penis with my butts up against
My dad, I mean goddamn. He's got a bubble, but I'm excited to go home for Christmas
but again
Patrick was bouncing on it like a trampoline. I'm getting my dad. I'm gonna hit the ceiling teeth first
Caleb's gonna have a half-brother and I'm
I'm getting my dad like six pairs of lululemon yoga pants. Yeah
Tradies own walk around for me. Yeah. Oh dad. I drop your present
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- You have to bend over and pick it up, Dad.
- Yeah, I'm just like placing like a trail of cigars
that he keeps picking up and bending over to get,
and it'll lead to my room.
- And then what?
- And then there's a heart made out of cigars.
- Uh-huh. - Yeah.
- Yeah, and then I'm like--
- It's cool that Dad loves cigars.
- If you wanna smoke one of these cigars,
you gotta smoke every last one of 'em, Dad.
- It's cool that guys love cigars.
- It's just cool.
Cigars just gave my grandpa bladder cancer.
pretty beast
and it's funny 'cause cigars look like poop
yeah so you think it would go you think the cancer would land in your ass
but it actually goes directly to your
for a fucking pee tank. yeah how does it go to your bladder how did he get bladder cancer
from
you don't know how he was smoking him. there was this pretty trick that he would do
where he would he would he could
you know you know how some women can like
like drink a soda with their vagina he can smoke a cigar with his wiener
i didn't know that women can do that really you haven't talked to your mom
recently home i got a easy dude
it's too fucking easy for me
anybody else when i go against the champion the ring cameron does
cameron your mom's fat
fucking easy
another one by which is there another guy here and you say that
i'm sorry mom larry and you can say that you're gonna have sex with my mom but
that's the second you do you start doing that
because your mom's evil so I feel like I can make fun of her easier.
What? How is my mom evil? She called me stupid one time.
She did. She has called you cocksucker a couple times.
Every time I've seen her she calls you like either like a pedophile or
yeah some kind of she says something insane about somebody.
Yeah that's true and it's just it's I mean
it's classic sort of middle school tension between you. The last two times
the last two times that i talked to her was she called patrick a pedophile and
then she called me and caleb a pedophile the second time
yeah i think she's just got a thing for pedophiles i think she just thinks it's
funny to call you i don't i don't think she's a thing for pedophiles i think
she's a thing for pedophiles no i don't think don't don't insinuate that my dad
is a pedophile my dad's a great man yeah i think she
might be married to a pedophile that's the only explanation say that
No, you guys would like my dad.
Yeah, I think I like you as much as I like your mom.
I think my dad did get mad at you one time, Caleb.
Why, because I just came on to your mom too hard?
Yeah, you remember we were on like FaceTime or something and like
you were saying like, "Oh, look at me, Trish" or something like that.
My dad went, "Hey!"
I will fucking, I will cave your dad's shit in, dude.
You won't do anything to my dad.
I will fucking, I will destroy your dad.
My dad's huge.
I'm gonna stick a broom through his fucking orbital bone.
How big is your dad?
My dad's like six feet and he's a six feet by six feet
Yeah, you six feet by six feet perfect cube and he does a he does diamond Dallas page yoga. That's cool
Did it and he does like p90x? Oh
Man, it makes it makes sense. You would think someone who's six feet tall is huge. I do insanity
I do insanity which is like you did that to order. Well, I did insanity -
He has the same pull-up bar as you I think there's only one. I think I think we have to I think we have to
uh I think we have to put Caleb in the ring with my dad. I'll box him dude. Dude that'd be amazing.
I actually want to do this now. I actually want to have Caleb fight my dad. I would take I would
like I'd take some insane like psychotic medication and just like yeah I just like start biting your
dad. Yeah the fucking scratch him. I'd throw my fingernails out and shit. I'd get like I'd get
like dermal implants of horns so i can take the jacob's ladder like like bloodlust vietnam drug
yeah exactly i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna smoke aging orange and i'm gonna attack just to fight
my dad just to fuck him up yeah i'm gonna pepper spray myself right before i get myself mad
a giant indiana jones whip into the ring with me
i'm gonna train myself
circle around and just go *whip sound*
in the air
what's up motherfucker
he's just sitting there with like
boxing gloves just like a kind of
he'll tape it up
he's not gonna whip it up
he's standing in the opposite corner
just whipping him from across the ring
his lashes all over his head
it's just like masters of terror
kassai like the star wars game
where like luke has like a lightsaber
and he goes up against a Tusken Raider,
he's fighting with fists.
I'm gonna put a giant lash in your dad's fucking chest
and then say, "Hey, man, take credit cards."
-Okay. -Yeah, I'm gonna do that.
-I'm gonna mentally -- -See, now more and more,
more and more, I want to see this fight.
I'm gonna mentally -- You want to see your dad die?
No, I don't want to see him die.
I just want to see him go -- I mean,
I want to see him go a couple rounds against you.
I'm gonna wear -- I'm gonna dress up like a goth
and scare your dad to death.
that we get boots with spikes on it. I'm gonna be dressed up in a full gladiator outfit. I'm
gonna have a spear and a net and I'm gonna trap your dad and I'm gonna pin him against the wall.
You're not gonna trap my dad. You can't trap your dad in a net. You couldn't even go one
round against my dad. I could go a thousand rounds with your dad. Now all right you know what?
Yo if I was with your dad right now I'd never tap out. I could keep going with your dad all day.
yeah right we gotta see this now i think both you have to i basically i do i'd go to the boxing
ring like the night before and i'd set a bunch of traps in the ring you do it that way you do
have a mcallister style box a big a big trip wire that makes a giant pendulum swing down and chop
his head off if he steps out of the corner you didn't say no booby traps that's true that's a
big thing that they don't realize that they don't recognize in boxing is that uh booby traps are
completely fair game. Completely. That's what Michael Tyson was doing. Michael Tyson.
Michael Tyson. That's technically his name. That's what Mike Tyson was doing was, you know,
he was doing a booby trap when he bit a baby boy. I hate when I fight Mike Tyson, I slip on all the
marbles that he throws all over the place. My ear flies into his mouth. I hate when I get glued to
to
fifty times. Yeah, I thought it was sixty-five.
Whatever it is, it's the funny number.
Just like, how do you not defend yourself after like...
also, how does that person not get tired after like eight punches? I think he must
have been like...
well, eight times eight is sixty-four. He must have been tied to one of those like wheels, like a medieval torture
chamber. Yeah. And a guy was just there, just going in on him. Yeah, eight times eight is sixty-four, so then
it was probably eight guys circulating with one punch. He was standing in a circle doing this.
that might be true
uh... all you know he was sitting okay argues on a result of office chair he's
on an office chair spinning around and they were punching his belly
one at a time uh...
yet and it was a frat party
and i think it's like one of the it's like those black and red to take turns
hitting
a thing with the hammer
yeah i see those videos
and i mean i mean i think how many spins of that be in the chair
what's the numbers so it's eight guys punching one time sixty four times how
How many spins would that be? Would that be eight spins?
Eight. Yeah.
Come on.
You did it in reverse in front of us.
I know.
Yeah.
I did figure that out.
That's the one time on the pod I've done math correctly and I completely, I completely
backtracked.
It kind of seemed like you were bragging that you could do part of it.
No, I wasn't.
Yeah, eight times eight, 64, man.
That's one of the only, like, things like that.
Yeah, hey, what's that? 64, eight times eight?
That's what you said.
I wasn't bragging.
- I'm casually doing the easiest math in a bragging way.
- Yeah.
- I mean, five plus six,
that's gotta be like 11 or something.
- Yeah, I mean, but I don't know.
Yeah, what is that?
No, what is that, guys?
Oh my God!
- I was right?
I mean, what are the odds?
- I was guessing, dude.
- Oh my God.
Easy guess.
You wanna see me do it again?
- You know, I'm honestly, I'm proud of myself.
That's all I need.
- Pat, do you wanna see me do
the biggest math problem in the world?
- Sure.
- You wanna see me do it again?
- Oh my God, no, come on.
And that's how I'm going to destroy your dad mentally,
psychologically.
- You will never wear my dad down.
- I'm going to mail your dad raw meat for a month
leading up to the fight, just to intimidate him.
Yeah, and I'm going to say, this is bad to be you.
This is the last guy I fought.
- I'm going to come into the ring.
I'm going to have a boxing glove on one hand
and on the other hand,
I'm going to have a Freddy Krueger glove,
but instead of knives, it's feathers.
And I'm going to tickle him to death.
- That's right.
- I'm going to talk to my man, Donkey Kong.
i'm a time in downtown to get that glove that he uses in super mario baseball
no one shot i'm not your dad in a right field
i can't home run up that strong
and i just i thought crazy news story
what's happening
here at the news website yeah i'm on the new york post he's watching c_n_n_
new york is that your go to new finding out things to do i just i don't know
arrest talking like it's a story that i wouldn't even do not only
I did one of you guys, you guys were making fun of me for math so I found something to talk about.
Wannabe Instagram star allegedly ripped mom's heart out in shocking murder.
Holy shit!
A young medical student wannabe Instagram star allegedly ripped out her mother's heart, lungs, and intestines
then calmly washed the blood off in the shower and met up with her boyfriend according to report.
It was your name Chucky no no recina.
Or something yeah it was there was a.
Yeah it was a Sonya blade yeah what was it Sonya blade Chuckie the doll.
Wall.
I thought you three and.
I called Chuckie on the phone real.
On the phone at 1 a.m. And he was small
No, what's it called I forget
For tonight is one of the one of the swag in a row I want every fortnight game
I ever played at this point in my might be the greatest
this
- Yo, I have a better ratio of wins to losses
than Ninja right now. - You look like Ninja too.
Oh, we should get Cameron the headband for Christmas.
- We should get Cameron Ninja for Christmas.
- Yeah, we should get Cameron Ninja gear.
- Whoa.
- I'm going on, all right, Cameron, what's your address?
Cameron, what's your address?
- What?
- Cam, what's your address?
- Your address in two, three, your poop.com.
- Don't just say it, just say it.
- Oh my God, is it seriously your address?
That's such a funny address to have.
How'd you get that? Did you have to pay extra for that address?
Yeah.
You should be able to get a vanity address.
Like a license plate, right?
They have to put like a custom street sign that goes right next to your house.
That's a really good idea.
It's all done, the mail is all done by GPS anyway.
If you put it in the database at my address, it's like Diarrhea Street 4, then they can find it.
Right.
Dude, that'd be so cool to be able to walk by a house and just see like, oh, these people
paid $500 so they could live on diarrhea street.
And guess what?
It's per house, so their upstairs neighbors have to deal with it too, even though they're
a 90 year old couple.
Yeah, it would have to work only for like resident, like people who live in homes.
I don't think you could do it for an apartment.
I'm buying a vanity address for the Burger King down the street and I'm not telling them.
(laughing)
- Yeah, and I'm gonna call it McDonald's.
- Oh my God.
- Yeah, it's McDonald's on GPS.
But that'd be sick, man.
You could get, it'd be just be, that'd be so sick, man.
- That'd be the coolest thing to get of all time.
- Yeah, I don't know.
I think, you should be able to do vanity everything.
You should be able to do a vanity phone number.
- Yes, you can, I think.
- You can kinda do that, right?
- Yeah, you could definitely pay for a 1-800 number.
- You should be able to do a vanity
social security number, too.
- Yes.
- Yeah, you should choose it for your kid.
- I'm sick of mine.
There's too many zeros in mine.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Dude, you just leaked.
That's a big leak, dude.
I'm gonna reverse engineer your number.
Like how many zeros? - Six.
- Six?
- Six zeros?
- And how many different other,
of each other number is there on it?
- There's one, two, and there's one, eight.
- And then what's the order of those numbers together?
- Michael, I can't tell you that.
really
we
Ninja Windbreaker is only $50. Is it sick? I already told you guys I want 23 in me. I don't want any
I don't want you out Christmas for my for whatever whenever you guys want to get me
We're getting you we're getting you the full ninja sweatsuit. I don't want that. We're getting it for you. I won't wear that
You're so ungrateful. It's unreal get it for me yet. It's not ungrateful. It's so you're so ungrateful. It's unreal
- The other one is ungrateful.
- The Ninja Gamer hoodie has mesh things on the side
so you can wear your headphones over the hood.
- Whoa.
- That's it. - And you don't want that?
- I wanna know where I came from.
- Poland.
- Yeah.
I hope you get 23andMe and it like immediately
just like changes like your Netflix recommendations and shit.
the
i'd like to know what you do you should do those cool they got monsters in it
you guys like anything in my city has like netflix and love my brain i love
netflix originals don't get me wrong do you guys think we could get a netflix
original
yeah sure
way that's my dream
what would it be did all my god i don't know where's from our friendship
uh... yeah we have to have stories from our friendship
so for those of you don't know i'm fortunate there's a bunch of there's a
bunch of movies and tv shows wanna make but due to our contract we have to make
stories from our friendship first and it's going to be thirteen seasons
thirteen it's gonna be basically every at and just so you know that the golden
age is going to be three to ten just so you know yes it lock in like you can
come ignore the first two
and the last three
but that that middle seven is going to be is going to go to do something else
as i was a good crazy
i mean do you know it's just like every good tv show third seasons the best
nine seasons the worst
do you think whatever run out of stories from our friendship to tell our show
all you know that's going to be that we're gonna go about it in the uh...
the the british way we're going to six episodes seasons
yes that's my words i have in every five years mhm
well that's how they have every british tv show works that's how they have to do
curb your enthusiasm because larry david
can only like
fuck so many thirty-year-old women and
yeah
you know that's a very happy
the british brain can't process like too many episodes at once so they have to do
what i can't get more higher than six years ago
so they just get stuck
yeah after six it becomes a quid
yeah exactly
yeah and that doesn't make any sense that's not a number
yeah that's a thing
and then after that there's a quinn
or quaint
one yeah
you should move to the u_k_ did
i would do great there is the nation we should do a show where we take you did
different countries
okay we have you interact with all the people
a friend abroad friend abroad a friend with some broads
uh... i mean here's hoping buddy
yeah we need you to fucking we get you need to romania those women will do
anything for food
come on what the hell are you talking about?
come on
dude I'm trying to get you laid here
that's disgusting
why?
do british people still use shillings?
yes
is a shilling still a thing? yep
yeah they still use little picture little gold coins with
they do, they do
yeah they do use those though
yeah they do
like
In Canada they do that too, like a loonie is like a coin.
You can, in the UK, you can trade a chicken for stuff.
You can buy an Xbox with six chickens.
What is a shilling, Patrick?
Bring that back.
A shilling, five shillings is one crown.
Yeah, I'm sure they can use that, Pat.
But then two shillings and six pence is a half crown.
Wow.
But--
What's a couple of quid?
but two shillings is one florin which is a two bob bit
and twelve pence is one shilling but that's also a bob
and six pence is one six pence aka a tanner
see this is why i like that they make fun of us for using like inches and feet and miles and shit
and then you have stuff like this
yeah i mean i'll trade you one king's toe
but then you go down the list and then four pence
is one groat
three pence is one thruppence, two pence is one tupence or a half groat.
Yeah because two pence tupence. That's what I knew.
You know what's kind of weird thinking about it? You know in Fortnite,
Fortnite in the U.S. is just like an awesome game where you can dance and be
the Mandalorian and baby Yoda, but in the UK it's actually just a week.
True. Okay. One pound is 20 shillings.
How many shillings are you weighing right now?
Well, one shilling is 12 pence, obviously.
Okay.
Wait, how many pence?
Listen, we got enough pence over here.
Yeah, we got one pence too many.
That's right.
Oh, this is old British money.
[Laughter]
Oh, shit, this is old.
Oh, shit.
Oh my god, that makes so much more sense.
Yeah, no, and they, I mean, they don't have any new money, so.
I'm gonna call the Bobbies on you so soon.
[laughter]
God damn.
Fuck the Bobbies.
[laughter]
Hey, Bab!
Hey, Bab! Hey, Bab!
The Bobbies rolled up and got my partner.
[laughter]
Yeah?
Yeah.
They locked my partner up.
The Bobbies did.
Yeah.
The Bobbies rolled up.
the bodies pulled up
with the body bodies pulled up with the with the musket
yet it's not going to cut him
bobby's pull-up is one of the musket
who dot would have been unit
pretty my lad
they put the bayonet my lad yeah is a lot of sun or a best friend i don't know
that is just a guy
a lad allowed to be a bloke but i think a bloke how many letters of blood
I think a bloke is an older lad, and a lad...
You can call a group of lads blokes, but...
Are we allowed to say lad?
No.
We're just saying it because we're nasty.
Dude, we're culture vultures right now.
Yeah.
I hate being a culture vulture today.
Oh, I hate being a British culture vulture.
I love being a culture vulture.
Dude.
You're being a culture vulture, mate!
It's so funny to me when, like, a tweet will go viral that's like, like, wow, do British
people do that accent all the time and then there'll be a bunch of quote tweets that are like
like i can't believe americans retweet americans retweet stuff like this they sound they're the
ones that sound so stupid all the time and every time i see one of those i just i just can't help
but imagine that it's me like the americans sound so stupid they think they're so smart
just like so dude i think i beat up any british person it's so funny that every like british
person is like, "Yeah, how's your maths class? You're getting shot up in there. How are you
getting shot up in maths?" The thing about a British person is any British person you
can do the Looney Tunes punch all their teeth out like a bowling pin strike. It's true. Very
easily. Also, you can also they start every fight by walking 10 paces in the opposite
direction. Yeah, you can do that thing is they already they already have piano keys for teeth.
i had to i think the most
the most british thing about me on my twenty three and i twenty three years old
so i have like
some british
it was a british thing about you know the most british thing about me is
probably not a lie i guess with i think it's a good thing you like french fries
yeah
that's it what's the you know it's literally every sorry every british show
that's ever been made
yet and i will leave it was seen
uh... of most of them
Yeah, you love British TV. Is this a normal episode? Do you guys want to do our job?
This list I found from the couple minutes. Oh, I found from the discord.
Remember who posted that? Yeah, I just scrolled and found it. It's someone named guy. So thank you.
Yeah, thank you so much. Could be anyone. I knew a guy named guys a pastor. And I put him I hated
him so much because I hated God when I was a kid and I went to the like fall festival
at my church and I paid $20 the only money I had to keep getting balls to dunk him in
the dunk tank.
And I finally got him on my last one.
That's nice.
It's like a dollar a throw and I was like this fat fuck's going in that water.
This guy's going to hell.
That's who gave us this list today.
Thanks guy.
Thank you guy.
This is Top 10 Most Random Things to Do in the Middle of the Night.
And this is by user JaysTop10List, whose icon is Chance the Rapper.
Woah!
He's got his city doing front flips.
Shut up dude.
He has a really, he has a really big profile blurb.
Really?
What does he say?
Anything so cool?
He likes the Soviet Union.
That's so awesome dude.
Paste this on your profile if you like Beyonce.
The this profile picture is the logo of my favorite band the gorillas. They're very creative and I admire their work very much
That's show that's it's the
No
Well, I think it's because the cartoon
It's a ring of God. It's the rapper that he could be confused. I does does list days once a month
whoa
Damn, we do that - yeah, we should have one of these people on the podcast one day
It's not a bad idea.
I think that was one of the original ideas for the 50th episode was to like interview
someone from uh like list verse or the top ten.
Oh yeah.
I think we should have my mailman on he's super sassy.
I was like we should have Patrick.
You have a sassy mailman?
I have a sassy gay Indian mailman.
Oh.
Yeah it should have him on.
He fucking rules.
He always gets mad at me because my mailbox is broken and he's like that's gonna kill
me one day man.
Oh yeah you told us about that.
the door on my mailbox is falling off and every time I go down he just like rings
my door and he's like you got to get that fixed man that shit's gonna kill me
one day. How is it gonna kill him? It's like yeah it's like a fucking half pound of piece of sheet
metal. Right. Top 10 most random things to do in the middle of night. Number one
munch all the food. Facts. Big facts. Dude if that ain't me I don't know what is. It's the food for me.
It's all the food for me that I'm munching.
It's all the big food.
God damn.
I love munching on the big food.
Me too, man.
What's your go-to late night snack?
Ooh.
When I was a kid, I used to eat cold baked beans.
What the fuck?
[laughter]
I just eat them out of a can.
Oh, you're like Rorschach.
That's Rorschach's best vegetarian.
You're exactly like Rorschach.
Yeah.
I saw a kid in college heat up a can of baked beans in the can on the stove.
of
who wants to be born tonight love acting i will be boy
all right i'll be dead
these hostesses so good bite
all my god you look fat as a big angry bird
i do
doesn't it look nice slaps
you slap me
that's that's taken exactly word for word from the angry birds movie the dead
but it's a shit out of it
on an angry birds movie uh...
Can you imagine just getting slapped by your dad
'cause you ate something?
'Cause you ate a hostess.
Yeah, well what if you ate your dad's last hostess?
Then he has the right to slap you.
That's true.
You're acting like an angry bird right now, son.
Yeah, yeah.
What is an angry bird?
I fly at the pigs.
So he's saying that he's--
You're flying your way into being a pig.
You're flying your way into pigdom right now.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're so, right now you're a bird,
but pretty soon you can be knows you can be one of the pigs
and that's all that's on that's on my mama i really like this comment to
i will eat all the cheese steaks and drink all the mountain dew and for my
way to a nearby bathroom because i had diana
and
or and i a m
uh... diana
i need to
for my way to a nearby bathroom
what was he trying to write is it
the whole or
he's a little and his way power and try to have a my way
turn our you know what word that would be
other than
hope and
with a little work
whole
whole yeah whole work
i'll try to learn more about it
for the head of the area
and uh... that
dot iraq
maybe we're misunderstood maybe
maybe we're misunderstanding
maybe the like maybe die a hair is not
a misspelling
maybe die a hair
is his girlfriend
of the other hand i have a friend i a hero or into a whole after he eats and
drinks is you know before you fuck you
for you make that girl's
where do you know if you stay together because i don't think
you know big fat sixty four ounce code red
and he bring die a hair to the bathroom
and you know what happens next, you gonna fart on her.
yeah yeah you don't make her smell that fart.
you gonna smell my fart. you gonna smell my fart bitch.
oh man we should add that to the uh theme song.
oh chuck berry saying you you don't smell my fart.
new year for the new year we can have that instead of crab monster.
it's so good dude. it's the best sound of all time. yeah you know
smell my fart while you're peeing on someone? I mean is there a better...
Oh he's not peeing on her then. No? No, there's 69ing and he farts right in her face.
Oh I thought this is when he's sitting in the bathtub. No, no. Which by the way, that is pretty
respectful. Peeing on her in the bathtub? If you're gonna pee on somebody... We haven't even said that
that we're talking about Chuck Berry.
It's just out of context.
People can put
these context clues.
What other sex tape is somebody asking
someone to, or not even asking, demanding.
Telling. No, informing.
Informing.
Yeah, informing.
You are going to smell my fart.
It's not even a question.
You can try, but it doesn't matter
what you do. You're smelling this
fart.
You're going to.
Yor can smell my fart.
Yeah.
Number two, jump on your parents bed while they're asleep.
I would never.
Oh my God, could you imagine the ass whooping you get after that?
Yeah.
No, because my dad would, my dad would wrap me in a chain and slam me against the wall.
My dad would lock me in a freezer if I did that, dude.
I hate when my dad wraps me in the chain.
and that's what we know what i was a non tumble does the image i could get out of
my head with this week so we get a really angry about
the uh... jill byron's dog breaking his ankle is be like i'm gonna wrap that dog
in a chain and she was a little bit of a little bit of a little
i will destroy that dog that her president
yeah i mean i don't should be in jail
that's true
you know if any of literally anybody else did that to jill byron they'll be in
jail
yeah if i if i heard his ankle
it was a result of my tail while i was in the bathroom
and i broke his ankle
which you know he would be that kind of guy
they put me to sleep with the way i'm sitting at the urinal mind my own damn
business pull my pants all the way down to my head to go to this
yeah maybe my tail pops out maybe you trip on it
doesn't give you the right
to pull that shit
i'm breaking that ankle man yeah that's right
i'm gonna break that i got the longest i got the longest pig tail you've ever
seen. It spirals around. Joe Biden, you keep looking at his tail. I'm gonna break your hymen Joe.
I don't know if we can even joke about that anymore. I'm gonna break that old man hymen
right now. We can't we can't joke about breaking his hymen. Why? Because he's the president now.
Oh is he one of these girls that lost their virginity to a horse's back?
What? You know what I'm talking about. You know that type of girl.
You know that type of girl.
No!
Rides those horses, breaks that hymen, you know what's up.
I've never met...
You know that type of whore-ish bitch.
On them stupid girls' braces.
No!
They got red hair.
No, they don't!
That type of girl has red hair.
You're describing nobody.
I'm describing...
I'm describing Morgan.
who's more you're afraid it
you you're describing a fourth grader you know named morgan when i was in fourth
grade it is a little bit and
is the fourth grader you know
no
she's older than me now did no you guys have to speak to a faster than you
she grew up faster than me because she was a virginity to horses that's
You guys have never heard that?
No!
You can break a women's...
This must be a southern thing.
Yeah, probably.
No, girls sometimes will break their hymen riding on a horse.
This is probably something your mom told you in home schooling.
Yeah.
Well...
That's true.
That might be true.
Yeah, that might be true.
She also said that my hymen could never break.
Because it was protected by God.
I can't break my hymen.
Yeah.
I don't know why.
for years. I just one day I can't wait till my hymen breaks. You can try to break my hymen
but I'll just curl my tail up to cover it. You're not getting in there. Every night I
sit there with a ball pen hammer trying to break my hymen. I got a hammer and a nail down
there and I'm trying to get through. I've got a hammer, a nail, and a blanket of glue.
I'm like Michelangelo down there, dude. I'm trying to sculpt something beautiful.
[laughter]
Dude, if I could just break this hymen, dude, everything would be better for me, man.
I've got a hammer, a nail, a plank of wood that says "No Girls Allowed" and I'm slamming it.
I think my luck might be turning around! I just broke my hymen at work!
I got a...
Don Knotts breaking his hymen?
I'm wearing a welding mask and I'm going to town with a blowtorch down there. I'm trying to melt it off.
Dude, I don't even want the stuff that happens after you break it.
I just want it gone.
Yeah, just get rid of it.
Hey, I don't care what you do with it.
I just want it gone.
Who was it?
It was T.I.
Right?
T.I. said that he had a doctor inspect his daughter's hymen every month.
Every month, dude?
Yeah, something like that.
What a freak.
I think I could regrow it.
Didn't he say, like, no, I was joking, like right after or something?
I think so.
When people got mad at him.
should say there
my that he was a joking but definitely
the p_r_ person at atlantic records is like
please just say that i was
the from funniest joke of all time
as a kind of doing i was doing the i was doing uh... a funny bit
yeah i was doing a character actually yeah i think i think my son of the
doctor every month to make sure nobody pulled his tail
uh...
the doctor checks the area around
around his i remember being worried there's no stretch marks
i'm really worried that my hymen would break when i was like a kid that the doctor would
be able to tell that i jacked off
yeah and he would tell my parents like
he uh... he has come before
and then i'd go to jail
or something
yeah well it's a good you don't do it before you go to the doctor that's the
thing
true
you're sitting there with dried cologne
while your doctor is checking
all i was saying your stomach yes and i when i was when i
i think that on
i think i'm gonna try and learn how to just
hands-free bust
what are you telling us that
i don't know
i think i'm gonna try and
train my kegels doing pilates and the like
so that i can just bust hands free just fucking come in my hands
i just think it'd be like a fuckin swag thing to do if i got in a fight with
someone
they just think you peed though. you'd have to take your pants off first. no no no
nobody pees as little as i come there'd be like one little dot
it looked like i dropped a bite of ice cream on my pants
and i'd be like
wait did you have that ice cream stain?
dude were you eating the smallest cinnabon ever out of a thimble?
I'm getting really scared.
Yeah, I'm getting really scared.
Did you just did you just lick the spoon from your mom?
Dude, is that is that is that is that a pearl on your on your zipper there?
And I just go I just go no.
And they'd run away.
Somebody in here steaming clams.
Did you drop a booger on your pants?
What the fuck is that a white booger?
no laser pointer down you still wanna fight you pussy
how come how eating cum is the same as eating boogers right
cum is just a kind of booger I think yeah
exactly yeah cum is boogers yeah
alright so I need me a girl that eats her own boogers that's how you know she's
she's a freak certified freak yeah number three dance around in the dark
living room
what's the dark living room all
all like
capitalize first letter is that our only room sounds like a uh... eighties goth
band i'm going to the dark living the top cut the top comment is don't do this
with a flashlight bad things will happen
it's true
the bloody mary
here's another script here
uh... let's read it again who wants to be boy who wants to be on to do wants to
be denied on this time i'm so sick of the idea of the only other way of the
boy
okay i'll be the narrator
are you gonna narrate
no there's a lot of it starts with blind bro
sorry we kinda reacted there that's our bad
alright well now you're putting it
okay sorry it's just this is a very hostile acting environment
i feel like klaus kidsky right now no this is good this will bring the best out of you
okay alright
YOU SUCK
hooptie dum dummy had a dump
he wants us to dance around when he takes a dump
what are you doing
um...
few hours later
uh...
shut up
no say it more like smosh
how did they say
shut up!
let's do it one more time
let's do this entire thing as smosh
wait, smosh isn't around anymore, we could just do smosh
we could just become smosh
oh my god, i'm gonna grow my hair out
no
did you should start to have you should grow your hair out and start
straightening it
that would be sick i think my hair when i was a kid maybe that's why it all fell
out
that yeah i did it so i i i had like uh... i'd i'd i'd
my brother worked at hot topics i'd
uh... okay
it was pretty swag at the time it is pretty sweat and then nintendo fan
replies the script is as he hear comment just made my day
you know what it made my day to jay's top ten list me too
thanks for that good yeah i like your little scripts
it looks like you put a bunch of scripts on this one
when i get down later today when i'm
trying to like flex my butt in a way that makes me come no hands
and i get sad because it's not working
i'm gonna think of that, it's gonna cheer me up
you're gonna think of a boy dancing around in the dark living room
i'm gonna think of the funny scenario okay
yeah i might think of a family circus comic too
does that make me weird? no
and it's just funny
number four yell out the window
so that i think then people be like what the heck
some says i do this every saturday night
disguise them as wildest cat on earth
can you know parties to hardy this case to jazzy i would yell finland to summon
the holy patrick starred from josh it on josh it
josh
kitchen
jackie chin
josh tish in twenty four josh's kitchen
subscribe
he cut number five
jam music
positive on wild talk
so are are what i want my ipod speakers on as i fell asleep will commit to a m
by dead mouse it was hard getting back to sleep
i fell asleep with music on last night
you know i know i have a good stuff
as i said i'm times do
nobody was like uh...
we look at
i thought cd counter strike videos i will call it a lie atmospheric black metal
or something that was there
i think it is a huge amount of his mind so we're white boys to them
i've i woke up at five a_m_ to uh...
pablo picasso by modern lovers
as likewise focus and i think that it isn't that a painting
no
you listening to a painting i was listening to a painting
maybe you know i a book of a painting
we're going to describe it
uh... is a bunch green
which regrets over there
there's a weird guy in the ground we're going to like one i always to i was
just on what's on his head on
and that's it
that's the whole painting net only to square
it's done on the square k_-eight square canvas
you guys ever fall asleep to like
you falsely to music and then like that music comes on shuffle or something and
you listen to and you can just you just think of your bed
no that's all you can think of no no there's this one album i would listen to all the time to fall
asleep and now i can't listen to it without just thinking like man sleeping is awesome actually
you know what psychosocial by slipknot does that for me because i used to listen to it when i would
go to bed in like sixth grade yeah i listened to one time i listened to danny brown while i was and
fell asleep by accident. I had a dream where I was at a Danny Brown concert.
Do you guys have any smells that give you a boner?
What?
Why am I so nasty today? But yeah, I'm sorry. I just I've been thinking about this.
There's a hand soap that I used to use as lube when I was growing up to jack off and
when I smell it, it gives me a boner.
That might be the key to going.
Yeah, we're gonna we're gonna figure out we're gonna figure out that smell
What is the brand hold on it's
Fuck, it's soft soap. I think
Yeah, it's the blue soft soap. Oh
Yeah, that could wake me up from any like drug-induced coma instead of like smelling salts like just fucking yeah
a
I'm getting to that soap no matter what.
Number 6, watch scary videos.
Can you guys watch something scary before you get a Nike Mare?
There's a script here.
Yeah, not really much of a script.
It's more of a monologue.
Camera, do you want to read the monologue?
Okay. Should I do any special voice for it?
Uh...
[laughter]
I just think it would fit the...
I don't know, I don't think it would fit the character.
to
voice I can do guys besides Scooby Doo. I can do the Crypt Keeper now.
Alright, well read it in the Crypt Keeper. Okay.
Oh, this baby elephant is eating the tiger alive. Now it is looking straight into me through
the screen. Oh my gosh, blood is dripping out from his mouth. Wow, the baby elephant is
really coming out of the screen? Um, something like that. EEEE!
You sound like my auntie.
I don't know what the Cryptkeeper is, but no cap, you sounded like a pumpkin.
You sounded like a pumpkin and I'm-
The Cryptkeeper is a scary skeleton who says scary things.
He's the scariest skeleton of all time.
Take it back, dude.
Wait, but he's just like a normal guy, right?
He has like a normal job and a family?
Oh no.
He lives in the scariest house of all time.
Please say "psych" dude.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Oh fuck.
Is there any way to delete your brain so you can't remember something?
Because I'm going to get so scared at lunch.
Number 7, play Slenderman.
I would, oh my god, are you kidding?
I would never do that.
I convinced myself Slenderman was real.
Yeah?
Yeah, for a little bit.
Because there was this like, I would always bike home from my grandma's.
Yeah, it was yesterday.
It was yesterday.
I would bike home from my grandma's, there was all these trees, and I was like, that
motherfucker's in there.
Is Slenderman in the tree?
He's in the tree, dude.
you know what I'd be scared of confusing him for a tree and then...
Okay, number 8 has a script and it's a good script.
Okay.
Open the front...
Number 8, open the front door and run around the neighborhood.
We got boy, mom, and narrator.
Okay.
I'm sick of being a girl and I'm sick of being a boy.
I'll be the mom this time.
Okay, I'll be the boy.
Yay, it's recess!
You would be more excited if you were a boy and it was recess.
That's right.
Yeah.
Okay, do your job now.
68 minutes later. Are you serious? That's your narrator voice dude? Come on. Take it
from the top. Okay, alright. Yay, it's recess! 68 minutes later. Shoo, I'm so... MOM! I'm
going to tickle your feet for punishment! Mom, that's not punishment. Whoa, what is he
he's saying here.
What the fuck is he saying?
Also there's no...
None of these scripts have made sense.
It has nothing to do with opening the front door.
This one has made the least sense though.
This is just like kind of a fantasy about your mom tickling your feet.
This feels like one of those like jav porn titles.
It's just a long one.
Number nine, start twerking.
My father wouldn't be in shock at all.
I'd be more in shock to see him do it.
If I throw it back, is it fast enough?
[LAUGHTER]
Where do you start twerking, dude?
Like, anywhere?
Like, if there's no one around, it's not that--
-With your butt.
-Here's a comment from Buttercup12353.
Yeah, baby.
[LAUGHTER]
-That's right, dude.
-Here's a good one.
Here's a good one. Um, I don't do this just in the middle of the night at those parties
three tongue emojis
Dude, this is a this one's for it's getting nasty nasty
This is nasty with a z dude. Kale. This next one's for you swag
Number 10 play with yourself. No, the whole thing i'm saying is you don't play with yourself. No this this is the comment
Mentally you top comment Josh liked playing with his poo in the bathroom late at night. Come on from that's from Josh
Josh tissue who up playing with they
In the bathroom late at night, so is the other bus in a fat nut
Sick dude
Dude, this is a triple X episode dude. Yeah first we talked about fucking Pat's dad or something
Fighting him. Oh, no, maybe you were talking about fighting. Yeah, we were dude Pat put your put your dad
That what you meant by all those rounds
Your dad put your dad in a room with me I know he gonna fold I'm putting a ring on your dad
That's what we were saying before. That's right. I'm gonna marry him. I'm gonna go
Then put a ring on it. You're not gonna marry my dad. I'm gonna put a ring on it
I'm not putting a ring on his finger pal. Are you putting it? No
No
Number 11 spam friends with memes and funny texts I okay
This is so true. This is so yes, I do this way more than Pat. I have to I
You said you guys just know this be it's it seems like more for me because nobody responds to me when I do it
I just said five messages in a row
They're spaced an hour apart
Let me see. What was the last what was the last I said a bunch of them yesterday. You can scroll through them
You said, "I just spit all over my computer from Disney+, heart emoji."
Remember that one?
That's true, I did do that.
Yeah, I sent you guys a picture of my poop.
Yeah, I sent a lot of troll faces too.
Your poop looked like a tadpole.
It was too dark of a picture, I couldn't really see what was going on.
That's why I thought it was funny, because I took it while I was on the toilet.
Also I'm looking and there's pubes in the toilet as well.
That's one of the worst photos of all time, dude.
horrible. Yeah that's not good. Number 12, get naked and dance around the street. I think
you'll uh, yeah this is a random thing to do in the middle of the night if you love
going to jail. Yeah that's true. Ooh. Skipping ahead here, number 15, try to summon Satan.
Top comment. I'm a wizard. No one tell me I ain't, cause I summoned a ghost yesterday
in my backyard at 8 o'clock. I found this ritual online and it worked. I don't know
if I trust this ghost though. Oh well.
[Laughter]
Here's another comment. At this point I feel like satin.
Yeah, I guess I've tried to summon Satan I guess before.
Yeah, have you guys done rituals?
I mean I've like sat in my bed and I've like prayed to the devil to see if he appeared.
Did you guys ever try to do a seance?
No. Have you guys ever tried to kill yourself just with your brain?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, just like sit in bed and you're just like...
Dude, I've thought about that. I've done that recently.
and see if I could kill myself. I mean there's gotta be some thought that's just insane enough
that just kills you like just having it will kill you like see I never just try to have a weird thought.
It's the way that it lights up your neurons. Yeah I just always try and yeah something just like causes a
massive stroke and makes you die. Yeah. There has to be some like Konami code for the brain that
kills you instantly. Yeah there's this story I read about like it was like we should try to think of it.
It's a sci-fi story about like these terrorists that invented a fractal that if you look at it
It like freezes your brain because like you can't process it because it's too complicated
Whoa cool thing in the world dude. Yeah, they try to do that with pig poop balls
It'd be funny if Pat was in that story and he was just completely immune
Just looking at like like a yeah looking just looking like I like into another dimension. Yeah
You guys don't see this
It's going like damn that guy looks like a squid
You guys want to watch TV guide?
Trivia
Watch the trivia show
Do you guys have TV guide on this TV man?
Do you guys remember the time my brother had a video game?
Number 16 make out
Do that all the time and we're bored
You do Patrick. I didn't know that about you Pat. I didn't know your boyfriend. What's wrong with that?
What's wrong with me making out with my boyfriend when I'm bored nothing, okay?
Anything
Number 18 number 18 is poop the comment from the 21 panic fan is bruh who does this?
is
all my uh...
all set to go to shit
all my god
do creepy rituals
do a creepypasta right now
let's do a creepypasta right now
all right you start
there once was a scary was a guy from nantucket yet but
and he got his head stuck in a bucket
is dick was out
and he screams
when a show
and he had a lot of that kind of christmas day
that's terrifying
sneak and start a fire on the lawn that's just arson
no thanks
be quiet
yet be quiet
honestly the most normal thing here
who the hell would go outside in the night
uh... somebody's not a vampire
found the not vampire yet
number uh... number twenty three quote howell
at the full moon
so sometimes i wish i was part wolf
me too as it was as lol i am a wolf now bitches
number twenty four is my favorite comment on the list twenty four is give
hickeys
My friends do this to me when we have sleepovers and my parents now think I'm gay
Yeah, I could I could see myself getting
Like a truth or dare thing, you know, yeah, it's like dude, it's like truth or dare we sit around we suck each other's necks
It's normal. I do we just we just watched Dracula 2000 dude doing the movie
I'm just trying to be a vampire at you. I think I'm Dracula. I'm like Gary Oldman
Dude, it's real shit though your mom in your room at a sleepover. That's a scary sight. Yeah. Yeah true
True as hell. I hate to see that. I hate when I see my mom at the number 25 is just play episode
So true dude, mm-hmm
face on a friend to text you're thirty-one ash yell out something random
on how it never takes my career never
never done that but for some reason i want to
pass a request live on air
are you not gonna like it
is it's me
are you serious man this again passes other we stop finding this funny like
eighteen episodes ago
now it started ever since me and and patrick both
side of the uh...
snow mystery he might have the same time which i guess now i'm saying that that's
not out yet
and so shut up
we have a friend like
you know some bird brains
now we have no brain with links and for your friendship we have a lot of
argentine c_n_n_ jimmy dean's sausage you know i think i might be a lot of it
might be controversial to some people out there but to me
life i love lovely
well
So you actually have changed my mind with your sweetness.
(laughing)
And I'm not mad anymore.
- Yeah, it's the love for me.
- Yeah, you actually wrote a poem so beautiful
that I'm crying, maybe not on the outside,
maybe not on the inside,
but at some point I'm gonna cry thinking about that.
- I'm crying right now.
- I'm crying right now,
and I'm thinking about that right now.
And I'm sad.
- I'm thinking about crying.
- You made me so sad, I can't be mad anymore.
Number 38, watch a video on full volume.
- Are you insane?
What is your problem?
- Do you have a mental condition?
Turn the volume down, dude.
What are you doing at 100?
- You never need full volume.
- 70 at the max, dude.
- Yeah.
- What the, you're--
- You know what, sometimes I'll watch it at full volume.
- Take it back, dude.
- Don't do that.
- Don't, you're-- - You never need full volume.
- There are kids that listen to this.
- I'll listen at full volume.
- You're endorsing a dangerous--
- Nine-year-old children that listen to this, Patrick.
- And they all have a Samsung soundbar
that goes to like 50 decibels.
- So?
- They're gonna see the movies too loud.
- And then they won't be able to hear anything at school.
- You know who really has a fucking problem
with this is my brother.
- Talk your shit.
- Yeah, let's do it.
- No, it's been pissing me off.
- Talk that talk, dude.
- He, I swear that we'll be streaming sometimes
and I'll have to text him.
- Can we get a beef alert?
- I'm beefing with him right now.
I'm beefing with him. - Beef alert.
He listens to his, he plays his TV too loud.
He watches these fucking Viking shows.
Don't know what they're called.
He's watching these damn Viking shows.
- More than one?
- I think it's one show.
- My brother is fucking Viking shows.
- I'm so sick of his fucking Viking shows.
- So what kind of like TV are you into?
Mostly Viking.
- Viking stuff.
- Mostly like Viking is my genre.
- Yeah, and full volume too.
I like Viking full volume.
Viking full volume is my show.
That's my favorite genre.
It's like a rom-com.
What's your favorite genre other than Viking full volume?
Viking full volume.
Hey, do you guys want to come over after school?
We're going to go watch Viking full volume.
We're going to watch a Viking full volume movie.
I'm in the mood for Viking full volume right now.
It's gonna be the loudest one we can watch.
[laughter]
Yeah, we're gonna watch a really quiet samurai movie, if you guys wanna come over.
We're gonna watch a clown movie on mute.
We're gonna watch the mutant clown.
Whoa.
What was that about, dude?
I think you actually...
We were joking around.
I think you may have just invented the coolest genre ever.
A mutant clown?
i was just
free associating and
you know i think i made a flight might have to be a little more free
association on the show
yeah where did you learn to improvise like that
rather than i got god damn dude
yeah
learn that for my boy robin williams goblin williams
well
Oh, I'm a goblin.
>> I was sobbing Williams when he died.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Goblin millions.
A million goblins, Lord of the Rings.
>> What else? >> Lord of my things.
>> Lord of my things. >> Need some new toys.
>> That's right.
>> And?
>> And need some more new toys.
>> Mm-hm.
>> I'm just getting stuck in that.
>> And I need more toys.
>> And more toys.
And I need toys and I need toys.
And I need more toys.
And everybody starts snapping, dude.
Like the goofy, like an extremely goofy movie.
I get angry like a bull seeing the color red.
Uh-huh.
I start charging the audience 'cause snapping, 'cause I think
they're snapping in my face.
Yeah, you think they're waking you up.
Yeah.
Number, the last three, number 49, turn on every light in the
house.
I did this when I was 12 and got into so much trouble.
Number 50, play dirty.
Yes, sir.
Number 51, do yoga. Do some unusual yoga poses.
I would never do unusual yoga.
In my eyes, dude, all yoga is unusual.
Why is that?
Um...
It's just kinda weird. You're on the floor.
Yeah.
Can you do yoga on your bed or on the couch?
If God wanted you to look in the shape like a tree,
He would have put your soul into a tree's body.
That's also true.
Namaste.
Cameron. Dash Cameron.
[laughter]
and i haven't made a new quote no i'll put i'm working on some what let's let's
let's run at the episodes and quotes
arica
needs to be one quote
uh... them
most beautiful part of life
examining
your your wife
caleb to act
uh...
let's
let's make kindness go viral
we have no one way what
uh... no he's get one
when i get a look at this one i now
okay uh...
this one is like
kind of maybe gonna be controversial but
uh... i also think that
is important a lot of people need to hear
hitler
was a bad guy
he stole that quote shut up no not done
not that
hitler
hitler was a bad guy
might've also been a sad guy
okay you know what you've convinced me
united and i think i i i think i quote
baby yoda's really added something to our lives
and that's why they call it disney plus
home
home i a christ
uh... i t
well
Alright subscribe to the Patreon guys
I'm gonna start flexing the space between my butt and my legs
*laughter*