You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts for the homeless.
You're a crap monster.
We're not being recorded.
Oh my god, Dan.
You're in our house now, dude.
You're fucking...
Welcome to Boston, boys.
Yeah, we have all of you on in Boston.
Welcome to fucking Boston, kid.
We have them in Boston.
and we're taking them to all the landmarks.
- Yeah.
- Taking them to Twin Donuts.
- This is where a bunch of guys got shot in the 1700s.
Okay, here's another place where a bunch of guys
got shot in the 1700s.
Here's a church.
All right, that pretty much covers it.
Let's go to--
- In this neighborhood, the white guys are really mean.
- In this one, they're really racist
against the black guys who don't live here.
- They're racist, but they still voted blue, baby.
Let's go.
- That's right, dude.
This whole neighborhood has never forgiven an imaginary black guy for saying Larry Bird wasn't that good.
They just get mad in their head.
Larry Bird, greatest ever, fucking do it dude, come on.
Better than fucking Jordan, for sure. Better than fucking Jordan.
Better than LeBron James. I bet he's taller than Yao Ming.
Look, he fucking understood the fundamentals, alright.
Yeah, triple threat position.
The fundamentals, push ups, pull ups, six pack of beer every night, that's the fucking fundamentals of the game.
You ever look at Larry Bird's shirts? He's got a fucking cock like a summer sausage in there.
That thing would bounce out, it would bruise other guys legs when they went to the block 'em, you know?
Hit 'em on the shoulder, they'd be like "What the fuck where'd this come from?"
It was his cock. It was the guy's cock.
And Larry Bird... Larry fucking Bird, he was the king of shit talking too.
He fucking, he told everybody "Hey, get out of my way." That's all he said.
He wasn't afraid to say the word.
You know what? He fucking, you know, he fucking conquered IBS. That's an achievement.
Yeah, I got an aunt that just looks just like him. Aunt that looks just like him.
He looks like a fucked up mubbet, dude. I miss him. I miss him every single day.
Larry Legend. Rest in peace.
Larry Legend.
Rest in peace.
They don't have handsome guys like that in the NBA anymore.
Nah, he had that kind of old school.
Gordon Hayward? No, he's got nothing on Larry Bird.
Oh, nah. He looks like...
Looks gross.
Bird looks like 007, dude.
He looked, I mean he was a fucking, he was a Casanova, stone cold killer.
That's why he got HIV.
Larry Bird, he looked like a young Bryce Dallas Howard.
Larry Bird was so handsome, he could have been on the OC.
He should have been on the OC.
I don't know why he wasn't on.
I mean and nowadays you got guys in the NBA like Tyrell Hello, you know?
Oh I love Tyrell Hello.
Yeah, I mean he's one of the best in the game right now.
I don't know why James--he's dating that chick James Charles, see, Oakley.
Aw man, James, that chick is so hot, dude.
Oh my god.
Flyer than a motherfucker.
Look at the ass on this bitch.
Shanks out there Shane Dawson, that guy gets so much pussy.
That guy gets so much ass.
It's insane.
Those YouTube guys.
They let Shane Dawson into the bubble.
He was foaming at the mouth.
He was saying, "Oh, I need pussy now!"
Yeah.
"Gimme pussy!"
"Ahh, gimme that!"
Yeah he's bringing Instagram thoughts in and they were fucking sucking his dick on
live okay yeah that's how much of a boss this guy is. Shane Dawson this dude
this dude's borderline criminal with how much pussy he gets and the way he gets
it. I mean save some for us man. You remember that uh that orange drink or
purple drink Crush? Donald Trump. That was named after Shane Dawson because that's
all he does is he crushes. He crushes Tang Tang with purple. And his penis is orange and purple.
He actually coined the term pussy
This is like fucking pussy to me man
He's been on YouTube like 10 years and that's when that started was that whole
He's the first guy to say pussy. Who's the first guy to say she
See before pussy was all everybody's saying cooter cooter some fucking cooter snatched
Yeah, piss pocket. And all these kids, these zoomers, they're going around talking about getting clown, getting tune.
Yeah, bro, I got some fucking clown last night. What's up? And then like... Dude, I got some sick Doberman last night.
Put my tube in the heat hole, you know, they're saying all that shit. The new one I heard is stooge, getting some stooge.
This all sounds like 1920s shit. Yeah.
Stooge is definitely... Oh man, we were necking last night, and I put my thing in her stooge.
get some Larry, get some Curly, get some Moe
oh man I got some shemp last night
I got some Moe, Larry and Curly bro
first she give me Larry, then she give me Moe
she give me Curly, now I'm ready to go
that'd be like the greatest Juicy J song ever
damn I got that Curly Joe I'm telling ya
yeah she gave me that Jerry Lewis know what I'm saying
She had me saying lady
Fuck did we introduce you guys I guess it doesn't matter. It's it's episode
You met these guys at the model in Austin this is like yeah, this is these are some Boston guys
we're gonna be so excited for this because this is like them this is like
the back table at the comedy cellar right now mm-hmm just like green room with
Paul Provenza this is like green room of Paul Provenza this is like green room by
Jeremy Saulnier you know at least half the people in here are Nazis the Boston
Garden yeah Madison Square Garden yep in Madison Square Garden in Boston this is
comedians and cars getting top. Hell yeah. Do comedians hang out in their cars after the
comedy show? Every single time dude. We do a set at the fucking pissing donkey and then
you hop in a hop in your your Fiat. A rav4 yeah. Yeah that's where you bring a couple of cuties in the
backseat a couple groupies. Yeah and we all watch a DVD on the flip down DVD player. Sorry babe the
seatbelts are broke. Hey we're gonna watch the elf special features in the back of my rav4.
You wanna get in the back of the safari we're gonna be watching small soldiers
I got a plug-and-play Galaga joystick in the back of the Honda pilot if you want to come and hang out
my
Early years I was actually like a comedy groupie
Just really like waiting for people to do shows and going how early have for after like ten or eight or nine years ago
Yeah, and you know I still do it, but like I'm not really much of a groupie cuz there's not a lot of comedy going on
So I'm just kind of like a old slut I guess
Okay, yeah, so do you give you give them those classic sluts? Do you give them whole I give them stooge?
You can just well I give them bottom stooge. I don't give top stooge no
That's not ladylike yeah, no cuz you know like it's like the difference between Hustler magazine and Playboy magazine
I was getting that Alfalfa, I was getting that Spanky.
Damn.
I was getting that Elmer Fudd from her last night.
I never give up that Stymie.
Uh-uh.
Dude, I saw her Gremlins and her Gremlins too.
I saw the new batch, god damn.
She's got a whole new group of gremlins.
She was begging for the little ET, you know what I'm saying?
I phoned her home.
What's up?
I went in there, she went, "Ouch."
(laughing)
My shit too big.
- Listen, if you're listening to this,
all you need to know is we all have a lot of sex
with a lot of different people.
- Amen.
- All the time.
- You got her in the back of the car with that TV
and you're making out and stuff
and she's trying to show you her boobs and stuff.
You're like, "Yo, you play Mario Kart?"
That's what I do.
She's trying to show your boobs.
You say, "Shut the fuck up!
Jon Favreau's making a Cubano right now!"
I don't want to see those disgusting tits.
What the fuck?
What, you think I'm 13 years old?
I'm watching Chef, bitch!
Sophia Vergara's in this.
She'd think I'm thinking about you.
In the backseat of Andrew's Subaru...
I would never use that word.
I would never use that word for a woman.
I wouldn't say that.
Caleb said that, but I don't agree.
Vergara?
You don't know Spanish.
That's why, bitch.
In the back of Andrew's Subaru Outback, he likes to time his orgasms with the point in
Small Soldiers where the Gorgons die.
Is that a thing that happens in that movie?
Do you actually know that movie?
I think one of them dies.
Okay, Charles, listen to something.
You got Archer, he's the emissary of the Gorgonites.
He's not the leader, he's the emissary.
You have Slamfist, you have Insaniac, you have Punch-It, you have--
Can you close your eyes so I can tell if you're reading or not?
have Frankenstein then I think there's a couple of others you have the the
commando elite which is major Chip Hazzard Brick Bazooka Nick Nitro butch
meat hook Kip Killigan and I think that might be it I'm sure I'm sure you got
Dennis Leary you got David Cross you have who's gonna you know it marks the
last on-screen film role of Phil Hartman who died before the film's American
premiere that's true yeah you have Kirsten Dunst who is the love interest of
the main character Alan Abernathy who is little bitch but and you know she gave
up because his dad had this sick his dad had the sick toy shop like toy trains and
everything like the sickest toys of all time he's like these toys are gay and
then like he discovers the toys that had accidental nuclear missile chips put in
them by accident so it made them alive whoo and that actually what happened in
(talking over each other)
- And like the big wig is Dennis Leary.
- Yeah.
- The king of comedy.
- Exactly, the king of Boston comedy.
- He still does comics.
He does comics come home every single year.
- Oh yeah, TD.
- He fills the Boston garden, or the TD garden,
which fits like 30,000 people.
He fills about 800 people into it
and gets like all of his road openers
and then Wanda Sykes, who is not from Boston.
yeah isn't this the most amazing comedy show in the world?
He's still doing like coffee stuff like skinny jeans at Starbucks and manbuns
what the fuck?
Small soldiers for a movie about soldiers that had a lot of coffee material
yeah
where do you get a black coffee in?
yeah they're like going over the plans and he's drinking a coffee like
God you put milk and sugar in this you homo?
What the fuck is this?
And I had a friend go to Boston or comics calling home or coming home or whatever and he told me that all the transitions
Were him just like repeating like the the comics jokes and then be like wasn't that great anyway? Here's
Leary's the fucking boss. Oh, but really a boss though. He would say their punchlines before they come out
Yeah, true. Yeah, he's like Flava Flav. I'm sure Andrew already knows this cuz he fucking rattled off all the small soldier shit
but the rodeo burger at Burger King
Amazing the rodeo burger barbecue sauce
That fried onions. It has the fried onions rings, right?
That was created as a promotional item for small soldiers. They still have it. It's a still there
So good that they fucking have to keep it on the menu. It'd be funny if they named it like the Gorgon burger
and they just have to call it that forever.
- They should've just kept Small Soldiers in theaters
all these years as a promotion for the burger.
- Right.
- Well, I think they should have, like,
Dina's Villain Wave makes Small Soldiers 2.
I think that's the next big thing.
- That'd be great.
- Oh yeah, after Dune.
- Small Soldiers had one of the best uses of,
one of the classic movie songs of all time.
♪ Wa ♪
♪ Hoo ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
- Edwin Stoddard.
- Wars.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
That used to be, I would go from the Open Mic that we hosted, I would go from there to the
Burger King up the road and I would just get like a rodeo burger and then go home.
So funny.
Can I get a Small Soldier's tour with that too?
I know you have them in the back.
Can I have a Small Soldier's burger please?
The Burger King I haven't had in years because like everything they make, you like burp it
up for like two days and when you shit it smells like it too.
And it's just so gross.
And then you get hungry for more Burger King because you're smelling the Burger King in
- I've seen you eat that fucking smell twice.
- They butter the buns, I don't like that.
I don't like that at all when they butter the buns.
- They should do a Dennis Leary burger
and it's just a black coffee and a condom
that they hand you in a bag.
(laughing)
- Right now, I'm drinking this porter over here.
Do you think, can I become the Dennis Leary?
Could I be the Dennis Leary of porters
where I'm like, coconut porter,
what happened to just a porter?
- Am I on fucking vacation while I drink my beer?
What the fuck?
I think Dennis Leary just hates adjectives.
I think that's just his thing.
Oh, baby Yoda. What the hell happened to Yoda?
Okay? Back in my day,
we were happy with an old
creepy green pig man.
[laughter]
He used to be
a little green guy.
Now he's even smaller?
Come on! What the fuck is this?
I don't think he's that current still. I think he's
that irrelevant where he's like,
"I saw the other day they had this fucking thing called Second Life."
(laughter)
- Yeah, that's the exact era that he's locked into,
is like mid 2000s.
- Oh yeah.
- Yeah.
- I can't wait until we're all that old
and we're all that watched. - Have you guys seen the show
called Equals Three?
I'm trying to get a spot on Equals Three.
- He's still doing material on the failed NBC show,
The Slap.
Have you seen The Slap?
- Look, it's based off an Australian show.
I don't know what the fuck's going on down there.
Their toilets turn different.
How about your toilets turn normal?
What's a mini-series?
Is that like a...
You're watching on a Motorola Razr?
What the fuck kind of show is this?
Caleb, your audio's all fucked up.
Your internet's bad.
You're freezing.
You keep freezing over and over.
He's got that classic New York Wi-Fi.
It's my spectrum Wi-Fi, dude.
People get mad at me because it's bad.
I gotta switch to FIOS.
Turn off your video or something.
You better shut up.
I just switched to you.
Fuck you.
Yes, sir.
You guys keep talking.
- Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, bop, bop, bop.
- No, it won't, trust me.
- It will disconnect you.
- Trust him!
- Trust me.
- I don't trust him.
- I don't trust Caleb about internet.
- Hey, brother, trust and believe.
- I'm a tech god, hold on.
- Yeah, see, your audio's just changed.
- I'm about to, I didn't even do a single thing, Patrick,
so that's how I know you're lying.
- Yes!
- It's louder in my ears.
- Yeah, you did get louder.
- It's better.
- It's just louder.
- Anyway, back to Dennis Leary, right?
- Yeah.
Dennis Leary is like, he's still got these fucking Survivor shows going.
Remember Survivor?
The guy walked around naked with his cock out?
Richard?
Remember him?
What happened to him?
Is he dead?
Is he in jail?
Nah, fuck it.
Isn't Bill Burr just Dennis Leary now?
Dennis Leary is Dennis Leary still, but Bill Burr is, yeah, he loves the bitch too.
Yeah, they just complain, right?
And I'm back, easy.
Yeah, fucking easy.
Who's that, wait, who's that guy from Survivor, Richard Hatch?
Yeah, he walked around naked.
Yeah, my mom met that guy.
I remember being a kid and that was going around and everyone was like, "You see this guy on Survivor that walks around naked? He's so hot."
They all wanted to fuck him.
My mom got a picture, my mom has a picture with Richard Hatch.
And I thought it was, I'd never seen Survivor.
And I didn't learn who he was until I was like 16.
I don't think you were born yet. I don't think you were born yet, Patrick.
I was, I was like 6, maybe, maybe like 4, I don't know.
But still, like, yeah, like it's...
He was a gang guy, right?
I was three.
And he walked around naked and he won a Subaru or something?
He won an Emmy for walking around naked.
Yeah.
Whoa.
Dream.
He walks around in public with an Emmy in front of his cock.
Yeah.
So he gets arrested.
That's how he avoids public nudity laws.
Right.
And anyway, yeah.
Hey, what's next?
Survivor Mars?
You guys want to go to Mars?
Yeah, I just thought Richard Hatch was an uncle I didn't know for a long time.
- I was growing up, Earth was growing up for us.
- Everybody so familiar, it's crazy,
Survivor's not really around anymore, is it?
They still do Survivor? - It is, yeah.
- Really? - Yeah, Survivor Boston.
- My brother has seen every season, it's awesome.
- My mom buys the bootleg DVDs off of eBay.
- Survival. - That'll just have
Survivor seasons on them.
And then you'll get this sun-faded photo
of a low-resolution picture of the Survivor logo
on like four burn CDs.
I'm like, mom, why are you paying for this?
What the fuck are you doing?
- It's also crazy--
- I should have shown you BitTorrent like 15 years ago.
- It's crazy that there wouldn't be
just like survivor seasons available
that she could buy anywhere but eBay.
- I would never bring up BitTorrent to my mother.
Are you kidding me?
I'm never having that.
- Give me your phone number.
- Give me, hold on, let's get her number.
- I can explain anything to you.
- All right, let's get my mom on the line.
I'll patch her through.
- Yeah, here she is.
Hey, beautiful Mrs. Branson, how are you?
Hey mom, what did they used to call pussy in the old days?
They called it cooter!
[laughter]
Yeah, pre-Shane Dawson, what'd they call pussy?
Have you seen this James Charles chick?
She's hot to trot, huh ma?
God damn, she's got a horse ass, huh ma?
Yeah, you can just tell!
You can look at her
and just bite your bottom lip
and go, "Ooo, I know that pussy is
so good!"
God damn, what a femme fatale.
Shane Dawson was actually fucking James Charles when he came up with the name
Pussy. Yeah he was like whatever this thing is that's Pussy for sure. If I know one thing, it's that I'm
fucking Pussy right now. Yeah. Do you guys want to talk about this list?
What the fuck are we doing here? No, no
You build our own on survivor
Bowling ball, what the fuck is this? Huh? It's got three holes in it. I put my fingers in here. I can't even there's no pins here
What the fuck? Oh
So I'm supposed to kill a fucking boar now, okay, I guess I'll go get a spear
Yeah, I'll get a spear. Sure. I'll throw it. Whatever. Oh, they got to create Alliance
What are they you the United Nations? Oh great. That's awesome. What is this Star Wars? We're creating alliances now. Jesus. Okay
I'm the fucking rebel Alliance. How about that? I got my own fucking Alliance over here, huh?
How about my fucking dick? I'll just stand over here being have a fucking Jar Jar Binks. How about that?
Oh, yeah
Me so wanna poop boo
Me so wanna fuck all the girls here. How about that? How about I say that?
Yeah, yeah, I'm gonna win. I'm gonna win
Yeah, Jedi mind tricks don't work on me, huh? Only money.
I know that's Wado, I don't fucking care.
Hey, they should do Survivor Boston, huh? See if people can...
That's a good idea.
At our college, when we were in college, they did a...
like a...
Survivor, I guess Survivor has like audition series that they do.
at like different colleges in the United States
where they'll do like,
they'll fund a student-led version of Survivor
that just takes place at the college.
And then they will like, like a farm league,
they'll take kids from that
and put some of them in reality shows.
- G League Survivor.
- Yeah. - Exactly.
- G is fucking crazy.
So what you get is you just get like college psychos
who are just like, like mostly theater kids,
at least at our school.
- Oh yeah, 'cause they wanna make it,
we gotta get their face out there.
- We had a couple friends on it.
I know that I know we had a couple of people who are 19 and want to be famous.
Yeah, Cameron. Yeah, Cameron was kind of the like, I was kind of like the
psychopathic bitch. Yeah, one.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, it's crazy. It all took place in the Boston Common, too,
which was like, yeah, just like, you know, that's just a city park.
That's just tourists and homeless people. And I honestly I don't know why
that I mean, I understand why the cops really got these got to get these hot
dogs grilled or else
the night that is seriously as some of the fucking challenges are it'll be like
you have to do this puzzle in under an hour yeah there's nothing like fucking
survivor dude right you got to play ultimate frisbee for a couple hours
yeah we had he under a dorm room couch who just made them do useful chores
like you got to clean up all the leaves in this park and all the homeless people
out of the park all this beer and take all this Adderall dude good luck man the
producers were really mad when I did that for my college and I I killed a pig in
the middle of the park they said. I thought this was Survivor. Didn't Alex and Joe our
friends Alex and Joe like watch that like religiously? I guess the real appeal of that is like
imagine Survivor but you know every single person on it. That's true. Like
that's the best version of Survivor. Oh yeah that's got that's has to be fun it's
like I'm gonna get your ass. I like the idea of a survivor that you can betray people multiple
times. Yeah you can you can like triple cross somebody. Just like sociopath practice it's
wonderful. Oh I mean like that's okay we earlier we were talking about uh it wasn't this. Small
soldiers. Oh yes. Yeah no let's talk about that again. Let's keep going with that. So we're
talking about not on this but when we recorded the E1 we were talking about like you are
the weakest link is that your final answer you're fired and the other one was voting
someone off the island.
What did they say?
Great shit.
They would just hold it up to the camera right and then like cast it silently like kind of
forlornly like well I have to do what I have to.
Yeah.
I like this person but they got to fucking burn.
I think the line was.
Fucking die.
Fuck you.
Get the hell off this island.
Get your white ass off the side!
I think that was the exact one.
That was Richard Hatch's catchphrase.
It was zooming in and out of their face really fast, like boing-yong-yong-yong-yong-yong-yong.
The trap door opens underneath them and they just fall.
What happened to reality shows, man? Now it's all fucking Minute to Win It and whatever fucking Ellen does.
Yeah, we need Rock the Love back.
Have you guys heard of the reality show The Circle? It was like a new Netflix one.
I watched it with my girlfriend. It's crazy.
Everybody's everybody's like dating each other through a computer. It's like it's like it's like a reality show
That's based on like social media and so you can like other people and shit. I also have a girlfriend so I had to watch this
Amazing timing
Funny that like Branson manifested her
Wait, Patrick, do you have a girlfriend?
Can we edit this out Cameron?
Anyway, I just I are gonna move in together. Yeah, I'm moving in with Andrew. We're having a bachelor pad
They're gonna share a bedroom that's a big circular bed. It's a heart-shaped bed.
They're all twin beds that are pushed together.
Well, here's what I want to know.
Here's what I want to know.
How you getting these
Pardon my language, these hoes in that sweet pad.
I mean, what are you doing?
- A ladder.
- A catapult.
(laughing)
- A perfectly aimed catapult right into an open window.
Now that you're here, would you like a martini?
- These women are building siege weapons
to attack our apartment.
(laughing)
Get up in our apartment and fuck us.
- Yeah.
- And we're all like, no, no, don't do that.
- I'm going over to their new apartment
and I'm about to open the door and Andrew stops me.
says if you open that door a cauldron full of boiling pitch will fall on you
yeah a big bucket of lube is gonna fall on you. Bucket of lube that's not that scary
something boiling that might stop me if I'm a girl I'm worried about my skin
women come to the gate of our apartment. You say the gate?
Rattling the bars. It's Baldur's Gate. There's a pork colas and Patrick Eyre up there with their hoods and their
class will say "OI! Who's that there?"
Better not be any more snatch! Better not be any more snatch down there!
Have enough of that lately!
We have a cooter here, thank you please!
I hate pussy, I don't like it! I don't like it!
It's all red! Open a window, it smells like stooge!
You don't come in here unless you bring a lobster with ya!
Oh that's right, the Lords have been enjoying quite the reverie of all that lately.
"Oh, c'mon, look, oh dude!"
"Hoo, hoo, hoo, hoo, hoo!"
That's the toady. Which one, who's that?
Who's that in real life? Which one is that?
That's Igor, from Frankenstein.
Oh, that's the actual Igor you guys know?
Yeah, there's gonna live in the castle.
"Hoo, hoo, hoo, hoo, hoo, hoo!"
"Look at that Larry, hoo, hoo, hoo, hoo, hoo!"
"Look at this guy's getting shamp, hoo, hoo, hoo, hoo, hoo!"
"Hoo, hoo, hoo, hoo, hoo, hoo!"
"Oh, they're getting so much clout, hoo, hoo, hoo, hoo!"
Do you know what my favorite part of sex is?
It's, uh, the orgasm.
orgasm. Ugh. Not for me. I gotta take a leak. I'll be right back. Why's that? Not for me.
Hey, buddy. Different strokes for different folks, I suppose. I like the end. I try to
actually get as fast to the end. What about the journey, though? Because I like it so--
Oh, no. The journey is boring. I feel like the journey is the most important part. The journey's even worse. It's like doing push-ups. It hurts. And the end is like--
It's like the end of doing push-ups when you feel good. Yeah. Push-ups that make you feel good.
yeah I've always like like part in the middle where you put your shirt back on
she's like hey can you come on okay I just be real here all right yeah either
either you turn the lights off or the shirt goes on yeah could you also wipe
the sweat off of your forehead it keeps getting and I do and then I do my
British voice as you wish my lady Simon says during the whole time yeah yeah I
was kind enough to give you my stooge and you just keep doing impressions of
toweling can you okay first I'll give you my stooge and now you're doing
Philip Seymour Hoffman to me while we have sex yeah real quick can you take
off the tap shoes I mean seriously can you take the tag off your new era fitted
hat at least if we're gonna know no I'm
gonna return and have you realize that
ruins the entire value of the hat you
fucking money you bimbo can you please
just uncross your eyes just literally
give it for a second you keep sitting
there you're going cookie monster on
the flat brim and that's why her eyes
are could you could you please when you
orgasm this time not say did I do that
in the Urkel voice. You please. It'd mean a lot to me. Yeah you don't say mamma mia
papa pia baby gotta come for real-a. You don't pull out a cigar much and go I
like you kid.
All right we're about halfway through so I feel like we should. Yeah that's good enough.
So what's this whole thing you guys do? Okay all right I get that you climb off your
giant fucking mountain to come do our little operation here but how about you
listen up because you're in our house now I'm just saying it's kind of like a
play thing for the listeners they know what you do I'm just playing like what
do these guys do I don't know I don't listen to podcast I just do that I just
record shit I get it you're the talent okay I'm asking you do one of your
little episode one two three I don't care do I actually picked this list
specifically for you guys because I think this like really plays to your
strengths. Welcome to episode one this is Pot of Hot Licks. Well we maybe didn't specify earlier but we charge by the
amount of things on a list when we come on a different podcast. Ah shit. So I hope this is a short list for your sake.
Wait sorry. God damn it Cameron this has like. We don't get out of bed for less than five large. We get more exposure per the list.
This has 51. Yeah we need about a hundred exposure per each item. Shit. I know I know
I know you guys like to do, you do your little stories and your, your, whatever you do.
We're dreamers!
You little, you know what, who cares, whatever it is you guys do.
But I know that you guys love to do, you guys like to make silly songs.
You guys like to make parodies like, like, um, All the Fall Guys by Blink 182, that kind
of thing.
I know you guys are really into the song, silly song scene.
No, all our songs are serious, dude.
I don't know if you fucking, are you saying you thought those were funny?
Yeah.
they were very funny and I laughed at them. This guy laughs at everything sad. Yeah, that's
true. That's fucked up. We were putting our heart on the line and you guys just had us
here to mock our- But doctor, I am Pagliacci, right? I remember that. So these are best
ideas for a song title. Yeah, this is best ideas for a song title created by user Dynastinobel.
It's a cool name. This is helpful because usually songwriters just can't come up with
the title. They have a great melody. We have the song Best Song Ever but we don't have a name.
They already have the lyrics but what do I call it? Look at song 2 by Blur. Yeah, they had no clue what to call that.
Look at how many untitles there are. They should have called it WooHoo.
They should have called it WooHoo. They're stupid. Scott Walker, what's he got? Track 5, Track 6, Track 7.
fucking what is he doing hold up also how many how many bands you see have a
song called intro you fucking kidding me Charles had a super exhausting bit that
he wanted to make a band named various artists mm-hmm I remember that bit well
- I'm not exhausted yet.
Continue.
- That's it.
- Okay, number one on this list is Filet-O-Fish.
- That's not true.
- No.
- We're not talking about that, man.
Come on.
- Wait, what is that?
What is the Filet-O-Fish?
- That's an idea I had.
- It's a sandwich at McDonald's.
We're moving on.
- No, it's not an idea you had.
- Oh, what is your idea then?
- Branson's been talking to me about it.
I think he talked about it first.
- Look, I'm not gonna talk about this yet, all right?
Maybe we get this at the end of the episode.
- All right, I'll take that deal.
- All right, Pat, you have until then
to think of what that is.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- Good luck, my friend.
I mean, I already told Cameron.
- I hope you just aren't copying my filet-o-fish idea.
- No.
You don't even have one, so.
- No, he wrote it on E1, that was it.
- I did text it to you.
- Yeah, I did text it to Cameron.
- I have it on my phone right here.
- Can you read it for us?
- See, it's right there.
I did see something right there.
You guys see that?
Best idea for a song title, number one, "Run Away With Me."
I mean, is that not the most beautiful thing you've ever seen?
So beautiful.
It's so romantic to like, leave a place.
Or just go jogging.
True.
Did she do that?
She must have looked at this list.
Did she run away?
That literally is one of her song titles.
"Run Away With Me"?
Oh, well fuck this then.
She stole it.
She stole it?
She didn't steal it, she had the idea.
She looked to Google "best ideas for a song title"
So she's resourceful, she sounds like a great gal to me.
Sounds like you're trying to get in her pants.
Isn't she like fucking 30 by now?
Yeah, what is she? She's old as shit.
You don't run away at like 30.
You're where you're at.
I think you're being real constrictive of what a woman can do Branson.
A 30 year old woman is not running away.
away if she is she's a fucking mess now but he's gonna text me and Andrew
tonight like dude I'm doing it I'm running away from home I'm a real messy
32 year old run away I'm packing a bag I'm putting one toy yeah I'm putting a
maybe she's in a cult oh running away from the cult or to join the cult that
changes well that's like that that's like the ambiguity that makes the song
like you know she's just a Jehovah's Witness she's running away from one cult
to another cult maybe she's just really scared maybe she saw a scary guy or a
scary monster and she's telling him to run away with her you're making no
another she has a pet or a friend or something I'm the guy or Andrew is there
Andrew you're not the guy she's not gonna run away with you dude shut the
fuck up you guys all have girlfriends I can hey hey Andrew you would be the
scary guy let me tell you something yeah here's what happened I gotta work I gotta
work Friday so you have to work on your on your plan to capture and scare Carly
Ray Jepsen she's gonna see you she's gonna go she's gonna turn to me don't
listen to them she's like a Metal Gear Solid soldier there's gonna be a you're
You're a fucking 10, Andrew.
She would be lucky to have you.
That's not true.
I'm like a six.
Yeah, a $10 bill.
I can buy a Subway sandwich with you,
you fucking monster.
When I see a woman, I also get the Metal Gear Solid
exclamation point above my head,
and I go, "Look, a box!"
(laughing)
Jizz!
A stooge!
I get the, I'm like the NBA's scarred stew
where I see the exclamation point,
and then I see the woman, I go, "Huh?"
I'm like NBA 2K and I get fire above my head and it's just "He's heating up!"
Number two is Hit Me Baby.
That's half of an existing title.
Yeah exactly.
That's already a song.
Also that's either about domestic violence or blackjacks.
It's the prequel to Hit Me Baby One More Time.
Or about training your fighter child.
was yeah maybe one more time about domestic violence. No it's about blackjack.
Yeah. What's she talking about like getting stuck? I mean let's be real she's talking
about getting fisted over there right? She's talking about getting like fucking
stuck. She's trying to get stuffed like a turkey. Let's be honest. Yeah. That's nice.
You guys are disgusting. I'm sorry. Andrew I take it back you're not a
monster oh that's where you're wrong brother no he's the loco gringo for my
one of my favorite videos of a guy or the guitarist and slipknot there's a
video of him or so I like an interview goes up to him and it's like like man
you got a scary mask are you a monster and he just goes you have to ask my wife
and then leave. That's so cool. Solid bet. Yes, he's a monster. Please get me away from him. He is a monster. Solid bet. Yeah.
Is he insinuating that he fucks like a Frankenstein? Yeah, that's the thing is it's
completely unclear. It could be something really bad or something really cool.
If you want to do a witty retort, you just bring up your wife though. That's why most
people get married. The documentary Some Kind of Monster was about that one guy from Slipknot.
Yeah, the guy from Slipknot idolizes Rodney Dangerfield.
Yeah, most Slipknot songs are about Rodney Dangerfield bits.
Right. Yeah.
That Slipknot song about your doctor asks for a stool, semen, and urine sample so he
gives him his underwear and he leaves. That's what that song is about.
Hey, let me tell you. Yeah.
I forgot all the Slipknot lyrics.
As soon as I did the Rodney Dangerfield.
I felt that he rise up in me.
Yeah. Slipknot has lyrics?
Yeah, no, it's just screams.
Slipknot.
I thought they were just saying bullcrap.
These guys are scary looking, huh?
I thought the lead singer was a dog.
Hey, hey, let me tell you, I did my time and I won out of my marriage.
Yeah, "Hit Me Baby" could be a Rodney Dangerfield song title.
Yeah, true.
Hit me baby.
Yeah.
I need to buy a new TV for my wife.
It's the only way I can come.
Hit me baby.
(laughter)
My wife told me, "Hit me baby, one more time."
And I said, "Hey, I'm on parole."
(laughter)
Number three, I will hurt you.
Huh.
What?
Okay, this guy's, whoever made this list is a--
Is a freaking psycho.
The two comments on this one are,
"Sounds like a bossy bitch," and "Sounds bitchy."
(laughter)
Who made this list?
It's like Ted Bundy made this list.
It's a bunch of kids.
Yeah.
Here's a list of--
It's Dynaston, it was made by Dynaston Noble, who I just clicked on their profile
and their bio is "I'm Dynaston Noble and I'm a middle school teenager whose life
is disrupted by darkness."
Aren't we all bud? I think we need to save him. Send him the healing power of Jesus
Christ. Well he's probably like 40 now. I think he needs to discover the power of comedy. True. That's a really, yeah we should
send him a DVD copy of Brass Eye. Uh-huh. That'll save his life. Look I have one I can send it. I think we
should send him a Dane Cook special. Yeah. True. I can send him my Dane Cook
vicious circle tour t-shirt. I can send him that. It's not a bad idea. Yeah. I'm
gonna call him on the phone. I'll send him a VHS copy of a Bill Hicks stand-up special. You need Bill Hicks,
George Carlin, you need the latest Dave Chappelle special where he bitches about
trans people for an hour. Uh-huh. Exactly. George Floyd. That's what's funny now. That's what's
funny now, you know? Because he's this guy who disappeared for like a decade, then he came back
and was like, "Well, I'm gonna say this because I'm right and everyone's gonna agree with me." It's
like, "All right, man." Well, he's a tricky situation because it's like a caveman got
unthought. Right. Like, he really, none of that was happening when he went in, and then he comes
out and he's just surprised. And we got to give him a couple years of him saying horrible shit.
- That's where it's like, it's cool man, he's like,
- Shut up. - I'm buff.
I'm buff now.
- He did get so buff in Africa, dude.
- That's true.
You know what's a weird thing about Dave Chappelle?
He loves to skateboard.
That's a--
- Really?
- That's just a fun fact about him.
- Well, he watched so much Jackass,
he's like, oh, these guys are really funny,
they're really funny, but they also all skateboard,
so I'm gonna be like them.
- Exactly.
- Hey, do any of you guys skateboard?
- I do.
- Okay, when are you gonna give that up?
'Cause I see like old guys skateboarding
and it's fucking depressing.
That is one of the best questions ever asked on this show.
When are you gonna give it up, man?
He's 23 years old.
We need an exact date, Patrick.
Yeah, that's still young enough, though.
Probably when I get bone spurs or some shit.
I think you have to stop when you're the oldest guy at the skate park.
No, 'cause even then, that's the guy who teaches the kids about the old skaters.
Nobody fucking cares.
Are you native American?
fucking well this is how Bucky Lasek did it no one gives a fuck people do no
skaters do
I got this one right here I think 40 is a good age to yeah 17 years left to
skateboarding yeah yeah but like you still have guys like who are like the
best ever do it like Rodney Mullen who are like 80 years old and they're still
out there like just want to ride bro that's a goal they're gonna have a
senior tour they gotta get rich enough to have their own shit in their backyard
so they don't subject people to it yeah he's the original street skater bro he's
got to be on the streets you're thinking you're thinking of Mark Gonzalez Syria
you're getting all your history mixed up. I hate you dude. I fucking hate you. I wish I never asked you.
I can't believe you opened the Pandora's Box and brought up skateboarding.
Alright, so, I have a question though. I have a question to follow up Brant's question.
Does skateboarding have to do with the Filet-O-Fish idea? Look, I'm not gonna
talk about that right now. Oh, it could be a skateboarding trick. Filet-O-Fish could,
that does Charles shut the fuck up yeah they keep um in in the in the new Tony
Hawk the remaster they keep renaming tricks for some reason they renamed
Smith grinds to Monty grinds cuz in the 2000 they're probably all like slurs that
they did yeah well yeah there's the Smith the Smith grind was originally called
that because it was a guy named Smith who ground like a minority's teeth into
the curve. That was a big problem. Let's change it to Monty Grind, because Monty was a guy
who ground a white guy's teeth into the ground. Yeah, Monty Python. They named it after Monty
Python. It's the dead parrot grind. But you're still riding Mongo in the game. Did they change
the Hitler air? No. No, the Hitler air stays. It's still you go up in the air and pretend
you're on a cross like Hitler. Yeah, and then they have the Hitler air to Mengele flip, and
still in there. Mangala Flip would be a great name for a skate trick honestly.
I think that a Mangala Flip is just when any white person moves to South America.
Also I think all these tricks would be less offensive if they were done by a cartoon
like why don't they have Bart Simpson in the game yet? They got Spiderman in it.
I think because it's in a game everybody does a cartoon. Spiderman does skateboard in Pro Skater 2.
No but fucking Bart Simpson actually skateboards in real life not just some
Well, he's a car. He made his own game. They had a Simpsons. Cars are you saying that spider-man's a poser and Bart Simpson is a real?
What I was a hundred percent. I legitimately believe that
Bart Simpson rides a cruiser. He doesn't even ride a real you better not fucking better. Watch yourself next time
You're in New York City talking in diapers. He can kick flip it though. Yeah
You're like my biggest problem about the old names in skating and you're not gonna tell him about Bart Simpson
I think Scott is the worst thing about skateboarding. Yeah. Yeah
Why do you not so much it it was just goldfinger and in pro skater - that's it our new
Is people still making skies Scott's the sweatiest doughiest guys all banging their heads together
like with t-shirts and checkered shoes I'm going like
And it is fucking epic it was really funny in like 15 years to make a ska band
I think yeah, I would love to maybe I'll get addicted to heroin and start playing a fucking p.s.
I'm like a bongo
What I think I'd be sick dude we have six people here we could form a scub and we oh my god
We need like three more guys on the whole
Play the trombone. Yeah. Oh, yeah, that's right. Cameron can play trombone. I can play bass
How does it make any money when there's nine of they don't you don't get paid in money?
You get paid in fucking Cameron Cameron knows all of the mighty mighty Boston's he knows all of them
I don't my parents know some of them, but
Now you know the point you're wrong
Number number four this girl hates Mondays
That's already
Here's and here's a comment
I think it's a good title because it can relate to any age really and you go wild with the song
in this girl's Garfield?
Yeah, the female Garfield.
What emoji is that? That's the party horn emoji.
One of my friends growing up, his mother was referred to all of us by Garfield
because she had orange hair and she often complained.
That was it.
The thing about Garfield is that, say what you will about his comedy, but he was right about most things he said.
That's true.
History will vindicate him. I mean lasagna kicks ass. Yeah. Yeah
Dog shit. Yeah, it was a loser Odie was stupid as hell. Mm-hmm
Nermal don't even get me started. Nermal was straight up the devil. Uh-huh
That cat got the devil in him. Let me
know
Normal normal got the devil
normal often gets persecuted
What is the behavior of normal any worse than the behavior of Garfield himself?
No
Abuse odi and mock John relentlessly
Yeah, I gotta let normal go. Yeah, y'all know the prosecution may be
Confusing Garfield for for Heathcliff
See when he brought up the evidence about him being homeless
that that was that was Heathcliff that would not Garfield. I present to the
jury October 17th 1996 comic strip where Garfield kicks Odie off the table not
once not twice but three separate times and you gonna tell me normal is the
problem here? Garfield's so famous it would be hard to get him into court like
you know how they have to like find a place where the where the case isn't
well-known yeah put him in a put him in a crate that's true yeah he's a guy he's a
goddamn cat the guy that does all the drawings for the court cuz there's no
cameras a lot as Jim Davis
started it was a real story he drew the cat in court
Garfield looks in the original strips where Garfield is just like a fucking mountain of
fat shit.
Yeah.
Oh he looks...
It's like the original Simpsons, like season one they just look like fucking monsters.
They still look like monsters.
They look terrible.
Yeah.
But also they hadn't figured out the voices yet at the time.
Yeah it's like Burr's like "Wow, wow, Homer, where you at?"
It's like a fucking fever dream in the hotel.
Homer's like slippery, like he's like this like jelly that like slips through the episode
like just a guy chained to a bed trying to get off a heroin and he's just
imagining Tracy Oldman show Simpsons yeah I think that's what the Simpsons is I
need butterfingers right now I don't know what's going on I fucking need
butterfingers that's it do you guys think the Simpsons the people on the Simpsons
that are supposed to be white people.
Do you think they all smell like banana runs?
- Like Carl?
- Like banana runs?
- Yeah, I mean they're bright yellow.
- Oh, you're talking about a candy.
I thought you were talking about some--
- Are you insinuating that people just smell
like the candy that is their skin color?
- Yeah.
- So what do you smell like?
- Mahogany.
- Maybe I smell like fucking nougat.
- You are not nougat.
- My client has alabaster skin or the ivory complexion.
He do not represent Nougat in the slightest!
[laughter]
Uh, number five.
I'm gonna take a zero bar, baby.
[laughter]
Wait, zero bar is a fucking good--
--what Andrew was on trial for in that?
Yeah, no, zero bar is underrated.
Oh, I'm a southern lawyer who only represents transracial clients.
[laughter]
So Nougat was the race he was trying to be?
Yeah, and he's obviously--
he looks like that French Moon movie.
Now I wanna talk about how I'm Portuguese.
Alright, that's all.
I'm from Brazil. That's where I'm from.
I'm from Brazil.
My client has clearly stated he is not white.
I wonder what he was.
Excuse my Cajun demeanor.
He is Acadian. He is not white.
I'm from Brazil. Or as I would say, "Bah-seel."
(laughing)
- My cousin Gambit.
- I wanna talk to y'all about a reggaeton.
(laughing)
- Y'all like Bad Bunny.
Y'all know Bad Bunny?
You gotta eat rain.
- Real quick, can I get a J Balvin meal, real quick?
- Can I get a J Balvin meal, real quick?
- Real quick, and I'm gonna get one of those.
- You don't know Baba Boss Simpson?
(laughing)
- See, basically he had invented a skateboard.
Basically he the first skateboard.
- Basically, it's a big green skateboard
with purple wheels and blue trucks.
- Boss Simpson, he from Baton Rouge.
I grew up with him in the swamp.
He from Baton Rouge.
- This little guy, he's a little prankster.
I never would've known because of his orange shirt.
He's got a big old bright old shirt.
- Y'all heard of him?
- In the movie, they showed his peggo.
(laughing)
- Wait a minute, wait a minute. - Wait around here,
look like a little shrimp.
- Wait around here a little bit.
- My boy Moe, he used to call Moe, right?
Moe, down in the swamp, Moe.
He used to call him with a wicked prank
from the devil brain, man.
(laughing)
You got that good then, man.
- Hang around Baton Rouge long enough,
you're gonna see Marge Simpson
walking down that cops on the street.
(laughing)
I tell you what, I swear, on Jesus Christ name.
- You might see a peep out too, Mr. Homer, right?
I mean, I mean you might you might be eating a donut one day look the other way don't hug on man
Don't get me started on mr. Burns
Mr. Burns he could probably sell me out of voodoo. He got all the money
But he he he he'll mean me he nasty
I'm not gonna do I'm not gonna do the voice
But I'm just imagining a black Israelite talking about how Smithers was once a black man
help a he like Louisiana chupacabra I'm gonna skip ahead on this list just
because uh there's a bunch of them um wait you're gonna skip number eight
why don't you just rattle off I was gonna skip I was gonna skip I was gonna
skip to number eight okay number eight is cookies and cream number eight okay
- Okay, cookies, let's talk about that for 10 minutes.
- Charles, go ahead, go ahead.
- Charles, sing what you think cookies cream is right now.
- I'm out cutting with a cookie monster.
He loves our cookie cream.
- Now you don't wanna get down to the bayou
when you see the cookie monster.
You don't wanna--
- Now my dad says he looks like cookie and cream,
but everyone focus on that cookie looking nice and dark,
but there's cream not of a lot of complexion in the cookie.
The cookies, your honor, are a fool's gold of some.
within the cream. If you would make an amalgamation of the entire color you
won't find that it is close to the cream. Now these were mega stuff cookies and
cream let me tell you real quick. Number eight is the body of boys and the only
comment is a bunch of question marks and exclamation points and then in all caps
What?
Can't do it man.
He gets a pass because he's a middle school teenager.
I guess so.
He can talk about boys bodies all he wants.
But you better cut that shit out.
What's happened to this damn thing?
This shit feel weird.
Number 15, lip gloss stance.
The top comment,
"This is a great idea, it could have any meaning."
That's just,
isn't that a line from a train song?
from a train song? Man shut up number 16 murderous miracle now this is my
favorite comment here because this person wrote out the whole chorus. Hey
buddy every murder is a miracle to me. Caleb will you sing the
will you sing the chorus that's written here yeah number 16? Maybe the chorus
goes how am I how oh sorry I fucked up. How I am that lonely in the stars where did I
I'll go wrong and take this too far. I'm not gonna say it no more. No, no, I'm gonna have it all tour
I'm not okay, and I promise I might punch life with my fist. Whoa is me. I'm in a full circle
Oh, baby, it was all right from here like a murderous miracle
Pretty good. It's a good chorus. Yeah, it says it reminds them of a 90s grunge rock song with teen angst lyrics from
2000 emo song I had cam set this whole thing up so I can do one of y'all songs
Had a time to long vibe to it. I'm I was getting a vibe. Oh, that's the only band I've ever
Song with that title and those lyrics already so you have to come up with something new fuck. Can you do an Owl City voice?
Which one is our city?
Firefly a million
You would not believe your eyes
fireflies
Pretty good pretty good dude. I knew those two guys in Cajun voice so
Song just sounds like a new app. It's just like what the whole thing fireflies all city just sounds like an app to me
Yeah, cuz these people have their fucking man buns. They got the fucking skinny jeans. Let's go
Fucking Bernie. Mm-hmm. Do you think they drink?
Fruit Seattle
Bullshit, that's what I call it. That's what the flavor I call it bullshit. What the fuck is a large?
Can I get a venti coffee, please?
It was such to be the the barista at the coffee shop where Dennis Leary goes every day
Like you know the fuck I'm gonna say
(laughter)
And she's like, "You want a black coffee?"
And he's like, "Fuck, yeah."
(laughter)
No, actually, can I try one of those frappuccinos?
Can I have a coffee flavored coffee?
So just coffee?
Yeah.
Number 22 is kind of like a riff on a Korn song here.
It's N-I-K-E.
What's a Korn song?
Oh, like Adidas.
Yeah, like Adidas, yeah.
And the comment here is,
could stand for no innocence kill everyone let's go that's kind of that's kind of
violent I think yeah that's kind of like Drake it's kind of like Drake's name
true middle schoolers think like the coolest thing they can do is like kill a
a guy yeah you want hello she wanted to drink the wax it's too strong you're
burning scented candles yeah it's the it's the lava scent dude it's a fucking
- It's lava.
- Yeah.
- I'm smelling it now, I don't want to--
- Alana's like, "I just feel like making a sacrifice.
"I don't get it, like, it's a scent.
"It just makes me want to throw someone in a volcano.
"It's weird."
- Yeah, Branson's just lighting
the Joey Diaz flavored candle.
(laughing)
She's like, "What the fuck is this, dude?"
- Yeah, this fucking candle smells like North Bergen.
That's what this fucking candle smells like, yo.
It smells exactly like Jersey.
It smells like fucking Hoboken and North Bergen.
It smells like fucking Santeria, I'm telling you.
I got my Boston Garden candle.
Silly, you fuckin' grab his ass. It fuckin' stinks.
[laughter]
Sounds like Joe Rogan's head in the hot Austin heat, dog. Real shit.
Yeah, that man's fuckin' sweatin' in there.
That's where he fuckin'.
I don't even know what voice that is. That didn't even sound like Joey Diaz.
I don't know.
It's a kind of a monster...
Yeah, that's what he sounds like.
It sounds like a five-foot-two...
I sound like Joey Diaz having a stroke.
[laughter]
A genius.
Yeah man, my fuckin' arm stopped working before I got here.
I'm basically just gonna ignore it.
Yeah I don't know what's happening but my whole left fuckin' side, my whole left side has stopped
working.
Smell fuckin' toast.
What the fuck?
Fuck I'm hungry, gimme the toast.
Stop fuckin' stop.
Somebody find that fuckin' toast.
Unplug that fuckin' toaster now.
Where's the toast?
Can somebody scratch my fuckin' back for me please?
Come on.
Man this reminds me of *gibberish*
*gibberish*
*laughter*
Yeah and the people
he's like recording with just don't stop him
for like 10 minutes because they think he's just telling a story
in a wild and he's guessing
on the bottom of his lungs
they think he's just clearing his throat
*laughter*
(mumbling)
- Joe just in there, what the fuck, that is crazy, man.
- Wow, really, wow.
- That's possible, I'll tell you that much.
- He says, you're doing like a sling blade impression.
(laughing)
- He says, his whole fucking body went limp
on the right side, Jamie, did we get that?
(laughing)
- Replay that, replay that, Jamie.
- Come on.
- He does the entire speech fucking Brad Dorff's character
does in Child's Play when he's possessing Chucky,
he's like, "Depella!"
(laughter)
- Patrick, I thought you were gonna say the Exorcist 3.
- Hey, that's what I thought you were gonna say too.
- I believe in slime.
(laughter)
- That's a great movie.
- It's such a good movie.
- It's the best, okay, so the best Exorcist number three,
best Halloween number three, best--
- Yeah, no, I agree.
- Nightmare on Elm Street number three.
- Yeah, okay, I'm with you on that one.
- We're both-- - We're all shit.
- I disagree about Halloween,
but I'm with you on the other two.
how are you please this boring and all state
so i you know it's just a matter of how are you know
and all to come over here is a little bit of a lot of the free will i write books
every doubles water read
or
you said i want to do but i don't know the smart i guess i feel pretty stupid
for the other way to write a little more movie that ever got a burger a fucking
burger king exactly exactly i was the first of all soldiers stupid
(laughing)
- It's a really good point. - I brought it up!
Charles didn't even know what to do with the bow.
- Let's talk about small soldiers again.
- Dude, I could go, I could--
- I forgot, I mentioned punching,
I didn't remember his little bite
that sits on his shoulders. - You see this?
I'm gonna pee on it.
I'm gonna pee on it right now. - Do not pee on my book.
- This little guy-- - Do not pee on my book.
- This little guy that sits on his shoulders,
there's punch it, there's scratch it.
Punch it's the big guy 'cause he punches it,
and the little guy's the smack. - I'm peeing right here.
- Do not pee on it.
- Pee on the signature, dude. - Do not pee on my signature.
Take care of that thing.
- He wrote, his signature says dumbass.
- Hey, I guess I'll have to get your book and pee on it.
Oh, fucking wait.
- Hey, we have a book.
We have a book. - We do have a book.
We have a book.
- Okay, you have a book.
You have a copy.
I love that.
- It's a PDF. - Oh wait, here's a title
for your book.
List about list.
- Okay, that's the next one. - Oh my God.
- Here's a title for your book.
- Yeah, you guys can write us the check right now
if you want to.
We can figure it out offhand.
- Yeah, sure.
I'm writing it right now.
Zero dollars and one cent to poopy head McStupidpants.
Whoa!
How are we gonna cash that?
Wait, do we just start a beef?
It's actually the Come Drinking Guys LLC.
(laughing)
It was a joke, it just kinda stuck,
it's weird at the bank.
Ours legitimately is Birdbrain Media, LLC.
Ours is Sullivan the Frog Enterprises.
(laughing)
It's so funny when we have to go to the banks and shit
set up the accounts because like bird brain. The banker at Chase was like, when I'm walking
out the door, he's like, I'm just curious, I'm just gonna ask. He's like, what is the
podcast about? And I'm like, gah. Mostly b-ball. I'm like, it's about getting pussy. That's
what swag is. Have a nice day, sir. I don't know, who cares? It's about finding your own
business. It's about being CEOs of fucking cash, pussy. We were wondering the other day
whether we or you guys have worse SEO. True. It's pretty impossible to Google.
Right. I mean you're just gonna find Star Wars prequels if you look up episode 1,
right? Right. That's how we remain kind of underground. It's kind of cool. Yeah.
You guys are like the Talib Kweli of podcasts. Yeah, we have all the same hats. I got a lot of...
We're gonna mash up all the E1 episodes with the Ocarina of Time
soundtrack mm-hmm damn that would be pimp is fly that's just a fucking fire talk
just put it in the background oh shit they're talking about being cops but
also I love this game what's up I just want to read one more one more from this
list and then I'll never feel the fucking fillet of shut up number 49 is
the queen of the good girls and then in parentheses that rocked everybody see
I'm interested. Who's this? Annie Kaminsky? The hottest girl in school. The goodest girl in school. Turns out she can rock.
Damn. That's crazy. That's the ultimate male fantasy. Do you guys think that she's like doing a guitar solo?
Maybe. She's Lita Ford. She's an elected prom queen and she does a guitar solo? Dude, they put Lita Ford as the prom queen.
You gotta bite your knuckles in the whole thing like...
Dude, Slash is the prom queen this year. He looks so beautiful in that gown.
And the prom king.
He got a quinceanera dress and he's wearing it to prom.
God damn he's pretty.
They have prom in November so they can play November Rain.
Prom king is Axl Rose and they perform One in a Million.
Their most famous song with the best lyrics that are not racist.
Is Slash still doing like Super Bowls and shit?
I think so.
I think the Super Bowl is mostly football nowadays actually.
Yeah.
It's Pepsi and commercials and football.
It's so cool how it'll be like still like 2019 or whatever, 2020, and it's like, yeah
we got the Rolling Stones and halfway through Slash comes up on a platform.
Like everyone that liked these bands are fucking 90 man, like who gives a fuck?
They got their weekend at Bernie and Slash.
Get BTS out there or some shit. What the fuck are we doing?
Please put BTS on there dude.
BTS, Ariana Grande, and Pete Davidson.
Yep. Pete Davidson as Eminem.
In the middle of the song.
Wait, why do you guys want BTK to do a halftime?
BTK fancam.
He'd just be cool.
He'd just be fucking swag.
Oh my god, should BTK just pull out the leather straps?
Am I fucking alive right now?
Is this a dream?
Dude, look at it. He's not allowing his family into the basement.
That's so fucking sick.
Y'all really said that BTK wouldn't be sniffing snow panties on the stage tonight, but then this?
[laughter]
How did, uh, he, uh, I always wondered that. How did he convince his family there's just a whole room
and you just can't go in there?
It's his man cave.
Yeah.
Yeah, but like you can't even look in there.
He's just like, "I'm doing trains and stuff in there."
Because he was a violent man and probably intimidated his family.
You know what I bet he did? I bet he kept being like, uh, like kind of sarcastic.
They were like, "Hey, Dad, what's in the basement?" He'd be like, "Oh, it's a bunch of murder shit and dead women."
Yeah, totally. Yeah. Oh, no, seriously, go take a look.
Oh, yeah. Whatever, man. I guess I'll do the dishes.
If you can get past the dead bolts.
Yeah, if you can unlock the door, there's definitely a woman's head in there.
Dad, you're so lame. We hate you.
He'd come out of his secret room and be like, "Oh, do not go in there."
(laughter)
- And everyone just thought it was like a secret bathroom
where you go and take secret shits like Arnold's grandpa
and Hey Arnold that everyone got mad about.
When they found out he had a secret bathroom
where he went to take shits.
When he was like, I'll be in my office.
Like no, he's going to shit again.
Which is all he had I guess, I don't know.
(laughter)
- That's how he--
- Anyone remember that, remember?
- No I don't, no we don't remember that.
I'm just Widow Babies.
- We don't know.
- Remember the song titles after that one we just read?
'cause they get, the quality kinda drops off a little.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- What's the worst one you think?
- Like number 50, not your typical teen pop rock song.
- Yeah, I did. - Bro, see now that's cool,
'cause like some guys are rockers, you know?
Like me, I'm a rocker.
- Some guys in East LA walk up to you and say,
"Hey, fool, are you a rocker?"
- Hey man, you like Rock Band 3?
You like Guitar Hero 3 and shit, real shit?
You playing cool for cats?
Damn this guy likes Megadeth, he's one crazy gringo.
Damn.
Are you playing Alex Chilton on drums?
Bro you playing LA Noir right now bro?
What's up?
You wanna go back to my house and watch me play LA Noir and shit?
Fuckin crazy story bro.
Yo what's up Wei?
You listen to Eno?
Oh you like Eno?
Damn you listen to Saint Elmo's Fire?
Did he listen to Earth, Wind & Fire?
Damn bro.
Yo, you heard a hundred gigs bro, it sounds like my fucking car and shit bro, it's fucking beast mode.
Fucking sick.
All right, we're at time. So yeah, everybody go listen to episode one. Yeah, listen to one. Subscribe to them on Patreon and shit.
Hey, everyone listen to this podcast instead.
They're already on! They're listening right now!
They're listening!
Listen to it again! Go back to the beginning!
Check out E1, he's got a Filet-O-Fish idea you've gotta hear.
- If you listen to the beginning of this episode,
you'll hear a lot of references that will make sense
now that you've finished the episode.
- That's a good point.
- That's true.
- One of us is the cookies, one of us is the cream,
and together we make a great combination.
We're the cookies, by the way.
- Ooh.
- Yeah, okay.
- 'Cause we're the crunch.
- We're the cream 'cause we fill you up.
- Yeah.
- Fill up what?
- You. - Your butts.
- 'Cause stooge?
- You'd fill up.
- Fill your stooge up with cream.
that stooge up with cream.
- Patrick is talking to all the MILF listeners
that the chat list has.
- Yeah, we have a huge--
- All those hot MILFs that sit around
in their Versace robes with their big boobies.
- Yeah, big boobies and tiny legs.
- Their glasses on and they read their Kindle
while they listen to this show.
- Yeah, oil night, exactly.
- Yeah, those are our most oil listeners.
- Their glasses are huge by the fucking point.
- If you want a nice man to come up
and zip the back of your ballroom dress.
I think Pat's your guy, dude.
Give him a call.
Hey, if he can reach it.
And then the MILF is like,
Patrick, what is the Filet-O-Fish idea, by the way?
Oh yeah, you do have to tell us.
I said I'd say it, you know what?
We did do two hours of this.
I gotta give you the Filet-O-Fish idea, all right.
You have to.
Are you guys, I can see you're all sitting down.
I'm leaning forward, I got my arms folded.
I'm just--
Yeah, I got my hand down my pants,
even though I already know it.
Take a big bite of this giant edible that is all melded together.
So just eat it like it's...
Alright.
A thousand milligrams.
Oh look at that shit!
He does!
Dude, don't eat that!
It looks like a bunch of erasers melted together.
No, eat that, you're gonna need it.
You're gonna need it after this.
It looks like a Rubik's Cube.
You're gonna have a crazy 10pm.
You gotta nibble a little bit.
The filet-o-fish idea.
It's more cheese.
Is that it?
cheese on the fillet of fish there's already two slices dude no there's not
there's only there's half of one slice all right now I look this up full slice
people think slice on it I've already read this I read a lot about the play
efficient could do it could do with more cheese all right you know that was the
idea you might be aren't you glad you fucking stay listen how many slices are
we talking but wait you said this was an episode idea look I'm not gonna talk
about that. Look, you're just gonna talk about your- Episode one, we'll field that one. We'll do the
fish episode so don't worry about it Pat. We're gonna record that right after this.
Sounds good. All right, bye. If you do that you will be getting a lawsuit so goodbye.
All right, see you in court.