You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
You're a crap monster.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, Joe Biden.
We always knew you could do it.
We never doubted you, and we never
recorded anything else otherwise.
Now we knew you were going to win.
We have never said that you weren't going to win.
We never said that--
We never said anything bad about you.
Yeah, we never said that you're like the worst candidate we could have thrown up, you're the
worst candidate that could ever exist.
We never said that if you lose it's entirely the fault of you and it's not, it's the entirety
of the fault of the Democratic Party.
We never said in the set we from, we don't rep, no Joe Biden, we didn't say that.
I never said that.
We never said that.
I've never said anything mean about you.
I've never said anything bad about the DNC.
And...
I knew you were always gonna win.
Dude, if he wins, I'm just in jail right now.
That's true.
Yeah.
Fuck.
I'm like literally in jail.
That's true.
That's why we're recording this the day before, because if he wins, I go to jail.
He has won.
He won, and I'm recording this from jail right now over a phone.
God damn, dude.
Oh, what's up?
What's up, man?
You look good.
God damn, I hate jail.
Hey, man.
Oh, what's up?
You're fucking fine as hell.
Jail sucks so bad, dude.
What are they feeding you in there?
I'm fucking toilet paper holes.
Yeah?
Yeah, the holes in the rolls of the toilet paper.
Do you think he'll go to jail if he wins?
Not for anything I've done before he won.
Yeah?
Yeah, but probably for something else.
Or, I mean, now that he's won.
Now that he's won, I might go- Here's all I'm gonna say to those who are listening that
this might be pertinent information to.
I might go to jail. I might do something and go to jail.
No, I'm kidding. I guess we have to explain it. We're recording
this on election Tuesday. Or selection Tuesday as I like to call it because you select your
vote. You've had a new one for every time we've
recorded this. That's so true. I wrote it down. That's my thing.
Whoa. I mean, what do you mean every time? This is
the only one recording. Yeah. But so yeah Joe Biden won. Yeah. The first president named
Joe Biden in the history of United States University. How about you come to my, hey
buddy, let's chop it up, we'll talk it over, you come to my storage unit in rural North
Carolina and we'll just have a chat, you and me. Yeah. I won't bring any security if you
don't. Let's just hang out, you know. Just hash it out. Just squash the beef. Yeah. I
I think that's the thing. I think now that he's president, I think finally we can squash a beef
with him. Yeah, I mean, because we've been beefing since, I mean... I mean, we have, we have, there's
common ground here, you know what I mean? Yeah. Like, I mean, we're, we're both like awesome,
like rap style white guys. That's true. Yeah. You know, we're like, I don't know, amazing speakers.
Yeah, yeah. You know, we talk for a living. You guys are both pedophiles.
Yeah, that's a huge one. See, we have more in common than we have not in common.
Yeah, I mean, the only thing you guys don't have in common is that your name and
who wants to do what to who. And you're six feet tall and I'm, you know,
five eleven and a half. Modest.
Yeah, we're the same height. Five eleven and three quarters. Almost six feet.
Yep. Not quite there.
You're 5'3".
Congrats, buddy.
No, I'm not 5'3".
No.
Yeah, I'm 5 times 3 inches into your mom.
Dude, it's easy for me.
Throw anything at me, I'll throw it right back in your face.
It's so easy for me.
Jesus Christ, put me on Wild 'N Out already.
What the hell am I doing on this podcast?
I think we gotta get on Wild 'N Out.
Dude, we would be so good on Wild 'N Out.
Yeah.
Oh my God, are you kidding?
We would probably wild out.
I would wild out.
You wanna see me wild out?
yeah somebody raps at me they're like all right Caleb you're turn a while
just doing that machine gun Kelly how you gonna spit back at that he just goes up
and goes nah dude I would I would kill it on while and out though yeah especially
if they had a trivia section yeah yeah I would crush it dude they should work
trivia section they should get trivia on it yeah yeah and now for the bikini
contest portion of the wildin' out competition yeah you in that - yeah do I
got small balls all right I tuck him easily small and long I've a huge sack
really small balls I can pop them both in my fucking ass did really yeah dude so
it right now you let me show you yeah okay here you go oh why did you why did
you kiss it after you did it twice with your mouth? It's called good luck.
That looks like a it looked like a bulldog eating a hot dog. Yeah that wasn't
good to look at. Yeah that was like a grape being sucked into a vacuum. Yeah
yeah that's right yeah I got some suction in there. It looks like it was playing in reverse.
That's why I'm the most popular guy in prison. It looked like two pill bugs being
born out of a monkey. Dude I saw a chimp's ass the other day. Yeah. Yeah yours. It's got
like the biggest fucking asshole in the world. Yeah would you look in the mirror? Yeah sorry
you guys got me. I'm a chimp. I looked at my asshole. Basically the most normal thing a
chimp could do. Yes. Really. Yeah. I'm being actually serious right now. Did you hear that?
Oh my god dude. That's what a chimp would do. A chimp would burp and fart at you. I hate
doing political. I think Joe Biden's ass probably looks like a chimps ass. I think
I think he should have to show his ass. He's got like Santa's beard on his hole. He should have to show
his ass and his pussy now that he's president. You should have to if you
want to run for president you should have to get like just fucking absolutely
humiliated sexually. You know what I mean? Like just like, like there should every candidate, if you want to run you have to fucking just like. There's a video of you just getting your balls
balls just fucking like a cigarette.
Just like a scarab bleeding down your fucking face.
Uh huh.
We should get to eat Joe Biden's pussy dudes if we vote for him.
No I don't think we should.
I think there should be a video though.
Can you imagine?
It's like motorboating a rubber boot filled with steak sauce.
(laughter)
- That's all.
- Come on.
- What the fuck?
- That's what it would be like,
I just was thinking about it.
- You don't.
- I'm gonna make him fucking red, white, and blue all over.
- I don't even know if we can say that.
- You gotta lay down some newspaper.
- Yeah, like you're getting fish and chips.
No, he should just get fucked on like he's you have to get fucked on
Nationals put together so should Trump
No, he's not president. No, he's not. Well, he's not president. No, no, but if you're gonna run for president
It's here's everything about
Yeah, and this is you see I'm not out on cam
You should that's right. Just like I'm gonna fuck you out
You have to get like fucking like throat punished on
You know what I mean to run for president? Yes, so they have so they already have the dirt cuz yeah, it's like there's no October surprise
Sun smokes crack. It's like who cares dude. He literally
He got fucking ripped to shreds
Whatever. You got one of his balls popped under a high heel, dude
They brought back og mud bone to do this
Oh gee mud bone is is like the greatest fucking treasure in American history because he he fucking
Wheat from the chaff there, you know what I mean?
We were finding out who can take it and who can take it like a fucking president. Yeah, you know
Right he and he and basically og mud bone is the one who decides
I should be part of the election about registration at all
I just forgot about part of the registration is you sign away your rights
For one day to just get fucking just fucked out like a fucking like a couch, dude
It's like a fucked out like a couch.
Like a, like a, yeah, like a bag of yeast.
Yeah, you get flipped over like fucking rice, dude.
Yeah.
It's just like a pizza dough.
You're gonna get fucked like a spaceship flying around in water.
Yeah, you pop like a balloon.
Yeah, you get, yeah, you're gonna, you're gonna, you're gonna...
You're gonna turn your hole into slime.
I mean, I want, I want somebody to do to Joe Biden what that monkey does to that frog in that video.
No. That's what should happen.
No, I don't know if we can say that now that he's president.
Yeah. No, you can.
No. Oh, I can. I'm already in jail.
What's that mean? I'm already here, so it doesn't really matter.
Yeah, we can't say that. No, you guys are fine.
But I don't know. I feel like that'd be a great, like,
Be a good reality show.
Also, it's a reality show. I forgot that part.
Right, and that's the thing. That's the thing.
And it's exactly like The Batchelor, but it's OG Mudbone deciding the president
based on who can fucking take it the hardest.
Yeah who takes it presidentially. Yeah. And he's such a good
presenter too because he looks at the camera goes like yeah
you know he does that stuff. Exactly dude I want fucking
god by the time the general comes around everybody's gonna be fucking wearing
eye patches and shit. The general? General. The car insurance?
From the car insurance. He should have to fuck up. Oh my god yes.
to decide. Because then there's the thing because during COVID and everything. OG Mudboat in a
mocap suit just fucking the shit out of someone. Yeah and especially because of COVID his penis
will be at least long enough that they could social distance. True. And I think having the
general in there too I think adding the layer of CGI. The general watches. CGI people can't get COVID.
Yeah. That's a really good point. Yeah. As long as they stop making those like
those diagrams yeah that's true they can get it from that 3d they gotta stop
doing the 3d models yeah the CNN breaking news 3d model of the virus that actually
the general can get and then he would be wouldn't be able to fuck just seeing
that their their 3d model of the virus just float off screen and come back
during during a Geico commercial just kill the Geico. No no no what are you doing?
What are you doing? What's that? Oh, what's that? What are you doing, chap?
That's my tail. I would seem we got a virus. I got my tail. Hey, if you get virus
protection if you switch the guy. It's going down his throat. I've never felt something like this in my life.
now he should he'd be fine just just the guy the guy could echo just waking up in
a doom wad of high school all right so in honor of Joe Biden yeah I think it's at
the list yeah you did it's in the chat it's not not yet in the channel I'll
send it right now this is top top 10 song titles that describe one Joseph R
Biden. I know one song. From user Murph. I know one song that would uh. Well don't say it because
it might be on the list just wait till the end. I think we'll have someone else here who knows too.
Is it a Black Eyed Peas song that they had to change the lyrics of? No. Oh. Yeah I'm a bee.
It is I'm a bee. I'm gonna say that every time that you don't say the name of that song I'm
i'm gonna say i'm a b instead
i'm punished for being pc
yet again
uh... number one can i touch you there by michael bolton
there's a comment from evan the nerd
that just says oh my god
oh my god they did not go there oh my god no michael bolton
i'm looking at evan the nerd's profile he's twenty one he's from
tennessee
i'm afraid his the top first line of his about is i'm afraid what we shall be
be forever be forever lost in darkness and ignorance Winnie the Pooh.
Whoa.
There's not much to say about me actually I'm just some random nerd on the internet with
bizarre obsessive opinions way beyond your understanding.
Hey here's a Michael Bolton song that describes Joe Biden when a man loves a woman.
Jack Sparrow with the Lonely Island.
That's right because Joe Biden gave a few visits to a certain lonely island.
Yeah, that's fucking right.
Hey.
You can listen to samples of the songs.
Oh, dude, let's listen.
Yeah.
[music]
I can't turn it off.
Is there no stop option?
The pause button isn't working.
I have to reload the page.
All right, I won't click to listen to sample then.
Thank you for warning me.
The pause button worked for me.
Dude, Google Chrome hates me and loves my Google.
Caleb doesn't have the capability to pause.
It's true.
I see two lines, dude.
I start fucking zoning out thinking about the heroes we lost on September 11th.
Every time I see a pause button, I refuse to touch it.
Yeah.
Number two is tears in heaven.
I don't know how this relates to Joe Biden at all.
You tripping if you think that.
Yeah, his son.
Because his son died?
His son died.
I think that that's a stretch. I think that, yeah, it's about a dead son.
Yeah, Eric Clapton's son smoked crack too.
Yeah, that's why he jumped out that window.
Yeah.
He was just bugging, dude.
He tripped on that video of the guy smoking salve and then falling out the window.
That's Eric Clapton's kid.
That's Eric Clapton's son, yeah.
Very unlucky, Eric Clapton.
Yeah. Just raise your son better.
Seriously.
Number 3, Crazy by Gnarls Barkley.
Hey.
Yeah.
Whoa.
I mean this is an all-timer of a list already, dude.
Yeah, already.
I mean-
Already we're all float on.
They should put that on this list because then it would be a classic.
Well it's Gnarls Barkley because he perfectly blends sort of like indie sensibility with
like hip hop roots.
Which is exactly what Joe Biden does.
what I mean yeah he's kind of the perfect like kind of cross-section of those two
worlds yeah and he says crazy yeah and also he's yeah and he's well also we
could read this as as him being like kind of guilty of the same stuff CeeLo's
guilty of right I guess that could be. Yeah, dressing up in a big gold suit yeah
being a cool robot. Dressing like a robot yeah. Having his Samsung Galaxy explode.
Gnarly Davidson that's the name that's his uh that's the his name when he dresses up
in the gold suit. Oh. Yeah he said it's a different persona he says he claims it's
not him well he's like what you saw was not CeeLo Green that was Gnarly
Davidson. Yeah Gnarly Davidson was one slipping those things in those women's
streaks it was not CeeLo Green. Goddamn dude. That one definitely came out of nowhere. Yeah.
The CeeLo allegations. I was really like, he's like fucking 4'11 and like 700 pounds. I feel
like that's usually a good guy. You know? I can't think of many evil small people. Really.
at this what about a gnome look at it all back look at this picture and tell me
that the you're saying this guy doesn't seem that evil but but but look at this
okay click on this link okay save for this is the evil part of him yeah yeah
this is the guy who did everything bad CeeLo could never just search gnarly
davidson guys on and google images you haven't seen it's the picture with him
with red and purple glowing lights on his head this is his like mr. Hyde you know
yeah yeah number number four is liar by bikini kill that's kind of a lazy one
if I'm that's a very lazy one because there's because I feel like liar by a
bikini kill is a very feminist band I don't know what's it is song titles
so yeah that's true that is true I guess it's not the content of the song and I
guess we have to go back to tears in heaven and say and that one just doesn't
make any sense at all yeah that one really is if you're not considering
content I guess his son is crying in heaven because he's dead there's nothing
about a son about in the in the name right out of context it just makes no
sense so I declare Murph creator of this list I'm declaring you idiot of the week
I'm calling you out.
Murph you dumb as hell.
I don't know who won the election but I know Murph lost.
You know who won the election was Joe Biden.
It was Joe Biden.
It's again, it's so difficult.
Yeah it is tough.
I would be the world's worst time traveler.
I'd be so stuck in the day that I left apparently.
Just getting sent to future jail for being white.
Kanye West is weird as fuck.
- And is being like,
we don't even know if this actually happened yet.
- Number six, creepy smell.
- You skipped number five, where's my mind, Pixies.
- Number five, where's my mind, Pixies.
- Oh, that's 'cause he's from Delaware,
and in Fight Club, if you remember,
they go to Delaware and they blow up all those buildings.
- Yeah, in Project Mayhem.
- Yeah, that's the only reason that that is on that list.
- Yep, all right, now we can go to number six,
creepy smell by the smelvins. This one's clever. Yeah, he's a sniffer right? Yeah.
Yeah. What if he's looking for, he's looking for a crime. He's a crime dog. In a seven year old's hair.
What if he's looking for a missing person? Yeah. He's checking. He's making sure nobody else has
touched that seven year old besides the parents. Yeah. He can actually, he can
smell a pedophile's hand because he smells one every time he washes his face.
yeah he's like he's like Dexter he uses his powers for good yeah I know what
just happened but my computer froze yeah I thought you my computer froze and you
and Caleb just went whoa that's pretty cool yeah that didn't get picked up I
don't even know why I brought it up number seven is tragedy by the BGC it's
It's gonna be a real tragedy when he passes away.
Rest in peace, sir.
I salute you.
I hope that your son can fill your giant size 17 shoes, because you know Joe Biden's got
those size 17 shoes.
He's packing his shoes.
You know he's got long toes that look like fingers.
That's right.
You know what they say about a guy with big shoes.
And he holds his feet together like hands.
Yes!
Yes, you got it!
He holds his feet together
Like hands!
Like hands, yes!
You're so right!
Yeah. Wow!
I'm sorry you guys, I'm so stressed out right now.
Yeah, why? It's over.
I know that there's Antifa thugs running around my neighborhood right now.
No, that was the last one.
Celebrating Joe Biden's will.
Either way, Antifa is taking the stand.
They're winning at some point.
Yeah, either if Trump won yeah, do you think if I still wins if Biden wins antifa if by it will bite him one and now
Antifa is now we have to keep or I couldn't I
Yeah, dude earlier today at freaking antifa thug was celebrating and he tried to throw
He tried to throw in a rainbow latte through my window and I couldn't see his face as or his identity because he was wearing
A damn infinity scarf. Oh my god. I
Luckily, I got a good look at his eyes though because he was wearing glasses with no lenses
Oh my god. It is nice that this is, if Biden wins today, the coronavirus is just gone.
Yeah, it's gone. It is gone. And Bella and Sebastian, the leaders of Antifa, are gonna make a great album.
Mm-hmm, that's right. Yeah.
Yep.
Number eight, "Been Caught Stealin'" by Jane's Addiction.
I don't get this one.
Joe Biden's...
Oh, he steals your hearts.
Yeah. He's a fucking smooth Casanova.
Yeah, they call him Joe Casanova. They do. They call him Joey Smoove. Like J.B. Smoove.
Yep. J.B. Smoove. He's eating something. He's eating something. Listen Barry. Listen Barry.
He's J.B. Smoove dude. He is. I would love a J.B. Smoove presidency. Me too man. Yeah.
There are so many celebrities that I want to be president.
Yeah.
And it sucks that we already got our number one last year.
I can't believe it was Donald Trump that was the celebrity president.
We couldn't have like...
Mario.
Yeah.
Mario wasn't easy.
He's not an American citizen.
Well, he's not naturalized.
I mean, neither was Obama.
It's fine.
It's true.
Yeah.
Obama was from Italy too.
have
I
Yeah, very bad. Don't want 'em. I want Flo.
We need Flo. Please, I need Flo.
I need Flo. I need Flo in my life.
Number 9, Dumb by Nirvana. Ohhhh.
They went there. They went there. It's a comment from Stuart that says
"accurate and I despise most of Nirvana's music. The rest is either
just bad or okay." What the fuck, Stuart? What are you talking about?
Kurt Cobain didn't blow his brains out for you.
Yeah.
Freak.
Yeah, we love Kurt Cobain.
Mm-hmm.
Kurt Cobain, you can come on whenever you want after the surgery fixes you.
Kurt Cobangz, you can also come on.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Much respect to Kurt Cobangz.
We're gonna sing with Kurt Cobangz.
My brain is stuck in the 2013 XXL Freshman Cypher for the rest of my life.
Yeah.
It's just me and Kurt Cobangz rappin'.
Who else was in the 2013 one?
Me.
or
What if he won, dude?
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Trinidad James?
What was his song?
All Gold Everything.
Oh, well he did win because of Donald Trump.
Yes, dude!
Yes!
Yeah!
Let's fucking go, dude!
Let's take him down!
Dude, he likes gold!
He's got a gold doll in my toilet.
He likes gold!
His skin is gold!
Gold doll in my toilet.
Gold doll in my... in Mar-a-Lago!
Gold in Mar-a-Lago!
I'm saying Mara in the White House.
Pop to Molly, I'm sweating.
Yeah, talk to Putin, I'm sweating.
Yeah, that's right.
Giuliani, I'm sweating.
Oh my god, you did not just do that, dude.
Pooped a lot and I'm sweating.
There we go.
Because he poops a lot in his gold dollar bike diaper.
Any guy with a toilet that golden must have to poop a lot if he's going to be using it.
I'm a fat guy, I'm sweating.
- Yeah, there we go.
- Let's go, yeah dude.
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah.
(burps)
- Gold all in my ass.
- Michael Che, if you're listening,
you can use that on SNL, you don't have to pay me.
- Mm-hmm, it's free.
- It's free, it was in my package.
- We're throwing you a softball.
- You can take anything from my Twitter, use it on SNL.
I appreciate you Michael, much love.
- I really regret submitting my packet
'cause they have been using everything I've said.
(laughs)
- Yeah.
this is the past four years have been everything out of Patrick's packet.
Uh-huh yeah most of the Trump stuff is from my packet. Yeah Patrick just wrote a bunch of
funny situations that he thought were goofy that ended up being turning into
just tone-deaf political comedy like he didn't know who he didn't know anything
he didn't know who was president. He was just writing characters and they they turned out to be perfect.
They were like these would be great for Trump what the hell we're not gonna
hire this guy but his packet is amazing we can't hire this guy because of uh
because of our anti-iron because of our didn't put a return address on the packet
or its name this showed up one day in a manila envelope
there they can't hire you because they don't hire irish people anymore that's
true yeah after bobby moynihan yeah you got
everybody the fuck out of there every irish person
Well, Kate McKinnon's still there. She's faking it. Yeah, it's just Irish for her stage name.
She's really Polish. Her real last name is Miscovitch. Yeah, there's no chance there's a
fucking Irish lesbian in the world. No. No fucking, especially not under a Biden presidency. Right,
yeah, Biden would nip that in the bud. Yeah. Immediately. I hope he does go on SNL and he's
like are you sure you've never have you ever kissed a man I mean have you ever
even tried Kate and she's just dancing and smiling at the camera with their
hand over her heart yeah she's doing the play oh my god wait I'm sure we chiseled
I've got the best idea they do the Pledge of Allegiance on SNL dude yeah uh-huh and
- And they say some funny words in it.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I pledge allegiance to my crab.
- Yeah, I pledge allegiance to my rod.
(laughing)
The pledge of the penis.
Dude, that's good.
- We, okay.
- Dude, we should do political,
this is our only political show from now on.
- Yep.
- I mean, we are crushing them, dude.
- We should bring this to Broadway.
- We're taking down those fucking,
the lizards that are in power.
- That's right.
gotta bring this to Broadway immediately yeah once everything reopens mm-hmm
we're gonna have the best we'll do the first Broadway show the first Broadway
show ever we're skipping off Broadway going straight to Broadway yep it's
gonna be a double feature us and wicked back-to-back yes yeah wicked yeah what
what's that about Donald Trump now it is my god it is wait he's wait wait she's
green more like he's mean and orange yep the Wicked Witch of Queens that's me
that's no that's Donald Trump he's from Queens see from Queens yeah uh-oh what
no dude he's from that's where I'm from he's from Jupiter and you know where
people white people go there uh-huh get more knowledge number take a chance on
me by ABBA okay a little okay maybe a little positive okay yeah okay all right
16 smile by uncle cracker he's everybody's number 15 is follow the
leader by corn which is not a song name it's an album name yeah there's no song
called that that doesn't make any sense stupid Biden it's like how Bill Cosby
was America's dad Joe Biden is America's uncle cracker that's true wow this is
really is number 14 this is really genius politician by cream oh my god
Wow they really got him that actually does act that literally describes that
is so true that might be the most accurate one yeah it's pretty good
number 18 Delaware by Perry come oh yeah nice one straight to the point did
number 19 I'm the coolest by Alice Cooper well you have to know to understand that
one that Joe Biden thinks he's very cool mm-hmm once you know that it all yeah
number 20 old-fashioned by panic at the disco yeah more like old fascist sorry
Joe Biden I love you. I mean let's fuck another round of applause. Oh my god
We're putting up numbers today. Yeah, we're on fire today. You know what it is is Jordan
We don't have to be stressed out about anything anymore. We can go eat bunch Trump Trump lost comedy's good again, dude
Yeah, this is what we panic at the disco more like preschool where his dick go
I mean just fucking just quit. Slithers into preschool like a snake underneath the door.
You're not coming back. Number 21, Lazy by Deep Purple.
More like Crazy by Narls Barkley.
Number 22, Old Man by Neil Young. That's most of the presidents.
Old Man, Neil Young. Yeah, did you ever realize how that song kind of makes no sense based on the artist's name?
not this is why is the young guy can't be a real man this can't be a real song if
the real Joe Biden saw that he would immediately have an aneurysm yeah he
would not understand mm-hmm an old man a Neil young a young Neil a man's old a
man can be old it's just like that it's just the way it is to be like that
number 23 pervert by the descendants another punk rock song which is gonna be
so much better. How about revert to the Obama years? Punk rock is gonna suck so much under
Joe Biden because all the punks are gonna be too happy. True. All the punks, what are they
gonna rage against? Yeah, exactly. There's nothing. He's awesome, dude. He's the punk
rock president. Yeah. He should get a mohawk. Yeah, oh my god. That would win. A Joe Hawk.
uh...
uh... deceiver by impending doom
okay
that might be a little dramatic. I feel like we covered that with liar too.
I think you need another one
this is uh... number thirty one redneck by joe south
is he a redneck?
number twenty six put your money where your mouth is by chet
he what he...
always that puts his money on on babies p
yet yet while he's flying on a jet
and you know which it was for the news team spirit airlines iraq's he was
flying on the record sees frugal yet it is a regular jill
number twenty seven white man by queen
that's that's true
that's actually is a way to bring in true yeah he is a white man
that songs about uh...
that's a lot of murder of indigenous people
really
and i say we endorse this at the end it's not that yet
we are not so much
yeah
number twenty eight mad mad me by wendy walled men
well it's mad mad at me
it says that mad me
it says mad look at number twenty eight it says mad mad me and i was saying that
She, I'm saying Wendy Waldman made a typo.
I don't think that's true.
Yeah I think that's it, because why would you say no?
That doesn't make any sense.
Who's, who's, why is, is he mad?
Is he mad mad?
He's mad, well he did get mad at Joe Biden.
Why why why why why?
Oh yeah, why why why why why why why?
Come on man, give it a go.
That's one of the best videos, it's so funny.
Yeah.
He looks sped up, that's what I love about it.
running into a journalist facing me.
Why, why, why, why, why, why, why?
- It's like he's supposed to ask why, dude.
He's a journalist.
- Yeah. - It's true.
- Yeah, trying to own a journalist might be like,
man, stop asking so many questions.
You're crazy.
- You're weird.
- You're a weirdo coming to this debate
and asking me a question.
- You want me to know, you wanna ask questions?
Uh-uh.
- You wanna know something?
How about you go to the bookstore?
- How about you go to the library and read up?
yeah i was a lot about you calm down and settle down with the nice lady
who tolerates you
hey big guy champ
how much you go get a library card yeah
how about we do this one now let it famous books connect
h_m_ power we do this was not a literal fascist running for office ok kiddo
that's right yeah
far it's cc
corporate may fucking ccp says shit get out of my face yeah all you like a
little you you'd just a little
You're a little worm.
You're a little, I'm gonna catch a fish with you.
- You're a worm. - Get over here.
I'm gonna put you on the end of my fishing rod.
- Yeah, I'm gonna catch a fish.
- I'm gonna catch a fish later.
- You're just a worm for the wolves.
- Why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why?
I'm gonna catch a fish with you.
- Why, why, why, why, why, why, why?
- Come on, man, calm down.
You're not Borat. - Come on, man.
You're not Borat.
Come on, man.
Why, why, why, why, why, why, why?
- Why, why, why, why, why, why?
- If you vote for Donald Trump and not me,
then you ain't Borat.
My wife, my wife, nice, nice, very nice!
Come on, man!
Listen here, Borat.
Number 30, big mouth blues.
He's got a big blue mouth.
That's right.
His mouth is blue.
Dude, get him!
Because he's a democrat.
What, have you been eating fucking blow pops?
What's wrong with your mouth?
Crud!
cream lay off the sweets fucking fatty stop eating sugar oh gonna end up like
your son what are you freezing cold why is your mouth so blue what are you cold
so cold your whole body turn what are you like a shivering what are you a
smurf hi he cold he cold he cold he's cold he not even warm he cold no get a
scarf hey get yourself a blanket cold you're cold as hell number number 38
blah blah blah by Kesha oh my god Kesha Wow that's just too far I think yeah I
think you say what you would have some respect for the office president
Sleepyhead by Passion Pit. He's sleepy as hell. Let's add to this list to end it off.
You know? Okay. Mm-hmm. Hmm. Yeah. What are some weird songs? Let me think of a funny song that
would be a funny name to call a guy. Why don't we do it in the road? You can get Kim by Eminem
because his wife died. Okay. Right? In a car I think. Lose Yourself. Lose Yourself by Eminem because he's lost his
brain uh-huh Rain Man by Eminem because he has a disability yeah there's a lot
of good Eminem things
well I think there's too many songs there's too many songs it's hard to
think of a song yeah freak out le freak by chic freak on a leech yeah yeah freak
of the least freak of the week yeah the leash is the Democratic Party yeah daddy
by corn that's right see this is what they're saying that comedy is gonna get
so much harder yeah yeah yeah rocket man yeah he's got a red right beautiful
girls yeah that's true yeah promiscuous promiscuous girl yeah any Timbaland song
yeah about what about what about Odin no not Otis that's about a different guy
about Otis by but Daisy and Kanye West that's a different guy that's about Otis
rating what about Joe's Joe's house Joe Joey by for non blondes for non blondes
I don't think I think it's concrete blonde what about the Joe what about the
Joe Rogan experience for non blondes is they do I said hey what's going on okay
What about Deep Cover 99 by Big Pun and Fat Joe?
What about Finger 11?
There we go.
Paralyzer.
That's right.
What about Chris Benoit by ICP?
Okay.
Yeah.
No, that's a different guy.
What about Fuck the Club Up?
Okay.
Grove Street Party.
is
of
please don't put me in jail man
uh... yeah i was in the middle of the jail we need to know me as you are
please let me please get caleb out of jail
yeah please get me out of jail
uh... yeah
so i play checkers in the back with uh...
barbara pieces
uh...
so i have to do that i was yet patriotic and he already here it we have a
minecraft server that was supposed to play which is our minecraft server for
honor discord so you could go to pot about lead dot st
or pot about allied dot s_c_ depending on how it whether you type
by letters or by set humps
uh... and there's a link to our discord on there and you can join and join the
minecraft server
uh...
c_u_a_ graduations again to joe biden gradually are not going to die
and if you're listening to this right now if you're listening to this one
and he didn't win
you're wrong that's your naughty little guy
you know you're a little
your trip in his cell do you have don't and don't listen feed and because he did
when if you're hearing is right now you don't listen the other one
yet you don't let you if we find out that you listen to it
there's gonna be held up a
you're gonna delete yours your
everything off your phone
that's right we're gonna try to log into your phone ten times it's gonna race all
your data
and don't forget to vote
Don't forget to vote!
Goodbye everybody.
(static)