You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Chetch.
- Ew.
- Chetch, chetch, chetch.
(choking)
- Chetching.
- Oh fuck.
- Chetch me.
- Fuck dude.
- Ooh.
- Oh my god.
- I didn't get to, I want to bid at eight o'clock.
- We already talked about that Patrick.
- I'm talking to the fans now.
- They don't need to know.
talk to the fans no Patrick's talking Wow that's sort of a talk to the talk to the
booty cuz hands off duty kind of thing talk to the fans cuz it's Patrick's turn
now so tell us tell us about your night so I went to bed at 8 I woke up and then
stayed up and I've been up since midnight and now where are you getting
these lattes from you you claim to bring your fourth latte what it's free made
Yeah, so you're making them. So you went from the fridge, you went from drinking
the Monster Energy to drinking those those Starbucks like chocolate latte
glass bottle things, right? Yeah, okay. No, not those ones. So I've
thought the whole time I thought this was a creamer and turns out it's just
pre-made latte and I've been putting it in coffee. Oh, so putting, okay, you'd be
Creaming your coffee with I was creaming my coffee with latte and I realized that it was
Latte why it was creamer I
Comes in like it comes in a bottle. Yeah, I thought it was like I thought it was like a caramel
Caramel on it. I didn't read
Based off shapes
Everything yeah, it is shaped. It is shaped like the creamer bottle and the latte is shaped like cream. Yeah
I
Am I I think my favorite customer interaction with a customer at work
So far the other day I came in and said hello
a
Guy a guy was paying at the register and he was like digging through his pockets for change and he had like a handful of change
He was going through and then he said really quietly. He he like leaned over me was like look what I
I have and I was like oh no he was like look at this and he like covered it with
his hand so nobody else could see and he showed me he had a golden penny Wow
he had the gold coin the gold and coins should have shown in the black it was
really cool and he said yeah and then he put it back in his pocket
well he didn't show them the black no he was like yeah yeah yeah of course I
know it's a golden penny yeah you fucking moron and you're like I'm
Imagine though going to just a bunch of stores and just showing people your golden penny
while you're paying for stuff.
I would never show off my golden penny.
That's a boss lifestyle.
Come here.
Check this out.
Look what I have.
I would hide my golden penny from the world.
Is it one of those ones where it has like Jesus Christ or Donald Trump on it?
In case of pirates.
No, it looked like it was just like a penny covered in gold.
Like it looked exactly like a penny but it was golden.
It was dripping in gold.
It looked like it was like it was like it was it had it had Abraham Lincoln on it.
Mm-hmm our golden president our goldenest president. Mm-hmm. That's right the golden age of presidents
Yeah, golden age of presidents probably
Not when he was president Reagan to Bush. Let me tell you yeah
Reagan to Bush it took a long time to get to their golden age
Yeah, Reagan to Bush. It sounds to me more like the Molden age of president
At one point they were the highest office in the land and you're disrespecting them in that way that's rude
They did the most coups.
Yeah, how many coups have you done, pussy? Actually wait, then we should probably do Nixon.
Nixon to Bush. You know what? We'll just say...
We'll just say George Washington...
Everyone until Obama.
Yeah, George Washington until Obama.
We'll just say that.
That's the golden age of presidents.
And then it started again after Obama.
[Laughter]
Yeah, he's sort of entering his second golden age now.
that that that
now that's not true
the exact opposite is true there was only one of those majorly over all of that
was his name was present all the no problem golden obama
from super smash bros
because i'm going to fight golden obama
and i don't know what i don't know about metal obama yeah
it's very actually
uh... i yesterday i i think i'm really like
I think my ability to talk to strangers is just like completely atrophied like I just
can't do it anymore.
I'm better at talking to strangers than I ever was.
I'm way worse at it.
Yesterday I...
I am.
I don't like going anywhere.
Shut up Cameron.
Yesterday I went to a new corner store to get, I got an 8 pack of Guinness.
A new one that they just put it in?
A new corner store.
It's brand new.
New to you or new to the world?
New to the entire universe.
Oh okay.
I went because I was down the street.
A new bodega just dropped.
Okay it's not the importance, it's new.
I got an eight pack of Guinness, okay?
- Whoa.
- I put it, what do you, any,
you have 50 things to say about that?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- How many Guinness?
- How many?
- An eight pack of what?
- Which by the way, insane number of bottles
to put in a pack.
I got an eight pack of Guinness,
I put it on the counter.
- Caleb trying to be Irish now.
- Eight like the number or eight like you ate it?
- I, yeah, an eight.
- It's thick enough that you could eat it.
- If someone had already eaten it, the pack of Guinness.
I put it on the counter, the guy was like,
he's like a younger, like, bodega guy,
which I'm not used to,
'cause it's usually like a 50 year old guy,
and so he's talking to me,
and he puts it on, he's like,
"Hey, how you doing, man?"
I'm like, "Uh, mm-hmm."
And he sees the beer and he goes,
"How old are you?"
And then just instinctively I go, "21."
And he was like, "You sure?"
And I was like, "Uh-huh."
And then he's like, "Can I see your ID?"
And I handed it to him and he was like,
it says you're 23 and I was like oh yeah you're I'm yeah I am 23 I forgot how old I was
I wouldn't have accepted it I would have told him his math was wrong
he should not have accepted it yeah mm-hmm he should have thrown that ID in the
trash it's from North Carolina it's 10 years old every time I go to the airport
the person and TSA gets mad at me because my ID yeah dude they get mad at me too
did at a middle school. It looks like shit dude. And they're like you gotta one
guy said he was like you get this in the dinosaur times at the TSA.
Yeah which first of all not a good joke. Yeah. Fucking back off. Dinosaur times
would be a great restaurant. What does dinosaur times mean? That's not a... That'd be a great restaurant in like the same vein as like medieval times.
Yeah. I like it's funny to say. What did you get this in dinosaur times to
mean like what did you get this like six years ago? I'm still on Dinosaur Times
the restaurant because now I've got a great idea. So it's basically
all the elements of Rainforest Cafe and Medieval Times put together. And that
equals dinosaurs to you? And well you so it's it looks like Rainforest Cafe but
there's a jousting ring in the middle like Medieval Times and... Like when the
dinosaurs were there. And they're on velociraptors instead of horses. I'm on
velociraptor time. VPT. I'm on, we should we should start sort of a kind of like a
more intelligent, more intelligent, we should do the brain forest cafe. Yeah.
Right? Where you come in and immediately they say instead of, instead of, hey how you doing.
It's the library. It's the library but it's but it's rain forest themed. Yeah. And so you
You have a toucan who's a...
Toucan librarian.
Yeah.
He's not good.
He's not good at all.
He's terrible at being a librarian, but he is a toucan.
Yeah.
He has a colored nose.
And instead of food, you get chess.
Comes on a plate.
Or information.
What about chessman cookies?
What if you get those?
No, that's food.
I don't know what that means, man.
Well, it would have to be library-themed food, and there's cookbooks at the library.
No, there's no food.
You can't eat in a library.
It's against the rules.
You can't eat candy in a library with the lights on.
I didn't say anything about candy.
You just said you want them to serve you food in a library.
Yeah, like Prime Rib.
No.
You can't have Prime Rib.
You would get the Prime Rib juice everywhere.
I want them to give me Prime Rib at the library.
Well, you'll have to go to a different library.
You're not coming to Brain Forest Cafe, okay?
You better get the fuck out.
God, I'm going to start my own.
I'm gonna start Dinosaur Times by myself.
No, you guys are gonna be sorry.
It's gonna be your newspaper.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, the Dinosaur Times.
Yeah, 'cause you came from Dinosaur Times.
That's how old you are.
Pussy, bitch.
No one's gonna read it.
It's gonna have a very low readership.
People would wanna read about
what's going on with archeology and stuff.
It's not about archeology.
It's about the daily lives of dinosaurs.
Yeah.
Hey, Pat, what's going on with archeology right now?
Yeah, tell us.
There's so many new bones.
Yeah?
I'm not even kidding about that.
Really?
Yeah.
Wow.
So, what's the latest headline?
So apparently, the stegosaur or triceratops was actually just like a baby of a different
animal, a different dinosaur.
So the triceratops is not an adult, it's just a baby version of something else.
So it's like you.
That's terrifying.
No.
So it's like you're a baby version of me.
I'm not a baby.
You are, you're a baby version of me.
Only a baby would think that he could start a dinosaur newspaper.
If I was a baby version of you, I would have one hair poking out of the top of my head.
And you do.
No, no, because, yeah you do.
It's very thick.
That's why you're wearing a beanie right now.
To hide it, because you don't want us to see it.
You knew we were going to keep you being a baby.
No.
You'll never own a newspaper, bro.
I'll own it.
I'm not, I don't even want the newspaper.
I want the restaurant.
Good, because you're not going to get it.
I want the Dinosaur Times restaurant.
Okay, and what are you going to put on the tables for people to read?
I'm going to put the menu on the table for people to read.
They didn't have menus in Dinosaur Times, so you can't have a menu.
It's a stone menu.
To you I posit this question.
What language do dinosaurs read on the menu?
Jurassic?
No!
Wrong!
That's a movie!
Spanish.
They read Jurassic.
Dinosaurs.
speak spanish
No, dinosaurs don't speak Spanish.
Yeah, they did.
What are you talking about?
Spanish, yeah, they did.
No.
Yeah, they did.
You're so stupid about language.
I'm not stupid about language.
You're right.
I'm not, definitely not stupid about dinosaur.
Speak every language right now.
All right.
Hello.
Bonjour.
Hola.
You're reading off of your tote bag.
Bienvenidos.
That means welcome.
I'm saying welcome. No, you're saying hello and then you switch to welcome.
Guten Morgen. Disqualified. That's good morning. That's different. Guten Tag. Different.
Just skip the Chinese, man. Guten Abend.
Uh, gut. Shut up. Nisch sehr gut. Nobody wants to hear this. Cameron's told me to do it.
It doesn't mean you have to do it. It means I have to do it.
So since when do you obey everything I say? I like to order when you drink energy drinks.
I don't like latte Patrick. Why? Because it kind of looks like you're eating poop.
This is a weird color. Yeah, it does look like poop. It's like got that green tint to it. Maybe
it's because you're sitting in front of a green screen now that I think about it. It could be
that. But maybe the light is reflecting off the bright green wall behind you. No, I don't think
so. Maybe this green poop is green because of the green screen. Yeah. See that's what I'm talking
about. That sentence would never come out of Monster Energy Patrick's mouth. It would. No.
this is the center so come out of monster energies of monster energy I miss when I
miss when aspartame was fucking calcifying your brain yeah turning you
there's no aspartame in monster zero yeah there's a we've been over there's
something it's some sweetener something worse it definitely wasn't good for me
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure yeah, I'm sure yeah, no, I'm really sure I know I'm sure about that
Yeah, I'm actually gonna have about that
I if you had kept drinking monster energy in ten years you have like the tongue version of Artie Lang's nose
Completely I'd have already like teeth. Yeah
You look like
great teeth. Heroin is really good for your teeth. Especially when you snort it yeah.
When you snort it and yeah. It's like Daredevil where he goes blind but his
other senses get better. When your nose gets fucked up your teeth get better. Oh
his sense of hearing is probably great now. Tell you what's great, his sense of
humor. Yeah this guy's one of the funniest guys of all time. Mm-hmm yeah. And that's
just the facts Jack maybe I do need to lose some of my senses yeah I think if I
was if all if I was just a just if I was just a voice what about your eyebrows so
if we just get rid of your eyebrows that's not a sense that's lose your
sense of hair good feature now I have no hair on my body you should get them like
wax imagine you should get like Morticia
Adam's eyebrows yeah like divine all the way across his head all the way to the
back of his head just lines I you guys want me to look like a freak I'm gonna
get him shaved oh we want you to look good and stop looking like a freak
yeah replace him with a script tattoo that says southern mm-hmm people like
and then also divine eyebrows.
- That'll go over well too.
That'll go over very well for you.
- I know somebody who has a Southern tattooed
in their eyebrow.
- Really? - Pretty cool, yeah.
- Yeah, it's Lauren Southern. - Very fucking swag.
Yeah, yeah, exactly. - Who's that?
- I don't know who you're talking about ever.
You say, we've been over this, you say names,
I go, yeah, Patrick, yeah.
- Lauren Southern was one of those alt-right people.
You choose one of those,
'cause like, those like alt-right people
from another country who's like--
- Alt-right, what does that even mean?
Yeah, they have a website?
One of those annoying, like, "Oh, I live in another country, but I'm very concerned about
American politics."
Oh, yeah, like Ian?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Like Patrick Miles Chung.
I'm not concerned about any other...
I'm not even concerned about American politics.
Oh, your Twitter tells a different story, pal.
You're out there tweeting about the spineless ghouls at the DNC.
Think you might be a little justice.
Those goblins at the DNC.
I'm...
I'm not justice.
These freaking rat fucks want us to vote for...
These rat fucks at the DNC hate the gremlins.
Sometimes like the Democrats, sometimes like the Demacrips and the Robledicans.
I'm Patrick.
That's genius, I've never thought of that.
Yeah, you should post that.
Wow, you really blew my mind there man.
It's like they're two gangs dude.
Oh my god.
Yeah, that's real shit.
And the hood is our, is the, is the Supreme Court.
The hood is the Supreme Court, real shit.
And the hood is Congress.
Where I'm from, the hood's the Supreme Court.
Wow.
And it's like, and it's like the third party is the Latin Kings.
And a switchblade is a voter's ballot.
Yeah.
And a gun is a, is a gun.
Is a gun, yeah.
Because both sides want guns, more guns.
Uh huh.
It's true.
Yeah, my friends want-
We gotta change the world from the ground up.
Give everyone a gun.
Yeah.
What's that Black Eyed Peas song?
Let's just get that playing under this whole-
Let's get retarded?
No, not let's get retarded, the other one.
Oh.
Let's get it started?
I'm a bee?
Yeah, let's get it started.
That's the one I was talking about.
Okay.
No, fuck it.
um fucking where's the love oh yeah back when they were like trying to be the fugees yeah they're
trying to be like yeah the conscious yeah they're trying to be conscious hip-hop yeah yeah yeah that
it's still so funny that they made a song called let's get retarded i love all of the like funny
about it to me it's not it's not it's kind of offensive actually it is offensive but it's so
funny how it's just like they only changed it so that they could put that in the commercials for
the NBA yeah yeah if the NBA didn't want that song that song would have been
called that yeah it probably would have gotten it probably would have gotten the
same amount of radio play - oh yeah back in the day well that's cuz like con all
conscious rap from like the 2000s is age so poorly you'll listen to like an old
most deaf song and it'll be like George Bush hates those fucking stupid homos
yeah he's dropping the f-bomb yeah fuck yeah freedom that's what I used to be mm-hmm
f-bomb used to be freedom and the s-bomb and the g-s-bomb used to be some Supreme
Court g-o-d a-m-n-i-t well and that god damn it mm-hmm taking the Lord's name
in vain did yeah taking the Lord's these these conscious hip hoppers are taking
the Lord's name in vain oh my god I'm I'm ready we got to make a we got to make a
conscious hip-hop song that's against cursing. No. That's right. Mm-hmm. I'm pro
cursing. No I'm anti-cursing. Let's make one that's anti-women in STEM. What about a bunch of white guys?
I'd like to see a woman in a bath. I never want to see a
woman doing math. Right? Yeah that's right. Women should remain silent and not work in
science that kind of these bitches going to Cornell they gotta go home they gotta
go home and ring the dinner bell yeah there we go this bitch shouldn't be
thinking about PEMDAS she should be thinking about my penis if you keep
talking to me about the wage gap I'm gonna do a rage slap yeah that's too
That's right. That's what I would say. That's what Caleb would say in the song that he's recording. Why am I the rapper?
You're the one who came up with it. I'm the cool black one. I forgot.
Oh my god. What? Oh my god. I'm the rapper of the group. That's true. Yeah.
I'm more of the, I'm the producer. Yeah, you are. You just got storched, dude. You're not the producer.
I'm making firehouse beats every day. No. Yeah, you are. You've never produced a thing in your life.
You're the producer?
Yeah.
You're not the producer.
I produce the podcast.
Name one...
Beat battle right now!
We got Big Cameron vs Big Patrick!
I made the theme song for the podcast. That's one beat right there.
Alright. Well...
I'm writing a new one.
Beatbox challenge!
Cameron...
Who goes first?
vs Patrick Pedophile.
3, 2, 1, GO!
(beatboxing)
He got some cool alternativo beats, now Patrick talk yo shit!
(coughing)
It cuts out.
I think Cameron wins this one. That's right.
Yo, this is a hard fought battle, but I'm gonna have to give it to you.
(coughing)
- What was that cough?
(groaning)
- Oh no!
- Let's do this list, dude.
(coughing)
- Oh, I'm good now.
I coughed, I choked on my own spit.
- Yeah, I bet you did and you liked it.
- Oh, I wish I liked it.
I wish it was good.
- Top 10 most embarrassing moments.
- Yeah, I just had number one just now
and I choked on my own spit while we were
- Life has an evil way of putting every one of us
an embarrassing situation once in a while. Think about the most embarrassing
situation you have ever experienced while voting. Not the imaginary
conceptual "ooh that would be bad" but more of the "that was the worst of the
ones I've experienced." Do they mean vote- *burp*
Yeah, keep going. Yeah, no, keep it going. Let's go. Do they mean most embarrassing
thing you've experienced while voting? Like- Yeah, no. Yeah, that's exactly what
they mean yeah while voting for president yeah we're on the list yeah yeah yeah
wait wait wait what's yours Pat most embarrassing I know exactly what it is
I'm not embarrassed you're not embarrassed so you voted for Jill Stein
no okay moving on I think it's funny yeah no it is funny number one pants with no
underwear now the comments are where it's at on this list once in April
Fool's Day my friends plan to do prank with me after school she said me to wear
trousers and come in her home. I was very happy, but when I go there with flowers to
give her immediately, some strong boys of my class comes and down my trousers and ran away.
I wasn't wearing underwear in front of my friends, so embarrassing."
That's all in a sentence.
Ow! I hate the strong boys of my class.
Oh my god, the strong boys of my class need to tone it down.
My favorite comment on this one is this one here that says, "Once my neighbor came. She
is a small children, but very dangerous. She has a room where girls down boys' pants and
underwear if anyone don't she make him walk fully naked from head to toe she
also beat whoa she beat what he beat also be all of these these are wait hold
on this it has like one two three four five like six fucking things that all
that all of these start with once like all of these comments start with what I
think the same person yeah this guy's been pants so many times by the
strong boys in his class. I hate those guys in my third grade class who were
always wearing red speedos and oiling each other up with Pam and getting
really really brown. Once I was falling water and auntie in school said you have
to undress fully I forgot to wear underwear but I have to be naked in
front of all of my classmates. Sounds like America to me. Mm-hmm. It has to be
in America right? Once some friends called me in an underwear party and I forgot to
wear underwear so I was forced to put all of my clothes off and make fun of me off
and laugh. Have you guys ever been to an underwear party? I hate going to an underwear party. I hate when I get the invitation because it's like I don't really want to go but I don't want to let my friends down.
Yeah the soccer team in college used to have the craziest underwear parties.
It's like a birthday card shaped like a cake but it's underwear and you open it up.
Captain Underpants party. Yeah yeah you are you are cordially invited. You were
- We are courtly invited to Captain Underpants' lair.
- Whoever posted this item in here has some issues.
I'm glad that never happened to me.
- Once I am wearing shorts in my school bus
and then it stuck on something and torn,
I am not wearing underwear
and higher class students are laughing at me.
- There is a girl who wherever saw me checks my underwear.
If I was wearing, then she'd take my pants in her home
and if not wearing, she forced me to be fully naked
ejaculate and take every clothes even if I was not wearing a pink underwear then
also she gave me that punishment and if wearing still she stripped my pants and
made me walk the whole town. There's definitely one guy out here who has a
serious fetish. It keeps happening to me. I keep getting pants by the strong boys at
school and then Bonti take me home and check my underwear. And my strong neighbor make me
little boy and wear no pants and she beat.
Once I was like this, then a bully pulled down my pants in front of my crush and her friend.
I felt so embarrassed she was as well as she couldn't walk past me for one month after that.
Once I am swimming my underwear was lost in pool.
I have to go without underwear in front of whole class.
Once I was changing in mall, then the mall owner came and said you look great without
clothes.
*laughing*
and said that see a boy can be fully naked for you
then everyone naked, me, impulsively made me walk out a whole colony
and embarrassed me
*laughing*
it took me to the fashion show
the whole colony, dude
that's embarrassing, that really is
once in a whole colony
sees me naked at the fashion show, dude
show dude. Oh no, it's one of those famous naked fashion shows at the mall.
The whole colony saw it.
Once in a beach I am playing with my friend and talking about underwear. I by mistake
accidentally pulled his underwear then for that. He beats me very much and then he put
off all my clothes and made me naked from head to toe. And then in front of every friend
he showed me naked and everyone laughed at me. And I have to say that I am a poor guy.
And as a third punishment is that I am his servant forever. And every time comes naked
comes make in front of him when he says put off your clothes
i have to do it by saying him boss and all his friends and do what they says
these are his five punishments
candid this guy's had a rough
i wasn't wear underwear for one year once my friend call me after school when
there were no teachers or anyone and they locked the classroom i am a new
student so they do ranging and forced me to down my shirt and pants
and doing this slowly but some strong boys head down your pants
there are girls also a girl's before boys so i doubt my pants and they said
he don't wear underwear I will tell it to everyone if you not dance so I dance for
30 minutes can you imagine this guy's like predictive text that's what it
sounds like fuck dude I wish this guy had a user now I wish we could like look at
this guy's got I bet he's all over this list yeah there's no ways not Betty has
one for number two having your diaper changed in public oh baby he has to be
here right yeah yeah one time I was at SeaWorld and two grandparents were
changing their granddaughter outside in public my grandma even yelled look at
that girl naked grandma's a freak what's wrong with your grandma come on grandma
well this one's like this one's weird this one's just like weirdly racist Asian
kids always get their diapers changed in public. I have seen this way too many
times growing up especially in Philadelphia's Chinatown where I live.
If I ever was caught having this done to me over the age of three I'd kill
myself especially if it was on YouTube. When I was in high school a lady and a
baby girl was visiting my homeroom special ed teacher later the lady
proceeded to change the girls diaper on the floor in the classroom in front of
the students and the teacher we all witnessed it this is not a joke it 100%
happened for real it reminded me of the scene from the Rugrats episode little
dude where Tommy got his diaper changed in a classroom I look at they specify
special ed teacher saying that they're in a special ed class it's just nice to
know I feel like there's a pretty pretty big alpha dog move yeah honestly so get
your diaper change in public just it's like when you you know when you pull
your pants all the way down to your ankles to pee at a urinal and you look
around the bathroom to make eye contact with everyone so they don't look at you.
You turn around and then you start shitting in the urinal. Yeah exactly.
Nobody's gonna talk to you dude. Yeah I think this comment here is from our guy
I saw a seven-year-old getting his pant down by his mother to change in public
his pant down that's his key that's his keystone phrase. Well it didn't start with once though but he
- He did say pant down.
I feel like nobody else has said pant down.
- Number three, he's back.
Walking in on your parents having sex.
Says, "Once when I was like five or something,
"I was not getting sleep 'til around midnight.
"Suddenly I heard noises coming from my parents' room.
"I went to check.
"My mom was saying nibble continually.
(laughing)
"I opened the door and I saw them doing it.
"M-mom was asking my dad to nibble on her.
"To this day I am scared."
(laughter)
- We have to find this guy's account, dude.
This is so unlucky that he's posting anonymously.
- Oh, I know.
- Here, listen to this comment.
"No, I don't want to see my parents nude
"and having their genitals clashing against each other."
That's a comment by the user Swagflix.
(laughter)
- Swag movies.
- Swagflix, swag Keno.
did that twice when I was little. You clashed your genitals? Yeah. Yeah. If this happens
to me I'd be like no question. I have no questions because I know exactly what's going on here.
That's like the inverse of no comment. Yeah. Walking in on your parents and just going
no comment. That did not just happen. Uh yeah no thanks. They have sex now? They have sex now.
Get a room. That's Judd Apatow or fucking Joss Whedon writing a fucking... That's Judd Apatow.
That's Judd Apatow and Joss Whedon and my two parents having sex with their genitals clashing
together like symbols. Ah when when Judd Apatow's genitals clash against Joss Whedon's and you get
Let me tell you, it's something.
- Yeah, when you hear it, it sounds like somebody
let Lisa one of those locked up monkeys.
- Let me tell you, that's a freak versus a geek.
- Yeah, hey, there we go.
- That's right.
- That is, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Okay, that was good.
Number four, being caught talking to yourself.
- I hate it when they hear my plans
when I get caught talking to myself.
- When I'm talking to myself, the post office bathroom.
- Yeah.
One time I was talking to myself and my friend saw it.
- Damn.
- Oh my God. - That's a scary comment.
My mom thinks that I have mental problems
if I talk to myself.
- This is bringing back some bad memories.
Left 4 Dead 2 Nick.
(laughing)
They put a quote from Nick from Left 4 Dead 2 in there.
- I've been talking to myself a lot more recently
because, especially when I'm out,
'cause I have a mask on, so I think nobody,
and I always have headphones in,
So I can't hear myself talking to myself.
And I think nobody else can hear me
'cause they can't see my mouth.
But then the other day, the homeless guy
who lives out front of my building said,
I was like, I guess, talking to myself.
Like I was like, talking to myself
about like a video I'm trying to make.
And he just goes, "What?"
And I was like, "Oh no, I'm not talking to you."
- I'm talking to my phone.
- Oh, you don't understand, I'm talking to my own brain.
yeah you don't get it no you wouldn't get it they tried to the cops tried to
evict that guy the other day really from the bit he lives on a bench out front of
my my yeah he sees he always is having a meeting with somebody like a different
person every hour comes and sits next to him and talks to him Jana calls him the
mayor and yes sir oh we had we had a mayor in Austin two days ago he the cops
A bunch of cops tried to like...
We had a mayor in Austin.
Sometimes towns or cities could have a mayor that's in charge of them.
Yeah, sometimes there's a mayor.
No, we had a guy similar.
We had a guy who...
Let Caleb finish his story, please.
The cops kept trying to like move him off the bench.
And he's like, "No! I no move!
You abuse me!
Stupid, dick-sucking
police officers!"
He sounds exactly like that.
That's a cool voice.
just like picking him up off the bench and putting him on the ground he's like
seven feet tall they can't do anything right and then they just gave up they
were like all right well you have a good one sir after just like beating him up
for an hour it's so weird they had there was a guy in Alston who like brought all
of his shopping carts to the front of this Indian restaurant and would just
scream at everybody when they tried to walk in maybe he's trying to start a
grocery store yeah maybe that's a good idea what are you what do you buy first
you buy the building you buy the grocery this Charlie was calling he I did get
Indian food there once and he did call one of the employees the n-word so I
don't know if I grocery store no he was okay nah well maybe he's from maybe he's
like Eminem okay yeah maybe he's just one of those Eminem guys yeah yeah
Maybe he's one of those M&M guys from the M&M store. Maybe that's why he said it.
Yeah.
Number five, peeing on yourself. Some people like this. Okay, I was in seventh grade last year when I was in science class.
I have to use the bathroom super badly.
I was going to ask the teacher, but the announcement said that the girls bathroom is off-limit till lunch.
OMG, I can't believe it. I have to hold it for a couple more hour.
My bladder was screaming at me. At the end of English class, I peed myself.
Thank goodness no one saw it. When I got home, I changed my pant before my mom noticed it.
- Somebody just says, "My mom beat herself once."
(laughing)
- This comment I really like,
"Laughing with a friend and they pee."
(laughing)
I just imagine that on like a Tumblr aesthetic image.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Just teenager things.
- I have been, I shit myself fairly often.
I almost never pee myself. - You shit yourself often?
- Yeah, dude, once every six months, like clockwork.
- I don't shit myself. - I think you told me,
I think you've definitely talked about this before.
Yeah, you've definitely talked about that.
I shit myself a lot.
It's still a surprise every time.
I would say like my last, probably six weeks ago.
That's weird.
Uh, no.
Probably six weeks, not to me, it's just normal, you know?
That's not normal to anyone else.
No, it's a modern family.
You would think, if I was the one who said that I shit myself like once every six months,
people would be like, "Oh yeah."
You know?
People would think you were gonna die.
But because it's you.
No.
People don't think I'm gonna die.
People think I'm gonna live forever.
I would think you were gonna die if you shat your pants every six months.
I mean I definitely have cancer.
Yeah, you don't have hair.
Yeah, exactly.
Like the telltale sign.
I don't know why I haven't been diagnosed with it.
I just haven't been to the doctor since I was like 15 but...
I thought I had a mouth tumor the other day but it was just an ulcer.
Just an ulcer? And you thought it was a tumor?
Yeah.
Nice dude.
Yeah, because I had a headache.
myself is on my on my my notes I have a note in my phone that's just everything
wrong with me you just tally it I just every every time I have a new symptom of
something it's for one day if I eventually go to the doctor I'll just be
like day you're gonna want to sit down for this and I'll read him off every
symptom that I had I did that with the dentist when I when I went when I was uh
17 this tooth is dirty this tooth is dirty this tooth is dirty I don't brush
my teeth I didn't I still don't dude I brush my teeth probably once once a day
once every two days it's dude it sucks they should just make a pill that brushes
teeth just fucking make a pill that does it for you dude yeah yeah they should
make a pill that's like a nuke for plaque in your mouth it should be yeah
no I agree yeah like something or poison that just melts off your teeth or it's
like a small type I think if I have if I ever have kids it'll be one of their one
of their chores yeah specifically for that you should get like a tooth tunes or
so like a juice world tooth no I want it to be as as trying to finally because
the thing about the tooth tunes is you got to like press it up against your
teeth so that would work sound though yeah yeah I think it's press up it's
No, if I had a Juice WRLD Tooth Toons, Badger, probably one of his songs.
Yeah. Lucid Dreams. Yeah. Evil House. Scariest song of all time by Juice WRLD.
If I had a... High School is Crazy. If I had a Tupac and the Outlaws hit them up Tooth Toons,
I'd probably... I had to kiss Tooth Toons when I was 10. You had to kiss Tooth Toons? Yeah.
yeah i had to kiss heim witz that's gene simmons real name oh i don't want to know that
why are you grossed out by his name what's gross about it the sound
okay just didn't like the sound okay but yeah kids should brush their parents teeth
right yeah yeah yeah yeah it should be like doing the dishes it's like a respect thing
- Exactly, yeah. - In some cultures they do it.
- I bet they do that in China.
- Yeah. - I bet they do that in China.
(laughing)
- I bet they do.
- I don't think they do it in China.
- I think they do because I--
- Jerry Seinfeld thinks they do that in China.
- Sorry, have you been in China?
- Yeah, I have.
- In China, they can't, it's supposed to be parents' day.
It just makes sense.
- What's the deal with that?
(laughing)
- He's so, that's, yeah, I'm so rogant.
- Jerry Seinfeld just making up shit about China.
(laughing)
- I heard they joined the army at age three.
- In China, the vaginas are sideways.
it just makes more sense
this is how it should be
it just makes sense to me
look everything in china says made in USA what's to do with that
i'm thinking
i'll become a chinese
i'm thinking of converting i'm gonna get a new surgery
i'm gonna get an experimental surgery
to make me chinese
i don't think jerry seinfeld would ever go to china
I feel like I don't think that's... I think he'd be so rich, it makes perfect sense for him to go to China.
That's true, he could drive on the Autobahn there.
He could drive on the China-Bahn.
The China-Bahn!
Yeah. Mmm.
China-Bahn. China-Bahn.
Mmm. Yeah, you pick that up at the airport.
Sounds good.
Yeah. Oh, that's another business idea I got now.
China-Bahn. China-Bahn?
Jerry Seinfeld's Chinese Restaurant?
- Jerry, it's a Jerry Seinfeld owned Cinnabon.
That's all, it's like a Cinnabon.
- My business idea is for something
that's owned by Jerry Seinfeld.
- Yeah, I'm gonna get a bit on it.
- I would love a Jerry Seinfeld Chinese restaurant
and you're like, "Hey, sorry, can I have chopsticks?"
And he's just like, "Chopsticks?
"What do you want chopsticks for?
"You have a hand, you have a mouth, use a fork!
"The hell's wrong with you?"
- It just makes sense.
- It just makes sense!
- It's a Cinnabon. - Why are you using chopsticks?
Are you a caveman?
You wanna eat off a stone?
How are you gonna eat your soup?
It's a cinnamon roll rangoon.
Whoa.
That's a pretty good idea.
That's China-bon.
That's Jerry Seinfeld's China-bon.
China-bon, yeah.
Okay.
Alright.
You got me.
I think I want you guys to go 50% on this with me.
I'll go 100% because I'm stealing that idea.
No, you're not.
No.
I'll tell you what.
for a hundred percent of your idea right now,
'cause I'm stealing it.
- Hmm.
And Patrick, after you open up
the Jerry Seinfeld's China Bar
and you can open up a spinoff restaurant
that's Michael Richards' soul food.
(laughing)
- It's open mic night at Michael Richards' soul food.
At Michael Richards' country cooking.
(laughing)
He's hosting.
That's how he tries to make up for it?
Yeah!
I'm trying to give back to the community.
Oh my god!
Jerry, I'm moving to Baton Rouge.
Oh, that's pretty good.
Yeah, number six, caught stealing.
Once you are in trouble, then you are in big trouble.
I never got caught stealing, although I did only steal one thing in my life.
I stole Pokemon cards all the time.
Yeah, I stole Magic the Gathering cards when I was in high school.
I stole a cigar with my friend.
What the fuck?
How did you even get to where cigars are?
You were the lookout and you didn't steal it. You abetted.
I was an accomplice.
I smoked the cigar, so...
I used to steal stuff out of kids' houses.
Yeah. I never stole things. I would leave things at people's houses.
That's ingenious.
Like I would put, like, I would bring framed pictures
and put them in their stuff. I would steal
I would always steal headphones. Oh yeah, that's not bad.
I just thought it was funny.
like a jacket maybe. A jacket? You can't steal a jacket. I feel like a jacket's too far.
Yeah. Unless it's like somebody has a lot of jackets. They'll see you wearing it. Yeah. Well, you don't wear it, you put it in your
backpack. Well, then what are you gonna do with it? I'm gonna put the jacket on my
legs. I'm gonna put it on my... And make it look like I'm a little guy. I'm gonna put it on my beautician
dummy. Dress it up. Is that so wrong? I'm gonna make it look like Sonic the Hedgehog.
yeah come on number seven calling your teacher mommy yeah I do that top
comment especially if I do that to all teachers yeah I do that to all teachers
regardless of gender yeah hey mommy question for the test hey mommy what do
you think that Hegel's dialectical I'm talking about different guy I'm talking
about a PBS show you're talking about talking about Hegel you're talking about
you're thinking of Hoggle from Labyrinth. You're thinking of Heckler, the documentary.
Yeah I'm thinking about the dialectical praxis in Heckler. Imagine a German guy named Heckler.
Hey mommy I couldn't help but notice we only have very few indigenous authors on
this reading list and I was wondering. Yeah. Hey mommy am I supposed to present
today? That'll throw them off I feel like that's a good... you record
yourself doing that and this is the Patrick challenge you record yourself
telling your teacher say say mommy this my mommy is this gonna be graded on a
core call hey mama
- Mom.
- Do the Stewie Griffin challenge.
- Mom, mommy.
- And say mom, mommy to your teacher.
- Yeah, it'll work dude.
- My head hurts.
- Mom, can I have detention?
Can you give me some detention?
It's been a while.
- Yeah, ma.
- Yeah, mommy.
- Ma, ma.
- I called my best friend mom on accident.
(laughing)
How do you do that?
Maybe his name was, maybe his name was man.
Man, yeah.
Oh, okay.
Maybe it was Jason Momoa.
This is my best friend Darlene, who's also my mother.
I'm not scared to call my friends mom.
Hey, you guys are kinda, I'll just start calling you mom.
Is that embarrassing?
No.
That's normal, right moms?
It's fine.
How many of us?
How many moms?
moms there are three of us Patrick's you were so I can't see number eight laughing
so hard milk squirts out your nose that's not embarrassing that's just uh that's a
trick that's just having fun with your friend that's it that's a magic trick
exactly top comment agrees how is this embarrassing it's just funny but weird
can't believe this is number five it's actually number eight so you sure I beg
on your face now pal and milk you know David Blaine can squirt a gallon of milk
at his nose when he laughs.
Number 9.
Caught listening to Justin Bieber songs.
luckily for me i'd listen to music by other artists
that's for me is a saturated sunrise
like who now
yeah i don't think you do if you can make another artist i don't like so it's
i'll be listening to sticks you don't like sticks
i don't listen to the all-man brothers band
uh... there's no one has no one i've been waiting to get to this whole time
on. Number 10 is nude on stage during nursery play. What does that mean? If that
happened, I would fall down, my head would spin 180 degrees, then my tongue
would turn upside down and pop out of my eyes. Then I would turn bald and all my
hair would turn to liquid and come out of my pores. Then I would have no hair
anywhere on my body. Then my legs would do a splits and my upper torso will rip
out of the bottom and then the worst part is coming up I would turn into Justin Bieber
@smoothcriminal did this actually happen to you?
Would you guys ever do like a naked on stage naked show?
No.
Probably not.
No one is going to see my penis.
I got asked to do the improv boss one I gave him a hard N-O.
Yeah.
I mean yeah it's like.
You gave him a hard N.
No.
Why did you do that?
No, no.
Yeah, I mean the thing is that--
A lot of people do that shit though,
I don't understand it at all.
It's not even like it's gonna be a good show.
It's not even like, it's like,
oh, this is the thing that's gonna make my career,
I guess I--
I would just be confused on like how hard do I get.
Yeah.
And also, I mean like--
If you get hard, is that okay?
If I get hard, do they have to have sex with me?
Do they all hold me down and have sex with me?
They can hold me down and suck my dick and fuck my balls?
Do they fuck me in my balls?
Wait, if they see my balls, they have to fuck my balls?
Do they have to hold onto my balls and run across the room?
What if I accidentally dip my beer in my balls?
Yeah, what if I spill water on my balls and I have to run around the room to get them dry?
What if I have to run around the room so fast to get my balls dry that I accidentally go forward in time?
Oh, what if they start throwing Skittles at me and I gotta windmill my penis to whack them off?
What if they throw a Skittle at me and it goes into my pee hole and I have to go to the hospital?
Oh, what if I have to do a naked stand-up show at the hospital for all the patients?
What if I sit down on the stool but the whole stool goes inside my ass?
What if my microphone gets stuck in my balls?
Yeah, what if the little antenna at the end of the microphone gets in my pee pee?
Yeah.
Yeah!
I don't know. There's a lot of like okay, so that would be a horrible place for that
What if I accidentally summon an evil genie
Hamburger meat
What if they have a meat grinder on the stage
and my asshole falls in the meat grinder on the stage
What if my penis comes off of my body and flies around the room like an RC plane and people are reaching at it and trying to grab it
The sexy lady grabs it and it squirts everywhere.
Oh no, my penis turned into the golden snitch.
So in short, ImprovBoston,
(imitates farting)
(laughing)
Sorry, I don't wanna skip ahead.
We can skip ahead if you really need to.
Number 12 is just parents making love.
It's one thing to walk in on your parents having sex.
It's another thing just for your parents to make love entirely.
Yeah.
[Laughter]
There's a comment on here that says, "It's actually very cute, isn't?"
Oh, oh my god, what are you?
Oh, my bad. I thought you guys were fucking.
You two are making love. This is very cute.
This is cute of you to do.
Anyway, could you heat up some milk for me?
I'm really tired, but I can't fall asleep.
I'm really tired, but you know I can't fall asleep.
I have a stomachache from looking at this.
Can you go make me some milk?
There was a time in high school when I was like,
every night I'm gonna have a warm glass of milk
to go to sleep and I hated it.
- It's so psycho dude, it's so disgusting.
- It's horrible.
I would heat it up in the microwave.
- Yeah.
- Oh, I did that once.
- Dude, I don't get it.
I've never, my younger sibling would do that all the time.
It's so disgusting.
- Terrified, dude.
- Milk was meant to be hot.
It would come out of a fucking cow piping hot.
- That's right.
- And it would stay hot.
it would never cool down. It would never cool off. That's what a hot toddy is I think.
That's no that's a hot tata. Hey. I think you're being inappropriate right now. I'm not dude.
I think you're being inappropriate a little bit. Did you guys come come out cold or hot?
Hot. Hot though like freezing cold. No it's like lukewarm. Icy cold. One degree above freezing.
I feel like it's like when you throw boiling water on a freezing day and it turns into
ice.
On your girlfriend's back.
Yeah, and it turns into ice.
I feel like it's like that but for room temperature.
I don't know.
I'm always pretty disappointed in the temperature of my gum.
As soon as it leaves your pee hole it turns into like...
It's like the temperature of spit.
I wish that it would...
Spit?
Do I have cold spit?
Hold on.
Oh, oh
Come on what do you mean? You can't waste it? You only have a little bit in your life
It's like heartbeats finite amount of spit. Yeah, come on. You don't want to waste a lot of spit
Can I have some?
You're gonna spit transplant from you
Okay
Number 13, farting in public.
Not embarrassing.
Not embarrassing, dude.
That's, uh, someone who's boss.
Once you're a master at holding farts in, you can go into a corner and let the storm rage on.
I hate Frozen, by the way. I know this is stereotyping, but it's just a meme.
How boys fart. Let the storm rage on.
How girls fart. Conceal. Don't feel. Don't let them know.
So true.
That's so true.
Boys fart like this, girls fart like that.
yeah you know with this so you can get with that I think I'll go with this
because this is where it's at I love wait I want to skip ahead to I want to skip
ahead those crazy hamsters and their Kia I want to skip ahead to number 16 caught
masturbating and I want to read this comment that says I always bet
masturbate in the bathroom with the door locked or in the dead of night in bed
Kyle watching porn number 17 has a little script here if you guys want to read it.
Alright let's do it. Kyle watching porn. Who's gonna be the mom?
You're the mom Pat. Okay, Caleb's the mom. What are you looking at? Wait, okay, who's me? You. Okay, then
you really have to read the note at the end. This is serious. Who's on first?
What are you looking at? Mom! Wait, there's a girlfriend. You're the girlfriend Pat.
No, Cameron's the girlfriend.
No, he's me.
Wait, there's four parts in this script.
Oh my god.
I'll be mom because mom only has one line and then I'll also be the note at the end.
Okay, and then I'll be me
and then Patrick will be the girlfriend and the friends.
Alright, let's do this.
We've done so much, I feel like we need intro music now.
Yeah.
Is that Candy Shop?
What are you looking at?
Mom!
Tom, are you looking at other girls?
girls? Uh, no. Ha ha ha! Wow, you're a girl of year! No I don't, now leave me alone. Yes,
that would be embarrassing. Note, Tom is not my real name. I'm Darren, and I'm
making a cartoon of it.
Yeah, I'm just, I'm making a cartoon of it. Yeah, I'm making a cartoon of it. Yeah. The
The podcast about list players present
Caught While Watching Porn by Darren
Darren's cartoon
Yeah, uh, Pat, just a little note
I feel like you could have maybe given a girl voice
Yeah, do two different voices, let's run this again
Make some different character choices
Okay
What are you looking at?
Mom
Tommy, are you looking at other girls?
Uh, no
Ha ha ha, wow, you're a girl, I love you
No I don't, now leave me alone
me alone yes that would be embarrassing note Tom is not my real name I'm Darren
and I'm making a cartoon of it I think that was good I think that was really
good I think I could sell that for money we can sell Darren's cartoon for money
and doesn't fucking find out yeah I think we could option Darren's script off
Darren if you're listening right now we would love to to work with you on this
production watching porn Darren we want to we want to we want to
- I'm gonna pick your brain for a little bit
and see if we can expand upon your short here,
your short cartoon.
- Your short.
- Hey Patrick.
- Yeah.
- How would you like being embarrassed
and getting punished too?
(laughing)
- I wouldn't like that.
- That's not convincing.
It sounds like you might actually really enjoy that.
- I wouldn't like it at all.
- You wanna get punished and embarrassed.
- You wanna get punished. - Oh my God.
- You wanna spill. - I wouldn't like it.
- You wanna spill Kevin's chili.
- I wouldn't like it.
- And then you wanna get spanked.
I don't like, I wouldn't like it.
You would.
At all. I think you would like that.
I wouldn't.
Stop smiling when you say it.
Number 21, number 21. I wouldn't like it.
Number 21, opposite sex public restroom.
Sorry, this is the opposite sex public restroom.
(laughing)
Yeah.
I'm here to have sex.
Oh, I think he's back. Not in here.
One time I had a dream where I went to the boys bathroom
and even my unrealistic second grade dream was horrible.
On an unrelated note, I sing in public bathrooms
until someone comes in, then I stop
and hope they didn't hear me.
It's not them.
- I'm female.
I was in Chinatown once during a banquet.
(laughing)
And I had to use the restroom.
So I went and I saw the ladies restroom
was constantly closed and when I knocked,
no one responded and the door was locked.
So I went into the men's restroom instead.
- That's a crime. - How do you guys feel about,
you know when moms or you know when moms or dads
or dads or moms or something else.
- Bring their kid into the bathroom.
- Bring their kid into the wrong bathroom.
What the hell man?
I was under the impression there was no girl zone.
They gotta have a kids bathroom.
Where only the kids go.
And that also, that...
It's ingenious.
That is ingenious.
Well that's why they have the family restroom.
Yeah.
Which I would use because it's a more comfortable shitting situation.
Yeah, cause you're a family.
Cause yeah, yeah.
Family of one.
This happened to my friend who went into a girls bathroom
and bike cops just happened to be riding by and wrote him a ticket.
I found number 33. He's back.
Oh my god.
Ready? This is number 33. When your crush rejects you.
Comment here.
Once my crush rejects me and made me naked head to toe in public,
I have to become naked head to toe in public.
Then she called me in her room and she beats me and said that I will do this daily.
Once me and my friends are walking, my old crush came and said,
"Strip all of your clothes with an hunter on her hand."
And said to my friend, "You too."
She said, "Come in my van and then be naked.
"I will take you to my home."
I said, "Okay."
And the I do that, then she removes me from her van
and said, "Come to my house to take your clothes."
And I went there and she slapped me and rejected me.
- Wow.
This guy's had the worst life ever.
- This is like, yeah, this is like now scarred.
This is just like, just over and over again.
just insanely amazing stories.
- Yeah, like imagine,
imagine like just being that guy
and just waking up in the morning being like,
oh man, I hope strong boys don't strip my pants down today
and slap me, reject me.
And just every single day a new--
- Walk in front of the colony.
- Yeah, a new neighbor beats you
in front of the whole colony.
Every single day just waking up like, oh please.
- And then you go on top 10s to the vent
everybody just laughs and thinks you're making it up yeah yeah please don't
leave this guy we need to rescue him yeah yeah we need to say anybody has any
information on who this guy is number 34 people seeing a black spot on your
underwear sorry that that's just the blight of my underwear yeah the black
at
can't hold your poop anymore and excrete it publicly.
Number 57, being ass kicked by your teacher.
Number 63, failing at trolling.
So true, once I put a bucket of paint balanced on the door for my annoying big sister and
and I made sure that I do not enter the room,
but while I was going to the toilet,
I forgot about what I said and went inside,
only for my bucket to splash all over me.
By the way, it was blue paint, if you were wondering,
and worst of all, my sister came two seconds later
and said, "Mom, I found a Smurf in the living room,"
and all my family came to see me
covered in blue paint, so embarrassing.
- That's still a pretty good troll.
- Convince your sister that you're a Smurf.
- You told your family that Smurfs were real, yeah.
- Yeah, a Smurf is a kind of troll.
Uh-huh
64 throwing up on your own birthday. I did this year on my birthday for some reason and in 2014 I did trains 45
We I think trains is on the last episode 65 goes to school with no underwear on and your crush sees your bum
Yeah, Tom Green would like that yeah fucking freak yeah, my grandparents told me to have a good day at school and I said you too
Wow. Number 70, wiping your butt and getting poop on your hand.
I feel like that's not embarrassing because nobody else sees it, right?
Right. Yeah, no, I mean it's embarrassing to myself when I do that.
Number 77, trying to get an autistic kid to try to stop taking your stuff.
Whoever added this as 6, so disrespectful. I'm autistic and I only steal your things
if you say stuff like this to me from I Hate School.
- Get that, get that dude.
- Number 78, the infamous awkward silence.
- Oh my God.
- Especially after that magpie hit the window
in the middle of a Naplan test and now everyone is staring.
- (laughs) 83, thinking about something gross
and gagging in front of your crush.
(laughs)
Baby, I'm having an amazing night tonight, really.
- Yeah.
- This has been (gags)
Sorry, I thought I was poop.
I'm sorry. I'm a dog asshole. I thought about throw up.
That is such a funny thought to me, is like having sex and being like, "Hey, can we stop? I just thought of a poop."
I just imagined a poop and now I just thought of a poop.
Number 90, you order a triple decker cheeseburger with bacon and when it arrives you get a little too excited.
That's just like somebody seeing a burger and just going like, "Ooooh!"
Oh my!
Oh heavens!
Number 92, being caught masturbating by 20+ people.
Oh this is a long comment here.
Do you happen to be a Japanese schoolgirl on a train?
With a bunch of cameras around?
What?
Let's not read this comment.
This comment is too much.
I just skipped it.
Yeah, it's no good.
If you want to read it, you go look for it yourself, because that's just borderline fanfiction.
96 the person that you have a crush on being revealed at the worst possible
moment oh my god number 98 erection and swimming class number 101 things are
going to end on parents check your browsing history only comment looking at
my search history on Safari I'm a bad kid parentheses it is a parody I made
mom dad I'm parodying something yeah I know I'm doing a parody of what search
history should look like I needed that on there for a parody thank you yeah
picking a pair of you have sex so I needed to watch all this porn research
doing research to make my parody of I'm on a boat called I'm fucking an ass I'm
parodying this video but cute cute girl fucks red panda this is part of my
parody oh yeah that's a that's a video Caleb watched I've never seen that all
right
the patreon watch art we have I don't know if we've ever mentioned that we have
twitch a twitch stream on the show yeah we have sure people know yeah if you if
you like the show you like the stuff so true what else I mean just just t-shirts
Bye!
Oh shit.
Bye.