You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts for the heartless.
You're a crap monster.
Alright, I'm recording.
Oh, I got poop all over my glasses.
Me too.
No, not that part.
Me too, I'm recording.
I do not have any poop anywhere on my body.
I actually don't, but Kayla does.
No.
You said it first, Patrick.
You can't back out of it.
You guys both do.
And, started recording, Patrick immediately gone.
on yeah well left yeah and when he comes back he's gonna go well I had to wipe
off my glasses and it makes a lot of sense that he has to leave his chair to
do that mom whoa didn't have to do that horrible tone for this yeah that was
just like not right to say okay we're one second in I wasn't really you fuck
his no one no one has ever five years old by the way yeah so what the fuck is
wrong with you dude. No she isn't. Yes she is. Okay so now. I was saying that to get a rise
out of camera. No you were gonna rise out of you when you're thinking about a five year
old mom. Fucking bitch. See this is what happens when you leave the camera and you make us
think that it's that we're alone. We laugh. You have separation anxiety. We go stinking.
Like a dog when you leave the camera we start tearing up all the pillows in our rooms. Yeah.
shitting on the floor. I had a dream last night that they think that they think they're ripping
up a pillow is gonna bring their parent back. Not gonna happen. Not gonna happen dog. You're
gonna die alone. It'll just make your mom mad at you. Yeah. Stupid dog. Dogs are so
stupid. Last night I had a dream that I died and I became a ghost and instead of like haunting
somebody I just went to like the news and I was like "ghosts are real" and "I'm a ghost
if you guys want to interview me and then everybody just found out that ghosts were
real and I was like yeah that's that's pretty good proof that ghosts don't
exist is that no ghost has ever gone to the news yeah and yeah I've been like
this is the biggest story ever. Do you guys want to interview me? Yeah.
Or can I be in a TV show? Can I have my own TV show?
Can I get a sitcom? Can I have a show with Casper? Can we bring Casper into the set?
- Yeah, you bring Casper into the studio
and see what he's up to lately.
- Yeah, Casper and his Italian uncles.
- These 10 pictures of Casper will blow your mind.
He is so hot now.
Casper's glowed up.
- No.
- And he's not just glowing 'cause of the ectoplasm.
- He can turn into anything though.
He could be, he turns into like a hammer.
- Does Casper--
- You know he turned into army hammer.
- Does Casper turn into stuff?
I don't know.
- No, you're thinking of Ditto from Pokemon.
- Yeah, you're thinking of the Green Lantern's finger.
- Yeah.
I'm thinking of the Green Lantern's finger. That's my bad.
Yeah.
No, he can't turn into anything but a ghost.
You're thinking of Play-Doh.
You're right, I'm thinking of Legos.
I didn't say Legos.
You're thinking of toys.
I'm just thinking of imagination.
I'm thinking of my imagination.
Oh, yeah.
Sorry about that.
Yeah, my bad.
Oh, Seinfeld, right? That's that show where the
where the night fights the robot and he's riding on a dragon and and there's
explosions it and unicorns and rainbows i was sorry
i was there was there was my imagination i was thinking about my imagination
thinking of the coolest thing i was thinking of an awesome i was thinking of
an awesome movie i invented
my bad
a man that was on me
my bad maybe i'm gonna be fat again
yeah i'm putting it in the video
caleb clump yeah
let's do it yeah let's get caleb clump in here
Let's try to the Red Scare subreddit is gonna love this. Why?
Did you see that that post about us on there?
No, that's embarrassing that you should yeah, why subreddit?
You know somebody in the discord posted on somebody in the discord posted it and I read it on it, bro
I clicked on it because I wanted to see what people
What Red Scare said on their subreddit up did it wasn't that it was a fan
Did you guys see what fans of Red Scare said on there?
It was somebody who said that they liked us but they hate the podcast.
That's just like fat gay guys who think they're skinny.
Posting on the red-
Yeah, why do you think I was reading that?
Patrick and Patrick clicked on it.
Patrick saw that link and he went "Spill the tea, honey" and he clicked on it.
Spill the tea, sis.
If you're over 260 pounds, don't even call me.
Meanwhile, they're 220.
No, they're exactly 260.
They're exactly 260 and they're like, "Anybody who's bigger than me is humongously fat."
Like me right now with this pillow in my shirt.
Why don't I do this more?
I haven't done this since I was 17.
Why don't I do this?
You were doing that at 17?
Yeah, dude.
It was really funny.
You put the pillow in your shirt and you tell the teacher like, "Oh, no.
I have a stomach ache right now.
Oh, God.
I ate too much food at lunch.
I ate something nasty, I have to go home now.
Oh no I'm fat!
Why are you talking in that voice?
You weren't talking like that before.
It's Taco Tuesday!
I ate a taco Tuesday, I think it was a bad meal.
You just get in trouble.
You just get in trouble for racism.
You don't even get to go home.
Oh no, I turn racist!
Oh no!
The food at the cafeteria made me racist.
Oh god damn.
I need to be educated.
One of the best feelings ever was when I broke my foot on the soccer field as a kid.
Seems like a pretty bad feeling to me.
Yeah, that's not a good feeling.
Trust me, that was one of the worst feelings ever.
The best feeling ever was my teacher didn't believe me and she was like, "Just walk it
off."
And then the next day I came with a full cast on my leg.
just like yeah that was one of the best feeling your teacher just starts saying
that she like tries to take your cast off she's saying you're doing it for
attention really she was a little bit skeptical even after I came with the
cat that's the funniest type of teacher is the one that like hates a fucking
student this is a tough teacher yeah yeah who's done it for like three years
and it's like yeah I'm a I'm a veteran yeah the best kind of teacher is like
the 27 year old teachers and nurses are such a such a bullshit job where they
they pretend that they served in the military seriously dude yeah I'm sorry
that you have to like buy your own supplies yeah they have to military to
yeah you think to go to the why do you think army surplus stores exist exactly
because there's a surplus of all their shit you know what you all right all
right here's the okay here is the solution ready this is gonna change the
world yeah change it so what if we convince whoever the bait the whoever
this in charge of the military William Barr if that's him that's what he does
yeah Roseanne bar Vince him that Isis hates school supplies Wow yeah so then
the army surplus stores get filled with like Ticonderoga pencils and shit and
then teachers can go to the army surplus stores and then just get those so we
have a surplus of pencils. You are one of the smartest people in the United States. That is pretty smart yeah yeah but they would still have to
buy them yeah no they still have to buy the wrong stuff. So nothing changes. But we have a surplus of it.
But you they can also get a cool camo jacket for playing paintball.
wall while they're getting pencils.
If the army found out that ISIS hated school supplies, then they would start selling guns
to school supplies and then school supplies would become a new terrorist group.
Just a little bit of political humor for the episode.
Wow.
Wow, that's huge.
Yeah, now we can go back and talk about the other part of it.
But I just wanted to make sure we got a little bit of knowledge in there too.
Now let's do Bolivia.
Okay, Bolivia.
Where is that?
Bolivia what's that like? What is that a girl named Bolivia?
What do you want me to be Olivia?
Well yeah what is that supposed to mean?
*laughs*
There's a town in North Carolina called Bolivia
Oh what's that? There was a cup?
There was a cup in Bolivia?
There was a cup at the government cup?
Margarita?
No *laughs*
No?
The CIA put a cup of
of mar- ee- agua
in Bolivia?
Is that what happened?
That's not what so this is what yeah, so we're supposed to believe that the that the CIA could carry a cup that far
Yeah, yeah, right you'd spill all the water. Yeah, I couldn't even carry. Hey, man
JFK's brains all the way down a street. Yeah, they tried to put those in a cup
That was in a cup as skull is a kind of cup
Someone was doing because JFK was very promiscuous. They were actually just collecting DNA for a paternity test
Yeah, that was the...
That's why he blew his head open.
He used part of his brain to see...
They took a part of the brain from the kid and then a part of the brain from JFK.
That's the origin of QAnon.
Yeah.
And it turns out that child, Chester Bennington.
Chester Bennington was leading clues in all of the...
Yeah.
I mean, just look at the names of the albums.
of the albums hybrid theory a hybrid of JFK and and the mother mm-hmm that's what
Chester Bennington is Meteora a bullet hitting JFK's head is kind of like a
Meteora Meteora kind of like a Meteora hitting the earth what are the other
albums minutes to midnight I don't even have to you don't even have to think of
anything for that one. Yeah it's a really good point. In the end, the end of the world. In
the end, how did he kill himself? Was he a gun? Oh yeah and that song they had called
um Donald Trump is the warrior of light, you guys remember that? I do remember that one.
That was the Linkin Park song that came out like before the election and a lot of people
like it that was actually in the third transformers movie it's people are mad
at 50 cent cuz I guess he said that Trump has swag yeah I said it yesterday
but I need praying - I need praying - to disavow his best friend who's that yeah
yeah who's brain sex man you don't remember sex man nope tell me about it
he was like an early youtuber make your eyes look completely crossed yeah yeah
dude you look like you're wearing goggles yeah it's pretty funny it looks like
you're staring at your nose I'm not maybe he just is I'm not maybe it's not the
glasses you see something interesting on your nose are you trying to cross your
eyes now cuz that was the only time it didn't look like yeah I think these
glasses are still to look like look at the sides of my head I think they're
still too small yeah I got these are like they do look like they're squeezing
your head I know dude I know where those what's
probably not where there's twice cuz you don't need I can see dents on both sides
of your head yeah it's squeezing your head I'm gonna take them off there we go
that's better now I can't read the list but that's fine I think you can I can
still I think yeah yeah what are you talking about okay I wore glasses I wore
glasses when we went to PAX that was cosplay yeah yeah you were cosplaying as
nerd you're cosplaying as Gordon Freeman no yeah you were oh my god I'm hungry
I have a rumbly tummy. My stomach rumbly. I had a bunch of pancakes for breakfast I
had breakfast today I had some cereal for breakfast. It was fucked up for me. Why'd you eat breakfast you
never eat breakfast I had an egg sandwich. Every time I see you eat breakfast you're like hung
over and you're only there cuz me and cam are bringing you there and you're like
sniffing the eggs that you got and putting it back yeah well I mean that was
red arrow it is a big no I mean it's have it's not just red arrow you do every
time every time he goes to a restaurant he always orders something that he's
heard of but has never eaten before which I respect but then he almost never
likes it I'll have the linguica and then I'll get it I would never eat
something called linguica. - It tastes terrible.
(laughing)
- No.
- What do you mean?
I've never done that.
- I don't think I've ever seen that happen.
- You're thinking of someone else.
- No, I'm thinking of you.
- I don't know that I've ever heard Patrick say
I don't like this when he's eating food.
- I do sit there and I kind of like
look at the menu for like 20 minutes.
- You do take a long time to order, that is true.
- Why is that?
Are you just such a thoughtful guy?
- Yeah. - I know it's not that.
- It's, yeah, you just finished--
- It's 'cause you're looking for
smiley face french fries. - The waiter comes
and you finished reading the second line of the menu.
- Yeah, I do read everything on the menu.
- You're a slow reader.
- Yeah, I am too.
I'm a slow eater too.
- And you're a slow cheater.
- That's right. - No.
- Yeah, I've never cheated.
- And you're a slow speeder.
- You got a slow peener down there.
- Come on!
My penis is fast.
My penis is so fast. - Fast and limber.
- Prove it.
prove it bring your penis to that rocking bed. You want to see my penis? You want to see it again?
There we go. That's all Jeffrey Toobin needed to do. That's all Jeffrey Toobin needed to do.
Who's Jeffrey Toobin? He's the guy, the New Yorker guy that showed his thingy on zoom. I didn't hear
about that. That's all anybody's talking about on Twitter. Everyone's talking about the tubes. I've
been kind of off Twitter. Yeah I don't know who the guy is. All I know about him is that he showed
his penis in a zoom call yeah quote-unquote by accident do you guys
want me to show my penis now not really no do you remember when you guys were at
my house and I twisted my wiener and put my balls did you go get that camera
developed that yeah yeah so I took my balls in my wiener and I basically
reversed them like what you do with like a mr. potato head to be funny and I got
my penis on the bottom and my balls on the top it was a really it was a really
like like striking image like kind of burned itself into it did look like
potatoes yeah it was like just like a little it was like you just had a lump
like a potato yeah it looked like something was seriously medically wrong
yeah but it's not I just like you had an egg sac down there yeah what if I had
given birth to a tiny me you could out of that you could give birth to a mini
you get a ball and hatch like eggs what would a mini me of Caleb be like
probably like Caleb but smaller yeah yeah it'd be the same size okay yeah all right
you can't get any smaller than me I'm already so little they should when they
need when they need like a child actor they should just cast Warwick Davis just
a separate thought just thinking okay just like if they need like you know like
if it's like a coming-of-age movie and they want a kid who can really sell the
lines and really doesn't have trouble reading or memorizing stuff should just
at Warwick Davis and they should still have him in the in the Harry Potter
Gringotts outfit yeah that is how children look to me yeah yeah did he was
he the Gringotts guy or was he he was the music teacher was I was he I was he
might have been both to be on yeah yeah I mean yeah I know he was the music
teacher but I'm pretty sure he was also British movie and they needed a little
person yeah they only you'll see it's him or Peter Dinklage and Peter Dinklage is too
sexy yeah he is home he is so hot I bet a lot of women would fuck him yeah no
absolutely but I can't think of a single girl midget I would fuck that's not nice
I mean I do just the true you got to get to you got to get to know them do you
have what you're talking about what are you talking about you saying anybody that
you have sex with you have to get to know them yeah yeah Patrick is a
a demisexual all right okay Patrick that's very nice of you that's very
sweet so you're so you're saying that if I found you the right the right little
person you probably I don't know so you're saying okay I don't care I don't
care you don't care you don't care about them I ain't got no type so you don't
I'm gonna tell little people.
- Bad bitches is the only thing that I like.
- There we go.
That's what I like to hear.
(laughing)
There we go.
All right, our list today is top,
is this the right one?
Top 10? - I don't even wanna
do the list.
- Why not?
- Let's just hang out.
That's what, no, we can't, no.
- All right, yeah, no.
- No one likes the lists.
- Yeah, let's hang out.
Yeah.
You know what I wanted to show you, Patrick?
I've been wanting to show you this for a while.
There's this thing,
it's the top ten everyday things that could be eliminated by 2030.
Oh really? Do you want to just have like a hanging out conversation about it? Yeah, we just hang out and talk about it, I thought.
Really? Wow.
I don't know if I want to do that. Me and Caleb actually wrote all of it.
We just came up with it. Oh really? Actually we didn't write it, we're just gonna come up with it on the spot
like you do at a hangout now that I think about it. Oh, okay. Yeah.
Yeah, you know, to me it feels like this list would be written by someone, if there was an actual list,
I bet someone named dark_shadow would have made it.
well that's caleb's username on most sites that's true
fear me and it is the and that he does have the same lakers profile picture
i like the lakers whatever
let's look at the list of those profile a
spin awhile and awhile since i've looked at at somebody's profile on this website
if you know the first thing about it caleb is that he's always like i love
l_a_ i love the beach and i love the the wind blowing me
never know the avengers endgame favor tv show big bang theory favorite rapper
Favorite sports? Baseball. Favorite food? Ice cream. Favorite video game? Mario Kart Wii.
Favorite YouTuber? Nathaniel Bandy.
I'm neither liberal or conservative. I'm more neutral if anything.
Wow.
Wow. Okay, we have a cool kind of centrist writing this list. I like it.
I love a cool centrist.
So this is the top 10 everyday things that could be eliminated by 2030, which is only
what?
10 years.
10, 20 years.
years really hard to tell when number one TV okay I think cable TV could be
eliminated by 20 I think it's gonna be all it's gonna be all podcasts yeah it's
all it's gonna be it's gonna be we are gonna be Fox News yeah mm-hmm this is
gonna be sort of the Fox News of the podcasting world yeah we're gonna be
huge with older older my mom mm-hmm yeah older than your mom or older versions of
your mom. The 10 year older version of my mom. Okay. And then the 10 years old version of
Cameron's mom. She'll be 10 by then. Yeah, she ages at a very slow rate. She ages at about
half the rate. She's born on a leap year. She's born on the 4th of July. That would be 4, that
would be 1/4. And she has no legs. That's when I was born on. So that's not possible. The
4th of July, you have no legs. I have legs. Prove it. Walk to me right now. Walk to New
York City in this moment. Those are prosthetics. I've been fooled by that hot girl online.
with fake legs those are prosthetic legs if I if I had prosthetic legs I think I
would run around you wouldn't you wouldn't even dare I know what would do
you because then your legs wouldn't go no you're kind of good the prosthetic
legs I honestly thought about losing my legs if I got robot legs I feel like I
could walk to New York that is so true you know if I got on an airplane I feel
I feel like I could land anywhere in the world.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
But no, 'cause if the robot--
- If I got in a boat, if I got in a boat--
- No, no, like I don't lose my legs,
but I get like a pair of robot add-ons to my legs.
- Like a cybernetic implant.
- Yeah, if I got cybernetic implants in my leg,
I would walk anywhere.
- Interesting.
- You would walk anywhere.
- Can we fact check that?
- You could just fall asleep.
- Can we get a fact check on this one?
- Yeah, I could fall asleep while I was walking,
turn it on autopilot, walk to New York and like--
- You would fall in a hole.
- How long do you think that walk would be?
- I mean, it's like 100 and something miles.
- No. - It'd probably take days.
- It would take 77 hours.
- Yeah, that's not bad. - Days.
- That's not days.
What are you talking about, days?
- That is days.
That would take days.
If you ran at a marathon pace,
you could do it in a couple days.
- That's like three days.
- All right, but you're also not considering,
would have cybernetic legs we are considering that I'm no no cybernetic
cybernetic legs that go the speed of a car then that's just a car no it's legs
it's legs but it's what I'm saying as far as but so it would take three hours
then that's fine yeah okay well I have cybernetic legs that go from New York to
Boston in one second how long would that take I don't know it's the worst
conversation I've ever had with you no it absolutely definitely had worse
conversation we have not had a painful shut up
let's look at the comment I can teleport instantly with my legs from New York
I'm done with the legs thing there is no there these legs don't exist you're
making up legs and then you're exactly there's a cyborg leg you're supposed to
you can't you have to imagine something before it exists or else you can't invent it.
What if you have one fast robot leg and one of the slowest human leg of all time?
You take the average. What's the average? One minute. One minute per leg.
Hour. Okay, one minute per leg. How long does it take to go from Boston to New York City?
well two legs probably 77 77 legs well then you got to do one time 60 60
minutes in the house I think I don't do that one for me Patrick real quick one
time 60 is one yeah that is 60 it's 160 because you're adding 160 yeah yeah
hundred yeah so it'd be 160 minutes to get to New York that's that's you could
watch a hundred episodes of 60 minutes in that time. Which you're also installed on
your robot leg. Yeah you have it has a screen that pops up. Yeah as a screen on
the inside I've thought about having for a while a screen on the inside of my
thigh so that when I was like I was like jacking off I could use two hands.
Pulling a pod. What the hell dude? Wait you don't you don't you don't have a mount that you
use your phone? A mount? Yeah. In my bathroom? Yeah. Why would I have a mount?
Why don't you don't put your phone on a tripod when you jack off is what I'm
asking. Not it, no. There's not room. Okay you weird. I think you weird. You bring a
tripod? Hey mom, dad, I'm just gonna. I'm about to go jack off I need my I need to
borrow the Manfrotto. I need to borrow the tripod. The Manfrotto. I need to borrow the little
man Frodo to jack me off.
Nah dude, I fuckin...
I just hold my...
You hold your phone in your feet
and then you use
both hands behind your head to push
your head down onto your dick.
I basically put my phone between my
eyebrow and my nose like
this. Like VR goggles. And I'm just gonna squeeze
really hard. Yeah, I put it in my
Google Cardboard. Yeah.
And I just jack off that way.
Yeah, and I get really scared.
Yeah, and I play a horror game.
Well, even then, even then you have to hold the Google cardboard up to your head.
No?
Not, not if you have two rubber bands.
Oh, I didn't think about that.
Mm-hmm.
That's right.
Yeah.
Fucking no.
And so how long would that take you?
That takes me about an hour and a half.
Okay.
But what if it was robotic?
If it was robotic, I would be two minutes per leg.
Okay.
Yeah.
So slower than going to New York.
Way slower.
So jacking off takes less time.
- It's either slower or faster.
- Way faster.
(laughing)
That's right.
- You don't even know what it is.
- But it's not the same.
- No, it's not the same.
That's all we know.
- So that's the deal with cable TV.
- Yeah, so that's what's up.
That's what's gonna happen at cable TV in 2030.
- The number two thing is that we's gone,
eliminated, I'm sorry, eliminated by 2030.
Newspapers.
Sorry, buddy.
- No, we need newspapers 'cause what else
you gonna put fish and chips on in England? Where the fuck am I gonna read the funnies
now? They can keep- Yeah, where am I gonna read Garfield? They can keep newspapers in
England because they're like 20 years behind anyway. That's true. All of them still live
in castles with ghouls. They do live in huts. Where am I gonna read Non-Sequitur? And Hagar
the Horrible. Did you just google list of comic newspaper comic strips? And Ziggy. I
I gotta get my Beatle Bailey!
Where am I gonna read the Argyle Sweater?
You can't get rid of the newspaper!
Where am I gonna read Working Days?
What's that? What's the fuckin'
Where am I gonna read the...
Is it Argyle?
The Conservative Duck?
Man, how am I gonna read Zits?
Yeah, where am I gonna read Zits?
Yeah, and the...
And the one with the family.
Yeah!
Where am I gonna read that one with the family?
The one with the family.
Man, I don't remember what the duck one's called. Yeah, there's like a he's like a duck, but he's also like extremely conservative or
We're gonna read Mallard Mallory. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Where am I gonna read it? Where am I gonna read opus? Oh, oh, yeah opus
Opus looked weird. I had a open. Why was this name opus cuz that was his name. He was a penguin
Opus the penguin. Yeah, right. I had some opus opus books
Yeah, yeah
there's so many comic strips like that that are like there's so many comic
strips like that that aren't like I don't know what the were like iconic I
guess yeah yeah they're just are there yeah it's just like Garfield and Calvin
and Hobbes yeah and then the rest of the family circus yeah it's like the far
side yeah far side of course those are the four there's there's a lot of ones
that are just like made by and they all look exactly the same right yeah and they
all have like a like just a joke that makes no sense at the heart of it.
I love Heathcliff so much dude.
It's so insane. It makes literally no sense at all.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's probably the best newspaper comic.
Yeah, it'll be like a like one about like things in the fridge being alive.
Yeah.
Yeah and it'll be like the mustard, the mustard has fallen over and then the egg will be like
"Wow you really mustard that one up!"
Yeah, it'll be like-
And my Nana will call me at 2am, she'll be like "I just woke up and read the funny papers,
you have to see this mustard comic."
It'll be like a single panel comic of like two pieces of poop walking around and one
of them says wow you're a real piece of human and then the caption says poop
insults all right so here a pretty good forest I come honestly this is today's
Heathcliff this is the Heathcliff for today from yeah Patrick's new segment
yeah see today's Heathcliff it's Heathcliff standing next to a robot
there's two birds in a tree and Heathcliff is talking to the robot so
there's a robot walking down the street so there's two robots impossible and the
robot walking down the street has the word bro on his chest and the caption is
he's not a fan of robots oh my god he's on fire I was actually I was literally
looking at Heathcliff like yesterday yeah and one of the list is yesterday's
Heathcliff one of them that really okay well I wasn't I was just looking at old
Heathcliff I wasn't looking at that comic but there's one that was really getting
me that was like a picture of like they were like having a family dinner and
then Heathcliff is walking by with a helmet that says dirt and then the
captain is I don't like the look of that helmet this this yesterday's he live is
Smokey the bear and Heathcliff and Heathcliff's wearing jeans and nothing
else disrespectful and the caption is just I'm going with the shirtless jeans
look - cool yeah very cool the number three thing that it will be eliminated
by 2030 is magazines yep no no dude come on I don't online
magazine get rid of magazines you think I'm gonna fucking think no think about
- This is 2030, they're not gonna have games anymore.
- Yeah, it's true.
It's all gonna be in your head in a chip.
- Yeah, you're gonna have to eat chips in the future.
- You're gonna have to give head the chip.
- Yeah, magazines will still be around.
I mean, all of this stuff will still be around.
- I mean, Jackobin. - No, no.
- Is it Jacobin or Jackobin?
- It's Yaobin.
- Yaobin?
- Yaobin.
It's Yao Ming Magazine.
- Yeah, I think Yao Ming Magazine will still be around.
- Yeah. - You know?
- Why do they have so many of those,
like the Time Life, and then it's just like,
like Prince Magazine, and it comes out in 2020.
- What are you talking about?
- Like, it'll just be like, oh, this is--
- Prince, the guy.
- The Beatles Magazine.
- Yeah, no, they have a lot of those.
- And they have those right next to every grocery store.
- Ron Perlman Weekly.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
and then they have it's always a famous historical figure that's dead and they
make those like every month yeah and then there's one section with like six
different gun magazines that all have the same headline that say like the best
machine guns to perforate your neighbor if he tries to touch your lawnmower yeah
it's always got a picture of like it's got yeah it's in a plastic bag because
inside it has a coupon for one free bullet and they don't want people
One free round of 56, 5.6 millimeter ammo.
I use a coupon like a perfume sample and I just kind of scratch it and rub it all over
my body.
Yeah, I use a coupon too.
I've been using a coupon lately.
Yeah, I've been using a lot of coupons as of late.
Oh I don't know why this reminded me, but something that was making me chuckle at work
was like we have like like candy at the front like they're like
told what are you going to be in the yeah
but it's just so funny that like people will come up and they'll like the lake
buying like a hundred and twenty dollars of whiskey in the military ground is
really
yeah fuck it up
it's not going to happen
it's the uh... the funniest thing
like a guy who like looks homeless walking up and buying like two handles
of vodka and be like
yeah and a chocolate bar
yeah I'm just kidding a bunch of nips
while I'm at it can I get a payday
yeah let me get it
it's like the funniest, I can't imagine the thought process
yeah I need some candy too
you know I shouldn't be having all this alcohol on an empty stomach let me get a
Nutter Butter
here's like a fifty five hundred milliliter bottle of a jack apple
oh fuck I haven't had a zero bar in years
I don't remember what his Eurobar is. Is that white chocolate?
Yeah, I'll take his Eurobar.
Yeah, the guy who grabbed a Slim Jim was like, "I haven't had one of these in ten years."
Don't believe it.
First of all, I don't believe you.
I don't believe you, yeah.
I don't believe you know the date you last had a Slim Jim.
And second of all, I don't think you should have it.
Right.
We can deny service to anybody at any time.
We are a private establishment.
And sir, you are not getting Slim Jims.
I got a guy who comes in reeking of Slim Jims.
Slim Jims.
Five minutes before we close in.
You know, I haven't had one of these in ten years.
He's got Slim Jims poking out of his cargo pants.
I'll take 50.
Some Jims are good because you can ring them out for the grease like a towel.
Oh yeah.
And you can cook with it.
You can roll it up over your gas can.
I never ate a Slim Jim until this year.
I've never not believed something you've said more than that.
No, I really I didn't.
I feel like this is a trick and you're saying like I've never eaten one Slim Jim until this
year.
I believe that Patrick has never eaten a Slim Jim but he ate as a child every day he ate
some Chinese snack called like Let's Meat.
Yeah.
It was like exactly a Slim Jim but with pigeon mixed into it.
It's like made up.
Squab I had a squab meat stick. What's wrong with that? Yeah, they just like scrape off the suicide nets at a Foxconn factory
Oh my god
And that's all the animals and the and shit that get caught in it and the leaves and the guys
And then they just put it through like the the lo mein mold where they make all the noodles
And it legally has to be sold as incense
Yeah, it's like bath salts.
I did eat in high school.
I went to Chinatown once.
It's called Essence of Man.
I ate a lot of shrimp crackers one day.
See, that's the basis I was going off of when I said that about you eating a strange Chinese
star food for a high schooler to like.
They're good.
They smell like penis though.
They smell like unwashed penis.
You know what that smells like?
Why?
And you know what the weasel what the why?
The why?
Okay.
I don't wash my penis for religious reasons.
Yeah.
You don't wash it, dude.
It's like sourdough.
Yeah, it's like a cast iron skillet.
You're not supposed to wash it.
Men be treating their beds like a cast iron skillet.
Has anybody done that yet?
Oh my God.
Yeah, that's right.
I actually do have to wash my cast iron skillet this week
because the mice have been living in it.
Oh yeah, you talked about that before.
You gotta put soap in it.
Fucked up.
Uh, yeah, there was mice in it.
There's the only way, only way you can clean a casserole.
No, you don't understand, I said, "Baby, I still can't, like, we can't wash it."
No, it's seasoning.
I know there's rat shit in it.
It's seasoning.
Anything that goes in is legally seasoning.
Legally.
Yeah.
And that's southern law.
And that's southern poverty law, sir.
I was gonna say that.
I was gonna say that, but I don't know if you do.
Number four TV remotes that's right yeah that guy's but from the greatest freak
out ever wait here's a really good comment this is it has a picture of as a
picture of the the I list item as a picture of a TV remote and then the
comment says hey that looks like my TV remote and then a smiley face and then
Josh tition 24 but there's a space there's a space there's a space after
Josh Tishen and before 24 so it looks like is his age. Josh Tishen 24. This is good, this
will be a good one because then you won't lose your remote in the couch but what if
you're using what if it's like you lose your brain in the couch now because you
use it to control the TV. That can already happen you can use your screams
to control the TV. I lost my brain in the couch. This is a TV that runs
completely on screen. This is a TV that is completely fear powered. Yeah. Yeah, it'll
go to whatever channel you're most afraid of. If you want, yeah. It sucks because it
keeps opening up shutters. Dad, why does the channel keep changing to BET when you sit
it down. I got the respect power TV. I don't really want to watch Dateline. I can't change
a channel. No, I really can't. Life would be different without TV remotes. Like if you
You had to use your phone to change the channel or volume from trains 45, which you can already
if you have a Roku you can already do that.
Yeah, if you had a Roku you could already do that trains 45 get with the program.
Yeah, trains you stupid motherfucker.
Yeah, I do.
Yeah, Patrick loves Roku.
What's up with you and Roku lately?
It changed my life.
What changed your life about Roku?
I'm gonna report this in my life forever.
Is it the Pandora integration?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Is it you can listen to Tenacious D radio?
I'm reporting the picture of it.
I'm clicking report image on the picture of the TV remote and I'm reporting it saying
it is copyright protected.
Let's see if we can get that taken down.
It looks too much like Josh Tishen's TV remote.
It's copy written by Josh Tishen.
Oh no, it says you have to file a DMCA.
Alright, let's do it.
Alright, let's file one dude.
Please follow the instructions on our copyright policy page for submitting a takedown notice.
The DMCA is like one of the worst fucking things of all time.
Of all time?
Of all time.
Yeah.
What is the DMCA to you?
The DMCA ruined YouTube poop in 2010.
That is true.
It really did.
Yeah.
It took down one of the greatest art forms.
It took down Crobo Productions I think at one point.
It took down Vaser Vase.
Yeah, Vaser Vase could never recover.
He never got his fan base back.
- Where'd it go?
- I don't know.
- I don't see.
- Acer.
- All those guys, they're gone.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, and then people would file
false DMCA reports against each other
and then get their channels taken down.
- That is pretty funny.
That's a funny move.
If someone wants to DMCA our podcast,
that'd be kind of funny.
- Don't, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- Don't do that.
- That'd be a little funny.
- No, no, no, no.
- Don't do that.
- I've already gotten reported for impersonating myself.
They'll do it.
- No.
that was channel fans that did that that was because I told you under a Felix
treat matters one it said hey chopper fans can we all report this guy thank
you and it worked so fucking funny sheep change his name on Twitter because he
was impersonating someone Patrick yeah sick number six which is funny because
my profile picture is an impersonator. That is true.
Number 5 is movie theaters. Yeah, I could do without them.
I don't like them man. We've talked about this so much.
We've talked about this and this is one of our things.
Nah, I don't need them. Get rid of them. Fuck them.
Here's a comment. Reading, listening to music, going to the cinema is always a pleasure
and it is necessary to establish physical contact to get real pleasure, not just
just in the virtual. Physical pleasure at the movies? Excuse me sir, I'm going to the
movie theater for physical pleasure. Yeah, which row in the theater
would be the best for physical pleasure? Yeah, I just I'm trying to get as much
physical pleasure while I'm here as possible. Yeah, this is Surf's Up, right?
I'm in the right movie theater. Can I run around the theater for physical
Pleasure.
Yeah.
Can I crawl into the popcorn machine?
Can I, let me get in there physically.
Let me get in there.
I bet it's warm and I bet it's bubbly.
Did you guys know kids in middle school
would just go to the movie theater and just get blown?
Yeah.
No.
What is that about?
Why are the movies theater?
Because it's dark and there's no parents.
But aren't they on high alert for that shit?
Isn't that like the number one thing
they're trying to stop?
If you walk up to a 14 year old kid getting blown, you're the pedophile.
That's true.
Think about that.
It's a trap.
So why not do it in a park and just clear the whole park out?
Yeah.
Right?
That's the problem.
Because a bird could land on you.
Right.
True.
A bird can't be...
A hawk could see your wiener and think it's a worm and go at you.
And actually hawks are younger than you, so then you're the pedophile.
Yeah, exactly.
Because a hawk is only maybe two or three years old.
there's a kid that went to my high school who got who saw the Smurfs in its last week and
got a got a tug and everyone called him Papa Smurf.
From a Smurf.
They called him Papa Smurf.
Yeah.
Damn.
Yeah, everyone just called him Papa Smurf.
Who was his beautiful Smurfette?
I don't remember.
I'm not gonna say the kid's name.
It was Patrick.
Patrick was the Smurfette.
Yeah.
No, if you think I would be the person to ever do that.
You'd be Smurfete.
think I'd be cool enough in high school to get my shit tugged at the Smurfs no you
were talking the shit you were the tugger no yeah you were saying I mean I
was tugging but I was in the bathroom and the Smurfs was on at the movie theater
yeah yeah that's cool just listening to the very muffled faraway sound yeah I
have I have a gargoyle voice and busting all over the stall wall I was listening
to the George Lopez Smurf and I shot my shit over the wall of the stall
into the next stall like a perfect arc like a world of tanks game
head of the theater manager sitting in the next stall
number six passwords
what how does this work?
how is this one going to work?
oh because you're going to use your brain
everything's just going to turn into your just using your brain that's true yeah
yeah we're not gonna need food anymore will just think
moses and think and be sandy nurt nate nationalist nationalist shirt and
nurtured nurtured by our school being nourished by thought by a thoughts of a
big juicy steak
no
big state
uh... yeah i i i i have a personal for me i don't think that's what they're
going anywhere
i'll get in this one of the tony and i don't want to write about this food jobs
that's fucking right
fast food jobs we're getting rid of these scumbags yeah get get a real job guys
yeah i mean at the very least have the dignity to stand out on the street and
hold out a cup don't fucking exactly what do you think you think it's somehow you
think it's it's dignified you think it's cool to work you think you think you're
having fun and people like you know everybody hate you're the only thing
standing between them and getting a lot of jumping over the counter and jumping
and getting a lot of extra fries that's all right you're the most hated
pieces of shit who have to be homeless and panhandle.
While they hold their cup, I'm gonna go up to them and say,
hey, don't use that for water.
Or don't, or, I mean, water, soda.
- Writing, writing, don't use that for water on a $20 bill.
- Hey, don't soda your water.
Don't put water in your soda cup.
- Yeah, I hope you don't plan on refilling that.
- Yeah, hey, no free refills.
I'll give them one penny.
- Yeah, pouring out all their coins on the ground
and saying no, and don't refill it.
- No refills, pussy.
yeah yeah and also yeah and also uh your manager is my stepdad yeah and then i
walk into my job at at hell as the devil
that's a comment damn dude this new this new stephen king short story goes crazy
yeah just the devil walking by he was the devil
and then he walked into his job that's uh that's surely that literally is a
Shirley Jackson story actually that is yeah there's a one about whatever it
doesn't matter yeah it's called the lottery real ones know what I'm talking
about no it's not it's called uh it's a lot or something it's called mr.
lottery surely sir a lot of evil mr. jack money I'll figure this out um I
want to see like an air bud movie with the devil instead of a dog yeah there's
no rule that says that the devil can't play basketball can't play basketball
yeah he's playing against the Catholic school so there is a rule that's the
first that's the that's the first part that's the first rule any athlete go to
a public school yes the devil can't play basketball here yeah or maybe they maybe
he's playing for public school and then they have to play a Catholic school oh
geez they got Jesus on their team oh my god there's a comment from to storm here
that says "No way am I letting a robot cook my food."
Then again, I don't eat fast food a lot.
I actually like actual restaurants a lot more.
- So what's a fast food, what's McDonald's gonna be like?
- McDonald's is a gourmet restaurant.
They got the J Balvin video.
- That's how you eliminate fast food jobs
is you change it from being fast food.
- True.
- And then they're just normal food jobs.
- You're right, gourmet.
- You put the word gourmet next to McDonald's.
- Gourmet McDonald's. - That's true, yeah.
And then that's it.
- Have you seen the J Balvin meal?
Have you seen the J Balvin meal?
Why did they, he didn't even do anything special.
- J Balvin meal.
- It's just fries with ketchup,
a Big Mac, no pickles, and an Oreo McFlurry.
- Who is J Balvin?
- He's like a, he's the Prince of Reggaeton.
- That's Bad Bunny.
me hold on let me look up I saw a McDonald's say the prince of reggaeton
well it does seem like he I mean he looks like a reggaeton guy let me look this up
yeah he kind of looks like whatever Post Malone is going for yeah what Post Malone
wishes he could be that's right wait so it's it's really just a Big Mac with
pickles Big Mac no pickles there's literally pickles in the promo photo
really yeah stupid-ass fucking dumb-ass bitch you get it you get a temporary you
get a temporary tattoo of the receipt with every order really that's awesome
yeah that's sick and you can I was looking at McDonald's Twitter yesterday
yeah your daily McDonald's Twitter like I do every morning yeah of course yeah
it's like the times for you up late doom scrolling on McDonald's timeline
Every day he wakes up and he prints out like a tri-fold version of the McDonald's Twitter
and just reads it like a horoscope.
Can you believe this?
Jesus Christ.
God damn it.
Yeah, and the funny pages is all the, is just all of the McDonald's tweets from other languages.
Yeah, he's reading McDonald's Malaysia just chuckling to himself.
Hey son, come here, look at this.
It's a pretty good one.
I'm gonna clip this one and put it on the fridge.
Yeah, look, it's called L Big Mac.
(laughing)
Number eight, taxis.
Yeah, taxis are already kinda gone, I feel like.
- Yeah, it's all Ubers now.
- It's all, yeah, keep going, it's all Ubers now.
- Yeah, it's all Ubers and Lyfts.
- Yeah, and-- - Yeah, yeah.
- And the train. - I'm gonna put my tube
in your shit.
(laughing)
- That's right.
I don't know, I feel like--
- Kids nowadays will ride everywhere in an Uber,
but when they're having sex, they won't put on a Ruber.
Oh god damn Cameron.
Yeah.
McDonald's pinned tweet is "Grimace lives rent free in my head."
That's awesome.
That's so great.
Grimace lives rent free in my head.
Kids these days will all use their Lyft but at their taxi job they won't show up for a
shift.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Because the kids are the taxi drivers now.
Yeah that's true.
That's how you save the taxi industry.
You make a kid every taxi driver.
Exactly.
If kids were in charge of the taxis in the world...
If kids were in charge...
The Bruce Springsteen song.
If kids were in charge of the taxis, they could change the world.
Taxis will change the world.
I think that a good move was when they started putting TVs in the back of the taxis and play
like HGN.
that was a really good move because now I just want gas now you know what you know
what mr. taxi man I'm not worried about being late to this meeting just keep
driving I want to watch the rest of this Martha Stewart show do they have you
yeah kids nowadays kids nowadays will all be watching Robert De Niro and taxi
driver but they don't have them they don't even take a moment to change their
crappy diaper. Wow. Okay. I thought you were gonna go with like they don't
understand what the movie is because they don't get they don't understand what a
taxi is. Caleb have you gone in a real New York cab yet? Every single day.
I just ride it around. Yeah. Just keep driving. One of these times I'm gonna get Robert De Niro.
yeah I'm gonna play this knockoff of bejeweled with horses on this on the
Amazon fire tablet hey I know you're driving me around but if you could send
me a candy crush life right now that'd be yeah that'd be great I'll tip you I'll
tip me it's just me I'm sitting in the back just just basically punching the
headrest of the taxi driver so hard on the little iPad that he has there yeah
trying to play a sudoku like it's a crossword just putting in words
none of these are correct your games broken restart the car yeah that's
mostly what I try to do and then he tells me that his it tells me yeah that
his cousin is the president. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So we're not gonna do that one this time.
Number nine! DVDs. Oh, I hope that never goes away. I know. That's pretty dead-tight. I love
watching a DVD with you guys. It depresses me, dude. I love DVDs. I have so many DVDs.
I love watching DVDs with you guys. What am I gonna put on my finger and pretend that
pretend that I'm married to the TV. A blu-ray. Oh my god. Yeah they'll go down the
same way like VHS tapes did 20 years ago from Cubs fan 16. I think I mean I
haven't bought a DVD in so long. I just buy so many DVDs. I like DVDs.
yeah I think there I think I think it'll be fun in 20 years when DVDs are the
same have the same kind of like kitsch nostalgia that that VHS does now like
when people are putting like just fucked up like it's like like fucked up like
JPEG artifacts onto their their their fan cams like just like yeah whenever
there's black in a in a scene it just it just come it's just like giant squares
of black that just like like spread out mmm doing that greenish little doing
that instead of like video scan lines and shit yeah yeah be the best I just want I
think the DVDs are great for the the games that some of them have on them
that's true yeah yeah they all have fun some fun points and like Shrek American
Idol Shrek American Idol is really good yeah Simon Cowell sings when you pick
the wrong guy the Santa Claus one with with Jack Frost has a great game do you
guys remember being little and like watching a movie like watching a movie
on a DVD and then it ends and but you like want to stay up later so you're
like can we watch a special feature and it's just like really boring but you
watch it up 20 minutes longer you watch I remember doing that with the
Incredibles and it's just like so it was just like so here's how we animated the
hair of the different characters oh the Incredibles had a good one cuz they up
until 920 tonight the Incredibles had a Incredibles beautiful waist to pussy ass
ratio yeah Incredibles had like a list of all the other heroes that were in the
Incredibles oh yeah on the DVD and it's like they never fucking showed these
people in the movie no there's so much work that goes into that shit there's a
guy there's a character there's a one of the superheroes they mentioned his name
gazer beam which is so funny. Yeah. Is there trying to like gaze? His powers are looking at women?
No that's his like kryptonite. Yeah. He's like a skeleton they find us the
skeleton of gazer beam. Yeah yeah they take I remember that I take off his goggles
and they're like these belong to gazer beam. Yeah it's just so funny nobody thought that name over at all.
right yeah yeah number 10 DVDs number 10 number 10 key D keys keys keys yeah
let's go ahead and get rid of keys I'm talking car keys and house keys I mean
already we have key cards and pretty soon I bet you can use your phone or
there will be facial recognition technology making keys worthless from
dark shadow. Did you guys see that video of that guy who's like some like fucking
Bay Area like tech guy who's makes his wife get a chip in her hand so that she
doesn't have a key to open the door? That is the funniest shit I've ever seen.
So funny yeah. He makes his wife get a chip in her fucking hand? Yeah so so I know you're
always losing your keys so for your birthday I'm having a chip surgically
implanted into your thumb so you can get into the to the house and she's like
"Awesome! Yeah!" and then she goes to the doctor and she's like "Yeah I don't
really I don't really want to do this" and then they fucking just shoot a chip in her hand
with a big like comical needle. Jesus Christ. They go back and it like
doesn't work at first and she's like just hitting her door with her hand and
then it finally opens and then like the music plays like it's all resolved and it's a
happy and the husband's like thank you imagine now I always know where my wife
is the divorce thing is she can get in to kill him at any time I'm changing the
hands to the house and your honor my husband made me put a chip in my thumb
yeah I mean that's cut yeah I want custody of the kids in the divorce cuz
he paid for the chip yeah they can't get the chip out at any time if they fucking
move what do you know I know you don't want to do an IUD because you think it'll
mess up your hormones so actually we're gonna put a chip in your vagina that just
opens up the front of it shoots that detects and shoots sperm what it is
shoots my penis we're gonna get saran wrap installed over your hole
yeah number 11 checks slash cash I don't care it's a mix I know they don't get
rid of that never did they're never getting rid of cash dude I'm never gonna
fucking throw my my phone at a woman on stage number 12 is school uniform but
just fine to say that's fine yeah just throw my Samsung Galaxy at some woman's
face yeah just put in however much you want under $10 though under $10 or I
I will kill you. Yeah. Shining a QR code laser into her eye. Yeah, do you think that's gonna
happen? No. No, 'cause they'll abolish sex before they get rid of cash. That's true. Number
12 is school uniforms, which is funny 'cause it's like pretty much doesn't exist now. Yeah.
Like why, yeah. Lame pick. Except in my aunt's closet. Number 15 is I think one of my favorites
on this number 15 is music albums and there's a comment that says as much as I
love Spotify I still enjoy collecting music albums yeah I love music albums I
love music albums I love collecting music albums hey I like Spotify but I
also like collecting music albums one day I'll just be sheet they don't have
any others on Spotify is something about Spotify that's true they have zero
albums on Spotify they're actually taking all the albums off this week
Spotify and it's just gonna be last podcast on the left.
Yeah just them fucking talking about Hitler for the 50th time or whatever.
It's gonna be last podcast on the left and Michelle Obama podcast are gonna be the only
things on Spotify.
Joe Dogan.
We're making a move.
We're moving to whatever the newest version of.
We're gonna have Spotify buy us out.
How much, if we came to them and we were like you guys can buy us out, how much do you think
they would offer us?
Like $500?
Yeah.
- I feel like if we could make,
if we need 500 bucks super fast, we could do that.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Yeah, it might be a good move, dude.
- Wouldn't be bad, I'm sure.
I'm sure we'd make a lot more.
- Think about what we could do with $500.
- Like weird, decentralized, Patreon-esque startups
keep messaging us and being like,
"Do you guys wanna be one of our flagship things?"
And it's like, "No."
- We are a crowdfunding program a lot like Patreon,
we're but we're not chain focused and racist yeah if you'd like to join what
was that it was like we got an email once that was like I love to smoke a
bowl and listen to your podcast yeah and then that and then that website that
email was from was fake like it's yeah it said that Joe Rogan was like featured
on it but it's not it's just like a scam that's enticing podcasters into a scam
by saying you love to smoke a bowl while you listen to the episodes. I love to smoke in a bowl. Fuck yeah dude.
Yeah we should maybe just start our own patreon thing. We should start a patreon for the podcast.
That's a great idea. We should just have people Venmo us and we send them the episode for that
week. Yeah and Patrick and Deering used to do all of the work. Yeah it's all manual. Finally Pat's gonna start pulling his weight.
What do you mean? Look my weight's too big to pull. Oh you said it so I didn't have to dude.
Thank you very, very much.
Thank you, God.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much.
All right, I gotta go pee pee.
Yeah, me too.
I gotta go pee pee.
Bye, everybody.
Three pee pee.
Three pee pees?
Maybe we'll just keep the episode.
Follow us on the Patreon.
Let's bring this to the bathroom.
Subscribe to the Patreon.
Teespring, I fixed all the fucking awesome Caleb hoodies.
You, it was you who messed them up?
It was you that messed them up?
I don't know, I think the one--
You rolled away from the microphone because you were embarrassed.
No, because I had it hanging up and I was looking at it.
The first problem with the one that I got was the...
Alright, thanks for listening everybody.
Bye.