You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
- Podcasts for the hopeless.
(upbeat music)
- You're a crap monster.
(explosion)
- Okay.
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank God you made it, dude.
Cameron's about to destroy you.
- Cameron's about to kill me.
- Yeah, he's about to kill you.
- Cameron is fucking annoying, dude.
Every single episode.
- There's fire in his eyes.
- It's not funny anymore.
- Fire in his eyes.
It still makes me laugh
'cause I don't have to do any work on it.
- There's not a good energy to start the episode with.
to try and start it by pissing me off. It fucking makes me mad. It's not gonna be fun for me
to do it. Yeah, you're gonna- you're at the- you should wait till the end of the episode
so I don't have to talk to you anymore when I'm mad at you. This style play is not fun
for me. That Travis McElroy video was so fucking funny dude. It's- did you see the one- did
you see the one where he's like- he's doing that grating like baby voice, like that horrible
fucking yeah yeah yeah it's actually not fun for me to play in in DK mode with the
big heads on it's just not fun for me to play this style god damn shut up it was
so I mean those are people I learned I was reading about it those are people
he's like barely ever played with before yeah what's so funny about that too is
how clear you can just see like how alien his brain is because in his mind he's
like the people that are watching my stream right now are watching so that
they can see among us gameplay they want to see among us gameplay they don't want
to hear anybody talk about it yeah he imagine like like one day when they when
he eventually kills himself and then they cut open his head and his and his
brain is just like pickled in hair dye and they're like oh that makes perfect
sense this is why this guy was so fucked up. Pickled in hair dye? Yeah. God, dude, that's such a fucking crappy image.
The mascara like infected his optic nerve. It spread all the way to his brain.
Yeah it's like a venom symbiote. Who have you guys been up to other than watching
his streams? That boy looked like a clone. Yeah what if we start like a
a Paul is Dead type conspiracy about Travis McElroy that he was replaced with
the clone yeah that boy look like a clone that's all I'll say on the matter
what have I been up to I'm back in I'm back in the saddle dude yeah Carolina
I'm on my cowboy shit I mean I be candy fucking what's that fucking cracklins
I'm Caleb from the south. You sound like Bill Cosby.
Oh Rudy! Rudy you better get back in this house right now Rudy!
Yeah you do, you know a guy named Rudy.
Yeah we were just talking about him.
My old boss, shout out to Rudy.
Yeah shout out Rudy.
I'm sorry I forgot you Rudy. He was such a cool guy.
No dude I've just been fucking sleeping on a bed that I vomited on.
Oh yeah, tell us about that.
cut that. Yeah I just like I drove down it's like a 10-hour drive I drove the
whole way and I just stay awake I had like three bangs so I got here and I
just could not sleep at all so I was like okay I'll just start like drinking
everything in the house so I had like a bunch of vodka like like Aldi wine and
ying-ling and then I was like drunk but not tired still because I had 900
milligrams of caffeine so I called Noah and I was like Noah bring your dab rig
over to my house and come... That is the fucking worst idea! Why would that help at all?
You're like the stupidest guy I've ever met in my life.
I mean, truly, I felt like a complete crackhead. I was like... He parked in front of a basketball
hoop and we just hit his evil piss rig and then immediately I just went inside and I
just started vomiting on my bed and I just couldn't even... I couldn't even like wake
up to clean it up I just I just passed out you slept on the puke I'm not on the
next to the puke did you roll in it in your sleep you definitely did you did
yeah absolutely like a little piggy it's a big bad dude look at this thing Caleb
was doing so badly when he joined the zoom guy he also didn't tell he joined
the zoom call and told us then that he couldn't record it and you know
record I didn't say that at all you said we could do one without you fucking
dumbass you joined and you were like being sweet yeah you were so badly on
the last episode when I was telling when we were talking about it I told Patrick
like yeah when he joined he had a giant tear rolling down his face and Patrick
just believed me wholeheartedly I did not have a bad you were doing I've never
seen I mean no I've seen Caleb hungover but I've never seen Caleb that hungover
where he was just like you you looked like like there were like red spots on
your face from puking I looked fine like it looked like no it looked like you
You popped blood vessels in your face.
- I looked good.
I spent that whole day on the couch.
I kept like--
- You were on the call,
you were in the fucking Zoom call just like,
(groaning)
- I made plans with a friend that day,
and I was like, yeah, we'll do something later tonight
when I feel a little better.
And then I just kept pushing it back by 30 minutes
and being like, I can't get off of the couch right now.
It was not a good day.
I'm all right now, you know?
I'm enjoying the fresh North Carolina air.
- I have not felt like that in so long,
it feels so good. Don't have to wear a mask here, that's nice. You don't. And go around just
fucking licking shit and sucking dick. Yeah? Where? Where you suck a dick
in North Carolina? You're not sucking dick down there, I don't believe you. You know, the park.
Oh, okay. The park that was recently renamed, it used to be Hugh McCrae Park, turns out.
- Human Crate Park. - No, not Human Crate Park.
- It's the Wayfair Park. - No.
(laughing)
It was not Human Crate Park, but they renamed it, dude.
My hometown is so fucking awesome now.
That guy used to be a slave owner.
- Oh, okay. - So they said,
"You know what?
"You don't get no park.
"You don't get to own a slave and a park.
"That's why it's Human Crate."
- That's why it's too much shit.
- Yeah. - No.
- They were like, "No, we can't have this park
"named after a slave owner."
and they changed the name of the park to Slave Park
to honor the past.
- This was for the slaves.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- We should be putting statues of the slaves up.
- What do you mean? - Yeah, wait, yeah.
- Yeah, put statues of the slaves up.
Be kinda cool.
- They should just--
- Modeled after me.
Every one of 'em has my face.
- In a way, I am kind of a mental slave.
- Yeah, I used to be a slave to the school system, low key,
which is like kind of a worse kind of slavery.
That's, you wanna talk about modern slavery,
I'm pretty sure that's what people mean
when they talk about that.
Probably public school and public universities and colleges.
Yep.
You know, and the systems they're in.
You know?
And also lunchtime will only be in 25 minutes.
You used to be 30.
If you know me, you know I hate the system.
You love the system.
I hate the system.
You're like maybe one of the--
I hate the system, I flip off the system.
You subscribe to the system.
You subsidize the system, $5.99 a month.
I don't do that with the system.
I hate this. The only system I like is gaming system.
That's not true. You hate gaming system.
I love gaming system.
And you love the normal system.
I love gaming system. I hate patriarchal system.
You love the system. You love the man.
I hate the man. Fuck the man.
You love the man. You want to give the man a kiss.
Hey, the man. Check this out.
Yeah, he's holding up a heart with his fingers.
He's holding up a kiss from his mouth.
He's holding up an edible arrangement.
And he's saying, here you go, the man.
No.
Hey, the man, will you go on a date with me?
Can we find out who the frickin' man is so I can throw some shit at him?
You wanna throw him a party?
I don't wanna throw a party for the man.
You wanna go to a man party?
No.
Yeah, you do.
If I did, there'd be nothing wrong with that.
You wanna go to a-
You wanna get outside the man system?
Nope.
You wanna enter the man system as a test subject?
Maybe I do.
Yeah, you do.
And, buddy, that's fine.
I'll try to big dog me. Don't do that dude. No, not happening.
Yeah. But what have you guys been up to? Have you
guys poisoned yourself recently? No, I have not poisoned myself for almost 90
days now. Yeah? Except for like gyros and cold cubanos
that you get. Yeah.
- And Jool and--
- Yeah, Jool, I mean--
- I put no toxins in my body whatsoever.
I'm pure. - I don't eat or drink anything.
- I've been--
- Just information for me, thanks.
- Just infrared light for me, sorry.
- Just solar energy, please.
- Yeah, just pure radiation, that's all I need to get by.
- I'm trying to get you pure.
- Dude, this outdoor dining at the restaurants
has been great 'cause I can finally photosynthesize
instead of ordering.
(laughing)
- True, yeah.
- The waiter comes over and I just raise my eyebrow at him
and I say, "I don't think I'll be needing you today,
"thank you very much."
But do you have like a big reflective piece of metal? Yeah, I stripped down naked and I'm green
Yeah, can I buy it? No, thanks. Do you guys have any solar panels back there?
Is there a guy hat with a solar panel on it that I can wear?
I can plug it on my butt and I can continue to live and so you're still eating and drinking
That's really cute. You haven't you haven't converted your shit to electric instantly dies when it rains one day
Yeah
That'll be the next thing. They just find you shriveled up on the sidewalk. You couldn't get inside
Yeah, just like from the clowns just arms hanging down just body hunched over in the middle of the streets like ah shit
Yeah, his battery got wet
It's just a 9-volt. It's like it's like a 9-volt battery. That's just got a slot on your neck
We're headed that way dude. Mm-hmm. We're headed that way and there will be and we will be I will be one of the detectives
who investigates deaths like that yeah yeah cuz I'll probably be coming soon the
deaths like where they were saying is being a detective not yet but maybe soon
maybe like once once what's one of you what's it you go to the fucking costume
store again and open yeah and you you in a fucking I don't have a costume store
you go to a costume store every other episode no I go to the third store and
sometimes it's a post Halloween sale and they have costumes and I mean when was
there no there wasn't a post Halloween sale recently yeah how long did you have
that chef costume in reserve.
- No way.
- Actually a long time.
- You were waiting to do that for eight months.
- When I wore the chef's costume,
I found it in my closet and forgot that I bought it
like last year.
And I was like, this is gonna be sick.
And guess what, it was.
- Yeah, I mean, hey, it was.
It's true.
- So, fuck you, man.
I think you guys need to start wearing costumes.
- I was thinking about it.
I was thinking about getting like a Sonic the Hedgehog costume.
I mean I saw one in a window.
If you think about it, clothes in a way are costumes.
Actually I'm a robber right now.
You are dressed exactly like a robber.
Yeah, a French robber.
Yep.
Yeah.
I need to, you know what, if I put like a red bandana around my neck, maybe I could have
done that.
But.
Is it lunch in France to just eat like a piece of bread?
It's lunch, yeah, and a cigarette.
What the fuck is a cigarette?
- Eat a cigarette and a piece of bread.
- That is not keto.
Oh, I think that smoking that weed
also put me into ketosis.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, I think I've been in ketosis.
I think I've been in ketosis for like four days.
I'm feeling really, really strange.
My pee is like a new color.
It's like closer to white than it's ever been,
which I think is a symptom of ketosis.
I can't, I wasn't able,
I couldn't sit through a movie for a while.
I think I have ketosis. - I've been coughing.
I have no sense of taste.
- Dude, did you see the guy who,
the Texas Roadhouse guy got COVID
and then it gave him tinnitus
and he was like, "Fuck that," killed himself.
- That's so nuts, dude. - What?
- That's sick. - That's so cool.
- Yeah, just being like,
I got these tinnitus demons in my brain.
- Damn, tinnitus. - After COVID-19.
- Though I probably would kill myself
if I had really bad tinnitus too.
- It just depends on how bad it was.
- I have like slight tinnitus. - Yeah, if I had tinnitus
and it really is like not good.
- If I had tinnitus that sounded like Lil Wayne,
and that's like the perfect life I could imagine.
You know?
- Yeah.
- Am I just walking around like trying to like--
- Yeah, what dude, tonight is--
- If I was trying to listen in class
and I just hear, "A-me-lee, a-me-lee, a-me-lee."
- That'd be kinda awesome.
- It'd be sick to have tinnitus if you're a fan
of like sun or like drone music, you know?
- Yeah, exactly, yeah.
- 'Cause then you just like, you just walk around
and you hop into the beat.
- Yeah, bless me. - You know what I mean?
- I'm not gonna bless you, you just please.
- You bless yourself for a burp?
- Bless you, first off, you don't bless people for a burp.
That is not worthy of a blessing.
It's a disgust.
Do you say bless you when someone farts?
- No.
- Only yourself?
- I think I might actually say bless you when people fart.
I think I started doing that as a joke
and then it just became a thing that I do.
- A burp is a fart, so you're basically still doing it.
- I feel like a burp is more your soul
leaving your body than a sneeze.
You know what I mean?
- What?
you're like you know how like what is your soul leaving your body like you never
heard that yeah bless you comes from you you're shooting out your soul and then
you say bless you and the soul goes fuck you're right and he goes back into your
body cuz I get drats he caught me yeah yeah that's where it comes from right
yeah it was invented by the Pope yeah but I feel I feel like a burp is better
than a sneeze for that because a burp at least sounds demonic sometimes well
there's it's not a demon it's a soul yeah your body it would feel it would sound
demonic why I don't think that's true I think it would sound like a soul I think
it would sound exactly like a sneeze actually I just did a scientific
breakdown I think the real soul leaving your body is when you die and you shit
your pants yeah that's like honestly all that closest you get to sure like a soul
actually leaving your body you know it would be I do wish that maybe you burped
out like a blue cloud when you died or something because then I would yeah then
then you could sell to pay for the funeral you could sell tickets to your
death it can already do that why not have a blue cloud to do that but I don't
gonna watch like somebody just die on a bed if somebody was burping anything
about a bed I mean just make it up cool yeah I guess you're right I mean people
don't go to the circus just to see the gut people stand around you know you do
something you have to pay to see somebody be executed no I don't think you
do. No. You should. You should. You are giving that away. What the fuck. You need to, one
thing I learned from comedy is you never give away a product for free. Okay. Especially
one as good as a human death. Listen, and if the kind of people who are gonna be sitting
in on a death. It depends on who's being executed. If they, you know, you can tell if they have
no money they're gonna be much less well adjusted than someone who can afford it right? Yeah.
- Yeah, well a very rich person will be.
- Who's gonna be getting executed is almost always
a mentally disabled person, so that makes it
kinda hard to sell the tickets, I guess.
But you could, here's the thing, it's a $100 cover
with a two drink minimum to see somebody die.
- And there's a lotto spot.
(laughing)
- To die by, that's lethal injection, all right?
Electric chair, that's gonna be $500.
Yeah. If you want to see somebody get electrocuted to death.
And that's a bringer. Firing squad?
Yeah, firing squad.
Don't even fucking think about not paying for that shit.
Yeah, firing squad because somebody got accused of blowing a kiss at a woman in 1940 and now
they're finally getting around to shooting him a million times. Firing squad's gonna be
a VIP experience.
It's crazy that they blindfold all the firing squad guys.
Why is that crazy? I guess it makes it hard to see, huh?
Yeah.
Do you, if you don't--
No, they don't blindfold them. They just put like blanks in some of the guns, right?
I mean, I don't, I've never done it.
Oh. Cameron, do you know?
What? I don't think they blindfold, I think they blind--
Yeah, I know they don't blind--
--the guy who's dying.
Yeah, I know they don't blindfold the, that's the joke I was making.
Okay, well you, all right.
That was a banger.
It was.
Yep.
I've been on fire. I've been up with more questions that were kind of like serious questions to
hide that it was a joke maybe. I don't know. And to ask about like you know blanks and stuff.
No because then I remembered I remembered that I don't remember I think it's a White
Is Good sketch. Do you guys know whether they use like Nerf guns or real guns? You know
what they do is they give they give everybody a gun except one guy gets a banana and he has
to aim it and he thinks just so that he thinks that maybe he killed him mm-hmm
that's how it works so everybody has a different fruit and one guy has a gun so
that nobody knows who killed him mm-hmm yeah yeah I'd hate to be the guy that
gets like the durian yeah that thing yeah that would hurt to hold yeah I want
to shoot a point that guy fucking kid pull the trigger brother cuz I don't
want to smell this fucking fart thing oh yeah I hope I don't have to hold the
poop fruit. Fuck. Yeah. It is funny that people do eat that and they love it too. I don't,
I would try it. I gotta find a place that has a durian around here. Indonesia. Oh okay I'll
just go to Indonesia. I think that's probably the easiest way to get there. Yeah, okay.
That sounds like a fun trip. Any fruit that is the size of a baby is not a good fruit.
I do not like watermelon. Is a durian the size, I don't like watermelon either. How
- Watermelon either. - Durians are huge.
- Watermelon's like, okay, it definitely,
artificial watermelon's better than normal watermelon.
- This is why a watermelon is not very good
and a cutie is the greatest fruit in the world
'cause the smaller a fruit is,
the more powerful the flavor.
- What is it that you said?
- Durian. - Durian.
- No, the other fruit that you just said,
the small one. - Watermelon.
- A cutie. - What's that?
- You've never had a cutie?
- No, what is that?
- It's a tangerine or a clementine.
- Yeah, it's a clementine, but it's like a fake clementine
where there's no seeds in it.
It's basically just candy.
What the hell?
Oh yeah, that's one of the best.
I've seen these before.
I didn't know this was like its own thing.
Yeah, it's an artificially made fruit where they-
It's a what?
They bred out all the seeds and made it taste like a warhead.
And it's the best fruit in the world.
Yeah, I didn't know they were-
What do you mean artificially made?
You're right, it was made-
The indigenous people used to make cuties.
They used to grow cuties.
No, no, I-
every single fucking fruit you buy is is like it's like that yeah you mean like
GM okay sorry I I didn't know what the fuck you meant I just really talking
about artificial we were talking about artificial watermelon I thought it was
like a robot I don't know to describe it I'm sorry man I you're right yeah that's
my bad it's a it's not like it's not like a
cardboard cut out of a fruit that's what I thought you were fucking saying of a
durian looks like yeah it looks like a hue like a whale vagina yeah it looks
fucked up I've never seen this before yeah fucked up looks because a durian
looks like a jackfruit but it's not a jackfruit unless it is
on Google images and I found an article in popular science called we finally
know how durian got so stinky. Somebody shitted in a coconut 2000 years ago. The subtitle of
the article is "It's one funky fruit." Yeah I've never had it but I do I'm tempted
every time I go to like a like an Asian like dessert place I'm tempted to get the
durian whatever it is. Oh yeah. I want to stink up the place like when somebody gets an
Asiago cheese bagel and the whole bagel shop smelling like a shit. Yeah. Come on
brother. I mean it is one of the best bagels. Yeah. It's so good. No question.
Highest stink to flavor ratio of any bagel though. Bagels most of the time you
can toast a bagel I won't even notice dude. I might just think that the the
heat is on. But an Asiago bagel that's unlucky dude. You don't think the heat is on? Yeah.
- Yeah, you know that smell of--
- Somebody brings a bagel into the room?
- No, like somebody toasting a bagel, you know that smell?
That's like very similar to like,
like a light burning in a heat system.
But an Asiago bagel is like somebody,
I feel like I'm filming Jackass,
like that's probably the smell of the trailers in Jackass.
- I don't know.
I can't, if you had asked me if Asiago bagel smells,
I wouldn't have thought of it as something, a smelly food.
- I'm gonna make you sniff that.
I'm gonna stick one on your on your nose I'm gonna put your nose through the hole
and then just put it under your lip like Vicks Vapor Rub. But first I'm gonna sew
your mouth shut so you can't eat it mm-hmm and then I'm gonna make you I'm
gonna also somehow use a cork to kind of make your nostrils bigger.
more.
Yeah, and then I'm gonna make you smell it.
I said a cork.
I fuckin', I fuckin'.
And then I'm gonna fuckin' make you smell it.
I'ma fuckin' fart in your face.
I fuckin', I fuckin'.
And then I'ma make you smell it.
And smell it.
And fuckin' smell it.
Where we doing?
We were doing that the other day, right?
Where it was just like every.
Yeah, me and Patrick were.
Caleb wasn't part of it.
Oh yeah.
So it's kinda weird for him to jump in.
Yeah, you're right.
It's not like I'm the most hip hop one on the show, but whatever.
That's fine.
all the all the torture things were just him making you eat poop yeah and it goes
down real slow like I'll fucking sew your asshole closed and then open it back up
and make you poop then feeds you that poop they keep feeding you and feeding
you mm-hmm yeah why would you put that what was the one the nuts on the dresser
just the nuts yeah the red hot and the red hot poker it goes yeah I'm gonna make a
red hot poop I'm gonna poke you with it I'm gonna get my poop red hot with a
torch does anybody do that has it you know how they like burn food to see how
many calories there are in them poop is one of the extremely food that's all you
You know that prank where you put a flaming bag of dog poop on your neighbor's doorstep?
That actually evolved out of a...
That was created by a scientist.
Yeah, it was a laboratory thing that got adapted for use by children.
It escaped the lab.
It went to Mr. Johnson's house.
Yeah.
And it just started...
The prank was developed in a lab.
Yeah.
And it spread by accident.
It spread all across the nation.
It actually happens in most pranks.
Spread to Adam Sandler.
Yeah.
Yeah it was very irresponsible for them to put that in Billy Madison. Yeah yeah
cuz it is a it's a mental virus dude. Mm-hmm I did that I think everybody did.
I never did that that was the one. You never set a shit on fire dude? No I never did that either.
That was the one I had we had plans to do it and then we like thought about it more and
we're like well we have to pick up the poop. I used to shit in everything dude.
I would shit in bags and. Wait you did it with human poop not dog poop? Yeah.
the fuck is wrong with you? What's your problem? I don't know, I was a weird kid. I would like
spend most of my days looking for snakes and then shitting in bags and either throwing
them at a school nearby or lighting them on fire. Yeah man I'm weird, I would go looking
for snakes. That's how you knew I was fucked up, I would try and find them. Yeah, most
people, most people, they run away. Most kids, their snakes are trying to find them. But
I went looking for the snakes too many snakes found me fuck fake friends. Yeah, damn damn. That's actually true
That's actually deeply true mm-hmm
Society as well. Let's get into this list
Okay, this is sent by my friend Mike D
Fuck you Mike D. No. Yeah, what's that stand for Mike dick?
Stefano yeah suck Mike
He's dead. No. He's not the comedian
Comedian Mike de Stefano
who has a Jesus tattoo on his arm and he's on Last Comic Standing.
Yep.
Dude, Mike DiStefano.
This list is called It's Not As Easy As You Think, 15 Facts About Being A Centaur.
It's from the website Oneedo.co.
Oneedo.
And the author of this list is a guy named Mr. Peppermint.
Clearly a centaur.
yeah that's a centaur for sure I clicked on I clicked on his his like profile and
this author profile on this website and he writes a lot of lists he has he has
ten not so giggly facts about tickling and giggling that you didn't know inside
the glorious world of Romanian witches this guy is definitely a centaur this
artist this artist is letting people touch her lady parts for a strong
message 17 eye candy celebs with the best curves you shouldn't miss our centaurs
are horny as hell do because they got that horse dick dude he's got range not
a terrifying cursed objects that are genuinely linked to freaky paranormal
events the sexiest cop in the world will make you wish she'd arrest you I need to
see this this is this cop I can't find her you're never you're never gonna find
this clickbait she doesn't exist fuck that sucks I want to see the sexiest cop
in the world that must have hurt jealous wife cuts off her husband's penis with a
pair of scissors scissors in all capitals didn't hurt is that just the
Lorena Bobbitt case he's just talking about like it's something from like the
90s that was on TV all the time the hottest veterinarian ever cures pets but
breaks hearts with his beauty dr. Doolittle size does matter babies born
with big heads are likely to be more intelligent okay mr. peppermint thank
you oh this one came out of nowhere an uncomfortable truth under scope what
causes pedophilia. An in-depth analysis by Mr. Peppermint. Yeah, writing like 150 articles
that are like 17 pictures of dogs that will blow your mind and then be like, "You know
I need to tackle Max." I'm gonna take down the pedophiles on Onedio. Alright, so this
This is by Mr. Peppermint.
(laughing)
- Sorry.
- It's still so good.
- It's just so funny to write about being a centaur
with that name.
- Yeah.
15 cool Viking things by Flargus the Destroyer.
(laughing)
I wonder if this guy's a Viking.
- Mr. Peppermint the Viking.
(laughing)
- Centaur is a mythological creature
with the upper body of a human
and the lower body of a horse.
They're always portrayed in movies or books
as wise, kind, and strong creatures
with their six pack abseye, making most people think
it must be awesome to be a centaur.
But is it?
Let's objectively think together
about what it's like to be a centaur.
- Let's objectively think together.
- I will put my brain together with yours, Mr. Pepper.
We will mind meld to solve this problem.
- It's framed like a Ben Shapiro thing.
- Right. - Yeah.
Yeah, well, is it, how?
- Let's objectively think about this.
You have the body of a human,
but you have the lower half of a horse.
Now, people will try to ride you.
People will try to ride around on you.
People will take you by the arms.
And they'll try to use your arms like motorcycle handles.
- It's kinda hot.
Pull his arms back.
- I would never want a penis the size of a horse.
Structurally, it doesn't make any sense.
- I feel like I might tip over.
- It would weigh me down.
- I would never be able to go to the supermarket
ever again if I was a centaur.
(laughs)
Number one, problems start for a centaur,
even when it's a baby.
While they were not able to keep their human neck upright,
their horse parts start walking within an hour after birth.
- What? - Is that true?
(laughs)
- I mean, I'm not-- - I mean, this is a really
good one because he can just make all this shit up
as he goes.
- I don't know if he's making it up.
He might, this--
- This is all from experience.
- Yeah, dude, he's fucking Mr. Peppermint.
- It's Mr. Peppermint, dude.
that's a good boy does the mail i forgot it was mr pepper the male centaur in
this drawing is that a stick
uh... where the dick would be held at the bump
looks like a look at it looks like a hefty kinda
canopy g bump
you know i mean like a big again the cat it's it's like it's like it's like you
know it's a little bit of a little bit and all
although they did give juicy titties to the girl one
they did
so that's kind of an interesting double standard
I'd just like to point that out. You can't show a giant horse's penis but you can show a centaur's
boobs? Come on society. What kind of world are we living in now? This is so messed up.
That's what Ben Shapiro needs to talk about. The fact that they won't let a man's penis,
or a horse's penis be shown. A centaur's penis. A centaur's penis. See even I got tripped
up. Do you think it's different than normal horses? I think maybe it's a little bit smaller
than a horse's penis.
Why?
Because of the human genes.
Is any other thing smaller?
Yeah, is it probably their fucking hooves?
What?
Why?
Just think about it.
Why would their hooves be smaller?
I am thinking about it.
It doesn't make any sense.
Is half horse, half human, why would there be any cross pollination?
There's a line.
Their whole thing is cross pollination.
Yeah, but there's a there's a clear line where you could cut a centaur at the waist and you could say it's not it
These might as well be two different things. Yeah
Yeah
The hooves are covered up in this drawing right and they look small
That's one big thing about being a center you got by two pairs of Jordan. Oh, yeah, dude, that sucks
Yeah, that's a bummer dude also. I mean yeah, also. There's
Really a tiny one yeah
Your foot is a you and they have to be circles fuck this getting harder every have to be right
Oh, you the worst part about being a centaur starting to understand. Why horses don't wear Jordans, right?
Yeah, just stuff that look like newspaper thinking about this
Does not be fun dude if you own if you listen to this show and you own a horse
and you have a pair of Jordans,
can you put them on your horse and see what happens?
- Yeah, get right behind the horse
and try to put a Jordan on its hoof.
- Yeah, put like a Jordan 7 on a horse.
- Yeah, get down on all fours underneath the horse.
- With your head facing the same direction as its head.
- And put a Jordan in your butt crack
and then so that it has a place
where it can slide on the shoe.
- Yeah, its foot.
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
- Put its hoof on your foot.
your butt crack.
Number 2, like any other mammals, baby centaurs need to be breastfed, but how?
human breasts or horse breasts of the mother or from both for different parts
of a baby of a baby's body what does it have a horse mouth on its bottom half
what are they talking about you have to like hook up your penis like a tube
horse tip yeah how else for it or from both because they have a picture here
body they have a picture here of a baby centaur being breastfed the baby that's
- That's not a baby centaur though,
that's like a child's body growing out
of the back half of a centaur.
- Well maybe it hasn't grown,
maybe it has like tiny horse hooves.
- It has no legs.
- Yeah, do they grow the horse later?
- I think so.
I think you grow the two sides separately
and you snap them together.
- The horse half starts walking within an hour after birth.
- Have you ever seen a horse give birth?
- On like video, not in real life.
I've seen a zebra give birth on video, not a horse though.
It just falls out, right?
Yeah, it just hits the ground.
That's crazy.
I mean, they seem to be doing okay.
Damn.
Can you imagine how much smarter they would be?
I'm just thinking about,
no, 'cause it's like a centaur being born.
If it does have the legs
and it just kind of falls out like that.
true and it also has the soft human skull. Right, so it would just be kind of like
an Ace Ventura rhino situation but with like with horse legs. Wait, how would
the centaur baby come out? Head first? Head first, yeah. Hopefully.
Yeah, like most babies. But I will say, horse babies do come out hoof first.
Yeah. Do they? Yeah. Maybe what if the horse, the hoof and the head is pointing in
the same I would hate to give birth to a horse that's the it would hurt so bad
oh that's a good thing about that that at least zebras do I'm guessing horses do
too but the video I saw that the lady just pulls the zebra by his leg just out of
just into the world just fucking shakes it out it's pretty good
camera can you share this video of the horse birth that you're watching I'm
- I'm trying to look up if the horses come out here first.
- Centaur birth?
- I'm trying to find a centaur birth.
- I'm gonna look up centaur birth video.
- Whoa, when horses are born, their hooves are soft.
- Ugh. - Yeah, dude.
- Nasty.
Okay, I found a video right here.
- One of the recommended questions
when I Googled are horses born hoof first
is can a horse give birth to a pony?
(laughing)
- Yes.
- Check this video out I just sent.
- Is this a horse video?
- This is an Mpreg centaur birth.
- I am on my younger brother's computer
and he is not allowed to watch this video apparently.
(laughing)
Here, I'm pulling this up right now.
- Okay, so in this video the head is coming out first.
It's all animation, it looks like a storyboard.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, the baby--
- It's childbirth, male, this music is just heartbreaking.
- Yeah.
- Why are they, why is this,
Why did they choose this music?
There's a comment here on the video from Bobo.
It says, "I randomly saw this and at first I was disgusted,
now just watching the whole thing made my heart break."
Is this a sad video?
The music sounds like a sad scene in a video game,
where like a character that you don't care about dies.
I'm on the credits, programs, pencil,
iMovie, soundtrack, sad romance.
So it came out head first in this video.
special thanks to for serenity baby you are my only god i think it might be a
stillbirth
you know i don't want
that is awesome
if you are making yourself a car that works in the world pick up
i think i have to do it
that's what i like to see
yes that door
trying to get birth with
killing
those fucking it's like the monkey the people who think monkeys are pests so
So they like watch monkey torture videos on YouTube and comment like, "Yes, fucking kill
monkey.
I'm so happy."
What?
Is that a thing?
People don't know about that?
There's monkey torture videos?
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
What kind of crime could a monkey commit?
They're like rats in like whatever country they're like rats in.
Oh yeah, okay, that makes sense.
That's like dogs and- And you know, we watch like rat torture videos
this week.
Yeah, you know how we are.
You already watch people torture bugs all the time.
It's just because they're pests.
It's not because anyone has any weird mental problems.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
I do think one of the greatest things that I know is that in parts of Mexico, dogs will
just chase people down the street if they ride on a motorcycle.
And so you have to have two people on the motorcycle, one person to drive it and one
person to hold a bat at the back and just beat off all the dogs.
Jesus Christ.
That's so funny.
It is very cool.
cool yeah and also it's traditional to carry around steak in your pocket in
Mexico that might be part of the reason yeah yeah all right number three oh go
ahead you like no I read the last one you read the camera and you children are
picky eaters so imagine having us so just imagine having a centaur kid you
need to know not only the human food they would like but also the right horse
food I don't think there's a picture of a child
Let me think, uh, chicken nuggets and hay.
And oats.
Yeah, yeah.
Done.
What the fuck are you talking about?
With a deep fried hay.
I don't think they would need to eat two separate foods too.
You could probably just give them, figure out which one they like.
I think they're gonna like chicken nuggets more than hay.
I'm just gonna, I'm just gonna throw a guess at it.
Right, it doesn't have a horse stomach.
The mouth is human, but the back end is horse, so they like eating chicken nuggets better,
but they like shitting out hay better.
True, that's a good point.
I guess horses don't eat meat.
What would happen if you fed a horse a burger?
If horses ate meat that would be genuinely so scary.
They'd be so big too.
Can you imagine horses fucking hunting us down?
Those things are scary.
Oh my god.
It would be the kings of the planet.
Yeah.
Which I think of humans as.
They look kind of like xenomorphs, their heads.
It's true.
Horses look fucked up.
They have those fucked up teeth.
Yeah, and the long.
They have like human teeth.
No, their teeth go out.
They have like British human teeth.
Yeah, true.
Yeah, I don't like I like no animals that have like flat teeth animals should have sharp evil teeth look at this thing dude
What the fuck that's it? Oh my god dressed up like a centaur
Look at this look at this picture of horse teeth
Just Google Google image search horse. Yeah
This is more silly as hell
And search horse teeth there for this horse watching scary this horse is
Sorry, I layer the cable gas off dude. He's here in the bowling shoes joke for the first time
He's heard about the super finger. Mm-hmm. He's like, I wish I could if a horse if a horse could do the Sioux fi
Fuck it's over dude. They don't even need to eat meat then they run this shit
Yeah, do the horse to be taken over the BK lounge you're gonna fend me to death. Yeah. Yeah horses love coops
All right, what's that Dane Cook joke about the atheist sneeze or whatever?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Could you imagine telling a horse to try and say God bless you to you or whatever?
Yeah, what if the horse did the pimp walk across the street?
Right.
You know? Yeah, I saw this guy doing some horse walk across the crosswalk.
I saw a guy trotting.
He's trotting, he's doing a pimp trot.
All right, number four and I am
And I am NOT even talking about their toilet training. What do you mean is a horse it shits on the ground?
Yeah, it's standing up!
Non-stop, day in day out.
This picture is evil. The picture attached to this is not okay.
That is a, that is a, do not,
genuinely, the person who threw this should go to jail.
But they should go to jail.
The way that it's looking up to, ugh.
Yeah, this is a naughty, nasty photo.
I'd send that thing to the glue factory right away.
Imagine drawing this picture and then having the audacity to fucking sign your name on it.
Dude, the stork drops that monstrosity off at my house.
house straight to the glue factory yeah I'm not even taking I'm calling an uber
for it yep I know I know I said don't do moving I know that's like a big policy
right now but I'll make him wear a mask just drop him off at the glue factory
they have a bin it's like this coming back home with the Chinese take a bag
full of jello five or let's talk about it what what is this grabbing a rebound at
the end of the game just imagine half-human baby centaurs defecating
around like horses we already did an asshole dude mr. pepper the next
pictures my favorite. We'll post this picture with the episode. Number six, sleeping is another issue.
Did you ever think of centaurs sleep? And it's like an alcoholic centaur lying on the ground
like a human centipede. Yeah that is not a good photo either. Yeah. I never considered how long
it would be. I'm glad I want to meet the guy who drew this one. If it had longer arms it could walk
around the thing about this this art is that every every drawing of a centaur
that's like from the internet you it's fetish art right like it has to be
there's no way you just draw a centaur because you think it's great
centaur it's like suffering from some kind of alcohol issue and doesn't even
look sexy at all.
You don't think he looks sexy dude? Look at that. Look at how tortured he looks.
Yeah, that's sexy. Yeah, I just looked up fat centaur.
That's a mistake. The first image is
real, real good.
Yeah.
I'll describe it.
It is a fat
uh... fat centaur eating a whole cake outside of a Baskin-Robbins.
we need to get a new species on earth this is getting so boring I found I found out
how I found out why this centaur picture of the suffering centaur is horny I
reverse image searched it and found the deviant art of it uh-huh and the
description says the title is quote morning after you can make up your own
story to go along with that oh this is a post this is a post fetish centaur Jesus
Christ. Yeah, look, look, there's three centaurs behind him. He just got ran
through, dude. Yeah. There's like three shadowy centaurs. Wow, can you imagine how
much beer it actually takes to make a centaur drunk? It would be measured in
barrels. I'll tell you how much, I'll tell you how much beer it takes to make a horse
drunk. One sip, because they've never, they don't have beer, they're just not able to
drink beer. I don't know, I think, I think you could feed a horse a couple Budweiser's.
I would love to hotbox of the barn with my horse. Yeah, like people. I know no no no that's danger
No, I think that's I would rather get a horse drunk than get it high. I'm gonna get my pet bear high
And we're gonna watch we're gonna watch zombie land together inside
Actually turned on the revenant with
I can't wait to give my my pet 21-foot alligator abilify
I'm sure his mood is going to be so stable.
Have you ever seen that video of the guy who swims with a polar bear in like a pool?
No, is he a penguin?
No, he's just like an old white guy who kind of looks like a polar bear.
I've definitely talked about this before and now that I'm thinking about it, I've 100%
talked about this.
I want to see different centaur type animals where you just put two together.
know I mean there's the Seder a Seder is like a like a lamb and a guy right but I
want to see like a rhino it's a it's a goat I want to see a rhino and a goat is the same
fucking thing absolutely not that is one of the stupidest things you ever said in your life
you could feed you could feed a lamb a tin can the same way you can feed a goat a tin can
I want to see a gator with a cat ass yeah yeah you know what you should check out
oh my god imagine how terrifying a fucking there's this great there's this great
picture book i think you would like to
uh... and
i think it's called like mix-and-match animals or something
i think you really get a kick out of this
i think i might actually here all of us in the exam is actually a bit i have a
s_p_s_
i'm not just a little bit still thinking about sorry camera i'm still thinking
about just a cat with like
gator instincts
okay okay cool thanks for letting us know about that
i'm terrified of that i'm thinking of a cat with a gator
Wait, hold on guys, I'm thinking.
Okay, now you can keep going with your joke.
Number seven, and being unable to perform
your own personal care and dependent on others
for grooming your horse body.
You can reach, give yourself a reach around, dude.
I guess it'd be tough to, you don't really wipe your ass.
That's a, could you lean over
and suck your own thingy as a horse?
Just go in the water.
No way you can suck your own thingy.
Yeah, no, it doesn't matter how many ribs you get to move.
How much can you move with the centaur body?
Like, something like...
You definitely couldn't lean back.
You could lean back a little bit.
I mean, you're not gonna be like, you're never gonna be like comfortable,
like watching the Super Bowl, you know, like that's gonna be a tough ask as a centaur.
You know, a centaur friend in a friend group is gonna fuck up a lot of hangs.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
Especially when you live on the fifth floor.
Yeah, that's a walk up.
floor walk up no elevator good luck buddy that's not gonna be fun mm-hmm you know
I had to put my friend down the other day. Imagine waking up at like 3 a.m. cuz your
upstairs centaur neighbor like had to go pee so you like you just hear like
slamming around and then just a 10 minutes of a fire hose well that's a nice
thing about being a centaur is you could you could stand up to pee. You don't
stand up to pee already? No. What if I fall over? Sorry, I'm just thinking about...
I would need four legs if I was going to stand up to pee. You're thinking about something again, dude?
Yeah, your centaur friend getting stuck on your stairwell just because you can't
walk down? Or is that cows that can't walk down stairs? Oh, fuck. You know what, I'm
I'm gonna go ahead and say most animals cannot walk downstairs.
It's true.
I'm gonna say that's not...
What do you mean most animals can't walk downstairs?
I think a horse or a cow, any four-legged animal that is not like small, would have a pretty
tough time with human stairs.
I don't think that's most animals, actually.
I don't think a cricket could walk downstairs.
I'm sorry, I should have been more specific so that you wouldn't have no idea what I was
talking about.
A horse, I don't think, could walk downstairs.
Yeah.
can walk downstairs all right then do it get a horse go get a horse right now
yeah put it to the test fucking Jamie Heineman myth bust that I dare you we
should start our own myth busters thing okay it says they have difficulty going
down but doesn't say it's impossible
it says yes here on reddit.com I thought it was what about like a half man how
look at this dude I'm right it says depends on the staircase okay but like a
walk up in like an apartment I don't think like six stairs either side with a
platform it mentions that it says he's actually super good at it yeah it says
it's quite easy sis this horses hang out at apartments all the time I have a show
pony in my studio apartment. Number eight, not having a proper life at home. It must be
awful not to be able to use almost any human stuff. Well here's a show him sitting on a couch.
Here's a centaur in an apartment. And also he's eating popcorn and drinking beer. He's got a hookah, he's got some guitars.
This just looks like a normal guy. Can you tell what the album covers are on the wall?
I
Yeah, he's got, okay, he's got the Mountain Goats Tallahassee poster, he has a cake poster.
I don't know what the other poster is.
What's that other magazine say?
Is that Metal Gear Solid?
It looks like it.
Is that Game Informer?
That's Game Informer.
Dude, this horse is just, this centaur's chillin'.
He's a baller, yeah.
They have a gaming centaur?
He's drinking Budweiser?
He has like four colors.
This picture is answering a lot of questions we've had earlier about centaurs.
It's kind of blowing my mind, actually.
Yeah, I would hang out with this centaur.
He's- oh my god dude he's holding the bowl of popcorn with his middle legs.
Fuck!
Dude.
Holy shit.
I wanna be a centaur now just for that.
I need me the centaur upgrade.
Yo I need me a pair of middle limbs for real.
I mean this whole time we've been kinda like not into the centaur thing.
This picture right here is changing a lot of stuff for me.
That's the life dude yeah.
He also has horse ears which I think debunks one of Caleb's theories from earlier.
Oh man imagine wearing headphones as a centaur.
Oh that there's no yeah.
I just bought a pair of Beats by Dre and I can't even wear them because I'm a fucking
centaur.
If you're a centaur you'd probably be buying some eats my hay.
True, that's a good point.
That's pretty good.
Yeah.
So what do you think before you speak next time?
That's what I want to see dude.
I want to see the centaur products.
Yeah.
You know.
I mean mane and tail.
change number nine is except the kissing part their sexual life is technically
all about mating I guess they have an uncontrollable bottom half that just
needs to fuck for procreation life is but then the top half loves kissing the top
half is very romantic would you kiss a centaur woman yes you'd be a little man
for my taste as long she's under 5'6" sure that's fine she's got an ass so big
she needs four legs to support it. Ass so big I could see it from the front. She is a centaur.
The picture is like kind of like tender and pleasant you know yeah yeah this is a
kind of just beautiful mm-hmm number 10 you always have to walk around naked
have you ever seen a centaur wearing a shirt or pants? I'd be the first centaur to wear a shirt.
Yeah, I think we have it. Oh, yeah, that's a tank top. That's not a shirt
No, I don't sound like that
Pants, I also feel like somebody you you could give a horse pants. Yeah, just a male never been a reason to I put chain
Yeah on
Well, yeah, that'll weigh you down. Dude. I were like barding. I would be a fucking like Lord of the Rings horse
That'd be so cool. I mean if you're a centaur you could just do like yo if you were a centaur
I'm a knight's armor you could do you could wear one of those like two-part horse costumes by yourself
And then somebody would like run over and try and like like trip the back one or something to make a joke
They get a damn to the face
You see right by the way
This is in a world where there are centaurs that people see so the person is that's like a defensive costume
Yeah, well so the horse the horse part the back half of the costume would look normal
But then the front half the neck would be really long because you have your whole upper body - true
So it's like it would be a really cool-looking horse
Probably a giraffe actually now that I think about it more a giraffe with a really thick neck. Oh
Man
What half human half giraffe?
What about a giraffe?
The giraffe half is at the top half and the human half is the bottom.
So they just have a really long giraffe head.
Yeah, because the back half of a giraffe is not interesting.
So it's just like Geoffrey the giraffe.
Yeah, now we got a Bojang Horseman character now.
Yeah.
No, but it's not the head.
He's depressed.
It's the middle.
Yeah, and he's depressed.
Yeah.
Yeah, and he's a musician.
We're doing something different.
He's very happy.
He's the happiest horse in the world.
He's the happiest half giraffe half man.
has no mental illness yeah and it's just about him hanging out smoking weed with
Seth Rogen fucking getting pussy yep how about that and since he's got a human
lower half it's not weird to show it on TV when he gets some and he's got a size
13 foot but he is he does have a granny fetish though yeah it's a little messed
up but but it's like not illegal you're you're yeah you're thinking it's gonna
be worse so then it's fine yeah number one he's already so famous I mean he's
probably talking to like some famous grannies Betty White did yeah like
granny goodness I think Betty White's look is fucking so he's ran through by
Hollywood what I'm just wondering dude you think she's still fucking and sucking
for rolls I think that's how she has such a long career still you give me this
role I'll make it worth your while I'm a hundred and seven years old. She does not do that! I'm not
saying that she does, I'm saying it's possible. She does not. It's like you don't have an imagination.
I have childlike wonder so I imagine things like that sometimes. I yeah I'm more imaginative than
you. Okay well you imagine a disgusting sex thing for once. Okay all right. Go ahead if you're so
imaginative think about it what about sex missionary style yeah between two
crabs how about that that's funny hey don't don't try and fucking don't try and
add on to mine I'm still thinking I win the imagination for this missionary
style between two - - you almost said two men a man and a woman Wow
I can't think of anything. You have writer's block. Yeah. Dude, I have writer's block right now.
All I can think of is a man and a woman having missionary sex.
Oh, for three minutes?
When they were writing the Kama Sutra, the author was having a really hard time because
"Oh, I have a great new idea. Oh, fuck."
[Laughter]
That was such a guy, getting writer's block, just throwing stuff at the wall.
That's it, we got it.
He's like, "Uhh, upside down? I don't know."
Upside-- wait!
Yeah, that was the big breakthrough, is when he dropped the page and it like flipped around on the ground.
He was like, "Wait a second."
[Laughter]
Yeah, no, his fucking son got a hold of the manuscript and was making origami out of one of the pages.
he was like oh my god that's it there it is yeah he saw two squirrels fighting
outside as he's trying to write that's it that's the one I have to make a box
with the two people this is gonna be awesome
around and he just looks at an alley just sees sucking someone's dick it's like
Eureka!
yeah the Kama Sutra was written in 1948 yeah in Illinois yeah what will I call it
the Kama Sutra it was originally called David's big sexy
David's hobo fuck positions. It was called the ways I've seen hobos fucking in the alley near my house.
The publisher was like that name is not doing it. We can't do that.
Why don't we just use the hobos names?
Number 11 although centaur bodies always depicted muscular in a perfect shape being an overweight an overweight centaur must really suck
Ah true probably be fine
She's eating the whole cake outside basket Rob. That's true. It's a good point
Number 12 a centaur is doomed to be a warrior. There is almost no office career for them hold on
Oh, what we are I said warrior. You said a centaur is doomed to be a what yeah?
I did not say that you did
I hope I did.
That's a weird accent choice to make.
Yeah.
I didn't say it.
I liked it though.
I thought it was good.
I thought I said it normal.
I think a centaur could have an awesome office job.
Warrior.
See I just said awesome.
It happens to the best of us dude.
Read the thing again.
A centaur is doomed to be a warrior.
Is that really how you say that?
Yeah.
Why?
Warrior?
Are you joking right now?
No I'm not joking.
I can't tell if you're leaning into it or not.
Warrior.
There it is.
You realize there's two R's there.
not like a made-up letter new letter that makes the Y sound. He thought he was
speaking Spanish. Yeah. He said warrior. How did I say it? You said warrior. You said it like it
rhymed with lawyer like three times. Oh fuck. Anyway that is that's fucked up. I
don't think it's true but it's fucked up. No you could have it you could easily
have an office job for a centaur. That'd be like a hilarious NBC sitcom.
Yeah, it'd be great.
The next picture is something else too.
It's too late for subway.
Can you give us a ride, Centaur?
We will move our house this Sunday.
Could you help us, Centaur?
This little guy wants to ride you.
Can you let him get on you for a few minutes?
Why would you hire a centaur to help you move?
Yeah, I don't think that's true.
No, just, I mean, people still are gonna have cars.
There are a lot of people that look weird around.
don't go up to him that and ask for rides yeah it's also hard to ride a horse
it's not easy but do you think it'd be easier to ride a sensor I also think I
don't know why you would that's like a session or reason we want to ride a
horse would probably be fucking scared shitless of a centaur right just a point
I mean cuz it's like here's the thing I love but there's also an ugly shirtless
man on top of it yeah it's part of it true how many more are there so only two
- Two more. - Yeah.
Four legs, two arms, and one tail.
They must be used in a harmony, taken good care,
periodically horseshoed, et cetera.
- One of the things I hate most about having my two arms
and two legs is I have to use them in harmony.
- Right. - It's so annoying.
I wish I just had one of everything.
- Yeah, I wish I just had one thing.
Like I'm not even, not a head or a body.
- I need to be more streamlined.
- I wish I was just-- - Dude, it's the cloaca cube.
- True, but that's even two things,
'cause you have a hole.
I wanna just be-- - It's a cloaca and a cube.
- Yeah, I just wanna be a cube.
- I just wanna be a cloaca.
- I would look, just like on,
and you just slap it on something like a black--
- Yeah, like a googly eye. - Like a hole in Looney Tunes.
- Yeah.
- Number 15, and you know what fate awaits you
in case you ever break your leg.
I don't know, probably cast?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, baby.
Yeah, I mean, I see a centaur in real life. I'm not waiting for it to break its leg.
Yeah, that thing's on site.
Yeah, definitely.
If centaurs are around and it's acceptable to shoot them when they break their leg, it's
absolutely acceptable to shoot them before they break their leg too.
Yeah, it's also like if you ever want to murder a centaur, it's like the easiest fucking...
Yeah, just break his leg after you do it.
You shoot him in the head and then break his leg.
Oh yeah, he broke his leg. I put him out of his misery. Oh, it was so horrible.
Yeah, you can also just say...
I actually loved that he fucked my wife with his big horse dick.
I had no reason to kill him.
But he broke his leg. I'm lucky, dude.
Yeah, he broke his leg going up the stairs to fuck my wife.
Yeah.
He was in the middle of fucking my wife.
Oh, he was so miserable.
And he broke his leg.
The Martin Scorsese cameo in Taxi Driver.
You know what this does to a centaur?
[laughter]
Alright.
There it is. Centaur facts.
How do I feel? There's a reaction button on the bottom. I'm gonna hit him with a
thumbs down. That was a terrible article. I'm doing thumbs down. I'm hitting him
with a surprise. Mr. Peppermint, a surprise is coming to you.
Yeah. From Patrick. Get ready Mr. Peppermint. All right, bye everyone. Bye everybody.