You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts for the homeless.
You're a crap monster.
Lollipop, lollipop, oh lollipop, lollipop, lollipop
Bobo, Bobo, call me lollipop
Tell you why, it's just as sweet as an apple pie
And when it goes to shaky rocky dips
Man, I ain't got a chance
I'll go lollipop, lollipop, oh lollipop, lollipop
(laughing)
- Sorry guys.
- That's the intro to the greatest episode we will ever do.
- I couldn't look at Caleb doing it in that fucking suit.
- It's the best episode we're ever gonna do
and I dressed to the nines for it.
It's called Dressing Appropriately.
- I plan to do the best episode ever today.
- Cam texted us yesterday and said,
let's do the best episode we have ever done tomorrow.
And we said, you know what man, why the fuck not?
- I haven't really done that yet.
I'm wearing my shoes.
That's right, we're all in Miami right now.
Mm-hmm, I'm in Miami, I'm wearing my dress shoes
that I got for my brother's wedding
that he said are too red for his wedding.
That's cold.
Mm-hmm, they're too red.
That's what happens when you're the best man,
you gotta be color coordinated with the groom.
You're the best man?
Me and my brother, we're doing best man duties.
Why don't you just get him redder shoes?
We're both best men.
We're doing best brothers.
You can't, so neither of you are best men.
Yeah.
No, we're best men.
Best, it's either one.
there's one yeah this is the best episode we can't hide best episodes so we're
tied you can't know hide for best dude we're tied you might as well but you
might as well be worst woman the way that you're everything that's true who
I'm not the worst woman you are unless you kill your brother you're going to be
there's a certain iron lady who is the worst woman if you ask any British person
Yeah, your mom.
Yeah.
What? Who sneezed?
Who was that?
I think Jan is in the other room having a sneeze attack.
Okay.
Having a bit of a sneeze.
Yeah, having a bit of a sneeze, so let's not bother her too much.
[Laughter]
She's busy.
Yeah.
But yeah, we're all dressed in the nines.
Honey, I told you not to come in here when I'm sneezing.
Can you fucking just give me five? Can I sneeze for five minutes in this fucking house?
Without you coming in here and saying, "Oh, having a bit of a sneeze, are we?"
- Ew, I'm having a bit of a sneeze.
- Oh heavens.
- Oh goodness.
- Mind if I partake?
- What's all this racket?
Are you sneezing again?
- Are you sneezing?
- Yeah baby, sometimes I'm sneezing.
It's one of my favorite things to do.
- Oh how delightful.
- Oh beautiful.
- Yeah, women love to sneeze dude.
They like it 'cause it's,
you know it's actually a miniature orgasm.
Did you know that?
That's the only one my wife's ever had.
- Here's an idea for a stand up bit for everyone out there.
- Okay.
- Women sneeze like this.
(mimics sneezing)
- Men sneeze like this.
- Yes, dude. - You could do that on stage.
- Yes.
- Men do scream when they sneeze.
- My dad, I think I've maybe said this before,
my dad one time sneezed when I was a kid
and I was upstairs and I ran downstairs
'cause I thought he had a heart attack.
I thought that's what a heart attack sounded like.
Was just like (mimics sneezing)
(laughing)
It's pretty horrifying, dude.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
I don't have a loud sneeze, I nipped that in the bud.
I think I had it.
I started developing a loud sneeze
and I was like, I can't be a loud sneezer.
- I sneezed at the beginning.
I sneezed at the beginning of the premium episode
we recorded and it just sounds like I'm screaming.
There's a sneeze at the beginning
and it's just you guys talking and then I just go.
- Yeah, but you do that on purpose though.
You guys know those girls who sneeze like a mouse?
- Yeah.
- They go, (squeaking)
- Yeah, they're faking.
yeah I think they sneeze like this oh you know why this is the best episode ever
because I'm dressed to the nines no because tomorrow the Cheeto and chief
leaves oh my god oh my god oh ding dong the orange witch is dead like a
basketball coach you you look like you're trying to sell cutco you look
like you're selling knives. I think I look good. Yeah? Yeah. I think you look good too. I think I
might do dress to the nines every day. You should dress like this when you go to the bodega,
like with the headphones and everything. I might become, yeah, I might become like one of those,
like a Paul F. Tompkins type, like wear a suit every day and just be a miserable son of a bitch.
Yeah, those are cool shoes stop laughing
God I gotta stop trying to show them in the web. There's no way
23 yeah walking around with a roller backpack
Parent roller backpack, I knew you could just see there's a monster energy and one loose Adderall pill
I knew a kid who was a new suit kid who brought a briefcase. Yeah
You'd be so different dude, I know I was like this suited skater I
Well, I would wear a suit cuz I thought it was funny
I would sometimes just like where like no, I mean what's funny about how I look right now
Say it to his face say it to my fucking face if you think it's funny that you look like a corporate cog in the machine
To me. Oh, that's what's funny. Yeah, guess what? I'm playing these had giant headphones. I have you're playing rock chemical romance. Yeah punk rock
Yes, no
Yeah, cuz when I get home from the office, I hit the office every day, you know, and then I get home 9 p.m
At night, I worked one hour. Yeah, I I would I rock you listen to rage against the machine, dude
Yeah, I'm a business guy.
And then I look at my hands and I go, "I am the machine!"
And then I fucking strangle myself.
Do you guys know the secret message behind the song "Killing in the Name"?
Basically it says some of those that work forces, so that's like the workforce, like
workers.
So like everything.
So every, every workforce.
Yeah, well like some, like worker, yeah, the workforce are the same who burn crosses.
So it's basically like this, like, this kind of commentary on how many employees don't
like Christians and they like kind of fight back against Christian holidays
that's actually a really good point a lot of these like dog shit like minimum wage
workers burger flippers they hate Christianity and they want to they'd
rather work at McDonald's on Christmas then go home and hang out with their
family yeah I was I was at McDonald's the other day and I actually heard one of
the guys flipping a hamburger say I love Muhammad he actually said that and I
made it I made a very serious complaint yeah cuz that was the manager's name in
sexual harassment in the workplace yeah exactly yeah no laughing matter yeah
that's not a joke man yeah yeah but yeah I was almost a suit kid what I did was I
would there was like a thing there was like a path near the dumpsters in my
neighborhood growing up and I would stand on the side of the road in a suit and I
would kind of jump out at cars like I
wouldn't jump out in front of them but I
would jump up on the side of the road
and start dancing so it looked like a
weird kid in a suit is like dancing it
would just look like that it would but
it wouldn't be that though it wouldn't
be a weird kid it would look like a weird kid
it would be the illusion of a weird kid dancing in a dumpster
it would be a normal kid acting weird
pretty cool for his age kid
actually very mature for his age
I bet you were a kid who got into British comedy pretty young
You may think I'm a weird suit kid, but actually I'm completely normal.
No I'm just wearing a suit to look like a suit kid.
You may think you're seeing a fucking little freak dancing in a dumpster wearing a suit,
but I'm actually a normal guy.
But I actually live here and it's an okay house to have.
Yeah, it's called a tiny home.
I stopped doing it because this one time a guy in a gold van saw me.
You stopped doing it?
How many times did you fucking do it?
I did it a couple days in a row.
Okay, what was it? Did you like do it after school? Was it like?
No, it was on a weekend. I think it was during the summer.
You spent your weekends dancing.
And were you with anyone?
No, it was just by myself. I did it for me.
[Laughter]
So I...
I'm going to have a great story to tell on my podcast.
Yeah, whatever.
In two years.
[Laughter]
I did this at 18. No, wait.
You're 20 years old, dude.
I'm 23.
[Laughter]
and like a gold like it was like a wind star like pulled up and was like what are
you doing and I was like I'm dancing he's like why why are you doing this I
was like I don't know cuz it's funny he's like all right
Caleb what's really so I got so I was right that I just went how to read a
book oh honestly I don't know yet I haven't gotten I haven't gotten to the
halfway point where I'm guessing it teaches you sorry I didn't mean
interrupt the little the little color pictures in the middle the show pictures
of a guy reading a book from the TV show I do think it'd be funny to just sit on
like a park bench with this and just shake my head just go a book called how
to read a book I found it online I paid $18 for it yeah I want to know how to
read a book. This is where your patreon money is going everybody. Well now that it's on the
podcast we can write it off. Write that book off. Needed to learn to read in order to do
the podcast. Yeah I'm gonna start just like showing like baggies of Adderall that I buy
on the podcast and just be like write off baby easy money. Yeah. Taxman not getting me.
So what fucking tax man could tax someone
who looks as good as me right now?
- You look like the tax man.
- That's true, he'd walk up to your house and he'd go,
"Oh, sorry, I didn't realize you were a tax man."
- Yeah, they'd come to audit me and they'd be like,
"Sir, I think you have to be audited."
I'd say, "Look at me, buddy.
"Look at this shirt I'm wearing.
"I'm auditing you right now."
- Yeah. (laughs)
- Yeah, first off, your shoes don't match your tie,
so I'm gonna need you to leave and come back.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I'm gonna send you to Brooks Brothers.
Here, have a gift card, it's a write-off.
yeah oops looks like I dropped a gift card yep oh you're auditing me looks like I
dropped $10 mm-hmm just think about that well ten less dollars you have to audit I
suppose but somebody's gonna have to pick that up not me certainly won't be me
because this suit is very tight yeah I tried to do a pull-up in this suit
because I do pull-ups so I keep my back strong wear pull-ups yeah when you said
you do it you do a pull-up you mean like do like I don't as in drugs like a like
a line of coat like you snorted a pull-up I didn't snort the contents of a
pull-up. You cut a pull-up open and you're the one who would know. You took the powders out.
I don't even know whether it would get you high or not. There's no powders in a pull-up dude
it's a it's a it's a like a fucking membrane. No it's it's powder.
Isn't it like gel? It's like a powder that turns into a gel. We learned this in
diaper talk I think it's filled with gel we learn this in diaper school no not
anymore now look at me I'm the teacher at diaper school you guys class in its
session right now dude oh my god I feel so powerful I'm saying you guys have to
get on dressing to the nines yeah I think you guys might enjoy it yeah yeah
I got the shoes already see what's great about these shoes is that they also
double as a skate shoe so I could be dressed to the nines and I could also go
to the skate park
how tight is that fucking suit so woman's extra-large nobody can see this
cuz I'm a big-ass bitch is your hand still bandaged up nope just like this
forever no one can see this at all it's okay I got a very tight oh my dude the
fucking shoulders are pad look the shoulders got shoulder pads I can't
reach it I can't reach it to brush brush off my shoulder because the suit is so
tight but basically I wear this tights
Imagine you open the door to audit me, and I'm just standing like this with my shoulder pointed at your head.
You're built like a fucking Digimon villain.
You open the door, you're gonna audit me, and I point this at you and say, "Which eye is your dominant one?"
You're about to lose that shit.
They knock on the door to audit you, and you open the door and just bats fly out and you vanish.
Oh, hello.
Good evening.
Have you ever audited an evil monster?
Have you ever audited somebody so evil?
I can control your thoughts.
Yeah, that's right.
They open the door and there's just gold coins just in black cauldrons all over the place
and you're like, "Be my guest, my friend."
Yeah, go to an audit.
Would you like a drink?
Here, do you need to audit this cursed amulet?
Sorry, all my goblets are in the dishwasher.
perhaps you will find what you're looking for.
(laughter)
- Yeah, you wanna audit me, start with the--
- He doesn't know there's a dark clone in there.
(laughter)
- Start with the void in the den.
Try auditing that.
- You turn to your hunchback and you give a stage whisper.
- This is my wife.
- He doesn't know what will happen
if he touches the cursed coins.
(laughter)
- Yeah, you could fully hear me talking to my hunchback.
- Yeah.
sorry what what is your relationship oh we're filed jointly we're doing law it's
like a common law situation yeah I also you also will notice I did write him off
cuz he cost me a thousand he is my property let me just let you know from
dr. diabolical I have me a receipt if you want me to yeah but it's not necessary
oh you have the wrong at you're looking for mr. sinister I'm sorry oh I think
I think you actually meant to go to 667 Satan Avenue.
Yeah.
This is 666.
Mm-hmm.
Mr. Sinister is there.
Yeah, sure.
No, I would be so happy to sign this form as long as I can sign it in your blood.
Here, take this needle.
Prick your finger for me.
Do you have an inkwell that I can use?
Do you have an inkwell full of your blood for some reason?
Yeah, sure.
No, sure.
Here, I'll fill out this W-2 real quick and then as soon as you're finished, just the
writing disappears.
You're like, yeah, you're gonna want to hold this up to a candle.
It burns immediately from the bottom up.
It ashes.
You're like, okay.
And now that's contract.
There's a dark laughter in the smell of sulfur.
And I am officially an employee of Quiznos Enterprise.
What an amazing day.
Anyway, I'm going to be wearing a suit to work every single day.
I do not wear gloves.
They make my hands sweat.
And I will not be wearing a face mask.
Oh, you want to audit.
My eyes have sharp teeth.
Oh, you want to audit me, huh?
Why don't you close your eyes and put your hand in this bowl full of eyeballs?
Yeah, oh I think I just felt a cobweb I hope there are no spiders about I
Think my audacity is fooling around fooling around what you mean? I think it's I think it's not working
Yeah, I'll do a very well. I'll a son that on that really awesome thing. It's okay, but it's okay
Do you guys remember I'm wearing a soon remember what the hell we were talking about what the hell's happening right now
Yeah, we just had to take a five-hour break because the episode was getting too good. Yeah, we just had too much of the best
Yeah, we got a call from the president. He said pump the brakes. Yeah, he said you guys are being so mean
He said then the news is gonna ignore the fact that this is my last day cuz you guys are doing too good of an episode
right now that's all CNN is gonna talk about. Podcast about Liz may have done the most evil
episode yet. Folks the evil sorcerer being audited bit is too good. People are telling
people are saying everyone knows it's too good. People are tattletaling on them. People
are leaving time out. People are leaving time out. People are leaving time out they're being
emboldened by our podcast. They're not doing their homework. They're people becoming evil
we love them they're beautiful evil people. We folks we love the people who are standing
up to the substitute teachers okay? We love these people. They're calling the substitute
teacher gay. That job is a joke. How many times can I see "I'm just a bill"? I know what happens
to it. Folks, they're making us watch Rudolph in class. It's a kids movie. I've already
seen it. Why is my Trump impression just a gay guy? You might have to ask him that one.
Oh my god, it's really funny. It's so funny to imagine like whenever like a big decision is going on in the White House
So just like the AIDS just wheeling in a TV for Trump just well, they're like everyone else is talking
Yeah, it's like you can watch like yeah. Yes schoolhouse rock. Yeah, he's watching the the Eve Evo
Super Smash Brothers tournament. Yeah. Yeah, he's a big fan of fighting games. Yeah, they're giving him
they're giving him an unplugged keyboard to type in Twitch chat he doesn't know
it's unplugged. By the way if anybody has my phone number and keeps calling me
every two minutes I had to turn my phone off because of recording please if
you're gonna call me don't if I answer which I don't answer most of them but if I do answer
don't just say I'm sorry and then hang up. You have to tell the fans of that
Fitz that streamer that leaked your number. That guy sounds to me like that
person who called you is a pussy. I got three calls last night in a row and I
just answered all of them it was like 2 in the morning and I was watching girls
and I was just like you know I'll answer a few of these whatever I answered the
first one the guy goes oh I'm just I just and then hung up the second one I
said hello immediately hung up and then the third guy I answer I say hello and
he goes I'm sorry and then hung up. If you're gonna call me can you just write
Oh my god. Just write something funny to tell me. Leave me a funny voicemail. Don't just
puss out dude. Come on. What is wrong with you? Yeah. Threaten my life. There's so many
people. Tell me you're gonna kill me. Six thousand people saw your phone number and
they're calling just to just to be anxious on the phone. Yeah. What is wrong with you
dude? I'm so sorry. Did I curse you instead? Back in my day prank, I mean prank calls were
just vicious dude. This is prank yankers era. Back in the 80s you'd get a random phone call you hear a guy on the
other end going "huh huh huh" yeah nowadays you get a random phone call you hear someone on the other
end going "huh huh huh huh" yeah am i right? mm-hmm yeah nowadays people just say i'm sorry to hang up it used
- It used to be you get a prank phone call,
they say, "Wazzup!"
- Yeah, that's right.
That's right, then you get a beer together.
- That's right.
- Prank calls used to lead to something nice.
Now it's just 'cause of COVID-19,
everyone's afraid to leave their house.
- Yeah.
Hey buddy, you don't have to social distance on the phone.
- Exactly.
- You can ask me about my penis.
Just saying, dude.
It's just absurd what these people,
what these kids expect from me.
- It's sad, it's honestly sad.
- It's honestly sad.
These people, these 6,000 people got such a layup.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Yeah.
- You can literally say anything.
You could just make a, you could fart into the phone.
- You could, if you fart into my phone.
- That would be a good one.
That would be so funny if you leave six fart voicemails.
- Everyone who had Caleb's number called him
and just started farting into the phone.
That would be really funny.
- 'Cause I actually have a very sympathetic sense of smell.
- You're a smell path.
- Yeah, so if you fart, I'm gonna imagine what it smells like
and you might make me vomit, which might be kind of cool.
- That'd be such a cool power. - I'm gonna vomit
over the phone.
- You can smell farts that you hear, like on TV and stuff.
(laughing)
- That's my only X-Men mutation.
- My grandma, when my grandma sees a fart on TV,
or a burp, she does go, "Ugh!"
(laughing)
It's like, you're not smelling it.
- Yeah.
- They're through, there's a window between you guys.
You can't smell that fart.
- Yeah, but what if the window opens?
I haven't taught her how to do that with the TV.
I taught my grandma how to open the TV.
Yeah, and pick out all her favorite characters.
It's so annoying, Scrappy Doo's at my house now.
Scrappy Doo as Mr. Bean.
She took out the entire cast of Days of Our Lives, but they're literally, they're six
inches tall, because that's how big, she has a very small TV.
Yeah, she's using one of those hand-cranked TVs that you use for emergencies.
with it with a stationary bike attached yeah yeah and now now the cast of the
days of our lives are running around my house and building little so stuff to my
grandmother how it's so strange the the TV soap but like they the soap opera
actors just kind of like switch out with every show like someone who's on days of
our lives can go into like all my children or General Hospital but they're
different characters or they're the same characters and sometimes the shows on
different channels. Soap operas are so sick dude. It's so weird. It's so funny. My
grandma who is basically at this point almost senile she would spend a lot of
our time of our at our house like last year we're just watching soap operas and
she would she would act like I was really stupid for not understand like
I mean someone would be like I'll be like oh we have to like we have to get that
that secret entry from her diary and I was like oh what's in the diary just like
and make conversation he's like the antidote I watched I watched soap operas
with my mom growing up so I I kept intricate I kept details I remember yeah
you know all this shit well knowing you were in cyclopedic media brain yeah you
will always know the specifics of the I haven't I haven't watched no I watched
all my children in general hospital and I can't all my children I can't how many
children does this motherfucker have I watched general hospital with my mom
because the voice actor for cloud strife was on it cool like zombie outbreak
shit on there's something a Smith was on an episode there's something soap operas
that are like so they have like demons and shit Stephen Smith was yeah well I'll
find that I'll find there's one that someone was that uh that I would that I
was seeing clips of a while ago where there's like a portal to hell or
something yo I think he was on all my children Stephen a Smith and there's a
there's a really funny clip of him talking to Sonny Corinthos and he's like
you're being surveillanced I love Stephen a I gotta look that up speaking
of soap operas we have a we have kind of a TV centric oh yeah today oh you're
right dude I know he's been episode ever let's go hold on hold on let's hold on
let's wait let's wait for the list let's hear what you're gonna say here he's
been on Alma he's been on general hospital since 2016 well I was right
that was worth it okay let's do the list I'm kind of dressed like Stephen a Smith
yeah you are yeah you said yeah you are like I said you were dressed as yeah you
are Smith yeah you are that's a bug you get neat out of your brain yeah you are
close the page Patrick no I'm reading nothing interesting is gonna come out of
this you got so excited just to tell us the Steven the year that Stephen a
Smith started being on General Hospital I know you're not gonna find anything
here nothing is interesting nobody's gonna care about anything that you find
in the next five minutes. Please, for the love of God, Patrick, this is supposed to be the
best episode ever. I buttoned up everything so that my jacket gets real tight and all
the blood hits my brain. I'm really smart. So please, give us a chance, please.
Close it. I'm on a different window.
You're on Facebook.
Go to the list.
I'm on the list.
Okay.
Oh yeah? Then who's the list spy if you're on the list?
Sam Cleel.
(laughing)
- His name's Sam Cleel?
- Sam Cleel, yep.
I saw that and I just wanted to hear Patrick say it.
- Got a bust ass name, dude.
That's horrible.
- Yeah.
I clicked on his profile.
This is Buzzfeed, by the way.
I clicked on his profile and it just says,
"Sam is a content producer based in London."
Pretty cool.
- I don't believe it.
- He doesn't follow me on Twitter.
- Oh my God, he's rude.
This is, "People are sharing the most bizarre fan theories.
they've ever heard about a TV show or movie. You should finish reading How to
Read a Book. Well I need to read How to Read a Website. It's a different book that this guy made.
It's a different medium. Yeah. Recently we asked members of the BuzzFeed community about their
favorite weird movie and TV fan theories. Here are some of the best suggestions.
Number one, Dr. Heinz Doofenshmirtz is Phineas's father in Phineas and Ferb. Don't believe it.
there's no way he's evil he's evil and phineas is silly
mm-hmm those are opposite sense dude those are opposite on
on dnd alignment chart the thing is i guess they both have a kind of a
triangular head yeah but so does so does uh hey arnold
so maybe he's hey oh he could be hey arnold's dad too so does triangle head
from uh silent hill that's true resident evil
whichever one that's yeah so does crazy head from yeah
from day Z.
- True, yeah.
So I don't know, I don't think this one holds a lot of water.
- I mean, there are a lot of triangle people out there.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, that's true.
- I knew a guy whose head was shaped like a triangle
and we called him triangle head.
- Is that true?
- Yeah.
- Was he mean?
- No.
- He was nice and so he didn't deserve it
and you're a bully? - He wasn't nice
but he wasn't mean.
- He was kind of just, nah, he was kind of nothing.
He was annoying and you called him triangle head?
- Yeah, you heard me.
Was it annoying that his head was a triangle?
No, that didn't really have anything to do...
He...
One time he farted really loud in class.
That's one memory I have.
That's Savage, actually.
Anything else?
Yeah, I don't have many memories of him besides the shape of his head and his name.
Did you guys ever know those kids who had like a perfectly square head?
Yeah, you?
I do not have a square head.
I have a basketball head.
- Oh yeah, no, no, no, no, no.
There was a kid at my school who had a very long square head.
- There was a kid that we went to college with
who had the most insane square head
I've ever seen in my entire life.
- I know who you're talking about.
I know exactly who you're talking about.
- To the point.
- As soon as you said there was a kid we went to college with
his face just entered my mind.
- Yeah, and I was like, anytime I had class with him
I would just look at his jaw.
And I would just be like, what?
Do you have like a perfectly symmetrical tumor
either side of your head that just gives you like a fucking insane square head he
got a guy say they got dropped on his head five times as a baby once he landed
on the top and then four times he landed on each side what if he's what if he's
a what if he's our biggest fan you guys he doesn't I don't think he has a square
head yeah nobody would be most insane square head anybody's ever seen yeah but
he seemed like a nice enough guy minus the square head yeah - yeah - is
horribly ugly head yeah he also he also was evil and he said he was gonna kill
everyone you know a square head yeah he also carried a bomb around oh I didn't
know that about him I take back so yeah and you were defending him Patrick Wow
take back my defense you sussed I'm now I'm now going to kill him no you would
defend you would defend Hitler if I made fun of his must I would you would you
would defend Hitler if he had a square head I would defend him you know what maybe I'm
sympathetic cuz my head's kind of square you you don't have a square head you
have a big head I do have a big head this guy had a big-ass square head so he
well I have to defend him cuz what if I'm next you are next yeah what if I'm
next hey man big head that's what we're calling you now big head what's going on
come on you guys big ass head you have but you have smaller heads than me I can
crush your head with mine no how do you like that heads very soft I wouldn't
allow that to happen my head is not soft my head I think your head is extremely
soft look at my shirt literally you drink just like corrosive energy drinks every
day of your life it's gonna no I'm gonna try your skull to mush do I stop doing
doing that damage is done no yeah it's not getting any harder damage has done
anything to me did you escape where you probably have like five holes in your
skull from all the bullets cuz skateboarders are thugs skateboarders are
dirty punks and thugs they need to be put in jail number two Bob's burgers is
about Bob coping with the death of his family listen to this one this is a
doozy dude Linda died and Bob bought the place next to where they held her
funeral the three accidents in the opening credits are how each of his
children died Louise died in a fire Jean is bitten by a rat and dies of an
infection and Tina is crushed by a falling utility pole each time Bob
reopens he goes a little crazier and the show is all about his wishful
hallucinations that would rule if there was like a functioning fast-food
restaurant run by a guy who's just constantly talking to people who aren't
there and shit. He's like, "Ah, but, uh, Luis, I need you to clean this stove."
"Oh, this guy's pretty fucking funny."
"Lynn, Lynn, stop singing a musical song." "Hey,
Tina, don't say about a butt anymore." Yeah, and you're just sitting there
eating a burger and you're like, "This guy might be the biggest burger genius
who's ever lived." "This guy's so smart." He was like a tortured soul
artist, you know what I mean? "Oh, my family's so crazy."
He says that to you every time you walk in.
My family's so silly.
Sorry, my crazy family.
My crazy family's here doing some weirdo shit.
Ah, yeah.
My crazy family.
Sorry, my crazy family's here doing some weirdo shit.
There we go, Pat got it first.
Pat got it.
Nice, dude.
It took a while.
We got a lot of misses in there.
Gene, I need you to help me wipe my ass.
there we go all right so you're overhearing that a guy taught you
thinking maybe that since there's a counter you're like maybe he's talking
like a really short little baby there's a bunch of short people that I don't see
a tiny guy to wipe his ass yeah and then he says this one's a musical episode and
you're like all right you know we're gonna do a cute cool musical we're gonna
do a musical in a little bit. Me and my wife. We're gonna do a weird musical. Yeah it's a
broom with a hamburger for a face. Yeah they're all gonna they're all gonna wipe
my ass when I'm done. Number three in Beauty and the Beast the Enchantress. I
don't care about this. Yeah I don't know anything about Beauty and the Beast.
Riverdale don't care. Yeah don't care. Alright number five Jar Jar Binks is a
a Sith Lord this one I really liked when I first heard it yeah when I first heard
this one I was like 15 year old brother told me this but he couldn't be he
couldn't be a Sith Lord though because there can only be two right but but he
has red eyes in the photo exactly good point no but the the let me let me just
read the thing it said he appears to be a bumbling idiot but somehow everything
works out for him the battle droids chasing him always end up destroyed and
takes out a battle tank nobody seems to really like him and yet he somehow gets
elected to be a senator which hints at some Jedi mind control this no they got
the wrong person the wrong commenter commented this okay so get so lay out
your case against Jar Jar Binks the people versus Jar Jar Binks weird kind
of weird that's all you have yeah that's all you have for me I really I teed you
up so perfectly for the one thing that you know stuff about.
I think he looks like a bunny rabbit. Yeah, he does actually. I think my fan theory is
he might be the Easter Bunny for the Star Wars universe. Oh, shit. I like Easter Bunnies.
You can't have my theory. I'm expanding upon yours. No, you can't expand. It's my, I copyright.
Copyright. I just copyrighted it. I'm going to sue you if you say anything else about
in a suit I do think that is legally it is copyrighted and I forgot the actual
Jar Jar Theory. Do you think Jar Jar Binks looks like the Easter Bunny? No I think he
looks like Cameron I think he looks and talks like Cameron. Oh shit! Pat copyright
that. Copyright. I said it first. Cam got it. No I said it first. No you fucking didn't.
I said it first. We're gonna look back at the audio and I'm gonna be correct. I clearly said it first.
- Uh-uh, this is another, okay, speaking of Star Wars,
this is a Greedo shot first situation, and I'm Greedo.
- Copyright.
- No!
(laughing)
- You just got double copyrighted.
- Fuck, dude, you owe me two trillion dollars.
- No, I don't.
That's copyright.
- Listen, Pat, I'm looking at the law right now.
- Cameron owes me two million dollars copyright.
- It says the copyright holder--
- Copyright.
- Sets the terms of--
- Copyright, just copyright what you said.
- What?
- Mm-hmm.
- What I'm saying?
- Yeah, copyright.
- You can't copyright me, I have a suit on.
- Copyright.
- I just copyrighted your suit.
- You can't, I--
- And you know what?
I'm sending out DMCA. - Can I just take it off now?
- I've been sending DMCA's this whole time.
- Hey Patrick, I'm acquiring you
so we can combine our copyrights
and work against Caleb. - Yeah, okay, all right.
Let's send Caleb some DMCA's right now.
- All right, we're sending Caleb cease and desist.
- I'm gonna read the law pretty soon.
- No, you're gonna get DMCA'd by us.
- Nope, no. - You're copywritten.
- I will, no.
I'm going to-- - I just copyrighted you.
- I will infringe on every copyright you ever do
for the rest of your life.
you're legally saying this yeah look at this you're legally saying this I just
infringed on your copyright we just got him we just got him shut up dude I got a
big guy for years you're done you're done you're you're going to the chair
and that's not right that's copyright collar check who's got a collar on their
shirt fucking me okay me nope a cop no a collared you sure see a collar right
here my shirt collar and his shirt more colorful his shirts more color than
yours he's got a tie dye on it I don't need color I want collar you don't like
the colors what are you wearing who's wearing golf attire
you're wearing what did you say right now Caleb's I'm something copyright
people can't just wait you just copyrighted a racist phrase so you
can't be right out as your ideal ideal copyright this is too easy I'm in your
head dude no you're not getting my head cuz I ate you you've been defeated by
the jaws of justice you haven't defeated me you're both going to prison for a
thousand years you're going to prison first you're going to the same prison as
Bill Cosby and Harvey Weinstein they're putting you in a cell with those two
guys yeah you're gonna have the phantom zone you promise I promise yeah you're
going to one of those fancy VR prisons okay mm-hmm this actually doesn't sound
that bad there's no beat saber oh fuck yep no beat saber no no super hot VR no
half-life what about what about thumper thumper is all you get cool fine ah
download mom I was hoping you guys hated rhythm games fuck mm-hmm
number six Spencer for my Carly is actually crazy Steve from Drake and Josh
I don't care about this one. I'm looking at the photographical evidence. Crazy Steve has
short hair. Yeah, Crazy Steve has a buzz cut, Spencer has long hair, who cares.
Yeah, your honor. They're wearing different shirts. Your honor, your honor.
It's not the same picture. Yeah, your honor. To be quite frank, who gives a crap on a stick?
Who cares? Absolutely nobody. So what, your honor? So what? And that's how they got OJ off. Yeah.
They said, "You know what? Who cares? What are we doing here?"
This is just kind of pissing me off. We should all be outside playing soccer on that field.
What happened to lunch? We could all be at lunch right now.
Instead we're in this damn room. I'm sitting on... what am I, in church?
I'm sitting on this damn pew, right? I'm dressed like a fucking...
Pee-you is what I'm saying. Pee-you.
What's that crazy wig you're wearing, man?
Yeah, why are you wearing that wig? Are you a girl?
if you're a girl then you can stay here but if you're a boy you probably need to let my man off
all right i and then the judge goes okay i move that all girls stay in here and all the boys go
out to play and be and be cool that's right the girls have to stay in and figure out the case
and then the girls tried to figure out the case but guess what they broke a nail and then these
who are these guys over here the what is it the the people all sitting in a group is it are these
your boyfriends your honor are these your you have 12 angry boyfriends is your 12 boyfriends
Are you gonna marry each and every one of them and give them beautiful kisses on their lips?
Are you gonna kiss these guys?
Are you gonna kiss them?
The more that you sit here and agree with them, the more it seems like they're your boyfriends.
Hey, uh, your honor, why is that chair you're sitting in so tall?
Is there like a guy under there doing something to you?
Yeah, sorry, do you need like a high chair like a baby?
Are you a baby?
Do you have a freak touching you?
Yeah, is there a freak hidden in your quarters that you touch?
Your honor, I think you have a slave.
Your honor, do you live in a castle?
I just wanna know.
yes or no question your honor your honor what planet would you go to to get more
stupider answer correct your honor the Kurgan versus the predator who you got
do you got straight up the current versus the predator the Kurgan oh I
thought you said the curd your honor have you ever eaten a turd I rest my case I
I rest my case.
Your honor, does your mom know you're gay?
Your honor, have you seen the clown who hides from the guy who is the clown who from the clown who hides from gay clowns?
Have you heard of a gay clown before?
We got him!
Cause I have. I think I'm looking at one.
And everyone here in this court has. Except you. Why is that?
Hmm. What is that?
Your honor, one out of...
It seems like one of us here hasn't done his research.
Your Honor, according to statistics, one out of every
one, two, three, four, five, six, fifty people is gay.
And I think the 49 of us in here aren't gay, so...
Your Honor, your shoe is untied and I'd like to call for a mistrial.
Your Honor, you're stuck with it. No further questions.
Your Honor, you just lost the game. Your Honor, guess what?
I motion for a mistrial as obviously the judge is in such dire
emotions due to losing the game that he cannot go any further in this
trial. OJ let's go fucking party baby.
Panama! Panama!
number seven none of the Rugrats actually exist the other cartoons yeah Sam
Cleo I'm stupid duh number eight an unbreakable Kimmy
Schmidt no thank you nope are the unbreakable clitty-clit
no not the crack who knows where it is yeah
the unfindable clitty clit. It's invisible!
It's like a fucking needle point. That thing don't exist.
Yeah. It's like finding a piece of hay in a haystack.
There's too many of them. Too many clitty clitty in there.
That's the problem. Yeah. Listen, I could literally find it right now.
This thing is covered in clits. I can't find anything.
My problem is that I've got homing vision and I can see it right now.
I know exactly where it is but I can also see every other clit in the world
world so it's really hard to focus and find where I want.
Yeah I don't I don't I've not seen maybe but two episodes of that show so I do not understand
I do not understand what this means as far as Lily and his Titus's biological mother.
Number nine.
Sounds like it could be right.
Frozen, Tangled, and the Little Mermaid are all interrelated don't care.
They're interrelated.
Don't care.
Oh like twins?
In the first movie we see Rapunzel and Flynn attend Queen Elsa's coronation and we also learn the death of Anna and Elsa parents
aboard a sub to shank the shit
- and it's a senator to the oral science. Yeah, I don't care about that
Yeah, that it's hey Sam Cleo. You're writing doesn't make any fucking sense. You have to fucking dumb. Yeah
What the heck is this next one? Don't go bobo
Putting out this
What passes for journalism nowadays
A server has certain sound rights her in a town armor, and I don't even get so nervous
You just see smoke coming through a doorway in the background.
Yeah, it's like, "wellness check."
Yeah, do you see this on CNN? They're literally suggesting that Joe Biden...
Number 10, in Pretty Little Liars, Aria was actually A.
Yeah, A stupid bitch.
Her name starts with A.
Yeah, that's pretty clear to me.
Yeah.
In the first episode, Aria returns from a year of schooling abroad and the mysterious messages start soon after.
There are so many subtle hints throughout the show that she is A.
And at one point we're led to believe she has a dissociative identity.
I honestly think the writers planned for it to happen that she was A, but they scrapped it when it became too popular a theory.
Who cares?
That would suck. That would suck to be like writing a show and people just first episode guess exactly what you're gonna do.
yeah you're like ah fuck never I guess a sponge bob and yeah it's so funny to
like to like change it to to be like that like that's what they did with Star
Wars too many people muster like I think that's what they said is that too many
people figured out like all the they were like some of the fan theories were
better than what we were coming up with so we had to like adapt like it's like
just yeah just something like this some of the some of the Snoke stuff I think
didn't he just like die and never yeah he turned out he was just like a Palpatine
clone he's just like a guy that yeah my neighbors doing power bombs upstairs by
the way power bombs they're just like slamming against the ground right now
they're slamming for them dude neighbors crashes through the ceiling you got a
bunch of kangaroos above you man yeah Cameron's upside down Australia it's
interesting you see you would suggest they're having sex Caleb because they
actually it's children that live up there. Just children? Yep, only children. I don't
think that's possible. Did you hear that one? Oh my god. Yeah, I heard that one. I think
someone just fell over. Uh oh, someone just fell over upstairs. Number 11, Snowpiercer
is the sequel to Willy Wonka and the Chocolate Factory. The hell it is. Yeah, and Parasite
the sequel to Snowpiercer and anime I think is the sequel to Parasite. I've
never seen I've never seen Snowpiercer. I don't like Super Stupid. I think it's
really bad. I think people are blinded by his other good movies and they think
it's good but it's bad. I watched it I watched it once a long time ago and I was
like this is bad and then I watched it again because I was like maybe I was
wrong and I was like nope it's bad. He's barely even Captain America in that
movie he doesn't do any more shield shit he doesn't have a part of that movie is
there's a thing like they eat they eat like protein bars or like gel bars or
whatever and they also like they're like it's all about poverty or whatever and
their shit where they like they're like we had to like eat a child to stay alive
and then they find out that the protein bars they've been eating are made out of
bugs and they're all like oh my god yeah did you know that movie is actually
about school yeah it's all big it's a teacher that shoots at them with a
machine gun it's I mean it couldn't be more obvious the thing yes that you know
that movies about sports whoa yeah it's secretly about sports
that was about a big train yeah that's how they get nerds to watch movies about
sports yeah it's pretty cool they get a big Erica in it a Korean guy to make it
it. What I love about it is that the train is almost like its own character though. Yeah
it's kind of like the train plays itself. It's just like how New York City, New York City's
a character in it too. It's like yeah, New York City. LA is also a character in that
movie. There's a bunch of cities as they drive by them you're like wow that's like almost
a character to me, that city that you can see. And also they do drive the train. It
has wheels, it's just a big car. Number 12, season, I don't care, they're skipping that
- Just read it. - Just read it.
- Seasons four to six of Glee
were a figment of Tina Cohen Chang's Met, don't care.
- You love that? - Don't care.
I hate Glee. - I had a dream
that the Mohawk guy was a pedophile.
- Oh, your dream came true.
- What the hell?
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- I wished that he would be a pedophile on a star.
- And kill himself.
Didn't he just like immediately kill himself
when he was gonna go to jail?
- No, I think he waited a bit
and then once he was guilty, he did it.
yeah that's what i mean
yet was going to go to jail he was like
all right well give my best shot
yet that's it
dancing my way out of this one
so i have a look at the trial is that the newsletters
where
the
that that choice is that i have a man that i have a good a lot of the park
i wonder why
uh...
Number 13. He started singing Kyle's Mom is a Bitch from South Park and it didn't...
he thought that would let them... he thought that would let them off but didn't work. Number 13.
Ross lost custody of Ben and Friends. Good, I hope he dies. What the... Which one? Both.
I don't think I've ever seen... I don't know anything about Friends, yeah. I just know the
theme song. I've seen one or two episodes of Friends. I don't like it. I fucking hate that show.
Ross never sees his son Ben in the later season of Friends.
No, people love Friends.
I feel like Friends is the one, Friends was like the office but obviously it came before
it so it's more time for people to get mad about it.
Yeah, well the office is also the office for Gen X people so I don't know.
Yeah, but Friends is what-
This is one of the worst conversations we've ever had on this show.
No, it's not. It's the best episode ever.
It's the best episode ever, Caleb, you fucking moron.
I can't believe you would say that.
The office is like South Park.
Mm-hmm.
But white.
The office is like the South Park of Simpsons.
The office is white South Park.
Harry Piter is...
Yeah, just bail on that one.
That's all we know.
I mean, the Harry Piter is...
Kind of like a spider.
That was fascinating.
Harry Piter is kind of like a spider.
I mean, the Harry Piter is kind of like a spider.
kind of like a spider. Harry Potter in the book he never drinks water yeah Harry
Potter be sure to drink some water Harry Potter don't be a squatter get out of my
house. Get out of my damn house. Yeah you think you can live in the attic I don't think so I
got a fire axe down here and I'm coming up the stairs oh no wait you like that
Harry Potter you like living under the stairs nah uh no way I'm gonna come after you with this big
hammer like Paul Bunyan I'm gonna look giant to you that's right I'm gonna act like Johnny
Appleseed I'm gonna put stuff in you did you see they're putting Johnny Appleseed in that Trump
like uh hero's garden whatever that's pretty cool he's a hero dude he is one of the all-time heroes
he invented the apple he invented a tree what did Johnny Appleseed do he plant what do you think
he did based on his name and what we just said i think he was a doctor take a guess he was a doctor
yeah it's like patch adams yeah he didn't patch anything i think he's the reason they say the
apple a day keeps the doctor away and they call him patch adams because he was a patch to the
doctor like these like the update to a doctor oh true they added comedy to being a doctor they're
funny now they patch comedy into doctor is they just got a funny doctor now doctor ism what the
the new update doctor number best episode best episode number 14 the man
Seinfeld actually died in the last episode I believe it didn't they go to
jail or something the main characters were actually in a plane crash and died
in the last episode instead of the plane straightening out and landing safely
then the following the Good Samaritan trial was actually them being judged on
who would go to heaven who would be sent to hell Jerry Seinfeld if there's one
person in all of history who I know will go to hell it's him yeah yeah I mean
for what you annoying yeah he's just fucking annoying yeah I don't know I
don't know why you think he'd be going to hell I would I think is it because of
his belief system no I think maybe it's cuz the devil the devil wants the devil
wants to laugh the devil is getting lonely down you're like the best piano
player in the world and you were like you're a really good person and then you
die and you start getting sucked downwards and you're like and the devil
is like sorry man I just really like piano music. It's because you were playing all
that rock and roll piano Jesus Christ now you're down here. He made a deal with God.
Yeah. He did like a midseason trade. Yeah I'm gonna send
you the guy who went to hell because he farted too smelly and he's gonna prank
all the guys in heaven. Well at least we need some levity up in heaven. Yeah. We need
somebody to be a prankster. Number 15, Ty Lee from Avatar the Last Airbender is
descended from the Air Nomads. I don't know who that is. I can't believe that
people still will try and tell you with a straight face that Avatar the Last
Airbender, that you should have to watch it. Yeah. Like people, 24
year old people will look you in the eyes and say man you have to watch
Avatar the Last Airbender. It's one of the best shows ever made. Yeah. I can't
- Excuse me, watch a grown up show.
- Watch a grown up show like Cow and Chicken
or Cousin Skeeter or--
- Yeah, Barn House.
- How about you watch a show that's actually Japanese?
- Barnyard.
- Yeah, watch a Japanese show.
- Avatar is Korean.
- Yeah, no it's not.
- Yeah it is.
- It's Nickelodeon.
- It's American, what are you talking about?
- I thought, are you thinking of Snowpiercer again?
- Yes, I was thinking of Snowpiercer.
- Did you genuinely think that was Korean?
You just thought it was Korean?
- You think of Bulgogi.
- You just looked at that art and you were like,
that's Korean no I heard somewhere that it's a Korean team and an American team
worked together on it well yeah that's because they outsource their animation
to Korea probably they probably have like child slaves yeah Simpsons is Chinese by
that logic yeah that's how animation works yeah the Simpsons is a Chinese
anime you said it I'm not gonna say that you whispered it you whispered it I'm
not gonna say that it's it's technically a Chinese anime because they do have I
I think that they have like a team of people that work in China. They just send them the
script like a year in advance which makes it even more impressive that they lampoon
Trump so much. Even more impressive. More impressive than it already is because of how
funny. Well you know the way that Trump talks about China those five-year-old Chinese slave
kids are really eager to rip him a new one so they get the episodes with him done extra
past
even pretend you think that word is I was just I just want to say if we skip this
one we'll finally get to one that we care about okay number 17 the whoa number 17
the briefcase in Pulp Fiction actually contains Marcellus Wallace's soul. Can I have a
burger? Can I have a humongous French burger? I got a motherfucking burger and
I'm gonna shoot this burger out my burger gun.
Eat a burger again.
Eat a sandwich right now.
Do they have a burger where you live?
Do they have burgers in French?
How do you say what in French?
Can I have a kiss?
(laughing)
The path of the righteous man
is always a French burger.
And God said the burger would come down from heaven
And you would eat the burger.
And you would see four burgers.
My brother is John Travolta.
My brother's a burger.
We're two brothers and we're here on an assignment to kill you.
We're the burger brothers.
And I'm gonna eat your burger.
I'm gonna get my friend's burger back and I'm gonna shoot your ass.
I'm John Travolta and I'm gonna drink some of your soda to wash my burger down.
I'm the soda brother. I'm the burger brother and I'm the soda brother.
And I'm here to drink your soda and he's gonna eat your burger.
I'm gonna dance with my burger wife.
I'm doing a French dance.
Damn, I'm hungry.
Oh man!
And she died and she had a milkshake on her.
We gotta pull the-
What happened to Jed?
Jed's bread, baby.
And I'm the burger in between the bread.
In Burger City.
I gotta go to- we gotta go to- we gotta go to Quentin Tarantino's house.
I shot a burger out the car.
There's ketchup all over this damn car.
Did you bring a dead burger and put it in my car?
Is there really a burger in my car?
A dead burger?
my house it says dead burger storage
what an amazing movie. Yeah and then he just looks into the cameras burger burger burger burger burger burger
It's like he just wrote the movie to say burger
and we're the burger brothers ABC eight o'clock nine central
the whole movie's an ad for Quentin Tarantino's new show the burger brothers
Yeah, ABC and then it's a diners drive-in and dives type show
You know, he bought an old burger restaurant turned it into a fancy Quentin Tarantino
Dijon go unchanged dude. Yeah, he went unchanged. He's unchanged mustard Dijon go. Yeah
Yeah, me too. We do care about that. Yeah. Yeah, we cared about that a lot
Shot the burger brother in the chest
Oh no!
I can't believe it!
Oh fuck.
Tim Roth you better not touch this reface.
My name is Ron Zlanda, do you have a glass of milk?
I'm the third burger brother.
And I'm a Nazi!
We need a hundred Nazis to open up this burger restaurant so we can burn it down!
I need a hundred black burgers for a hundred hungry guys.
Oh fuck dude.
A fan theory states that Gwen and Tarantino puts the Burger Brothers in the
background of every film.
Oh god dude.
The Burger Brothers have done it again, dude.
Damn, looks like we're stuck in Reservoir Dogs!
I'm Mr. Burger!
I'm Mr. Mustard!
I'm Mr. Ketchup!
I'm Mr. Cheese!
I'm Mr. Lettuce!
Oh no, somebody shot Mr. Cheese in the belly!
He's got- we gotta get Mr. Cheese to the hospital!
What are you talking about?
What are you talking about, Mr. Lettuce?
We can't get him to the hospital!
left and buns on the right somebody cut off the fry cooks here oh no yeah I never
I never tip burgers I never tip at the diner that feeds me a burger okay
Let's finish this.
Speedrun this.
Number 18, all the Pixar films exist within the same universe.
Don't care.
Number 19, Agent Coulson is Captain America's son.
(gagging)
Number 20, Derek Shepard from Grey's Anatomy is still alive.
Don't.
I'm glad he's dead.
Number 21, Loki is Noob Master 69 in Avengers Endgame.
Now wait a minute, hold on.
Now hold up.
This one might be true.
That's a comment from
Sherlock Harry Potter 01. I love this because it means Loki is still alive.
Also I can't believe they killed him right after he had a major breakthrough
in his character art. You have a baby brain and you should kill yourself.
Number 22, Prue died back in season one way before her actual exit in season three of
charm don't care. Number 23, Supernatural ends how it begins. Number 24,
Jack Dawson is a time trump carrot. Number 25, Harry Potter's little gem.
here Harry Potter's little gem yeah I hate these baby brained morons who think
that like Harry Potter and Marvel are like cool like worthwhile action films
you know by the way the Burger Brothers
they saved the day it was actually it was rumored that guys know is it a
all along there's a rumor that Quentin Tarantino was gonna have a sequel he's
gonna have a movie right after Pulp Fiction and Reservoir Dogs called the
Burger Brothers starring Michael Madsen and John Travolta they were gonna reprise
their roles as the two burger brothers from Pulp Fiction and Reservoir Dogs yeah
I'm gonna eat burger I love when they say the name of the movie in the
Eat burger boy.
When he says,
"Let me take a sip of your tasty beverage to wash your burger down."
Yeah, when he, dude, when he says,
when he's, when they're in that cowboy movie and he says,
"It seems like this really is the taste I ate."
(laughter)
- That's a good spot to end it.
- Best episode ever, ladies and gentlemen.
There it is, you're welcome.
- Subscribe to us on Patreon.
Watch us on Twitch.
We play Minecraft on Twitch now.
That's what we do now.
- Stop calling me.
- Tune into the Burger Brothers.
Burger Brothers ABC 5 9 central 9 mm-hmm they got to put the news on before it
Boy