You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- You're a crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Ooh.
- Okay, say the whole thing again.
- Right about, right about now.
- Okay, so basically Patrick is,
I wanna get this out of the way.
- Okay, so here, so yeah.
- No, no.
- So Patrick is not, Patrick is not a pedophile.
- We wanna say that right at the top.
- I really, I'm not, I'm not joking.
I'm not joking, I really hate when you guys do this.
- And there's a big but here.
He wishes he was.
- No.
- He wishes he had the balls.
- I hate when you guys-- - The gumption.
- I hate when you guys-- - The absolute gall.
- I hate when you guys do this
because then we get a million fans--
- You don't like being called a pedophile?
- In the discord making those jokes.
And I don't like it. - What joke?
- I don't like it. - It's not a joke, dude.
You're not a pedophile.
You think that's a joke?
Oh, is that a joke?
- No, no, you don't, no! - For me to say you're not one?
- Fuck you, you know what you're doing.
I'm not doing anything. I don't know what I'm doing. I'm so stupid.
I'm sitting at my desk.
Yeah. I'm so stupid I have no idea what I'm doing.
Are you recording a podcast and making you a lot of money, Patrick? Is that what you hate us doing?
Did we even decide on the list? We were sending squeezy pictures to each other.
No, we did decide on the list.
Which one is it?
Don't spoil it!
Don't spoil the list.
Okay. Alright.
Just scroll up to the top of the chat. It's that easy.
It's the first one.
And don't read out loud because I know you like to do that.
Today, I went to the gym for the first time in like a month and a half.
And since then, it was about eight hours ago, since then, my balls have been completely receded
into my body.
And I don't know how to get them out.
That's a symptom of COVID.
I don't know.
I don't think so.
I don't think it's that.
I don't think that it's a symptom of COVID-19.
That's a COVID symptom.
It's not.
No.
No, it's not.
I think it's because I was lifting.
that's actually where the name COVID because it's good your your balls get
COVID by your skin. They get COVID up. I they're always COVID by my skin. So you've
always had it? I mean I have ball sack skin yeah is that so crazy? I mean it's
not crazy just means you have it. I don't. That was so fucking stupid. I think it's my
body's way of like getting ready for battle. Yeah you have like it you have you
have a condition called tortoise penis. I do not have a tortoise's penis. I think
that my yeah I think it was like lifting heavyweights my my really heavyweights
we're talking like 80s, 89 pounds. 80 grams. 80 grams, 90 grams. In high school I tried to lift
I tried to lift the I tried to lift something I realized I couldn't even lift
the bar. That's pretty bad. Yeah, I know. That's pretty bad. Yeah. I had such a weak upper body.
I don't think I could do it now, honestly. On my walk home, I like noticed him in my body
and I was like, this would be a perfect time to be like attacked or mugged or something.
Could you imagine how scary it would be to kick someone in the balls and just keep walking
towards you? They're just like completely unfazed. Just advancing. Yeah, just like a
bullet bouncing off a Superman they're just like walking towards you so slowly
mm-hmm I don't know maybe I'll keep them up there maybe I'll tape maybe see if I
tape them up there that's why you should just wear a cup at all times no I don't
need any more accessories I already have my jewelry you should get you should oh
man you should get like cameo you know that they like the red codpiece the app
and do pick up my balls on it no no no no no cameo from the 80s it was like a
they sing that word up that's like "Oh pretty ladies around the world they got
a weird thing" you know that song? No. Yeah. Well he's got the guy from cameo has
like a red he wears like these leather pants and like a big red codpiece.
It looks sick. Codpieces should come back in style. Yeah. Like a big like jewel
encrusted like armor. What's a codpiece? Like it goes on your penis. I'll give you one guess
Caleb, based on what we're talking about.
Is it a wiener holder?
Yes.
Is it some sort of sashay for your penis?
It's like an armor cup.
Wait, wait, look at this guy.
Look at this picture of this guy.
I don't want to look at this.
No, you're gonna show me a man's wiener.
No, this is what we should get into.
Okay, that's actually beast mode.
That guy looks so cool.
I mean, he looks sick.
He matched the hat to the codpiece.
have to have a fucking powerful penis to have it locked right like that. Matching the hat
to the codpiece is genius too because then a mugger is going to come up to you and go
I should kick him in the balls and get confused and try and kick you in the head. Yeah it's
like a boss battle. It's a boss battle with two. It's like eye spots. Yeah. Yeah I guess
you'd think that those would be your weak spots as a boss but not if that's a hardened
ballsack holder. If I was a boss I would paint the strongest part of my body red. That's
really good point actually yeah yeah then you've given you fool the hero yeah the
hero that is fighting you you can you can fool them into hitting your kneecap or
something what's the hardest like your penis yeah that's what you do you make
your weenie red no no no getting hit in the elbow sucks not if they pinch it
compared to your to your glowing sacred heart yeah it's a thousand damage
heroes special attack is to pinch you yeah and so what you do is you have to
The hero's a crab. Yeah, you paint your penis.
The thing we haven't said is that the hero's a crab.
Go ahead, I'm invincible, see? Try my elbow.
And then he'll pinch you and go, "Fuck, I just give up, dude."
You can take her. I'm guessing that you have a...
It's a crab princess.
His crab wife.
You guys know that video of the crab cutting the crayfish in half?
Yeah, one of the best things of all time, yeah.
Probably the coolest video ever.
Yeah, I wish that there was a when I was a kid I believed in giant crabs because my brother told me that there were giant
crabs in Japan
No, no, not like spider crabs. He told me that there were like like giant like Volkswagen beetle sized
Crabs that sometimes if you were swimming on the beach in Japan, they would walk up onto the shore and cut people in half. I
Believe it. I did for a really long time. I also thought that
Yeah, I also thought that Ron Jeremy and Tony Clifton were the same guy for a really long time.
Yeah, I wasn't a very smart kid.
You know, it's weird you said that because you said it was a Green Room and I was watching that that's I don't know how
It came up in my recommendation. So I watched it the Bo Burnham on Green Room and Ron Jeremy's in the background. Yeah that clip
Yeah, and he's on then Tony Clifton is in a different one and I think he says the n-word and they kick him out
yeah which is such a funny thing to do like that guy who's he's like trying to
carry on an Andy Kaufman's legacy and he's like I'll go to the Bo Burnham
taping of Green Room right say the n-word and get kicked out that's gonna
be so epic dude that's such swag all comedy
Bob Zmuda made like his entire autobiography about Andy is like mostly
just like fabrications like it's just mostly like oh yeah actually we started
wrestling women because we were horny yeah you know what I believe you know
what actually that was he said that he like what's the fucking guys name I
don't know if it's David Mamet or somebody who wrote something like Bob's
Muta said he was like a script he worked with somebody and would record like his
audio or audio to get dialogue for movies and it was just him going up to people
and confronting them I don't I don't remember who it is but it's like a lot
of that shit though yeah yeah he made up a ton of that shit like in the in the
man on the moon movie when a when Andy goes to a fucking wherever and gets like
crystal healing done on his cancer oh yeah that shit rules just making that up
just being like yeah also he had he had a magic a magician do his cancer he went to
Thailand to get magic cancer surgery yeah like I mean that would be cooler than
pretty much anything Andy Kaufman ever did mm-hmm but I don't think he actually
did it you guys don't think Andy Kaufman used magic at all I mean he was definitely
a sorcerer so you're backpedaling now on this no he was a laugh so he yeah he I'm
backpedaling yeah he was a sorcerer he was actually a real-life sorcerer yeah
and he cast spells on all those women. He had to take locks of their hair to use in his cult.
Exactly that's why he had to get so close to with wrestling that he stole their hair and
then he cloned them. Yep. Yep and that's how he also survived. And that's how women were created.
Yep and then he - by Andy Kaufman. His greatest prank. He uploaded his brain to Lisa Lampanelli
and that's actually him. Yeah I was making myself laugh earlier uh I was like no one's home so I
So I was like you were tickling yourself.
I was tickling with yeah.
No, I was thinking about Rod Serling just like introducing two girls one cup.
Imagine a world.
Imagine if you will two women in a Brazilian in a Brazilian home making out on the couch
when suddenly one of them stands up and squats over a cup.
What happens next will shock you.
the Twilight Zone. Just like the whole thing.
And also he like he stays in the frame for the entire
of the thing. He's just smoking his lips in the corner.
Jesus Christ. Oh Christ. I mean it's disgusting. I mean that's just wrong.
But it happens in the Twilight Zone. A world where chocolate ice cream is not always as it seems.
*laughter*
Oh fuck.
Just him in front of any of those shock videos
from 2008 is really good.
Yeah.
I love those shock videos.
I may have said this before, but it's funny that they just went from like
the first shock videos were like
people just having gay sex
and then like a couple
weeks later it was like people getting beheaded.
Yeah.
one guy and they were like these are the same thing these are so shocking.
Right because it's a gamble you go through that the what was it lolshock.com you go
through that website and it's like like walk the dinosaur was on there and walk
the dinosaur is a 3d animation of two t-rex is 69ing and then like under that
is like two guys one hammer which is just murder.
yeah yeah I just be like oh fuck I don't want to watch these shocking videos oh
the worst is like the what's that one where did she put the well there's tub
girl but then there's the other one is I feel like the worst one is one guy one
jar yeah which is that somewhere between gay sex and murder yeah it's both
violent and somehow gay. There's just one guy. I forget how does the jar break in his ass?
Does he break it himself? I think he shoots it with a gun.
He shoots the gun into his ass. Yosemite Sam style.
Yo what in the blazes?
Marmot! And he shoots himself in his ass and then the the tragically the glass
explodes yeah and it cuts his asshole up what if he's an opera singer he has the
jar in his ass and he just he had so much he was he was he had so much
pleasure at the time that he had to he didn't know what to do other than moan
opera that's yeah he's trying to hit the world's highest note did yeah well
actually the real thing is that he he had been doing it with like like beer cans
and stuff and he just had the strongest ass ever he was crumpling him up and then
he just accidentally did it with the with the glass jar. It's like kids who can eat
cigarettes at parties and then they try to eat them all but are red and then they go to the hospital. A guy at a party being like yo check this out just pulling his pants down and everyone just leaves the room.
beer bottle into his ass and for my next trick. Yeah we hired this magician for
Tyler's birthday and I god I don't even know what kind of tricks he did. Man I thought
people would like this. I learned everything I know from Mac DeMarco. I
I finished The Sopranos finally. Yeah. I finished it and I... What are you gonna do
now? I don't know. I tried watching like all the like behind the scenes stuff to
get like more of the show but I can't do it cuz James Gandolfini's real voice is
too bad. Yeah. I loved playing Tony Soprano. And to have like the coolest guy
ever have that voice is such a bummer. You've never seen In The Loop? No. I've never seen anything.
It's so fucked up when like to have that moment of clarity that you realize like every like tough guy or like soldier in a movie
Was like a theater kid. Yeah, exactly. Yeah, just being so realizing that you were like so easily fooled
Yeah, it's like the acting actually I've always thought I was impervious to acting. Yeah
Thought you were impervious to baby Yoda. I did think I was impervious to baby Yoda
Nobody nice. No, he's
His pull was too strong, but James Gandolfini, that was such a blow dude.
I was like, I could, there was points in that show where I was like,
I'd fuck this ugly fucking fat guy. And then to hear him be like,
well, to get into the role, I really had to fucking think about pizza.
Like that's such a disappointment.
I was like, I was doing, I mean, I did so, I just talked to myself today because I had nobody around
and I was doing James Gandolfini reacting to Two Girls, One Cup, like Tony Soprano.
I don't know why.
I'm thinking on the mind.
Did you watch any video today?
Maybe?
I watched Two Girls One Cup when I woke up.
I was just sitting there just like, "Whoa, look at these fucking two girls.
What are they fucking...
You're telling me they're gonna poop into a fucking cup?
Disgusting."
Okay, any other celebrities that you thought about watching Two Girls One Cup?
Jimmy Stewart.
How about John F. Kennedy?
Jimmy Stewart?
Yeah.
What did that sound like?
I don't remember.
You don't remember?
Now wait, now wait just a minute!
Wait just a minute! You don't, you...
Get away from that cup right now, ma'am!
Wait just a moment!
What are you doing?
That's not for eating, that's for the bathroom!
There we go.
Anybody else, Squidward?
Spongebob!
Spongebob, they're eating poop again.
Mr. Krabs, they're eating poop.
Mr. Krabs, Spongebob and Patrick are eating poop in the bathroom.
Arr, get ice creamy boy!
You're too easily tricked!
I'm cutting back on costs!
It's the new Krusty Krab ice cream, it's poop.
Yeah dude, a damn crappy poopy.
Oh, what the hell.
Yeah, sir.
No sir, that's nasty.
I'm trying to think about poop less.
That's my new year's resolution.
It's a little late.
Starting in March.
for that yeah from now to next March I'm gonna think about Chinese New Year
Chinese New Year was like two weeks ago that's my Chinese New Year resolution is
to think about food less well I a new year the Caleb New Year it's March 1st
uh-huh yeah is it a what animal year is this I found out the other day I'm year
of the ox I thought that was so badass this is the beetle the coolest coolest
year for me is up yeah the ox is cool ox dude ox is your coolest shit cow no it's
like a bull right what you think a bull is the cow is a girl and a boy and a
bull is a boy. I can't believe that you said that completely earnestly. No, it's a bull.
I think ox isn't that bad but I mean when you got like tiger or dragon. Dragon is great
dude it's cool that they can do a made up animal. An ox is tenacious and industrious
independable and authoritative it's crazy you just know that yeah Wow I just found
that I just found that out in my mind I don't think you would think any of those
things if you met an ox what do you mean I think you think this is a very stupid
animal smells bad yeah this is a stinky animal no no the smell the smell would
be the first thing I think about I could drive this animal off of a cliff with
peanut butter this is not a smart witty animal I do love those Chinese you can
it'll it'll be like this snake is sarcastic yeah like it's a snake you are
stupid well the snake was being sarcastic I'm sorry you're Adam and Eve
yeah yeah yeah totally don't eat the apple yeah it'll suck
oh that Apple's so bad yeah God'll definitely make you not be naked
anymore yeah ooh that's fine I'm year of the tiger I just found out oh I'm eye of
the tiger better watch out my mom told me when I was a kid she was like yeah if it
wasn't for Adam and Eve we could all just be naked I don't want that dude yes I
don't want to fucking I don't want someone to look at my fucking tootsie
roll penis yeah I don't want anybody see it like this my balls secret that I told
you guys that's mine I I have the choice whether or not to say that you know I
Between you and 8,000 people.
Exactly, yeah.
You gotta give it up for nudists, I guess.
I mean, it's crazy that somebody can be that comfortable.
Yeah, nude beaches, it is funny that nude beaches,
your idea--
And why do they only exist in France?
Because they're French or perverts.
'Cause they're fuckin', yeah, they're freaks.
What do you mean?
They also don't only exist,
I think there's some in America,
but they're private beaches.
They're like owned by freak nudists
who are like, "I wanna go here."
And--
yeah and they walk around. They're owned by like naked Waco people. Yeah, because if you own it
like you can be as nasty as you want to be on that beach. Yeah. You know what I mean?
The ATF rating a nude beach.
They would have to be nude too because how else would they sneak up on you. Exactly, they couldn't get to the beach.
Well yeah, the bouncer would stop them. Right.
I'm sorry, you're going to have to take off all this SWAT gear.
yes is a new only be about search is the guy with the biggest wiener
the only the only police officer they could take down a new disc on his
robocop
and true as he's gotten when i was a little trip and down to just be the
brain
yet you know i don't know all the metal like whether he doesn't have like the
pleading on
that's a very rare a lot of a cop
yeah
that was that was very fuckin weird in the a_t_m_s_ i want to see this boys
veins right
It did look, you know, it did look cool. I will take that back. I am backpedaling on that.
He doesn't have a penis too, like...
You should have a penis as a guy.
As a robot.
As a robot, come on.
Where else is the, where else is the oil gonna come out?
Yeah, exactly, yeah.
Yeah, when you do the funny gag where you're like peeing on something, where's the oil gonna come from?
Right.
Doesn't make any sense. You have to have like a USB stick.
You're telling me, you're telling me a guy named C-3PO don't have no peno?
It probably comes out of his mouth.
Nah.
They put a penis in C-3PO's mouth?
Well, I don't think he has a hole anywhere else.
I'll give him one.
His eyes aren't even holes.
He's got a hole in his belly.
He shows...
Why does he have an exposed midriff?
I never understood that.
Why does C-3PO show off his belly?
Because he's a gay robot.
That's like the whole thing.
His whole thing...
He doesn't have clothes though.
It's not like he has an exposed midriff.
He is plating.
He wears a suit.
Yeah, he wears metal plates.
He wears a tuxedo.
Let me see.
Are you remembering this wrong?
Are we thinking of different robots?
He wears a funny tuxedo and he's the waiter.
He's the maitre d'
I see what you mean by an exposed midriff now.
I get it.
Yeah.
That is weird.
Why does he have that?
Yeah, there's no reason for that.
Show off the abs dude.
I guess it's so he can bend over for R2D2 if you know what I'm saying.
Oh shit.
You did not just say that.
Oh hell nah, but you're not wrong though.
uh... although but you're not wrong though
i was a the droids in the in the mandalorian big downgrade from the
probably don't you know like the idea
i don't know what that means idealized the one specific one that's in the
ideas
that the class the bounty droid that like spins around and shoots
yeah i was yeah i was kinda cool yeah
those are so those are based on the one that's voiced by richard i a lot a
yeah i would have a right now it's the i have a lot to stand
I
on
and the devil yeah yeah fucking bizarre episode so weird that's right is that
- not as a not I will watch the rest of it there's like out of all the
characters have introduced so far we're gonna bring bill burr back you're the
one who needs more screen time you know they definitely got along with that
brick brick house lady pretty well oh yeah I know dude they were fucking
chilling they were both smoking cigars yeah blowjobs they were talking in the
green room just like yeah comics I bet she has a bigger clit than his penis
what yeah I bet she has a big extendo clit seriously she got a banana clit
don't say that she does did damn I was like I'm looking at pictures from that
episode I forgot they had like a I had like Rick Rubin we started talking about
droids and I just got hyper focused on droids yeah I know I should know better
yeah we've been doing this too long for me to realize like I should not you
mentioned you mentioned what like what droid Richard I a wad a plays and then I
was like oh yeah that's like that's the same one as Zuck is you should never
bring up like the 15th most important part of a movie that Patrick is seen
because that is he will talk about that for an hour completely uninterrupted
it's fucking crazy it's such a bizarre skill that you have and you memorized
all of them you have an encyclopedia of things that nobody except you cares about
and you tap into it you go into a Sherlock Holmes mind palace do you think
about like like well Artie Bucco's restaurant yeah the menu is actually not
technically an Italian restaurant you just know all this weird stupid shit
mm-hmm yeah and it's why I hate you so much you don't hate me you're right how
could I hate that's you know look at that dude oh my god you don't hate me
you are so pretty right now please say you don't hate me I don't hate you oh
yeah oh I despise you
from the prison heist episode and it's so funny that you didn't like that I
I loved that. I hated it dude. The Clancy Brown Satan, it's like he's also just like fat.
Yeah, so, no, I was just, dude, I fucking caught myself about to explain why he looks
like that. He looks like that because he's played by Clancy Brown. I, oh man, I was about
to explain like, oh well that's a race from the Cantina in episode 4. Yeah, you were about
to but you didn't do anything about episode 4 god yeah I just didn't like
that cuz it may at least make Bill Burr fucking do a voice yeah like don't make
it just he's just doing this like I'm just expecting him Boston yeah like they
don't he does it like every other character they introduce in that show is
like oh this person has like some like really cool trait about them and Bill
Burr's is just like oh he has a robot gun on his back I kept expecting to be like
like talk about like traffic or something in the middle of it you know what I mean
but I got fucking socks tickets what are you doing
he's just walking he should he they should have fucking just put him on
tattooing and let him walk around to just comment on everybody yeah yeah
walking around oh yeah like that like that Hampton Beach yeah exactly yeah we
got two fucking droids here yeah I was fucking wado I'll say it women shouldn't
Jedi I'll say it I don't trust Toydarians I don't know why I can say
that I'm married to one
my fucking kids half Toydarian yeah whatever look I tried I tried Jedi mind
tricks on my kids it didn't work yeah I arian daughter's a fucking fucking cunt or
something I don't know one of those fucking stand-up sitcom shows about the
Star Wars universe yeah like they should make the fucking like a Louis Holmes one
yeah like yeah can you imagine it could be it could still be called crashing
right but it's about their crashing spaceships yeah I just had a heart
attack that's so pretty Wow it's so pretty
it's crazy crashes a Corellian Corvette or something and then I'm homeless now I
gotta do I don't think he like crashes his car in the show no no no we're
talking about spaceships yeah you're right you're right I'm sorry don't
fucking don't lose the vision of this goddamn show all right it's a really
good idea for a show. Okay so Pete Holmes, everybody's favorite leading man. Yep.
He's a Gungan too. Perfect yeah. That makes perfect sense.
Mm-hmm. He has a Gungan attitude. He kind of is real-life Jar Jar Binks.
Yeah. Just like everybody hates him just because of the way he talks. Yeah and
And then he does stand-up comedy in different places.
In the different cantinas.
I gotta go do five minutes on Dantooine. Can you guys give me a ride?
He gets a ride all the way to Dantooine to do five minutes.
Yeah.
Yeah, likely story, buddy.
He's like, "Oh, there's gonna be some agents."
What is this Pete Holmes voice I'm doing?
I don't think I've ever seen or seen Pete Holmes or heard him talk ever once in my life.
He looks like...
looks like John Ritter's son he kind of looks like white Slimer give you a
approximation but like seven feet tall right it's really a terrifying floating
white yeah yes like slimers entire body is like Pete Holmes his head okay yeah
like the whole like the shape and the features like that's kind of his thing
he's also always drooling and he loves watching people fuck his wife or
something is that him or I thought that was Thomas Middleditch they're all into
that dude all those fucking improv freaks love fucking having people fuck their
wives it's a scene exactly yeah I'm throwing out suggestions the whole you're
right that's a good boy toothbrush yeah and the guy runs to the bathroom and
grabs the toothbrush thumb and her ass go for it yeah the guys like can we not
have inappropriate suggestions please you're being a bad partner right now
you're being a really bad right so they're doing other just really trying to
do a see ya yeah oh hey I saw you were you're eating pussy mind if I join
right across the stage like I hate disgusting people me I hate people who
have sex differently than me. What's this list? This list is 100 fright, 100, sorry,
100 plus frighteningly badass nicknames for gangsters on this is find
nicknames.com. This is by the editorial team. They do a, this is like, they're
sort of like a like a spotlight type, like team of the best people for nicknames.
They work together in an office on one project at a time and this is the, this
This is the result of like 15 or 20 years of work on gangster nicknames.
This is such a good website.
So I'm just scrolling around here.
First of all, at the bottom of their page, like where the copyright would usually be,
they have a little paragraph that says "Responsible usage.
Nicknames can be used in several positive ways.
Similarly, nicknames can be used as a negative tool.
While there are some outrightly offensive terms, we have found that with nicknames,
context matters.
So, we encourage you to be responsible in using the nicknames found on our website.
use nicknames as a tool to hurt others I mean that's a that's a fair warning I
feel like I also just a list on this website it's 40 plus witty nicknames for
guys with one testicle wait I wonder if there's nicknames for Caleb dude 30 plus
popular nicknames for Caleb I've always wanted a nickname well we're not doing
that one we could see what these are here really uh
Sea Dog, Sea Man, Sea Bug, Sea Bear, Kaby, Kaby, Kaby Baby, Klayb, K-Bop, Kaylee, Kaka,
Kalobs, Kale Baby, Kale Baby, Lebs, do not call me Lebs, Kalobs, Kalebs,
I
Searching this
Looking up. I'm gonna look up Pat. This is I'm looking at you right now
Yep, I I fucking knew I knew P Diddy would be on there. Yeah, I've been called P Diddy my entire life by bad
Diddy my entire life I have I have by man is like my music managers at
group I change it I change it every year because I'm sick of the name of course
getting called that going puffy I win these nicknames are insane listen to the
I'm just gonna run through these really fast just listen to these in a row
trick slash tricky Pat man patty boo maverick cutie Pat pat arena Rick on
crabby Patty P Diddy Pac-man three three three yeah it's a nickname for Patrick
pulled from try in the name because wow dude these are I mean again I'm not
gonna I'm not gonna argue with the experts here pate what the fuck is pate
pate from now on patch I mean we use that one already well when you search
Cameron the first result is 30 plus ideal nicknames for Cameron second result is a
hundred plus creative nicknames for tall people.
Whoa.
No.
Good for you.
You're making that up.
You edited the HTML code.
I didn't edit anything.
You searched it yourself right now.
You have inspected the element and you have hacked it.
You guys don't want to hear my nicknames.
That's fine.
Let's get into this fucking game series.
No, don't care about your nicknames.
Well, now I actually do want to hear Cameron's.
No, it's okay.
I knew that my friends didn't care about me.
We can just move to the list.
No, I, hold on, because I'm sick of calling you Cameron.
Yeah.
That's right.
There's nothing else you call me.
Ron.
Ron, dude.
Ron. Ron! That's my dad's name.
Cams, CM, CM Ron.
CM Ron. Cammy.
Camster, Camo, Camalicious, Cammy Bear, Cammy Cakes, Cam Ronnie. Camalicious might be good dude.
Camren, Camerone, Shrimp, Sea Dog,
Cameroon. That's his country? A fun nickname for Cameron inspired by the African country Cameroon.
Oh, that's all you dude. What's up Cameroon?
Yeah, what's up? Camsy a cool screen name for anyone named Cameron. I'm gonna put that on right now
Yeah, can't camazing. Oh
Okay, creative name for an amazing friend named Cameron. That's perfect for me
webcam
Caleb that's what I'm looking at. Yeah. Oh, oh shit
Okay. Now that I've been owned I would like to start the list instead of talking about me not having a webcam
Okay, go ahead.
Do you need a list of nicknames for gangsters and gang members?
Then you would find this article useful.
Growing up, grandma used to say to me and my cousin, "Once the other gang members give
you a nickname, there is no getting out."
This was her funny way of warning us about the dangers of joining a gang, but she was
onto something.
"Once you have risen to a level where the other gang members have a nickname for you,
There's no getting out because for most gangs, death is the only ticket out of the gang.
That's a link.
In this article...
The phrase "death is the only ticket out of the gang" links to a 404 on missouristate.edu.
What?
In this article, we share a list of badass nicknames for gangsters.
These hood nicknames have been compiled from information available on popular gangs around
the world.
So they're not fictional names.
People actually answer these names.
- Definition of a gang. - Never, never,
ever yell any of these names out in public.
- Someone might think you're a gangster
and then they might let you rob them.
- Well, it might be somebody's gang name.
- Somebody-- - That's a good point.
- My friend growing up told me not to say,
I think I called someone Whitey
and they said not to say that
because Whitey Bulger could be around.
- He could, dude.
They didn't know where he was for a long time.
- Yeah, no, this was in like 2004.
- He could have been around,
he could have killed you for that.
somebody say my name yeah why behind the swing set that we were on yeah hey you
guys need me you need to hire me for something yeah he's like Beetlejuice
dude this is definition of a gangster there are a few kinds of gangsters the
dictionary definition is a catch-all description of them though I'm not gonna
read that yeah of course if you think about it there are as many different
kinds of gangsters as there are stars in the sky this is so beautiful this is so
mystical and when I say they are not nice people it's the understatement of the
millennium did you know that there are 1.4 million gangsters in the u.s. 33,000
gangs and these gangs commit 48% of violent crime like the idea that that'd
be like a question on the census are you a gangster it's not a funny subject but
just so we don't all start crying about it can you imagine how many nicknames
there are for gangsters? Okay so now this is the different types. That's my guess. I guess a hundred
or or plus. A hundred plus yeah. All right now let's take a look at the biggest gangs around the world
and the nicknames for gang members associated with these groups. Here's the first one is Mafia and
the the thing says the the blurb here says first of all the oldest and baddest the mafia or la
cosa nostra our thing made glamorous by the godfather and movies of that ilk and colorful
criminals like Al Capone, Buxy Seagal, Sam Giancana, and Jimmy Hoffa, whose body has never
been found.
I found it.
Yeah, I didn't tell anybody.
It was at the store.
It was washed up on the beach.
Got preserved by the ocean and it got washed up on the beach.
I just found it in my house.
I poked it.
Mafia nicknames.
Joe Banana.
That's number one.
Alright, off to a great start.
I can visualize exactly in my head the gangster Joe Banana.
I know exactly what that guy looks like.
He wears a yellow suit.
He wears a yellow suit and a brown hat.
Can you visualize Johnny Sausage though?
Oh Johnny Sausage probably wears a codpiece like Cameo.
Baby Shanks and this is one of my favorites so far of these four.
Butter Ass.
Yeah, but oh man.
You fucking-
You- uh- the dudes I used to run with, man.
Fucking butter ass.
He had the nicest fucking ass of any man-
Any man I've ever seen in my fucking-
Real tough guys back in my day.
Butter ass, bubble butt,
beautiful butthole,
big roundy-
Amazing ass butthole guy,
and fuckable butt.
Those are the five-
The most dangerous of our fucking crew was fuckable butt.
New York.
fuckable butt, fuckable butt, come and weep
everybody in this town knows Joe the twerker
you don't wanna fuck with Joe the twerker
you don't wanna fuck with Joey twerks
Joe the twerker used to put a tommy gun in between his ass
and he would shake that thing until the bullets were flying
butter ass
he would spray bullets at you from his fuckin ass
we told him that he would sit on a stick of butter
That's how they got Bonnie and Clyde. They got Bonnie and Clyde because they had butter.
This guy could sit on a stick of Amish butter, one of those big logs, and make it disappear.
Uh, Whack Whack and Quack Quack. You gotta imagine those are brothers.
Those are twin brothers. Yeah, come on dude.
Riddle me this, Mikey.
Riddle me this, NYPD.
Is it Wack Wack to which you speak or perhaps I am my brother?
One of us tells the truth and the other sits on a stick of butter.
We don't know whether to nail Wack Wack or Quack Quack in this Rico case.
Pistol Pete that's like yeah.
Pistol Pete.
That's a cowboy yeah.
That's just a gun and then a guy's name that's not that impressive.
Deagle Darren.
Yeah.
Gun Greg.
Yeah, M14 Marvin, dude. That might be a good one.
Tick Tock, Pat the Cat.
Tick Tock is one of them.
Uh, Horse Face.
Oh, that one's just mean.
Come on, dude. Yeah, you're just calling your friend ugly now.
You guys, I don't like the fucking name you give me. It's not good for my self-esteem.
What do you mean, boophead?
Calling a meeting with all five families?
I just want to let you know, I, uh...
I'd like to change my nickname.
me in a boy's been told by the file peter always complete
uh...
cheechee that's like a it's like a southern grandma name yeah
uh... they would be to see the booties like a girl cowboy name
account if you will
the owl that i will let his good that's cool that's that's like a
that's like a of kate he's going to be going to be slashed
like seven really is a huge drop off here
yeah yeah okay i was just gonna read all these
sam sings in the night
chicken man benny squint
the reluctant prime
fourteenth street steve baldy dom larry fabb and shellac head
i love chicken man that's a really good one
chicken man is what they call wade boggs
i don't
know that is way boxes he's a baseball player
they call him chicken man
yet is he would eat like a registry chicken or something before every i
don't know i thought he would like to say as a as a as a mafia so gangster
maybe he did
his his twitter account is chicken man thirty ten
thirty ten it's always password to
yet
just acting into his account
did you see that that
uh... open anthony
clip where rich Voss just gives out the password to his like Facebook account
now where he somebody asked him they're like what what is your what is your like
thing on Facebook and he's like I think it's comedian 2008
and they're like what that's not is that's not your name
oh that's your password and then somebody
somebody hacks his Facebook and calls them on air
it's like yeah of course that's rich Voss' fucking password anybody over 40
you can just guess their password to everything. It's just their child's name.
Yeah, yeah. One, two, three. Or their profession and a year I guess.
Yeah. Yeah, Wade Boggs used to eat a whole like chicken before every game.
That can't be good. That's his superstition. I don't know. How old was he?
How old was a baseball player? I don't know. Dude, Wade Boggs was fucking sick. Wade Boggs
would, he like, I guess he drank, well it's an Always Sunny episode where they said that he drank
like 72 beers on a plane. I mean how long is this trip though? Right I don't know.
72 days. Could have been around the world and back. I think it was Boston to LA or like Philly to LA. That's a lot of beers. Yeah.
Yeah that's too many beers for a five-hour flight. Maybe he's my favorite
baseball player ever. I've needed one for a while. Yeah yeah he drank he drank 60
something beers he says. Okay next up is the Russian mafia. Well I'd say the name
of it Oh either Russian mafia
*gibberish*
*more gibberish*
shuffle loin stitch borscht I do speak Russian number the number number one
Russian mafia nickname is that guy bond are stars and bibba I'm guessing it's
beba no but bibba cool yeah yeah call you later yeah quiet godfather it's like a
Wu-Tang name generator name yeah yeah the quiet godfather yeah my name my mob name
is crazy scarface I'm awesome Al Capone the head of the Russian mafia
Tonks ku Tom Lord Lenin that's pretty scary
Hosea stealing from Jay Z yeah this is with a Z oh they put that they took they
took the V out of Jay-Z's name and took it and put it into Hova in the mid-hose-a.
I don't fucking know man. Mussolini? That's an Italian guy. Alik the Greek.
That's what yeah, Alik the Greek, the Mussolini, the Italiani. Pat wants to
Alika Greek. Maybe. That's right. You want to Alika Greek. Yeah I do. Georgian, Taro.
that's a bubble tea I think they just said that one because it was fun to say
Oh Oh tear most these are in fucking Russian what the hell
Lasha rustavsky grandpa Hassan was a grow jr. hey you think shag row juniors
bad wait till you meet fucking shag row yeah this guy's this guy's a savage dude
none of these are that good honestly these Russians Russia Russia low-key
although the problem is that most of them are in Russian if they had English
names like a translation next to it the translation of Bebo which is probably
like bouncing ball yeah that would be a cool name that's pretty scary yeah it is
really scary it must have been hard for them when they would win like American
media would would cover Russian mafia goings-on yeah do the translations you
you know maybe like hungry Steve today is responsible for the murder of a czar
they've czars there right I think they still do it's a czar a human or is that
a different creature it's a czar is kind of like a guy it's a type of it's a
type of Russian spirit that lives in a doll it's like a king from the waist up
and then like a like a like a phantom form from the waist down it looks like it
looks like worm tongue from Lord of the Rings. Okay. Very greasy and evil. So that's a
czar. Mm-hmm. All right. I'd be scared of going to Russia because of those guys.
Yeah, there's so too many czars hanging out. Yeah, and my brain, anytime
somebody says czar, I just imagine like a Fallout 3 ghoul. Mm-hmm. Yeah. The next
one is Far East Gangs. Mm-hmm. This one says, "I couldn't find any Chinese
gangster nicknames but I found the gangsters and it's just names of Chinese
yeah one of them's name is you zoom in one of them is Henry fuck yeah Henry
Foff you ganglong these are just yeah those are just Chinese names I see
wiener what are these names huge-ass wait hold on look at the fucking blurb at
the bottom. These men were all tried for serious crimes like rape, murder, drug
trafficking, racketeering, and robbery. You don't want one of these sweethearts as
your best buddy. These aren't even nicknames, these are just names. So these are seven
guys. This is kind of a list within the list where it's like these are
nine guys that you don't want to be friends with. Yeah. Here's my
buddy, his nickname's Charles Hwang but his name's Adam Lambert. Adam Lambert.
I said the first thing that popped in my head.
Yeah you were thinking about Adam Lambert all day weren't you?
I was thinking about his music.
Yeah I bet.
Mm-hmm.
His songs are queen.
Who's Adam Lambert?
He's a musician.
He's the greatest rock god of all time.
What's he sing?
What's that song?
He's a "What Do You Want From Me?"
I've never heard an Adam Lambert song.
That was a banger.
That was a banger in 2014.
He's one of those like...
He's an American Idol winner.
Tabloid celebrities that like you've never heard of except for in the grocery store when
you're checking out.
Oh wow look what he looks like.
He looks amazing dude.
He looks like something else.
He's the he's like the front man for Queen now like he's Queen and Adam Lambert.
He looks exactly like the guy who hosts Ink Master. Dave Navarro? Yeah similar vibes.
Yeah, he looks like he looks like the between phase of like an
Animorphs from like a Hot Topic guy to one of those like like steroid Iranian guys on Instagram. True.
He does yeah, he looks like he got a chin implant. Yeah. Yeah, he probably did dude. Maybe who knows?
I'm not against those. I think they're awesome. I'm trying to look like
Robert Z'Dar after we watch that fucking Gnome movie. Yeah. Oh, Robert Z'Dar's
the all-timer. I'm trying to be a maniac cop baby. I saw Robert Z'Dar in some
like Mystery Science Theater 3000 thing and I just I thought he was
makeup for so long. Yeah. And learning that that was his real face was so shocking.
He has a condition called cherubism. He has a condition called being fucking cool
looking the rest of his life and God blessed him so easily. Yeah, all right
number the next oh no African-American gang so we'll just skip over this
there's you know no I wanted to see this so badly these are gangs principally
associated with ethnic groups such as the black gangster disciples, vice lords, the
Crips, the Bloods, and the black guerrilla family. These mainly started in the
fertile grounds of the prison system and the ghettos and inner city slums of major
cities they specialize in drug-related crimes oh no bumpy that's what I go with
first bumpy yeah it's gonna be it's a bumpy ride this fucking list
Mickey the Cobra yeah big Frank Nitti stacks parentheses all mafia members
anyone could be named stay anybody can be named that's like a free space and
bingo it doesn't matter what race you are you could be stags you can be stags no
matter where you're from. You can be a Russian guy named Stacks. This one gets
progressively worse. Ace of Spades, Da Boss, Dreads, No, The Prophet, Icebox, and
T-Bone, which is my dad's idea of a black guy's name. Yeah, exactly. My dad at the end of
this one says, "Excuse me if a couple of these are offensive, but don't shoot the
messenger. I only found them." My dad, every time he sees a black guy at Walmart, he
looks at the name tag expecting t-bone he's like it's probably t-bone here's a
Hispanic gangs well these are these are where the names get really cool these are
these are my god yeah Mexican a Mexican gangs have the best this is this is how
they got the plus of the hundred there's fucking right yeah 50 of these yeah they
have they have girl names - this is the first one to have your own names that's
so sweet. Women's History Month baby, we're starting off right.
Most of the Latino gangs originated as prison gangs. The Mexican Mafia never set
foot in Mexico they claim. They're not even Mexican. They're just guys.
Hispanic gang guy nicknames. Bullet, coolest one on the entire list so far.
Just straight to the point. Wait, oh you wait, wait till you get further down the
list cuz they get away so good minor my that's a great name for a child yeah
yeah it's like a bugsy Malone yeah that's that's fucking sick just like just
like an eight-year-old with like a full like body suit of like cholo tats oh my
god I would be scared of minor oh so doesn't oh so mean bear mr. scrappy that
is a dog's name yeah yeah it's a puppet's name yeah demon that fuck yeah dude I
think we have a I think we somebody's finally be right it took four names to
be bullet wait wait till you get to the next one spider mm-hmm okay yep this is
the coolest this is quick I mean sombreros off to the Mexican gangs these
are looking so good right now payaso don't know what that means Joker Joker
It's really good. Can we just that should be a white gang name
Wait, so can we have one name wait till you get to the bottom of the list? Mr. Cisco
Cisco
shorty creeper sniper
Wicked I were so good. Yeah bouncer
No
Gizmo is the yeah, he's the the technology gangster. Yeah
the the techie Ninja Turtle yeah he always has like that is that Donatello
he always has like big green like tech yeah yeah yeah yeah tank mm-hmm sweet
tanks got to be a big guy yeah yeah no wait what if it's a tiny guy that's what
I call it yeah a child dude that's actually a genius idea huh you got it
see it's funny if it's opposite
swifty
lil loco
spider but with a y
rascal
rascal's pretty good
baby gangster
baby gangster? spider again?
dude, name's so nice you need to do rice dude
el chewy
pop boy
like pop eye
with an o instead of an e
montana
Ooh, Bonified? Bonified, dude. That is such a good one.
Paco Magic and Red Rider.
Bonified, he's got a big vat of acid and he's like, "I'm gonna dip you in this and you're gonna be Bonified."
These are much better for supervillain names than gangster names, I feel like.
Almost all these would work perfectly as a super...
Yeah, baby gangster.
Uh, these are for the girls.
Hispanic Gang's gal nicknames.
These ones get ridiculous.
little little tramposo which cannot be a kind thing to say yeah sharpies, smiler,
smiler, joker, clumsy, shy girl, love shy girl, little puppet, dopey, little clown,
spooky, little clown, spooky, lil loco, la giggles, mousy, la giggles, you don't want
- I'm gonna mess with my girl like giggles, dude.
She'll fuck you up. - Baby one punch.
- Flaco.
- Chow is like a, that's a vegan cheese.
- That's a little creature from Sonic.
- Oh yeah. - That's what it is.
- That's right.
- All right, now we're getting into,
these will be some good ones, I think.
- Yeah. - Biker gangs.
- Oh man.
- What?
- The one that right after biker gangs.
- What's after biker gangs?
- All right, we gotta hurry through.
(laughing)
Well, why does it, it fools you here. It says, "Last but not least, let's not forget the biker gangs.
There are many and varied, but they all go under the umbrella name of the 'one percenters'."
Isn't that like the...
Yeah, what the hell?
Nation of Islam?
What the fuck?
I want those names, dude. Those are some cool names.
Yeah.
"They're even assigned military ranks."
Aren't... Okay.
"Women in these gangs have no status. They are the property of one of the gang members,
and can be passed around from one member to the other with the owner's permission, of course."
Ugh.
Oh I hate that. I hate that so much. These biker gangs aren't as nice as I thought they were.
There are also prospects who are hopefuls who want to get into the gangs. They have
to do all the dirty demeaning jobs for about a year and then they might or
might not be allowed to get into the hallowed ranks. Names of the gangs are of
course Hells Angels, Pagans, Mongols, Outlaws, Banditos, Sons of Silence, Vagos,
Cossacks, and other lesser-known ones who are just as evil and nasty. All of these
names are just Borderlands names. Right. Yeah, definitely. Handlebars. That's my biker gang.
My biker name is Seat. That's like a cop trying to infiltrate the biker gang. Hey listen partner,
what's your name? What do you go by? And he's just like, his eyes dart around. He's like
Yeah, Motorcycle. I'm Motorcycle. And I love Kevin.
Wait, hold on, no, you can't be called Motorcycle. He's already called Motorcycle.
Y'all are gonna have to race for it.
My name is Street.
Hold on, man, that's already his name.
My name's Guy in front of me.
That's my name.
My nickname is Stanley.
My name's Dirt.
We already have Dirt.
My name's Boots.
We have a Boots too.
Okay, what about Dirty Boots?
We got three of those.
What about Bootsy Dirt?
Different types of boots.
We got Chelsea Boot.
My name's Cloud.
My name's Clive.
my name is life they let my son pick my name I'm Darth Vader knuckles that's
another sonic name Jane's shovelhead gear and cetera that's a cool nickname to a
gear I know they mean like oh like we're not gonna list the rest but here's it's
Et cetera is cool.
Et cetera, et cetera, having your nickname have et cetera in it, like meaning that you
have more than one nickname.
Yeah.
So sick.
Um, the girl nick, the girl names, uh, Bear Trap, Bad Bitch, Ginger, Tigress, Foxy, Kiki,
Black Widow, Pussy.
Yeah, that's Pussy over there.
Kinky, Cougar.
Wait, why do they call her Pussy?
No idea.
No worth the call.
wait why do they call her pussy? no idea no worth the clue yeah I haven't looked
into it any further. this here's my my bitch her name's hair.
kitty and any other kind of cat. we call her clothing yeah her name's nose see that there on her
face she's named after that their thing all right and then white supremacist
gangs they don't even have the names yeah yeah what the hell it has it
unfortunately I couldn't find any nicknames for these people but I'm sure
you can think of a few yeah here I got one for you Bob Ted yeah hey I got one
you I got one for you right now Donald Trump. Ayyy. NOOOOO! Okay. Barack Obama.
Yeah I got Morgan Freeman I mean these are all white supremacist name gang
gang names these are made up of all sorts of people in the white community
from trailer trash to PhDs who all believe in the superiority of white
people over all ethnic groups the most famous of these is the Ku Klux Klan there
There are also the Nazi Party and the skinheads.
That's facts.
I want to skip over, there's got smaller gangs here.
The next one is, this is fucked up, this is, they have some shots fired here.
The next section is gangstas, and it says, "Gangstas are wannabe gangsters who think
they are real criminals.
They indulge in petty theft, graffiti-dobbing, and hurling sexist insults at women.
They are despised by the really mean guys."
will do you know. The next section is my gangsta names. If I was a gang member my name would
be Tigress because a tiger is the biggest fiercest cat there is and the most beautiful. You can
use gangster and rapper generators on social media. On one of them my gangster name is Crispy
Mama and my rap name is Smokeboo. Is it this by the editorial board? This is by the Boston
globe yeah one member of the spotlight team just snuck that in they have
popular gangster rappers there's just a list of rappers oh and now here's a
good part yeah yeah this is what I wanted to get to yeah good this is good
thing this is the plus yeah general from 100 so these guys I'm guessing are not
necessarily gangsters as the image is just a guy in a suit with sunglasses on
G, dog, peewee, pitbull, razor, hammer, scarface, screwdriver, shaggy, smoke, snake,
viper, Teflon Don, trigger Mike. Trigger Mike is a gangster name. Yeah. You're not a
tough guy if your name is Trigger Mike. Scissors! Guys I want to, I want, we should skip through
this because there's a bunch of comments that I think we should read. Oh, oh hell
Also it says, "In conclusion, if you are searching for gangster nicknames for yourself or for a guy or girl, I have tried to find every single nickname from every single source I can find, but I seem to have acquired only a very small number of African American ones."
And then here's a comment from Red Ass.
They call me Red Ass Ripper.
And that there's one directly under it from illegal vibes and it says mine is illegal vibes
Sean comments my friends call me bloody the blood
Little P replies and my friends call me a little P because I look like a small
Tyler Forbes says my friends call me death and then t says big menace is mine
and my little brother is little menace
Fabio comments Jake the peg and hot back Natalie comments blazing all right so if
If you, no you can go be a gangster, you'll have a name.
Yeah, you can each get a name.
All of our listeners.
I'm going to go with.
Yeah, everyone, nobody use the same name twice.
Everybody has to coordinate with yourselves.
Yep.
I'm going to go with Crazy Caleb.
That'll probably be mine when I join the army.
I probably will go with Demon.
I'm gonna go with uh...
Caleb and Cameron
What?
Those are our names.
That's my nickname. Caleb and Cameron. Because we're so tough and that works perfectly as a gangster name.
Yeah, because it sounds so cool. I want to change my name now.
Too late. We already locked them all in. You're already Caleb Cameron. The murderous canon. No, you're not the murderous canon.
The stinky pirate.
the insane evil trickster the insane car the insane clown posse the unlucky
building the crazy the unbelievably tough guy one-eyed janitor the craziest
crazy guy ballsack Fred darkwing duck
awesome Batman all right bye y'all bye
awesome Patrick