You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
- There it is.
- That's how they used to start Power Rangers in space
is five, five, five, I think.
- It's too scary for me when they put beloved characters
in space.
How they gonna breathe?
- Yeah.
- Leprechaun in space?
I don't think so.
There's no rainbows up there.
yeah golden space he can't breathe in space because he's magic never mind
he's okay he's not a leprechaun is a magic he's short exactly no they do
count it down in the pad they don't say five five five I think I think one of
them I think when they're because they have like they're thinking of phone
numbers from movies maybe but I think they're their wrists some of them do
five five five I don't remember I haven't seen it in a long time I got
Power Rangers on the brain. Why? Have you defeated a big... No, I found a Zord in my
backyard. Did you defeat him? No. Why would I defeat it? I don't know what a Zord is.
Zoids. You remember Zoids? Zoids is one of the best shows of all time. I never watched Zoids, but I
had a game for it for a Game Boy Advance. Zoids was the ultimate Toonami show.
Oh yeah, that's why I didn't see it. You didn't watch Toonami, dude? No, I hated
Toonami I like to swim better. Because it wasn't some funny bullcrap about it?
No it wasn't. No you know the only... It didn't have Meatwad in it? Yeah the only
thing I liked on Toonami was Bobobo Bobobo Bobobo. That has to be the most
racist show of all time right? Is it? Bobobo Bobobo Bobobo the Japanese show
about a guy who uses his afro to defeat enemies? Look I was like in third
great I didn't know drawing of Bobo Bobo Bobo Bobo yeah he's white I love it one
second I never watched that I remember hearing my friend described that show to
me and being like what the hell it's called Bobo Bobo Bobo Bobo I don't
have a friend who's this what do you mean yeah I think he's got a cabbage friend I
think if you listen to his voice you you you start to well in the localization
maybe yeah maybe the localization it has to be even worse in Japanese we don't
know yeah yeah that could be true he does have a very funny mustache yeah
Bobo I'll give you this much funny mustache brother mm-hmm we're not
brother whoops why did you call him that yeah they tricked me I have a guy have
again been tripped tripped and tricked by a Japanese television show and just
saying brother. Well this is this is Japan, Japanese television month. Is it? Yeah for us.
That's right. Yeah that's right. Yeah you fucking know it dude. Oh wait big news. Oh yeah.
Oh yeah oh shit. Oh fuck dude yeah huge news. We got this we got a really big sponsorship
and we can't like legal stuff we can't talk about it yet but
just you know keep your eyes open because we're gonna be working with some
big stuff stay tuned soon yeah stay tuned
yeah stay tuned stay tuned you're gonna want it you're you're gonna like it
you're gonna want to miss this you're not no
you're not gonna want to not yeah
Yeah, you're gonna want to miss this next episode, not got your ass.
Yeah, no, it's basically going to change everything for us. Money-wise, we can't disclose an exact
number, but substantial. We'll say that much. We're making a lot of money on this.
Even for us, this might be too big. Might be too much money.
Yeah. I mean, we're small enough that this is like gonna push us over the edge.
Patrick's gonna have enough money to like pay a scientist to correct his sleep cycle artificially and it's gonna ruin the podcast forever
Yeah, that kind of deal. Yeah. Yeah, dr. Dr. Dr. Melatonin. Yeah, he's gonna put a bunch of blue Z's in your mouth
After going to like a doctor to be like hey like a doc like I can't ever sleep there
I think there's something wrong with me. Just like hey, have you tried not using your phone and Patrick's like, oh
Yeah, that's why I got these blue light blockers glasses
You have blue light blocker glasses?
I was thinking of getting those but then someone told me that you can just set your monitor
to a different color temperature and it works exactly.
Yeah, there's one built into the iPhone.
Yeah.
It's called Night Shift.
Yeah, I didn't know about the Night Shift.
I didn't know that it was just what blue blockers did.
Yeah.
I have it on all the time.
I didn't know that.
That's why I fall asleep everywhere.
Well, now...
I had it on my laptop for a while but it would go, it would like glitch out and I'd be watching
movies and it would just change everything to like insane colors. Yeah it
does change that's what I love about it is I'll like have it on when I play a
game late at night and I just can't see anything because it's just orange. Right
yeah but it'll also be like suddenly like one thing on the screen like turns
bright green for no reason. I feel like I'm in a Sunny D commercial playing
Valorant. It's fucking rules dude but I can fall asleep instantly dude texting
while driving just knock out phone is it keep me up you know damn doesn't night
shit night night night shit I turned on night shit on my phone yeah now my
phone's capable of doing night she keep well it keeps you from using your phone
at night cuz it makes it smell like a dog and feels it's kind of a that's kind
of a genius idea dude turn my phone into shit just make your phone smell like
shit so you don't want to like have it in your hands and look at it all the
time and have it like close to your face you get like a phone call and you're
like pinching it between your fingers you're like this yeah hello yeah you
have to hold it at arm's length. You're like "HOWOW"
I've got Squidward on the line. No I was not Squidward I was pinching my nose due
to the smell of my phone. I didn't smell like Squidward. Imagine what
squidward smells like though smells dude have you ever smelled calamari well
that's a pig's asshole I learned oh yeah yeah it's not actually octopus something
like squids some insane I don't think either of you are right something some
insane like percentage of calamari sold in the United States is like actually a
pig's asshole all right well not if you buy it from but I don't buy it from a
giant octopus yeah Mon Calamari I get it shipped from Australia well they but then
it's a kangaroos asshole true they don't have assholes at all I think we talked
about it before but I would do it would you eat a kangaroo we talk about it like
fucking every week dude it's true about kangaroos anytime kangaroos come up I'm
like why are you want to eat a kangaroo so bad dude I don't know if I want not a
a fatty delicious like oh there's a wag you kangaroo you don't know that you're
right I don't know what I'm talking about
there's no Wagaroos dude come on they could have they could be breeding fat
kangaroos in Australia breeding a desert so cool dude it doesn't just like guru
yeah yeah the way you get that as you put candy in its power it's kind of like
you put candy in the passion it absorbs it into it yeah yeah it's kind of like
your muscular frosting it's kind of like Pokemon where if like it's it's holding
something or it has something in its pouch.
- Oh yeah, yeah.
- Once it evolves, it turns into that.
So if you put a bunch of candy in its pouch,
you'll get a candy roo.
- A candy roo, yeah.
- If you put like--
- Isn't a candy roo that fish that crawls up your pee hole?
- Is that it?
Is that the name of it? - A candy roo?
(laughing)
- That's what it's called.
- That's gotta be the biggest like discrepancy
between name and thing that it does of all time.
- Oh yeah, I think that is.
- Yeah, it's called a candy roo.
Dude, I want a candy roo.
Also known as a caniero, a toothpick fish, or a vampire fish.
Does it give you sweet pee?
No, it goes up, it can swim up your pee- I've talked about it before, it can swim up your
pee stream, and then it gets in the hole and your meatus goes through the meatus into the
urethra.
It could not swim up my pee stream, not in a thousand-
No, it could.
You should see-
It can swim up, and then once it gets-
You got a lazy stream.
You should see my fucking stream, dude.
Your stream goes inwards.
It gets stuck in and it's got like-
No.
Yeah, my stream-
You suck water up out of the toilet with it.
My stream is like a, it's like a, like shooting a hole in an airplane.
Everything's just fucking flying out maximum velocity.
Blood?
Blood, piss, shit, everything.
Fishes?
Yeah, the fishes that have climbed up there previously.
Bones.
No, and that thing, when that thing gets stuck up there though, it's got like, I think it's
like something in its gills or something, it's got like spikes on the side of it.
Yeah, so you can't pull it out.
Yeah, so if you pull it out, you're bleeding out your thing.
That would feel good to me.
Yeah?
Yeah, it's ribbed for my pleasure, dude. I want that fish in my wiener ASAP.
You think there's guys who are into sounding that have gone to like rivers?
There's guys who are into everybody--
No, no, you did-- let me finish.
Okay.
You think there's guys that are into sounding that go to the a river in Peru
just to pee in the stream with the hopes that a toothpick fish swims up?
Um, yes.
Yeah.
Those guys, yeah. There is a guy who thinks that the candy roo is-- it's not called a candy roo.
It's called the candy roo.
Zandru but not candy space rue. I'm reading this article about for on BBC about how um
about just like whether it's a myth or not what they do and listen to this this is a
this is a quote from the 19th century when they discovered it. Okay. The candy rue is
very small but uniquely occupied in doing evil.
A bitch that only knows evil and pain.
The German botanist Carl Frederick Philipp von Martius was the first European to document
candirus in the Amazon.
He described how local men tied their urethra shut when spending time around the water.
I think I'm safe.
Yeah, you live in America and you don't even take baths.
if I do if I go you take my baby if I go to Peru and I pee in a stream I can just
I can just get a clamp put it on my put it on my f-skin okay but listen to this
though this is where this is why that wouldn't work why I'll just be the
authors mostly focus on the vulnerability of penises to attack
perhaps because they themselves are all men but many emphasize that the fish do
not discriminate and will happily enter a convenient vagina or anus oh my god
If you're peeing out your butt off the side of a boat it can jump up in your thing.
Do you have to walk in all fucking corked up like Spongebob when he has his suds?
Just trying to not get a fucking candy ruin.
What is the solution?
Just don't swim.
Yeah, don't go in the water.
What is wrong with you dude?
Don't fucking swim in Peru.
When in Peru I guess I have to swim.
The rivers are so famous for how beautiful the water is.
Dude, this sucks so much.
I have to put a big cork in my wiener and I have to tie my butthole shut.
Yeah, sometimes it's worth it even though the water's infested with wiener demons.
I'm just gonna swim it anyway.
Trust me, trust me.
It's like floating in the Dead Sea, except instead of all the things that are cool about
the Dead Sea, it gives you a dead pee.
There's an actual evil fish.
Yeah.
the BBC describes as evil. I thought piranha would be the most evil fish but no.
No because they just eat stuff. They don't. Yeah. I want a candiru.
They're like little centibites dude. They want to, they're trying to pleasure you
and pain you at the same time. I want it to climb in my ass halfway and then I
become like a Peruvian version of Tanuki Mario.
Well if you take it. I can use it like a tail and I can swim.
I can fly. I can fly. If you poop while a candy roo is in your butt does it does you think it just eats it?
It eats all the poop yeah. Yeah. Well there's that's that's how evil they are.
They're so evil they like poop. It's like Pokemon again where there's a male and female version
that are different and one of them eats pee and one of them eats poo. Oh okay. And it's if you
use a pee stone on one or if you use a poo stone. And you don't want it to evolve in your ass. It's
exactly like Pokemon in that it's like it's like slow bro exactly yeah it's like
slow bro and Pokemon snap you have to like put an apple in front of somebody
so they put their butt in front of the water I would I would be fooling people
all the time as it here's what you do as a guide you're a tour guide and your
brother is a is a penis doctor right and then you kind of like where this is
grift going where you you are like oh yeah this is the fucking swag is river
in all of Peru dude you have to check it out and then when they come on they're
like my weenie hurts I think there's I think the devil's in my weenie you say
you know my brother can exercise any any penis demon he lives down the street and
he charges $2 yeah you could really get it because it's a dollar yeah it's
Yeah, they'll be like sucks it out. Why are those little fish in there looking at me get undressed and smiling?
Yeah, they like
Yeah, why are they arranged like a school of piranhas but only when I unzip
Licking its lips when it sees me
Yeah, why are they forming together like a giant smiley face
Gee I don't know again my brother is right down the street
Go look for him. Yeah, you should dive through the mouth here. Yeah, this is a coupon that I have
It says penis demon removal
Yeah, what does this sign mean? It's like
There's a little like stick man
Yeah, oh, yeah, that's it's trying to warn you of all the prostitutes
This river he used to be a fluffer on porn sets, but then he moved to Peru and he's making a killing
He sucks the demon the penis demon right out you yeah
Man, can you imagine just this pure suction that has to happen on your penis to get a fish out of it?
Yeah, oh my god, especially when it's like ribbed
I can't get any out of my wiener if it's stuck one guy prostate one guy keeps coming back to the the clinic like
Okay
Raymond I'm stuck in the penis Raymond. I'm stuck in your penis. I swam up your p-stream Raymond
That would be a terrifying new version of honey. I shrunk the kids
Yeah, it's inside your penis it's kind of like an osmosis jones movie though, you know, that's what
You know, I'm just spitballing here fish rock who would be who would be the Kelsey Grammer character what would that like the dricks
That would be the doctor's tongue that slides down the penis hole. Yeah
and it has to grab the fish. That's voiced by Oprah Winfrey. Okay. Yeah. Okay.
Let's build out this, let's expand this cast. Okay. Bill Murray reprises his
role from Osmosis Jones. I think there should be different, there should also be
different like doctors use like different techniques. Like I think we
could have like, like you know, there's the guy who just sucks it out but then
maybe like we could have Sam Elliott is like kind of a cowboy doctor and uses a
lasso to pull it out yeah that's a really good idea he's got like a tiny he's like
well he got a fish in that layer pecker he got it makes it a lasso at a dental
floss and he just perfectly bullseyes it through and then he's and then he or he
sucks it out and then he spits it yeah into a spittoon right well yeah I don't
mean that I think a cowboy doctor is a good idea Brian Cranston could
kind of play like the straight doctor because I need more Bryan Cranston it's
been a while since he did something we could have like you know maybe Mickey
Rooney could play like a samurai that's like that's a pretty good idea yeah
samurai doctor and he does the thing where he like runs back and forth and
then the fish falls out like a bunch of pieces that's a really good idea we could
have Creed from the movie Creed yeah yeah he's a boxing doctor and he could punch
it out he punches he punches he does a speed bag he does a speed bag thing on his nuts and it creates
so much pressure that it shoots out the fish weiner throws oh that's so smart actually huh yeah
how did they actually have like a robot doctor like chappy yeah play but yeah chappy could make
another appearance candy rue removal and d and where to of course you can't have one without
the other dude oh here's a video of sucking it out no it's a somebody
getting its candy removal the video contains graphic images I don't think so
there's no way yeah maybe if you maybe you blow into the pee hole and it comes
out the butt oh they have like a oh man they got a little camera on a device and
they have to oh I think the camera is the device oh man why are you rubbing your
hands together like Birdman.
Oh this is so gross.
You love that shit.
This is not going to make me act up.
Why are you cocking one eyebrow?
Oh dude this is so gross.
(Laughter)
Yo that's the nastiest shit I've ever seen.
Damn.
Here's another video. Stephen Fry horrified by
candy roo fish.
Yeah he's horrified. He's screaming into his penis hole.
- Yeah.
- What a horrifying, what a horrifying country.
I would never go to Peru now.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I think that's--
- Just because of that?
- Yeah, dude, I don't wanna risk it.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause what if you, you know, if you're in Peru,
I mean, it's in South America, it's under the equator.
- Yeah.
- You know, it's hot.
- It's too hot, I'll go and--
- You gotta go swimming, it's hot.
- Exactly, yeah, you gotta cool off some way,
but I'm not gonna trust any source of water in Peru now.
- Yeah.
- I've changed my whole mind on Peru.
I used to be so pro Peru until fucking two minutes ago.
It's true.
Now I found out they have devils in the water.
They used to call me Peru Stew and then now I won't be caught dead in Peru.
Not in a million years, dude.
Not in a trillion years.
Not in a hundred billion years.
Do we have an ad read coming up?
Our first ad read?
Oh yeah.
Alright.
Dude, so we're doing ads now on the podcast.
This will be our first one.
Yep.
Gonna be doing a couple of them.
I mean it's not an ad read though it's more we're just talking.
Yeah you're right.
I don't know what you said.
No.
Yeah you're right.
My bad.
Can't really yeah.
Alright.
So anyway just to continue the conversation we were having.
Yeah.
The guac is extra.
If you recognize this quote you might be a little extra yourself because you're probably
a Chipotle fan like me.
If you read any of their hilarious bags of receipts you know they love humor just like
we do at Podcasts About List.
Right guys?
Absolutely.
Oh man.
big ball of beans in a tortilla with meats, cheeses, and salsas to boot.
That's right. It's the burritos for me. It's the way they make me say bro-rito
for me. And I know what you're thinking. Doesn't Chipotle give you E. coli,
the deadly poop germ? Well, we at Chipotle, me at Podcasts About Lifts,
I like to say that there's no such thing as bad press. That's right.
When you press your giant burrito-sized and shaped and flavored poop out of your
poop hole, it's not going to be bad. This ain't no Taco Bell where it makes
your hole on fire like the ring a lion jumps through in the circus or a
motorcycle could jump through it too. Chipotle is the real authentic deal and it
hasn't had a Wayfair type scandal where they use menu items as a cover-up for
selling abducted orphans. Note, remove the previous sentence if Bohemian Grove
catering connection has hit the news by the time you do this ad read. Note 2,
don't read notes out loud they're for your eyes only. So use podcast about list
special code P-A-T-R-I-C-K-P-E-D-O-P-H-I-L-E for one free bean and remember if the
chips give you diarrhea it's Mexican people's fault for making tortillas too
spicy and it has nothing to do with our traveling beef chef Stuart "Poop Glove" Jackson.
That's not the code. That is the code.
What's that? Let me order something real quick on Grubhub.
No, the code was "PAL20"?
Mmm, I don't... I'm looking at the same...
That's not what we got.
Did we change the code?
We didn't change it. I think they got some news and they changed it. They may have done some investigation.
Oh yeah, it says right here. It says we hired a private eye to verify the coupon code.
No, it says that they followed you around. They confirmed the coupon code.
Anyway, I don't even know what you guys are talking about because nobody sent us this.
Oh yeah, that's facts.
That wasn't the code.
Yeah, what's up?
What code?
We're just having a conversation here, Pat.
I know, but we're having a conversation about the fucking code now because that was not the code.
I just read out what I thought in my brain.
Yeah.
Yeah, and you said a different code.
I can show you my email.
- What email?
This is just a conversation.
- I can show you my thoughts.
- He wrote all his thoughts in an email.
- Yeah, wait, let me pull them up for you.
Yeah, it says right here, P-A-T,
I don't know what this spells by the way.
- No, it's P-A-L.
- R-I-C-K-P.
- It's P-A-L-20.
- No, it's just one of those like nonsense codes.
- No, it's like it's not a random string of letters.
- It's one of those nonsense code like P-A-T-R-I-C-K-R-A-P-I-S-T
- That's not it, no.
- No.
- Just like another one of those random codes like that.
- No, just come up with random codes.
- I don't like the code.
- Well, it doesn't matter, then don't use it.
- Yeah, if you don't like discounts, that's on you.
- It's not, no, those aren't the codes.
- Okay, all right, man.
They are the codes.
- Okay, all right. - They're not the, no.
- Let's just move on to the list.
- Yeah, let's.
- We'll just move on to the list, it's fine.
- We can, yeah.
- What's the list this week?
- I don't care.
- Somebody send it to me.
You care, come on.
No, today's list that we selected for our podcast is the 14 things you need to stop doing at
Chipotle according to a Chipotle employee.
I was going to send you guys this list.
This is like the funniest shit ever.
I know.
It's, yeah, I almost sent it too but I was reading it before and I was like they are
going to love this.
I printed it out like a book and I just read it in my off time.
I mean honestly relationship goals.
Absolutely dude.
And squad goals too.
Yeah, you know what?
I'm in a relationship with Chipotle.
Bro-rito, are you serious?
We should get that on a shirt.
Wait.
No.
Did you guys know that they actually have like sustainably sourced bags at Chipotle?
Just like a random fact I learned the other day.
I think I was watching the Discovery Channel or something and they said it there.
Yeah, I saw.
I think I actually learned that in college.
I was talking to somebody yesterday and they told me that all the chicken at Chipotle is
sustainably sourced and it's all free range too.
Yeah they said they have substantially sourced beef there too.
Yeah it's all grass fed cows.
I heard the water and soda machines don't use slaves to crank it from behind the wall.
I heard there's not a little Coca-Cola slave in every freestyle machine who has to do hip
hop dancing to create all the drinks.
- Yeah, one of my friends told me
that their machines are never broken.
- They're never broken.
It's kind of amazing.
It's just like a weird fact that I learned
for no reason though.
- I think the friends kind of knew it could tell.
Or whatever.
- Yeah, you can just tell.
- Just like be respectful.
- They like clearly have that kind of vibe.
That like corporate culture vibe
that you like kind of want to latch onto.
Be like, oh, this is actually goals.
- And you guys know I'm a music fan.
And the music that they play at the restaurant
is always so good.
- Yeah.
I love the design of their stools and tables too.
And they always look so clean.
I get to sit wherever I want, whether it's behind a person or in front of a person.
Or next to somebody, make a new friend.
Yeah, and I love their boho vibe that they give off with their different things.
And boho stands for burrito huge.
Yeah, it's really something the way that they kind of like, they shine a light on lesser
known creators by putting Aztec art on the wall.
That's true, yeah.
at the Mayans for real. Not many people know about the Aztecs. And the bags! Oh my god I can't get enough of these.
Well I already mentioned the bags. We could fill a whole episode about the bags. Oh my god some of the celebrities that
they get to write these stories on the bags and the cups. And the handles, they're just comfortable. And I've
actually been using the bags to pick up my groceries. Yeah? People say hey would
you like a bag or did you bring your own? I say does this answer your question?
Here's a Chipotle bag with a Jennifer Lawrence quote. Same with the tinfoil
bowls that they put the bowls in. Yeah. I've been using those as bags. You can clean those out and it's good
because those are compostable. That's true. Everything there is sustainably sourced, including
the employees. They all get them from prison. Yeah. And that's sustainable because you're
bringing them back into society and they become basically like your friends behind the counter.
And that's facts, dude. Let me just read the intro to this list really quick. I know we're
having like a normal conversation, but we just have to like kick it off sometimes, you
know, even though like no matter how much we love stuff, we just have to get to the
Yeah, sometimes we just get so lost in our casual conversations.
Absolutely.
Everyone loves Chipotle. Seriously, Chipotle is like everything.
So for the life of me, I can't figure out why, oh why,
some people in the world can't just be nice and make life easier
for the people that hold our collective burrito destiny in their very hands.
I've been- It's like they've fucking read my diary.
It's like they read it.
So in the spirit of all that is holy guacamole, wow.
Oh my god.
I implore you to stop doing these things that make Chipotle employees hate you.
I spoke with my best friend who just so happens to work at Chipotle as well as several ladies
in my neighborhood.
Ooh, Casanova.
I got the facts.
Oh, it's a woman that wrote it.
Chips and Salsa Nova.
Several ladies.
That, you know, I've also, I've been talking to several ladies in my neighborhood about
Chipotle as well.
Yeah, me too.
And not everybody wants me to spread the gospel.
Yeah.
I have to say, lots of people are very hostile when I approach them.
Hey, ma'am, excuse me.
Yeah, in the middle of the night, I walk up to women on the street.
Chipotle now has queso!
They love it though. Mm-hmm. Do you want to read this bag with me? That's what I say. Yeah
Do you want to read? I mean, it's kind of like it's better than any book I've read
Definitely. Mm-hmm. Absolutely when they get Fred Armisen to write about beans. Oh, oh god damn Fred
Oh my god, Fred. You should if this was on a blog I would share it. Mm-hmm
Number one like it's kind of the type of thing where they like humor, but not comedy
Definitely, they're kind of a British
sense of humor.
It's like a British Mexican sense of humor.
It's not like you're not guffawing,
but you're definitely going like
You're dryly chuckling.
Yeah. While you're eating your wetly
buckled
chuckle beef.
Definitely.
Number one on this list.
Do not ask for a side of
diced tomatoes. What kind of a psychopath
would do this to an employee?
sick in the head you fucking freak somebody should kill you believe it or
not oh I'll go I'll go believe it or not the tomatoes are used for the salsa
duh yeah holy doesn't have a nice tomatoes waiting to be stuffed into a
plastic ramekin for you because tomatoes that sit in a tub for hours aren't fresh
not fresh not Chipotle oh absolutely mm-hmm there's one thing I noticed when
I go to Chipotle it's just how fresh every ingredient is yeah absolutely just taste
it on your tongue you can tell just by how how abusive the manager is to the
people who are cooking the beef how much they care about how fresh it is they're
not they're not abusive they're encouraging in a negative way it's
called negative and it's called threats of violence used to a positive end in
society and they're all credible mm-hmm why do you think they have that giant
The thing doesn't toast the burritos.
They use that for threatening.
- It's a hand.
- You ever notice how it's perfectly sized
for like a hand or a foot or a penis?
- That's why they wear those gloves
to hide all their, they call them battle scars.
- That's why they have an oubliette in the back.
It's in case they need to forget
about any employees permanently.
- This means someone now has to stop what they're doing
and go dice tomatoes for you.
Unless you're Obama or Adele, who by the way I stand,
don't ask, period.
Or should I say period?
- Yeah.
- Because that's kind of the Chipotle way.
Chipotle actually loves, has been supporting
the LGBTQIA alliance for, I don't know, 50 years?
- Period, or should I say, hold on one second guys,
I'm going to Google Translate.
Period, or should I say periodo.
- So, yeah, exactly.
That's what I would say too.
Periodo.
Sorry, I'm only 68 hours into Duolingo. I haven't gotten that far.
Number two, don't ask stupid questions.
You shouldn't be asking for that.
Number two, don't ask stupid questions like, "How do you know you don't have it in the back?"
Exactly.
It's just, their commitment to transparency is great.
because you can just see in the background of the restaurant.
You can see it all back there.
- Yeah, I mean one thing I like is it's transparent.
You can see the pipes that come from where the bathroom is
that go over where the food is made
and then they go into where the food is made
and then they go underground.
- Yep.
- And I know there's no leakage.
- Exactly.
- I follow those pipes.
I follow them with my eyes.
- Yep, I follow the employees with my eyes.
- That's right, that's why they have a hole in the wall
where the customer can see it all.
- Exactly.
So aside from the obvious answer they want to give you
consisting of something to the effect of
because I goddamn live here, I know what we have,
there is also the very modus operandi
of Chipotle to consider.
I encourage you to think about
what Chipotle stands for, people.
Fresh food.
- Amen, sister.
- Mm-hmm. - Yep.
- If they kept an enormous amount of excess food in the back,
how fresh do you think it's going to stay and for how long?
Duh, they know what they have and they know what they have prepped.
Don't argue.
Yeah, are you fucking brain dead?
Mm-hmm.
Are you stupid?
Are you fucking dumb as a rock, you piece of shit?
Are you dumber than a fifth grader?
Yeah, you must be dumber than a guy who spends 20 minutes thinking about what his order's
gonna be when he's at the front of the line and everyone's waiting behind him.
Oh, don't get me started.
You must be a guy who enjoys Will Ferrell and Adam Sandler movies because that's the
kind of stupid people who are not welcome at somewhere like Chipotle.
Exactly.
Chipotle is of a higher class than McDonald's absolutely dude McDonald's is
for fucking trash people it's basically Chuds it's for absolute corn cobs chuds
who need to be just catch a catch a whiff so I mean it's just it's just like
slack-jawed spineless ghouls absolutely yeah
yeps yeah yips just absolutely fucking piss people who make $15,000 a year
year ago to McDonald's. Disgusting. Just ass clown fuck shits. Yeah. Omelette fuck crustables.
Completely. And that's why Chipotle is taking COVID-19 very seriously. And actually, you
have to have, when they take your temperature when you walk in, it has to be below 70 degrees.
Yep. They need to make sure that you're cold as ice, because otherwise you could be infecting
somebody. It's true. Number three is don't make stupid E. coli jokes. Oh, again with
Oh my god.
Yeah.
Now mine just says, "Uh oh, we're having technical difficulties."
Scroll down.
Oh, okay.
There it is.
"When you make an E. coli joke at a Chipotle restaurant, it's usually because A, you think
you have a joke the employee hasn't already heard.
You don't.
They've all been used, so give up on your dreams as a comedian.
You're neither funny nor original."
That's right.
Yep.
At a restaurant that has bags, you're not going to be funnier than a bag.
You're not going to be funnier than the Chipotle bag that they're going to hand you.
Yeah, and this is the kind of like, I don't know, this is the kind of straight white male
humor about E. coli that is just like so infectious in society, you know?
Exactly.
I mean, I don't like to see that shit.
Like, this is like a, what are you, Anthony Jeselnik?
Like are you a disgusting pig?
Give me an hour in a middle school and I can find you a hundred people who are extremely
funny without having to talk about E. coli.
Absolutely.
you a hundred of the ugliest funniest girls who've ever told a joke. Fuck these
E.coli. I mean E.coli bros I'm done with you. You're never getting on the
Jesselnik offensive. Absolutely not. Yeah. No way. You're auditioning for Guy Code in the middle of
Chipotle? Yeah. No. Don't get me wrong. That hasn't even been on the airwaves for years. Exactly dude.
Spike TV is dead and Chipotle killed it. It was on MTV but that's fine. You
didn't know that see I don't have to know crap like that you know don't you care
about it so little because every morning you know what I do I have a kid deliver
a bag from Chipotle to my front yard like it's the New York Times and I sit on my
squatty potty and I read the jokes and it's some of the funniest shit I've ever
heard I mean don't forget the cups the cups have some some yeah even there's
also a cup a cup is included I you know I figured that was what do you think he
puts the bag oh god speaking of cups I just found this on my desk that's so
funny oh my god black beans I just I apparently have a black beans near my
computer okay you're at Chipotle addict and I might have to cut you off damn hey
that day I mean those black beans of the can don't compare to the fresh black
beans that they have at Chipotle that's absolutely I mean yeah they're out of a
can the boy they grow them they use the manure out of the you know what yeah
they have a whole hydroponic farm in the back where they grow beans.
But yeah it's just so funny that I just had these around I don't know it's just like I'm
kind of I'm kind of like what quirky Chipotle fan sometimes sorry guys.
We didn't finish or B you feel the need to make sure that they know to be extra careful
with your food as to not infect you with E. coli.
If you're afraid of the food or the prep why are you there?
The situation was handled and we all know it and are gleefully back to waiting in lines
that wrap around the block for our burrito goodness.
You're an adult, you should be able to figure this one out.
Absolutely dude.
Oh, wait, before we go on to this next one, I think we have a, I think we have an ad read
dude.
Oh no, this one is an ad read.
Don't even get me started on these.
Yeah, okay wait.
What even is the ad this week?
gay stupid burrito company what's it called cam what I don't know what's it
called yeah who cares whatever yeah I guess they have some I guess they have
some new burger on the menu and yeah I guess it's called the Chipotle burger
who cares what the fuck is this stupid who gives a shit I guess it's got like I
don't know like two crispy never frozen beef patties with probably like lettuce
and tomato, fresh jalapenos, and it's got something called their signature chipotle
queso. Yeah, sounds awesome. Oh, and let me guess, oh and let me guess, no it's stupid,
and oh let me guess, it costs $4.99 and comes with chips and a soda. Yeah, sounds so good.
Yeah, sure, who buys this crap? And I guess, I mean, I'm reading this thing, apparently it comes
of some some sort of Netflix free trial or something yeah that's some gay shit who
cares fart probably tastes like an ass and it gives you a shit I mean
*laughing*
*more laughing*
*even more laughing*
Dude that's it you can't say that dude
You can't say that about the ad
You're in trouble
I don't care dude who cares about this shit. I mean who wants this crap cream of queso drip
Dripping off of an all-american beef patty cooked to perfection
Yeah, I'm gonna Ralph. Yeah, and listen. I don't even care if we lose this sponsorship because who's it from who?
Because who gives a shit I think it's from Chipotle or some shit like that
It's all just bullcrap anyway, whatever if you're
Enough to still want this delicious bullshit use code dookie at poop
For a 1 million percent discount or some crap like that
Boy I just want to say I just you know coming off that I just really want to quickly say Brian nickel
CEO of Chipotle if you're listening this we do we don't know
Caleb why really we really we know no guys where we think it's very cool
You went to Miami University and the University of Chicago Booth School of Business and you were in five
fraternity with and one of the best businessmen no businessmen, that's
From I learned from other podcasts you you're supposed to like they want you to be like kind of mean to the thing
It's like people think it's like funny. Well, I would never I would never be mean to them
You're right. I'm
You're right, I'm fucking up. I'm sorry. Yeah, but Chipotle
I'm sorry. You have some of the most delicious
Jennifer nickel right now and I think you did a great job. Yeah, Brian nickel
You actually have an extremely bang of a wife and there's nothing stupid or fart about your company
And thank you for the opportunity, sir
Okay, number four stop filling your water cup up with soda, oh my god, I hate these freaks
I get a water cup all the time, but I fill it up with water. Yeah, I fill it up with maybe carbonated water.
I actually buy a soda and I fill it up with water just because I want to give them more money without taking any of their syrup.
Yes.
Exactly. Yeah, cuz syrup costs money. You know, that's like six or seven cents. They gotta get that out of trees. Exactly.
Yeah, they have to get it out of a Coca-Cola tree. You know how long it takes?
You know how many gallons of sap it takes to get the syrup? Probably millions.
Takes 40 400 gallons two gallons of syrup to make five million gallons of soda and we're wasting this
And that's just fucked up to the max
I don't do that shit because I don't I'm not gonna disrespect one of the most yeah
Yeah, sustainable and an amazing work culture restaurant priests it they treat their slaves well
Mm-hmm exactly the syrup slaves who?
Harvest the Mountain Dew syrup from the they don't have Mountain Dew they have coke products do the mountain tree
What they don't have mellow yellow yellow yellow do that again?
Yeah, okay the slaves who harvest the mountain yellow tree
No, some of them mellow yellow tree are some of the most well treated slaves way better than the slaves in Star Wars
Yes, yep, so absolutely they don't make they don't make them sit. They don't have a city
They don't have to sleep in the hut. They don't have to sleep in the sandcrawler
Exactly. They get a sleeping bag outside under the stars.
They get a normal. In beautiful Antarctica.
They get a normal metal bed like anybody else.
Mm-hmm.
Sheet metal, all sheet metal, 100%.
Well, it's the same stuff, it's the same foil
that goes over the top of the bowls when you get just to go.
Yeah. Yep.
Yeah.
Yep, and they get bag pillows.
Yep.
I would, dude, I wish I was living as a slave
for Chipotle right now.
Oh my God.
Seems like my everyday-- Consider me one already.
Yeah, my wallet is becoming like a slave
to Chipotle pretty recently.
you know especially during the war I mean recently like and also just like 24/7
before Korea pre yeah pre-war you know before Quentin Quarantino mm-hmm my god
absolutely yeah who's not welcome at Chipotle by the way too rude yeah oh
yeah and his movies scary yep number five don't be the one who doesn't
understand that blenders break see listen I know you're good you're headed to
- So, Chipotle, you're saying,
"I'm gonna get a barbacoa smoothie.
"I've been looking forward to this all week."
You show up, they say, "Sorry, it's actually under
"maintenance because we had to blend a bunch
"of barbacoa smoothies to feed some of our slaves."
- We were trying to shred a head of lettuce in there
'cause we ran out of shredded lettuce.
And it shot out and it beamed one of our employees
in the head and he ate his skull.
- A whole fucking thing of lettuce just cut off
part of our employee's head.
actually the Bloods and the Crips had a shootout in Chipotle and they actually shot the
blender to death. So we can't really make you a barbacoa smoothie right now. You'll have to come
back, I don't know, in five minutes. And one of these Karen's, right? I mean, stop me if I'm wrong,
but a Karen will be like, "Uh, excuse me, I want my meat smoothie ASAP." And it's like,
come on.
It's like, what? Come on, your name's not Rocky.
Yes.
And that's like, come on.
Your name's not Yams.
And that's the kind of thing that like a Chipotle--
It's like, come on, your name's not Ferg.
Chipotle's tuned in with hip-hop culture as well. Yeah, come on. Your name's not rock. Yeah. Yep. Mm-hmm. Come on
Your name's not ASAP
Yeah, one of them. I don't remember. I think you said all the ones I know
Yeah, but I just want you guys to read the first little sentence of this one though
Cuz it's like I know we read some crazy-ass shit
We find on the internet sometimes but I just can't imagine like what kind of person writes this. Oh my god
It says I know it's hard for you to accept but sometimes
This in quotes fecal matter hits the oscillating rotary propeller. Oh
Yeah, in other words shit hits the fan oh
Yeah
yeah, I'm glad they went with the first one because
Wow, yeah, that's insane. I mean yeah because after they said that first one I was saying to myself
Explain like I'm five. Yeah, you know. Yeah, I was saying change my mind
Yeah, and then they and they did I was saying am I the asshole
When the shit hits a fan, there's nothing the employees can do about it
In other words, they just may not have the precious vinaigrette your girlish figure requires today get over it
Stop acting like a petulant three-year-old newsflash. This is not the worst curveball life is gonna throw you
I'm sure you'll find a way to cope and that's very true. Sometimes I come in counterpoint though could get cancer or something
to me
Not getting my Chipotle order
That is maybe the worst curveball life is gonna throw. That's worse than that's worse than the big C. What Caleb is saying.
Yeah, I mean the real big C is Chipotle in my eyes. Yep. Yep
No, no negativity only positivity. That's right
Number six don't order over the phone. Who? Okay, grandma much? Yeah. Yeah, what do you what do you?
Dialing up your rotary phone you old bitch. Yeah, what did you use? What did you use the
What did you talk to an operator to get you there? Yeah, we fucking stupid old bitch. Yeah
Are you an immigrant? Yeah, I ought to break your knee. What wait? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
That's your chip. No Chipotle. No, what are you talking about? What don't say that? Don't
We'll cut that out ladies and gentlemen of earth. It is
2016 just
Yep, it is just like Millennials don't understand why old people insist upon leaving voicemail when they could just text you the employees at Chipotle
Don't understand why you feel the need to pull them away from what they're doing having fun working Chipotle
So that they can have a 10-minute conversation with you about your order
They have the internet you can order online and they have a fax machine. They know how to use them
See, that's what we're saying is instead of calling you should send them a fax
With your order.
Yeah, because what do you, you're so old school you're trying to use your phone.
Send them a fax.
You know what is on a fax machine?
A phone.
They have a phone on it.
That's a really good point, but don't call that.
Don't call the fax machine, all you hear is.
I send them, I mean, every morning when I'm getting ready for my breakfast order to walk
in and pick it up, I send my local Chipotle a fax and it says, it's a piece of paper that
says my burrito.
And they know exactly.
- Yep.
- 'Cause you're one of these next guys.
- I'm a regular.
They know my computer's handwriting.
The font, I mean.
The font I use, Wingdings.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
Number seven, don't be the customer who comes in every day
and asks the same stupid questions every day.
And they have a little script here.
If you guys wanna read this.
- Okay. - Oh, okay.
- I think you and Caleb would be great.
- I wanna be employee.
- Oh, okay, well either way,
I'm happy to be an employee or a customer.
let's just pretend it's two employees talking to each other.
- Okay, but one of the employees is named customer.
- Yeah, okay.
Are those black beans?
- Do they look black?
- I guess, smiley face.
- Do they resemble the same black beans
you ordered yesterday?
- Yes.
- Then yes, I'd have to say after using my Sherlock Holmes
like powers of deduction that these are indeed black beans.
- Oh my God.
- Yeah, narrator line, Patrick?
I think you get the point. Yeah, you fucking, you are such a piece of shit if you don't know
how to order a Chipotle. You're like a, you're an animal. You are lower than a human. You
are pond scum that should be fucking incinerated. You dog shit piece of ass. Stop asking, do
you know guacamole actually costs extra? You fucking mongrel. You should be put down in
the street. Piece of shit. Some of you guys, yeah, they just need to, some of these people
it's like you just got to knock him out yeah when you see you should you're
allowed you should be allowed to punch the person in front of you in line at
Chipotle if they are taking too long I need my stuff I mean really it's why I
have a doom wad of Chipotle is just in case there's a situation like that where
you know there's I've got three Kyle's in front of me in the line oh don't get
me started and they're saying and they're saying oh which is which is
- Which is white rice and which is black rice?
I only see one color.
- Wow.
- That is some Karen shit.
- Yeah, and the only color, green,
like the Monster Energy logo.
- Definitely. - Yep.
- Yeah, that's some Kyle shit.
- If you don't know how to order Chipotle,
you should be thrown in the trash
like a half-day-old tortilla
instead of being donated to a shelter.
- They should have a machine
like they use to kill the little boy chickens.
- Yep, definitely.
- And they throw all the Kyles in there at Chipotle.
- I agree.
I've been saying this for--
- There should be a trap door--
- 48 minutes.
should be a trap door in front of the Chipotle sneeze guard and you stand in
front of it and if you're taking too damn long you get thrown in a rancor pit
definitely dude defo for shizzle mm-hmm I would pay to have a rancor and
startled in a Chipotle yeah we'll get an animatronic Disney World rancor and he
will be he will be and get this they can milk him use it for sour cream well
- Oh! - That's definitely true.
That's definitely fucking true.
- So good, that'd be so good.
- Pat, you wanna handle number eight for us?
- Don't be a person on your phone while online,
especially when it's busy.
I'm glad I handled that.
- What, what's up?
- So finish it though.
- Okay.
- He started, he finished. - Fellow citizens,
I understand that you believe that your phone call
is indeed the most important thing,
not only in your life, but indeed the world.
Maybe it is.
Maybe you're on the phone with a high-ranking
government official discussing a detailed plan
on how to cure cancer or create world peace.
However, if this isn't the case,
get off the damn phone and pay attention
to what's going on in front of you.
- And that's actually Chipotle official policy,
is if you're on the phone,
they have every right to ask you to leave,
but if you say, sorry, I'm on the phone
with a high-ranking government official
discussing a detailed plan on how to cure cancer
or create world peace, they have to let you do it.
It's just kinda, I mean, that's just
for the kind of company they are.
- I mean, that's just how great they are to their customers.
- Yeah, it's 'cause they believe in cancer
and they believe in world peace.
- I also like, I really like on this,
we're just like a comment about the website
and not really so much Chipotle.
I just love the image they've selected for this one.
It's kind of like a blue, light blue picture
with some line drawings of forks and whisks.
- Well, then you're gonna love the next one.
- You're gonna love the picture, number nine.
- It's the exact same picture.
- Oh, it's the same one, but bigger.
This website, I mean, they get it.
That's all.
I mean, I don't wanna talk too much about it.
- They understand foodies like us.
- Oh yeah, I don't want it to sound forced,
but they get it.
- Yep.
- SpoonUniversity.com, check it out.
- Oh Pat, do you have something to read?
- Oh yeah.
- Do you have something to read today or something?
- I do, I do have a poem that I wrote.
- Oh that's so beautiful dude,
I bet it's about something that you love more than anything
as poetry usually is about.
- I mean, it is Valentine's Day when we're recording this,
so I figure, hell, why not talk about,
Why not spread some love?
Why not talk about love?
- Definitely.
- And this is a poem I wrote about love.
It's called "Loving Lifestyle."
When I was a much younger lad,
I went to Chipotle with my dad.
As we stood in line, it said chills down my spine,
and I thought, how could a restaurant have it all?
From delicious corn slaw and Mr. Pibb in a cup so large,
I turned to my father and I said,
"Dad, did we just arrive in heaven?"
He said, "No, son, we are just in Chipotle."
Fajita veggies, sofritas, and barbacoa.
I hope that this meal is never over.
Salads, tacos, and lifestyle bowls.
Without Chipotle, my life no longer feels whole.
Tapo Chico, Corona Lite, and Grapefruit Izzy.
Hell, it's no wonder why Chipotle is always so busy.
I miss my grandma so much, I wish I could text her.
And yes, I know that the guac is cost extra.
Romaine lettuce, cheese, and sour cream.
This restaurant is a white boy's dream.
Keto bowl, high protein bowl, vegan bowl.
When I'm at Chipotle, I wish I could eat it all.
Awesome chips and hot queso blanco.
This bullshit's turned me into a bucking bronco.
If I ever see you put soda inside of a water cup,
you will know that your time is now up.
Carnitas steak and beautiful chicken.
When you're done at Chipotle, your fingers get my licking.
- Okay, he did that.
- White rice, brown rice, and pinto beans.
Chipotle will show you what life truly means.
Thank you, Chipotle, for all that you've done for me.
I hope when I am to be wed, it is inside your establishment.
And that's called Loving Lifestyle by Patrick E. Doran.
- Jesus Christ.
- I mean, he ate that up.
- Yeah, is that the one that you're doing on the moth lighter?
- Yes.
- Wow, that's gonna be really powerful.
That's gonna be like one of those viral videos.
- Mm-hmm. - Yeah.
- That's gonna be huge, dude.
- I hope I can change the world with my poetry.
- Yeah, that'll definitely overtake that video
that guy crying about his dead daughter.
That'll be like a million times sadder
and like more touching, you know?
- I mean, yeah, this is about me and my father.
- Yeah, I mean, yeah, dude.
- Yeah.
- Father-brother bond.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, that's like unshakable.
- It's like another level of stuff.
I mean, Chipola gets it too, so.
- Yeah.
- I'm hoping that they hear this and they put it on one of their bags, fingers crossed.
- Oh, dude, okay, buddy.
I think that might be a little unrealistic.
I mean, you know, that's for people like David Sedaris or...
- Yeah.
- Well, hopefully I can be like them one day and get my writing on a Chipotle bag.
- Well, you're gonna have to navigate through the wild world of humorism before you get
that far.
Let me tell you what.
let's do an announcement for the fans let's say any we're looking for fan art
bag fan art yeah maybe you want to put any specific text on a Chipotle bag yes
that'd be like I'd love to really sick yeah yeah yeah and maybe you know who
knows maybe one of them will end up a Chipotle bag one day officially I don't
know it could be a contest here's hoping yep and that is a and please if that
does happen please put poem by P.E. Doran. Mm-hmm mm-hmm P.E. D.O. No it's not how it's
stylized. You can drop the end of the last name. That's not my poem name. It is your
signature is how you like sign check. Well you know what my poem name is. It's like R.L.
Stein. No my okay then my poetry name is Poet of Thunder. I don't think so. So if
you do that put it so yep so we're putting PEDO Thunder at the bottom of the bag
no yep that that works great number nine don't be the customer that gets asked if
they want chips and a drink only to say no and then later at the register after
you've been rung up ask for chips and a drink anyway yeah what the fuck is wrong
with you yeah you should be sterilized if you do this you should absolutely be
forced sterilized yeah you should be castrated you should have your hands
chopped off like a like a thief in Saudi Arabia. Hey when when somebody this is
this is a the guy when he this is a guy on one day he comes up he goes hey I'd
like yeah actually I want a chips and drink after all this is him coming back
to Chipotle the next day yeah I'll take a chips and a drink after all. He got
chopped he got snatched. Yeah now he's a he's a what are they called? Boys. He's a boy
Definitely, yeah.
You know you want the chips and the drink. Of course you do.
You always do. Everybody always does.
But if you are indeed one of the people concerned with your healthy lifestyle,
consider that the burrito you have just ordered is roughly the size of your torso.
Yeah, that's a big-ass burrito.
Ask yourself if the added calories of chips and drink really matter in the wake of the realization you have just made,
and commit to a decision and go with it.
But do so BEFORE you get to the cashier.
This saves him time and energy so they can crack right along helping the other well adjusted
folks in line.
Yeah, unlike you, you're a mental health disaster.
Yes, good, moving on.
Ooh, number 10 has another script.
And a Michael Scott gif.
Number 10, don't be the so-called regular who justifies a demanding attitude with frequent
patronage.
Okay, I'm done being the customer.
Somebody else take over the reins.
I'll be the customer.
Yeah, I bet you will.
I would love to be a Chipotle customer.
just start. Okay. Can I have a side of diced tomatoes? I'm sorry we don't have
any pre-diced tomatoes. What we did have has been used in the salsa. But I come
here every day! Okay, well I work in here every day. We don't have them. Should I
call in a grief counselor? Are you gonna cry like a baby? The thing about this one
is like if they'd if the customer had read the list they'd know not to ask for
diced tomatoes. Right, definitely. They should print this out and keep it in
front of the restaurant. Yeah, they should put it, absolutely, I think it would solve a lot
of problems. Yep. Number 11, don't be vague when specificity is obviously required.
Another office gif, one of the, I mean, what's a better show? You wouldn't walk
into a Baskin-Robbins and say, "I'd like ice cream," and then blankly stare at the
man/woman behind the counter as if they have a crystal ball and magically knew
what flavor of ice cream you want, would you? Of course not. So why then would you
shuffle down the food station, look at employees standing in front of six
troughs of obviously different meats and tell them that you want meat and your
burrito and look at them. Who knows? But somehow it happens all the same.
#UnsolvedMysteries. Yeah what are you? Are you fucking Rose Kennedy?
Are you being lobotomized? What is wrong with you? I think we might need to get the BuzzFeed
Unsolved guys on this one. Yeah absolutely. Oh my god. They would go to town. They just
have like a goofy rapport that I think would... mm-hmm. Yeah. Definitely. I don't have to
spell it out for you guys. Yeah. Number 12. Don't be the one to ask what do you mean
guac is extra. Ugh. They got a nice meme on here. Anyone want to read the meme?
Yeah, I got you. Guacamole is an extra two dollars and it's a woman who's
crying. Yeah. Oh my god. Yeah. It is kind of funny. Yeah, talk about first world problems.
Yeah. Oh, sorry guys, I just saw the picture of the woman under the text. Yeah, yeah.
It's pretty fucking... that's fire. Retweet. This is what hits you in two waves. I'm gonna retweet that one.
I'm going to pin this to my Pinterest.
Absolutely.
Let's see here, pin.
Oh my god.
Can I pin this too?
Hold on, I have to sign up.
I'm going to pin this on my body with a tattoo.
One second.
I'm going to create a QR code for this page.
That's such a smart idea.
All right, I'm downloading it.
You low-key a genius.
I'm going to share this QR code to Instagram.
Are you really?
Oh, then I can scan it from there.
Dude, I love QR codes.
I love shareable shit like that.
Number 13, don't be the customer that orders a kid's meal during a rush with no kid in
tow.
That's right.
If you don't have a kid, don't order a kid's meal.
Exactly.
We can tell.
We can tell that you're not a kid.
Unless you have a mental IQ of 90 or less.
First off, what the hell are you doing in Chipotle?
And if you have a mental IQ of...
It's a restaurant for smart people.
Okay, mental IQ over 90, you can order anything. You have to order adult's meal.
90 to 40, you gotta get a kid's meal. 39 or under, it's a bowl of water for you.
You might as well be a dog.
Because you're a dog, here's a treat. Yeah, be gone.
Call me when you've listened to all of Cereal. You know?
Get smart!
like the movie yeah and Terry Shivo we Chipotle is a fucking restaurant for real
people with thoughts and souls you know get out of here you might have to put I
would love to put yeah Chipotle and Terry Shivo's feeding - it could have
saved her it could have yeah yeah it's like yeah it's if you if you if your IQ
you're slow enough that you don't have the you're incapable of dreaming yeah
definitely I mean why would we expect you to be able to dream of a better food
yeah you're just a nothing person and I don't want to ever see you're like a
you're like a zero yeah zero or less you're like if you're like if somebody
like ripped the paper that we were all animated on there was a scary hole
absolutely right where you are definitely and it's no use to pour to
put chipotle into the hole because it's just I love to pour some chipotle into my
hole. Okay well that's kind of disgusting. My mouth hole. You're actually, oh okay now
you're making me really hungry. So let's finish off this list so I can go get
some chipotle. How's that sound? Yeah. Yeah. Number 14, don't be the customer who
makes a redundant order. Yeah. Yeah. When a customer has something like, "Can I have
some cheese in my quesarito?" The employee may say, "What do you think it's called that for?" Yes, yeah sorry. Do you not know that
that queso Rito is Spanish for queso burrito yeah cheese burrito for cheese
queso Rito idiot the employee may say yes but what he or she really wants to
say is it's a hybrid of a queso dia and a burrito it's already filled with cheese
mm-hmm so the next time you visit your friendly and inviting neighborhood
Chipotle which it always is by the way please resist the urge to interrogate
annoy torment pester plague molest worry badger hairy harass heckle persecute
irk, bully, rag vex, disquiet, goad, beset, bother, tease, nettle, tantalize, or ruffle
the employee in front of you. Do not tantalize the employee. Stop molesting Chipotle employees.
It's, they don't, listen, you gotta stop doing that. Knock it off. It's a big problem.
If you dangle a coin in front of the sneeze guard, the Chipotle employees don't know any better.
They'll try and jump through the sneeze guard. They'll shatter it with their forehead. Their
Their head's gonna fall on the meat,
and the meat's gonna be not ruined,
but their face is gonna get really messy,
it's gonna waste a little bit of it.
- Yeah, and don't come complaining to me
when we're out of chorizo.
All right, I think that everybody's pretty well educated
on how to act at a Chipotle now.
- Yeah.
- Like we said, we have some big sponsors coming up,
so just stay tuned for that kind of crap.
- Yeah, and we can't really say what--
- Can't really tell you who it is yet.
is yes however much money we receive to do whatever many hundreds we already did
or are going to do it's kind of all up in the air
well for you we know exactly Chipotle no okay I'm leaving all right we have the
episode all right see ya what what did I do wrong