You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
- Podcasts for the mindless.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Ah, that's the intro.
Ah, me screaming.
- That was some Twilight Zone shit right there.
That was so scary.
I hope I wake up from this nightmare
where Dustin Diamond has died.
- I heard they're making a new Twilight Zone
where the guy looks on the Zoom call
and they see and he sees there's a gremlin that joined the zoom call
he looks at the zoom call and Dustin Diamond is back
yeah oh my god Dustin Diamond is digging around in his computer and ripping out
parts and his computer is
Dustin Diamond
none of his co-workers believe him
Dustin Dimebag Darrell
oh my god
two guys that are dead
that's so sad to think about
yeah
I would love to, did you guys watch the updated Twilight Zone one with Jordan and Phil?
No I didn't watch it, I heard it wasn't good.
Kumail Nanjiani's in it.
I thought you were gonna say, have you watched the Timebag Darrell assassination video?
[laughter]
I genuinely thought you were gonna ask me that.
I haven't seen it.
Me neither.
Dude I could never watch that, it would break my heart.
Assassination, that's a strong word.
He got assassinated.
It was an assassination.
He was assassinated.
assassination yeah the assassination of Dimebag Darrell by the Coworkers
on stage well I guess I need to see the the I don't think there's footage of it
assassinate well I just googled assassination for some reason instead of
Dimebag Darrell. Oh like the first picture is Dimebag. I think he was assassinated yeah he was
assassinated. That just brings to mind like Kill Bill style like Kung Fu Death
yeah when you hear somebody like a political figures a samurai that's like
agent 47 like who killed this guy who agent 47 did I make arrows and killed
it no see was it was a deranged welcome 47 that's still he has the Confederate
flag on his guitar he gets kicked out of the show where you live yeah
You're too corporate to be here for Dimebag Daryl, dude.
Did you, I talked about it before and it's, and you guys have no idea what I'm talking about,
but the 8-bit guy is his second cousin.
Yeah, I don't know. Again, nobody knows.
That's for the fans. That's something I'm saying for the fans, not for you.
You know what you should say for the fans? A fucking joke.
Oh, I didn't know Dimebag Daryl and Vinnie Paul were brothers.
Vinnie Paz?
All fat like white guys with fucked up mudslide faces are all related. That's true. Yeah
Dude, they're the Pantera brothers. They should have called that band the Pantera brothers. Yeah, that's their last name
That'll be a way cooler band. Yeah, Pantera's Pantera even mean the terrible music
What are you talking about man? Pantera is not good. Y'all are old
Pantera I mean okay Pantera is cool as hell. Walk is a great song. Yeah Walk fucking
Cowboys from Hell is a good song. I think they're they're a great hit. They have some good
ass songs. I miss the pants era. Yeah where Joey Pants where uh. Who's Joey Pants?
You can pant somebody in a whistle and salt. Who is Joey Pants? Joe Pantoliano the guy who plays Ralph
Oh yeah yeah what about Joey Pants era? There we go yeah what happened to him dude he
was in a good string of Memento Matrix of Sopranos yeah oh yeah dude the early
2000s that was the Joey Pants era that yeah and then it ended the Joey Pants
era ended exactly at the same time that Dimebag Daryl was assassinated Wow mm-hmm
think about it makes you wonder about it I've been watching a lot of the kid from
Brooklyn oh yeah yeah as he doing doing a read he's dead he's been dead forever oh
he's dead yeah you know the guy the I'd walk a mile yeah yeah dead yeah yeah I
look at that guy a couple months ago you could like I could have looked at you
and guess that you were dead even though I was on a zoom call with you really
yeah was I I don't know I don't think I was that big you had it looked like that
guy you just had evil eyes yeah yeah kind of because I was fucking drinking all the
time and I wouldn't sleep yeah that's true now you have straight hours yeah
now that I quit right now I'm drinking Budweiser zero bit by a sober spider
yeah man sober man dude it's gonna be is a new era
sober man you just walk over man's parties and then just just bore
everybody's here sober man putting I just pushing drug addicts off the top of
buildings sober man's like superpower is his ability to put on jazz fusion at a
party yeah and be like this is like this is like gets my brain high almost this
yeah this is kind of like like there's the amount of notes in this gives me
more dopamine than a cigarette ever could I feel like Steely Dan is the ultimate
sober man's music no are you kidding I feel like that's it that's a no no no
that's that's like good what you said old sober dad loves Steely Dan no no I
went to a Steely Dan show in October there was a dude fucking
rolling a dude who looked like Michael McDonald in the front row going fucking
clone yeah he's standing there he keeps taking like they you weren't allowed to
use your phone because it's fucking dude it's all fucking boomers I don't know
what like it's lame to say boomer but like it was all boomers there and they
were like oh stay off your phone experience the show or whatever that's
this guy is in the front row pulling his phone out pointing at the band he's
doing the fucking he was doing the rope thing like he was doing the lasso to the
Danettes it fucking it rocked. Also you fucking, if you listen to Steely Dan you're old you're
gonna sit down with a with a little thingy of whiskey you know? Right.
You're gonna sip some scotch dude. Drink scotch whiskey all night long.
I've heard two Steely Dan songs.
That's more than enough to tell that you would drink whiskey while listening to it.
It's not, no, not for me, no.
It feels--
- Because you're stupid and your brain doesn't work.
- That's fine.
The oldest guy I ever saw at a concert
was at a Snoop Dogg concert.
It was like a 90 year old man
in the front row with his girlfriend.
And I have a video of him and he started during
Drop It Like It's Hot, he started like
doing like a, making circles with his fists.
But it looked like he was like, he like could barely move.
- Yeah, that's awesome.
yeah he was the man dude yeah yeah I just want to be that kind of music
enjoyer where I'm even late in my life. When you're like 90 years old. Like imagine Snoop Dogg came out when you're 60.
And you're really fucking into that. And 30 years later you're still doing it.
Showing up to a Trippie Redd concert in 60 years. Yeah exactly. You know what'd be weird though is like a
60 year old now being into 100 gecs. That wouldn't be weird.
Sounds like a dialysis machine.
I feel so clean like my dialysis machine.
Yeah, I don't know.
I feel like that makes sense.
Just, you know, computer noises.
Yeah.
Yeah, might be scary.
You'd have to be an old man who was really into soldering to get to 100 kits.
Yeah.
I feel like that is something that like, that might be the limit for like even somebody like
my parents age where you show them that and they're like I don't even know what
yeah I can't process yeah it sounds like a like a white noise machine yeah sounds
like my computer crashing in 1998 I think the speaker I think my Alexa is broken
yeah what's going on I can't wait until the next wave of music that's impossible
for us to understand because like I think a hundred gecs for a lot of people
our age is kind of already pushing it which is crazy like you know what I mean
like yeah fucking well that's early 20s and already people will be like I can't
even what is this but like so I want the next thing that's like just so far
beyond that you know it'll be it'll be you know those websites where you play
different tones that only people of certain ages can hear
but it'll be they'll do it so that if you're older than like 22 you physically
cannot yeah yeah I'll be like listen to this I don't hear anything well you
fucking yeah yeah that's the thing I think like the generation before us like
probably 2004 and up they all grew up listening to like chipmunked versions of
fucking like yeah that's true of regular songs that like 100 gecs just makes so
much sense yeah yeah nightcore zombie yeah oh yeah I'm wearing a heater
we're in boxers right now instead of briefs and my ball my ball is poking out
I can feel it I can feel it through my jeans like I can feel my ball is like
getting pinched out of the leg opening what are you doing what are you looking
I'm looking at my balls.
I'm free-balling in a pair of cut-off sweatshorts that have a rip that goes all the way from
the inseam on the leg to the other inseam on the other leg.
So it's just like a kill.
Oh, are they split in the middle?
Like your balls?
Yeah, so my balls and my penis are both making an appearance.
It's doing that to me, but it's only pushing them to my right side of my leg.
not doing anything to you you are in control of both your body and the clothes
just yeah I wanted to have my balls out cuz it's a little bit hot in my
apartment the heat is not as cold as you're I have to I have to get some
jacket you hippie yeah you just took off your hoodie at the beginning I I
underestimated you want to be naked all the time no I know you just want to show
I'm not it I'm the furthest thing from a nudist that's not and what's that a mummy
You claim you're a mummy right now, I guess
Why did you get Patrick really until wearing like a Victorian dresses where you have to put on like three corsets under it?
I get under dress and a dress and an overdress and a petticoat. He should get back into wearing dresses. Yeah
You used to be a girl like two or three years ago. No, I did it or something like that
No, we're dresses. Don't start a rumor. It's not a room. I'm right. What's up?
Remember Pat used to wear dresses. I did
Pat you can't hear that. He was whispering. I heard it
He put his hand over his mouth to block I talked in a tone that was too too low for you to hear. Mm-hmm
Yeah, hey, yeah, you see yours can only hear really high-pitched noises and not low
- I hope his voice is, 'cause he's a baby.
- Why aren't you-- - What?
- Now you do sound like a normal dude.
- Hey, yeah, man.
- This is fucking offensive, dude.
- Hey, Patrick, why are you talking in your normal voice?
- Yeah.
- I don't know.
- You sound like my friend's deaf Spanish teacher.
(laughing)
I don't like that.
- Your 14-year-old friend?
- Yeah.
- Why did that, why was there so much like,
that resonated, yeah.
I echoed a bunch.
That's when you just like stepped on a reverb pedal when you said that.
Did it do it again?
No, it didn't do it again.
I think it was the springs on your mic arm.
I'm gonna get more into effects.
Yeah.
Oh, I would love to.
I'm leaning towards effects right now.
Yeah.
We should get more effects on this show.
Okay.
I don't think so.
Why not, Kim?
Did that do an effect?
Oh, okay.
okay that was a guy was actually pretty cool I hope people are listening to this
and Dolby digital 7.1 surround sound right now oh man did you hear that new
effect that I just used you sounded like I was insane do that again okay towards
the end you sound like miss foul I think if you can hone in on the end you sound
like miss foul I think you both smell pretty foul oh now let's do this damn
list how about that oh yeah you do no I don't you smell like eggs dude I don't
smell like it that's on I'll blow I smell like a delicious fresh eggs right
I'm still laughing at IO Block, dude.
(laughing)
- Just like Chicago, like improv.
- Yeah, Dye L's, man, Second City, man.
I, Improv Olympic, man.
IO Block, 300 gang.
- Yeah.
- There's so many, there's so many improv beaters.
- Delve Close with a dove emoji.
(laughing)
FBG Delve Close, man.
That's real shit right there.
The Annoyance, man.
Shout out The Annoyance, man.
- Yeah, man, 300 hour.
- 300 gang, man.
Hideout gang only, man.
Hey Big H up, what's up?
(laughing)
For some reason I--
Chief Keith spotted with Vanessa Bayer leaving.
(laughing)
Oh fuck, yeah, but that was making me laugh earlier.
Yeah, me too.
I was thinking about, man,
there's so much improv in Chicago.
Damn, it's like a--
They should improve.
Yeah, what's up with that?
They should improve their mare.
They're always mad at their mare.
Their fricking Rahm Emanuel, Lori Layfoot, doesn't matter.
Lori Layfoot, what is that, the name of a hobbit?
Hey, there we go.
Come on.
Yeah, they should call her Lori Stinkyfoot.
Oh shit.
Oh shit, god damn.
Oh.
Damn.
I'm all out, sorry guys. That's all I have on Lori Lightfoot.
Stop! Stop dude, she's already dead!
Come on man, stop!
Knock it off, Dammit.
You did too much!
You're on too much of a heater today, dude. Tone it down, dude.
Did you see, um, it was like a...
Somebody posted it.
It was like a thing about how her road
was like the most plowed
in all of Chicago right now.
Yeah, so was her ass.
Oh no! God! That's not fair! What? No! Oh fuck! Stop! Oh fuck! You play too much Cam. Yeah, yeah.
Did you guys hear that her, that she actually, something about Cam you might
want to listen up. She had a, she had a pet cat, right? A cat. And the cat was
apparently like really smelly for some reason that's interesting fuck you dude
come on you supposed to sit I don't know who this lady is I forget who we're
talking about yeah she's like scary look we're talking about Gordon light yeah
what she looks like she wrecked her Edmund Fitzgerald am I right come on my
ass oh she looks a little bit like uncle
fester if I'm being honest don't say
that yeah oh my what other songs did
Gordon light foot just the wreck of the
Edmund Fitzgerald that's kind of all
he's known for is that really no he's
known for one other song no wreck of the
Edmund Fitzgerald I mean Gordon Lightfoot hey great-looking guy I'll say that whoa
never seen a picture of him before he back in the 70s he looked good he looks
like a wizard now but back then that's a good-looking dude you're saying a wizard
doesn't look good nowadays no yeah what are you talking about dude nowadays a
wizard looks like shit what's wrong all these wizards they got nowadays are
looking like shit yeah they should be going
god you're driving me crazy with that cuz I can't find my thingy mm-hmm that's
right one of the saddest things of my life today I can't find it's it's
fucking I'm snowed in I'm snowed in I'm Edward Joe hey come get it hey come get
him NSA am i right mm-hmm cam did you take like a comedy pill before we started
today or something. Like you're the funniest thing you've ever been. I can't leave my house,
I can't go get a vape, I can't go get a gamers delight. I'm in like the worst mood I've ever
been in. There's snow everywhere, I can barely open my door, I walk out of my window to get
to the street.
You walk out of your window to get to the street? You don't walk out no damn window.
You're on the 100th floor.
Yeah I know and I fall about 95 feet. There's 5 feet of snow.
so much but it breaks my fall and then I just wait every floor is one foot tall
yep I live on floors on floors 80 to 90 yeah so every brick is a floor it's true
Yeah, this is my 1000 story home. Yeah, I'm gonna stick. Yeah, hey cuz if you come
hang out with me you're gonna have a thousand stories spending time in this
Wow one apartment is worth a thousand stories exactly Wow especially in NYC
yeah that's true nowadays I'm thinking of buying a house yeah yeah I don't have
any money to do that but I'm thinking I'm really rich soon off of some
I've been watching Property Brothers lately, because with my girlfriend.
Yeah, those brothers go crazy.
They go nuts, dude.
What are they dating?
Zoe Dachanel.
It's so fun to just...
I think they're both dating whoever one of them dates.
That's right.
If I'm being honest.
Do you think they can only date twins?
Aren't they triplets?
Yeah, there's another one who's like goth or something.
Yeah.
People always post and are like, "Look at this."
Yeah, it's always like, "Yo, look at the goth Property Brother."
so fun to just be imagine being on that show and just being really mean to them
because everyone's so nice to them all the time they're all like just like being
with their like when they're like yeah we found asbestos in your house to be
like fuck you man you may be by this house you yeah I'm in the fantasy
festival how about you get up there and you eat it you fucking monkey go how
about you and your brother fucking go up there and finger each other you fucking
weirdo get up in the attic and start ripping that asbestos down cuz you do
not want me to get my hands on you yep the property brothers and Travis Scott
I have this house for three weeks and it's not done.
What are you guys doing?
You just fucking each other all the time?
I'm paying you to build my house.
Just calling them on the phone, doing one of those scenes where they call the person
on the phone and it's going, "Buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh,
buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh,
We have it on speaker? Alright, let's call the homeowner and check in to see what they want to do about the asbestos in the living room.
Hey Maria, are you there?
*Duhs*
Maria, we can't hear you.
Oh sorry, I thought that was your language.
Yeah, sorry, I thought I was speaking twin.
Fucking dumbass.
*Laughter*
Pussy boy. Pull up, you have the address?
Speaking twin is like doing like a Sklar Brothers thing where you just kind of like wait until they finish each others.
finish each other's yeah finish each other's this home is gonna cost sentences
exclamation point just two twins you suck at it yeah finish each other's finish
each other's finish each other's spinach finish each other's start each other's
finish each other off what the hell is wrong with these two gay twins that fuck
each other in their face somebody call the cops on these twins yeah
brothers scary yin-yang yeah more like the ah hurdy brothers they're talking
about their butt cheeks which make each other they have fucked they slap each
other's butt cheeks when they're in the house dude how are your butt cheeks after
your brother fucked them and they go "aww hurdy"
okay?
they wouldn't say that
they would say that
they say weird stuff all the time
they say a bunch of weird shit
that's how it works being a twin
I have friends who are twins
one of my friends who is a twin
yeah I can say that about the property brothers
because I have friends who are twins
I do! Twins like to fuck each other
I have a twin friend
I have a twin friend, he says it's okay if I say that the property is brother's fucking
son.
No, my twin friend said it's okay.
In my experience, twins, one twin always loves to call their brother because they got put
in rehab by the city of Detroit.
I had a friend in college who was an identical twin and he was like doing great, like my
friend was doing great, he's a very smart guy, and then three times, three different
times that I was hanging out with him he would get a call either from the police
or from his brother letting him know that his brother was
in rehab for heroin in Detroit. Dude it must be so hard. Does that happen to every twin?
It must be so hard to be a twin. It must be hard to be a twin and like just have to
resist the temptation every single day of your life to become the evil twin.
Well yeah because I think as soon as one pulls ahead just a little bit like as
soon as the first one to get like a star in kindergarten on there like next to
name yeah that's gonna the other one is just immediately gonna turn evil it's
true yeah and start which is evil it's evil to be addicted to drugs it's
evil to have addictions exactly I agree yeah I'm expunging the evil from me yeah
that's why that's why this is the sober man episode mm-hmm yeah are you
throwing caffeine - are you one of those guys I'm not gonna quit caffeine no I
I mean nicotine is already hard enough to quit. It's easy. Yeah? Yeah. You just stop.
Just suck and stop dude. It's easier to quit. It's so much easier to quit
cigarettes than vape. It's literally all you have to do is you sit down and that's
it. That's all you have to do. Because the thing is with quitting cigarettes is that
you can just start vaping. With vaping you can't be like alright I'm quitting
vaping I will replace him with cigarettes. I'm gonna yeah I'm gonna
right I'm gonna lick empty Juul pods that's what I'm replacing it with. I'm
I'm gonna be I'm gonna get a bottom yeah I was thinking of getting the lodges is
I'm gonna get a lozenge I was thinking I'm gonna get the long jizzes yeah I'm
gonna get a nicotine eye patch yeah yeah
that's a good one. You take it off at the end of the day and your eyes just yellow.
It just looks like you have big eyes. You just have a snake eye.
Be cool dude. You have one Sith eye, one regular eye.
I think it would work. Yeah that's the evil coming out of me. It's coming out of
me through my eyes. Yeah it's all, I'm gonna get all the evil
concentrated in my right eye and then I'm gonna have it removed.
yeah that's why the Sith get yellow eyes mm-hmm cuz they smoking fucking you get
that's the thing I don't understand the Sith eyes Anakin got them when you
there I their eyes turn yellow when they drank tuss yeah you remember that young
thug picture oh no it was a picture and said my eyes turn yellow when I drank
tusks and um he just has really bad jaundice. This is what happens dude. Yeah you get, yeah
you siths are all jaundiced that's again why they're evil. Yeah. Yeah. Is Homer Simpson
a sith? Time for some film theory. Yeah he has normal yellow skin. Yeah. Well he's jaundiced.
Hey I don't think he's jaundiced. No. No he's. Then why? He's he's he's Flanders neighbor.
Whoa.
All right, let's start the list.
Flaunders.
Ned Flaunders.
Hey, I'm Ned Flanders.
Hi, I'm Ned Flaunders and I'm here to tell you about the God.
Tell you about the God.
There's one God.
You better fucking, you better believe in this fucking guy.
Top 10s.
I love you.
Top 10 ways to tell someone to shut up.
hey buddy this might come in handy for me that's what I was thinking yeah yeah
Ananya business that should be number one that's right that's fucking right so I
guess we have to do this like when we were doing the comebacks episodes we
have to somebody has to say something to make the other person to tell okay all
right hey check this out blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue blue
shut the f star star star up yeah it's a better read let's let me try that I was
gonna go with clean profanity yeah let's get a cleaner take bloober bloober
bloober bloober shut the f star star star up and more than that what no I actually
want to hear you say what are you what is bloober mean yeah why are you saying
blue why would you go with bloober instead of like blah blah blah like why
did you why'd you go with the bloober dude that's like why don't tell him to
shut up I need to know what in your head is bloober
even process it. I was like, oh yeah, he's saying blooper to me, I better tell him to
shut up. What is blooper, dude? Sometimes you gotta hit him with the blooper. No, you don't
have to hit him with the blooper, because nobody's ever said blooper before. No, it's like blooper
with a B. Alright, new rule for this show, you can't, when you're trying to say nonsense,
you can't just say blooper. It'll throw off everybody's lines. Not true. It will. The
top comment here is, one time I got angry at someone so much about all the crap he kept
saying about me that I accidentally told him to shut up in my native language and
it actually made him shut up yeah I feel like getting told to shut up or anything
like that in a different language maybe say bluebird hey buddy L shut up oh got
your ass do you shut up and no do you stop and
the shut up and I always use this it works sometimes other times you just need
to be straight up and say your breath stinks stop polluting the air that's
kind of a bonus one under yeah they gotta hide they get a hidden one yeah
chill out gore sometimes people need to learn the hard way that nobody wants to
listen to them yeah use this all the time on my siblings parents fake friends
trying to hit me up again and just annoying people talking like that I'm
gonna hit you with the blooper I like you like it with the blooper I hate
fake siblings dude that's one thing I can't stand fake sibling what my BFF
said once dude that's it one time might be a serious the scariest shortest story
ever this this is just hecka funny mm-hmm just be quit and don't be a dumb
arse always works and offends everyone win-win this one I use and that's from
Bobby the Brony. Nice. That's my man. That is hilarious. I use this one a lot
especially when someone is bothering you like your enemy. Burger also didn't work
that idiot kept talking. I wish it was more acceptable to have an
enemy as an adult. I use this all the time when that bitch won't stop talking
a sheet just I think it's good for people to have a nemesis I think it's great to
have an enemy like if you're a kid and you say like this person's my enemy yeah
and then people are like oh yeah that's normal but if you're 20 22 years old 20
22 years old you say to somebody you're my enemy you're gonna get sent to jail
mm-hmm you don't get sent to jail for having an enemy you go to jail for
having an enemy if you're an adult the last kid no that's don't act on your
enemy urge well telling them that they're your enemy is is acting on it I don't
think so the last comment on this one is um and then it says I'm lowercase and
then in all caps I'm not gonna sleep cuz of y'all she's laughing too hard dude
yeah it's true yeah number two
I can finally shut bitches up
Finally just gain the power
What to say bitch you better stop bloomin I
Know you did not just say blooper to say blooper in my
You did not just hit me with the blooper
When your wife has friends over and you hear the word blooper from the other room
His eyes go just burn in red light.
Get out!
Yeah.
Get the fuck out of my house if you're gonna say "bloober".
Alright, so someone needs to talk so that I can spit this number two.
Bloober, bloober, bloober, bloober, bloober, bloober, bloober.
Well you have to stop for this one.
Yeah, I just stopped.
It is over now?
'Cause I've had enough of your foul mouth smell.
Oh my god.
There we go.
Doesn't really work on the Zoom.
That guy, there's a comment from Trigger Trash Kid that says,
"That guy licked a skunk."
like
okay, they have went overboard stick a cookie in their mouth.
That's no that word yeah, you shouldn't you're rewarding somebody
that's up on the street. There's hollering at your woman's are saying
shit like blue bird. You don't put a good mouth.
You tell him to shut the fuck. I say you say, oh, it is over now. Yeah,
somebody's
to be saying bloober with your mouth. I'm going to put a goober in your
mouth. Hey, I sneeze there we go and not a cougar
Cougar for you. No cougar for you that's a treat. Yeah. That's right.
Really they suck they're disgusting. Who? The people who talk nasty yeah have nasty
things in their mouth. All right I'm gonna I'm gonna bloober now ready? Yeah.
Bloober bloober bloober. Oh just shut it go shove your head in a toilet. That would
sound exactly the same as bloober here's the top comment on this one is no way no
one should stick their head in a toilet stool which they won't tell them to go
catch a butterfly and fly with it trigger trash kid says dog poop would be
worse than a toilet yeah well what's dog poop is one is one poop of people poop a
thousand times in the toilet yeah I don't the toilet gets that in over and
over and over and over but those are all little teensy weensy parts of other
different poops so they might they're not exactly all the worst one is it all the
parts that were bad enough to stay in the toilet no no getting flushed down
it's like panning for no no no it's like panning for gold exactly so the gold
there the gold stays the most the most disgusting hold on those valuable
parts of the pool no one gave me an answer to leave you don't even answer
sports what is dog poop worse than human poop um no i would rather eat dog poop
than human poop really i guess it depends on what the dog has been eating yeah and
the person too i feel like on average dogs are you dogs dogs will just walk
around the house and just lick the entire floor clean dogs will eat out of
the trash yeah if they're not but what people people will eat out of mcdonald's
which hey true don't you fucking dare no but I feel like okay would you rather
eat horse poop or human poop? Because horse poop is like just hay basically.
okay well I don't want to come out so big. And then that guy in Philadelphia ate it.
I'd rather eat something that used to be a sandwich than something that used to
be hay. Okay. There's still parts of the hay in the poop. That's what I'm fine with.
Like I would eat the poop of a guy who only eats horse poop. Would you rather eat hay or a
sandwich um hey no a sandwich but like imagine a guy who okay it's corn rather
would you rather eat would you rather eat the poop of a horse that only eats
sandwiches or a guy that only eats hey a horse it'll need sandwiches so you just
like horse poop no I just think that it would be a better good you said you
would eat the horse poop because it had hay in it. I think human poop is designed to repulse
humans. Horse poop is inspiring. It's designed to entice them. Yeah. Horse poop is inspiring?
I get inspired when I see horse poop. Also, somehow there's like horse shit all over my
block constantly. Oh, it's because of the horse cops. There's no horses in fucking,
there's no horse cops in Ridgewood, dude. Yeah, there are. There's not. I've seen one.
You're lying. There is not. How do you know it's horse poop? I saw one in Buddy the Elf.
biggest poop I've ever seen could be just a guy I saw one in how high - well then
maybe I want to eat homeless guy poop the homeless guy with the biggest ass of all
time oh I forget I did forget about Donnie dump trucks the homeless yeah the
biggest ass of all time those on my block he was when I was in LA with you
guys I went that day I went skating by myself I yeah I found the biggest human
poop in a parking garage I had ever seen. That was a car. Really? Yeah. It did say
Winstar on it. You saw a poop car. I saw a brown Winstar. But no, I mean nobody really
answered my question I feel like. I'm sick and tired of your words so just shut up.
Oh. That's like out of nowhere almost. Yeah where did that come from? Came from number
before on the freaking list that's oh what I forgot we're you I thought I was
so enamored by poop the list of horse poop types different kinds of poop you
could eat yeah yeah baby poop or adult poop I feel like baby poop you can
convince yourself it was like baby poop the thing is baby poop babies have just
been eating like what but then would you go to jail if you're like a baby you
would go to jail immediately if you ate a baby poop. Would you okay is it like the
first baby poop the green one? It's a baby poop. One baby's poop. Yeah I it's
just like it's like first. Okay so it's okay milk. Oh no no I would never eat I
would never eat a baby's poop. I would much rather eat an adult's poop than a
baby's poop I think. Is a baby's poop is like yeah that's like the disgusting
level above diarrhea. A baby made out of candy. Yeah, would you eat that one's poop?
Is the poop made out of candy? What's the adult made out of? Candy.
Would you eat a poop made out of candy entirely
and it came out of a candy boy?
Would you eat that? Would I eat a poop from a candy boy?
But, candy man's poop is all black licorice.
I would eat the black licorice.
Would you rather eat...
Four a million dollars.
Would you rather eat four a million dollars?
Yes.
Would you rather eat a...
I don't think I would do it.
A hamburger where the patty is poop or a hamburger where the buns are poop?
Can I have poop in all three?
It's the same amount.
I'd rather have just like a...
I don't want to...
Yeah, I don't want to pollute it with anything.
I want to convince myself it's just something that I have to eat and it's not like...
You know, because I'm a picky eater.
I'll take the buns off and just eat the burger.
I'll eat a hamburger where the bun is poop as long as the buns are lettuce.
Yes, yeah, because I'm low carb right now.
Yeah. I'm doing keto. I can't eat the buns.
I'm doing Aikido. I can't eat this.
Yeah, I'm too busy fighting.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm sick of your tired of your words so just shut up.
Let's see.
Nah, I got cancer from your words.
So true, Trash Kid.
am I actually lowkey that's fire cancer from you talking damn you gave me cancer
do you have to pay their bills now if you give somebody cancer you have to pay
their medical bills yes damn I would love that's Patrick's law what about a
corn dog would the corner of the dog would be poop which is the dog be poop
yeah okay you the thing that you taste the most in a corn dog is the corny part
yeah honestly I'll pay for that like a Korean style corn dog I don't what's a
Korean style guys poop that's the difference well then I know there's a
different one Korean corn dog Korean corn dog Korean corn dogs are made out of
of it's a hot dog or cheese stick and it's dumped it's made out of rice flour
and I think it has a cheese that's really neat that just wanted to show us that he
knew that there was a corn dog that was no no no no no no Pat just wanted to
show you Google something yeah she likes to show at least once every episode
French right it's got Fred it's called the ganja dog I was from Monty Gangnam
dog a ganja dog yeah I'll smoke that it's a hot dog in french fries on a stick so
it's it's poop wrapped in french fries or would you rather so poop wrapped in
french fries corn dog would you rather eat a corn dog or a plate of french
fries
french fries poop I'm guessing poop comes with a bigger reward than I'm all about
the reward even if nobody told me I'm gonna I'm gonna eat it and just be like
I will either get my reward here on earth or in heaven from yeah this is this is
exactly like why I would pick Jay Z I would pick dinner with Jay Z rather than
a million dollars cuz he's gonna poop on a plate
Would you rather eat poop with Jay-Z or 1 million dollars?
A poop dinner with Jay-Z or 50k, what do you say?
I'll take a poop dinner because I can stick him there for a while.
It's going to take us a while to move through some poop.
I mean he's going to want to watch.
He's going to want to sit there and see me eat the whole thing.
If he's not, every second he spends not talking to me, he legally has to be eating poop.
Exactly.
And I've got a camcorder and a connection to the internet.
Yeah, so I fall asleep like it's a lecture and just record it and watch it all later.
Yeah, and then I can upload the video to YouTube and only take it down if he gives me two million
dollars.
Plus free poop.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir-ski.
Be careful, you might choke on those words.
You know, that's--
No one's saying anything.
Oh, right.
Hey, be careful, you might choke on those words, Cam.
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
Yeah.
Got your ass.
the perfect trigger trash aggressive my thing yeah my start my style of telling
people to be quiet lol humor yes I'm saying this is lol humor this is this is
lol humor yeah we should start a website called lol humor where people can post
their memes if you yeah yeah if if a poop is going at 30 miles an hour and another
poop is going at 40 miles an hour which one are you at the train track your
mouth a middle school a middle school math test that says find that's like
poop plus 2 equals 4 find poop find poop and bring it to the teacher
socially awkward penguin got to decide between a million dollars and a poop
dinner with Jay-Z took the money yeah damn that penguin was so awkward
god damn that was the most awkward penguin of all time that really is lol
humor there was a bloodhound gang song there was is are you gonna Google
something again no I'm not gonna oh no yeah and I thought just and I thought
that Justin Bieber was boring oh come on got your ass slipped it in the
conversation thank you that is a good one dude yeah and I thought Justin Bieber
was a girl turns out it's you top comment then a Bieber fan says you are the most
boring person on the planet and no one would want to talk to you ever goodbye
loser damn next top comment I like this because I can use this against my mother
yeah mom's mom's a hey when you compare them to Justin Bieber yeah no mom calling
you a beautifully young girl yeah no you look like Justin Bieber hey guys check
this out Justin bluber oh hey dsa members put that one as your display name you'll
get some laughs that's true justin bluber can you shut your trashy dustbin please
I mean I want to read one more comment from the Bieber Wow I jumped yeah and
then you can try it Pat okay yeah cuz no one was really talking very much either
I was telling you to shut up I wasn't talking talking so you're you're Bieber
is just a young man who tries to please everyone. He does make mistakes, but he keeps the money
coming in. Sometime we do learn. We just have to see.
Damn. Kind of shed some light on the situation from a different perspective.
Wow. That's kind of like the boss of the boss stuff.
A nicely creative way to include him, wink wink, from Billy V. I'm nice and creative.
All right, now you can try, Pat. But someone needs to say something also.
Yeah, and I wouldn't be caught dead. Can you shut your trusty desk?
please that was horrible what you just did was horrible can you shut your
trashy dustbin please that was such a bad read dude can you shut your trashy
dustbin please there we go can you shut your trashy shush can you bejerbers can
you be a trashy dust can you get your shaman nerf hey hey hey Pat can't read
right now someone says oh my never leave you charge shut can you charge your
fucking trash trashy charge your fucking mouth
charge your ass shut your first time around can you charge your mouth yeah
you're just talking to somebody so we're looking at the fourth quarter can you
charge your car charge your further melt your trashy touch that space
Blarcher Sarkin starts
What are you talking about? Sorry, I thought you said blue
But he said blooper I had to tell you
Someone says just tell them to take a walk or else you will take their gas money case closed
Case closed I like number eight a lot
a good comeback to the trashy dustbin one what is it you use it on me use the safe
say can you shut your trashy dustbin please um I would never leave the lid to
my trash can open oh what if both of your hands are busy
can you chart your pooper can you charge your blooper there we go
- Can you charge your blooper?
- Oh man.
- What?
- That one's nuts.
That one goes far.
- Bye for now means I'm going on vacation for a while.
No phone calls, no text messages, just me and the wind.
My life has begun now.
(laughing)
- Just me and the wind.
- Yeah man, just me and the wind.
- Yeah.
No one around to say blooper to me.
- Mm-mm.
- No one around to tell me to charge my sharshy sharsh.
- Charge my farts and scars.
And then you're chilling at the hotel pool, you see a car pull in, who jumps out the back?
But Jay-Z and a big plate of poop appear to interrupt your vacation.
And he kills you.
I thought I told you I wanted the money, get the fuck out of here.
Jay-Z keeps following me.
He's trying to treat me to a poop dinner.
Would you eat Jay-Z's poop for one million dollars?
Or would you read a book and eat...
Would you read a book and you open the book up and hollow it out as a piece of poop that
you have to eat for two million?
Would you rather eat a poop book or read a fart book?
Would you rather eat a chocolate book or throw up and eat the throw up?
DVD or a Blu-ray?
Wait, HD DVD?
(laughing)
- Wait, HD DVD?
- Would you rather feast on a frozen fart
or prowl on a pretty poop?
- Yeah, that's a tough one.
- I'd feast on a frozen fart.
- Would you rather--
- Or dine on a dark diarrhea.
(laughing)
- I was thinking the other day about,
like if I was into shit, it would be such a problem
because it was like, you know, people are into shit,
They want like a normal like poop swirl on them or they want to see their poop swirl on somebody.
It's just people that like soft stuff.
And I would just like, I would just like, like buckshot shotgun blast diarrhea on whoever
I was fucking every time that I wanted to come.
You have like a...
I'm like, I'm like physically incapable of having that fetish.
You have like a Gatling gun crank on the side of your ass.
Yeah but it's just like, it's like if you pop the top off of someone mixing paint at
Home Depot.
Yeah.
And that's like...
when the lid comes off the blender when you're making a smoothie. Yeah, it's like dude, it's
impossible for me to. Just like Barret from Final Fantasy 7 just with poop in his
gun. Exactly dude. You have a poop connected. A blender bus. Yeah. Got a blender butt. Yeah. Alright. You look
beautiful with your mouth closed. Thank you. Keep it closed. You look beautiful with your mouth closed.
- Oh, watch this. - Your mouth is sharp.
- Nobody can see you except us.
- What are you doing?
- And it's not, nope, it's not that small.
You're not even making that small of a mouth.
- What about this one?
- Okay, for the listeners, - Pretty small, right?
- Cam and Pat are making their mouths small.
- Whose mouth is smaller?
Caleb, answer.
- Between you and Pat, Pat.
Pat has less lip going on here.
But I think he has the advantage of more facial hair
on the bottom.
- How about now? - It covers his lip a little.
Hey, you know right now I just wanna put a fork in it.
(laughing)
- I wanna put a fork in my mouth too.
- Yeah, full of that fucking spaghetti.
- Yeah. - That's right, there we go.
- See, that's a good comeback to the shut up comeback.
- Yeah. - What, spaghetti?
(laughter)
Hey man, shut up. Hey, spaghetti!
Yeah, I don't know.
I want to shut up too. I need a plate of spaghetti.
Yeah, that would work.
Someone says,
"That was a really bad one and mad my friend
stabbed me in the face with a fork and proceeded to eat my skin.
Mad, mad, mad. Do not
use on anyone you would like to know to be
in prison or psych ward. I would also
like to know the real name, home address, and personal
email/phone number of the original poster
you will be hearing from my lawyer."
friend ate his skin yeah crap my friend ate my skin or his poop eat I would
rather eat poop than skin but yeah friends I'd rather eat skin well it's my
friend I guess I'm old my like old man like good for me
gold member is not a role model Pat I look up to evil monster from a TV show
show TV show come on he had a long long TV show a really long one-hour special hey
Pat do you know how to tape your mouth closed for free I just did it no you
have to use tape why does it have to be for free shut up I said it first you're
right you beat me to it that's number 11 why is that the contender sometimes
number two you've got a stick with the classics from Turkey asylum the person
This is a poster who's seeking asylum in Turkey.
(laughter)
It's a political outcast.
He's a refugee, yeah.
Wow, a prisoner.
I think this one is really common from Cosmo.
This is the only website that you get in Guantanamo Bay.
I'm sorry, hold on.
Cosmo.
I clicked on Cosmo's page and their profile picture
is just the logo for Six Flags Magic Mountain.
(laughter)
That rules.
zip it up no you zip it up no you no one want no one wants won'ts to zip it up
but they will shut up try giving them a list of chores that need to be done they
will run question mark okay I've had enough that's kind of like a kind of
parenty I don't know if I like that yeah yeah that's not a good parenty we all
have enough that's when you leave the house and take the bank card in the car
and say hello Florida or anywhere town to get this stressed off of me even if you
have to hop a bus just go go go hello Florida stop whining I get enough of
this crap from my six-year-old then he's less annoying it than you at least he
shuts up your six-year-old husband no
you just got a little six-year-old brother better than the big whining child
whining child isn't what it's like a the big whining child is a cryptid yeah
whining child is like one of the things from killer clowns yeah it's like a baby
that runs through a grocery store I said this to my friend and everyone was like
oh as if it was a diss and the gay boy started crying just a perlative boy and
gayest girl is just a man they already give out the class gay boy award it's
called best eyes am i right oh did they give that out at your school they did
yeah they gave out best smile same thing they give out they gave me next will
ferrell they gave me best dick sucker Wow yeah I don't think I got anything I
I sucked a guy's dick at school. He was the principal. He was my dad. Yeah.
Give me best son award. Best son for it cuz I blew my dad at school. You need a
promotion to best son. I'm sorry you were talking? You read it wrong. I'm sorry were
you talking Pat no comment is my teacher didn't care about my cousin passing how
rude just just like just loudly whispering your friend in class just
being an asshole and really annoying and it's talking about my cousin who died
sorry I didn't realize there's a rule against talking about my dead cousin and
being sad oh there's a there's a good script here down here
let's read it Patrick is Sally okay but the title of the script is best come
back to say to girls that don't shut up mm-hmm oh so this is a micro list um you
be you be a you be the narrator Caleb okay speaking of them makes the tiniest
peep shut mix you so like sure talking while I am as quiet as can be shut up
why don't you know you show me 24 made a note that you're supposed to say and
sound that's between shush and shush. Shush! You shushed up! Shush! Shush! Shush!
Stop talking your voice is worse than Bieber. Oh. Whoa. Trigger Trash Kid says I
will practice to make it better. LOL this is enough to force a person to
commit suicide a good insult always includes dustbin beaver being better
dustbin beaver Wow number 17 I'm not interested please top comment from
trigger trash kid I'll try to make you interested Oh for trigger trash kid easy
I mean oh he's a good guy yeah hey Caleb you know that your vocal cord is
horrible what of course my vocal is tre bill triple triple I talk on the phone
at work scream at kids when I get home yell at my hubby he was out all night so
now I cannot talk I put on a tape with Britney Spears and play a couple of
songs by the Beatles and a song by the the Dells oh what a night so my vocal
chords seem to be doing all right until tonight
iron sabbath priest comments lol what is this 1970 I'm gonna use this well I
wonder what iron sabbath priest favorite bands are let's take a look at this
profile yeah iron professional doomer dark music lover I love dark music damn
I love dark. I love being gothic. Oh really Pat? You know the smartest people stay silent for long periods of time.
I can't take it anymore! Put a sock in your pie hole you big buzzard!
Fuck dude. You think I'm a big buzzard? Don't talk crap about the only friend you are gonna get. You think I'm big?
Don't ever pass up your chance to shut up. Go die.
K.Y.S.
What?
Shut the fuck up noob also get rekt.
Can you shut your mouth or is it always open?
Are you writing a book?
Just stop.
Do you know how to shut your mouth?
Just give it a bloody rest.
We're all fed up with you.
Use your right to remain silent.
Do you kiss your mother with that mouth?
I'm sick of all these people talking.
Wait, you're so annoying it sounds like one more than one person.
I honestly do not care at all.
Go to hell.
Can you please STFU?
Kill yourselves.
Chup.
this is very cool xx chop chop chop chop
when they bloober you a bit of shush thanks he said bloober so i told him to chop no
yo you did not just chop my bloober that does those both of those sounds like
sound like uh philly slang yeah yeah i'm about to jump this john
Yo, I told that John to bloober and then he told me to chup.
Yeah, I hit that John with the bloober and he chup.
He chup.
You didn't even get it right.
The word John is so, for the fact that it just means like thing.
Anything.
Like yeah, it's just like, they're just like, we thought of a funny word,
we're going to use it as much as possible.
Right.
It's just like frindle.
The coolest slang word ever.
Let's come up with a cool Boston.
Bloober.
Bloober, yeah.
We already got it.
Bloober is the new John for Boston.
Yeah, I just picked up a bloober from the bloober.
Yeah.
- Yeah, yo. - I'm about to go home
and bloober it.
- People have these bloopers I just bloobered.
(laughing)
- Yeah, I just put my bloober in the blub.
- Yo, chub my blooper.
- Yo.
(laughing)
- Don't say my bloober.
- Yeah, my blooper.
- No, that's not, that is a bad--
- No, I meant it like--
- In the YG way, no, I understood.
- No, no, not in the YG way.
- I heard you, yeah, like YG, yeah.
- No, not like YG.
- You meant it like the Michael Richards way, right?
- No.
(laughing)
Come on Pat, what's wrong with you dude?
- That's not true. - Oh, this chups you.
(laughing)
- Did you see that somebody downloaded an old Morrowind mod
and it had the Michael Richards, it's called Morrowind 2,
and it just has Michael Richards doing that,
but it replaces all of the stuff with elf slurs.
- Yeah, that's so funny. - You're gonna find that.
- Yeah, a bit of-- - Hey, la la la la la.
- La la la la la.
Close your speaking hole. Shut your face grandma. This one's good. Do you know my friend Chad?
Chad up. See because that sounds like chat up which means to talk though. So it doesn't
really work. Yeah it's true. Yeah you're chatting me up right now. Yeah. It's like yeah. You
look ugly with your mouth open. See it's like a. Play shut up by Charlie Brown. Shut up by
- "What Charlie Brown, a DJ, Do" is an awesome EDM song
that I first heard a part of when I watched
a daily CNN 10 episode played at school.
It played at the end.
I watched the episode again and asked Siri for the song,
which is how I know the name of it.
It has no lyrics, but the title is enough.
Not to mention, the song is awesome.
- Shut up with all the dustbin stuff.
- Yeah, your dustbin is full enough.
- Your dustbin is full enough, you turd.
And then number 53, erg,
when are you going to shut that dustbin?
It stinks.
- It must be British slang.
- Number 51, me, me, me.
(laughing)
- Nee nee nee.
Put it where the sun does not shine.
All right, nee nee nee. - Please just please.
- All right, I think--
- Yeah, oh, today-- - I think, uh,
- Chep. - Uh, uh, uh,
our episode with Up Close and Personal--
- Oh, yeah. - Comes out.
If you're listening to this right now--
- Go listen to Chep Close and Personal.
- Chep Close and Blue Burl.
- Mm-hmm. - That's right.
- 'Cause they're great guys.
We love them. - Yeah, Jay and Matthew.
Yep, give him a follow, give him a subscription.
Hit it baby.
Yep.
Yeah.
And then we're going to play the episode at the end of this one.
We'll just download theirs and then put it onto ours.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey Patrick, chat up.
Oh, fuck.
[BLANK_AUDIO]