You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
- Podcasts for the heartless.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Bang.
- Woo.
- Oh, ooh.
- Damn.
- I'm trying to hit the spring.
- What?
- Did you hit the spring on your mic stand?
- I hit the spring on my mic stand.
- Oh, okay.
- It's possible.
- Like this.
- Ah.
- It's a new instrument.
- Yeah.
- Sounds good.
mic stand Geiger? Yes I do, thank you for asking. Does it have a funny string?
Let's see, yes this guy right here. Whoa! That's a brand new sound. Yeah the spike on the levels on that is very high.
At first I thought you were going to say the spike on the mic stand. Not a defensive mic stand.
Bowser's mic stand. Yeah, well if you don't want to get too close you get too many pops. So it's a
pretty good invention by the Chinese I believe. An evil spiked mic stand? Yes. I
might have to invest it. It keep me from touching it all the time? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
and also it's covered in like hot sauce too. Yeah. So like if you have any cuts on your hands. Yeah.
It'll fuck them up. That's kind of genius. That's from my own various spillages
though. Oh come on. I'm disgusting. I'm a good fast liar. Jesus Christ. Yeah it's true. Fuck you. We're here with
Geiger from what report this post I'm sure everybody knows great podcast sure
he's decided to join us and I've decided to leave virtual reality for exactly one
hour yeah do this yeah you've been you've been playing it all like weekend
mm-hmm yeah if I went out of town to go visit somebody and I brought it with me
and just did it the whole time I was there
it I've been in fucking it's also it's the it's like the Facebook one it's the one
that's like owned by Facebook mm-hmm so I'm just like I feel like I'm wearing
the the bucket the chum bucket from the Spongebob movie yeah and just like at
any time it's just gonna turn on yeah I'm just gonna like go by like 50 Disney
Plus subscriptions or something you have no control over my mind I'm pretty
excited for it I mean it's not like you already have you're already bringing it
everywhere I think that's yeah just how fun it is to a vacation so yeah that was
my vacation it was too snowy to go outside so I opened up beach VR yeah I
was in rec room I was watching Rick and Morty with a bunch of nine-year-old you
know and then one of the nine-year-olds was like on the voice chat he's like why
got blue hair it's a good time it's a really good question why why he why do
you got that now pardon my ignorance but what is this virtual reality game you're
talking about oh again you're 50 years old yeah well I know about virtual
reality and I know about games I'm playing various virtual reality games
it's not just okay and one of them is just a is just a theater that you sit in
with other people other disembodied heads and hands and you all watch movies
together and throw popcorn and you talk to each other and eat their tomatoes at
the screen they could have been women with your high voices I didn't ask their
age yeah it's probably a bunch of hot babes
fucking it definitely was I think about it
they weren't children I just told you they were hot babes everywhere and they
just couldn't say their ours very well we're kind of Eastern European model
types you know. That's just, that is the reason. But yeah I've just been stuck in VR so that's
been my week. Have you uh, if I got a VR thing I would try going to sleep with it on and see
what happens. So you can wake up in it? Yeah. What? That would scare me dude. I know, no
I would just want to see what, I would want to experience it you know. I feel like that's
probably want to that would be too scary but I want to do it I want to see what
it's like I want to put a dream in virtual reality so that I don't have to
do it myself that'd be pretty cool you just whenever you go to bed you just
watch him basically a an eight-hour movie about like you in middle school
you think anyone's ever like gotten high and done VR no no no that would no that's
illegal what are you talking about? I think the laws apply in virtual reality?
That's a good there's a lawyer out there that will take that case. Yeah definitely
some laws were being broken in that theater that I was watching Rick and
Morty in. A whole lot of laws. Not by me. What laws? What are you talking about? But there were other people there that were
that were they were being a little weird to these beautiful women. It's just how it
is dude. I mean it's it is the wild wild west. There's no there's absolutely no
regulation. There's only the terms of service of Facebook. Dude that just
reminded me of the time we played VR chat. I've completely forgot about that. Oh
yeah. Yeah I'm too scared to go into that one. Yeah. Why? What would be scary with that one?
Because people use it. So I found out that in VR chat, which Geiger, if you don't know
this, it's like a, it's like second life basically with like virtual reality.
Okay.
But people, I guess what they do in VR chat is that there's tons of people buying these
haptic feedback tubes and putting them on their penises and then they'll like walk up
to you in VR chat and be like, put your hand on my crotch because it'll make their like
actual dick vibrate.
I feel like you can defend against that by just not putting your hand on their crotch,
I'm easily manipulated and I will try anything once which is a rule.
One day you're gonna come on to the podcast and say you jacked off Kermit.
I wouldn't jack off Kermit dude. Yeah you absolutely would. These are hot babes we're talking about.
Exactly. These are hot babes who just so happen to use their Kermit avatar.
It was Kermit or Caillou or one of the backyardigans.
I'm not gonna fucking jack them off unless I have...
If you see a guy walking around VRChat with the Caillou avatar, you know that's someone
really fucked up.
Because like no kid would be using a Caillou.
I wanna look like Caillou.
That show sucks so fucking hard, man.
Caillou?
You're not a fan?
No, fuck Caillou.
What's your beef with Caillou?
It's not even funny.
and there's no good violence.
They don't even like, if you're, like there's the whole scenes aren't even colored in.
There's just like white around.
That's just lazy.
Yeah.
You're right.
Come on.
And they don't do any like family guy cutaways.
Yeah.
Didn't, I think I read something that somebody posted about like a Caillou episode got like
banned because Caillou like pinched his baby sister too hard with like malicious intent.
He's a savage dude.
Yeah.
Savage being savage makes your hair fall out.
I saw an episode of Arthur the other day and I caught the end of it and it was
what's what's the girl's name in the show again I caught the end of it
TD or something DW. She walked up to this sandbox full of kids and
she was like what's going on and then they started talking to her and then
their words were bleeped out and so apparently earlier in the episode DW
accidentally taught the kids some like slurs or something this is a real
episode I don't understand I don't know what I taught them slurs yeah because
they were like hey what's up beep and then she was like oh brother what did I
do so there's an episode of Arthur where DW teaches a preschoolers hate speech
Jesus Christ they just bleep it out they don't even go for like a like a fake
word no that would be good but yeah they're all art for she can just make
something up they're not like maybe maybe anteater is like a slur in Arthur
you know maybe it is so true what else would be a slur in Arthur dog dog face
how about yeah rabbit bitch yeah yeah well what else other animals yeah but um
yes I that's have you guys done anything interesting this week I have not like
left my house except to find cables to plug into my VR headset no me neither I
guess I did go out of the city and stay at a lake house for a couple days but
that again doesn't count. Yeah I did some real fun shit this past weekend we had
the Super Bowl here in town and we I watched it with a local family and then
the game over and there was a bunch of people setting off fireworks because our
local beloved team won a championship and I went to a neighbor's house I never
met before around midnight and drank with that guy for a while. Wow what's it
like to have Tom Brady on your side now yeah no he stole he stole Tom Brady he
stole Tom Brady from Patrick mm-hmm from Patrick from Cameron Wow dude from
Cameron and really fucked New England is a lot of different states it's true
definitely doesn't include Massachusetts that's for sure okay all right
famously fucking taken whatever dude wait how old is Tom Brady now he's kind
like the Geiger of football. He's like the oldest shit and still doing it. Yeah.
Yeah. Is he like 50 now? How old is that fucker? He's not 50. He might be 50. He's not fucking half of a hundred.
He's 70. No. He's 43. 40, that is fucking, that's pretty old to be doing football. Yeah. To be so good at it.
Can you imagine a 43 year old podcaster? No. That would be disgusting.
Now a 36 year old podcaster. That's right maybe in the money zone. That's where they need to be.
That might be the perfect age actually now that I think about it. What about two 36 year olders
hosting a podcast together? Oh my god dude go on. Where could I even listen to a podcast like that?
Well it's interesting you asked. I would check out Report This Post.
Oh I actually listen to that it's terrible. I have no interest.
I think the hosts are pretending to be 36 too.
I thought that the title of the show was an instruction and I kept, I keep reporting every
episode.
Every episode you're like, yeah this is uh, this is impersonation.
They're pretending to be old.
We were honored to have Caleb on for an episode a little while ago and I think my favorite
part was probably about what 45 minutes in we're doing it and then Caleb's like
oh I think my recorder stopped like 30 minutes ago
not to me though by the way let me check my yep we're good just making sure yeah
it seems like every time I go on somebody else's podcast I have a massive - the
other day when we did when we did Chapo my downstairs neighbor for the first
time since I've moved here decided to drill into the ceiling for the entire
hour that we were doing Chapo Tram House he was like yeah and then and then it
stopped and I was like okay thank God he's not drilling anymore and then he started hammering the ceiling
yeah he was putting a tin can up there so he could listen in
I think he was a damn liberal. He might have been a damn lib. He was so mad that I was
I was well I did go on there and destroy socialism that's the other part.
That's true. Yeah I took him down. We kind of roasted them on their own turf.
Yeah exactly we were like there's no such thing as a free lunch and they got
really mad at that. Yeah but the thing is like the way we did it too was so subtle
that they kind of almost did it for themselves. Yeah they didn't realize that
we weren't laughing with them we were laughing at it was like a Borat thing
and we all did insane ethnic characters to expose the hypocrisy of the Jumbo
Tramazos. And we were all being Polish. Yeah. What they didn't realize was at the
end when we said thank you so much for having us on thank like thank you so
much we were actually it was actually just like a dark intellectual technique
called sarcasm that we were using. Not many are aware of.
They were not.
And let me, their internet addled brains, they were not able to comprehend it even a little
bit.
No, they didn't even realize that we were making fun of them the whole time.
And we still are.
We didn't even watch that movie.
No, we just barely.
We made up the whole movie as we went.
That's like a lot of sarcasm to use in one podcast, it sounds like. Just sarcasm and
irony too, I think.
Yeah, we actually did a little bit of both.
Yeah, I had to lay down after because I did so much.
Yeah, yeah, Pat had a headache.
I will say one thing, one more thing about VR.
The other day, I went on a four-hour VR trip
through Half-Life Alyx, which is very realistic.
Yeah, what was that like?
How late at night did you text us?
You were like, "Half-Life Alyx is the craziest thing."
It was like 2 in the morning and I was playing forever.
And then I couldn't fall asleep because I was so freaked out.
And so I had to just stare at it.
I had to pour a glass of water
and then move it around in my hands
and then just stare at it for like an hour.
(laughing)
I was just like, what the fuck?
Like, am I alive?
And it really terrified me, dude.
I don't know that I'll ever play that game again.
It was so scary.
Yeah, that's a problem.
They need to make things just not realistic.
- True. - Everything needs
to stop being so awesome.
- Well, like, reality is realistic.
virtual reality shouldn't be also realistic exactly there should be a
cartoon in it true you should be able to be a car you should be able to put
yourself in the Simpsons house and be kind of an extra Simpson family member
oh that'd be amazing yeah and you create your own Simpsons episodes so VR and you
can just like Walker it like you could like it could be like oh this in this
episode like it's like while Bart is at school I can walk from the school and go
of the house and see what Homer was doing. Oh my god. While the show was showing Bart. I bet he's watching TV.
I bet he's watching TV and eating donuts. I would bet he's at work.
It's during the day. That is okay. All right. It could be a weekend. Okay but hey. Somebody's a Simpsons fan.
This is Homer Simpson we're talking about though. This guy doesn't like work. You know I think
there's every chance he could be. You never know. That's the thing. They don't have these kind of
behind the scenes stuff for The Simpsons. They have it for most other shows. They need it though.
Yeah, he's at work asleep at work, right? Yeah, famously hates work, but still goes to it like a
fucking idiot. I got fired like nine months ago. That was like great. That's it.
So you're saying if only Homer had been fired,
maybe he could have been saved. And I don't think he's ever been fired on the show or
taken on new jobs or anything. No, but I have seen every episode. So yeah, Simpsons Pro.
all right uh you guys want to do this list no not really all right that's that's fine so anyway
about my simpsons idea this is what if you found out that bart had an identical twin and sometimes
it was that twin in the show and you didn't you know and you could be the twin in and you could
be the twin in vr i wouldn't want to be bart simpson's twin dude i'd be so short i'd be short
as fuck you would not be any shorter than you already are bart simpson is not five nine and
three-quarters you don't know that he is not six feet tall everyone else is like
eight feet that's a secret they don't tell you about the Simpsons that everyone's really big
you would know in VR you find out all the Simpsons are actually 30 feet tall
I don't see I don't want that kind of forbidden knowledge that's why VR is a
problem well then you just wouldn't play the the Simpsons behind-the-scenes
experience but that's an easy Marge upskirt if she's 30 feet tall that's
like dude where's my car remember what she walks over him oh yeah do I do yeah
that's right that was it that was a movie I just remember that finding the
car that's all you remember uh-huh I'm gonna remember movie you got to check it
out the barbers are funny as hell it's so funny and that's the see it that's the
other thing you think anyone's ever gotten high and watching dude where's my
car again I don't think nah those don't really go together okay what about a
VR thing where you can go to dude where's my car you can see where the car
was the whole movie oh you can wait it's a car!
And then the movie just happens far away from you.
Yeah, that's the car's point of view.
Yeah.
The director's cut.
He'd sit in the car.
Yeah.
You just sit in your car looking at your phone and that's an hour and a half of that.
Yeah. It'd be perfect. I do that all the time.
90 minute lunch breaks every day. Just staring at the phone.
There is one thing in VR where you can just use your computer.
And it's like, why would you do that?
Why not?
I guess the appeal is you can use your computer like in space.
But it also looks like shit and there's like insane latency
But it's using your own computer via
Okay, it just streams to your VR headset and you're like, okay, you're just looking at like you're so well
it's it starts up and there's like this music and like all the like a galaxy forms in front of you and then just
Your computer pops up and then you're just on you just like looking at your files
Damn, it's pretty fucking awesome, dude. That's cool. I can't wait to pour so much money into this
Yeah, just be broke every month because I'm buying how much you fucking it's only like 300 bucks
Jesus Christ, yeah
It's not that bad. Yeah
Hey, man for a portal to another to insider worlds. Yeah, how much a wormhole Pat?
library it's called it's called your library card oh my god that's that yeah
no books are bullshit dude yeah I'd rather get lost in a good movie you can
actually watch movies with all your nine-year-old friends and oh really yeah
well just saying dude that's 300 bucks ever spent you already you've you've
pulled your thingy out on there. I didn't. Where would I put it dude? I don't have a third controller.
No, in real life you've watched the, you've gone to that website.
What website are you even talking about? VRBangers.com. VRBangers? This better be a
hip-hop song. I have to check this out. I'm gonna check out VRBangers. That, what
could that be dude these drum solo videos or something? Where I get to be the drummer?
This is it's a POV shot from Travis Barker's drum set. That actually sounds awesome and
I would do that game. Yeah. Yeah I will not do the porn I refuse to. That surprises me.
Yeah I honestly I thought. I feel like you're just saying that for the show because that's
like the opposite of the person I know you to be. What I don't like porn. You know what
it is is he hasn't done it yet I haven't had the house to myself I think once
you're in the virtual reality world that you are by yourself from you can just
start jacking off that no one is a very good point yeah you put your headphones
on and you have the headset on your own little world there will be one day when
Janet gets back from work and like I'm I'm in the bathtub and it's filled to
the top of peanut butter in VR like moving through like a colonoscopy in
virtual reality drowning in Riley Reid's ass please save me yeah that day is
coming that that will be a reckoning because you're gonna have to have like
the court going across the house from your computer to the bathroom
you have a whole pulley system and there's like scratches that go from the bathroom
all the way to the computer desk and back and you're like I'm just jacking off I'm
like okay don't say anything but fart my face but don't let me know you're there
just fart right near my face. Ugh. Come on dude. That's pretty gross. Come on. Come on Caleb. What's wrong with you man?
You nuts. I need to stop making purchases. Okay let's do this list and stop talking about my awesome new life.
This is things you do that you would never admit to on the top tens. Yeah kind of
irrelevant. Yeah the description is no sex-related or x-rated items please.
Items that fall in that category will not be added to the list. Yeah we'll see
about that. Yeah. Number one you like a person but you are insisting that you
hate him or her. I would do that. I hate fake friends. Mm-hmm. No this is it.
This is the opposite of fake friends. I hate real friends. This is if you like someone but you say you hate them. Why would you do that?
Oh yeah you're right. I don't know about this situation. Yeah I thought it was a hating
fake friends thing. That's why I said I would do it. Well Ron Luna comments, two comments
actually "You can't hide it because you are blushing" and then also "I know lots of people
doing this. They are so bitchy with that guy and they do lots of fantasy about him." What's
up you pussy bitch? Like fuck you man. Get the fuck out of my, this is my fucking block.
Hey man, you're blushing.
I think you secretly like me.
I think you might be doing lots of fantasy with me.
Teehee, you caught me.
Are you do- Dude, you cannot do fantasy with me right now.
Come on.
I swear to God.
I swear to God, if you do fantasy with me- If you do some fantasy shit with me, I might
wild out on you.
I'll freak the fuck out.
You do fantasy at me.
I hate my fantastical friends.
Number two, don't wash hands after using the public restroom.
- But just public?
- Here's a comment from Hi there.
It says, "In the pre-COVID-19 world,
"I did this from time to time.
"Now, not so much."
- Oh, they mean not washing.
For a second, I was confused there.
I thought they were saying they stopped washing their hands
because of COVID-19.
- That's what I did.
- Yeah, that's a boss move.
- Build up an immunity.
- Yeah.
- I've never really cared about washing my hands
or germs or anything.
- Oh, yeah.
You don't have to wash your hands after you pee.
I don't really I don't really believe in germs as much as most people I think.
After you poop though you got to wash your hands.
You know I mean it depends.
You're touching your butt.
Well no you're touching paper that touches your butt.
Right but it can get through the paper.
What kind of toilet paper are you buying that has like are you buying like lace toilet paper?
I'm using tissue paper.
Doilies.
Fishnet toilet paper.
It's from all the presents I got.
I'm using the tissue paper for my presents.
That's right it's a happy birthday man.
Yeah, happy birthday, Pat.
Thank you.
No, I mean, you should wash your...
Do you guys ever just wash the hand that you wipe with, though?
No.
What?
[laughter]
You guys don't do that?
Why would I do that?
That seems right.
How do you wash one hand?
Just like that?
Because I'm using my phone with my other hand.
[laughter]
I don't want to put it in my pocket, so I just wash the...
You're on a phone call.
Yeah, I'm on a...
started you were taking a shit I mean you wait on my mom I can't fucking put a
cat away explain that to her now it was it was stated that you shouldn't you
don't need to wash your hands after you pee which I normally agree with but I do
I do stick my fingers up my ass while I pee I mean then you just again you wash
that hand that's just something you got to do when you get older though
You're checking for lumps.
[laughter]
Once you turn 30, you have a free pass for the rest of your life if somebody catches you with your hand in your ass.
I've found many brown lumps.
[laughter]
You gotta get in there and you gotta squeeze your balls from the inside like a clown's flower.
Yeah, just play in your fucking butt balls wiener and taint like a one man band to see if you have prostate cancer.
That's what you have to do, just shoot like a popcorn.
Like a clown's flower?
The penis really is a clown's flower, isn't it?
Yeah, dude, it has a button that makes it squirt.
That one's in your ass.
Yeah.
Number three, you drop food on the floor, but you eat it anyway.
Oh, you nasty.
Big time.
I have no problem with this.
Never had an issue doing that.
I have an issue with this.
It depends on the floor.
yeah I will say if I'm in a barn I will not eat the food right yeah yeah I've
seen osmosis Jones if I'm in my poop floor room I will not do that if I'm in
war-torn Syria and there's just bodies everywhere I'm not picking up you know
anything that's I don't want all that shit on my eggs just walking around with
with a plate full of three scrambled eggs and cereal.
(laughing)
Fuck, I hope I don't drop any of this.
- A giant Scooby-Doo, like quadruple-decker sandwich.
(laughing)
And just tripping over body, whoa, whoa!
- Yeah, starving kids are like reaching up from the ground
to try to eat the lettuce off of it.
Hey, if it drops, you can have it,
'cause I'm not eating that shit.
Disgusts me.
I dropped a Mike and Ike on the patio,
then ate it two minutes later. I'm fine. Yeah.
I think, I don't think a Mike and Ike, I think it's impenetrable to germs.
Yeah. It's got a hard shell.
You got anything that's not sticky, it has, when something falls on the ground, it's sticky,
it sticks up germs.
Anything wet.
It picks them up like Katamari Damacy. But anything that's normal, you can't get germs
from.
Yeah. Any normal thing, any normal natural thing like a Mike and Ike.
a McDouble like if you drop a McDouble on the ground now I pick that back up if you drop
a McDouble and it comes open then maybe some germs can get inside it but the outside of
the bun and the edge of the patty that's safe.
If the bun stays closed as it hits the ground you're fine.
Have you guys ever eaten an old chicken nugget in your car?
No.
Yeah I've done that.
I think three days.
I've eaten an old fry.
We have fries.
Fries are different.
Chicken though.
about what if you what if you had you had a McDonald's okay okay and you you have
fries it you don't finish all the fries because you're too full okay the fries
are in the bag you put the bag in the trash not much stuff in the trash oh yeah
no you get hungry you take the fries out of the bag I've had two bites of a
turkey sandwich that I put in the trash and then went got it later was it in a
rapper? I don't remember. Right like I people used to call like I found like a
like a sealed lollipop on the like one of those dum-dums on the ground in my in
the hallway in high school and somebody called me gross for picking it up and
eating it. Okay but to be fair that was probably a trap laid by the janitor and
it was gonna like poison you. I did fall asleep immediately after I put it in my
mouth I fucking hate janitors for all that shit they do like that yeah they're
always trying to clean up your spill yeah I put that chili on the ground for later
mm-hmm don't you dare mop that up you don't touch that that's for me yeah
frost feather a snow clan says I've done it he he he very very coy about it but
Yeah, it's a little it's a little sneaky somebody says I haven't done this in the past decade
I just clicked on their profile dawn 20 male
I'm a non-denominational follower of Christ a staunch conservative and all I say in list is purely my opinion. I
I just uh speaking of those programs I just found out that a program that they have that's like
is this VR still? No, no it's one it's one of those like anonymous programs. Okay.
But it only exists in Los Angeles and it's called codependent anonymous and it's for people who think
they're codependent and they go to meetings every week like drug addicts. Oh my god. That rules dude.
they only have it in LA. Guys I just found, I'm sorry to derail this.
They're gonna have it in New Hampshire next week.
I'm sorry to derail this but I just found something insane on this guy's profile.
I think you might remember this this message that we read this a long time
ago on the podcast from someone's profile. NeonCo31's grandfather died
because of difficulty in breathing. Copy and paste this if you care, ignore if you
don't. Oh my god. So we have that but there are also at
least 15 other people's relatives who have died here.
And they're just putting on for it?
DreTop10's Uncle Tom died in a car crash on October 3rd, 2018.
Please post this on your profile page if you care, and ignore if you don't.
Catacorn's Bunny June died because of a disease. Copy and paste this on your profile.
MusicLover123's Great Aunt died of cancer.
Bamber73's Great Uncle George died.
PowerfulGirls10's Dad died from a blood clot.
Jack2244's Cat died.
Chat Noir fan 18 school security guard died at the site
Not a weeaboos classmate have passed away
Peppa Pig sucks neighbor has passed away
Katilda lover 93's father has passed away because he was shot in the chest
Bloodfang's mom died from coronavirus
Frostfeather of snow clan and twig the survivor dog's fish crystal died
To the 21 panic fans dog died from a skin disease
The 21 panic fans grandmother's dog died from cancer in the throat
hi there's great on show to death in late july his uncle's cancer has come back
hi there all my god dog ginger down in february
if you would have died anyway if you did
only got a crypt keepers fucking i know it's a
well
that's heavy for the top i know it's a lot of little kids dead market is marked
and they got shot in the chest
that's jesus christ and someone's neighbors dog died too
*laughing*
*overlapping*
God, that's so sad.
Yeah.
Number four, you lied.
Not me, I don't lie.
You lie all the time.
Yeah, I do.
That was my first lie I've ever done.
So it wasn't a lie then?
No.
I'm already too confused.
I'm instantly too confused to do this with you.
That's the point in saying that you lied.
That's a good point, Frostfeather of SnowClan.
I'm sorry about your fish crystal, by the way.
That's now I'm going to remember these usernames from that list and we're going to see somebody
who comments on here and is going to, "Oh yeah, their uncle choked on fish."
And their fish died.
Recipes to your school security guard.
Number five, you masturbate.
It's a good picture for this one.
I'm going to vomit.
Yeah it looks like the obey thing.
Except it's a guy coming.
Didn't they say no like filthy stuff on this list?
They did.
It should be taken out.
Yeah you're right.
And then the guy, someone in the comments says it's funny because the description says no sex related items.
Oh okay so this guy's kind of bucking the rules.
Wait a minute.
Wait don't tell me he's a bad boy.
Jackhammer619.
So the description lied to us.
Yeah you're right.
Oh my god.
that's a that's a fucking lie right there mm-hmm
jackhammer 619 comments I ate a basketball once teehee
the same guy said he he he up at the time no it's a different person it's a
different that one was the frost feather of snow clan I think so you got a laugh
through the pain of your fish crystal dying you have to eat he he through it I
I clicked on the TeeheePerson's profile and it's just a list of their comments,
which I've never seen a profile in this format before, but one of the top ones
is just "Ew, I don't want to eat powder."
What kind of powder? Who knows? We will never find out.
It's a comment on McDonald's on the list of top 10 places to go eat breakfast.
Dude, McDonald's, are you guys gonna get this new McDonald's breakfast, the McPowder?
Yeah, it sounds amazing.
Yeah, it's like a, it's like Huel or something.
Yeah, it's just sugar.
Just white sugar.
Number six, afraid to swim.
Okay, so you do afraid to swim, but you would never admit to afraid to swim.
Okay.
All right.
I don't like swimming.
Yeah, no, I mean there's a lot that can go wrong with swimming, you know.
You could end up a pothead like Michael Phelps.
Mm-hmm.
That might be the worst outcome possible.
Yeah.
Look where he is now.
I hate that drug addict piece of shit.
Someone should fucking-- I wish he got fucking domed in a deal gone wrong.
I think it's so disgusting when he swims.
I wish he got eaten by a shark in the Olympic pool.
That's right.
When he swims you can see the track marks all up and down his arms too from where he's been
using. Yeah and also the ones where he got bit by sharks when he was practicing in the ocean.
Yeah he's a fucking piece of shit. And it's crazy that they didn't even kick him out for using PEDs.
I know yeah. Being bit by a shark by the way does give you the swimming powers of a shark.
Yeah he got bit by a half man half shark. Yeah.
Yeah.
And he did it on purpose.
Do you remember when that article came out that he sleeps like 30 minutes a day and then
just swims for like 15 hours and eats like 10 pizzas and shit?
That's sick.
He has a pretty awesome schedule.
That's so cool.
Yeah.
He's going to evolve.
Yeah, I remember it was like what, 15,000 calories a day or something like that?
Yeah.
That's insane.
Something awesome.
Something that I would do any amount of swimming to be able to eat.
Yeah.
That's why he does that.
Yeah, he just wants to eat. He doesn't care about the Olympics at all. He doesn't give a fuck about swimming dude.
He just wants to eat fucking 30 pizzas a day. Right. He just lives like a ninja turtle now.
Yeah, including the weed dude. Yeah, those guys are fucking stoners. That's why they live on the ground. That's why they're green.
That's why they're fucking stoner. You're telling, hold on, you're telling me
that there's a group of turtles that love eating pizza and do karate under the sewers? And their dads are damn rat.
yeah hey hold on were you guys high this stuff are you smoking yeah yeah hold on
you're telling me there's a guy named there's a guy who's a little a little
blob and he lives in it inside a guy's stomach and you're telling me his name's
krang what the hell kind of name is that well were you drinking beer when you
wrote that name you smoking sherm they must have been high on PCP when they
wrote that shit yeah mm-hmm why do they all have like California accents but
they live in New York and what the hell do the turtles crazy names even mean
yeah what I have these California names - oh like what avocado yeah and Jose yeah
these are the names and there's California Los Angeles LAX yeah Robin
big in and out and and what's this and what's with this guy shredder what is
this TV show supposed to be the office max show that's so true yeah what are
you but yeah what are you supposed to be a paper shredder what kind of fucking
shit is this? Sorry he's got a foot clan? Hey hold on, they got a freak. Whoa, okay. It was
weird but now it's just awkward. Yeah, a foot clan, that's what I would call it if
Quentin Tarantino had a clan. Hey. Another Hollywood man. Tarantino, another name of
the turtles. Famous turtle, Quentin Tarantino. Number seven, you sucked your own blood from a cut.
what I would tell people I did this yeah dude that's a brag yeah yeah one of the
comments is I got to the point of taking a swab of blood from my classmates face
and dot dot dot I think it's continued I think dot dot dot is supposed to be the
I do this a lot well I don't know why you under misfortune that why would that
because there's another dot dot dot so there's another road dot dot dot and
their message you assume it's a two-part message it also would not surprise me if
somebody tried to do a two-part message on this fucking it's not even it's two
separate sentences you don't know that. The dots are at the end of both of them.
They're not. It's not like at the end of one and the start of another. Well one of them you can it's like the
fridge magnets you can put them wherever. Okay so in that case it makes way more
sense if it says I do this a lot. Hold on wait I wait these two comments both end
with a period so I think they might be part of the same comment. They could.
Well I didn't consume it like a vampire but it is kind of my natural reaction to
suck on the cut and then from a different user it tastes fine. I think
those might be a two-parter. Yeah. I'm not some if I get a cut dude I'm not I don't
want to know I don't want no blood in my damn mouth. I sprayed or if it's a
big enough cut I just kind of wiggle it around so the blood gets everywhere. What I
will say is if I will I'll suck the blood off a cut if like I don't like I don't
to wipe it on my clothes I don't have like a napkin like cuz I don't want to
like I don't want to smear it on myself you know what I mean if I get a cut I
just whip my dick out and I use the foreskin
I let it pool up in there and then I go to the toilet.
Me and Cam don't have that privilege dude.
And I shoot it like a super soaker.
Got my blood on you.
For the record, I also have that privilege.
Just so everyone's on board as far as the cut corner around here.
I remember as a kid I would like pee in my foreskin let it fill up and then yeah
blast it out everywhere.
Drop it on the toilet?
Blast it out!
The water balloon?
Yep that's right.
What kind of foreskin were you rocking as a kid where you could do that?
Relax fit?
That's the 90s.
Yeah this was the 90s we're talking here.
Boob cut, fucking penis.
Yeah.
Ready to rock. You put all your coins in there?
Oh yeah.
sure I've done that before actually yeah. You've put coins in your penis hole. I think I did that when I was like
eight I think I put a penny. Did you ever try putting like whipped cream in it I
feel like that'd be funny. No. Oh yeah okay. That's crossing a line. Funny for who?
Your penis. Okay. Oh cuz you could fill it up with like the whipped cream or like
the easy cheese and then just dispense it out. Yeah. Somebody's like damn I'm hungry.
You want a tiny bit of whipped cream?
You pee a tiny bit and it forces that it displaces that amount of whipped cream out on top of
your friend's strawberry shortcake.
Now that's I'm so glad that I went through the terror of having my penis chopped off as
a child so I didn't get to do any cool pranks with it later.
It would have made me too powerful as a kid.
Yeah.
It would have been bad for the people around me if I'd had an extra compartment.
In virtual reality you can see what it's like yourself.
Oh that's right.
Yeah.
Oh my god that's a really fun tab simulator.
That would make a killing.
Four skin simulator?
Yeah, because all those people, like the anti-circumcision people, would go out and buy VR headsets.
We gotta get on this.
I think we got an idea dude.
We gotta talk to a developer right now.
Okay.
Yeah.
Patrick, you should email back that guy who keeps emailing us about chipset.
Oh yeah, okay.
Have you talked about that before?
I heard you had one idea for my other app, but I have a completely different one.
Who the fuck did you email that guy in the first place?
No.
I don't know how we found the email.
Some guy, some app developers, like a month ago, he just emailed the podcast email just
repeatedly, like fucking once a day for weeks, just saying like, "Hey Patrick, just wanted
to circle back about your idea for Chip's app.
I would be willing to develop this app if you like, and we can talk rates," and just
kept emailing over and over.
Matt had an idea for an app that is,
you can look at different bags of chips.
And then this guy has been,
he's probably sent about 600 emails to the podcast email,
just trying to make some money.
He doesn't do it anymore.
Yeah, he took a hint.
I already talked to, I already had a fucking,
I already had it in the works.
Yeah, dude, he was trying to fucking undercut you.
Did we ever reply something mean to him or not?
Dude, he was trying to Mark Zuckerberg you, dude.
I think I was gonna reply something mean to him
and then Patrick told me not to.
I'm gonna check really quick.
the Winklevoss twins and this guy he was gonna hire him and be like yeah how's
chip sap going? Austin had adopted highway on on Twitter he and I were- Patrick I saw your
chip sap query. I mean it was a golden idea you know. So fill me in you look at
like different brands of chips or just like actual potato chips? You can post
about which chips you ate okay it's like the letter box media yeah exactly
letterbox chips that's pretty good I found out why he stopped replying to us
why cuz I replied to him after he sent a bunch of emails and I said we are going
to make an app for pictures of poop
Wow he got really offended trail yeah I don't want to make an app like that
that's disgusting well now we have to we have to contact him back tell we got a
whole game right now okay new VR game
development company we believe it will corner will quote corner the market as
as business folks.
- This is a great email.
- 10, yeah.
- I can tell you.
- You're killing it.
- Yeah.
- I've written a lot of business emails
since we were right up professional.
- This is one of the top of all time.
- The app will center on restoring certain parts of the body.
- Just come out and say it, dude.
Don't tantalize him like this.
- Which were unfairly taken at the time of birth.
(laughing)
I refer, of course.
- At the time of birth.
I refer of course to the noble four skin and then enter enough with the bullshit
let's make some money with the bullshit colon for skin simulator are you in or
or are you a coward
this email will self-destruct in 20 seconds
this email will self-destruct
in 20 seconds
sincerely yours
wait wait wait, just kidding, i don't want to, that could be a threat
that could be considered a threat
what the fuck are you talking about? i'm trying to cover all the bases i don't want to
sincerely yours, geiger
And say from a report this post on record this post and subscribe to the patreon
I think we just got Geiger a new patreon
Driver dude Wow
It's amazing. Yeah, don't nobody ever say we don't treat our guests. Well
I've seen a lot of people saying it online
unbelievable amount but can you link all their accounts and like their posts I
need to do something yes sense we need to send them a self-destructive email
number eight is you imagine that you have sex with your crush that's what I do I
imagine I have sex with my crush is that so wrong what else would you imagine
doing with them holding their hand and watching Rick and Morty with them
Yeah, imagine spying on them from the back of the classroom.
You just imagine doing that?
You don't even actually do it.
No.
Opening a joint checking account, that's what I imagine.
With my crush.
We're starting our life together.
You're so beautiful.
You're starting a registry at Target.
I skip way past like the courtship, I skip the dating, I skip the fucking marriage.
Joint checking account.
Yeah.
I go straight to that.
I know what I want.
- We're doing a registry for my foreskin restoration surgery.
(laughing)
- Start again, start again.
- I would love if somebody could buy me an ice pack.
(laughing)
- An ice pack and some weights, and some strength.
- Yeah, I'm hoping to get really, really strong
while I'm recovering.
- Have you guys seen those devices out there?
- The foreskin restoration ones?
- Wait, there's a device?
I thought it was a surgery.
- Oh, well.
- There's both.
- There might be a, is there a surgery?
- There's a surgery where they just put
little bit of duct tape on it. Oh, these are the, you like stretch out your
foreskin, right? Yeah, yeah. It's like, it's like a, it really is like a system of
weights that you just like wear all the time. Yeah, I was on a, what's that, How To
with John Wilson. Is it like jelking? TLCTugger.com. Is it different from jelking? Yeah, that's the guy, that's the guy from How To.
That's our, that's our friend. TLCTugger.com, notice, COVID-19 delays are
possible, Black Lives Matter, and the product has been discussed on Jimmy Kimmel
I'm on I'm on r/forskin right now and it's uh it's just it's just pictures of
uncut penises I thought it would be something different but there's some
guys with a there's some guys with some baggy fits here hey Pat number nine
number nine you are gay so you're supposed to say just say be mad ah there
we go that's better yeah that's much better you are gay which is something
you would do but you would never admit to doing is being gay I guess that's a no
no I am a straight lady yes you are Caleb are you serious I talk to you about
virtual reality for 28 minutes yeah and this is how you repay me that's that's
how I repay you with I can't well I'll tell you this much I'm not gay and I'm
not a girl my compass is towards girls which I guess my guess is that their
compass is their penis when it's erect yeah it's always pointing towards a girl
yeah I mean my penis points towards the nearest bitch even if she's behind me it
goes completely inverse and it pokes out of my butthole towards a woman standing
behind me in line. Did you let women stand behind you? No. No. That is gay dude. No, I don't let a...
No. Come on dude. I don't dude, I'm normal. Number ten, you pick your nose. Do you pick
your nose? I pick my nose and I think every... I do think all the time about like
every time I've sold like a bed on Craigslist or something I wonder if they
like got the bed or the chair and they like set it up at home and then they like
went to like put you know people store stuff under their bed they'll like put
something under their bed yeah and it's like five years of my boogers yeah yeah
and they'll just be like oh it must be an odd design yeah I guess if they're
really stupid they might think that yeah yeah yeah but also you see me there's no
way you think that I'm somebody who puts their boogers everywhere oh of course not
why would you know that based on looking at me that doesn't make any sense I'm
clearly I have class and I put my boogers in a job toilet is that where
they go you don't have a booger jar no no save all the money gauge I do you're
ready sick save all your boogers up to the end of the month to start doing that
don't save my boogers for the rest of my life yeah you put them on top of a
Casserole.
That is fucking gross, dude.
Dude, can you imagine how great it would be to have your girlfriend's friends over for
a dinner party and when you want them to leave you just go, "Hey, I've been meaning to show
you guys something I've been working on for a few years."
Oh, I thought you meant like you come out with a...
You want them to leave so you bring out the booger dessert?
Yeah, I thought that's what we were...
You serve them the boogers.
I feel like just...
I feel like the very appearance of a jar full of boogers would make any woman leave your
house.
Why?
If I showed you a can of my boogers that I've been keeping, would you, like a Folgers can,
like a Folgers tin that I've just been throwing boogers into.
I don't have a lot of glass jars, okay, I'm not rich.
He likes to recycle.
Yeah, I love the feeling of recycling.
Yeah, that's why you're recycling boogers too.
Yeah, exactly.
if I showed you that you would leave Pat I would stay you're a braver man than I
I'm not a coward I'm not afraid of a booger number 11 is great because it
doesn't accuse anybody of anything it just says I farted I farted yeah you I
would admit to that someone says I always admit to this yeah because what
What if it's a good one?
Yeah, what if it's a really funny, stinky fart?
What if it smells funny?
What if it makes the air green?
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, you're also, you're not getting away with saying you didn't fart if you have a
giant green cloud in front of you.
Yeah.
Or behind you, I guess.
Number 12, you have a nickname.
I would never tell anyone that.
How would you know?
I would never admit that I had a nickname.
I would never admit to this.
Oh my god.
Can you imagine?
No fucking way.
fucking kill me or my family to get me to even think about doing that shit.
I have a cyanide tooth just in case somebody asked me if I go by any other name.
I just popped it.
First day of like class.
So they don't know that my dad called me boogie as a kid.
Mine was Buka.
I think I've told you that already.
Buka.
Yeah.
B-O-O-K-A-H.
A-H.
my brothers my brother couldn't say Patrick when I was born so he said yeah
I think your brother has a something wrong with his brain I feel like he
should get a nickname for that not you yeah yeah that should have been his
nickname not me yeah he was like a year old should be slow and then whatever his
first name is donkey his first name is
buka yeah he calls everybody his name
yeah it's like a Pokemon yeah I know
if you if you
dropped your wallet on the street
street and a guy picked it up and handed it to you said oh thank you so much and
he looked you in that went book up
I would let him keep the wall I would have said oh my god are you Buka cuz that
guy in real life would be famous so I bet are you the Buka oh my god it's so
crazy running into you Buka can I take a photo with you he's like no I'm just
doing an impression you are broke I would yeah that's all I did when I was broke
yes I got like so many free meals out of telling people that mm-hmm and beer
number 14 watching pornographic films oh that's just now no oh hell no but you're
I admit that shit.
Oh hell no.
But you're not wrong though.
Uh, 15, addicted to sex.
I think people admit that.
Hell yeah.
Hell yeah I'm addicted to sex.
That's like the funniest, that's like the funniest like dumb guy thing.
It's like yeah I'm a sex addict.
Yeah.
Yeah man, I love sex.
With one woman.
Yeah I'm a sex addict dude.
Yeah.
I can't even.
It feels good when I do it.
Oh man, I'm the biggest sex addict of all time and it's like, I'm addicted to sex.
I'm addicted to sex.
Yeah, I can't it feels when I do it. Oh, man
I'm the biggest sex addict of all time and it's just like guys just ruining their lives
Yeah, like no no idea. No idea like what an actual like I don't think sex addicts are real. You know what?
Yeah, the more you think about it the more you're like, yeah
How can you get addicted like drugs?
I understand cuz drugs are like anywhere from an 8 to a 10 sex. Yeah, I feel like it's
It's real, but it doesn't matter. Like you can be it like it's like if someone's like I'm addicted to
I'm addicted to watching TV. It's like okay you might be but I'm not
People are like I'm addicted to coffee. Yeah. Yeah, it's like dude. We're all addicted to coffee cuz it's like kind of okay
I'm addicted to my my god. I'm addicted to religion. You're not addicted to Christ
I know you don't know anything about the Bible and I will test you. I'm addicted to rising and grinding. What's John 316 right now?
I thought you were uncircumcised, dude.
You know, guys, I gotta admit something real quick.
I'm addicted to my friends.
No.
I'm addicted to never backing down.
I'm gonna stop enabling you.
I'm addicted to being true to myself.
Listen, this might be a problem for you.
If it is, just leave right away.
I'm addicted to keeping it real.
I think I low-key might be addicted to standing up for what I believe in.
I'm addicted to good vibes.
I do it too much.
I'm addicted to just being a good person, for real.
I'm addicted to alcohol.
It's like a really big problem.
But all your shit sounds really good.
It's not nearly as hard as our shit, but good luck, I agree.
rehab and is here everyone's like like heroin stories in the circle just like
man sometimes I'm too addicted to having fun I'm addicted to winning I'm addicted
to go into Disney World I'm addicted to not judging a book by its cover number
17 liking a pop song I'll say dude I love hips don't lie mm-hmm and SNM by Rihanna
for no reason I you skipped one dude I'm not gonna it's your show but you skipped
the number you're right well you know we're getting close to the end we're
kind of relaxed yeah we're not you know what it was in order all the way up to
that you know we don't like play by the books you know yeah and also we can't
count too well maybe you guys are kind of like you know straight-laced goody-two-shoes
shoes over there but we kind of just like to play things by ear and and rock out
hard yeah if you never heard punk rock it sounds a little something like this
I don't I'm not a if I eat ice cream before I go to bed I'll have an evil
nightmare yeah no yeah the heartburn that I get from that come on yeah the
I love you.
think a lot in the shower admit it you think in the shower no dude straight up
I just sit there and I completely don't like dad I can tell people I'm doing
that all right take the left and right earphones too seriously what do you mean
what do you mean to serious well come on you got it you got to take that serious
Hey Patrick, number 30, I shagged your mother.
Oh my god.
No you didn't.
What does shagging mean?
Shagging is like British for...
It's like British for long shaggy hair.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
You're saying you cut his mom's hair.
It's giving someone hair.
Oh, that's actually very sweet.
Yeah, it's especially sweet since my mom lost all of her hair to cancer.
True.
Yeah.
She doesn't have cancer. No, I just wanted to have a nice moment.
You just want to say are you the 21 panic fan by any chance? Why? What did they say?
Uh, because their mom died of cancer
All right, let's see north 35 you buy soundtracks to movies
Why would that be bad? You guys got us
Now statistically one of us on this podcast has to do that.
I bought the Halo 2 soundtrack. I think I probably bought the Fight Club soundtrack
but I also might have pirated it I can't remember. I definitely had it in my iTunes library.
I had the Train Spotting soundtrack. I'm pretty sure none of those are good.
Yeah. Yeah. I think I got Team America.
Oh that's a good one. Okay well that might as well be like a Weird Al album though.
Right. You know. I got the soundtrack to Weird Al.
Which I have, I did buy straight out of Linwood.
Oh me too.
Yeah.
Yeah the one with the two disc, the two disc one with the DVD and it had all the music videos.
Fuck yeah I had straight out of Linwood.
But here number, sorry, number 41.
You don't go trick-or-treating for Halloween.
And there's a comment here from Mocha Cat that says,
"After 2012 I stopped going after my friends and I had a creepy encounter
with this really tall bald skinny man.
He kept on following us so we decided to take a different route to my friend Cat's house.
An hour later we saw him on Cat Street walking around.
It was really weird.
Caleb do you want to talk about why you followed mocha cat?
yeah it said really tall and skinny I was wearing a stilt yeah yeah your slender
man costume yeah I don't know I thought it was a good look I like number 43 you
kissed your dog's mouth and someone says okay now that I have done. Well that's
Pegasister 12 said that. It took her till number 43 to find something she had done.
you hate chocolate you smell your genitals you have diabetes I'm really
falling off you hate ice cream well wish I could relate buddy I'm addicted to
stuff you hate alcohol and jacking off oh fuck your parents are divorced and
number 51 you sing death metal when nobody is around Wow what I would not
admit to that because it's embarrassing dude that's creepy yeah yeah you wouldn't
Because of what Varg Vyrknas has done. He's not death metal but nice try dude.
You fucking idiot. I knew you would say that. Yeah.
Because you knew you were wrong. Yeah. You knew you were wrong and you still said it?
Mm-hmm. That's bravery. That's like a lie. Yeah that is almost a lie.
It's kind of a fucked up lie. So you think it's okay to lie just to make a joke for the audience?
no I'll never do it again thank you thank you all I wanted to hear this whole
episode was a setup yeah this is my this is my intervention yeah we got Geiger on
here yeah your best friend I'm here for you
that's so sweet Geiger yeah do you want to tell everybody about report this post
well it's a podcast where my co-host Christian and I find goofy stuff online
line and read it and I believe it's original idea.
We've been caught. I do think you guys started like a month or two before us
which is so - that sucks. But here's the thing Geiger, we actually have three guys.
That's true. We have two. If you can't tell.
first we have like do we have like two two different lanes there clear it's
like our show on steroids it's like one extra person exactly yeah yeah yeah
which is what's yeah I'm the lump that forms when you take steroids yeah and
what a lump you are yeah check out report that if you like the lists on the show
you'll like report yeah yeah they have a very good diaper they research a
thousand times better than we yeah I will say the hardest I ever worked for a
podcast was being a guest on Report Disposed. I was like what the fuck is all this shit? I gotta like look stuff up.
Fuck this. But it was fun. I can't imagine putting effort into anything. I know. Can you believe it?
It's so dumb. It's part of the reason why I got fired from my last job was I
was like doing everything for the podcast while I was just I was like
researching and then editing the podcast at work. Just on the clock? Yo yeah.
Oh, fuck. That's sick, dude.
Like a hundred percent. Like everything.
Yeah. Respect.
Yeah, I would bring in the episode like on an SD card and then put it on the computer and then do it.
So it wasn't even like...
Because you can't do it at home. You're too busy drinking alcohol and eating ice cream.
Right.
Yeah. There's no time.
Yeah, so, but I also did that at work too. So, because I am addicted.
- Well, yeah, that's the problem.
Your job was alcohol and ice cream taster.
(laughing)
- All right, Geiger, thanks for coming on, man.
- Thank you, everybody.
Reportthispost.com.
- Check it out. - Oh, you got a website?
Fuck.
- Yeah, actually, it's a website I made
using the HTML knowledge I learned in the '90s.
So it's really-- - I bet it looks great.
- It looks really sharp, yeah.
- I gotta check this out.
- It's got like images and text on it.
So if you have a modem, it might be slow.
Yeah.
Man, I could embed so many images.
- Oh my goodness.
All right, thanks man.
Bye everybody.
- Bye. - See ya.