You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Podcasts for the homeless.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
You're a crap monster.
[LAUGHTER]
[EXPLOSION]
Oh my god, dude.
Ooh, Saturday morning.
[HUMMING]
It's not Saturday morning.
It's Monday morning.
Why you gotta be so rude?
It's Monday evening.
Don't you know I'm human, too?
You are not a human.
You remember that song?
Remember how-- remember everyone fucking liked that song?
summer you make that song never existed Pat that is you never heard rude by
magic rude why you gotta be so rude it's a reggae song white reggae song human
poo remember he sings that line you don't remember that in the song it's a
- Yeah, and they got a Grammy for best poop song.
- Yeah, he has a grandmother.
- Yeah, she gave me.
♪ Can I have your grandma for the rest of my life ♪
♪ Say yes, say yes ♪
- Remember, the song's about asking--
- It's about her dad being rude.
- Yeah, her dad is being so rude 'cause he's like,
"I wanna, hey, I wanna fuck your daughter."
And he's like, "What a weird question."
And he's like, "You're being rude to me right now."
It's a pretty amazing story.
It's kind of a fairy tale.
It's such a bad song. I hated that song so much.
That's because you don't believe in love.
No, but I love reggae too much and he was ruining reggae.
You think that he ruined reggae with that song? How about Bob Marley ruined it with drugs?
That's true. You ever think about that?
These reggae guys gotta stop smoking weed. Imagine how good the music would be then.
Yeah, if they didn't fucking fall asleep in the middle of every song,
have their bongo guy pick up the slack. Come on, dude.
step it up reggae artists. Can you guys wear just like some normal colors too? Hurts my
eyes. I don't like the bright yellows and greens and reds. Whatever happened to red
white and blue? You know what I mean? Yeah. Why does this gotta be all this all this
green and black and yellow shit? Can we get a normal drum? Can you? I don't know what?
A steel drum? Make a drum out of fucking I don't know drum shit. Why are you making
steel drums? Where's the guitars and the? There's guitars. Where's the guitars and
the cowboy hat. Where's all the Scremo shit too? There's no solos. There's no fucking drop
D tuning. What the hell? Where's the bass drop? Doesn't make any sense. Yeah, well where's
the bass guitar? Where's Skrillex, okay? Yeah, there needs to be a knob that somebody cranks
it all the way up. You know what happens with reggae? It's not real music. You know, people
are all talking about Dillinger. It should be Dillinger Escape Plan. That's what I say.
I don't know what that Dillinger is. Dillinger is a reggae artist. Oh. So you're
so yeah. I don't so you're a reggae fan. You're like into reggae. I like
reggae. I like some reggae songs. Okay make one up there right now. I'm not like a Mr. Lobo. You just tried to name drop a reggae artist and neither of us knew so you clearly aren't a
reggae. I know. I know two reggae artists both of them have the last name Marley.
somebody somebody on Instagram I forget his name showed me Dillinger and I've
been listening to a lot of it lately and it's very good I like that you said
everybody's talking about
I was just trying to make a rate
Left and right front page news Dillinger Dillinger Dillinger
I was contributing to the bit that we were whatever whatever Pat Marley I
I would be honored to be a part of the Marley family.
Bet you would, you druggie.
No.
Fucking drug addict.
No, but I was contributing to the bit.
Dillinger is a reggae artist and Dillinger Escape Plan is like a metal band or whatever.
You're gonna go out like Bob Marley fucking smoking weed and choking on his own vomit.
I hope I die like Bob Marley.
I fucking hate myself.
He smoked four hits of a joint, choked on his own vomit, and his sleeve...
He took one hit of a joint and got cancer.
Weed actually gives you, it's the purest form of cancer, of lung cancer you can get.
It's actually the most dangerous kind.
That's why it looks like a little green blob like that.
That's what a tumor looks like.
Why would you smoke, it's called a cannabinoid.
Why would you smoke anything that ends with -oid?
Right?
Especially -oid too.
That's even worse.
That's like clearly dangerous dude.
What are you fucking, what are you doing to yourself?
Anyway, more Red Thunder for me.
I'm drinking Green Monster, baby.
Sounds worse.
Monster versus Thunder.
In real life, thunder takes that.
What's a monster gonna do?
- Wally the green monster.
What about him? - Thunder's just a sound.
- Thunder's gonna wake up the monster.
- No, thunder is-- - Wake up the monster
within me.
You're thinking lightning. - Lightning is the sound.
- The animal within me.
(laughing)
Are you kidding me?
- No, lightning is the sound.
A thunder, a bolt of thunder.
- What are you fucking saying?
A sound bolt? - Lightning is blue.
- A sound bolt. - Thunder is yellow.
- Light is the sound, of course.
- Lightning is not blue.
- Yeah, lightning is blue and thunder is the yellow.
Anytime you see a blue bulb, that's lightning.
- Thunder is the cloud, and lightning is what happens
when a thunder hits something.
- Oh no, wait.
I'm thinking of the hurricanes.
- I think that might actually be true.
- Yeah.
- Lightning is fire, and thunder is air.
- Everybody else knows that thunder is just
a yellow lightning.
This is like how you guys call the stores
a racial slur in Boston.
- That's true, the liquor store is a racial slur.
It's not a racial slur 'cause it's spelled differently.
- It's true. - It's short for package store.
- Do you get packages there?
- Yeah. - You get packages of liquor.
- The hell?
Packages of liquor?
Bottles of liquor?
You call a bottle a package?
- You can't even say the word pen right.
- Dude, you're not one to be talking.
- Pen.
- Here, see I'm stupid like you guys.
- Hey, let me get a pen real quick.
- Are you guys even aware of the fact
that three of the top universities in America
located in North Carolina. Hey guys listen I can do a really good Griffin McElroy
impression. Wait I haven't started yet guys stop laughing. No that's not, I don't
sound like Griffin McElroy. I actually don't sound anything like Griffin McElroy.
Oh I have a very straight voice. I don't sound like either of those two fucking dumbasses. I sound really normal and like myself.
back to your normal voice. Oh, dude, I hate this. I think COVID is affecting my voice.
I'm actually COVID free. I'm negative. Really? Oh, nice. Are you like immune or something?
Dude, I think that I can't get it. I think I might be immune too. I think I'm protected
by God's grace or something because it's impossible for me to get COVID-19 apparently. Because
I've been, you know, I've been living with this, with a monster. Yeah. Who has the virus.
I've been living with the--
Maybe you'll get it like right when she's done having it.
Yeah.
That would be so funny.
And then we just trade back and forth for the rest of our lives, saying, "Yes, say yes."
It's a good song, dude.
Oh man, I can't-- what did you say, April 6th is when everyone can get vaccinated in
the state?
Yeah, dude.
I can't wait to put that fucking chip in me.
I'm so sick of wearing my mask.
I mean I haven't been wearing it when I skate but like when I leave the skate park or something
or I leave the skate spot when I'm by myself I'm not I can't wear it because I'm gonna
sweat.
Patrick I want you to wait I want before you keep saying what you're gonna say I want you
to know that no matter how distraught you are when you text me after the episode and
ask if I can cut out that part where you mentioned the mask so you people don't get mad at you
I'm not gonna do it.
Okay no no.
Now you can keep saying what you're gonna say just want to let that caveat out.
riding around New York with no mask on giving people rides on his skateboard.
He's been shooting spitballs at people.
No, I just, I don't wear it when I skate, but then I'll put it back on
and then I just have like the sweat on my face
seeping into the mask. I don't care, I don't care, like,
you're not gonna wear it while you're like riding a bike or something, like.
I did.
You did?
Kind of what you're supposed to do, yeah.
Are you supposed to, I don't know.
I mean, I didn't always, but yeah, you definitely are supposed to wear it.
You on a skateboard is a far cry from someone on a bike also.
Yeah.
You spend a lot of time, I've seen you skate,
you spend a lot of time kinda just sitting there.
Yeah.
Yep.
I know, I think it's definitely much harder,
if you don't have a mask that's made for athletic stuff,
it really sucks to wear one when you're on a bike
and you're running and shit, you can't breathe.
I got one for athletic stuff, so I might start wearing that.
But just like, just wearing like the shit that I have now, like the paper ones
It's just like
I'm also sure the people that you're like hanging out with at the skate park probably have far worse diseases
Like eating away at their minds or whatever, so
I don't think it's that big a deal
I pulled up and like nobody's fucking wearing them
So I was just like, well I don't wanna be a pussy and
You, oh my god dude
Masks are fucking knee pads to you
They're knee pads and helmets
You just get there and you're like, oh I guess it's gay to be wearing a mask here
because all the skaters will think I'm a I'm a new jack so I'll fucking put on a
I will take off my mask and give them all my diseases I'm fine I I don't go near
me no no one goes near anybody it's all look I don't the coolest the coolest
thing is what I did to my head really bad the coolest mask thing is when you
like walk by a really old person who's holding a mask like in their hand like
just like holding on to it and whenever they walk by somebody they just kind of
like move it around in their hand like to look like they're about to like put it
on to walk by you but it's just like they do it every time they walk by
somebody so there's just them like just turning it over in their hands a bunch
of times right you can just leave it at home nobody's gonna yell at you you're
80 years old I'll wear it yeah you're the one who's gonna I don't care if you
don't if you're over 60 and you don't wear a mask yeah you don't have to be
like a sleight-of-hand thing whenever you walk by me I'm not gonna like deck
you yeah I'll wear it in like a store or whatever like yeah I'll wear it like if
it's like a big public thing or like a fight like I was like going into a store
or whatever I'll wear it I don't care if an old person's not wearing it around me
yeah I mean I'll wear it if I'm within one inch of someone else otherwise right
never never I will never wear mine and I'm I got a wet mouth let me tell you I
I'm just I'm shooting particles everywhere Jesus I can't wait to just
pour my spit onto other people again. My shit's like an aloe vera plant dude.
I have a camelback pouch that I spit into and then it sprays back out on the people around
me like the fire hose in Mario Sunshine. What's that thing called?
The flood. The flood, yeah.
I got one of those but it's filled with my spit.
And does it talk to you? Nope.
- Hello, Gameron.
- No, it doesn't do that.
- Hello. - It doesn't even--
- Stop! - I love you, Gameron.
- The flood didn't talk like that.
The flood was just like--
- I love yours. - Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
- No, uh-uh.
- Yeah, it did.
- Not in the cut scenes?
- I think you maybe bought a foreign version
of the game, Patrick.
- No, I'm thinking of Professor E. Gadd
from Luigi's Mansion.
- Yeah, remember it speaks in Chinese in the game?
- No. (laughing)
- Remember that?
- No, I'm thinking of Professor E. Gadd.
All Professor E. Gadd says--
- The Flood had a beautiful voice.
The Flood was the only talking character in that game.
- Yeah, Professor E. Gadd, all he said was, "Oi!"
- Except for the beginning where Peach goes, "Mario!"
- Whoa, oh my God.
- Wow.
- Sorry.
- Princess Peach.
- Yeah.
- Hey, hey.
- Oh my God.
- She doesn't say that.
- Princess Peach entered game as well.
- Hey, hey Mario.
Hey, Papi Mario.
- Nah, she doesn't sound like that.
- No, not at all.
That's what Toad sounds like.
- Yeah, you're right.
- Toad's like,
(screeching)
- You clipped.
(laughing)
- No, that was just my voice.
- Wow, dude.
Wow, you really sound like you.
- I can see the recording right here, I didn't clip.
- You did Jack Black reverse singing.
- What's that? - That's impressive.
(singing)
- Oh no, that wasn't an in-tail, that was an exhale.
- Oh, sheesh.
- You guys will never, never nail me down.
I'm too good.
- Not too good in my house.
- You'll never figure out how I made that noise.
- I'm nailing you down so fast.
Do you think when they open up the vaccine thing
New York we're gonna have to wait like a year maybe probably right that's what I
want Carolina you can you can literally it doesn't matter how old you are you
just ask for extras cuz there's like nobody getting vaccinated here it's like
every like I know so many people who should not be getting the vaccine who've
got vaccinated like they just have like rich parents or whatever which is like
fine but it's like if you guys are already like managing to trick the
system when you'd like you're supposed to either be like 70 years old or have
like two life-threatening conditions like once it like loosens up more there's no
way I'm ever getting it like everyone's gonna go nice right oh yeah yeah it's
gotta be absolutely yeah I think I need to we need to argue the podcasters
should be on the absolutely dude yeah we bring so much more joy to people's lives
than a fucking like nurse or school teacher those people bring negativity
everywhere they go yeah also also weed addicts both of them yeah nobody likes a
CBD gummy more than a nurse, you know?
Yep. They're just wasteful.
Because they'll have back pain.
Nurses are just, they're a drag on society.
It would be funny to get it like as soon as the vaccines start opening up to the public.
Just get it immediately?
Yeah, just like the day of.
I mean, that's kind of exactly what Jana did.
Yeah.
They opened in one week and Jana got it a week ago.
and she's just asleep with YouTube. She can't even like stop the YouTube autoplay.
It's just like playing in my living room. She's like, "I'm watching it."
See, now I feel like I've had it. Like every time that somebody describes like COVID, it's like,
"Oh, yeah."
You're just tired.
Yeah, you've had like two bad days in a row.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's probably what you had.
It lasts two weeks, you know.
Yeah. It lasts two weeks and you go--
I had it for six months then.
I've been just she falls asleep and I'm just like a weekend at Bernie's using her body to make me lunch.
Just walking around the house making her do her normal chores that I give her every day.
Just making sure they get done. Hey listen bitch I'm not doing that shit. No excuses.
It's great to finally put that pulley system to use.
Like exactly yeah I got the marionette.
In case of something like this.
I got the marionette the human marionette system installed in my apartment
just for stuff like this, you know what I mean? And it's coming in handy, finally.
Yeah.
There goes all three of my stimulus checks were spent on a giant marionette pulley system that
can support a human who weighs 120 pounds.
I used to use it so I could go pee in the night without having to wake up and get out of bed,
but it's nice to repurpose it.
Yeah, I would pre-program it for shit.
Yeah.
For anyone at home who wants to pick up this pulley system,
go to daddysausage.com.
(laughing)
- Exactly.
- That's right, you can pick this pulley system up.
Is that a website?
Let's see what--
- Daddy Sausage.
Don't go to daddysausage.com, dude.
You have no brain.
- No, guys, we have to see what's on this website.
- We have to check just for no reason.
- Wait, just for laughs, though.
- Daddy Sausage has to be a website, right?
- BigDaddySausage.com.
This site cannot be reached.
DaddySausage.com.
- Let's just see what happens if we search Daddy's Sausage
on X videos.
Let's just see if something comes up.
- Daddy's Sausage dot com is a,
it's like someone's sitting on the domain.
Let me see, Daddy's Sausage.
Daddy's Sausage and Peppers recipe.
(laughing)
- No.
- That article is a, you're gonna click on that article
and it's gonna take you somewhere dark.
- Nobody would click on that article
unless they're looking for something evil.
- Step one, slice each sausage link into five pieces,
heat one tablespoon of oil in a large skillet
over medium high heat.
- That's dirty.
- I thought you said eat one tablespoon of oil.
(laughing)
- It's delicious, dude.
Now, if I get COVID, I'm going full FDR.
You guys will never know.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
You guys will have no idea.
It'll be like--
- So you already have it then.
- It is funny that they,
how long did they do that with FDR?
- Probably like a week.
I think they did it for a while dude. Can you imagine just like FDR like a
Yankees game or whatever in the in the 1700s? And now I'll rise for the
National Anthem. He's like I'm good. I'm the president. I have to go to the bathroom.
I have to go shit. Can somebody randomly move my chair to the bathroom for no reason?
I'm the president. I should that's probably what he did he was probably
like yeah I'm just not gonna walk now cuz you know I'm the president like I
shouldn't have to walk my peasant dude I'm not gonna walk Walt Disney got in
his head all right what are these uh here's one right here
stop looking is what recipes for sausage dude father smoked sausage roll one
pound roll from father's country hams calm I'm about one second for muting
your microphone you don't have the power to do that only Cameron does I I will
mute you mentally okay I just won't hear anything you say from now on damn I wish
I could mute myself sorry what did you hear anything cam yeah oh fuck I didn't
mute you I didn't mute him for you fuck me dude all right I really fucked this
up you're unmuted now all right it's like number 11 this is the 11 surprising
uses for 11 starting on the number 11 oh yeah we have a poop and pee nasty list
11 surprise science comm we've been talking about a lot of live science it's
not it's actually live psi equal sign nce based on the logo okay let's just
terrible I made by Lance Armstrong this websites live science live strong
science well vampire squid ancestor died an eternal embrace with its dinner Wow
that's how I want to die embracing my dinner internal embrace yeah I want to
embrace a stew that I'm eating right before I die here's an article and
atheists and believers have different moral compasses yeah millions of dead
jellyfish are washing up around the world the blob could be to blame the blob
what this I know I honestly I don't need to know about the I don't need another
thing I get on my plate right now do not tell me about anything about the blob is
real I don't want to know dude this is the best kind of website the website
where it's like branded is like oh this is like Neil deGrasse Tyson's website
but it's just like clickbait for for 13 year olds who think that the world is
actually changing around them they don't realize what's important yet mm-hmm like
they read about the blob and they're like mom dad did you hear about the blob do
you think FDR had to take the presidential fitness test this article
could humans ever be venomous humans have what it takes to make venom but it may
not be worth the trouble wait what okay that I want to know yeah if I wait if I
have what it takes to make venom this article is definitely poppus I could do
so much cool shit with venom dude are you kidding me yeah here I would rob a bank
essentially my mouth all the building blocks in play every guy now it's up to
evolution to take us there shut up fuck if I if I had the power of venom I
probably just like it depends on what type of like is it like a brundle fly
venom like that kind of shit it's human venom yeah but I'm thinking of like the
closest does it being to like human venom which would probably be like probably
be well a platypus it has has mammal venom also you probably wouldn't be able
to kill other humans with it I'm thinking you probably be immune to it
yeah you would only be able to like put your dog down with your teeth yeah that
would be the main you know it's I'm going with the platypus model I think
you're gonna have little like spikes on your legs that you know that's like
- Stomach acid, right? - You kinda kick into someone.
- The brundle fly, he spits up like stomach acid
to break out. - Yeah, that's like acid.
That's like a-- - Yeah, that's a lot different
for venom. - 'Cause that's what flies do.
- Yeah, 'cause there's like a huge--
- Venom, I think, congeals blood.
- Right, venom is like poison.
I'm, goddammit, I'm so fucking stupid.
I'm so fucking dumb. - No, venom,
poison you eat, and venom gets injected into you.
- Yeah, okay. - That's the difference.
- Yeah, I mean, it's a very confusing topic for me.
- It's really confusing. - I don't have to deal
with venom often.
No, thank God.
Luckily Patrick doesn't have venom.
Imagine if my side job was just like a snake tamer.
Just the worst snake tamer of all time.
You just always walk around puffed up in red, full of holes.
Yeah, I got bit again today.
Shouldn't have been fucking with him.
Oh, here we go.
Another mammal with venom is dead.
I was trying to reason with the snakes today.
See if we had anything in common.
I was trying to make a song with a rattlesnake.
I don't see the problem.
you would get in trouble. You would be like the guy at the snake handling place
who like feeds them human food. Yeah. Yeah. I let him have a lick of my giant jawbreaker I always have on me.
I wanted to see a hamburger outline in a ball python.
Yeah. There's just forever there's snakes at McDonald's now because the snakes told each other about it.
I ran the snakes out of the observatory and now they all fled to McDonald's.
It's called a serpentarium.
Okay.
I think it's called a herp- Much like my ancestor St. Patrick.
There was a serpentarium in Wilmington, North Carolina.
A herpitarium is reptiles.
I've talked about this, but the owner got shot in the head.
I've heard of this.
Pretty fucking cool, dude.
I used to see him fucking feed his Komodo dragon.
It was sick dude. I don't know why a person owning a Komodo dragon is very funny. He kept
a giant Komodo dragon in a room about the size of like a storage box. Like something you
would like pack your clothes in when you move. And he was like, yeah he loves it in here dude.
Look, there's this painting of a tree that he thinks is a real tree. Fucking asshole.
Here I'm gonna feed him a rabbit. Those things are so scary. Dude they eat fucking goats and
Yeah, he would eat them.
No, they don't.
What?
Yes, they do.
What are you talking about?
Yeah.
Komodo dragons are fucking crazy, dude.
I thought they were like vegetarians.
They have bacteria.
What is?
Are you the stupidest guy on earth?
Look at that fucking thing.
You think there's a vegetarian dragon?
Are you brain dead?
I thought that was the trade-off.
No, Komodo dragons are fucking...
We got to have dragons, but they were vegetarian.
You're thinking of like a bearded dragon, which I don't think is vegetarian either.
Oh, yeah.
It's a lizard.
It eats roaches.
I used to have to feed one.
But Komodo dragons, they have bacteria in their saliva.
So what they do is they bite a really big animal, they just bite it once and then they just
wait near it for it to die because the bacteria poisons its bloodstream and it just decays
and dies over the next few days.
That's what I do to a crunch rat, supreme.
Take one bite and just wait for it to die?
I wait for the heartburn to go away.
From one bite, take another bite.
I take one bite of a Crunchwrap Supreme and then wait for me to die.
Dude, putting, bringing a Crunchwrap Supreme into the apartment is like the
scene in Jurassic Park when the Tyrannosaurus eats a goat for Patrick.
He just comes like, the whole house starts shaking, he's walking out of his
room.
Just towards the Taco Bell that's on the counter.
Alright, so these are the 11 surprising uses for pee and poop by
by Mindy Weisberger.
- Okay, when most animal bodies process--
- By Fred Fredberger.
- Are you done?
- What, what did you even say?
- I watched that episode of Billy and Mandy again recently.
Remember the Fred Fredberger episode?
- No, I'm an adult.
- I remember the guy.
- Yeah, that was a good episode.
- When most animal bodies process nutrients,
they expel waste in the form of liquids and solids,
generally referred to as urine and feces.
Oh, come on.
Waste is usually smelly and unappetizing,
for people at least.
but it can also be surprisingly beneficial.
- Some people like to eat it though.
- Yeah dude, fly people.
Pee and poo have a wide range of applications,
providing nutrients for diverse ecosystems,
serving as a foundation for expensive perfumes,
what the hell, or even fueling robots.
- So this is just spoilers right there.
- Yeah I'm already ripped in.
Yeah my bad.
Here are just a few of their unexpected uses.
- There's a lot, I mean, having like a poop eating fetish,
that's a lot of work.
- Someone I know recently--
That's way less work than eating any other kind of food.
It doesn't cost money and you don't have to prepare it.
It just comes out of you.
What do you mean?
What do you mean that's way?
You gotta go make a sandwich.
Either, okay, either you have to stand up,
you go make a sandwich,
you have to make sure you have all the ingredients
and everything, all right?
Are you rationalizing eating poop?
No, I'm saying it's easier.
Just think about it.
You don't have to rationalize anything,
it just makes sense.
It just makes sense!
It just makes sense, you eat your own poop!
If you had a mini fridge stuck in your stomach,
Would you take the food out of it?
Yes.
(laughing)
You'd eat the food.
- Are you really trying to tell me
it's less work to cook dinner than to go poop?
- I'm just picturing a guy with like a door on his belly
just like taking poop out.
- Jerry Seinfeld just like slowly body modding himself
into like a cyborg monster to make his life more efficient.
- My hands are forks, it just makes sense.
Never have to pick up a fork again.
- I got one hand that's a fork,
I got one hand that's a knife.
I can fucking eat my food.
- What's the deal with that?
- Yeah, I think he should get into futurism.
I think he'll be like a Walt Disney style.
- What's the deal with phones nowadays?
They don't work with your fork and knife hands.
(laughing)
You can't press the screen.
- Keep breaking my damn screen.
- I can't use the face ID on my phone
'cause I turned my eyebrows into salt and pepper shakers.
What's the deal with that?
(laughing)
- You ever notice that your left hand has four fingers
And your right hand has no fingers?
What's the deal with that?
I shake my head over my food
I turn my hair into spaghetti
I'm a food monster
I never go hungry again
It just makes sense
I replaced my legs with a table.
I can sit down and eat whenever I want.
Never have to look for a picnic table ever again.
My ass is a soft serve machine.
I have to serve whenever I want.
I'm like a penis on a hot dog.
What's the deal with dogs?
Why are they always barking around me?
Why are they trying to get into my pants?
Isn't it the worst?
Isn't it the worst when you get on a plane and dog starts eating your spaghetti hair?
at the worst fucking Seinfeld
Strangers are so rude sometimes. I'll ask for my salt and pepper eyebrows
Do you have any pepper I say yes no for you it's in my eyebrows just makes
Okay
From poop to perfume a
Yellowish gray rock found on a beach in the UK was greasy and smelled terrible and no wonder
That's the most interesting news story of all time
That's what news is in the UK is this they found a greasy rock that smelled terrible
Fucking beach
At first I thought it was my mum but it wasn't my mum.
I was rubbing my tolja in some sand.
I walked up to the rock and I said "hey mum, what are you doing here?"
And it did respond so I knew then it was my mum.
It was a rock.
Mum, you've been quite odd today, you're not talking to me, you're icing me out.
You're quite greasy and smell bad.
It looked like my mum, it smelled like my mum but it wasn't my mum.
- Some kind of damn... - Does your skin feel like my mom's?
Some kind of damn rock.
And that's why I called the news.
That's the reporter, yeah.
That's not an interviewee, that's just the guy with the microphone.
So I'm here doing an investigative report on...
Back to you, Nigel. Back to you.
Back to me. Back to me.
Thank you so much, Adam Curtis.
Thank you.
We have Adam Curtis in the field, talking to a rock.
I say, "Hey, Mum, when is dinner gonna be ready?"
And she said, "Oh," she didn't say anything.
I started talking for her.
"And we'll be right back after I take a break to love a child."
That's what they're like in the damn UK.
And no wonder, as it originated in the guts of a sperm whale.
"Hey, what the? What kind of whale?"
"Sperm whale?"
"The slick, malodorous, like-it-eat."
I want to put my whale sperm in your guts, Pat.
*laughter*
The slick-
No! No!
I'm gonna make a yellowish-gray rock inside you.
I knew this was gonna be a nasty-
I wanna put my grease- my greasy rock-
I knew this was gonna be a nasty episode, what with the poop and the pee,
but does it have to be gay too?
*laughter*
Can we just pick one?
Well yeah man, you're on it.
The slick Malodorous lump was a sizable chunk of
ambergris a very ambergris fuck off
This fatty substance thought to form in whales digestive tracts around sharp objects
Objects fuck god damn it such as squid beaks
You're a sharp object fuck you
whales then poop out the ambergris
Which is right which is highly prized by humans as an ingredient a practice you keep talking about ambergris
Just know that you're the man for me
And
I think that you have a pricey fragrance too and I would estimate you to be worth at least
$68,000 and possibly as much as a hundred and eighty thousand dollars. All right popcorn Cameron
The love found on the beach was estimated to be worth at least sixty eight thousand dollars and possibly as much as a hundred and eighty thousand
dollars
Recommended videos for you live science. That's how we should do the rest of the episode
No
Okay, that's a really bad. That's true. Caleb never had to be in a class. I never did popcorn reading. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
I never died for to die this is number two a die for 1500 year old Byzantine copy
of the New Testament known as the codex purpureus resenatus okay fuck you dude
it's printed on purple pages and researchers recently uncovered the
long-held secret behind the parchments vivid color urine the thing about all
what names like that where they name it like codex whatever is like that's I
think just Latin for book so like literally like it's just that they
called the book like this is my purple book and then the researchers were like
oh my god we've uncovered the Kodak's perpureus. We've uncovered the Omnitrix Diabolico.
Yeah it's called like my favorite story. Cool stories with with Joe. Analysis of
the tome revealed, you don't have to call it, it's a book dude, revealed that the pages
derived their purple hue from orcyon a dye extracted from the fungus rocalla
ting blah blah blah and then processed with fermented urine the manuscript which
is about half complete is written in gold and silver ink on 18... 188. I fucking read
that. And likely originated in Syria between... I just gave up too, you thought halfway through the number. I saw that I said 18 to start saying
1800 and then immediately I was like I'm just gonna it doesn't matter. It's like accidentally
walking into the closet instead of the bathroom and just staying in the bathroom.
Yeah dude sometimes my brain invents an extra digit it happens dude whatever they should die
more books with pee. They should. I should say. What makes you think they don't you ever notice how old
book pages turn yellow? Also have you ever had to pee on a road trip and you have like a copy of
infinite jest in the car yeah that'll soak up a whole fucking piss dude big
book like that have you have you ever done the tea bagging thing with old but
paper to make it look old yeah yeah and then you put it in a bottle and then put
it in like a like a puddle outside your house you can like a pirate's gonna find that
thing yeah yeah the uh that with my tax return
running with a quill yeah the irs pops it open they're like
why does it smell like wood oh my god is in this is a tax return from the 1800s
this man is gonna get a million dollars here's what you here's what you do right
is yeah you you get your paycheck from your boss
you do that you like do all that stuff to it you bring it to the bank you're like
Well this was $300 from 1600 so who knows how much that's worth today.
That's a good point.
Yeah.
Because that's how this works.
Can you imagine how much black beardos and back taxes did?
Right.
Just like all that all that gold never paid a dime on it.
It says here it says here that this Popeye's fucking this Popeye's pay stub is from 1688.
Yep it's the first Popeye's actually.
works at the bank and then you you do it to a Domino's coupon you like hey I found
a coupon for a free pizza from 1500 that's gotta be worth probably it's got
to be like a hundred pizzas now like that right the pizza exchange rate like a
pizza back there was also way harder to find so that's hook a brother up tastes
like oh no oh no no researchers in Japan recently bought brought a
stomach-turning offering to the table
recently bought something really cool
it's called a game boy and you can play
Mario on it they have Lego Star Wars 2
by transforming human feces into steak
what the hell at the request of Tokyo
sewage let's do it Tokyo sewage is just
like the name of like a band yeah yeah yeah this is on their rider they were
like wait we will not fucking play if we don't have a poop fine ed penis we get
scientists investigated practical uses for XX sewage and discovered that they
could isolate proteins for bacteria and human waste combined with carbohydrates
fats, the result could be served as a meat-like substance.
See, the reason that they could do this in Japan is because they already have a whole
crafting system set up over there.
True.
They can just, they can easily craft it.
It's like a Pokemon typing thing, right?
Like steak and poop are the same type.
Brown.
The brown things.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
I'm excited to see Guga Foods make an A5 Wagyu poop.
Today we have a beautiful A5 Japanese Wagyu poop.
Dry-aged.
Let's do it.
Angel, Angel, what do you think of the poop?
- Tastes like poop, man.
What the fuck?
(laughing)
- Drink up.
Oh no.
- I'm not gonna drink poop.
- Me neither.
- Again.
- Eating poop?
- Eating poop, that makes sense.
(laughing)
- Bless me.
Who's reading it?
I read the one before the last one.
Don't want to eat steak made from poop?
How about eating, I mean Patrick, all I'm going to say is if you say drink up, I was
expecting you to be the one reading it, but I can go ahead and keep going.
I can't read this without bumping into you.
I don't want to eat steak made from poop?
How about drinking a nice glass of water that used to be poop?
An innovative processing system called the OmniProcessor heats sewage sludge, separating
the liquid as water vapor that is then treated to make it suitable for drinking. I have to
say turning poop into water is not that interesting to me. I would rather them find a way to turn
water into poop. I want to go on a liquid diet and still poop.
Yeah, that is a really good point. Can Bill Gates drink the poop water?
Turn poop to wine, you know? Or like something better, like orange juice.
Yeah, exactly. Would you drink a poop milk?
What I will say though is that you turn the poop into water, drink the water, turn the
water to pee that's a poop to pee pipeline right there that is pretty
impressive that is very impressive actually if you can figure out a way to
turn poop to pee or that's like a that's like a Jesus style miracle mm-hmm
exactly
building blocks okay oh I thought we were just skipping how long have we been
doing this fucking podcast and we can't get this down right now we can't figure
out who has to read this one doesn't have numbers on it it's throwing me off
Yeah, we're professionals dude. We're professionals when there's numbers, but I don't fucking see any
Yeah, we work best with numbers. That's one thing about us. We're really good. Oh, yes, you know me. I'm fucking
I'm the math genius
Okay building blocks
Bricks made from urine could one day service cheap sustainable building materials for homes and other structures
But how do you turn P into a brick and that's a link link?
It's a link and it brings you to a page that says very carefully it takes you to a page that says
It takes you to a page that says how to pee a brick and help save the planet while you do it
Wow, I just see that watch this if you'll pee bricks
Scientists mixed wait scientists mixed with fresh urine with lime
So there's a very big ingredient that they left out which is scientists
So you need a scientist you need and you need some limes the scientist is like a
bay leaf you know he's not in the final product but I used to be in there a
whole scientist yeah yeah you guys need to sit in this giant bath full of pee and
then just you just gotta finish all the scientists go home and he just turns it
into a brick easily. Yeah guys you did it. He pulls a brick out from under the
table. Great job you guys. And remember I need to take plenty of pictures and videos to
document my research. As the bricks are setting they do exude. I think your lab coat
and boxers are contaminating the mixture.
It says as the bricks are setting they do exude an unpleasant urine aroma though
the smell subsides in about 48 hours. There's no way that you smell, you like
get up close and you smell and it doesn't smell like piss.
Yeah, imagine if it gets hot in summer. Welcome to my beautiful home. What the fuck is that smell?
Well, my house is made of pee. If it starts like raining, I'm sure that
there's just pee is just gonna run off your walls, right? Your outside walls.
Yeah, I think we're being haunted by a pee ghost. There's pee everywhere. Also that
That feels more expensive than making normal bricks.
Yeah, because what, you have to give people water?
Who wants to do that?
Exactly.
To make the pee?
Uh, Poop-aroni.
Okay.
That's one where they started at the name and worked backwards.
Poop sausage may not sound like a tasty treat.
Oh dude, oh fuck, wait, no, keep reading!
But scientists have figured out how to use bacteria from baby poop.
It's the baby poop thing came to life, dude!
Would you rather eat poop or baby poop?
It's real!
You can either eat steak made from adult poop or sausage made from baby poop.
Make sausages that are both delicious and healthy.
Microbes are already harnessed to produce delicacies like cheese, wine, and beer, and
fermented sausages.
Why does it have to be baby poop?
And baby poop is chock full of microbes, particularly lactobacillus and bifidobacterium, which are
used in probiotics.
bacteria is cultured from poop in baby's diapers.
Researchers made a type of Spanish fermented pork sausage called "fit" and they claimed
that it tasted "very good."
Scientists seem to be locked away forever.
That's way worse than like making Frankenstein or whatever the evil scientists do.
Yeah, honestly, cloning is more morally like...
I can morally defend cloning more than I can defend eating baby poop.
There's an interview with a scientist and he just has a giant clothespin on his nose.
It actually tastes pretty normal.
It tastes like normal sausage actually.
It's very surprising.
The fact that they take it from diapers too.
Right.
Ugh.
There's gotta be something in the diaper that's making it.
Do you get like paid for the diapers?
If this continues, is there gonna be like people walking around New York City like going
through trash cans for diapers?
There, I mean there are.
The one- You do it, right?
Yeah, you.
i said it first the one where they turned into a mistake it's like the sewage
company asked them to like find something to do with poop
but i just want to say evil scientists were like i want to see if i can make
the man had to make a baby poop sausage
the mad scientist who makes baby poop sausage this mad scientist makes baby
poop sausage and he's and we stand this king
you know i hate how the media is always doing fluff pieces on mad baby poop
scientists so annoying so irritating to see on now this yeah dr. Heinrich baby
pooping
urine therapy and no you know you're in therapy in India cow urine has been used
for therapeutic purposes for at least 5,000 years and a Hindu group that
promotes drinking cow urine for its health benefits recently claimed that
the liquid offers a cure for around 70 to 80 incurable diseases like diabetes
according to Om Prakash of the cow protection department for the Hindu sect
RSS yeah I'm gonna trust the the cow protection guy
on like
fucking cow piss curing diabetes right yeah yeah my job my job is that I'm
obsessed with cows I love them I would do absolutely anything to be close to a
cow or even just like to live with it or or understand how it lives. I need to make sure there's as many
cows as possible and also it's their drinking their pee is actually really
good for you yeah for you you Michael because you are depressed yeah Michael
you're depressed Michael but just ask like a there's no way that this guy
knows Michael Roberts of of come on give me a place Portland Maine Portland Maine
yep all days on a 1843 suck my dick ass yeah Michael stay away from parking lots
yeah and me I'm coming for you Michael I'm gonna fucking kill you Michael
Michael Michael Roberts a second paragraph in the in the cow urine thing
is so great however health experts have questioned the effect of this of remedies
containing cow urine particularly when it is purported to treat or prevent cancer
yeah dude of course
that guy is like yeah dude I'm the guy who's like entire thing is protecting cows
cow piss is great cow shit is a you can use it like a condom cow fucking hair is
good to use as a seasoning my passion my passion for the protection of cows as a
species borders on erotic and I have to tell you you're gonna love drinking
there we have found we have found a fifth udder on cows and it cures cancer mm-hmm
it's called stinky milk we have found a fifth element and it is a cow's piss you
look look these cows out of their fifth udders they're producing this thing
there's like a Gatorade and we need to get that shit need to get that shit in
in giant containers being poured on NCAA coaches and I've got an idea we'll call
it Gatorade Propel. Zero sugar.
Robot fuel.
What the hell? The pumping action of an artificial heart sends
urine coursing over a microbial fuel cell in a device that could power
pollution monitoring robots, dubbed "eco-bots." These
p-powered bots represent technology that recycles waste into electricity.
Their fuel cells harness living microbes such as those that colonize the human gut and
sewage treatment plants. It's like the most like educational episode we've ever done.
Who cares? Yeah. Okay so there's robots that run on pee. Okay that's, just say that then.
Right. Just say there's a robot that runs on pee. Spare me the details. I don't care
that they help the environment. I do think it's funny that they're called pee
robots. Look if you saw how the poop sausage was made you'd
never eat poop sausage again. Yeah. Also, the old saying. This means that you have
to you cannot develop artificial intelligence because if these robots
find out about gasoline they're gonna be so mad you made us run on P you had
gasoline this entire time oh my god a guest appearance from Ray William
Johnson I have one robot voice dude sue me it also says urine isn't the nastiest
fuel source these robots have used previous versions ran on energy
extracted from sludge, waste water, dead flies, and rotting produce.
Sludge?
Yeah, do you guys think sludge is grosser than urine?
Also, sludge is like... isn't that like a... like sludge can be like anything, right?
Yeah, it's a slime.
It's just...
Sludge could be pee.
There's not like a natural... there's not like a byproduct of a thing called sludge, right?
Yeah, sludge is like... it's like an ice cream treat.
Exactly.
Ice cream sludgy?
Yeah.
- Worm towers.
- Worm towers. - Pat, you have to read this.
- Okay.
Giant soil mounds in the grasslands of Columbia
and Venezuela alternate with deep pits in the ground,
and the mounds were formerly thought to be the result
of erosion or termite activity,
but scientists recently discovered that they were made
of piles and piles of worm poop,
collecting in locations that the worms
would visit for generations.
Worms measuring up to three feet in length--
- What the fuck?
eat and digest dirt, excreting pellets known as casts.
Over time, the mounds can grow wider than 16 feet
in diameter, and groups of them form
in impressive landscape features
called surale, which is also found in Uganda,
New Guinea, and South Africa.
- If a worm-- - So when you said
three foot worm, I googled longest worm.
Do you wanna guess how long the longest worm is?
- Five inches. - 10 feet.
180 feet.
Whoa.
Wait, where?
A lineus longissimus.
How are you going to hide a worm that big from me?
I think it's probably not.
How have I not seen it?
The boot lace worm.
I think it's in the water.
I think it's a water worm.
Longest worm.
Buddy.
It also has a, it has a neurotoxin too.
Whoa.
Dog, that is a snake.
Yeah.
At that point it's a fucking snake.
It's called a boot, it's called a boot lace worm.
And its mucus is highly toxic.
This thing looks like shit.
Yeah, I hate looking at that.
not a that is not a handsome worm I found a list of the most nightmarish worms do
you think other worms look at this where I look at the worm like it's like like
Robert Wadlow or whoever that tall guy was like they're like oh he looks so
crazy right I think he's in the Wormley's believe it or not museum and a
big statue Wormley's believe it or worm
Wormley's I am a worm you will not believe what this caterpillar turned into
just I don't like it yeah no I again like that is not a worm making a worm
that long is one thing but then making it poisonous is too far yeah God you
fucked this one up so bad mm-hmm yeah yeah everybody's good you must have
must have let Jesus handle that one I bet that's what it was yeah this is you
He was like, yeah, you can handle the worms.
And he was like, okay, dad.
(laughing)
- And now I'll make a long one.
- Now I'm gonna make the biggest worm ever,
you fucking asshole, dad.
Fuck you, pussy.
- Yeah.
- Poop biotics.
- It would be okay if maybe there was like one of them.
Okay, I'm done, sorry.
Shh.
Say the poop biotics thing.
- Read it.
- I need a clean take.
- Okay, all right, all right.
I'm giving it to you right poop biotics god damn it Caleb Caleb can't remember
which one of us is which mm-hmm I'm bald poop by odd read this this is your
favorite thing no it's not my favorite thing and it's also redundant we've
already got this read it could a path toward a better hell could a path toward
fucking god damn it could a path toward better health begin with a baby's diaper
yeah you wish baby poop specifically the microbes inhabiting baby's guts no I
I don't could one day produce a biotic pedophiles inhabiting babies guts such
as Patrick Doran shut up why did I agree to read this one I should have fucking
you didn't you didn't agree you just yeah I wanted to I saw you I saw you
drooling the second you saw I was not drooling baby poop it's not funny to say
that about me what do you like baby poop yes you do you do like baby poop no yes
- Yes!
- No!
(laughing)
- He turned his mic off.
- Oh, he turned his microphone off.
- He just said, what is that?
Oh, don't say, don't.
- No, I didn't say anything when the mic was turned off.
I was just trying to make Cameron mad.
- You said something crazy.
- Why would I be mad that you're not talking?
- Yeah, that was like, I was so sublime for a moment.
It's back to the old days.
- You wanna get sublime?
- No, that's too close to Reagan.
- You wanna get Bradley Noel in here?
you want me to go Bradley Noel? You will not go Bradley Noel on me. I'm gonna go
Bradley Noel on myself. Don't do, do not start fucking, what did he do? I don't, did
he kill himself? I don't know who that is. I think he overdosed. Yeah well he killed himself with
something, it wasn't on purpose. Yeah. What's so special about baby poo
microbes? Some types of microorganisms in baby poop promote the production of
molecules called short fatty short chain fatty acid short fatty chain fatty chain
acids fatty chains which are associated with the healthy gut. Dude, fatty chains would be a good nickname.
Short chain, I'm a short chain fatty asshole. Short chain fatty spins. Okay, all right.
That's kind of cool. Yeah. How about you keep reading bud. Which are associated
with a healthy gut. Fecal transplants with these microbes could help to correct imbalances
in the gulp.
Fuck.
In the gulp.
Gulp? Where the fuck did the L come from?
You took it.
Oh, I took it.
Yeah, you knew there was an L coming.
Promoting the growth of beneficial bacteria and protecting against disease.
Why'd you bother reading that whole one? We already talked about it.
I know.
Come on. We told you not to.
You are doing badly, don't do it.
We asked you not to read that one.
You're high right now.
I am my own you're high like I don't know you're high on poop fumes you're gonna
kill yourself with a one of those mini umbrellas they put in a pina colada like
Bradley no just slitting your wrist with that I hate you you don't hate me drug
addict I love you I'm not a drug addict I'm the first drug addict druggy show me
your tongue if you're not a if it's blue you're a drug addict he doesn't even
have a tongue fuck right is that what that means what when someone has a blue
tongue that means they just ate a raspberry lollipop blue raspberry no I
think that means that they just smoked weed yeah or something worse yeah they
ate a fruit roll-up yeah that's way worse sugar is the real drug mm-hmm it
really we're all addicts yep I drink sugar-free Red Thunder guess what two of
them in 30 minutes. That's what kind of shit I'm on. Let's fucking go dude. There's a last
entry here. Don't drink your energy drink and try and brag.
Ocean fertilizer. Whales are among the largest living creatures on earth. As such, they generate
enormous quantities of pee and poop. And that's a good thing, as their waste provides critical
nutrients for a variety of marine creatures. Whales typically relieve themselves at the
sea surface before they dive, leaving behind a fluffy effluvia plume. This
fecal feast releases nutrients that originated in ocean depths and nourish
phytoplankton, tiny marine plants which live close to the surface and play an
important part in ocean food webs. Imagine God fucks you so bad where he's like,
"All right, you're gonna be so small that people can't even see you. You are gonna
live in the ocean. You don't get to go do anything in the cool stuff on land." And
get this you can only eat a cloud of poop from a giant whale yeah phytoplankton
yeah I'd like to fight out plankton stop trying to get that damn secret recipe
plankton where I might fight oh you dude was plankton eating poop that whole time
he was eating pearls poop what if yeah what if that's in the fucking with that's
a secret that's a fan theory right there yeah cuz pearl and mr. Krabs live
together so mr. Krabs was collecting and that's why I've planked in like the
recipe so much it all comes together mm-hmm and Sandy was a squirrel who
lived underwater and spongebob is a happy yellow friend breaking the theme song
was great breaking news what just Lane Maxwell has been charged with sex
trafficking a 14 year old girl oh just now you heard it here first on this
episode that was and that girl was Patrick Patrick no yep Pat you did it
buddy you've you testified you took him down dude you were you're a pro and I'm
happy for you I'm sorry about what happened to you don't say that that's
I'm sorry that you are a girl that's hard that's really really hard and you're
still 14 years later I know that's tough - you're stuck in time that boy stuck in
time I was born on a leap year so you're that's cool
wow that's crazy you know could could that not have waited maybe five minutes
I thought the episode was ending I didn't realize we were- I thought it said 57.
Okay so back to fucking whale shit. Yeah I can't remember you know exactly what the
joke we were doing was unfortunately. Ocean fertilizer I'm gonna turn Pat into ocean
fertilizer mafia style after that. Let's try to get back into the joke now. Whales they're
peeing poop I can't do it. Oh yeah Spongebob sex traffic- no that's not the-
see I'm getting my wires crossed right now and it's because of you. I thought
that it would be special if we broke the news we people have known this for days
now yeah it's not I forgot the news I I forgot that there's a schedule a
schedule you thought that this was live-streamed for a little bit that look
everything bleeds together now I don't know what which way is up that's a
different thing that's directional that doesn't have to do with time all right
You know what?
Let's finish this off with some cowboy insults.
Okay.
Some cowboy insults?
Yeah, I have a list of cowboy insults
that I was saving for a rainy day.
Did you write these?
No.
Yes, yeah, yeah, I wrote all these, you're right.
Best from bestinsults.com.
It's 'cause I'm a cowboy.
Yep, cowboy insults for best insults.
Oh no, come on, no, we have to save this one.
We'll do this one next week.
There's too much here.
Why?
This is, no, this is so, no,
we're not doing this all right now in two minutes.
Can I read one?
I'm really liking these looking at them.
can't read any of them. This is our first teaser. Okay. It's our first like
foreshadowing next episode. Okay, well let's get like a clean cut and then we'll
just edit this into the next episode. Yeah, we won't. Why not? Because I'm not
gonna do that. I'll do it. No you won't. If you remind me I'll do it. No you won't
because I won't send you the files. Fuck. Alright, ready? Yep. Alright, this is my one
cowboy insult mm-hmm everybody ready you prepared yeah even molasses would not run
down your legs yeah because of your laziness Wow that's a little that's
gonna be a strong let's get the hype going for next week's episode can you
harass everyone yeah just let everyone know the cowboy one is coming up the
cowboy episode coming probably you know I voice then but there will be a couple
of cowboy voices coming up I can tell you I think you better believe that you
know your hide on that yeah you know boys say right yeah you bet your saddle
and your lasso on that do not stop do not stop messaging anybody with more than
10,000 followers about this episode that's coming out you know what I want
you you send this to Chrissy Teigen I want Chrissy Teigen to hear this I want
drill to hear this I want yep who's in those are the two people I can think of
right now I want I want Marco Rubio I want him involved I want Paul F. Tompkins
to have to turn his phone off for a week I want Paula Abdul to go back to Canada
because she's being so harassed on the streets of the United States of people
Canada fuck yeah no name like that Paula Abdul Abdul is a Canadian name she's
not Canadian yeah she's from San Fernando Canada it does say CA
Wow told you I asked realistic bye