you're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
- Podcasts with a podcast.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Okay.
- Okay. - I did it.
Hey guys, listen to this.
- Yeah.
- I'm silly, I'm silly, I'm silly, I'm silly.
I'm silly, get it?
- Oh, like a Millie.
- What? - Yeah.
- What is that, Caleb?
- Like, wait, like what, Caleb?
Caleb, is that a whoopee cushion?
It doesn't pick up.
It didn't get picked up.
It didn't pick up.
It picked up on my mic.
That's good.
I see a humongous spike on my mic.
You clicked zoom so we couldn't hear it.
I'll hold it further away.
Yeah.
Here, ask again.
Hey, Caleb, what did you have for lunch today?
No, no, ask if it's a whoopee cushion.
Hey, Caleb, what did you have for-- did you eat beans for lunch today, Caleb?
Hey, does this answer your question?
it's still clipped that's still clipped in zoom you guys remember the loudest
whoopee cushion of all time I won it I won it where did you win it the arcade
you went to the arcade I went to the Chinatown fair arcade why did you do
there it's not a fair it's a fair arcade isn't it's it's that none of the games
are the fairest arcade of all yeah I went to the arcade I got a whoopee cushion in
They didn't call it a Chinese finger trap in the Chinatown arcade.
I'm not kidding. They just called it a finger trap.
That makes sense.
I was like, "Yeah, I guess so. A Roman candle in Rome is a candle."
It's true.
Yeah. I went to the arcade. I won a Whoopie Cushion.
And I played Guitar Hero. Pretty great night.
Wow.
You played Guitar Hero at the arcade?
Yeah, dude. You can versus all your friends.
The arcade is open?
They have like limited capacity. It was like just me and two other people there.
Oh.
It's pretty fun, dude. Except for all that stupid hand sanitizer.
Yeah.
I hate that shit.
Smells bad. Makes your makes it if you eat like a hamburger or a hot dog.
I never until COVID I never realized how many different like types of consistency of hand
sanitizer there are. Like I assumed it was all just like, oh, it's like hand sanitizer.
Like there's only one.
It's all runny.
I feel like every time that I get hand sanitizer, it's like a different kind of disgusting. Like
There's some that just like stays on your hands forever.
There's some that's like a film.
Yeah.
Somebody that like smells really bad.
Like I don't know how there can be that many different kinds.
Like it's just like alcohol, right?
Yeah, it's alcohol and beads.
Yeah.
So that's the worst kind.
The bead stuff.
I like it.
It gets in all my cuts.
Ugh.
I love it, dude.
Yeah, it makes me feel like a warrior.
Mm-hmm.
I hate that.
When it gets in my paper cut that I got from
taking from putting a dollar bill in my wallet too quickly.
Yeah, it's gonna feel tough to which I do all the time.
Yeah, you know dollar bills are so sharp because they're just made out of normal paper and they'll cut your fingers. Yeah
It's fucked up. You know, what's the most fucked up hand sanitizer when you go into a bathroom?
And they have it where the soap should be
And then you put it on your hands and then you wash it off
And you're like am I what the what what is this? Am I on earth? Yeah
where the fuck am i with
you're in america and say that i is so
is a handsome just using hands and washing your hands is better than just
using hand sanitizer a
so but what about what about now and i want to wash your hands with their
using all the with someone watching your hands is so gross
i agree
which is better washing your hands with soap and water are using hand sanitizer
it's better to do nothing because the different things on your hand builds up
a pretty answer to my question
one of the other i didn't know you could say neither
i'm i'd say i would or there was an option so i don't think you can pick it
i don't play by your rules and i'm kind of a bad boy
you're you're kinda sitting here like
you think you own the damn place
i mean you just too stupid to pick one
okay hand sanitizer then hand sanitizer i think soap is probably better
so but yes so then here's the
question right is
is plus soap without water
or hand
could you put soap on your hands and then use hand sanitizer instead of water and
would that be better
now or what if you just use so play kills and sanitize it what are you use water
what if you use water like it was so
and what i like it was a lot of reaction
what if you use
what if you have
what if you use like a what if you give your hands like a dust bath like a
chinchilla or a sparrow
okay could that get you and i think they can get covered
chinchillas can get covered
i'd just found that out
Can any animals get COVID? Is that confirmed?
Can we check on that?
Is it is in the bat where it came from?
I think the bats get sick.
I don't know.
Is that how you say that?
I think it's a penguin.
Penguin.
It's called a penguin.
It's a flightless bird.
OK.
That is a very funny ass movie about.
What's it called?
The fart of the penguins or whatever.
You remember that one?
Yeah, I do.
It's just like them talking over like penguin footage
and being like, suck my penguin ass, dude.
That was talked about. Yeah.
Have we? You said that you saw it in the theater.
It's one of the ultimate movies, dude.
Yeah. Sick.
We should bring back doing doing funny voiceover over nature footage,
like, you know, making a lion sound like he's going, Hey, yeah, roaring.
Yeah. The lion with a lisp.
Yeah. Yeah. It's like, what you're I love the zebra.
That's why I totally love the.
and people like Derek you look ugly today
Derek the lion that's what they said they would make the lions talk to each
other or like it's like you know like
Comedy Central is knocking on my door right now yeah like we want to make
a show in 2004 we want the sassiest gayest animals
can you guys just make a bunch of gay animal voices?
we say does this answer your question I'm a giraffe
yeah I'm the little ant eater
I love eating ants oh my god there's another ant
I'm going to buy stuff like that.
I'm going to buy six seasons of this show.
It's going to be produced by Adam Carolla.
It's called Gay Nature.
It's called Gay Nature, and it's going to be a hit.
It's on. And also for 20 years after it's done airing,
it'll be the only thing on Comedy Central from 10 in the morning to 5 p.m.
Yeah, it'll just be a just a seven hour block every day of gay nature reruns.
Breaking news.
Gay Nature canceled after controversial monkey segment.
and it's a monkey, it's a monkey and he's going,
"I think I'm gonna have sex with a guy and start a disease."
(laughing)
- I feel sick.
I'm gonna suck that guy's dick.
- Yeah.
- I'm a gay monkey.
- That's the kind of writing you get with Adam Carolla.
- That's the kind of swagged out,
man-centric writing you get with Adam Carolla.
- And then Adam, and then, and then Adam ruins everything.
Comes on the scene and he goes,
"Actually, the monkey that gave the guy AIDS was not gay.
It was straight."
(laughing)
- That's the only thing you said.
It's the only thing he fact checks.
The monkey actually had a wife and her name was Alessa.
The monkey was paid to do it.
[Laughter]
Yeah. I'm not... that's a...
I think, um...
Can you imagine if you were a monkey and you were in monkey college and you were like,
"I'm gonna experiment this once," and you started AIDS?
[Laughter]
I love thinking about the guy who fucked the monkey
Because for him to have transmitted it to humans, it means that in his life,
he fucked a monkey and another person. And that's game.
That's some fucking game.
He wasn't just some monkey fucker.
He fucked a monkey and then he was like, "Time to get some pussy."
He fucked a monkey and he was like, "No, I don't think so."
I don't feel so good. My bones hurt. And now I'm gonna fuck his other guy.
I don't know why fucking a monkey wasn't for me. Anyway, I'll just fuck this guy just normal
Yeah, but that is ultimate game if you can is that how is that how it started? I don't remember
Yeah, guy fucked him. Oh, you don't remember you weren't there. No, I was you were the guy. Oh
Yep, I don't know. I don't know whether that's how how AIDS started but in my brain. Yeah, that's I
I kind of if a scientist came up to me and tried to tell me how it really started I would say no because it's less fun
so true
So true. Yeah, I'm surprised that
Kovat wasn't started by monkeys because it seems like every day. It seems like every disease
That just like destroys you is started by monkeys. What as revenge like what like which diseases?
Monkey's caressless leg syndrome the monkey's paw. Yeah
Banana addiction. Yeah
Yeah, true
Uncle's life. Mm-hmm getting bitten by a monkey
Swingers yeah, did they get I feel like getting bit. I feel he was probably got bit by a monkey
I don't know. So I think it was a guy fucked a monkey having sex style. Yeah
Reverse cowgirl with the monkey.
[laughter]
I wanna look at you.
Keep the lights on.
Keep the torches on.
I have to look at you.
Yeah, do you think he was like playing music?
Yeah, he had
banana peels leading to the bed.
Yeah, how do you seduce a monkey?
'Cause a monkey
is faster than a human.
It's not like he like caught him and fucked him.
That monkey was like down.
he was down to fuck.
Yeah, the monkey was into it.
I hope it was a baboon.
I feel like that's the most fuckable monkey, right?
No. What?
It's got a big fucking slit on its butt.
It's not the most fuckable monkey.
It's got a big puffy vagina.
It's like the biological equivalent of a sign on its back that says "fuck my ass."
Exactly.
It's begging for you to fuck it.
I looked up...
These whorish monkeys, they're putting their ass on the glass, dude.
I did, I did just google "most fuckable monkey"
What'd you end up with?
Um...
Uh, the human, technically, it's a monkey
Wow, here, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Should we... nah, we shouldn't read this list
I found a list called "The World's 7 Most Fuckable Lesser Apes"
Um, yeah, we should read that list
What, what website is this on?
It's on Runt of the Web
web
The website loaded but nothing else loaded.
Oh, I got it, dude.
I'll tell you what number one of eight is, right?
Also, there's eight entries here.
I can't, I can't, oh, it's 'cause I have Adblock on, huh?
Turn it off, dude.
You're gonna want to see this hot monkey.
Okay. What the fuck, dude?
Oh, yeah, mine won't load either.
It must be Adblock.
Yeah, it's Adblock.
I actually love supporting websites in Amazon,
so I never have Adblock on.
I hate supporting websites.
Dude, you should use--
All right, I'm on Adblock Plus
I'm whitelisting "Rent of the Web/Fuckable Apes"
[laughter]
I can't wait to, in a year, see that on my whitelist
and look at my ad block.
It's so funny that we had something else planned.
[laughter]
We'll get to it. This is more, this is really pressing right now.
What the, dude! The blurb for the first one, what the fuck?
What is this website?
Wait, this is...
this website let me let me read the only three categories the only three categories on this
website it's runt.com then at the top it's originals galleries then donald trump
the world's seven most fuckable lesser apes um number one is the hulak gibbon wait you gotta do
the uh you gotta do the okay go ahead the intro shabani an 18 year old gorilla at the hayashima
zoo in japan has become the center of worldwide attention
since a story about women flocking to see the handsome a point viral but if tall
dark enhancements in your thing don't fret
we've rounded up a few equally fuckable aids for the simian curious
uh... yeah i'm ready to know what you want to do what you did
uh...
made it does have a uh... nice eyebrows this is the last sense about the
eyebrows is like one of those evil things i think it's the
that we've ever read on this show.
- Oh my God.
- They say, he might not be able to give consent,
but those come hither eyebrows scream yes, yes.
- Oh my God, dude.
- What have you put us in that?
- What is wrong with this,
you wrote this wrong website.
- Yeah, what the fuck is this website?
- Hold on, let me look at the Donald Trump stuff.
- I think this is a,
I think this is a satire website.
- A satire website.
and this is like
but this is not there's nothing satirical about this it is posting yet you know
i'm on the main i'm on the main page for and this is this is the these are the
headlines
this russian guide is amazingly creative cosplay on a hilariously small budget
fifty-two teen tweets at least the future is funny twenty seven times spot
spotify exploited its users have is for marketing and it's a funny as expected
like these are just
the city to best clap backs of all time
We I think we should spend some time on this.
And in the world's seven most fuckable lesser apes.
Right in the middle. What's number two?
Siemang.
Oh, the Siemang. That's the best ape.
That's my favorite. Maxing out at 30 pounds.
Oh, he's got a middle part. The Siemang is the biggest.
The Siemang has a guller sac.
So it's like, it has like a throat like a frog.
And it like makes these crazy noises.
Two ball sacs. That's ultimate.
Yeah. Maxing out at 30 pounds,
the Siemang is the biggest of the lesser apes
in more ways than one, they said.
Just the thought of getting inside this fru-vigorous member of the mor-moraceae
Oh, come on.
Is enough for us to overlook its inability to say no.
Why are they obsessed with this- with monkeys?
Dude, what the fuck is this?
Saying yes or no to sex.
Who wrote this? How did we-
How do we report this to the police?
Yeah.
I'm trying to-
Before we finish the list off.
I'm trying to call the cops.
Hey, there's like a guy online who is making pictures of monkeys that are horny and I might
commit a crime if you don't take it down.
Number three is the northern buff-cheeked gibbon.
This newly discovered species of gibbon from the jungles of Southeast Asia makes us hot
and heavy.
In fact, we'd like to buff its southern cheeks.
With its sleek, dark pelt and relative of manly gait, who cares if it lacks the understanding
to acquiesce to a sexual act?
Why?
Why are they so-
is this this is like the evil version of the like like because
of his great size.
He cannot be a human being and thus and yeah, the same this
is the same writing style.
This is the most readable by this is written by the guy who
got AIDS.
This is that guy.
No, it's not.
It's him dude.
I think this is his website.
Number four is Kloss's Gibbon.
They all look kind of the same.
Yeah, they're all as as called also called the.
Yeah, why is it all Gibbons?
Long arms, dude.
They hit it from the back.
Slap that ass.
Choke you.
Put a finger in your mouth.
That's just the truth.
You know how like girl,
but sometimes you'll have to like be like,
hey, move your move your when your doggy style,
you have to be like move your knees further.
I don't know what that means, but go on monkey style.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Yeah, because they have long the distance from their hips to their knees is too long.
"Clauses given, also called the Baloo, this primate is considered a threatened species."
Yeah, when I'm around.
"Probably from all the fucking people want to do to it."
Well, they stole my joke.
[laughter]
"One thing's for sure, give us ten minutes alone with this guy, and we'll show you an animal to which the concept of permission is non-existent."
This is like...
Ugh! Awful!
Oh, Christ!
Come on!
Come on, dude.
I mean, we talk about fucking animals, what, every episode, fifteen times?
But not like that!
not like that.
But not like that, dude.
I like that the recommended stuff on this page is still like, "The funniest reactions to
Capitol Riot.
Best toys.
Buy one of these 35 toys for your niece or nephew."
Like they don't even have anything that's similar to this.
Bizarre photos that prove history was far stranger than you ever realized.
It is just like a random...
This is the best website.
So this website minus this.
Number five the Bornean white bearded Gibbon.
Endemic to a small range between the Capuas and Burrito Rivers.
Burrito River.
Okay, sign me up dude.
Hey, somebody somebody send Perry Grip an email.
He's going to want to hear about this one.
He's going to think of a pretty funny song.
In Southern Borneo.
We imagine it gets its name from the amount of cum people shoot
into its face when they see it.
those piercing eyes unable to reflect either implied or express agreement
definitely get our panties dropping
uh... so it's a woman
of learning this or a man who wears panties
skinner way it's getting pretty hot
uh... let's just finish this was just cut the rest of the way here to come in
with what you don't like it yeah i don't like i mean it's anymore
i wish it people need to go check out this website and you see that
this is clearly supposed to be a a satirical uh... list
but it's the only one from the website
i think that was just a normal you had a place for you to have a table section
dedicated to donald trump
well he said he's good let me tell you he actually did all that crap
all that wild crap that he did that
of the crazy as shit
uh... i just would like click
of shit
actually clicked one of the the
when i fucking click up here
I accidentally clicked one of the ads and it brought me to coffee magazine dot com.
We should write an email to coffee magazine and be like, "Do you know what your ads are
on?
Are you sure?"
Here's coffee, here's coffee magazine.
Coffee brewing methods, coffee reviews, coffee stories, coffee recipes, coffee musings, and
coffee perks.
Yeah, I don't think they'd be thrilled.
We should try and get this website de-platformed.
Start with the advertisers.
Yeah they want to fuck a bunch of different kinds of monkeys.
Dude I just clicked on the Donald Trump heading and the first image is just a picture of Donald
Trump standing up and behind him is the Israel flag and in front of him is Jesus.
Pretty strong Photoshop job.
Yeah.
That's pretty good.
We don't have to say, we'll just say, okay, the next two are the Lar Gibbon and the Silvery
Gibbon.
It's all Gibbons.
Yeah, so the thing is, I get that this is a joke, but it's also like, at least pick some
like actually fuckable monkeys, you know what I mean?
Right, you just looked at Gibbons.
Yeah, like you just found, you just searched like lesser apes and picked like the first
group.
Oh, here, okay.
I'm really glad they have a, they have a Facebook share button, guys, in case you want.
I think I might share this on Facebook right now.
I found the author.
What's his name?
Michael Gibbon fucker.
Wow, what are his other articles?
Top 10 Gibbons I fucked.
There's a podcast called Gibbons We Fucked.
And who does he host it with?
Channa's Ape.
i found that i found the about page for run to the web
uh...
run to the web is a spirited site that brings a breath of fresh air to the web's
comedic landscape
by marrying a blend of biting original pieces with highly clickable curated
content
run to represent internet comedy at its very best
and then it has a section for the people behind runs and it's three people here
the first two people
are morgan in gary and terry dorgan
and they have pictures
the third person does not have a picture and it's alex baldwin
and it says founder
helen paul came in to get a guy who did a great alex baldwin
now i don't think so
i'd is a quick dot i would i would see a picture of the right here
and uh... it's a bit of a guy's on the
we should we call your address is twitter
has he done
Not too good.
Not too good? Is he dead?
No, he's alive.
Do you think he's getting top from a monkey?
I don't know.
I think a really fuckable monkey would be a gorilla
because they have those big nostrils and you could maybe fit your penis in it.
Oh, come on, man.
Come on. What the hell?
What? I don't want to fuck a monkey.
It's definitely not okay for us to fuck any monkey.
No.
Correct. Right?
I would never fuck a monkey.
Agreed.
But can like a gorilla fuck a gibbon?
- I mean that's the way of nature, yeah.
- What, but is it okay?
- If a dog--
- What if a duck fucks a bug?
- If a dog fucks a cat in the forest and nobody's around.
- Yeah, that's a very good point.
- Can they make a baby?
- I don't know, man.
I'm just trying to figure out the math of all this.
- The offspring of a dog and cat.
- It's a fox.
uh...
uh... that's why they're in the woods yeah if you're abandoned that's why they
can't be pets because
uh... i don't know
his you're just just as we have to speak i don't like them
i think they could uh...
i think you could only seen videos of russian people in info
that's the craziest that's the thing i love about russia's area of record
fund us to cause disorder in politics but they also are gonna let me get a
caracal. It's much like a fox is what happens when a dog fucks a cat if a
robber breaks into your house and your guard dog starts fucking him that's how
raccoons are made. Wow really? Oh my god wow. That makes so much sense.
Like a criminal outfit. True yeah that's a good point yeah and that's why raccoons love
stealing it's in their DNA dude. They steal your trash.
Because they're part robbers. A dog will eat a trash.
Dogs like trash. Robbers like stealing.
Yeah so you get a perfect trash.
Exactly. Yeah. You ever seen somebody call a raccoon a trash panda?
Yeah it's pretty epic. You ever see?
Pretty good. Yeah. I'm really excited. I love those people like
freshman year of college who would just do like reddit jokes to you in class
yeah and they'd say shit like that yeah dude total trash panda oh look at the
little trash panda mm-hmm oh that dogger oh oh no look at this
look at this wholesome wiggle boy and it's a snake yeah
it's so cool dude little do you know that's so cool
that snake will kill you dude yeah wholesome wiggle boy is not
yeah all right that's the if you're using that to describe a snake
It's, I guess I'm fine with that, but if you're using that to describe anyone else...
If you're using that to describe a person, I got a real problem with that.
Yeah, that feels really charged and a lot of different ways.
Yeah, I don't like that.
Did you hear that?
They're talking about Jeff from The Wiggles.
He's always sleeping!
Did you guys ever know anybody with a snake, a pet snake, like a big one?
No.
I knew a guy, what are those snakes that are like yellow and white?
What the fuck?
Yeah, my neighbor growing up, his dad had like an alligator for a couple weeks.
Oh, that's not a pet.
What do you mean?
That's a guest.
He had an alligator stay over.
He didn't have a pet alligator for a couple weeks.
Yeah.
That's fucking, it's a rental, dude.
Yeah, I guess.
Yeah.
Did you get to meet the alligator?
I think I got to see it in the cage it was in.
Yeah, alligators are not like...
The case?
I would say they're the only animal that people...
It's impossible to anthropomorphize with cute photos and be like,
"Oh, look at this sweet..."
It's just a fucking dinosaur.
No, people do it.
People do it.
Have you seen that?
People do that?
People do that all the time.
It pisses me off because it's like...
I don't want to see a video of...
of like people post the videos of the really fat alligators.
Oh yeah. And they and they act like it's cute and it's like I know
you give that thing one second with a baby with it with its brother and it
will rip its brother in half. Yeah dude. It's like the only baby. It's the only
animal. Why do you want to give a baby to an alligator? You want you want to give
an alligator a baby? I just want to see what happens.
It's like I'm doing experiments okay. It's like do you guys remember the
The scientific method.
You guys remember those like YouTube videos,
early YouTube videos where they would just
make two animals fight?
Yeah.
Those ruled.
They put like a scorpion in with like a fucking, a snake.
Yeah, or like the classic mongoose
versus a cobra or whatever.
Dude, those were so sick.
Or like, there was one that I always heard about,
which probably didn't exist,
but my older brother told me about it,
and it was a, it was an ostrich versus a lion.
And he claimed that there was a video
of an ostrich versus a lion
where the ostrich kicks the lion in the face
so hard that it dies.
- Yeah, I don't believe that at all.
- I believe that.
- Yeah.
- Do you think an ostrich, okay.
Ostrich versus kangaroo, do you think that,
or kangaroo wins, kangaroos are nuts.
- Probably fall in love, dude.
- What are ostrich native to?
ridge
there were ostriches around here dude
i thought there were ostriches in fuckin'
australia
i think australia is emus
they already have their kicking thing
okay so kangaroo vs emu
uh... i'm sure that's happened and i'm sure you can find a way to do that
kangaroo beats anything that can't punch it
yeah
Yeah, but dude getting pecked out by a bit like oh
And they have claws and getting pecked out. What does that mean? Yeah, dude?
And I just got pecked out
Yeah, I don't wear
picked out of your eyes
Guys get all pecked out and shit not get it you're getting them pecked out though. Yeah, I just got
he pecked out.
Oh dude, this kangaroo is smaller than this emu.
He shut down the zoo for a private party.
Kangaroos are so fucking strong though and they have claws and shit.
They can fuck people up.
I do, I...
Like if we're talking like a big kangaroo, like a full grown kangaroo.
It's gotta be like a baby.
It could just like wring its fucking neck dude.
I just think of that video of that guy punching.
Dude, this emu is, oh my god, it's bucking out.
That guy punching that kangaroo in the face and the kangaroo is like, "How did you just
kick me with your hands is one of the fucking greatest videos.
Dude, there's so many videos of kangaroos like walking up to like a glass door and just like
going through it because they don't realize that it's a door and then just leaving.
It's like smashing through shit, dude.
A scary ass animal up close is a fucking pelican.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, they're weird.
It's the size of a polar bear.
Birds look disgusting up close.
No, a pelican will like attack you.
It has a giant mouth that it uses to eat trash and free meat.
do that thing where they like hit their neck up through the bottom of their mouth and like
turn their mouth inside out?
Yeah, they're really scary.
Every bird looks disgusting up close.
Honestly, every bird fucking sucks.
I hate birds.
You know what the worst, yeah, the worst bird, the worst looking bird is the condor.
Condor's bad.
The California condor.
I think the worst looking bird is the potoo.
What is that?
I hate fucking potoo.
That's the one that has the eyes that go the opposite directions.
I need to spell it.
P-O-T-O-O.
I can't imagine.
They're just like, like, it's just like a demon.
I'll say this much, as a socialist...
What are you talking about?
As a socialist, I think the worst is the, is the bald eagle.
Look, dude.
Yeah.
It's an ugly, it represents so much...
Dude, this looks like this, this looks like a, this looks like a sleaf stack.
It's fucked up, dude.
It either has, the eyes are either pitch black or they're like bright yellow with pupils pointing
the opposite way.
You know what? No, I just saw this thing with its mouth open.
Yeah, dude. It's fucked.
I wanna throw a stick of dynamite in there.
Do you guys ever see something natural and you just think, "Nature's so metal."
Yeah. Nature is metal.
I do sometimes wish nature was more hip-hop.
Yeah.
I wish that there was more kind of hip-hop animals.
Like breakdancing and graffiti.
I'll accept anything in nature as long as it's not rap or country.
So true, yeah.
As long as nature is not rap and it's not country, I like it.
Even like the old stuff.
But nature, there should be more like, you know, hippos that can do graffiti or something.
Hip hop hippo?
Now I wasn't even thinking that, but now that's the best thing you've ever said.
And I'm really proud of you and I hope you keep talking.
What if there were two rappers from New Zealand called the Hip Hop Hopotamus and the Rhyme
Noscerous?
Wow, and what would their rap sound like?
I don't know.
Some wild shit.
Any lyrics you could throw out maybe?
I'm the Mother Flippin' Rhyme Noscerous.
Wow dude, you can't even say the F word.
They don't have it in New Zealand.
No.
No, it's because all the vowels move down one.
Fleep.
So.
For fuck.
A-E-I-O-U so it's like their it's the last vowel don't know where it goes.
The only the only whenever I start thinking about a New Zealand accent the only phrase that ever goes
through my head is is I'm Hitler yeah on because of Tiger with TT. Oh I'm Hitler. I'm Hitler. Does
he have a New Zealand accent in that movie? Check me out I'm Hitler. I think he does I don't remember
I think he does have an accent.
I'm nice Hitler.
Um, yeah.
Hello, it's me funny Hitler.
Hello, it's me very funny Hitler.
Oh, hello, I'm here to be funny with you.
Do you have any porridge?
I'm hungry, I'm Hitler.
Do you have any ported meat I could have?
Hungry, hungry Hitler?
I've got a long ride home, and I like to eat spam from the camp.
Back to heaven.
It's a long train back to heaven where I live.
He doesn't live in heaven.
Yeah.
For him, for Hitler, hey, well...
Don't set me from heaven to be your imaginary friend?
For Hitler, heaven is...
I'm your guardian angel?
His heaven is hell.
Dude, if Hitler was your guardian angel, you'd be... you might be a bad boy.
Yeah.
What if he was your family out there?
What if the guy in like It's a Wonderful Life, he's like about to kill himself and his guardian
angel comes up to rescue him and it's Hitler?
He's like, "Oh, fuck you."
Oh man.
(laughing)
He's British Hitler.
What if he had a guardian demon?
I do.
That would be sick, dude.
Dude, guardian demon,
'cause a guardian demon would protect you.
Dude, I have a guardian demon, it's called my mind.
Isn't that just big mouth?
Doesn't, don't they have demons in big mouth?
They have puberty demons.
No, yeah, I think they have like--
Ugh.
Like--
Yeah, it's disgusting.
I thought it was cooler.
I thought the whole thing was that they're all,
it's like devil worship.
Yeah dude, I thought that it was like those were like the souls of pedophiles that were like trapped within monsters that were trying to like teach them to masturbate and stuff.
I guess that's what it is.
Yeah, yeah, I thought no I thought it was like like eternally cursed like pedophile souls that were like trapped within a crystal.
I was like pretty sure about that but and they get punished forever by having to watch kids jerk off.
Yeah, those are the good pedophiles that go to heaven so they get rewarded by becoming.
Oh, it's just priests.
Puberty monsters.
Oh, holy shit.
Dude, fucking Bill Maher over here.
Look at me go.
You're serious.
I'm going to call you spotlight, Patrick.
Serious spotlight right now.
Why?
Cause I'm cause I was born in Boston and I'm shaped like a globe.
Yep.
Recently I, uh, since we decided 2021 is the year of the frog or for Sullivan, I
keep, I've like, keep seeing the name Sullivan around.
I'm like, damn, it really is you're the frog. And I'm like,
Oh, wait, no, I'm just in Boston.
True. Oh, Sullivan. Wow.
Every year. Oh, well, oh, the Sullivan brothers cars. Oh,
Sullivan management. Oh, Sullivan. Oh, yeah.
Podcast fans down at the
Hello. Hello. Yes.
Hi. Just walking into Boston, sand and gravel. Just
I'll have some
Hi.
sticks to go and a Coors Light in an open bottle.
i'll take some gravel
from the house
yeah he is going to do our original list it's not about fucking monkeys yes sir
night at this is on top two lists for one of their these people in spoil your
spoiled you should pay a sway more money than you do and yeah
please i had to give i'd give that money back to that all you guys that are the
sponsor money
yeah galaxy like money
i gave that money back i don't know why i did that because i found out i i feel
it's a jenny and i told them like
all i'm i'm gonna take my post down because i found out it violates the t_o_s_
and they're like well if you just leave it up for another twenty four hours uh...
you can delete it
and you can keep the money and i was like right
fucking did you give me a day or two did it money forever they're not going to see
you know i know i'd so i get for trying to be a fucking good person about this
You suck dude. You give money back to the scummiest people on earth.
I know. You literally, that's like maybe the worst, the stupidest course of action.
Like making the post, taking the money, and then deleting the post and giving it back.
Yeah.
That's just like...
Everyone's gonna, everyone's gonna fucking hate me for that.
You're a sellout. I thought we were rock and roll.
You did, you posted that ad just for, just for like the, the feeling of selling out.
You didn't even get the money.
I just want everyone to think I'm a sellout and not like me.
No, fuck you. Fuck me.
I just want everyone to hate me because I'm such a sellout.
If you had kept the money, no, I would have taken the money.
I would not have given the money back.
That's where you're wrong about this.
That's where you did wrong.
No, I know. I just...
I fucking...
You know?
I feel like such a fucking idiot.
I feel like the dumbest guy of all time.
Will you run an ad for me on your next big viral post?
I can.
It'll be a post under...
If you give me...
I'm Patrick and I suck.
And also I'm the guy who fucked a monkey and got AIDS.
No.
And I'll give you $100.
And then...
I shouldn't even have brought that up on here.
You bring it up...
I mean, you're fucking with the...
I could have died with that secret.
You're fucking with the Meisters right now.
I could have died with that secret, but I wear my heart on my sleeve.
You already told us the secret earlier.
You just brought it up here so that we could meister you again.
I hate being meistered.
I know you do.
You know I hate being meistered.
You're being owned by the mean meister and the stink meister right now.
Top 10 questionable things all moms do but don't admit.
This is a list of things all moms are guilty of whether they admit it or not.
So laugh it off and plunge forward.
Nice.
I'm going to plunge forward into the mom list.
Okay.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
I'm gonna listen to seven fuckable lesser moms.
Don't plunge into my mom.
I'm gonna plunge right in there.
Don't plunge in.
I'm gonna plunge in there and I'm gonna cause her to number one forget to pick up the kid.
That's right Patrick, I'm gonna make her leave you at theater practice.
I never went to theater practice.
Yeah you did, just admit it dude, you love Hamilton and shit.
I never did theater.
Yeah you did.
Cameron did theater.
You did In the Heights. You did an all white In the Heights.
Cameron did that.
You did a one man In the Heights.
one man like kinda Norbit style in the heights.
yeah
and it's funny because the part, the thing that made it Norbit style was really in
bad taste.
yeah I tried, I did, I did. It was not that you played all the characters.
I did try to bring Rasputia from Norbit into in the heights I thought it was a
good idea.
Thought it would work. Yeah, no it didn't work. No.
Actually a lot of people were mad at me. You paid fifteen thousand dollars for the
rights to the book. I paid another fifteen thousand for the exact suit.
Yeah, you had a tailor-made you had a light and magic design
You got the actual you got the actual suit that was used in filming, but it was like years old
So it was like rotten it rotting the latex like had holes in it and was like there were maggots in it
It was like a Chuckie cheat like an abandoned Chuckie. Yeah, like one of those old
Yeah, exactly like a Five Nights at Freddy's in the way, you know, you know, I
Do anything for the I'd do anything for this thing we called show
Wow, I
I will say you left it all on the stage.
Mm-hmm.
Yep.
You did.
You left so many voices on that stage.
Voices I could never do again.
Yeah.
And probably could have never done then.
Mm-hmm.
But you did it.
I did it.
And it was, it got, I got one and a half star.
Yep.
Roger Ebert.
Mm-hmm.
That's what killed him.
Because I filmed it.
I sent it to him.
He survived cancer and then died at your show.
I sent Roger Ebert the suit.
He died of racist shock.
Yeah. He did.
You sent Roger Ebert the suit and the like plastics in it got into his bloodstream and gave him cancer.
Yeah.
What's wrong? Are you crying?
No, I just imagined Roger Ebert and Norbert, Norbit for some reason.
Roger Norbit?
I don't know. I don't even know what I'm laughing at.
[Laughter]
Here we go.
Oh, we're getting there dude.
Hey Patrick, Roger Ebert. He died. It's not funny that he died. Dude I'm so upset
that Roger Ebert died. Is it gonna make you laugh Patrick? Maybe an ostrich
kicked his jaw off. Yeah that would have been cool. That would have been some pimp shit.
Roger Ebert just fucking lost his jaw in an ostrich accident.
Yeah and then people constantly like "oh he lost his jaw to cancer"
That was the name of the ostrich!
Nah dude he was in the Sahara and he got his shit rocked by an ostrich.
You know who wins in ostrich versus Roger Ebert?
A kangaroo literally slid his jaw dude.
It slid right off.
do just I watched Rick Moranis get his jaw slit. I forgot about that. That's one of the funniest
sentences. Kangaroos just walk around Australia doing the knockout game to people. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. It's like a it's like a random encounter in like an RPG. It's like when you like like find a
Pokemon in the wild grass. It's just like a kangaroo can just hop up to you at any moment
and just fucking rock your shit dude.
Just fucking, just...
And you know that they laugh so hard.
And the thing is, it's for the love of the game.
They don't take anything.
They have that pouch.
They could put your iPhone in there.
They can't even do it.
Have you...
Oh, we've talked about it,
but the inside of an ostrich pouch?
Yeah.
Disgusting.
It's wet.
It's a pussy, dude.
No, it's bone.
Um, oh yeah.
Just imagine hollows rounding the corner
in like a chicago and it's getting knocked out of the game by a kangaroo
any midwestern state having a kangaroo problem
any
any gang that gets a kangaroo
they win. ultimate yeah
three hundred block. a kangaroo with a gun? it's like when you get a mech on your team
or something. yeah exactly
though did i tell you guys about the racist and at the pool hall
like old man
i don't know
i don't know how it was in north carolina you don't even say that
when i was in north carolina with it it is commies off guard
uh... my brother dislike old man was like
a partner you wanna play a couple of games of coolies probably in the
seventies is this true
if you listen to uh... you know i thought you do
he was like uh...
he's super sweet he was like
talking about his family and shit
and just seemed like a really nice guy.
And then he was like, so your brother tells me to me,
he was like, your brother tells me you live in New York City.
And I was like, oh yeah, yeah, I do.
And he's like, well, I only went to New York City once.
It was with this girl that I was going steady with
back in the day.
And you know, the thing about New York City
is you shouldn't go out late at night.
You know that son?
And I was like, yeah, man, sure.
And he was like, yeah.
So one time I went on a walk around her house
at about 10 p.m. Brooklyn, New York City.
And what do I see across the block from me?
But let's just say five of New York's finest youths.
- Oh man. - That's what he said.
And then he was like.
- Oh no. (laughs)
- I basically had two options.
I could either run away, at which point they would chase me
and they would kill me, or I could just walk past them.
And so I held my breath and I walked past them
and then I ran away all the way home.
so he just told me a story about this scene five black guys are just running
home
and i was like okay and and uh... yeah new york's crazy dude
yeah and then we started to see it is he still does he think it's still like
that
it is he still has never like that there was never a time where you said that
that's what i think i don't know what you like
I have to run home!
Oh, I'm glad you ran away safely.
No, I'm not glad you ran away.
Did you know that I never had to do that?
That's not what I'm saying.
Yeah, but that was
that was the only, actually
the only racism that I saw when I was home.
In North Carolina,
that was the only racism you saw.
Yeah, it was a pretty record
year for me.
You didn't see any Confederate flags?
My granddad kept his lips
lips shut about Tiger Woods for an entire two weeks.
It was really impressive, yeah.
- Wow. - That's crazy.
That's actually, I'm impressed.
- Me too. - I'm proud of him.
- He was high on Oxycontin 'cause he had surgery,
so it could've been that.
He just kept falling asleep and asking for pretzels,
so he didn't have a lot of time to complain
about Tiger Woods.
- Hey, dude, what kind of-- - All in two ways.
- What kind of surgery do they give him?
They take the freakin' racist bone out of his body?
- Wow, maybe.
- You get it?
still leaves like a hundred and sixty something.
Yeah, two hundred and five other ones.
[Laughter]
Uh,
have you guys ever been
abandoned by your parents?
Like, once or twice.
Was it funny? No.
No. Pretty upsetting.
At, uh, at,
I think, um,
it was like, uh,
I was in band, so I played the trombone.
And we had dead Kennedy's. Yeah. I'm actually the guy who runs the account now. That's wrong. Oh nice
It's not an interesting story
I did let I was like a weekend like there was like we would do like weekend
practice session or something like we'd have to do like some kind of band thing on like Saturday mornings and
My parents forgot to pick me up after so I was just at school for a while
My I was in elementary school. So it's not old enough to like walk home
Yeah, my mom left me one time when she went on like an hour drive out of town and apparently I like it like
Ruined my relationship with her for a couple months and I like talked about it all the time when I was a kid
It's not I brought it's the only time I remembered and then I brought that up to my dad kind of recently
I was like, oh, yeah mom left me at the house once I was a kid
He's like she left you the house once you don't remember I used to do that shit all the time
I used to forget you for like eight hours straight and he reminded me that he like left me in a Walmart twice
He lost me at Busch Gardens once and I was like, yeah, I guess just you just had like a dad pass
Like I just didn't expect any better and my brain just kind of didn't think about it again, of course, you know
Number two things that all moms do is tell little white lies. Yeah
Yeah
Yeah, like he's just a friend positron wild talk has a comment here. Oh my man
He's back quite easy for me to smell a rat when as a kid
I had minor roles in school plays having only one line in the whole two hours of the production
Alongside bigger kids with more actions and words to memorize and time perfectly and according to mom and dad I made the best performance
Good for him dude. Sounds like a lie though. Yeah. Yeah
Let's see anything else good on here. Yeah, so they tell lies about white people what?
That's what sir Skeletor the third says damn that's some funny shit, where's my pillow?
Grandma sat on the Sun and her cheeks suffer from claustrophobia and your pillow is the only cure
when my grandma steals my pillow to unburn her cheeks.
- Yeah.
- And then my mom lies to protect her.
- Dude, I would never let my grandma's ass
touch my pillow, dude.
- Blue Topaz Ice Vanilla comments,
like saying we'll get candy if we fold the clothes.
The amount of times I've been tricked by that,
too many to count.
(laughing)
- Just stop and say, you know,
if you keep getting tricked by it,
you're not really getting tricked.
- How many times can you get tricked by that?
Totally I swear this time you're gonna get candy. Yeah, just pull in the football every time. Yeah good for them
Number three throw away drawings and homemade gifts not really a white lie. Yeah. Yeah, that's that's a different thing
I'm just a bad thing. Oh, that's a thing mom. Mom's - sorry
I thought that it was a white lie list all of a sudden
You thought it was a white lie list and number two was tell white lies
Yeah, you know, yeah I did
Yeah, moms do do that shit. Mm-hmm. Yeah
Turkey asylum asks doesn't every mom do this?
That's what the list is turkey. So I'm your fucking dumbass
Yeah, my mom doesn't I don't have any like thing from when I was a kid
I think it's all a goodwill probably still and she donated ten years ago. Yes. Oh your drawings
Yeah, good. Well the by some drawings. Yeah, she would frame them and then donate them
and so that people would think they were art.
They should have a section in Goodwill that's just like a stack of papers.
It's just like if you, instead of recycling papers, like if,
'cause I like papers, you know, I like to look at them and see what's on them.
Yeah.
I could, like, they could be like forms that people don't need anymore,
or like a drawing that they made, or like homework assignments.
Yeah, I mean, why are you allowed to, why can you donate like photos,
but you can't do paper?
Yeah, just pieces of, like, receipts.
Like, every, every thrift store has like a giant box of like old photos.
Yeah.
you just put like you know like my 1099 stores are you going to every fucking
every big thrift store who has like has fucking like five shelves full of like
blu-ray players that are $2 that they won't let you plug in to test it's like
don't you think you'd be don't you think people people would be more likely to
buy a bunch of drawings yeah throw a couple court summons on there yeah no
they're like a they're like a parking ticket what about like an empty envelope
sorry around it sorry all my parking tickets got donated to Goodwill
I couldn't pay any of that anywhere.
You know what I'll do?
I'll go there and I'll buy them for three bucks.
- Yeah, you buy a parking ticket from Goodwill
and then you get to pay it to save someone else.
It's kind of like a pay it forward kind of thing.
- That sucks.
- Or you can buy it and put it on your car
so they don't give you a ticket.
- I buy it, I put it on the card.
- No, they don't stop giving you tickets, dude.
- I've never had a bad parking ticket.
- Thinking that they stopped giving me parking tickets
when I put one ticket on,
You're like, no, this is all the same ticket.
(laughs)
I don't stack, dude.
- I knew somebody in Boston who like,
every time they parked their car,
they would just put, they had a bunch of parking tickets.
They would just put one of the envelopes on the car,
thinking that that would fool the parking people.
- Yeah.
- No, in Boston, they put new tickets
into the fucking envelope.
- Yeah, that's one of the life hacks
that people think will work, but it's a...
- Does it?
No, it doesn't work.
- Yeah, it's so funny to think that that's the way you,
I would smart the system like as if like,
it's like everybody hasn't thought of that. Like a thousand,
you know what I mean? Like,
like as if the meter maid will walk by and be like, Oh,
I guess I did give a ticket to this car.
Like even though I just started my shift.
That's what I do. Any, anytime I'm about,
I think I'm about to get mugged by New York's finest use.
I go ahead and put like a use a special effects makeup to put a stab wound on my
stomach. No, I already, there you go. You already got it.
You guys already, you guys must've forgotten. Yeah. There was a,
there's a different crew
and they got me
it works every time it's a life hack
uh...
use t_v_ and other screens as a babysitter
there's nothing wrong with that
not did what do you think they invented that shit
exactly
now and now you know we tell you and i saw the zoom school and stuff
young whatever happened to whom school we schooled in
uh...
Yeah, now kids nowadays kids are in zoom school. Yeah, that's what I'm saying, dude
Uh number six is slack on baby books and scrapbooks
Whatever happened to soon school. It's 7 15. The bus is here
Yeah, i'm so good at those
Yeah, it is interesting not everyone's doing zoom school there's no more boom school
Well, that is true. We got out of boom school.
Yeah.
Goon school.
Yeah, exactly. Yeah.
That's a really good point.
I'm trying to go to school.
The way that the way that it's going nowadays,
kids are sitting in their room school on Zoom school.
Oh, my God.
Instead of the school room on school for Foon.
Yeah.
They're sitting on their Foon on Zoom
and instead of being Hoom on school.
Yeah.
And then when you have to, you know,
you got to go to Vroon school to get your license.
Nowadays kids are on Zoom, whatever happened when they were going to
screw.
That's so true, dude.
Yeah.
You should go to, I think it was called scoom where you had all of your
different books and you had lunch in the middle and there was different
classes and there was a teacher, uh, and it was called scoom.
Right.
I heard that.
Yeah.
Heard that.
Uh, seven.
This is one of Patrick's big complaints.
Yeah.
Um, skimp on bath time.
The two comments here are, "It's a process, and sometimes we just don't have the time or
energy.
The bubbles, the toys, the mess.
A spit shine or a once over with a baby wipe will do in a pinch."
You're gonna spit on your kid?
I spit on kids.
What the fuck?
What?
Everything, what?
Why are you...
I don't spit on kids.
Do you shine them?
You already said it.
You can't take stuff back.
You see a bald kid, you spit on his head, you shine it off, it's got a good polish.
on it. You don't need to polish any kid, dude. You'd make that kid's bald head shine. Why
does he need to shine? Listen, hey. Sun. My kid doesn't need any spit to shine. Sunlight.
Sunlight? That's why he needs to shine? Sometimes you need your kid to be reflective. So you
have to polish his head like a bowling ball. Mm-hmm. Look, if you're in a dungeon and there's
- Three holes in a kid's head like a bowling ball.
It would be so easy to put them in their room.
- Yeah, that's what you can do
with a newborn infant soft spot,
is you can burrow your fingers in.
- That's where they have it.
- Yeah.
- And then they have a cool like La Vida Loco thing
on their back of their head.
It's pretty neat.
Number eight, lose their cool.
- I hate that.
- I hate when my mom loses her cool.
My mom's so cool usually.
She's always sitting on the couch,
sunglasses and a saxophone.
I misread it says we have all growled at our kids, but I misread it as we have all growled
around our kids.
Everybody's growled around their kids.
Yeah, everybody everybody thought their kid was it was it.
I caught my mom playing kickball and started growling in the living room.
Yeah, just staring in the mirror, growling at your reflection.
I'm just looking into the closet with your hair standing on end and just going,
"Oh, hey, son. Hey, I didn't see you there."
Yeah, I thought you were in the closet.
Don't tell dad.
Number nine, ration diapers.
There's one comment that just says Asian parents in a nutshell.
What?
Do Asian parents just make you poop your pants over and over again?
I don't know.
I'm not changing that thing until it's hit.
I don't, I mean, I don't have any parents yet.
Yeah, you need a lowrider for me.
Yeah, that's right.
Otherwise, that's a waste of time.
I want to see sparks.
You know how it goes to do a butt sniff and a quick squeeze
of the diaper to see if it warrants changing.
If it is only half full, we'll let it ride for a while.
Two hours later.
We realize the kid is soaked.
Yeah, great job mom.
Let it ride.
Just let it ride for a while. Just let that thing play.
Don't think we need to hold it yet.
Run that shit back.
Run that shit back, dude.
Number 10 is skip pages in a book.
I do this shit when I read to myself.
Number 11, co-sleep with baby.
Co-what?
Co-sleep?
One comment, at least the baby is protected in the arms of a nursing mother.
That's not like a...
Why is that like a thing that...
Sleep with baby?
It's very questionable to co-sleep with baby.
Yeah, that's true.
All moms do it.
Be overprotective, throw away their kids' stuff.
Roast their children.
It's number 16.
What's up, goofy?
Hey, back from school, huh, goofy ass?
You fail math class again today?
Man, you stupid.
Let me, come here.
Your head's looking dusty.
I'm going to polish that shit.
Look at that hair loss.
that hair line. Goofy ass hair line. Hitting your kid like a spittoon from ten yards away
and it just goes ping really loud off the back of their head. If that shit don't ding, you're
going to the doctor. Dude that's what the. We're going to shave that skull down. That's
why when the baby has a soft spot you push it in so it makes a little hole you can spit
into. True, yeah it's like a dip cup. Yeah. We should be molding them to have like hammers
for heads or something.
- Yeah. - Yeah.
- Like I feel like they're like,
make your kid wear some sort of like,
like cookie cutter mold. - It's like.
- So that like later in life,
he has like a calculator on his head or something.
- Yeah, they used to do that.
And like, they would be like, they would like--
- They used to put calculators in kids' heads?
- They used to put calculators in kids' heads.
No, like in like the Mayans or whatever would do,
they would like shape their kids' heads
to be like, look long like aliens.
That's why they think they find alien skulls.
Like they would do all this--
- Oh, that's that?
- Yeah, we don't do that anymore.
It's fucked up.
I mean, it can't be a downside to having a bigger head, right?
It looks cool as hell.
Exactly.
Can you imagine walking around and having like the head shape of a xenomorph?
Especially if your kid later in life gets into body modification, that's like a huge
head start.
Even better if your kid doesn't, he's just an accountant.
Exactly, yeah.
And then he would be the most trusted accountant.
He's got Charizard horns on the back of his head, dude.
He works at Shake Shack.
My lawyer must be really smart.
He has a giant cylindrical skull that holds a very powerful math brain.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I think probably your brain does get, it grows constantly, right?
Yeah.
It's either that or fingernails.
So I can't remember which one.
It's probably the brain.
I think it's brain.
Yeah.
It keeps growing after you die.
Because fingernails don't really grow.
You keep learning after you die.
Yeah.
You learn about like the underworld or whatever.
Exactly.
I'm putting a racing stripe on the side of his head, dude.
That'd be kind of fucking cool.
A little indenture.
I'll put a racing stripe on the side of his head.
I'll put a racing stripe on the side of his head, dude.
That'd be kind of fucking cool, a little indentioned racing stripe, and then turn it into a spoiler
at the back.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
That'd be awesome.
You could be confused for a transformer.
Putting like a nitro booster on the back of my kid's head.
Oh my god.
But because of like, inertia, his feet don't move, so it just slams his head straight into
the ground.
I want to make my kid look like Minecraft Steve, put his head in one of those Japanese watermelon
molds.
Yeah, yeah.
And then just have them walk around like, "Yeah, yeah, my dad loved Japanese watermelons."
It's true.
Why do they make them square?
Is it just easier to cut?
It just looks cool.
Yeah.
Yeah, a kid, a guy with a cubicle head walking around just being like, "You would not believe
what shape my mother's thingy was."
Talking about box.
(laughing)
- That bitch had a box on her.
That's right.
- Yeah.
- My dad's a Lego man.
- That thing had four quarters.
(laughing)
- Yeah it did.
- That's right.
- And four G spots.
- Oh, come on man.
- I would love like one of those Iranian barber videos
where they like wrap around,
they like take the towel off the guy's head
and wrap around and show the cut
and he just has a completely sharp edge.
(laughing)
Right, they're like sharpening a knife on that anvil.
- Yeah, they're sharpening the sword.
(laughing)
- Oh, or you could give your kid an anvil head.
- Oh, that'd be cool.
- I mean, that's a lifelong hobby.
- Or like a knife head, like a sword shaped knife head.
- Straight up, my kid's got a blade for it.
- No, not a cone, like a blade.
- Like a really thin, wow.
- That'd be awesome.
- That might be sick, dude.
- Yeah.
- He has like a Wolverine style.
It like keeps breaking his skin, but he like gets used to it.
- Sure.
- That'd be really cool. - God, that'd be,
that'd be amazing.
- I might have a kid now, like right now.
- It might be time for me to have a kid.
I might have a baby.
- I'm gonna walk into the orphanage.
So yeah, I know all these kids are all sad or whatever.
Which one do you think has the softest,
most moldable skull right now?
- Who is the most malleable kid in here?
- And the most, what's the,
and who's the most expensive also?
- Yeah, I'm not skimping out. - I'm not taking that one.
- I'm not skimping on a-- - I'm not fucking skimping
on a kid.
- I will not be buying the cheapest kid here.
Give me like the most expensive of the skimpy kids.
Give me the most expensive and the least expensive,
and I'm gonna make them both have sword heads
and they're gonna battle at the end of the month.
- Do you guys have like a PayPal pay-in-for kind of thing
where I can use four payments to pay off my kid?
- Do you guys take Best Buy gift cards?
(laughing)
- Yeah.
I just need a payment plan for my adoption.
Please.
Number 22, forget their kids in the backseat of the car.
Well, that kills a lot of children, actually.
Yeah, it's true. I feel like you hear two of those stories a year where it's like this guy was
He went to work and forgot that he had his kid in his car and they came out the kid was dead
It's like that kid's a pussy dude. Yeah, I could have survived. I just in a car all day
Mm-hmm a hot car could not kill me. No, what is up with this kid? Why is he so easily easily killed?
Yeah, you know, it's you know, probably saw like
I'm scared or something. It's disgusting. It's disgusting that kids die in cars and they should they should get
Should grow up, you know, you should do here's a way that car manufacturers Chevy if you're listening
You know throw me a hundo. They could put a second wheel and gas pedal in the backseat
So the kid can drive the kid. Can you do it? Yeah, they can escape or at least turn the fucking AC on, you know
It's not a bad idea.
Little toddler.
Not at all.
But then, yeah, the guy walks out of...
Or like an ejector seat that launches the kid, like, into the air to get out of the car.
Oh, that's a really good point, actually, yeah.
Or like, um...
Or maybe just like a TV they could watch, 'cause they don't afford them usually.
Yeah, like a game. You could just give them a Game Boy.
Yeah, that might be actually a cheaper, better alternative.
But I also think maybe the...
I mean...
If they can find their way home, that's an even better story.
You know, the dead kid, that's a pretty good news story.
story but kid drives his way home. Kid dead from heat stroke lands in front yard of a
parents house on a parachute. Yeah he was already dead his head fell over and hit the button.
Yeah but at least he was home. Yeah landed, flew into the skylight and landed in his moms
cooking pot right in front of her.
Alright, is that the end of the list?
Yeah.
Subscribe to the Patreon.
Please.
Subscribe.
Pat has to make up the money he lost from the lights.
That's true.
I have a message for all the fans.
If it's a Saturday and you don't see that a teaser is posted for the premium episode,
You should just DM Caleb about it.
- Yep.
- So I can stop like reminding Caleb.
Maybe he'll set like a reminder on his phone,
like for the first time or something.
- I probably won't.
- But just like if, yeah, he probably won't.
So if you know, it gets to be Sunday,
there's no teaser from Saturday.
Just a bunch of you just message Caleb.
- I'm gonna switch to a flip phone that has no alarms.
And also I'm gonna get rid of my calendars,
my clocks and my computer.
- You already got rid of your clock.
- But yeah, but like Caleb might respond to you.
- And once we get, hey, if we get--
- You might like start a friendship or like,
dude, you might be able to like--
- Oh yeah, he's gonna--
your
the
nine
yet now we're getting also
you get to see cameron in the dress and you get to see a bird in caleb's house
that's two birds one night we're not putting a bird in my you're changing
where you're getting a good idea what we're gonna get a bird in my house
I don't want a pet bird dude.
It doesn't matter if you want it.
I'm gonna buy the bird.
You do want to wear a dress also.
I'm gonna buy a bird for Caleb.
You're gonna get a sexy maid outfit and you're gonna look good.
You're gonna buy it for me. If you ship it to my house.
Really?
I'm gonna buy like a $500 maid outfit.
And I'm gonna send it to your house.
And then you have to wear it.
And I'm gonna buy a $500 bird.
I'm gonna get the smallest one they have.
And I'm gonna send it to Cam.
send it to cam really really soon okay yeah all right all right bye you guys
bye
Morning, night, whatever.