[Music]
Somewhere between Bed-Stuy and Honolulu, the perfect little town of Boston, California,
sleeps peacefully among the Brady Woods, a small forest nearby where Bostonians will
hike and throw rocks at animals.
Nothing crazy really ever happens in the Brady Woods, though.
Sure a bear might stick his hand in a beehive to get some honey, then his hand will get stuck,
and then some bees will take the shape of a giant boot and kick the bear in the rump.
Then the boot will chase the bear around and around in a circle, hopping of course, while
the bear desperately tries to shake the beehive off his hand.
Like that'll happen.
But other than that, and the occasional dead girl Jared Letoberry is here, nothing strange
ever happens in Brady Woods.
But as the day begins to break after a night of long rain, on this March 16th, the day
before St. Paddy's Day. A rainbow crests across the sky in the wee hours of the morning. And
along that rainbow, if you listen closely enough, you can hear the gleeful giggles of some fantastic
little creatures, proudly bearing their four-leaf clovers in their buckled shoes, but obscured by
the morning mist, which is actually smoke, because the Pats won, so everyone decided to blow up the
Italian Community Center for shits and gigs. These little green monsters frolic about the woods,
hardy and tardy in a way, turning squirrels inside out and tricking fishermen into catching
their own trousers.
One in particular, however, got a bit lost in all the excitement.
For you see, he saw what he thought was a giant potato, the most sacred of all starches.
As the little guy scurried over, pulling down his green top hat on his ginger curls, he
geared up to take a chomp out of this big brown thing.
"What the fuck!" said the potato, for it was no potato at all, but just a man wearing
brown.
Before our friend could issue an apology, the man was chasing him across the woods, dashing
frantically among the trees.
This little creature showed great agility, using his grubby little hands and feet to pivot
and tumble among the branches, trunks, and roots that populated the brady woods.
Eventually, he found himself no longer in the forest at all, but on the outskirts of
town, in what looked like a backyard of sorts.
Mangy and unkempt, the face scamp seemed to have lost the angry potato man.
What joy!
The little fella began to twirl a gold coin between his fingers, produce little trinkets
and charms and magical effects from beneath his path in an impromptu jaunty celebration.
Meanwhile, on his way to Duncan to get 10 kreles to stand in front of a paki until it opens,
another potato looking fella shuffled across the outskirts of town.
When he spotted our stout pal prancing about, shocked, thinking he might be still drunk from
the bottle of Jack he had about 20 minutes ago, this Bostonian rubbed his eyes but no
clear as day, or as clear as day could ever be, but with it being all blurry all the time,
He was seeing what he was seeing. He was seeing something weird.
I don't think I need to tell you what happens next, but in case you didn't know,
they got a saying in Boston, California. If something seems weird, you should probably
throw a beer can at it. And with a crude wind-up and thunk, our leprechaun was knocked out cold
in the backyard. The tiny guy's friends were starting up the rainbow again and heading out.
That's right, you can start up rainbows. They had a big day tomorrow, and they needed to make
sure they were ready. Thinking they had everyone accounted for, they rode the rainbow back into
the
This is where I start my and Keith benefits mom is is you know huffing and puffing around and yelling all the kids and
Yeah, who are you kids you hanging outside hanging out inside playing the sex life and videotape board game. You guys are friends
Who are you? I'm Keith benefits. I'm the class prankster
I'm known all around town for my pranks the other day
I did an awesome prank where I took all the money from the Jerry's kids bucket at the arcade
I don't know who those kids are, but they got hit with the prank of the century
If anyone gets mad at me for my pranks, they should calm down because it's just a prank. Hell, I love doing pranks
So much, but I hate getting in trouble for my pranks.
I got in trouble for feeding the class bird a bunch of Alka-Seltzer
So I and the teacher got mad at me, so I pranked her by replacing her daily candy with a bunch of chiclets
It's the 80s! That kind of stuff is just fun pranks right now
You know pranking small animals lighting fires wetting the bed all that stuff is pranks
Last week I did a prank on use of DVD where I said his mailbox on fire and he was pissed I burnt his decoder ring
That's a good prank. I
Hope none of these pranks that I do now as a child affect the way I act or the decisions I make as an adult
Anyway, I'm seven years old. I'm the youngest of the group and I guess I'm the leader. I don't know. I
Don't know why these guys hang out with me. I think I might be half brothers with one of them
I'm not entirely sure. I don't know
I started following them around or they started following me around
Around the time that I moved into the neighborhood with my aunt after I pranked my mom and dad
Okay, so keep benefits aunt is the one who's in the house
Okay minor correction for me
Keith benefit
Has a has a few sort of a tried-and-true
Abilities he has his up close and personal attacks with his dropkick Murphy and rocks
He throws rocks as his long-range attack. He's got wicked smarts, which allows him to use
Some fancy sort of confusing types of wording to get away with pranks using and get advantage on charisma checks and he has luck of the benefits which will get into but it is powered by beer.
What do you want to change that.
this originally luck of something else
and now yeah so we're moving around the table
you're playing as the
the playing as the what's his name
fuck it up what's that there is a slice of videotape
Robert California James Spader yeah you think is the James Spader character in
the game
a buddy Bowser but you also started chewing on it you are you buddy Bowser
Hello everybody, my name is Buddy Bowser. I am in 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8th grade, and I am 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13 years old.
My doctor told me that my IQ is so low that my brain is physically unable to dream.
He said even dogs can dream and they don't even have IQs.
My favorite hobby is eating paste from the jar of paste that I wear on my belt.
One time when I was eating a spoonful of paste, I tripped on a dry leaf on the sidewalk and
the whole jar went into my hair.
After I refilled the jar, my mom had to shave off part of my bowl cut and hair doesn't grow
on that spot anymore.
at school says I look like Friar Tuck now, but I think I look more like that fat monk
from Robin Hood. My mom doesn't let me watch Robin Hood anymore because I get too scared
of Maid Marian and I pee myself. Anyway, my favorite hobby is playing tetherball and eating
paste from my jar of paste and going to the doctor and playing tetherball.
Buddy Bowser is Mommy's special guy.
He has a couple of abilities.
He has Big Hug, which I think is my favorite, mechanically, that I've made in a while.
We'll probably just see that play out.
I don't even want to get into it.
And then Choke on Glue, which is just his ranged attack.
Also he can smell a pretty teacher lady.
There's no real benefit to that.
It's just an ability he has.
We rotate over and we see another kid who,
he's dressed in a little tux.
He seems to constantly be checking his watch
and putting his finger to his ear
and he's doing all kinds of spy stuff.
Who is this guy?
- The name's DVD, Yusuf DVD.
And as you may have gleaned from my pinstripe suit,
my rosewood cane and my Mickey Mouse ears yarmulke,
I am no ordinary eighth grader.
I yearn for the old days when your lawyer smoked and your cousins died.
Oh, how I dream of dialing back the calendar to years of yonder, when your best chance
of seeing a panda was not at the state zoo, but at a traveling freak show in a colorful
tent labeled "Dog of the East" or "The Bisexual Man."
Born and raised right here in Boston, California, I was trained in the accent of my motherland
by a 7 year old named Josh Gad. He had a secret from Josh and I, wherein he would show me Monty
Python Laserdiscs in exchange for loose slices of ham and the odd piece of avuncular advice.
"Hey Josh, Air Duster isn't deodorant. Stop buying wedding cakes. No one cares about your
salt lick." Through his tutelage I mastered this lilt, and I remain close friends with
him to this day. But enough about me. Everything I know I was taught by my father. He's the
coolest guy in the whole world and there's a reason you haven't heard of him.
He's an elder spy on her majesty's secret service, a member of the elusive Queen's Dozen.
To this day I must spend my time parrying infiltration attempts by French PSYOP agencies impersonating
my mother on Atari Facebook, knowing full well that when I was 2 years old, my dad made her
so horny she had to kill herself.
In the past 30 years he's been hiding in plain sight, disguised as a waiter at a British intelligence
themed restaurant working for tips from casual dining literati.
That's right.
The Royal family have been sending coded messages to his customers instructing him to do everything
from cleanse the city's tap water supply to doing open mics under the name Paul Provenza.
With God's blessing I will follow in his footsteps and enter the world of espionage myself.
Youssef DVD forever.
Amazing.
I don't know.
YusefDVD picked up a lot of those spy moves from his dad.
He's able to do some kung fu, spy kung fu.
He's got a waiter's corkscrew he carries around.
He's a couple of tools.
He has a laser pen and some quote unquote knockout gas, which is really just sort of harmless
gas that he has.
And then he has, and the laser pen doesn't like burn things, it just distracts people.
He has a packet of mysterious powder from his dad in a clear plastic bag.
He also has a gun.
And now, to move over, and next we see someone else.
We see sort of like a real tough guy, a real fucking bully type.
Who are you, Vince Foster?
Oh, what's up, assballs?
Nice to feet you.
I'm the tough kid of the school, Vince Foster.
My mom got fingered by Edward Cigarette Hands in 1975 and 3 months later I popped out.
Now I fuck frogs and beat up dorks who don't know their place.
Some think I have a secret sensitive side, and they're correct.
It's the bottom of my smelly white ass, and it's sensitive because I hold the Guinness
World Record for longest time spent mooning an active volcano.
Now I'm gonna go practice swirlies on Buddy Bowser and watch the news because I am terrified
of AIDS, which I think comes from the library.
[laughter]
So, uh, Vince Foster...
...his fuckin' name, god damn.
What's up?
[laughter]
Has brass knuckles 'cause he's a bully.
I guess they get them.
That's what I decided.
He has the ability to improvise with sort of any objects nearby,
to make them into arranged objects.
He can do a little whining,
uh... to to get enemies to not hurt him and he could sneak attack them will
no bully whining
uh...
he's got a deacon deflect a lot of projectiles to with his cool leather
jacket
uh...
and uh... you can't kill himself
and so
uh...
yet you guys are all hanging out
you guys are are playing the sex lies in videotape board game
uh... your auntie keith benefits
Uh yells, uh, it starts starts coming by and she brought you guys pizza and she's saying uh, keith
Keith, I need you to go outside take out the trash. Ah, fuck what?
No, fuck you. No, fuck you. Auntie. This sucks. No, you know, what sucks is feeding you ungrateful fucking friends go outside
No, fuck you. They they get to eat whatever they want here. Yeah, I know that's the whole fucking point
That's what I mean by ungrateful. I ain't here one fucking. Thank you. That one started fucking drooling
Thank you to you this guy keeps trying to fucking pinch my ass. What are you 12 you fucking leather jacket weirdo? Yes
He's all right. You're right. It makes that
Look and when you know what I say take out the trash. I mean try to see if you can wake up your uncle
He's still he's still asleep the odd
from last week
So if you could just try to see if that you could take care of that for me, that'd be nice
I thought fuck this sucks and take it take a sister with you and I don't have a see what do you mean my sister?
Okay, I'm remembering my sister now, yeah, you have my sister you have a little sister named Sullivan the frog
That's her Sullivan the frog my
Do you see a frog?
Looks a lot like another frog guy
Okay
Just was saying that I'm this board game gets me so angry I love to play with dolls and
Yeah
I don't know when I became your little sister, but somewhere along in the writing process
The DM must have just couldn't stop laughing at this idea and now he's not so sure about it
Yep
All right. Well, you have to wake up our uncle. I'm scared and take out the trash
No, we're gonna go outside and smoke this cigarette I found
the
Just yeah, great. I'm your mother - amazing
If they see my half-brother, I don't remember
No, I just call every Sullivan is he I have brother
What's a half brother I'm
So a half is like like what half of two is one oh
Oh, I mean, I'm confused by that. I don't know how much in what direction I got really didn't think it through
the
if you have two kids. I'm upstairs and I'm jumping on his uncle's bed.
Yeah, you're jumping on his uncle's bed as you do.
Each time you land on it, like a smell comes out
that you didn't know was a kind of smell you can smell.
Keith, your aunt is very tantalizing. Does she shower?
I don't fucking know. Why would I know that?
I give a big cartoonish smell right next to her and I go,
No!
I don't have time to shower, okay? I work 10 jobs, alright?
And I raise five other kids you don't know about.
Okay, so it's not easy being a mother. Let me tell you.
You're not a mom, you're an aunt.
What?
Well, I'm an aunt of children that I'm the mother of.
Okay, it's a complicated, familial thing that us Irish do.
You can't be a mom and an aunt.
Yes, you can. What are you talking about?
Wait, hold on.
You can't be both a mom and an aunt!
She's trying to think about it.
[laughter]
Wait, yes you can! Yes you can! I thought about it. You can. You can.
You're- you're getting fucking smart, you know that?
You better start watching that mouth.
I'm seven!
Yeah, that doesn't mean you're not getting fucking smart.
I'm gonna hit you with the other side of my hand. The bad side.
Oh, god. Alright. I guess we gotta go wake up the uncle now.
[laughter]
When you guys come upstairs, I have the uncle's pillowcase over my head and I'm saying,
a
20 years later.
[Laughter]
So you guys, uh, uh,
wander outside the backyard, prodding,
poking and prodding, uh, uh, your
little sister, Sullivan, and, uh,
she's supposed to go, like,
look for, uh, um,
your uncle. Uh, let me get her.
Oh, he's not on a bed. My bad.
Oh, no, you were just on
his bed where he's supposed to sleep.
I thought he was sleeping up there.
No, he's out in the backyard, um,
where he likes to hang out or you think he likes to hang out and uh, uh,
Sullivan's going to like, you see the backyard, it's just disgusting and dirty.
There's a pile of hay for some reason and a fish there's fucking beer and wine
bottles everywhere. It is like way too big a property for what your aunt should
have. Uh, but she, there's a Pontiac GTO.
Yeah. Yeah. It's a Pontiac GTO that's in perfect condition.
and then there's one that's been did is not functional
is both of them are in the backyard
and uh...
solvent sort of wanders over to uh... her her uncle
and she pokes him again and and she's like
yet he's still breathing but he's just been out for a week i don't really
i don't know what he did
well how do we get 'em up
uh... buddy has to do mouth to mouth
yet but you gotta go do not like money
okay i think that will bring him back to life and i put on a bunch of paste on my
lips like lipstick
yeah
and i will all over him
you guys are separate to get to his notes
okay buddy while you're doing that role a perception check
okay
the correct one
the okay
you uh...
you are unable to notice anything for the rest of your time in the backyard
there's nothing that you'll be able to perceive it'll all just be blackness
as far as you're concerned you essentially just have like an extended
version of like i have a follow-up to the army i just yeah i'm close face
yeah yeah i can see
the athlete buddy inhaled some of the uncle's breath
passed out
yeah uh... but but
Yousef, I would say with your like spy sort of like abilities, you're able to pick up on a sound coming from the shed.
Oh my god, what's that?
Okay, you could wander over there, you can move stealthily, you can move less stealthily, it's up to you.
I crouch walk to the shed.
Okay, yeah. So you start crouch walking to the shed and it's pretty tough, there's a lot of like, if you're trying to like move stealthily,
you have to like try to not step on like a beer can or a beer bottle and break it or
some broken pottery or a magazine. So roll a stealth check. 24. Very good. Yeah, you
from your years of of of pretending to be your dad, you're able to pretty handily like
get to the shed, get pretty close to it. As you do, you hear like a bit of rumbling in
the
it's shed there's like six back here
the one painted green
all okay
i know that shed the bright green shed that usually holds all of your saint
patrick's day paraphernalia
there's one for each holiday
this is the saint patrick's day one
the nicest shed
I have to say you guys want to do with the shed.
I don't what are we doing?
I think follow me.
We're going in.
Okay, so you guys are following you were yelling across the
the if the backyard and as you were yelling you started to
hear the movement stop and as you get a bit closer to the
shed you see two little feet dangling in a big a big chest
where there is like all this fake gold
and also all these all this beer
and he sees two feet dangling in your book will go to go to compare to take
advantage of the
willful group of people are to take advantage of
something else my uncle's waking up
and when you hear you hear
whatever that thing is
here to yell he pops his head up
and this
rosacea
fucking absolutely destroyed, drunken-looking, little, tiny, leprechaun man
pops his head up and he sees you, Keith Benefits, and he goes
"HARDY TARDY HARDY HARDY TARDY HARDY TARDY!"
"Oh my god, they shrank and cloned my uncle!"
and he starts freaking out and he's running around, he hits into the wall,
he passes out, and then he poof, he disappears.
Whoa! Did you guys see that? No. Buddy, did you see that? Your uncle's nose is like chewing
gum. Now also, Yusef, roll a perception check. Yusef and Keith, I should say. And also actually
Vince Foster, all of you can do it except buddy.
- I got a 20.
- Buddy can't do shit.
- I got a 10.
- Okay, Keith Benefits and Yusef.
Keith, you know your backyard, you know it well.
You know when there's something out of the ordinary,
when there's something weird.
It's a classic sort of tell in Boston, California.
And Yusef, again, your spy abilities come in favor for you.
Vince, you're too busy trying to figure out how you can suffocate Buddy Bowser on Keith's uncle's nose.
[Vince laughs]
And you guys see a... looks like a man in like a suit, but not like a spy suit, like a FBI-looking suit,
skulking outside of the fence, peering in.
Oh my god.
Not him again.
[Vince laughs]
not the guy that watches me sleep
and uh...
the a_t_c_'s there were you talking
uh...
this is an instruction for me
it's a little bit of a small
yeah how much you go over there talk to him
i think he may be running for a little towards the mania
so
there's a
uh... and uh...
he uh... he takes out uh...
uh... going to freeze phrase
This FBI, and he looks like he's maybe in the FBI, but he also looks like he has like scales underneath his skin.
It's hard to tell if he's a person or some sort of snake man.
I take it as a challenge.
I walk up, hold the bow of the gun and put it in the center of my forehead.
Shoot me.
(laughter)
Uh, he's like...
I'm rolling intimidation check with advantage, uh, Yousef.
Okay. Oh no.
You are still a child.
So, he's just like,
"What? What are you doing?"
And, and, and, and, and sort of like,
that
the
to
to go first. So this guy, this FBI guy looking guy who also looks a little bit snake like
sort of just busted through the shed and saw Keith Benefits and he is sort of going towards
him right now. It looks like he's trying to maybe do like a sleeper hold. He doesn't want
him to, you can't tell if it's like he's trying to kill him or hurt him just to like, you
But um, you're pretty sure that there's something going on.
So yeah, you're up Yusuf, though. That's sort of what's happening now.
I, uh, luckily, I brought the gun my dad keeps in his drawer.
[laughter]
To shoot at cars. Which I pull it out. Freeze!
Okay, uh, and you have a pretty clear shot at him.
And so, um, I'm gonna say that you can
you can roll again of intimidation with advantage before you even, but this would be your action
is to just point the gun and say freeze.
Oh my god.
Six and three.
Yeah no, you're not very intimidating to him.
He's so, an actual gun.
This guy got nerves of steel.
Yeah this guy's like, that's not.
This kid has a cane, he's not shooting a gun at me.
This kid's, what are you some sort of steampunk dandy?
Get out of my sight.
the 80s all toy guns look real true where did that's where did that stinky stinky
little man go who was in here and about yourself my uncle's right over there
oh both of you will make you mad for different reasons and and yeah it is
though based on dexterity it is your turn Vince Foster okay I will I will use my
brass knuckles. Hell yeah, so you can run up to this guy. 21. Yeah, that's a hit. You could just...
Yes! Yeah. And I got 12. Fuck. Okay, yeah. I'm so good, dude. Yeah, so you just run up to this guy.
How do you beat down on him? One single, like, old-timey 80s movie punch.
Just completely unrealistic. I'm like three inches away from his face and it's... Yeah.
and uh...
pretty teacher lady. I thought that was an accident.
okay
Buddy you smelled a pretty teacher lady. I didn't mean to click that.
Buddy used his turn to smell a pretty teacher lady.
You look like my teacher, she's beautiful.
But yeah, you sock him in the jaw and he's like "Ah! That was like three feet away! How'd that happen?"
He's like freaking out
about that but he got hit pretty hard
there.
uh...
i keep benefits or is it money notes but it's your turn
you for first you smell
so then
before your old frog
little girl i was a little bit of the other guy yet the i got a good it's
distance gap
if you're like forty feet away from him by the local and i can smell you from
here and you smell fragrant
the
black
you smell fragrant
You smell like- he's saying you smell like a vagrant.
What? No, I- I- I shower plenty.
You have- you have scales like my mom's leg.
My scales.
And he starts to rub down on the scales and they sort of smooth out.
Um, and it becomes more like skin-like.
That's what my mom does too.
With her ointment.
So what do you wanna do, buddy Bowser?
Uh, I can only move 20 feet 'cause I'm-
you can't use the ocean and i have a couple of the peace
on the bottom i see it's really hard for me to walk
so i don't like halfway to the shed
we could also be good news for movement though too
that's true okay
you don't do anything else except get their yeah
i quote unquote dash which is the a_s_ looks exactly the same i just walk a
little more before i stop
uh...
and meanwhile is cowering behind her passed out uncle.
Like, "Ahh! Oh God! What is happening? I'm sore!"
And, uh, it's your turn Vince Foster.
Oh, not Vince Foster, sorry.
Keith Benefits, now it's your turn.
Is there anything...
Okay, can I do like a perception check
to see if there's anything in the shed
that I can do a prank with?
Yeah, so, yeah.
There's... Don't even have to do a perception check.
So, it's a St. Paddy's Day shed.
So, there's...
Jameson?
There's Jameson there. Oh, yeah, there's alcohol in there
Yeah, there's like
Yes, oh, yeah, there's like there's like a little like a leprechaun outfit that you could you could use as a cloth
Okay, there is Jameson in there
Most of the alcohol in here has been completely drunken though by you assume that little creature that was in here earlier
But there is a bit there's a bit of Jameson left in like one of the bottle
I soak a leprechaun outfit in Jameson and I pull out my Zippo and light it.
Toss it at this FBI agent.
Okay, a couple of things. One, it's going to be an athletics check.
Okay.
Vince Foster, you're going to have to do a dexterity saving throw. You're right there.
Okay. Awesome. I got a four.
Okay.
You you
Do a dexterity based attack so that'd be like your throw rocks your rocks attack just do that
Just the rocks. Yeah, that's actually yeah instead of athletics 16. Yeah that hits
Now that you it does get in your general area though, but it hits the FBI agent and
shit, I
Guess what a Molotov cocktail?
How much damage is that?
I
But yeah, your pant leg got a bit on fire
from the Molotov cocktail
And now the shed is starting to get on fire, too
Yeah
So, yeah, so the FBI agent now is like he's like
He's like, you know
Burning a bit. He got socked in the face by another kid. And so he starts panicking
He starts to to run away
Tries to run paths use of DVD you get an opportunity attack though Vince Foster while he's running away
Okay
Mm-hmm. He's so he's out of the shed now. Yeah
Okay, so I will
Is there any objects in the shed that I could throw? Yeah, I mean
Empty beer cans empty beer cans. There's like there's a blarney stone. There's a blarney stone in here, too
Is there a shuriken a shuriken? Yeah, there's an Irish shuriken. It's just a cross. Okay, I will throw that
Yeah, okay throw it really improvise
12 yeah that hits him. Yeah, this guy's not the highest five damage. Okay. Yeah you throw your cross and it's Catholic
Cross so it has Jesus on it. Yeah, it's just spinning in the air
It spins and you see you said you see it just like land in this in like the the small of this guy's back
and just like jut out Christ first.
Um, and he's just like, "AHHHHH!"
And just like, falls on his knees.
And, uh, um, and Yusef, what you see,
is you see this guy disappear, and it's just his clothes remains.
And then you see a snake slither out and slither away.
Um, past you.
Um, the initiative's over,
but Vince Foster you need to get out of the shed
before I do I'm in the shed too
you're kind of in the shed too but you're much further from where the fire that you threw
I'm not going to say exactly what he says but
based on the cross and the snake thing my character says something deeply anti-semitic
and then he leaves
*laughs*
Just roll a... just roll... nah, I mean you could just leave the shed. It's just like lighting on fire and he's gonna fall down.
Yeah
But yeah, that was that was a weird thing that happened. Solvin meanwhile, she lifts her head up and she's like
He's not waking up
He's not gonna wake up. Can we go back inside now?
Well, why don't we just put him next to the shed?
*laughter*
I don't want to.
Maybe that'll wake him up.
Maybe if the, maybe he smells the fire, that'll wake him up.
Um, okay, I guess we could try.
And did you guys, do you guys want to try to bring your uncle towards the, I've, I've
got some, uh, I've got some powder on me.
Oh yeah.
You want to try to use the powder?
Your dad's powder?
Yeah.
My dad has some magic powder.
Oh, okay.
That's a good idea.
to
you put the powder like in his nose you try to figure out like how does your dad
do it and you do your dad sniffs it usually you would think but so you just
sort of like put it up in there and you want to cover it in like spit and you
just watch like the blood vessels you maybe they get redder you can't really
tell and his face looks a little like it's maybe it's swelled a little bit
more like you can't tell but he's like and he just goes like huh and like
nothing else happens
uh... you guys can still try to drag into the burning shed i have a better idea
uh... so
i'd take
so on the map here there's a fish
yet on the ground there's a couple of the couple of cards sort of uh... just
never
i'd be after when a her anger
i'd pick up the fish
and uh...
I just just shoved the shoved the whole fish head in his mouth.
Okay, roll a medicine check with disadvantage.
But do it.
Yeah, 11.
Okay, that and I'll say plus the cocaine your uncle now is like
trying to breathe through his mouth, but he can't so he has to
breathe through his nose that is filled with cocaine and saliva.
And so you watch his him just like his eyes.
shoot the fuck open and he chomps on the fish and he just starts vomiting what is looks
like completely undigested beer.
It's like it's completely just regular beer you could drink from it.
It still has a head.
Yeah.
He vomits into like a cup like a really big mug.
it
in
like
Like that time I ate a pack of thumbtacks
He's like
Keith where was I? I
I thought I saw God and then I was chewing on a fish
What the hell is this you brought sir? Your potion is delicious
But you brought the
You brought the special guy back with you. What's this?
And Vince Foster. Oh, hey Vince, how you doing? He just knows this. Yeah, he knows
We hang out of the bowling alley. Yeah
anyway, anyway, uh
my uncle
Yeah, anyway, my uncle
Going on in the shed
I think you did it
What what I oh shit
Takes in that the shed is on fire
He's like and roll roll a persuasion check with advantage because he's completely fucking out of it and like yeah
22 yeah, he's like
Don't say a fucking word the end. Okay, I wasn't gonna okay. That's my guy. That's my don't accuse me. It's doing it
I won't I'm just saying don't fucking say anything. I don't know what I think Ghana when I go to sleep
I don't know what I do. That's the only thing I can say for sure
I walk. All right. Okay, it wasn't gonna say you wasn't gonna I'm just doing my due diligence
It's nothing to do with you. Don't take it so personal you being sensitive. You know, I say
You're being sensitive. Yeah, I'm not being so you're being sensitive. That's what you're doing right now. Oh my god
I wish I didn't wake you up. I wish you didn't wake me up either. I was dying. It was great
We saw a devil that looked like my mom's leg
a
Um, you know investigate the clothes the FBI guy do whatever you guys want
There's shit around here. Maybe the other thing was around here the leprechaun thing. I'm gonna investigate the shed
You have to wait like 20 minutes, yeah
Wait, is there a hose in the backyard? Yeah. Yeah, you can also try to do that. All right, we're gonna play guys
Let's play firemen
So I get I get the hose yeah, you all need to sort of you're all kids
You all need to try to get together and do well. We have to go inside and get our fireman costumes first. I'm
I call being the pole
Okay, do you guys go get changed who does this just
Richard scary town of sheds yeah what are your firemen costumes look like do
they differ between each of you or you all the same one uh they're very big I
can tell you that yeah right perfect I'm dry I'm wearing a nurse's outfit okay so
we take the hose off the fire yeah yeah yeah yeah you guys run did there you
You close it down, the shed is sort of saved.
It's like, it took you a while to get it on.
Yusef got his on very quickly.
He practices changing in and changing out of outfits for spy reasons.
Or Yusef, did you take off your spy outfit and put on the fireman costume?
No, I put it on top of my spy suit.
Of course.
And Keith, did you put on a fireman...
Lucky Vince, did you put on a fireman outfit or what did you do during that time? No, I just I took my jacket off
So I did that's what I wanted to know. Okay, and so yeah, you guys mostly save it like burns all over my body now
But yeah from being in the shed and fighting with the shirt on yeah
Yeah, you look you look like a little like a little too old for
But yeah, so the shed is the shed you can still investigate to roll an investigation check anybody who wants to investigate the shed
It could be all of you
Mm-hmm 17. Mm-hmm
three
17 yeah, well Vince is just so uninterested in
Investigating the yeah, or what or why Vince? Why do you think you did so poorly?
I should because I got distracted by one of the like
Broken down cars in the backyard. Yeah, I start working on it with a wrench just like kind of screwing stuff making it worse
this
know what I'm doing. There's no like grease on my hands. I'm
just wiping my own blood onto the onto the towel over and over
again. Yeah. Somebody is just like walking by and like the
neighborhood. It's just like looks over the fence. It just
goes **** I'm not even going to **** touch that **** ****
bloody kid. Not again and yeah, the rest of you three though
you guys all sort of scour the scour the shed and you find a
couple of like little gold coins through investigating and and gold coins that
you've never seen before.
Buddy, you guys are going to have to roll a strength check to stop me from eating these.
Right in my mouth the second I see them.
Buddy, get it out of your fucking mouth!
Yeah, I...
Buddy, uh yeah, Yousef, yousef, yousef, you have to roll too.
And you roll strength too, buddy.
Oh God, I'm gonna eat the coin
So you seven just completely failed yet, what are you like completely succeeded? Yeah
Yusef Yusef, why do you why do you think you messed this up describe to me? What what stopped you look?
I'm gonna be straight with you. Mm-hmm. I'm
The the nurse outfit was distracting me. I
I didn't want to touch him because he was covered in too much glue.
Yeah.
And he looked like a girl.
You were like, "I don't want- I hate girls with cooties."
I'm still-
Uh, buddy, you just fucking eat one- the coin you find.
You just fucking eat it.
I need more coins.
You're not touching mine.
You have coins?
No.
We don't have coins.
I'm just lumbering towards Keith Bennefitt very slowly and ominously.
No, I don't have a coin.
Buddy, no.
I
Don't hit check this out. I take there's like a fake pot of gold like one of those like plastic. Yeah, right
Yeah, I
Give him a whole pot of plastic coins
Yeah, buddy just eating that
Yeah, the coin there is just a coin inside of you now. I guess we'll have to address that later
Yeah, and so that's that's it for the for the shed though. I mean you find all the burned-down st
Patty's Day stuff you were gonna wear to the st. Patty's Day parade
Tomorrow, they're all tattered, but I'm still gonna wear it
Those are already tattered. Yeah, and
I'll say at this point you guys you guys retire
Retire for the evening unless you want to do a little bit more investigating in the backyard
I burp and the gold coin flies out and hits Keith in the eye
It sticks to his face
Oh, fuck!
It's stuck on my fucking eyebrow! I can't get it off!
It's also covered in paste.
Yeah, the paste and the coin on my eyebrow, like, waxes my eyebrow off.
The shape of the coin.
So I just have a circle of a missing eyebrow.
Yeah, your aunt sees you later and she's just like,
"Oh, no, I'm not dealing with one of these things you're doing now, okay?
You gotta talk to somebody else about this!"
I wasn't even gonna ask for any help. It looks cool. No, it's no it looks cool
You look like you look like a fucking victim is what you look like. You look like a freak. Okay, cool right now
You look weird. There's nothing worse than being weird. I'm going back in the back. Where's the shed? What'd you do?
There was a shed here. There's one other shed. No
deception check
Great one. I know there was a fucking shed here cuz I was for st. Paddy's Day tomorrow
Ask your fucking husband about this shit!
Oh no.
You see the- the uncle- the husband-
*laughter*
The uncle crashes his head through the window one floor up.
"HEY!"
"I thought you fucking said you weren't gonna fucking say anything!"
"She was yelling at me, I didn't know what I was gonna do!"
There's just like this-
Three, like, this perfect triangle of like-
Like you in the yard, her one floor down, him one floor up, yelling at each other.
Blood vessels popping out of your necks.
Um.
Uh.
But yeah, I mean, unless you want to look at the, anything else in the backyard, we could retire for the evening.
Yeah, I'm going to investigate the backyard some more.
Yeah, okay. You can do that. All you guys can do that.
Six.
Okay.
I guess I'm not.
Maybe you could investigate the gold coin that was stuck to you or something.
Oh yeah, that's a good idea. Okay. Fifteen. I investigate the coin.
Yeah, okay. Um, I would say that for you
Patrick
you look at the coin or Keith brother Keith you look at the coin and
You you start to hear as you stare into it
Like you start to hear like a very faint Danny boy and your eyes start to like water well up with tears. Yeah
I could hear them singing Danny boy on the Muppet Show tonight
Singing he sounds beautiful. Yeah, and
Then it then it then it stops
But you you you feel like there's something magical with this coin. You're pretty sure now
I'll say I'm pretty sure there's something magical
I hear you say coin and I'm walking at you
again.
Just drooling.
No, I have to pick up another like, there's like six different plastic pots of gold in
here.
Yeah, now whenever I take a step you can hear just like plastic just clicking against my
stomach.
Yeah, and so the night kind of ends, Yusef, your dad, comes to pick you up.
the
their trunk yes okay look if they see that I have a son it's all over for us
yes I understand that I understand hey and you have you have the little I'll
put a straw in there now so you can breathe so I don't want to hear any
complaining all right thank you okay yeah you go in your trunk there's like
what do you have in your trunk where you where you spend most of your time you
stuff. There's a stain that I can't describe.
Yeah, it's just there's residue everywhere.
Yeah, right.
Yeah, there's a there's a chamber pot.
Yeah, and there's one of those red tennis balls.
You give children that yeah.
Yeah, you like like a like a Tardis you're able to like fit
inside of it and throw the tennis ball against the wall.
the
uh... and uh...
you uh... events do you have parents do you walk home with your bully life like
what are you
uh... i got i go i go sleep at the school
uh...
that i have to uh... i'm a student of the game i spent my time studying
all the different corners and angles i could be a people from
you see the uh... there is there's a one other guy who sleeps at the school
who's like a janitor
uh... he's like
Hey Vince, how you doing?
Uh, good.
How about you, uh, Rod-Rodriguez?
That's me.
I'm good.
I ate a bunch of grass today by accident.
I might be Buddy's father.
(laughter)
Well I'm sure we'll explore that later.
And Buddy, what do you do?
you do? So my mom comes to pick me up in her SUV and there's because they took
out the the backseat of the SUV and there's just a dentist chair that I get
strapped into like Hannibal Lecter. Oh sweetie I oh you just you're covered in
new things today oh goodness it's usually just a man who copied your leg mom are
Are you proud of me?
He's like, I'll find out what that means in five years, honey.
Okay, deal with it then.
We live like in the apartment above my pediatrician because we moved there.
Make it more convenient for my mom so she doesn't have to drive me to the doctor twice a week.
You have a, you sleep in the head of a lecher chair and like a platform.
And your mom could just lower you down with a crank to the pediatrician's office
And a pediatrician sees you coming down. He's like fucking God damn it again
What did he do and it'll see like a new sales? No, he gets lowered like Mission Impossible. Yeah
He gets lowered that way yeah
He'll get lowered he'll be like what what happened to him you're coming down like belly first and then when you get down you see like
a toy truck.
Yeah, he has to replace the kid.
Like Indiana Jones, he has to like, weigh the kid and sit there.
He tells the kid, "Go outside, I gotta deal with this thing."
They sit me down on one of those like, the like, the seat that's covered in like paper.
Paper just sticks to me like a roll, just wraps around me.
You just get, you go down like face first, onto that, and it's just stuck to your face,
And he could see like the toy truck that's stuck in your back like like today like he's like, ah fucking
Okay
Yeah, and
Yeah, and so you all go to sleep in your respective houses and the next day it's st. Patty's Day. It's a big day
But first everybody has to go to school
Because
Boston had a rule when they realized that they were making up too many Catholic st.
holidays and so there's a lot of pushback and so now they have to go to school even on
St. Paddy's Day.
So you guys go to school and you go to class, you're all in the same class together of course,
and of course there's always the Italian kids.
The Italian kids are these, just these awful little punks who love to bully you guys for
not being Italian, even though that they are also the most bullied kids in all of Boston.
and you see them sort of waddle up to you.
And I should say all the Italians in Boston, California.
- So I'm in their class, even though I'm seven?
- Yeah, you're all in the same class.
Doesn't matter.
- Boston only has one grade.
- It has one grade, it's called school.
You're in the school grade.
Yeah, you have like 30 year olds in there
learning something completely different,
like taking like a trade school class.
- It's like an automotive job.
Yeah, like there's like a car being repaired. Yeah, like a chemistry lab
Like it just like yeah, you know, there's like the alien. Yeah. Yeah. There's a clown school too. The clown school is the largest school
Um and all the italians in boston california are just meatballs
They are anthropomorphic meatballs that are the size of people and they sort of squish
To you guys
They have to keep dodging the culinary students
I didn't eat fucking breakfast. Oh, you didn't eat a bite cuz you're Irish you're Irish kids. You can't eat anything
Oh, oh you guys you get up cuz you always a hungover and they all laugh
One of my pranks oh they all go like
Yeah, and the teacher comes in just you wait and the teacher comes in he's like
He's like, all right. So uh today
We're gonna do some dissecting. I don't remember
a fucking what do we have and he looks inside is like the another room we opened it up here's
a bunch of animals they got okay we got pit bulls today and so he brings in a bunch of
pit bulls.
They're all strapped to like cutting boards basically like you know exam tables and wheels
the mount he's like all right so today you gotta you gotta cut open this pit bull and
figure out what's inside of it. I guess you know you kids Keith your friends
your one group everybody you know just go with your friends I don't give a fuck
if you you learn or anything just cut open the pitbull tell me what you find
extra credit if you don't you know you don't vomit while you're doing it and
yeah so everybody has a pitbull and you see some of the more easy how these
things are alive yeah you see these more ballsy kids are just like stabbing in
the pitbull just like immediately just like are being terrible.
If they're alive I start tossing the pitbulls at the meatball kids.
Yeah. I keep mine.
Yeah, yeah. I was gonna say. Can I add a pitbull to my inventory?
Yeah, you can. You can add a pitbull, a real pitbull to your inventory.
But yeah, Vince, you throw one of the pitbulls at the...
I throw it in the nursery.
(laughing)
- And yeah, Keith, you,
Keith, you throw a pit bull at an Italian kid?
- Yes, I do.
- No, Keith, sorry, Vince.
- I am Vince.
- Yes, my bad.
Yeah, and yeah, you throw it at the Italian kid.
It's roll your improvised roll.
- 13.
- Yeah, you like, you hear,
it just sort of like squishes against.
He absorbs him. No, it just it kind of hurts him but not as much as you would think because okay, because he's a meatball
You know, hey, who did the fuck gonna throw that?
It was him and I pointed buddy
Okay
Don't hold deception. Yes
Here I got this. Don't worry about it and I push him over. Okay. Yeah, buddy. You're face to face with this giant meatball
And what do you what do you see? Oh, you got a problem glue boy. I
I
Yeah, he shoves you you see two little arms come out of his a
Meatball body and just shove you back buddy
You trying to start to something
Yes
Do I roll at least buddy does if everyone else wants to start fighting with the I'm
I'm petting my pitbull and I'm naming him
No, go to him
E.t
Yeah, uh, yeah, yeah so so buddy it's just you against these meatballs
Unless anyone else wants to help out buddy. No, I give putty buddy some of the magic powder. Okay? Yeah
Buddy, you can move twice as fast and attack
Twice in a turn for one minute which for you because of your hug ability you guys want to start a lemonade stand
I have a really good idea for a lemon
So, yeah, you go first buddy you got this meatball coming at you. All right, I use my big hug ability
the
I see people tie it to decks, but I think it should be any... whatever, anyway.
So! Big hug!
Uh... oh fuck, it's doing a thing where you can't see the fucking character sheet.
I- I can't see it on the character sheet. I sent it to you, so...
I can read it here.
Yeah, just read it. You know what? Fuck.
Buddy will give an enemy a big sticky hug.
They will be grappled, unable to move, attack, or anything.
The enemy will take 1d6 plus strength every turn they are in Buddy's embrace.
Buddy will also suffer half damage as long as he is embracing an enemy.
once buddy starts hugging an enemy he will not stop because he is stuck to the
enemy and because he is dumb
until he squeezes the life out of him
meaning he can do other actions only if they do not get in the way of him hugging
an enemy
if he bumps into any other enemies while doing this hug they can stick to him if
they fail a DC 12 deck save meaning they will be grappled as well but will not
suffer damage from the hug
yeah so buddy basically hugs his meatball and is like "what are you doing? what are you doing?"
"what are you doing?" and like he is just stuck to you
and roll for damage on that
five and you just squeeze you see a bit of the meatball come out of it was like
hey hey what's the matter with you and uh uh you just now have this guy just attached to you
um you're just hugging him big hug um uh and uh meanwhile uh the this guy can't do anything
this guy's gonna try to come up to you but he's gonna have to roll a deck save to see if he can
do it without getting stuck to you and well he got a crit one he is stuck to you
hey what's the matter you hear like all of it like a chorus of it keep going this is happening i
have i've already put a leash and i got the dog registered at the state it's now my pet pit bull
and yep they are all stuck to you so just all these stallions failed their checks
and they're just stuck to you while you're hugging one of their friends and
they're like "hey, ah, oh, oh, oh, hey, hey, hey!"
You hear all this stuff. Meanwhile...
You guys want to go to the bathroom?
And I just start walking to the bathroom and pulling them all along with me.
Meanwhile, Keith, you start to hear that little Danny Boy song again.
And you look outside the window.
"Danny boy, Danny boy..."
And you see a little rosy-faced little leprechaun guy.
and he's looking over and he's sort of tilting his head back and forth
looking over at you and he's like "hardy tardy, hardy tardy"
he's like trying to motion you to come come to the window
I point at him?
mm-hmm
does he does he point?
yeah he he sees you pointing at him and he's like "hardy tardy"
and he takes out a bottle of guinness and he tips it towards your finger
I lift up like I'm smelling like a pie in a windowsill
and start floating towards it
yeah yeah
You start playing window because the way is all shattered anyway, yeah, these are shattered
Yousef and Vince. What do you do when you see this? Well, buddy's taking all the Italians to the bathroom
I'm gonna go I I I will follow buddy to the bathroom. I want to help. Yeah. Okay and Vince
Jumping grab Keith's legs and he takes me with him. Yeah, you're flying away with this
Magical little man. I'm holding him like a ladder from a helicopter
So you start floating out the window so we'll get to that right now let's do buddy
and
Yeah, Vince. Why don't you roll initiative just to enter into the turn order? Oh, I'm just there to like eat popcorn
Okay. Hell yeah, okay, buddy
Buddy you can just hug again roll another d6 and add your will add your strength while I'm while I'm floating
I have my pitbull on the leash
Yeah, that's what I'm holding on to no
Yeah
Okay, so I rolled a five plus. Yeah, I think that just to seven. Okay, cool. Yeah, so you just
You just squeeze this meatball harder. What'd you do five last time? Is this this Italian? He's not looking good
He's like, please let me go. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I'm he's cozy. He's cozy, please
Please you hear the other ones in the back, please
They're all just you be quiet I have to go to the bathroom. Yes
Hugging for Italians and just take all the toilet not even hugging my arms are just at my size. They're just stuck to me
Like get into the bathroom stall, but I can't fit in because there's a bunch of meatballs stuck to me. Yeah
And Vince, what are you doing? Are you eating popcorn and just watching this happen?
Yeah, I'm sitting on the counter eating popcorn, which I bring with me. I've hidden popcorn
at different places around the school at night when I live here. And I just grab my boy's
bathroom stash. I'm sitting watching. And also I'm throwing pieces of popcorn into Buddy's
mouth that he's just missing.
the
cancel me sis walks in and he's like what's up Hernandez hey hey how's it
going oh it's that kid who might be my son I just looked into his eyes I just
freeze completely still the only time in my life when I'm completely still and not
saying anything and I just stay that way as long as he's in the room
He's a he's a he's a he's eating a bit of a book he's like yeah what
What you doing? He's got these Italians here. Talk to him. I
Blink my eyes and it makes a cartoon blink noise
And the Italians are gonna try to get out of this now, let's see how they do
Let's just roll all for all of them at once
Okay, one of them does manage to get out
And he's gonna try now to
Free his friends, so he's gonna give it another shot
And he's just can't he's just trying to pull his friends. I was like, oh, please please
Please try to pull off one of his friends and he can't the other three just still can't move their grapple
There's nothing else that they don't have any other abilities
So they're just like stuck to you and one of them's gonna die next heard probably
And yeah
Rodriguez is just looking him over and he's like a kid
And he hands you like a bit of his book for you to eat
I'm like a deer in headlights. I can't just it just like he tries to hand it towards you to just like
Gently like pushes it into your face
the
a
back to the battle for you to kill one Italian. Meanwhile, Yusef and Keith are flying away
with this little leprechaun and he's floating away with you guys and he heads over towards
to your house, Keith. He floats down and now you're back at your house with Yusef. He's
like "Heretic, heretic, heretic!" and he's like bouncing around and you see him looking
at all the empty bottles. He's like, "Hurt it!" and he starts to drink it and he can't.
He's trying to find another one. You see he keeps trying to drink it and as he keeps-
I tap him on the shoulder. Yeah.
Wait, hold on. You finish. No, no, no. I was going to say, him trying
to drink it and you watch his agony and you start to feel it too. Like you start to feel
like your head starts to hurt a little bit and you start to feel a little bit like a,
a
Let's go inside.
There's a liquor cabinet.
Under...
The sink.
He, uh...
You look down and you realize he's tied your shoes together.
He's like, "Hurty-turty-turty-turty-turty-turty."
What the fuck?
And he's doing a little dance.
He starts flipping around one of those gold coins that you saw before.
And he's like clapping his little hands.
the
them untie them right now and he unties them and understand me okay
he ties it from the back and now you should hide from the back you can't see
that they're tied again well all this happens I'm right yeah it will around
the yard yeah yeah you're just like experiencing a like sort of like heavy
metal movie like sort of experience of riding a giant beast around the yard are
Are you taking notes on this too, probably?
Like to send back to your dad.
(laughing)
- Man, this fucking sucks.
- Yeah.
- I start trying to walk towards the leprechaun.
- And I walk forward.
- Yeah.
- Oh, fuck!
And yeah, I mean, eventually you all manage to get inside.
Yousef riding the pit bull, you.
And you look inside your mom's liquor cabinet
and it's empty.
It's fucking empty.
- Oh no.
work in 10 jobs she hasn't had any time to restock.
Wait.
And you see Sullivan.
There's a little bit left.
Yeah, sorry, go.
You also see Sullivan the frog is just like playing with dolls
and watching TV.
There's a little bit left in this thing here.
It's called aromatic bitters.
And you see him before you even finish saying aromatic bitters,
he's like swallows the whole thing.
And he's like, "Hurry, TK, hurry, TK, hurry."
He starts to feel a little bit better.
You can see he starts to feel--
He sort of grabs you by your face now
Keith and is like hearty
dirty
Dirty hard like you think he's tried basically trying to say I need more alcohol
But he's just like saying slowly hearty dirty hearty turkey
Buddy and and Vince
Buddy you roll one more d6
You just killed this Italian just like kill this child and the other ones fall off of you like
They all just like sir
Like hop away meatballs run out of the bathroom
Terrified of you and this other one's just sort of like dead before you and when he's dead
He just reverts back into a regular Italian person
So you're just in the bathroom now, yeah, I go to the bathroom
Yeah, you finish going to do I watch him shit
Shit that is hitting the water is making the most insane noises
It's the toilet bowl. You see everything I ate in the past. Yeah, just like
coins
Towards the end you get a horn. Yeah. Yeah
The end is just like a minute
It's just a minute long at the like a minute long like like trumpet solo at the end
it's just like just sounds like
it's just or it's just like
And then I stand up and just say I want to hang out with Keith's uncle and I just leave school
the
I'm
Flipping a coin and like making bully
bully bully sounds
Yeah
And you guys eventually get back there and you see that the
Situation's gotten worse
The leprechaun is just like digging through the floors of the house. He tried to drink Sullivan. He couldn't
He's just doing anything he can
to get some alcohol so
Obviously Patrick you have your own beer that you I guess have been obscuring from this leprechaun. He also there's a
Hold on I'm gonna continue
To obscure the beer from him and I go out into the back and I start siphoning gas out of the GTO
Okay
I'm gonna see if the leprechaun notices you doing that
I'm going to say he probably does without even rolling, but I will let him give it a shot.
Yeah, he doesn't notice. He's craving the beer too much. He's just, he rolled that bad. So he's
just like, he's just like looking at you. He looks at you, buddy, and starts like seeing all this
stuff on you and trying to see if there's anything in there that resembles liquor.
I see the tiny leprechaun and I'm like, this guy is really far away from me.
me. He goes up to you, Yusef, and he's like trying to see if he has anything. He finds
a little powder. He starts to sniff it and goes, "Hardy, hardy, hardy, hardy, hardy,
hardy." And just like puts it, like gives it back to you, like it's not for him.
Thank you. Yeah. He says, "You're welcome." And he starts
like hardy, hardy, hardy around. He goes outside. He sees the hose and he freaks out. "Hardy,
He starts like freaking out when he sees the hose and scurries back inside the house and
now he's just like sort of feeling sick and sad and you start to feel it too Keith.
You start to feel whatever it is he's feeling.
There's like a some sort of link here.
I feel so horrible.
Yeah.
Oh god I feel awful and I pull one of the beers out of my pocket and I drink the whole thing
in like two seconds.
You hear it when you hear that when he hears a
Leprechaun
Like the kill bill sound like the leprechaun stories out and
Sees you drink it already. He's like
her
Yeah, that's
That's what you all these you want these yeah, he's like trying
He's like begging you for it. Oh
Well, why don't you just say that
tiny
hard
Dirty, he's like trying to find other words to say besides hardy and tardy. Yeah. Oh, well, all right
Well, I don't know where else to get it there's like a there's a packy there's a bar it's Boston, California
You could find it. Oh, yeah stuff you guys. Oh, I've got an idea guys. Let's go. Let's go to the dumpster behind the back
You guys want to do that also in like a couple hours the st. Patty's Day parade is gonna start to
And everyone will be dressed up in their st
Patty's Day finest and there's a corned beef and cabbage and beer eating contest as well
that a Kobayashi senior honorary Irishman
Has has won eight years straight. I
Say we go to the Paki. Yeah
Okay, cool you guys want to go you Seth Vince follow on the pitbull
You guys head over to the peggy my legs into its like sides
It immediately
understands there's no like gap in like it being needing to be a trained animal pitbulls are very easily trained and
You guys just sort of rush off to the packy
And yeah, it's open. You're all children is the only thing
and
and you do a little investigation check I would say yeah I look for I'm
investigating for expired beers mm-hmm 10 okay yeah you managed to find a couple
of expired beers I'd say that you can give to nothing you would be able to
drink just because it would like kill you but like that you could give to
to
is a bunch of shit attached to him, right?
Mm-hmm.
I feel like he's big enough now that he's--
Yeah.
He looks like an adult.
I'm also 6'7".
Yeah.
[LAUGHTER]
I feel like he's not going to get caught.
Somebody walks in with 2,000 pounds of stuff attached to them.
I walk into the packy, but I walk into the back door.
[LAUGHTER]
That's a real grown man move, dude.
You walk in.
You see people are there.
They're getting their drinks because it's St. Paddy's Day.
They get in their drinks together.
You see some of them are starting to look over and like a little curious about what this giant thing is.
Hard to tell if it's like a, I guess it could be a fucked up boy or it could be just a fucked up man.
It's not easy to tell.
So what are you doing there, buddy?
You trying to get something to drink?
What were your instructions?
What did you guys tell buddy to do?
okay go in there and pretend like you work there
and you're throwing out
bad beer
okay uh... so i walk in
the first thing i say is i look at everybody waiting in line and the
workers and i say
i am one thousand years old
and i pick up
i pick up like one six pack in each hand and they just kinda stick so i can
pick up more too yeah
and so i just have
I'm doing like Edward Fortyhands but with like five six-packs on each hand.
And I say, "This is my job!"
And then I turn around and walk back out of the door.
You're like, "Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, buddy!
We ain't never seen you before.
What's your name?"
How did you know?
I just said, "I haven't seen you before."
I start crying.
I just haven't you know, I just haven't seen you before
Any of you guys want to do something you said vids or Keith what's happening I
Guy can see my dreams
I
Walk up to buddy and I say excuse me, sir. Do you know where the candy is in the store?
Because you work here. I
*laughing*
I don't know what's going on!
I wanna see my mom!
And I wanna go to the doctor!
Okay, I'm gonna take this guy to the doctor!
*laughing*
I'm crawling around humming the James Bond theme.
Yeah, okay.
Uh, a couple of things.
Okay, uh, Yusef, you can roll,
roll a stealth check, 'cause you're crawling around the Paki store.
23.
You are so good at this.
So good at this they can't even see me
Yeah, yeah. Wait, how are you being so stealthy describe it to be you so
um
I've painted myself to look like
So, uh, uh, yeah, you are just blending in perfectly
So we'll we'll resolve we'll look over you in a second see what you're what you want to do with that
Uh vince, what are you up to?
Um, I can I uh stop buddy from leaving the store
Mm-hmm. Okay. I stopped buddy from leaving the start ago. Hey, it's me your doctor. I'm here. Oh
Let's see. What's this? I try and take his pulse through like a like a like a trash can lid. That's
Like oh, yeah, that's what I thought. I'm gonna prescribe you 50 beers
Okay, buddy
Vince roll
deception buddy, I
guess roll
Yeah roll insight, okay, I
Got a 19. I got a 13. Yeah, buddy here, you don't you know, you know Vince, you've known him for a while
So, you know, he's not your doctor, but you think he maybe did just help you
Yeah
Like do you think he healed you? Like what do you think? He did that? You got tricked here. I think that that he is
my doctor's son
That now because I can't imagine there could be another doctor
that's not related. I think all doctors are in one big family.
Yeah. Yeah. I should say and so I just ignore everything you said and I say,
can I come over for dinner? I look and I see I see one of the one of the shelves
behind me or behind buddy is like winking at me and I realized that that's
of
and i i got never never mind come on
then he's got it
weekend cool
and uh... yeah yes so uh... you guys sort of uh... go out and i still in the
story at you if you are doing you are yelling about getting candy your seven
yeah i was gonna have that and real fast in the if you want to keep going again i
still have six packs up to my hand yet you do you see still dot stuff i would
say that the store clerks are completely baffled there's no reason i and this is
and this is boston california in the eighty-five
i'm yeah i've heard about another gold coin
and i believe
and that
uh... you only have a couple of six back so you set if you want to keep trying to
get more beers to fuel
your new little friend
uh... let's use it exactly what i do
okay yeah
the group to more six-packs
and uh...
crab walkout
Yeah, you use your crab walking out like a little girl sees you and like sort of tugs his mommy
It's some kind of fucked-up spider. She's
Shut up
As you're crawling out of the store
Also, what perception check you stuff
The pitbulls on my back by the way, oh, yeah, it's all it's all making sense to me visually
Yeah, you got a crit one, you don't notice anything in particular as you're crawling out of the store with a pitbull on your back
You notice less than is possible to notice with that crit. We're getting a lot of crits today
Yeah, you guys go out of the store. You have all these these these beers and you watch as the little leprechaun is like
Like just drinking them down fucking pounding them that cat loves drinking water
the
okay
but yeah he's all field up he seems good he seems ready to go
can i take one of the leprechauns beers
yeah you can try it yeah you see what he does
what what would i roll
uh...
slight a hand if you're trying to like nab it from him
twenty
very slick you're very smooth
yeah you just like slick slide that in uh... very smooth
And the leprechaun's dancing around now, he's like, "Harty-tart, harty-tart!"
And he points up towards the Brady Woods.
And he's like, "Harty-tarty, harty-tarty, um, uh, harty-tarty,
[stuttering]
"Grainbowl!"
He says his, like, first word.
-Whoa! -That he heard him say.
He's gay!
[laughter]
He's-- he somehow is like, "No."
"Fuckin' nah."
(laughs)
Well, okay. Well, you know that Boston, California was one of the first places to legalize gay marriage, so I do accept you if you are.
I heard you, I heard you, Tyrone. He's like, feels a little embarrassed.
(laughs)
But, uh...
I turned to the rest of the crew and was like,
"Oh, he wants us to take him to that spot that we found the dead body!"
*sniff*
*ding*
That other time...
*sniff*
You know, by the trail- the railroad tracks and...
Kiefer Sutherland was there...
I just- I- I nod...
Yes, I remember that.
*laughter*
I- I put my hand in my pocket and I just have a finger in my pocket from that pocket.
It smells so bad.
Yeah.
*laughter*
*sniff*
Oh, fuck. Hey, put that back.
I put it back in my pocket.
So, you guys could get to the Brady Woods.
Obviously, this leprechaun can float a lot of you guys pretty far.
That said, you'll likely be noticed if you do that, though you can certainly still do it.
The other way is to go through the main street in town, where the St. Brady's Day Parade is happening.
You can kind of blend in there.
Um, those are sort of your two pathways to get to the Brainy Woods.
I will ride the leprechaun.
Me too.
I put a playing card in his butt cheeks to make him go faster.
So he makes motorcycle sounds.
So yeah, you all, how do you guys all configure yourself to climb onto this leprechaun?
I'm very curious.
We stand on a finger.
We each get a finger. I'm in a I'm in a pitbull sidecar
Yeah, yeah
I was gonna say I was gonna say we put the leprechaun on the pit and then have the
Leprechaun race the pitbull in the air, but I think if we each get a finger, I think that's a lot funnier. Yeah
I'm
Holding us up. Yeah. Yeah, buddy. You're somehow stuck to like the soul of your shoe like the least like
Least leverage you can get and grabbing on to something you are fine though
And you all start flying in the air, and we, even though it's like the afternoon, we see your silhouette against like, uh, the moon as you're doing it.
It's the most confusing silhouette of all time.
You don't know what it's supposed to be, looking up from the top.
It's like, it's like a, it's like a, guess, it's like a "Who's that Pokemon?"
It's for like, Tangela.
It could look less like anything.
It looks like a Rorschach test.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, somebody down there looks up and says, "Oh, fuck, my parents are fighting! I can't see them!"
[Laughter]
Yep.
Um, um, and um, uh, and uh, uh, as you're sort of flying up, uh, you hear, "Pshh!"
and and the leprechaun blood squirts out of the leprechaun fuck and you look down
and you see you see one of those snake men with a gun shooting down the
leprechaun I take one of my beer bottles out and I just plug I open it up and
plug the hole
so the blood is still falling out just into something it's a it's going it's
it's so it's like
the beers going into his body while blood is going into the
transmission
you start to lose altitude of that you're transfusing his blood into a beer can
and you see the the leprechaun is like trying to gain
some some leverage uh...
What what what do you guys gonna try to do cuz it looks like you're gonna land a little bit towards the woods
Right now how close to the woods?
I mean like kind of like where you live you live like on like right on the outskirts of town
So you can probably land pretty near the woods if you want to if you like like that's kind of where you were already
But not like in the woods
Like he shot you kind of a little too early cuz cuz nobody noticed him inside the inside the the liquor store
So I think we land near the woods, right? Yeah, you can do that
You can veer in other directions so you can try to drive the leprechaun in the directions. Okay
What if we go to the parade to try and lose the that's a good idea?
Okay. Oh, yeah, we can make it look like we're floating into the parade. Oh, yeah, we're afloat. Mm-hmm
Okay. Yeah. Okay. So you guys?
Steer this leprechaun. I don't know why I give you guys options and into
the parade and
You see everybody sort of like dressed up as either, you know, like, you know, they're wearing kiss me. I'm Irish shirts. They're
Wearing kiss me. I'm Irish or something like that. I don't know. I'm drunk shirts
You know all kinds of stuff you see people dressed as like Irish folklore creatures
Well, they're wearing I'm they're wearing I'm with stupid and the arrows pointing up. Yeah, right a hundred percent
Yeah, name all that stuff right now, because I can't think of any of it.
They're there.
They're there somehow have iPhones that have already
and they have the beer drinking app.
And yeah, you guys land in the parade in the street.
You see everybody there.
They don't really.
It's pretty fucking weird, but like it's it's not out of the ordinary
to see a leprechaun kind of looking guy.
You think it's just like a fucked up kid, maybe dressed up for the occasion.
Who just floated down from the.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
And but yeah, the snake man, you can't see where he could have been
or where where he could have went
at this point.
But yeah, you're in the parade.
You could see people having a good time.
What do you guys want to do in the parade?
There's like stands, there's like games, people just marching around.
Mr. Thorn, Mardi Gras beads of people.
Okay, yeah.
Uh, yeah, you throw it at a guy who looks like, exactly like Roger Clemens.
[Laughter]
Take it off!
He's like, "Fuck yeah, dawg!"
And he takes it off, he shows his body.
I vomit.
[Laughter]
He's a guy, right?
He's been worse. I've gotten worse.
Um, worse reviews.
Um, yeah, what else you guys wanna do?
What do you guys, just play around the parade.
there's tons of stuff you can do name something it's probably there
i go i go to there's like a standard you like throw
tennis balls like knockdown bottles yeah yeah uh... and i tried i'd i'd like paid
it with all green tennis balls yeah i go to throw the ball but it just can't
leave my hand stuck i just keep trying to throw it over and over and the guys
getting really mad at me and i just look at him and say the devil is chasing us
Wait box here. Yeah, wait box is here. I go shake his hand
He says thank you for your service no, thank you chicken, man
Yeah, you want to hang out with box yeah, I'm gonna hang out with my box and drink beer
Yeah
Very precocious
What are you doing Yusef?
What are you up to?
I've left a pitbull in a bull pit that I've seen.
Wait my pitbull or yours?
Uh yeah yours that I was riding.
The pitbull is just like eating the balls.
You see like a family of seven children going like "Come on let's play in the park!"
The jaws theme starts playing
You see like it's like the camera like gets aware like shakes a little bit and pans away as quickly as
And
Yeah, you uh, oh
Yeah, so you have yeah, you're hanging out with Wade Boggs and
Just I mean we just get plastered. Yeah, he's like he's like, yeah
No, we after that, you know, nobody could even look at Buckner, you know, it was oh
Trust me. I wanted to fucking kill that guy. I mean everybody the whole fucking city wanted to kill that guy
What a piece of fucking shit. He's got a fucking bend down a little bit. Yeah, fucking a grounder
one sec
Yeah, I know trust me dude I fucking
God, I would do anything that do that series again, man
I would fuck in if I saw Bucky Dent I'd kill him
And you see the little leprechaun now here Wade Boggs say I would do anything
to do that series again and
leprechauns like territory territory deterrence arts like flipping around gold coins and doing little magic things at his hands and way Boggs like
Is he?
Z what the fuck is that? Is it a little epic on? Oh, yeah
and Wade Boggs
like it's like I
Would do anything to do that series again and starts chasing the leprechaun just like to and just starts running around
Trying to grab him in the leprechaun just keeps dodging head of the way. He's not drunk at all
He's like that's a Terry like disappearing up on the tree branch on a tree branch
And he's like you don't understand I was supposed to get so much pussy that night
He's just like trying so hard to grab the leprechaun
Meanwhile, what are you, what are the rest of you guys doing while Patrick is dealing with this leprechaun situation?
Because that might ignite, you know, that might make other people aware of the leprechaun if he's teleporting around and doing magic things.
That's sort of the danger here in this instance.
I'm holding on to the side of the rollercoaster as it goes around.
[Laughter]
What about you Vince?
There's a I'm just cutting all the lines for all the the floats yeah, yeah the shamrock flow
Yeah, like everything is just going into the sky. Yeah. Yeah, you're just people in them also
Flying like uncontrollable hot-air balloons. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, we left the manual
We don't know how to fly any of these things. It's just the parade's just a complete chaos
And at this point though, it's it's the leprechauns been sort of like teleporting around like doing little tricks and stuff
And you see the a group more of those snake men
and
They start to approach you guys
And he said to chase you to say gets that leprechaun and they start trying to chase him
What do you guys want to do? Is there any way I can direct Wade Boggs on the leprechaun to the woods?
You could certainly try oh, yeah, I got an idea. Hey wait, there's a bucket of chicken in the woods
There's a whole whole KFC in there whole KFC dinner. You can go in there all the chicken you want
I know I know that's your thing. Oh
Roll persuasion with advantage because you said that
He he who's wanted to who he wanted to
He stops chasing the leprechaun he's getting kind of winded. He's already sort of becoming the age he is now and
He's like fucking chicken
He just starts to wander off towards the woods and the leprechaun he wants to keep tricking Wade starts following him and and it's like
Poking at him and prodding him and the snake guys are chasing after him too. And you guys are running into the woods
Is there any way I can make Wade go? I know I can I make Wade go faster
So the leprechaun goes faster. So the snake men. Yeah, what do you want to try to do?
Uh, if you catch the leprechaun Wade, you're gonna need to eat a whole bucket of chicken before the game to redo the series
And oh, that's a good point. It's chickens my fuel
Superstition. Yeah, that's my see. That's why I look like this soon
He's like moving a little bit faster now and you guys almost lose snake guys, I'll have you roll all you guys roll
Let's have you all roll nature checks actually to see if you could sort of hide in the woods if you know your way around
Critical got a crit
Do I count which one do I count I accidentally rolled with advantage? Oh the first one. Sorry damn six
Okay, a couple of things
Keith you got Keith and buddy. You have a regular relationship with the Brady woods
Nothing special that you know about it
Yousef you're particularly unversed in these woods. Why do you think that is? I want to know
What makes yousef have a hard time navigating the woods 70% of my time is spent inside a trunk
Yeah, yeah your dad's like your dad like also doesn't want you to go into the woods
Yeah, i'm not my dad doesn't like the outside because you know, the rain has tap water in it and he doesn't want me
Yeah
And uh, uh you uh, vince, uh that crit is going to be very helpful for you. What what?
Why do you know your way around the woods? So well vince foster the bully
Um as soon as I like get into the woods it it immediately becomes like a snow white situation and all the uh,
Woodland creatures come out and I start singing
In a beautiful girl voice
And I realize it's like the only happiness i've ever had in my life
Yeah, there's a connection in nature. Yeah, you see like the rabbits are like have like big eyelashes and they're like
Doing silly little like scurry things around you and and they're they're giving you like
They're giving you little outfits to wear try on they're helping you sew something right now. Yeah. Yeah
Uh, but your your knowledge around the woods helps sort of lift everybody else out of it and you guys managed to get
um
uh to
What looks like?
you know
who are magical
part of gold
on the car and you see way bogs is like
holly crap
and uh... the leprechauns like
and he looks up
he's like pointing up
and he's like you see way off in the distance from the rainbow that part of
gold is on this magical saint patrick's day
a few little leprechauns sliding down
maybe towards
the pot of gold
before anything can happen
you also see
a
some of people been waiting here
for this
is none other than the the greatest snake
in in boston history
roger fucking clemens
who left the socks to join
the yankees
my mom went to dinner with him once
and his snakes
Because he's a fucking snake
and he says
He says to you all finally the leprechaun i'm roger clemens. I don't think I sound like this
I think roger clemens is from like texas or yeah, right disney. Yeah. Yee-haw. My name is roger clemens
I fucking hate boston california. Oh, he's from ohio
and uh
And I have a disorder.
Um, just looked it up.
He's from trench town and I live in a hole.
I go back up and, um, you see, he says once long ago, St.
Patrick banished these snakes from all of Ireland and from Boston, California.
I'm bringing the snakes back one leprechaun dead at a time.
Give me that leprechaun.
No! Wait, hold on, I've got an idea.
Are we all here now?
Yeah, you're all here, I just haven't put your icons in yet.
What's a leprechaun?
You talking about that midget that says "tard" all the time?
[Laughter]
Yeah, he says "hardy, tardy, how do I sound?"
Roger Clements. He's just like freaking out.
Oh, those are the wrong characters. Sorry.
Uh, yeah, but you guys are all here now.
Um, I was gonna say roll initiative against Roger Cogman's and the snakes, but if you guys
have a few more words to share, anyone want to step on that?
Uh, I think the leprechaun is more sad.
Yeah.
Are you, I'm talking, I'm talking to Roger.
Are you my mom?
Oh shit.
Uh, no kid, I'm not your mom.
Are you my teacher?
I'm about to teach you a lesson.
Are you my mom's friend?
Alright, so this is-
Are you my teacher's friend?
You're doing a thing?
This is a thing you do?
Are you my mom's teacher?
Did somebody tell this kid to
fucking shut the fuck up?
Are you my teacher's mom?
I'm gonna tell-
Well answer his fucking questions, you prick!
No, you're a prick.
God, I'm so mad at you right now.
I whispered to Keith,
"That's my teacher's mom's friend."
*laughter*
Yes he is, buddy. Yes he is.
And, uh, yeah, you all wrote an initiative?
initiative. Okay. Shit. Okay. Wow. Okay. Cool. Um, okay. Yeah. All right. And so, uh, Keith,
you got to go first against Roger Clemens and his snakes as they wait by the rainbow.
Yeah. All right. I think I'm going to use wicked smots on him. All right. So if you
is
I'm gonna try and convince him to go back to the Red Sox.
[Laughter]
Okay, go for it.
Alright.
I open up just like one of the Guinness that we took from the Leprechaun.
I chug the whole thing in front of him.
And I just start talking like,
"Fuckin' listen to me, kid.
Fuckin' listen, dude.
I swear to fuckin' God,
you come back for one season.
one season is all we fucking need
you
Wade Boggs over here
I forgot Wade Boggs
you're gonna be a fucking
it's gonna be fucking amazing kid
it's gonna be so fucking sick
just trust me on this
trust me, you
and I'm the coach
and I'm the coach of the team
I'm the coach now
I'm gonna bring, you and Wade are gonna be
a fucking, we're gonna
He's caught in a bear trap.
He's bleeding out.
He's chewing through his own leg.
You know what?
You know what we're gonna fucking do?
We're gonna beat Bill Buckner down with fucking baseball bats.
That's what we're gonna do.
I don't even care.
I don't care if you cork bats either.
I'm gonna pump you full of fucking steroids too.
You're gonna be the strongest, strongest fucking team in all of Boston history, alright?
You fucking trust me.
You trust me on this.
persuasion with advantage see if you can get him to want to join back to Boston
team 16 he's uh he's like there's no hope left for me in Boston
oh fuck you there's no hope now I don't even know where I'm from anymore mate
I could be from anywhere and not after not until I fuck your mother you're
Fuck my mom. Oh, yeah
Did a prank on her right that's what you said he did a crazy prank
And that's your turn and how it's a project Clemens and his snakes turn. So Roger Clemens, so that did nothing. No, I did shit
Yeah
so Roger Clemens is gonna
throws a fastball at
at
you
Keith after that attempt
And that hits you and it does
Yeah, this is the only real fight
It does 11 damage to you
And he's gonna wind up another fastball and throw it at you
Vince he's he is not even gonna try to attack buddy. I'm totally scared of him
Let's see. Can I use my my deflection ability now? Yes, I forgot. Yeah, so you can use your your your leather jacket to deflect this
Okay, so roll d20. All right
Yeah, you deflect it. You can just deflect projectiles. So you deflect this baseball. It just goes flying off into the sky
with your cool leather jacket
And now the snakes are gonna come after you guys, so they're all like hissing away
They're there and they're going after
Yousef first because they see he's they see he's English and they have a certain
thing about that
and so I saw I'm okay, so there's a
dilapidated office chair
sort of on
The perimeter of the action. Yeah. Yeah, I can see me. Yeah, it turns around
Stroking a gun like a cat
*laughter*
Okay, um, let's see if the snakes understand what you're doing.
Uh... uh...
Let me see if they understand it.
Oh, do we have the pitbull with us?
Yeah, you do.
The snakes don't understand, like, what a gun is, so they're not scared of you yet.
Um, they can't even, like, be intimidated, but...
Um, they're gonna try to attack you.
Let's see how they do.
Uh, one of them hits you for...
Alright, he hits you for 7 damage, the other two snap at you and miss you.
And also you're a little bit... you feel your legs swell up a little bit.
Um, and that might be a problem down the line.
This last snake is gonna go for you, buddy.
Um, he's gonna try to chomp into you.
And he does manage to pierce your... your... your Katamari Damacy shield.
and do
For damage to you just like bite your leg
And you also see your leg to get this wall up a little bit. Yeah
But now it is your turn
Buddy, it's your turn
It's my turn. I got a one. Oh, you got one. Oh, sorry Leo. It's your turn you Seth. It's your turn
I was looking at your nature check. I
Take a pot shot
That the snake or Roger Clemens at Roger Clemens, are you gonna use the gun on him you're gonna use a gun on Roger Clemens? Yeah
Yeah hit gun, okay
it's
strong I made the gun
*laughter*
There's the gun.
He got a 32.
*laughter*
He blows brains out.
Roll for damage.
That hits him.
*laughter*
Yes. Let's go.
Shoot a man
He takes a shit ton of damage he looks so fucked up like oh my god
Hey, you shoot him. You swear. Where did you shoot him use this without killing him in this sort of stomach?
This is coming. Okay. You shot him in the stomach. He's bursted his kidney. Yeah
I didn't know the boy had a gun. Oh
my god, I
Start like screaming and crying because my my dreams of becoming the coach of the Red Sox with Roger Clemens and Wade Boggs
I thought I could still do it
It's like less of a battle now and everyone's just freaking out
When I see him get shot I just go I'm going to take you to the doctor and I just start walking towards him like Michael
*laughter*
he's like NO! PLEASE!
um, yeah and it is uh
uh, uh
I forgot to give you like a down time
after the cocaine thing but
it's fine, uh
yeah you said- you do that
the snakes actually like take a second
to go "whoa" like
they- just the snakes
internally realize that something
the vibe is different like
A gun was introduced into this.
It is, let's see, initiative.
Oh yeah, sorry, it's your turn Vince.
Vince Foster.
Okay, buddy, what's the biggest thing that has stuck to you?
There's a giant piece of drywall on my back like a turtle shell.
i use my improvised ability to pick it up and and throw it
hit you okay me too
the head
uh... i just roll roll a straight check just 'cause it's a bit bigger but a
regular improvised and a
nice now
if tolerant and yet you're fine you're able to throw this thing night uh... so
you have to move a bit closer to hit clemens
if you try to clemens
yeah all the clemens l all of them
I will grab it and then kind of do like a roll with buddy's body and then throw the entire
thing at him.
Okay, and so that's going to do that's so much stuff.
So don't roll just roll your attack for improvise like four times to see how much damage you
do.
Okay, so that's just after you but first do an improvise attack because you can lift her
and see if you can hit them.
14.
Yeah, that's that's that's that's going to beat his AC.
is
this
you
Yeah, you just say you smell good
Yes
Good as this terrible boy starts flying towards him the snakes are still here
Then the snakes still
Want to
Take back Ireland or Boston, California, so you can still you still have to fight that but Roger Clemens is dead
Well while Roger Clemens is dead
I go up to him and I take his Red Sox hat and I put it on and I say I think I'm gonna change
My last name to folk
Now become a relief pitcher
It is now your turn buddy
Or yeah, buddy, it's your turn I
Just start waddling towards the pot of gold because
Yeah, and you see
You can't feel it but the leprechaun is like on your back like
He's like clapping his hands excitedly as you're wandering wandering towards the pot of gold
Now it's back to top of the order Patrick. There are still snakes after you
you
Okay, I'm gonna try that. What do I roll?
I mean you could just run so just go uh, just do your full movement. I think you have 25 feet. Yeah
Oh, wait, what's the other just yeah, yeah, okay, so I run like here. Yeah
Yes, you just start running away
Um, do you want to do anything else while you're here or do you want to use your you can use both your movements?
If you want to okay, i'm gonna use both. Yeah. Yeah do that
I just leave vince and yousef with the snakes. Um
I I feel like I have to put this coin back
uh
And uh, yeah, it is now it's gonna be the snake's turn
so one of them
it
Let's see. What's his movement? Yeah, his movement I gave him was
I gave him like 35. Yeah
So they're they're gonna try to chase after you
Because you're putting the coin back. This one is still gonna try to fight you yousef
Um, he's gonna rear his head back
and uh... you're gonna see that uh... his teeth are green
thirty-eight irish green
you get ready to ask you
and uh...
the it he does it you
uh... he's a phone call
uh...
and he does
is nine damage to you so
you took would you take before you do you get you took
uh...
they have it over here so eleven
it eleven
and now you took nine
So you're at, uh, uh, Oh, you're dead.
You you're knocked out.
You said it was knocked out cold.
Uh, we're going to start doing death saving throws for you.
So, uh, uh, um, and, uh, it is now.
You Seth's turn too.
So you Seth rolled a D 20.
Okay.
You take one failure.
So you're slowly approaching death because of these snakes.
What do you see as death approaches you?
You're not dead yet.
What do you see?
I see in the distance a pitbull running towards the area.
Okay, yeah, you see your pitbull. You're like blinking in and out, like slowly blinking, and you see this ever faithful pitbull.
It has just like blood on it. Yeah, human leg in its mouth. It's like a ball pitbull.
I'm
penis hurts 'cause it's so big.
(laughing)
Oh, fuck me.
Ow, it's growing, ow.
- I guess we're all deception, yeah, on the snake.
- Oh, I'm being for real.
- Or no, what is it?
No, I roll against it, sorry.
The snake's charisma.
Technically, what you usually do in D&D,
when a creature can't even perceive that kind of thing,
you just don't.
But in this game, the snake can maybe tell
when somebody's in pain.
and he's very worried about you
he should be dude
it's sort of like
like quietly
and sweetly sort of like slithers over
to you and tries to look at your
penis to see if everything's okay
what the hell? get the fuck off me
yeah you just
punch it i guess yeah so
roll with advantage and attack on the snake
what do i roll?
with brass knuckles oh ok
mhm
Yeah, you hit and then roll that what you roll and then plus two more d6 after.
Okay.
Yeah.
Thirteen.
I mean, yeah.
Six.
Okay, yeah, you almost killed the snake.
You just like fucking like just like crushed its head with your fists into the ground.
You're gay, even though that's good here, I guess.
Whoops.
Yeah, and now it is your turn, buddy Bowser.
I'm just continuing towards the coins. Let's see. I think I might yeah, I reached the pot of gold.
Okay, what do you want to do?
I'm just I'm shoveling them into my mouth. I want to try to eat every single coin.
As you're eating the coins, the rainbow is slowly receding.
As you continue to eat the coins.
In character, I cannot reasonably stop eating these.
You see the leprechauns on top of the rainbow, they're like
You see the leprechauns on top of the rainbow like and then they see the rainbows starting to recede and they start running backwards
Yeah, you see the leprechaun on your back buddy
He's like, how did you turn the artists are trying to slap you get you to stop?
But he's just too little
Uh, and uh, yeah, well guess we'll have to resolve that. Um, it is now your turn again Keith benefits. Um,
Okay. Hold on. Let me see how much movement I have
because it would be
Funny you just killed roger clemens
Okay, is this enough room for me to do a drop kick murphy?
Yeah, yeah, you'll be five feet away. Okay. All right. I run and just do a drop kick murphy on him. Yeah
You stick to me perfectly perpendicular like you're about to the ground.
No, you hit him, you hit him though. Roll damage.
Okay, 11.
Yeah, you just fucking kick the shit out of, uh,
you stick to him, but you kick the shit out of Buddy Bowser.
I hit his neck while the coins are in and just like...
Buddy Bowser, roll, roll constitution to see if you like stop eating, uh, uh, the coins.
Like you, you're not able to keep going.
fifteen
you're going
i did i think you might have to take a good deal of a bunch of them back in
the area here you do see
and i'll buy you some more time also
but you do keep eating in your next heard uh... if that's like what your
character would do
you might just have to kill buddy has been stopped this from happening
uh... damage that i do the body you don't get a man you'd eleven something
else to eat give me something tasty
Yeah, okay. Well, we'll resolve that when it's your turn.
Now it is Yusef's turn / our faithful friend's turn.
So the dog is going to run over and he's going to lick your
wounds Yusef and you're going to get one HP back and then
the wounds are poison.
And so the dog is like, but he's still standing but he doesn't
look too good, but you have one HP back and so you can do
something this turn if you want to. I frailly pick up the gun and point it at Buddy Bowser.
Okay roll the- it's gonna kill him I'm telling you now. But if you do this you're going to
kill the character. Dude, that's just... Why did I give you that gun? What have I done?
Yeah, that hits him! 28! 36 damage? Buddy Bowser, you're dead. You're more than negative
your HP. What happens, Buddy Bowser? I fall... I'm like... I'm like... I'm like... I'm like...
like wobbling you know like I'm like kind of like like about to fall over and I
look at I look at Keith in the eyes and I say tell my mom I'm hungry and then the
entire contents of my stomach just floods out of my mouth and fills up the pot. You can't do a death
save so the way I do deaths in D&D is which people have different rules with
this
HP is like the idea. Buddy Dry Bones shows up. Dry Buddy. Like it's a wonderful world
of fantasy, maybe Buddy can come back in another way. You guys see my like my ghost like rise
up from my body and start rising towards heaven and it just touches a tree branch and gets
stuck
killed buddy
the product goals is filled again
the little leprechaun jumps on the product gold
he tips his beard
towards you keep
uh... for one last little poke
do i get a leash
can you get one wish which but it was still a lot
No, he's gonna eat the gold again, dude.
Don't fucking bring him back.
Okay, wait, yeah.
I wish Buddy was still alive and he stopped eating things.
You gotta have one wish.
Uh...
Hmm.
Clemmings?
Fuck, I forgot his name.
Roger Clemmons?
You can bring Roger Clemmons back.
Oh, I wish Buddy's, uh...
His soul's trapped in the tree.
So I wish that his soul
possessed Roger Clemens. You see the leprechaun like stare blankly at you like what the fuck
like what are you wishing for? I wish that my friend's soul. No no he understands it he's
just like why are you telling him. I wish that my friend's soul would transport into
to
the body of the crushed and shot Roger Clemens.
And Roger Clemens stands up and buddy, what does Roger Clemens sound like for you?
Hi guys.
I'm gonna go hang out in the doctor's office.
Just walk away.
And the leprechaun.
even waiting to see the finale just going straight to the
leprechaun flies up into the rainbow meets with all his
friends.
You guys wave goodbye to the leprechauns the snakes the
snakes at this point give up and vanish.
I don't think they have to keep fighting at this point.
It's kind of over and the camera zooms out on this beautiful
little town is beautiful rainbow on this perfect st.
Patrick's Day. And you see in the sky you hear it sounds like
sounds like sleigh bells ringing. And you hear ho ho ho it's me
St. Patrick
And uh, St. Patrick
And you see
He's so beautiful i'll have to post that visual
It's st. Patrick
I'll give everyone a visual aid when they're listening to this.
You should check the Discord or the Twitter and you'll see a visual aid I guess is what
we'll do.
And St. Patrick shows up.
Then Mary St. Patrick just belches and flies away.
The end.
Wow.
You really tied a boogaloo's end.
Yeah I made sure that the story made sense and everything.
That was so beautiful.
Thank you.
Happy Halloween everybody.
Yeah, Happy Halloween everyone.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[Music]