You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
- Hit record Joe.
You know that Joseph Gordon-
- What?
- Joseph Gordon-Levitt's Twitter handle.
- Oh yeah, his new thing he's doing.
- Does he still say hit record?
- If you have a stinky awful smell, send it to me.
I wanna smell it.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, you just tweet that.
old hit record on your webcam and never press stop send me the footage just
forget it sir do everything you don't tell mom don't tell mom yeah he has to
be a pedophile you have delicious dirt and mud under your fingernails and toes I
don't think I don't want he's a pedophile I think he's just like one of
those like like I don't know how to describe it I guess I guess it's just
like soy the is the way that like that's the only word that they really have for
it I call it I call it awesome culture where it's just guys who are like yeah
that's so awesome like guys who think everything is awesome guys you heard
that Lego song you call it awesome culture yeah you're trying to get
started it's not a thing I'm trying to get started I don't want to bring up
Joseph Gordon-Levitt see you could introduce us to no no no this is my
This is my coinage.
This is like a hot couch.
This is like the chad of potatoes.
Now I'm fucking, I'm regretting it so bad.
No, but you know, I actually, just randomly, you guys know Joseph Gordon-Levitt?
He's one of these guys I randomly call them awesome culture guys.
And they...
I don't know, I don't want to say, I don't want to say soy.
I don't want to say soy because it's played out.
I don't know what it's called, but I've heard some people, like people are saying awesome
culture. Yeah, like random people. I think I may have actually started it in my sleep.
But it's definitely going to catch on. You know what? You guys can make fun of me all
you want. I'm just going to keep calm and chive on. I just came up with this cool new
phrase called "You snooze, you lose." Which I think people are saying. I'm just going
to sit here and keep calm and chive on. I guess you're right though. If you want to
come up with something, you do have to force it on people. Because nobody started saying
"You snooze, you lose" until a guy was like, "So basically I came up with this new thing.
It's called like you snooze you lose.
And it's basically like if someone loses because they snooze.
I wish I thought of a funnier thing to say.
Awesome culture.
So wait, you... break it down for me.
I just don't want to say soy.
Did you enter into this episode knowing you were going to say awesome culture?
No, no I did not.
And have you said awesome culture before this episode?
No, I've never said it.
You said it, what about in your brain?
So you've never thought about it or said it before but you just said that you call it
awesome culture?
Yeah, pretty much.
You are lying dude.
You were like, this is going to be like, people are going to know this is like the day that
awesome culture started as a coin phrase.
Fuck off!
Fuck you!
I never said it before!
People are going to be like, oh awesome culture?
There's going to be a Wikipedia entry for awesome culture.
It'll be like origin.
they're gonna add it to the Oxford English Dictionary like they do when they add like
Google to the dictionary and everyone's like "WHOA!"
Wait you know my buddy Patrick came up with that?
They just added incel to the Oxford English Dictionary.
I didn't want to say soy!
Well you did though, you said it.
You said soy and then you were like "that's played out."
I actually called them "awesome culture."
Well no, no, because there's a delineation between soy and what I think is awesome culture.
Please elaborate!
Tell me what awesome culture is.
They're not like, cause Joseph Gordon-Levitt, I wouldn't call him a soy boy.
He's too handsome.
He's too handsome and he doesn't have a shitty beard and glasses.
He's just like one of these drug addict potheads.
It's like one of those, they're like.
The difference is there's, he's a celebrity.
Yeah.
Because I mean, every fucking, you know, Ryan Reynolds, he's.
That's an awesome culture guy.
No, it's just a soy guy who's been like, like, bred to look perfect.
Yeah. I guess that's, I guess that's what I mean by it.
Have you ever met an awesome culture guy in real life?
I have, yes.
Who is it?
Shia LaBeouf.
So you think what he did was awesome?
You think everything he's done is awesome?
No, no, he was like that though before he-
Yes, toxic awesome culture dude.
Oh, I'm sick of this toxic awesome culture shit.
No, that is the only famous person I think I've met. I talked about it, but...
And me.
No, Malin Akerman.
Oh, yeah.
She was there. Malin Akerman or Malin. I don't know.
Malin.
It's Irish.
Get a normal name.
Yeah, she's Swedish as shit.
Merlin.
Merlin Magic Man came into my... the first day at my last job. She was my first customer.
Yeah, and I was like, "Oh, now this guy right here,
here this is an example of magic culture before it's basically it's like a thing
I call people I would say like a warlock boy but he's like to play out he's
wizard ish I have so much I'm filled with so much regret constantly you've
now let this go and now it has no choice but to catch on right at least five
people listening this at some point are gonna make fun of me or just know they
will refer to somebody as being an awesome culture guy yeah some culture
guys awesome culture guys Joseph Gordon-Levitt he's one of them I think
Brad Leone from Bon Appetit yeah I would say they're in the same
binging with Babish I like that you know what about what about epic mealtime yes
yes Harley Morenstein so you're describing just epic guys yeah fuck fuck
you're right you're right I thought I had something what about Maddie Matheson is
he awesome culture yes yeah yeah yeah anybody yeah what about Hitler anybody
Anybody that you get lost in their eyes?
Anybody that it's like, they're kind of like Reddit guys,
but it's like, I like them.
You're just describing Reddit.
You're just describing like charming men.
Yeah.
Any guy with like confidence.
It's like guys, yeah, confident guys
that like the soy boys think they are,
is like gossip culture guys.
Yeah, exactly.
It's the soy gods.
Yeah, the gods of soy.
Yeah.
I should have said that.
I should have said that shit.
We wouldn't have made fun of you at all if you said "I like to call these guys the gods
of soy."
That would have gone over fine.
That was actually a soy boy.
He's more like a soy god.
He's on fucking Mount Soy-limp-us.
Soy-lint-opus.
And he's fucking just...
This guy's less of a soy guy and more like lint-y.
He's like a lint chocolate kind of guy.
He's very silky smooth.
What would you...
So what's a lint guy?
A lint guy...
Who's a German chocolate maker? Yeah, that's it. That's an artisan a Belgian artisan. Oh, Belgium. Yeah, come on
What about lint like laundry lint? That's I mean if you if you make a guy out of that
Hey, come on. Yeah, show me him. I want to see it
If you make a guy out of the laundry lint
You can have an electric power. Uh-huh. He's gonna yeah, it's gonna be like static shock. Oh
I'm so burping
Shut up, I'm hungover cuz I had that I went to the most insane party of all time you went to a party
Yeah, do the biggest party were you not invited to the party? That's so weird
I would have thought that you'd be there everyone you know was there except for you
Yeah, there's a humongous party with like all the shit that you want at a party
what and what happened there every wild thing you can imagine and
Hold on. Hold on, you know, you know, you know where the awesome culture thing came from in my head
where is the guy it was working in restaurants and it's guys who are like
if you have some stupid weird like it like the guys who are like who talked to
you about like the impossible meatballs or whatever and you're like yeah you
know it's like a hundred percent plant-based and like oh that's so
awesome honey come take a look at it like those
see that's what I thought that you were getting it like guys who say awesome
summer in the now that's its own culture yeah no it is it is like the guys culture
The guys who are really into CrossFit too.
Like guys who are like CrossFit is awesome guys and like
That's just like white people shit.
Yeah, I'm just describing white guys in their 30s.
Yeah, you're describing like upper middle class white guys.
Yeah.
I mean, yeah.
I guess that is awesome culture to upper middle class white guys.
Those guys are fucking awesome.
It does fall under awesome culture.
The thing is we're naming a lot of different types of people and they're all fall, it seems
like awesome culture maybe is a bigger term than like reddit guy or beard guy
or 30 year old white guy I think awesome culture might have legs I mean we're
gonna see where it goes after this dude. Anybody who acts in a way that's awesome is kind of cool.
Guys who like awesome things. Yeah yeah no it's very obvious that they're like cool
in their in their private life or they're cool in like social situations
but it's annoying that it's that they're cool people. I you know what I mean? I
feel like you're making it more complicated than it needs to be. It's hey
man I didn't create it. God bestowed me with the term awesome culture. Yeah.
Showing it to people. I got hit I got hit with God's lightning bolt. Yeah. I'm coming down
from the mountain with the tablets of awesome culture. Uh huh. Explaining to the people. Trying to make awesome culture catch on like going to like
sneaking into like a DSA meeting and raising your hand like what are we gonna do?
What are we gonna do with awesome culture?
Do you guys know what I'm talking about?
Oh my god, hold on.
Here's my book.
Delineating Awesome Culture.
A study in upper middle class white men who say awesome.
Uh-huh and then semicolon.
And also guys who are soy or have beards and epic meal time.
and maybe and a guy who likes impossible meatballs?
Parenthesis, Joseph Gordon-Levitt vibes.
Yeah.
Yeah, serious Joseph Gordon-Levitt vibes.
At least I didn't say Jared Leto. I feel like Jared Leto vibes is...
Why would, why at least? Why would it matter?
Yeah, what does that mean?
People would have gotten mad because people would have been like, "He's not awesome,
Gordon's not awesome at all."
Right, people would have gotten very mad.
He's crazy culture.
Yeah, he's psycho culture.
Which is another thing you've been working on.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Yeah. So what's psycho culture?
So it's kind of like hyper normalization.
You have my interest.
So it's kind of like how Jared Leto is obsessed with manufacturing consent.
Yeah. He hates it or loves it or he feels one way about it for sure.
I don't know. These are just things I've heard and I'm throwing them around.
Yeah. I agree.
Oh, fuck.
I've heard of Noam Chomsky but I don't know what he does. He's a breakdancer. He, I assumed that he
lived in a garden and he ate the plants and the farmer had to... And he was a chomsky. And the
farmer had to keep him away from eating his plants. He's a chomsky because he chomps so much. He
chomps on the carrots. Okay, all right. You're getting somewhere. We could get him on the podcast.
We tried once. Yeah, we did. We were the first. He tried to schedule it. Yeah. What did he say?
He kept blowing us off.
He would respond, but he'd be like,
"I can't do it right now.
"I'm actually busy for a couple months,
"but maybe in June."
- Yeah, he'd be like, "Email me again in June."
- Yeah, and then we emailed him.
- And then he'd email us back and be like,
"Yeah, yeah."
- Yeah, stuff's so crazy.
And it's funny that the second time they emailed me,
I was kinda like, "What the fuck's your problem, man?"
(laughing)
Like, seriously? - Stop responding.
- Yeah, like, what are you,
you're really just leading us on like this?
- What do you have to do?
Like, what do you, do you have nothing going on?
We already made this fucking poster dude.
Yeah.
What the fuck do you have to do man?
It's a boxing poster and it's us versus you.
And we had that shit printed.
It's all over Boston.
Yeah.
It's in Cambridge too.
We used wheat paste dude.
We went old school.
We fucking hung them up.
We hung it up everywhere.
Yeah.
You don't see enough of those.
they should do a pay-per-view fight with gnome chopsky on barstool
that'd be good you don't see any more what the the wheat pasted posters to like
sides of buildings whatever happened a lot in new york but
it's always like now it's like a rapper that
doesn't exist yeah yeah ricardo ricardo montalban
yeah new album is coming out that's the rapper's name
It's a different guy, Ricardo Montalban. It's uh, his name is also Ricardo Montalban.
I always like that when people try to tear him down and then there's another one right under it.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's pretty funny to just double make double do your poster so somebody
spends a bunch of time trying to get it off. It's like oh fuck, fucking fatty,
fatty penises, money on my ass.
Here's an idea.
Again.
So you, so you hang up one poster, right?
Yeah.
With the intention of it being ripped down.
okay so it's also promoting along the edges oh shit mm-hmm so you hang up one
poster it's kind of shitty and then you when they try to rip it down there's an
even better poster under it but it's both of the posters are promoting your album
and when they try to rip that down there's a window behind it you're
standing in the window and you're pointing your gun at them your arms are
crossed yeah what have you like what have you like sealed a live bat
underneath the poster. So that when they when they undo it, they...
A dead bat falls on the ground.
No, no.
Is it suffocated?
No, no. It's like a freeze-dried bat and then it rehydrates.
And then it comes back to life and flies with them.
The air, the water vapor in the air is enough to just melt it, to thaw it out instantly.
Well, no. You would have a contraption designed that dropped water on the bat.
There's fishing line attached to the poster too.
Yeah, you pull down the poster and it just there's just a thing that says please wait and a little elevator door and you just
Hear a bunch of clicks and clacks and like thumping and then after a minute the doors open in a bad
The contraption is they just they poke the bat a bunch yeah
The guy you pay they have a camera above the poster so the bat can see the person's face that's taking down the poster
Yeah, and also you think it's the one you're wearing like you're wearing like a mask like it's like a TV helmet
And it's got the person's face on the TV screen, so it looks like you're you're poking the bat
But it looks like you're the person's face. Oh
That's pretty smart actually that'd be some crazy shit. It'd be some fucking
sci-fi
Original movie maybe some awesome shit. Yeah, I'm on my awesome culture shit
I'm never gonna live that down. Damn. Nope, you won't. No, I'm gonna keep bringing it up probably forever. Yeah, I
Don't get ready. Well, I don't care now. Yeah, I don't even care
Those guys I'll just I got one of those guys. All right, show me. Okay. Oh, wow. Oh
That's awesome. Oh
Wow
You're not making any sense of these awesome cultures. They just show me what it's like okay. Oh wow
It's not what he sounds like
Okay, all right, I wish I wish I was more articulate to explain what I'm or just shows or to play
Wow, oh wow, oh wow
This is can I do this is what I think Austin culture is like, okay, damn
for real
See that's a that is even a little clearer than oh wow. Yeah. Yeah
- Yeah.
- Oh man.
(laughing)
- Here's my impression of it.
- I wish I could have explained this better.
- Here's my impression.
- Yeah, do it.
- Okay, ready?
What was that?
It'd be something like that.
(laughing)
It's like an awesome culture, I hate those guys.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, this awesome culture guys always come to you
and you're like, "Hey man, what's up?"
- Yeah, yeah.
- It's fucked up.
- Hey, happy birthday man.
fuck those guys. Oh it's your birthday? Oh we gotta sing for you. Yeah oh happy
Easter man I hope you like your eggs. Shut up dude. Yeah. They're not real eggs.
He doesn't get it. Yeah. Here's the mail. Shut up you awesome
culture piece of shit. Fucking idiot. Pussy. Alright. I cannot think about
awesome culture anymore. They drive me insane. I'm going insane because I can't
fucking articulate what I mean it will lose I it will lose my mind if I can
see it's already I'm going fucking nuts over here I don't know you're hitting
your head with a coconut right now stop fuck it I'm participating in awesome
culture when I do that see now there's even more stop adding things dude
yeah come on can we just do the list stop adding awesome culture fucking no
I'm adding more attributes as the show goes on.
I hate attributes!
Stop!
Awesome Culture guys are always using attributes on me.
They're always describing their features.
I hate the attributes of an Awesome Culture guy.
I hate Awesome Culture culture.
The people who just won't stop talking about Awesome Culture.
Don't even get me started.
Hey, you shut up.
I'm talking about you, Patrick.
What?
Yeah.
19 minutes you have been talking about awesome culture the whole time. I'm sick
here's my impression of awesome culture culture guys. Oh wow yeah right shut up.
Very true. And then I'm like yeah you shut up. I hate awesome culture but I
love but I remember when we had awesome creatures like the Abominable
snowman. Uh-huh. Let's just go back dude. Fuck. Fuck. All right can we do this list? Yeah.
All right this is oods that make you fart. This from the top tens, top ten foods
that make you fart. Number one baked beans. Ain't that a kick in the head.
I even wrote a poem about it.
Who wrote a poem?
You know, beans, beans.
Yeah, I guess you're right, but they don't say baked.
Baked beans, baked beans.
Oh, you're right.
I forgot about that version.
The baked fruit.
I forgot about Weird Al's version.
Do you guys remember Baked Beans from Whitest Kids You Know?
No.
Nope.
the comments okay what are you doing today I don't know I'm I'm this close to just
getting at you the baby beans I had last night maybe really gassy and it came in
handy since it was fart in the sorority pledges face night so it was time to go
over and by that time the gas was really one time to assume the position when the
first pledge had put her nose to sniff my butt I blasted one right in her face it
It was funny to hear a bunch of girls scream, keep farting in their face as pledge after pledge ended up gagging from the smell of my farts.
I bet their noses burned from smelling all the farts I farted last night.
Even after I came home and went to bed, I woke myself up by farting really loud in bed.
That's not real.
Next stats.
For lunch yesterday we had hot dogs and my wife made her famous baked beans.
Every time she makes them I load up on them.
After we ate I had to saw some pieces of wood with a handsaw.
As I was sawing, my belly started rumbling with gas.
I felt a fart brewing and I let it rip.
It was loud and smelled.
she walked outside to ask me something and she walked right into the fart cloud
she wrinkled her face at the smell I continued farting all afternoon okay so
what we got Nick Offerman and a sorority girl talking about their baked beans
and they both love to fart for lunch yesterday we had hot dogs for lunch
yesterday we had hot dogs yeah there we go you have the impression yeah in my
wife he farted in his wife my wife is this the same one this is the same guy
no this is from gross dude he says we just ate dinner hot dogs and baked beans
after dinner I went to clean the bathrooms didn't take long for the gas to
I felt a gas bubble in my ass and when I started to bend over and clean I let it rip
And I just kept farting my girlfriend said she not only heard them, but also smelled them
I have chronic gas issues and fart all the time my girlfriend says I'm the gassiest 22 year old man ever
The gross dude yes, I love yes, yeah, just being specific about how gassy you are
Fucking name. I'm the gassiest firefighter in the
Sink yes, he has like five other comments on here on this page like a little specific item like on baked on baked beans
Oh my god
He does I think I have a feeling all of these are written by him my girl lean the hard ones without nails
My girl learned the hard way not to stand behind me when I have bad gas
I had baked beans for dinner and afterwards while I was cleaning the bathroom
My girl was standing behind me while I was scrubbing the toilet and I had to fart really bad
I was bent over and I basically farted in her face and it really stunk. It's the same story
I just had a meal. Here's the next one. Yeah read this
These are all from gross - I just had a meal hot dogs and baked beans and I chowed down on the beans after dinner
I went to play my baritone saxophone
Then the gas kicked in I was farting like crazy as I was playing my instrument
As my girlfriend said she could hear me farting, but nobody could hear me farting, but she could smell it
She said every time I fart it smells like what I ate and they always stink.
Alright, keep going. Next gross dude comment.
I had a veggie combo at a Mexican restaurant last night and refried beans.
At the concert I just performed in, I think my ass made as much noise as my instrument.
I could feel myself farting and I'm not sure how anyone in the band didn't throw up from the smell
because not only were the farts really loud, they also smelled.
I love the story he's created here.
I mean, it's a universe here.
The gassiest 22 year old
who plays a baritone saxophone
which sounds like farts
*snickers*
The next three in a row are all about sports.
Football and soccer.
I'm gonna read the next gross dude.
Another gross dude about football.
"I play football, and the only job I have as the fullback
is to block for the running back.
I load up on beans, and the running back knows
what way to go is by the sound
and smell of my farts. I'm not kidding.
I fart the entire game."
God damn this guy here's another gross dude right here wait I want to read this
non gross do one really quick okay I stuffed I stuffed up on beans and in two
seconds I was trumping like a trooper when I came downstairs my sister fainted
and had a horrid look on her face then the pizza guy came and called the
paramedics that didn't happen to the line baked beans make me fart a ton I was
standing by my girlfriend and I felt my tummy rumble then I blasted this huge
fart and man did it stink she was really grossed out by the smell but I did warn
her that I had gas and the hiccups from the beans. Dude, gross dude's a fucking long suffering girlfriend. I had the hiccups too. My heart goes out to gross dudes.
Here's a comment. I am a girl I don't often fart but I just had beans my boyfriend and I
can't believe how much I am farting tonight just love that smell baby
Natalie Soden.
My friend is Mexican, so he eats lots of beans, so he farts all the time.
Come on.
That's just facts.
If you soak your bean twice and discarding the cold water each time, and then you cooking it, it should not create any more gas in your belly.
I found more gross dude.
Just wanted to share that I'm sitting in the break room at work, eating lunch and tooting.
We, here's another one, we had a cookout tonight with lots of baked beans. Caused a lot of gas,
especially my grandfather, who is known for his epic farts. I never heard anyone fart
as long or as loud as him. Anytime he ate, he had gas. You would hear a rumble followed
by a really loud, long fart.
Here's a good one. Oh, where'd it go?
No.
Here's one. Oh wait, I found it. So one night I eat baked beans. I fart a few times and my
wife is checking for dog poop I have a youtube channel called sausage lover 99
please check it out this is from one way street oh I remember the day it was all
wet the one right after that is shredded my
under crackers once after eating a family
that's leo shredded my under crackers
oh he's of shredded my under crackers
shredded ago the family to you are going
to get a bellyache if you eat too much
baked beans how is there a hundred and
forty what here's it there's a hundred
forty one comments here and here's one
that says I farted on your website they
they give you nice long one lol you will fart all day beans are awesome i ate just a spoonful
of beans then suddenly his saw i farted silently my mom was upstairs when she smelt it she dropped
her water on the bed my mom's water oh my god oh god oh it smells so oh the baby's coming
oh there's a there's really long scripts holy shit wait go to the last page yeah you have
to read these scripts oh my god all right the first one who we have Henry Ralph
and Peter it's so fucking why does every single list have us like a script in it
why do people write scripts on this look you got to get your you got to get your
shit out there somehow that's true all right who wants to be Henry many eyes on
it as possible I can be I'll be Ralph I'll be Peter I'll be Henry I don't get
it it's supposed to be making all the electricity we need why do you need to
electricity it's just there isn't it we're saving energy our house runs on
wind power except it's not running at all the TV hardly works and the racetracks
are stuck in first gear what is this I think you need a lot more wind to power
all that this is so unfair how are we going to make more wind what would Fred
Fartwell do Ralph and Henry eat from a can of baked beans so do fang and fluffy
Who the fuck are Fang and Fluffy?
This has to be from a show or something.
Mom and Dad want wind power. They're going to get wind power.
They high five with their spoons, then later they fart outside.
What? Poo-erg.
He and Ralph hold their noses. They look at each other. So do Fluffy and Fang. I'm guessing those are animals.
Wait a minute. If we're out here farting, we can't be inside watching TV.
They run back in only to find the TV turning off. It's already out of power.
What a sad ending.
Yeah, we out here farting fluffy and fangered
There their hat one of their Hagrid's pets. I looked up all right. I'm um
I'm not oh
These all oh yeah, cuz it's Henry. Yeah, Henry Potter
Henry Potter Henry Potter
Ralph Weasley
Yeah
Let's move to number two yeah, he's oh
Oh here we go. This one, this is my favorite comment that I, that I've seen so far I think.
I got this friend named Grayson. He had cheese during the day and now he wouldn't quit farting
under the covers. He said he is proud of his creation but it lingers like a lost soul.
Oh my god. It lingers like a lost soul. Oh here's one from Gross Dude. I had four slices
of cheese pizza late after work and I'm paying the price by making toots in bed and I let
out several big burps to get the gas out so I thought I was all good.
If the gross food is to be believed by the way, he has on multiple occasions
revisited this list to catalog his farts from the night prior.
There's this this guy who said he had a friend named Grayson, he commented again
right after and said "I got this friend by the name Grayson. Apparently he had
cheese during the day, now he cannot quit farting under the blanket. I mean it's
lingering hardcore like a lost soul."
He's really trying to make his expressions stick.
He's kind of doing an awesome culture type thing.
Yeah, you ever heard of that?
Farts sometimes linger like a lost soul.
Yeah, hardcore.
It's something I recently came up with.
Somebody's trying to dispute the friend Grayson's claims here and saying, "First of all, nobody,
and I mean nobody in the entire world has a friend named Grayson, so right there your
story is too ludicrous for words.
Asking us to believe that you had a friend named Grayson is like asking us to believe
in Santa Claus the Easter Bunny or the cystic fibrosis fairy gross dude says I'm
tooting in the break room right now what's the cystic fibrosis I've been
farting from 5 p.m. to 10 p.m. every three minutes smelled like green peppers
and mustard gas my dad busted out the gas mask from the SWAT team it was meaty
my dad's on the SWAT team my dad's on the SWAT team and basically he swats me
every time I fart at my desk spigotty with cheese on the top SPI GGE TY
spigotty with cheese on the top and my brother almost killed me that night with
his stink I farted so big my dad thought there was a skunk in the house love
Dallas oh I I want to meet all these people I know I smell their farts I feel
like at least half of these have to be gross dude right yeah I mean gross dude
is he's he's let he's been waiting for a platform just to show xxxxx killer
machine xx comments I am a Packers fan she's had did you got onions yeah onions
which I don't think is that true does it I don't know I don't know but this
comment is bad breath for sure this comment here is suspicious I think it
might be gross dude. I'm thinking it is, why don't you read it out. Before practice with
my jazz band I had a cheesesteak with onions and onion rings for lunch. I'm the only guy
in the band which is very small but awesome. As I was driving to practice my stomach started
making noises. Right before practice I let out a muffled but pretty loud belch. The saxophonist
next to me was like "you have gas?" I thought it would help but as soon as we started playing
the farts started blasting out of my ass. It was like loud music coming out of my
bass sax and my booty except the ones out of my booty really stunk and the
smell wafted through the room. Some of the girls faces show that they were
grossed out by how bad they smelled. Well this is not him because he plays a
baritone this guy plays a bass sax. That's true yeah he couldn't be the same
person. I had a cheesy mash with lots of almost raw onions in it and then an hour
later all of hell broke loose the three cats are wide-eyed and ears pricked
every time another mushroom cloud of onion stink is emitted if they survived
the fallout they're going straight to a pet shrink to be checked for PTSD the
funniest thing is how these malevolent ass male strums defy logic by smelling
more like onions than onions itself themselves it's almost beautiful oh did
I I mean I do believe this is all gross dude it's gotta be yeah I think like who
made the list it's about a sit grocery made the list for sure nobody made the
list just it's always been there yeah yeah it's about a six-hour wait period
after eating an onion dish before they begin my farts could easily be mistaken
for an onion scented propellant lots of gas
other foods don't seem to have anywhere near the same effect I use leaks as a
substituting cooking when appropriate. He uses leeks? Yeah, ass leeks. Yeah, that's
that's fucking for sure, brother. Yes, sir. Damn. I don't, I've never had an onion
fart. I don't know if you guys have. Yeah, I think it might be like a specific
thing. Maybe I have them and I don't know. I think it's a thing. I think I've heard of it before.
Now I'm gonna have to test this theory. Yeah, I'm gonna have to eat a whole onion.
Onion like from holes. Yeah, I'm just gonna walk around fucking
My blast and my onion propellant
My ass ate some ramen with fried onions been farting for about eight hours now smells like rank mushroom
If your onion smell like a musher or your onion fart smell like a mushroom you gotta get your shit
Yeah, you're if you're mushroom smelling farts come from onions if mushroom for
For you might be a redneck
You smell an onion scented propellant that might be a fart
If you're making a bacon cheese lasagna with bacon and bacon and bacon
you might be an awesome culture guy. If you're in a jazz band with only one guy in it and
he's playing the bass sax and his instrument starts to smell real bad, he might be farting.
He might be gross dude. You might be a gross dude if you have an onion smelling propellant
that you spray out your ass every time you walk past. I found a schizophrenic comment
on the end of this onion.
- Oh.
- What does it say?
- Okay, we have discovered that not only do onions lay eggs,
they also reproduce at four times the size of their self
on a daily basis.
They also attended the orthodontist for braces treatment
and then a corn emoji and cabbage squad.
- That's not schizophrenic, that's just random as hell.
- I farted Thor this food.
I farted, I barley ever fart.
- Number four is some really good gross dude once again.
numbers eggs of course
this is this is really good
had like twelve double bags of my boyfriend's family cookout and i had so
much flatulence bubbly low-pitched duck farts slipped out here and there
i was most embarrassed when his uncle flex
i don't know so i let a big one about seven seconds long and he said
who baby girl that makes done did something vicious to those guts that
part was belt bubbly is house smell like you just put some warm eggs salad under
my nose damn then he walked away and I seek tried to secretly fan the smell
that's what I immediately know what flex looks like what he sounds like I know
what he's wearing I know where he lives
flex is literally uncle flex is leaping off the page he's wearing a cangle cap
uncle flex heard this girl fart and he knew immediately it was eggs yeah he knew
the eggs done did that eggs done did something something vicious to you baby
girl he liked it also that's he was like he was like like a sommelier he was like
like wafting it into his mouth yeah I was in history and I had a bad case of
bubble gut so I walked in front of this really annoying guy and I went until I
felt my horrible flatulence bubble around and I said here Larry deviled eggs and I
realized I released the bubbliest horrifically gassy fart in his face and
after the eight second long fart I walked away and stood there and that boy and boy
that fart stunk like I'd given him a deviled egg platter I said whoo-whee and
slowly fanned the fart away.
That's also Uncle Flegg's.
I think Uncle Flegg's maybe wrote this one too.
Whoa Nelly, I'll tell ya, I had an omelette for breakfast and I farted the whole way to
school and the whole day in it.
Super long and extremely bubbly farts smacked their way out of tight jeans and into the
faces of many freshmen on the steps.
Uncle Flex's tight jeans.
They smacked their way out.
Damn.
I'm thinking about Uncle Flex now.
Yeah, Uncle Flex is walking around with like leather skinny jeans with like a fart stuck in it.
A Hawaiian shirt.
Like a kink in a hose.
Just getting ready to fucking absolutely let loose on some lady.
Just like a bubble, a bubble in a fucking, in a pair of leather pants.
Yeah, like an animal stuck in a snake in a cartoon.
Yeah, like when you get those in a box from Amazon or whatever where it's those packets
of air.
Yeah, yeah, it's just one of those, just ready to absolutely own some lady.
I had eggs for breakfast and all day at school I was letting out airy ones in class.
The best part was when I was talking to a friend and my butt was facing a group I hate
and I let out a ten second hot one.
I was just close enough to one boy that it blew his hair back a little.
No one knew it was me though.
Did not.
Blowing someone's hair back with a fart.
I have six hard boiled eggs a day.
They make me fart a hell of a lot.
Mix that with vegetables that contain soluble fiber like broccoli and peas and you're going
to constantly smell like you shat yourself.
Worst farts I ever had were 30 plus in one night.
Oh no, I had eggs for dinner on my hamburger.
I am planning on farting in my brother's room when he is in the shower.
It is going to stink, epic.
I'm Asian and my parents make me eat it so I fart a lot.
You do not want to smell my farts after eggs.
Once after breakfast I farted for 10 seconds straight, no joke.
Damn, no cap.
No cap.
That's how my farts smell.
I have a friend named Brooke.
Megan says hi.
I get nervous every time she eats eggs or beets.
Way to put Brooke on the fucking spot like that Survivor 101.
Someone just commented "Egg won"
*laughter*
Yep, egg makes you fart the most.
I had a egg buddy at 5 o'clock
and all I keep doing is farting.
Oh, like an egg sandwich?
No, like an egg buddy.
An egg buddy.
Yeah, I was gonna ask about an egg buddy.
Like a friend.
Like a friend who is egg.
I ate my egg buddy.
No, you didn't.
Here's a comment from Red the Gremlin.
(laughing)
- Okay.
- Curry, number five.
- Curry, curry's up there for me.
This will make me, I mean just everything gives me diarrhea.
I think I discovered that having a sip of milk
will give me diarrhea now.
My life is awesome.
- I mean are you just lactose intolerant?
- I have no idea, I didn't think I was.
And then I just was like, you know,
it just doesn't feel right.
No, I've been the same since I was a baby.
I think I gradually became lactose intolerant over time.
If I can eat any ice cream but if I eat Ben and Jerry's I'm fucking, I'm letting out.
It's the love which is a secret ingredient you're allergic to.
Yeah.
Make you shit.
It's all that freaking Vermont weed they're sprinkling into that ice cream to train kids.
To CBD.
To poison children.
I'm not gonna stop drinking milk because I will never let God win a single time in my
life.
Ben and Jerry are in a-
- I'm trying to define my nature.
- Ben and Jerry are in a giant, like, dark fortress and they have a huge cauldron full
of ice cream and they're stirring it and they're going, "Mehehehehe!"
And sprinkling in weed and socialism.
- I hate those drug addict pieces of shit.
- I see those track marks on you, Ben.
I know what you've been doing.
- Come on, hey, it's Adam and Eve, not Ben and Jerry.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Stop fucking each other and fucking cumming in the ice cream.
over the ice cream that yeah disgusting fucking disgust smoking a smoke a doobie
and fucking each other over the ice cream beds fuck you dude fucking disgust me
it was crazy how that the the story broke after they released that flavor
milky ropes yeah Ben and Jerry they threw some milky ropes onto the
chunky dunks turn you to turn you to blammin Jerry fuck you you did yeah Jerry
Jerry's fine you can keep Jerry Jerry you're cool I know back I know that Ben
talked you into all this fucking I was gay fucking we did but do you think
Jerry from Ben and Jerry's is the same Jerry from Tom and Jerry's Oh which one
is Jerry and Tom Jerry he's the mouth he's the ice cream one yeah the mouse is
a good guy. Yes, you're right. He kind of is the ice cream one. He loves food. They both
love food. No, Tom hates food. That's true. Tom likes milk. Yeah, he likes milk. But Jerry
does too and it kind of makes for a bunch of playful situations. That's why he wants
to eat them. He's made out of ice cream. Ice cream and a drink. Yep. Five seconds of silence
Patrick said that. Patrick says that Jerry from Tom and Jerry's made out of ice cream.
You're right. Also, yeah I mean I guess, okay. Oh well. Yeah, he's made out of ice cream.
You're right. I had to do the logic in my head. I had to do the math. Here's a, um,
here's another, here's a comment on curry. I think this might be somebody who commented
earlier I kept waking myself up last night trumping like a trooper
trumping like a trooper dude here's that that's good there's another my wife is
asleep on the couch she came to the bedroom and started checking the floor
for dog poo only to discover the smell was from between the sheets haha I was
here's I was asleep on my bed and poo was smudged on my face I don't think that
has anything to do with what you ate. I think you got pranked on Jackass.
You got hit with the Brandon DiCamillo congratulations.
Yeah. Number six Brussels sprouts.
Ooh that's my favorite food. Brussels sprouts smell bad just being out.
No they don't. Yeah it's kind of the same. They smell but they're good.
I mean I like Brussels sprouts but they're good. They smell like fucking shit dude.
I've never had a smelly Brussels sprout. They don't taste smelly if they're raw
and they like sit on your counter for more than like 90 seconds.
Oh I guess I just don't do that.
Awful dude.
I guess I'll have to.
I'll have to think of it.
You don't leave them out for more than 90 seconds because they're gone.
That's right because I'll I'll fucking smell the fart smell and I fucking slurp them up.
Yeah.
Just shooting them.
The brussel sprout is part of the cruciferous.
It's amazing that we do a podcast where Pat's job is to read.
"Cruciferous" vegetable family.
- Maybe. - "Cruciferous."
- What does that mean? - No, it's "cruciferous."
- You're right. - "Cruciferous beuler."
"Vegetable family and naturally causes gas.
"Usually dairy has me farting like a Clydesdale,
"but this is just as bad."
(laughing)
- Do Clydesdale, I guess I've never heard a horse fart.
I've seen a horse shit all the time.
- Oh yeah.
- Those horses fart, too.
- Those horses got, they got fart around.
- The reason I know that is 'cause
in I would always read like joke books as a kid and there would always be jokes
where it's like the whole like about horses farting it's just like a thing in
like that type of joke I mean I always read those kinds of joke books always
have like specific topics they joke about yeah I told you about the one that I had
that was all about is all about leprosy yeah yeah exactly there's like a person
who wrote the book just has like one fixation that they end up writing like
20 jokes about. I guess it's a hundred and one jokes you got to fill up. I guess I am
aware of in movies a horse farting and his tail pops up. Exactly yeah. It makes
me wish I had a tail. Well what if they don't what if horses don't actually fart
that much and it's just the visual in the movie was so funny that it became a
thing. Maybe horses can't even fart. Maybe horses don't shit. Maybe when horses fart
their tail gets sucked into their butt. Mm-hmm. And they might have a reverse
fart going on and they burp they burp and it sucks in air from there through the
butt of the horse we should work at the zoo we should work at all my three
should work it at the zoo and we should be in charge of explaining the animals
to all the we hey we work at the morning zoo am i right you're you're listening
the podcast about this radio yeah yeah we're gonna call some we're gonna call
someone on the phone and call them gay yeah yeah here I'm gonna call this
fucking gay guy Patrick Doren BBBBBBB hello hey what's up
your day.
(imitating a gay guy)
I'm a gay guy. You heard it first on the podcast.
It's just tuning into the
morning radio show and it's just
(imitating a gay guy)
And then it just cuts
in and that's why Nancy Pelosi's
a pedophile.
And it's just the emergency broadcast sound
for ten minutes.
(laughing)
- Comment on Brussels sprouts in all capitals.
I am working on all types of sprouts.
- Brussels sprouts made me leave the room,
left the hamster behind, RIP Hammy.
- It's so fucked up to get a hamster and name it Hammy.
- Yeah, yeah.
- It's like you couldn't think of anything.
At least, even like Hamwise is better than Hammy.
- Yeah.
Hamwise the hamster that's pretty good right? Hamwise Gamgee. Actually you should work at a pet store.
Fuck a zoo. You should be in charge of naming all that. You should work at the puppy mill. I'm good at naming
animals. We've been thinking about getting a dog and I just saw a dog whose name was Jexter.
They dude they the people that work at pet shelters fuck up those rescued animals. He was heavily abused and he
is so afraid of humans. It's so like. I'd be afraid too of a human named me
Well they give them like new names at the show.
I bet that the people that work there, they start out naming them like, "Oh, this one's
Fido, this one's Rex," and they run out and they're like, "Oh, okay, then I'm gonna name
this guy's Legos, this guy's like Mega Bloks."
You also just get such fucked up names after a while.
You get fucked up names because every like Rob and Susie that you named ended up getting
lethally injected in front of you and you're like, "All right, I'm never attaching any sort
of real names."
My dog's name before, like when we adopted her, her name was Fudge.
How fucked up is that dude?
That's a good name though.
It's horrible.
That's a good name.
Can you imagine yelling that across the dog park?
Oh man, fudge!
What if it's like a dog that gets away, like you're like devastated because it runs into
traffic.
Fudge!
No!
Like what if you're like, what did you do to Fudge?
Like John if the John wick dog was named fudge
Might as well like name the dog like dump or something
I would name it dog. He is a good one
Dookie is such a good dog name if I did not have a woman involved in this I would be naming a dog dookie
Right now is my dog shit dude
my dog do do do keep -
Dookie-do. Dennis Dookie. This is my dookie dog. Diarrhea doo-doo. Dookie David.
Diarrhea dump in his ear. I named him after my favorite song. Douglas Diarrhea.
Dookie poopie. This is the dookie dog. Yeah, it's short for dookies of hazard. This is my poop dog.
Yeah, he's a chocolate lab. He's basically a poop dog. Yeah, he's named exactly as
what he is my mom when my cousin got a dog and my mom got mad at my my cousin
because he this is like when we were younger because he suggested the name
crayon yeah that's a bad name yeah my my better name for a kid my brother's dog's
name is fucking crash bandicoot stupid number seven eggplant this is my least
favorite vegetable it's crazy that they got them both yeah I hate eggplant. I don't like eggplant very much either.
I love eggplant dude. It's because you're Italian you're genetically predisposed to liking eggplant.
My wife touched my belly and I sounded like a chainsaw dang eggplant.
Oh man the egg and eggplant sandwich you remember that?
That thing sucked. Yeah that thing is terrible. I tried it once just because it was like
Are you putting a fucking-
Wait, wait, wait.
GrossDude's back on the next one.
We gotta step ahead.
Yes!
He's back on.
Number 8, Broccoli.
This first comment doesn't have a name on it.
It's absolutely GrossDude.
Had broccoli at work.
Horrible mistake.
It was my first day on the job and I was so nervous.
I get the worst flatulence when I'm nervous.
Farts smelled absolutely atrocious.
God, I was so embarrassed.
I knew everyone could hear and smell the gassy farts coming from my cubicle.
Later I was on the elevator with another guy and I farted a bad one.
I got really nervous and said I was sorry as I quickly fanned my butt as a couple other
loud ones bubbled out.
And he said it was fine.
to everyone. Later I decided to take the stairs to relieve some gas only to fart
a bubbly broccoli fart in a hot intern's face. Why is your ass... how tall are you dude?
Why is your ass always in people's faces?
They've got Ewoks in the internship program.
I just remembered like when I was a kid and I would go to like youth group I
would always get super gassy and have but I thought that it would be really
embarrassing if I like went to the bathroom all the time I thought people
would be like oh yeah that kid loves going to the bathroom or something so I
would just like lay on the floor on my back during youth group because it like
helped relieve the pain I was like this is way cooler than going to the bathroom
nobody thinks this is weird yeah I was so awesome here's the gross dude comment
yeah and this he has some of his classic themes going here if you want to have
bad gas just eat broccoli I was waiting downstairs to help my grandfather I knew
he was coming when I heard a bunch of loud farts coming from him. He toots all
the time when he doesn't eat broccoli anyway. There wasn't anything I could do
he was just sawing wood with a handsaw and as he was sawing he was farting at
the same time. When he finished he ripped another huge long one.
I-
Wait, see, he doesn't even eat broccoli in this. He just mentions that it'll give you
brought it'll give you bad gas and then tells a story
yeah see what it's like to talk to me gassy farts at a funeral it was terrible
I farted as we walked around to observe the casket and everybody had to walk
into my gassy cloud of farts I tried to fan the farts away but an elderly woman
caught me and said so you're the one who's got the place smelling like egg
salad what did you eat sonny boy here's a here's a comment here my broccoli fars
are warm and stink like eggs it's FARR apostrophe s haha I had to laugh when I
saw this list but yes my confession is that broccoli can keep me up all night I
rip ads every time I eat this broccoli the shooting machine not gonna have it
in my dinner anymore I am firing like an idiot my ex used to blow me away at
night
he's back
the king returns
the break room
party
uh...
gaseous city
to pick up the break room
Number nine is pizza.
Hold on, I found a comment on the second page.
I found a comment, "I fart too much due to my unhealthy obsession with pizza."
That's from Pizza Guy.
"I do fart and smelling Italy. Absolutely disgusting."
(laughing)
- All right, number 10, soft drinks.
Bunch of gross dude ones in a row here.
- What?
- I've never farted after drinking soda.
- Okay, we just gotta get through
these gross dude soft drink ones.
- Okay, it doesn't make me fart, but gives me the burps.
Don't chug it before a game.
Imagine playing fullback in a football game
while blocking players while you had a case of the burps.
It also gave me a really bad case of the hiccups
the whole game.
was blocking all everyone heard the entire game was my hiccups and a big
burp
then the second one not only does Pepsi make a may fart a lot but it makes me
belt really loud that's why I am known as the belching blocking back all the
running back has to do is follow the sound of the fart or the belts coming
from me to know where I'm going to block and he can get the most yards and the
best part is the stink of the fart lingers I drink coke before a football
game perfect for a caffeine buzz but when you're blocking another player and you
get hit in the stomach you're going to belch really loud I play fullback and
the only job I have is to be a blocking back and believe me I belt belch several
times a game so much like like alliteration here it's so good dude
belching blocking back belching blocking back believe me I've built several times
times a game I'm the burpee black biggest baddest black black blocker and I bust
butt every time I block a full butt. When me and my BFF drink fizzy drinks I wet
fart and she burps they smell terrible so we taught the class bully a lesson I
farted on his face and she burped and blowed him for five minutes and she held
it's not the fact that i think that's what i think that's what i think that's
what i think that's what i think that's what i think that's what i think that's
I'm that bully blowing belching burpee
Busting but
Here's here's another gross dude comment I chug two cans of dr. Pepper and after letting out a few nice belches I let several farts fly
Let that thing fly dude. Yeah, let that thing go
You love something let it go drink my butt exploded like a time bomb
Duh, coke is a soda frown face
I always drink Mountain Dew and I fart so much I have to go to my room and lock
the door until it doesn't smell anymore. You're running away from the fart.
Dude, number 11 is cabbage and it starts with the same comment as from broccoli
but just with cab- broccoli replaced with cabbage. And Survivor 101 replies, "Dude
you're not fooling anyone I read number 7." You have passed, that's a cicada 3301
test is if you notice that you have passed survivor 101 you're moving on to
the next round. Number 19 is green beans and the only one comment it says don't
make me fart. I don't know if that's I don't know if that's them saying that
green beans don't make them fart or if it's a threat. Please don't make me fart green beans.
Comments on refried beans Jesus Christ. Should we just read
through these before the end? There's so many long ones. Yeah which one is it?
Number 14 look at these I think it's not number one. No wait. There's a lot of gross dude also on chili
Okay, let's read
Chili or refried chili
I own a cleaning service
What
And one night I had to clean bathrooms at a restaurant after they closed since I knew it was going to be late night
I had a dinner later in the evening, and I had made veggie chili when I do a job
I worked by myself by the time I got to the restaurant the gas was starting as I was cleaning the first stall I ripped
A huge fart it stunk really bad. I pretty much tooted the whole time
I was cleaning and the toot smelled pretty much like what I ate and the smell lingered
Yeah, lingered like a damn lost soul
I had chili before for lunch before I went outside. I saw some wood
I was working for a few minutes before it kicked in my girl came out to see how I was doing first thing that happened
was I felt a good belch coming up so I let it rip and then another belch came up
and then it was all farts after that and they smelled real bad. Why did he have to
say he saw some- oh I'm a fucking idiot. He's sawing wood, he always saws wood. He plays football, he saws wood.
I thought that he said he saw it physically. Not only am I a
baritone saxophone player but I also am a drummer. The people in the pep band are
happy about that because the way I was farting tonight because of the veggie
chili I had for dinner. Someone was like, "Now the crowd can smell your ass instead of
us." Believe me, that seat stunk after I was sitting on it.
Wait, this is not gross dude, but is this like a thing? This is the second time this
is referred to in this list. A sorority wanted to find a guy who had the loudest and worst
smelling farts, so I went over for the contest. I had vegetarian chili so I could definitely
win. This is definitely gross dude. Yeah.
I won easily so they used my butt one night.
I ate it.
So they used my butt?
I used my butt one night.
I ate a ton of it.
And all the new pledgers had to see how long they could sniff my ass while I farted constantly
and stink up the room.
Believe me, most of the girls were so grossed out by how bad they stunk.
He went to the sorority with this plan.
He was like, "I have an idea."
"I'm gonna get so laid after this."
Here's another comment from him my farts stinks so bad from the chili that my girl
told she'd rather listen to me belch after dinner. I had chili for dinner and
now I can't stop tooting tooting it's almost bedtime and I still have gas.
God yes chili is king of farts. I'm sorry I don't I just want to keep reading
green bean burrito number 25. Being a college student means you don't make the
best dietary decisions. I was constipated I thought having a couple of bean
burritos would do the trick. I was wrong. It did give me gas and throughout the whole jazz
band concert, the Barry Sacks wasn't the only thing making noise. While I was playing, I
could feel my tummy rumble and then feel the fart blast out and I could smell how bad it
was. I continued playing and farting the entire time. My girlfriend was playing next to me.
When I got home, I was still farting like crazy and my girl was like, "Seriously."
Here's one that's definitely gross, dude, but it doesn't say it. I own a cleaning service
and I just hired a girl who's a friend of mine who lost her job when Toys R Us went out
business. She's a pretty brunette with a huge butt. We're getting ready to clean
houses when she tells me that she ate refried beans at the Mexican
restaurant and she has gas. As soon as we went into the house her tummy starts
rumbling and a couple minutes later as she's cleaning a toilet I hear a huge
fart come out from where she's working and then right after she ripped another
one. Then I was hit by the smell of them. They really stunk but she's the best
toilet cleaner I have and I'm willing to put up with her farting problem. So we're
going to be cleaning houses and I'm willing to put up with her big smelling
booty with a gas problem. Hey, if you're going to work with a good-looking
college girl you got to put up with the fact that she farts like a dude and they
stink.
Okay, can I read one last comment?
Yeah.
Okay, this is under number 54.
Lamb.
Every time I eat it I can fart for England.
*laughing*
And they always smell like dog food.
Yum!
*laughing*
Okay, folks.
That'll do it for us.
That's the episode.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god.
I'm gonna cry.
Okay, bye.
(laughing)