You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
(upbeat music)
- Crap monster.
(laughing)
(explosion)
- Record.
Record.
- What?
- Just not doing well, man.
- Yeah, what's wrong?
- I'm a changed man, I'm different.
- You're different now?
- I crave blood.
- Is that true?
- You don't, no.
blood I've killed you have not killed I text you guys last night I fucking killed
man you did not Texas last night that you killed I did I did text you that I
killed I killed two baby mice oh yeah do you understand what that does to so see
you don't even know you drowned them that's bloodless you haven't not talked
about this all day cuz it's hurting me it's not I'm fucking hurt you don't
upset and I'm hurt it does not feel good to have killed man I'm afraid
afraid I might do it again. I don't think you I don't think you're that broken up
about it because after it because 11 minutes after you texted us that you
killed you texted us a prank to play on our girlfriends. Oh that was pretty funny
though a screenshot of the cracked phone of a bullet hole. Well that yeah dude have
you ever heard of somebody coping with trauma? What's wrong with you dude? I
thought it was funny. The way I just realized pranking my friends means that I had trauma.
eye. In the darkness of having murdered two innocent children, yes they were mice, I
needed a laugh dude and so what's funnier than handing your girlfriend a
phone with a photo of a cracked screen on it and saying "Bae, Bae I broke my damn
phone." Almost nothing. I need $300 right now to buy a new one. I'm so sad I need a
blowjob. Don't touch the screen, don't touch the screen. Don't touch it, it'll break it
more it'll break it more and don't look in the bucket in the bed yeah either
don't dude it was so fucked it was like 3 in the morning I was asleep
Janna goes to Mike the mice that I had a problem with last summer they're
fucking back I don't know if it's a mice but there it could be it could be but
Janna was like the mice are in the kitchen I was like fuck dude I want to
deal with this thought I was gonna have to scare him away I walk in there we had
a mouse trap under the sink I didn't put it there it's one of those stick traps
the glue ones. Well they say they're humane but then...
They're humane but you got to get the mice off with olive oil.
Well so I didn't know any of this because the directions say
that if you don't kill the mouse it'll eat its own
hands to get off of it. So I was like that's fucked up dude I gotta put these
mice out of their misery. So then I dunked them in a bowl full of
oil and I was like they'll probably just die
instantly just fucking just it'll be so easy I'll feel fine
about this. Both of them just fought like for their lives dude.
They were like squeaking. Drowning is like I think the most inhumane way
you can kill something. The box for the, I mean these guys may have a
vested interest in killing mice now that I realize this. I think I should
trust the trap that like that causes mice to eat their own flesh. I think that's what's most humane.
But I was like I'm trying to do this the most humane way possible. I ended up
fucking it up so bad because the mice one of them just died instantly one of them
just gay he was just like she just took a big breath of the oil the other one had
like a fucking he had a sight on his DVR he had to get back to you said he was
fucking trying to get back out of that thing he's stuck on the trap you said
drown and I thought you meant you like okay I like his head under the water
with my hands. I thought you took the trap and just put it under the sink and just let the water run.
Yeah. Well it said oil is the most like the most like humane way to do it because they drown faster.
One of them just refused to drown and then I started freaking out and so I just opened the
window and I tossed it out of the window. And then I was like, and then I like looked at my hands I
I was like, dude, what am I?
Why was that my instinct was to fucking throw it 30 feet?
- Dude, that was, that was my school Phelps.
He held his breath for so long.
(laughing)
Number one, dude, he was the Olympic swimmer.
- Dude, I felt so evil.
I was up for like two more hours,
just like looking for funny, funny pictures
of cracked screens.
(laughing)
To deal with my trauma.
- The only thing that would help.
you go when you do you google my shattered minds and that came up and
you thought i was i have a funny
yeah
i have a good idea for a prank on a girl right now
yeah you
well yeah you originally pulled that that that like cracked bullet
bullet hole on glass image and you held it up to your forehead and you said this
is what i want you to do to me right now and she said make it happen
crack my glass and she said wait is your phone broken oh shit damn that's a funny ass shit
damn that's actually a funny ass shit i forgot about those two things those living things that i
I murdered 10 minutes ago.
But yeah, I'm a murderer.
I think I might become kind of an evil blood craver.
Again?
No, but this is in a different, kind of more real way.
I was kind of faking it last time.
This one I've actually killed.
Oh yeah, we could all tell.
Yeah, I know you guys could.
But now I've actually done a dastardly deed.
And I feel really bad about it.
And I took all the--
So you're not evil.
I took all the other mice traps up,
mouse traps up, 'cause I was like,
I don't, I'd rather just live with mice
have to fucking drown anything else yeah I mean if you don't see him I guess it's
fine like if I so like I don't give a fuck about a mouse what's he gonna he
steals one of my chips I never finish a whole bag of chips you know you got it
you have to get some of those mouse traps that they do on YouTube where they're
just like scaled down saw traps and they're not even allowed to show the
footage no you know you gotta get rid of these mice cuz when Cameron and I come
over if they're in the chips we're gonna get mad I mean that's dinner time for
me right yeah well what I need is I need somebody like a Patrick to live in my
house like a cat and hunt the mice and catch you think you think I think
really I have to guard chips is what you're saying yeah pretty much okay
yeah or something you know it doesn't have to be chips you know I know you're
on this weight loss journey like maybe it's a maybe the mice are going for the
water well I've been I feel like I've gained a little bit of weight back you
been
old places I used to go like all my old spots and now it's all fucking wrecked
because I wanted damn me because I was like oh I'll try I want to do something
I haven't done since I was I haven't landed since I was 17 you're like
Robbins I every day I was in New York in the morning I was like hey Pat do you
want to go buy a cane or a crutch so that you can get a little better or
maybe help you out and every day he was like no no I mean how did I would have
Squandered such an opportunity there like how many times in your life do you have the opportunity to use a cane?
Exactly dude the first if I hurt my knee the first fucking thing I would do I would order crutches on Amazon
I don't care how how little of an injury it is. I'm not gonna do that
I don't I don't want to look like I'm fucking like I don't know like milky
I'm not gonna want your leg to get better. Sit around waiting for me to make a
Bad grandpa sequel. It seems so fucking lame. It seems so fucking lame for me like I got like a
a
at 23 I don't like walk around with a fucking just lie just lie no you got
shot in the leg I don't want to lie about my life you're gonna have a say a
you're gonna have a permanent fucking like like like the shape of a goat's leg
because you refuse to get a crutch say say a woodpecker thought your leg cuz
it's also one of the other was a tree name it's very cool it's literally on
the poster for jackass I'm gonna put it on there it's literally a skater
thing I'm like so nervous that now you're saying that about like my leg be
looking like a goat's leg I'm so nervous that that because that could fucking
happen to me and I could just never yeah I never seen it again and then I just
want to fucking kill myself like I don't like like what if you couldn't
skateboard it's you're done for everything yes really it's over mm-hmm
you don't think you could do like wheelchair skateboarding no I am NOT at
nitro circus I think they do that in nitrous circus they throw a wheelchair
guy off the mega ramp what do you mean by wheelchair guy the guy in a wheelchair
okay all right you cleared that up pretty well yeah I just don't like how
fast that came off your tongue people like yeah okay a wheelchair guy who was
in a wheelchair yeah sometimes they're not that's what Patrick's also you could
You could ride it on your hands like a chimpanzee.
True.
I don't know.
I already had a fucked up ankle from high school.
And you could skate after that, right?
Yeah, I could skate after that, but like...
And I saw a video of that.
That one was fucked up.
Yeah, I did...
That one was bad.
I did the same thing...
You're gonna be fine.
I did the same thing to my knee.
Well, knee's probably the worst place to do it, yeah.
Yeah.
I mean, I've taken my legs for granted.
I don't want to ever like, like I'm like full like, yeah, I'm the same way for granted way
on the same way about my heart and brain.
Yeah, like, I'm like my soul.
This whole thing is my right hand.
If I injure my right hand, dude, I'm killing myself into it.
I don't care.
How if I fucking touch a tea kettle when it's hot, it's over for me, bro.
Damn.
you don't have you know somebody could do it for you
nah dude no stepmom dad never remarried pretty fucked up he would never he never
thought of me once when he was deciding what to do the rest of his life oh maybe
Caleb was a hot-ass fucking stepmom you can try to fuck all the time I hate
nope I hate that so much my dad is so selfish what you hate stepmoms that
became like a like the algorithm people so many people look that up that the
algorithm only shows like stepmom stuff it's based on what you look at is not
yeah yeah it is it is private browsing does not keep your history yes it does
so you admit using private browsing
what are you looking at in that private browsing perhaps when I when I said when
When I go to PornHub.com it just shows me like how to make a million dollars in a day, how
to hustle harder.
Yeah, it's mostly cooking videos for me.
Yeah, I don't know what you're seeing on there.
Yeah, it's all based on the algorithms.
You're telling me you're seeing a bunch of stepmom crap where she's got her thing out.
Yeah, step crap.
She wants crap on her face.
She's stuck in the stepmom, stuck in the toilet.
Wait, she's eating crap?
Yeah, stepmom got stuck in the toilet.
I do not see that.
She has to eat her way out.
Yeah, I think you do see that.
Stepmom stuck in the oven.
Yeah, also what are you doing so deep? What recipe calls for putting something at the back of the oven?
What is that next to your foot?
How fat is my damn stepmom she gets stuck in the damn oven?
What's that next to your foot? Is that the bell jar? What the hell were you reading in the oven?
What the fuck you doing in there? God damn
Stepmom's on some weirdo shit. I'll tell you that much because they don't have jobs for the most part. They go stir crazy
At home, they're like maybe i'll fucking get myself stuck on a
On nothing.
Yeah.
Hey, I'm stuck in the middle of the air, stepson.
I think you have to fuck me out of this.
You walk into the living room, and you step up just like Exorcist floating in the air, just convulsing.
I've been cursed by a dark mage to be stuck. I'm in stasis.
Yeah.
Stepmom flipped through wall.
There's probably been like an academic paper written about it, but it's just so fucked up that that has become like-
Yeah, there's probably like an academic paper. Like, I wouldn't have tried to read it already, or like-
I have no like it's not like we're the first result that comes up when you
search stepmom porn and maybe I clicked on it thinking it was a video yeah and I
and I do not know any of the things that are linked in the bibliography no no I
keep walking into it I'm stepping I'm fucking stepping on rakes today you're
stepping on your step mom fucking idiot cuz she likes it I gotta stop I gotta
stop step on rakes my knees broken what I fucking hate myself
It's not a good day for me.
I'm sorry buddy.
You suck in your thumb?
You prick yourself?
No, I have just a bunch of dead skin on my thumb.
I'm trying to get it off.
I don't know, I've been honestly very bummed out that I have not been able to skate.
A very short guy in a light blue shirt just walked over in this alley behind my building.
He walked over towards my window, the whole time looking directly up at the sky.
He walked over, he was sitting right outside my window, still looking up, he started clapping
above his head, and then he turned around and he left.
Short guy looking at the sky, "Buddy, I think you just had a run in with Chicken Little."
You might want to listen up.
He might have something to say.
Is he still there?
No, I was trying to, I can't see the sky from-
Maybe he's getting his keys from the person who lives above you.
Maybe, but why would he walk around the corner already looking upwards?
To see if they're there with the keys.
No, he wasn't looking...
He was looking up at the sky.
You won't accept any answer about this, because you're too baffled.
I'm too baffled.
Stepmom got stuck in the window on the third floor, dude.
[laughter]
She said, "No, you're gonna have to come around the rear."
He's like, "Okay, I see what this crap is."
"You're trying to make me smell your butt."
Dude, imagine...
There's definitely...
Here's a free idea for one of the
free idea for one of those people who like who writes like internet horror
flash fiction that's like oh the scariest thing is like a in an infinite
root beige wallpaper that's the yeah yeah is you walk in you walk into like
the room your your stepmom is is is stuck in like a door or something you
see your ass and and you're like oh I need to go talk to her go around to the
other room other side is also her ass dude psychological horror sucks dude
mm-hmm fuck that shit my my brain can't be scared I mean it's it's so it's like I
don't know it's here my brain YouTube just brainwashed people into thinking
that that this that people will like tell you with a straight face like oh no
the ghosts aren't scary dude it's not vampires it's yeah it's a guy standing
still yeah it's a it's a water a glass of water you don't know where it came
from you know yeah you know it's scary it's not it's not a serial killer who's
which is about to chop your head off, it's an idea.
- Yeah.
- It's when you think of something and it's not there.
- Fire.
I've been thinking about this for a while.
They should do a horror movie where the main guy--
- Is made out of fire?
- No, he's not made out of fire, he's just fire.
- The main guy like the--
- It's like the blob, but it's just a big fire.
- So maybe like a building.
- So it's a guy running away from a fire.
- That's pretty scary.
- A whole building, there's like a party on the top floor
and then like one of the lower floors catches on fire
and everyone on the top floor has to figure out
how to get down.
- I mean, honestly, yeah, I mean, perfect, easy.
- So the towering inferno, fuck you.
- But yeah, but I mean-- - No, fuck you.
- That's already a thing.
- You wanna fuck your stepmom.
- And OJ is in that movie.
- Teens nowadays would rather watch a--
- And OJ is innocent.
- Would rather watch a movie
where the fire's in everybody's minds.
- Yeah, fuck that crap, dude.
Hereditary, what's that movie even about, dude?
I think that has a stepmom in it.
She's not hot.
What are you doing, man? It has a step devil.
Yeah, also there's no naked people. Well, there is naked people in that movie, actually.
Fuck. And they're so sexy. No, they're old, dude.
Horror movies should have at least one pair of the boobs from American Pie.
That's pretty crucial. Uh-huh.
They should have
a big, the shiniest knife. The knife that's never been used.
A buffed and waxed knife. A demon, which instead of like speaking in
Latin or like backwards or something it just says fucking shit and like fuck me
yeah well yeah cuz the devil I mean curse words what do you fucking exactly the
devil wants you to say curse words yeah what am I fucking 30 years old you think
I'm allowed to hear this crap people people people think that people it's so
stupid dude that's those are the scariest demons and the exorcist and
evil dead when they when they try to kill you and they're also going like I'm
gonna fuck you fuck fuck fuck shit yeah it's like I can't be hearing that word
Yeah, come on dude, I got school in the morning and you're gonna make me say this crap.
What does Reagan say in the exorcism?
"Your mother sucks cocks in hell" or something like that?
Yeah, pretty funny.
She also goes "Fuck me, fuck me, fuck me!"
If a demon said that to me I'd say, "Hey, I'm gonna wash your mouth out with soap."
They should have thought of that when they were doing the exorcism.
It probably would have worked, right?
Yeah, "Hey, put some fucking, get some dial with some holy water mixed in."
I'm gonna hit you with the with the with the old soap and in the soap on a rope
in your mouth Reagan just need to be grounded yeah that's all they needed to
say yeah stop throwing up on the doctor from throwing up and turning your head
around if you throw up on me one more time young man you are grounded
you know I think I told you guys before my dad my dad told me that he watched
the exorcist in theaters with like his friend and his friend got like insanely
scared and had to run out of the theater in fear and the scene that he ran out of
the theater in fear was when Reagan pees on the ground at the party that's nasty
that's some nasty crap yeah it should have been like a law drama where they
defeat her by outlawing being green yeah take that up to Congress yeah yeah what
I mean honestly they should have just given her plastic surgery to make her look normal and then just ignore the other stuff
Did you guys I've talked about my mom and jump scares before but I thought I like I I couldn't
Still to this like I've seen the Exorcist still to this day the scariest thing in my head is just that picture of
Reagan yeah, yeah, it's because it's because yes from the maze game
And then just every every picture you would like every time you go on like I can has cheeseburger calm
like one in every hundred pictures would have a get would have a jump scare of it
and a gift see the maze game bubble rap maniac the the car commercial where the
car is coming down the mountain these are all way scarier than something like
get out you know that might be because I'm a white guy now but it's still I
don't know those are like actually scary you know I'm not I'm not scared to know
the scare I mean yeah the scariest thing is scared of the Babadook is when in a
movie trailer, the sound effects line up with the song.
- You know what else is scary?
- Very scary. - In a movie trailer.
So imagine like an 80s song, slowed down,
and it's sung by like a choir of like kids.
It's got pianos.
- Oh, fucking Creep by Radiohead sung by a choir of kids.
- Yeah, but it's sung by the first person
that they saw on the street so that they could
sign them to a contract.
- Yeah, for pretty cheap.
Yeah, everybody wants to rule the world.
That's some scary shit, dude.
Yeah.
The Fat Boys, uh...
[Laughter]
The Fat Boys Whiplash!
It's like...
It's like a very poorly chosen...
It's a choir of children!
It's a choir of kids on like the slow piano,
piano they're just going whoa whoa whoa or that one that they did with chubby
checker the one that's like it's the only way to live in cars. They're doing that twist.
yeah dude just like a very slow creepy version of it yeah you can get away with that.
I'm gonna be checker and the fat boys.
Yeah.
Okay shorty, go to a party.
In 20 years they're gonna have to slow down Axl F Crazy Frog.
Yeah.
Cause that's...
That'll be crazy.
This is the crazy frog.
Big, big.
Ball, ball, ball, ball.
That one will actually be scary, the bing and the bong.
That'll actually be a little bit of a scary thing to me.
Coming this summer.
Did you guys see the song?
The Crazy Frog, the movie.
It's just for crazy frogs.
Oh fuck.
Did you guys see the spiral thing?
Not yet, I'm seeing a drive-in this weekend.
I just saw the trailer for it.
Don't spoil nothing about it for me, please.
That guy cannot act.
Who, Chris Rock?
Yeah.
Really?
He's just like, he's just yelling all the time.
He looks amazing.
Like he--
He looks young, dude.
Yeah, he looks like just as young as he did on SNL.
He's gotta be like in his 50s, right?
Oh, he's old as shit.
Yeah, I guess he's a millionaire.
He could have been very young on SNL.
I'm a 24 guy, he's 25, I just--
Ah, Christ.
He's four years old. He was born on a leap year.
Shit!
[Laughter]
Oh fuck. Did you guys ever know anyone born on a leap year?
Yeah, Chris Rock is 56.
Jesus Christ. Damn. Really?
Yeah, that's insane. That's nuts.
Good for him. He does look good as hell.
That's like when you Google how old Seinfeld is, he's 280.
Yeah.
You're like, what the fuck dude? Dude, he's gonna die one day.
Isn't that crazy? Seinfeld?
Yeah, Jerry Seinfeld is gonna die just like the rest of us.
Nah, he's gonna be a fucking...
they're gonna put him in a...
You think he's gonna be like one of those old comedians that they like for some reason are alive forever?
Like Dick Van Dyke or like Mel Brooks.
Yeah, or like Jerry Lewis. Like just one of those guys is just...
Jerry Lewis died.
Yeah, he died, but he was alive forever.
It's true. Yeah.
I forgot he died for a second.
They live in like Las Vegas in like a bunker.
And then the only time you ever see him is when Ricky Gervais goes to interview them.
Yeah. For AARP magazine. Yeah, exactly. Yeah. I hope to be one of those guys one day. I hope
to live forever, you know? I'm gonna die before I turn 70. I can tell you that already. You
think so? Yeah. You want me to make sure? Nobody in my family has ever, like, on my mom's side
has lived past like 70. Dude, it's fucked. Everybody in my family lives to fucking 100.
Really? I will, I can't kill myself. Yeah? I'm invincible. And they all smoked their
entire lives and they just ate like fucking potatoes and they just in grits
and then they just live to a hundred well we I think we're fucked as a generation
because we have all these like preservatives and like microplastics
and shit that like maybe we'll live way longer because like so like our brains
are being preserved by the same thing that like you're right that made fruit
not like all my slices of McDonald's not go brown all my relatives are born at
the beginning of the Industrial Revolution probably didn't have any sort
like you know outside toxins and even have McDonald's I mean we're probably
gonna live to it we'll live to like a hundred and twenty but then have children
that are like like half McDonald's toy yeah that's just like I don't know dude
my grandpa don't be born with a button on their back it plays it was like it's
naked they thought getting high was like fucking sitting at the top of the
chimney and just inhaling like I think like we're probably okay right yeah I
don't know I don't know I guess I probably did eat a lot of like bits of
toys that were in the cereal box growing up?
I uh, when I was like five, I was playing with Legos and I thought it'd be funny to lay down
and put a Lego in my, like a minifigure in my mouth, because I was like a giant.
And uh, well, a game I was playing.
And I remember, uh, just choking immediately.
That was the first time.
The second you get it in your mouth?
Yeah, that was the first time I ever got like CPR administered on me.
The first time?
What?
I think I had it one other time.
When we were looking for the list for this episode, I found a list that we're not going
to use, but it was just making me laugh because it was a list of toys that were very dangerous
and it was like there was one that was like an Easter egg that if you put it in water
it hatches and they had to recall it because children were swallowing it and then it would
hatch in their stomachs and create an intestinal blockage that was not detectable by x-ray.
I'm just amazed that Pat has had CPR done twice to him.
Probably not CPR, it was probably just my mom hitting me on the back.
Okay, alright, don't say CPR then, because I'm thinking that you're like dead and somebody
had to revive you.
Well, I mean, not CPR, no, I mean, fuck, I meant Heimlich.
Okay, so somebody fucking knocked something out of your mouth.
Yeah, I meant Heimlich, I got Heimlich and CPR confused.
Oh my god, dude, you damn near gave me a heart attack.
Those are very different things. Yeah, I completely understand why you're confused. Yeah, I had open heart surgery five times
I thought oh, never mind. I had a nosebleed. I thought CPR meant chest press rescue
I didn't think that
I would have believed that you thought that.
I've never choked on anything, dude.
Um, uh, that's not true.
I haven't.
My brother, my younger brother choked on water once.
At the dinner table.
Oh, that's happened to me a million times, dude.
He like, he like, he like choked, or it was he,
no, was it water or a hot dog?
I mean if it, those are two very different things.
Yeah, if you choke,
choking on water is just coughing,
that doesn't count.
Yeah, you're not choking.
actively drowning.
Yeah, choking feels good.
Yeah, my brother Eric, he either choked on water or choked on a hot dog and we were just
staring at him like, "What?
What are you doing?"
Yeah, do something.
Haha, very funny.
Oh, ha ha ha ha.
The list we have today is, are you sure you're above 18+?
Why did you get so purple?
Yes, I guess because I opened the splash page to ask if I'm 18
Wow
I'm gonna I'm gonna say yes. Here's a we'll have to come back to this website because on the sidebar here
It's the 27 erotic movies that will fulfill all possible sexual fantasies. You've ever had
This is a website called scoop whoop calm. Oh my god
15 Indian condom ads the government doesn't want you to see between 6 a.m. And 10 p.m. I
I fucking, I clicked on the 27, we have to come, ah fuck I don't want to spoil it, I'll
have to tell you, maybe Cam edit this out because this would be a good fucking list.
No don't say anything I have to edit out, fuck you, you make me do that so much.
Let's just open this one up, I don't give a fuck, we can try this one.
Okay, I'll, send it to me, send the list.
Maybe it's only good for this thing but number two, just read it, it doesn't matter.
Number two on 27 erotic movies that will fulfill all possible sexual fantasies is Lolita.
(laughing)
- Christ!
- Number two, Alita, number three, Hard Candy.
(laughing)
- I'm starting to notice the theme.
- I bet you that they're right.
- Number three, Happiness by Todd Solans.
(laughing)
- This is a nasty website.
- Yeah.
- The list we have are,
here are 69 quirky, weird, and kinky things
you need to add to your sex bucket list.
I mean, we all got a sex bucket list, right?
- No.
- Number one, sex.
- We don't. - Crossed off.
- It's crossed off, and that's--
- That's it, that's pretty much it.
- Gonna do it for my bucket list.
Sex and die.
- Die during sex.
- That is my sexual bucket list.
This is from Shaylin Jacob.
If you've been with your special one for a very long time, you know how monotonous sex
can become.
After all, how much can you experiment, right?
I mean, I for one fucking hate having sex.
It's fucking, what a chore.
It's disgusting.
It's painful.
It's like homework.
Yeah.
It hurts, dude.
Painful, revolting.
Boring.
Yeah, dude, my balls look weird after.
Difficult.
And it's like I have to call my mom, like my mom and dad have to be there, you know?
Yeah, exactly.
It doesn't feel good, yeah.
You know until you're 25 like what is it 24?
Yeah I think it's 24.
Yeah 24 is the age when you can finally start having sex by yourself and you don't need
your parents permission.
Parent or guardian.
Yeah.
I forget I forget a pen all the time for the permission slip.
I have to use my poop.
Yeah I have to sign it in blood.
Plus my fingers hurt by the end of it because I'm down there fucking fretting like a tar
hero.
I'm tired dude.
I hate that I have to be under the bed too while it's happening.
It's like can I get up there and like join in?
My back hurts after because the bed keeps hitting my spine.
It's moving a disc in my back.
Yeah, it's fucked up dude.
But if you still have hope and are willing to do anything it takes to bring back the
spice and kink in your relationship, we suggest you try these 69 titillating things with your
partner.
Number one, try out bondage.
You might just surprise yourself with your partner.
Yeah, my girlfriend comes home
and I'm wrapped up like Cindy Lou Who.
And I'm like, yeah.
- Wait, like who?
Hold up.
- The way you think about it.
- Like Cindy Lou Who.
- Yeah, I don't know about that one.
- Remember the Grinch wraps her as a present?
Are you guys stupid?
- Why go there?
- I don't remember that.
- 'Cause it was funny.
She gets wrapped up like a present.
- I don't remember that either, to be honest.
No, she sees him taking the Christmas tree.
And then he wraps her like a gift!
And then her dad walks in and he's like, "What happened to you, you stupid bitch?"
And she's like, "Oh, the Grinch."
And he's like, "You're a stupid bitch.
You don't know shit about the Grinch.
The Grinch lives in the hill."
I don't know what to tell you.
To me, this is the most iconic scene in the movie.
In the film, I'm sorry.
Number two, try rimming.
It's not everyone's.
That's number two, yeah.
Damn.
That means the rest of this shit's gonna be crazy.
Is rimming when you put your junk around the hole?
I don't know what rimming is.
*laughter*
What's rimming?
When you put your junk around the hole?
You're trying to draw a circle around it.
That's always what I imagine when I hear that.
Is like, use your dick like a pencil.
I'm surprised you were of all people.
I don't know.
I don't know dude.
What's rimming?
It's getting your butt ate out.
Oh what?
Well hell, that's nasty.
I thought that was when you draw your, you use your penis.
No!
Like you're playing osu on her butthole.
I didn't realize it was.
Yeah, I'm playing picto chat.
Yeah.
My bad dude.
I'm really fucking this list up so far.
It's a good thing you figured that out before you asked anybody to do it or anything.
True.
You could have avoided a very awkward situation.
No, I thought I'd just draw a square.
Yeah.
You're down there with a pencil.
Sorry, it's taking me really long.
I keep having to sharpen it.
Yeah, sorry, I'm following one of those, one of those like behind the scenes Simpsons videos
where they teach you how to draw Homer with three circles.
Number three, give anal a chance with lots of lube.
I used up all my oil drowning baby mice last night, so that might be off the table for
me.
You did it in lube.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, that's strawberry flavored lube.
Yeah, dude, at least it died horny.
I like this picture they put in of like a sculpture of a woman getting gangbanged.
Yeah, this is not a good... and then one who, one other woman who seems so horrified that
she has to cover her eyes.
Yeah.
Oh.
That she can't watch.
Source of this picture is the blog "Breakaway Backpacker".
What?
Try silent sex.
(laughing)
- What is this, what is this?
What is this made by fricking Charlie Chaplin or something?
- Yeah, I mean, come on.
- Hey, come on now.
- Yeah, it's actually the damn organist playing a tune.
No moans, no talking, just a whole lot of inward
and outward motion.
- That is what, yeah, you know it would be really hot
if we just--
- If you just shut the fuck up.
- If we just shut up.
- If you just shut up for one fucking second.
- Oh my God.
- It'd be so hot.
- And I'll shut up too.
- Yeah, I'll shut up.
- I'll shut up too.
- Here, we can both pretend we're dead.
Just shut the fuck up.
Everyone's gonna be fucking quiet!
*laughs*
Yeah, just doing quiet coyote in your face.
If you can hear me, clap once.
*laughs*
Uh, number five.
Have loud as fuck sex.
*laughs*
Go bonkers, hit the highest note you can.
*inhales* Me me me me me me me.
*laughs*
Oh, you don't like that?
*sings*
My leg!
hand suit of armor. Yeah. And I'm smashing baking sheets together. Girl, I know you always
wanted to fuck a one man band. Two cymbals just like, crash, bang, doot doot doot doot
doot doot doot. Number six, have no holds barred crazy sex in a five star hotel. It
has to be a five star hotel. And the sex has to be crazy. Uh huh. Yeah. And the craziest
I can think of sex in a hotel.
Yeah, let's get real crazy.
How about we both eat a warhead right before we fuck?
Make our hair fucking fly out like spaghetti noodles.
What do you think?
That'd be crazy.
Also, I'm going to look like the Play-Doh barber shop.
Yeah, we're going to be in the Hilton too.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
It's just how it has to be when you're with me, man.
We're on number six.
Look at these crazy tiny shampoos.
Number seven, watch each other masturbate and get off.
No thank you.
And get off!
Get off the bus!
I can do that by myself, thank you very much.
Get off the bus right now!
You two can't be doing that in the back of the bus!
Mission accomplished.
No, we read- You don't realize-
No, no, hold on!
I read this on scoopwhoop.com!
I was supposed to do this!
This is gonna save my marriage!
- Number eight, give your partner--
- This is a $15 bus to Chinatown,
you get the hell off of here.
- I like number eight, being a kink.
Give your partner multiple orgasms,
because they deserve it.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, my kink is I'm insanely good at sex,
and I make everyone cum.
Just my kink, dude.
- Yeah.
- When you rock it with me,
you gotta be okay with my kinks.
Number one, I'm gonna make you cum
a trillion times a second.
- Hey baby, you wanna get really kinky?
Okay, we just have to wait 20 minutes,
and then, okay wait, no, 30 minutes.
A little longer.
Okay, well you know what, I'm going to get in the shower, but you know, don't, this is
going to get crazy.
Here, maybe I'll just leave the room, you can probably handle the rest of this, right?
Number nine, devote an entire day to just pleasing your partner.
From oral sex to erotic massages, do everything.
Wake up recruit!
Attention!
"Days starting early today, make your damn bed!
That's no damn 90 degree angle!
I said tri-fold on your pussy!"
"I wanna bounce a quarter on it!"
"#10 Have sex in a place you might get caught.
It can be at your parents house, at your friends house, at a relatives place.
You get the drift right?"
What the fuck why would you?
What people want to get caught having sex that's so weird
When they want to get grounded yeah, well, yeah, what?
If you're gonna do it where you're gonna if it's gonna be about getting caught
I mean it could at least don't involve your family and friends
I mean your parents if you're like an adult your parents walk in they're just gonna be like okay. That's nasty have you seen that uh?
Like you're not in trouble. Maybe you're having sex as an adult like
That's another stepmom porn that you have watched a million times
No
The will our net episode of sex in the city where you know dating Miranda and his whole thing is that man
his whole thing is that he like his whole thing is he likes to almost get caught and then like
He's like like he invites his parents over for dinner or something and they get caught by will our nets, but it's a great
It's a good episode
But then what happens he gets caught by his parents and he's doing going wait doing having sex
Can you describe?
Can we hear more details?
What are they doing to each other?
They're having sex and we learn that's like
"That's my parents!"
What position are we talking about here?
I don't remember.
And they're just completely nakey.
Right? Socks?
It's tasteful nudity.
Sex in the city, I would think you would expect more.
HBO nudity.
Pre-2005 HBO nudity.
Pre-9/11 nudity.
nudity after 9/11 they're like we got to be rocks and balls dude I keep walking
Jan is watching Game of Thrones like for some reason I keep walking in fucking
guys balls and dick on the screen what the fuck dude that's what it was like in
the fantasy days it's true I mean that's true it's cool if it's like a fantasy
thing you can show a guy's full penis if it's like a TV show yeah a cell phone at
all you can only see their butt.
Do it yeah having just imagine how out of place it would be if you just see full hanging balls
in like a Star Wars show right?
You can't do that.
Well I mean I haven't seen the Bad Batch yet but.
That could be what the Bad Batch is about.
Yeah they're so bad their dicks and balls are always out.
That could be what the Batch is yeah it could be a batch of balls.
Batch of nuts.
Number 11, sext while you're in the office and get off.
If you're in the same office, great.
To my boss.
Yeah.
What up?
I'm in the bathroom.
I just took a crap of my wieners out.
Do you want to see that?
I got my thing.
You trying to see that?
You want me to send you the sexiest gif I can find?
Texting my boss and be like, "Yo, check out my thing, but it's just a picture of my desk."
Oh, I forgot to move.
It was pointing down.
Yeah, I forgot to scoot my chair out.
Sorry.
My penis would be there if I was in the office.
If I was naked.
If there was nothing but just me in this room, you'd see my penis right now.
Imagine if my chair was your mouth.
The whole chair.
Number 12.
Dedicate a full day to just trying out different sex positions and sleeping in.
Wait, sleeping in?
I can do that.
I can do that no problem, dude.
That's not very sexy, but I'll do it.
Number 13.
The picture.
(laughing)
- This picture, this guy,
I think they're trying to communicate
this girl is like jacking off this guy and he's coming,
but the way that he has his mouth open like a pog,
like a pog champ, and his eyes are just like
extremely uneven.
- This dude's going full Mr. Bean,
'cause fuckin' Jenny Slate has her hand up his ass.
(laughing)
- Yeah, this guy's a puppet.
That's why he looks like that.
- Number 14 and 15, did we read number 13?
I don't know. - No, no we didn't.
- There's 69 of these, I don't think we have to--
- You can skip this if you have to.
- Number 14 and 15, number 14, finger her in public.
She's going to love it.
I don't know about that.
- Yeah, well, yeah.
- There's, I don't know, number 15,
give him a handjob in public.
He's going to find it hard to keep calm for sure.
- And that one's bolded.
The handjob one is, but the finger one isn't.
So what's up with that?
- Yeah.
Think about that for a minute.
I don't think people like,
I don't think I would like that.
If I'm in my, especially, you know,
I'm like about to go up a belt in Taekwondo
and my girl just starts jacking my shit.
Yeah.
You know, I'm in the dojo right now, bitch.
I'm in that damn dojo right now.
I'm in the dojo.
I'm in that dojo, you can't disrespect.
Don't you hate it when you're in the dojo?
Can't you disrespect?
You see that Korean flag over there?
That means we in the dojo.
Yeah, you're not, hey.
You're not touching my thing.
This penis is off limits.
You are not- uh-uh.
Not Lingo Joe, you are not undoing this belt.
I'll take you down.
I worked fucking hard.
I worked so hard.
This is a blue belt.
Only Master Ray can undo this belt,
and it's when he's replacing it with a new, better belt.
Leave my shit alone.
I'm almost up to red, I think.
I don't know the order.
Or my girl, we're in public, like at the zoo or something.
She starts like unbuckling my belt, and I'm like,
"Babe, what are you doing?"
She's like, "You know what I'm doing."
I'm just like, "Are you trying to wipe my butt right now at the zoo?"
What the hell are you doing, trying to wipe my butt right now?
What the hell?
I swear I wiped earlier.
It's not that bad.
How'd you know?
How'd you know that I didn't wipe?
Number 16.
How could you smell it over the animals?
Have sex in front of a glass window.
You know, the kind that looks out on the street maybe?
all right well I don't need all that attitude no yeah come on come on dude
give me a don't act like I'm stupid about glass yeah I know where else is a glass
window gonna go as I mean a glass window from the living room to the kitchen yeah
dude dude all the food can see us right now we're oh man dude but the fridge is
looking at me have you seen a sausage party that foods about the top that's
actually true sausage party taught me that actually food that is shaped like
vaginas and a penis is actually so horny. Yeah. Pretty sick. They're hilarious too in an odd
sort of way. Yeah. This one, 17's a little vague. Stop that damn elevator and get going.
That's ruining the day of a lot of people. Can you stop an elevator? Yeah, you hit the
stop button. There's a stop button? Doesn't it also like call the fire department if you
do that? You gotta go quick. True, I guess so. Yeah. I feel like most-- Police report
with cum all over your face. Most buttons that stop an elevator I think also set
off an alarm like a loud alarm. Yeah, yeah they call the fire department I think.
Or at least the bellboy. I think they have like a phone like I'm pretty sure they can
like talk to you in the elevator. And there's a camera in the elevator. Most
elevators at least. Plus there's the elevator attendant.
Well there is that you know there is that Aerosmith song. I am just
remembering there's an aerosmiths on a love in an elevator. Is that what they talking about?
Yeah. God. They're gonna have sex in an elevator. I mean you could do it in like
a mineshaft elevator. Put no cameras in there. Yeah. You just have to worry about black lung.
Now what see this is just the same fucking. Yeah they keep repeating.
Number 18. Spend a day naked in each other's company. You can choose to have
sex or just lay back and relax you know it's really kinky yeah lay him back and
relax even my fucking white cloth bear asshole on the fucking on the on the
couch scooting on the couch like a dog yeah just leaving a brown tree lemonade
and I'm playing Zelda without her in the room I'm so glad we decided to follow
that list of kinks this is you walked into the room and you said get out I
think this might be my sexual fetish babe can you stay in the other room
Number 19, have sex at your office or your partner's office. It makes for good
stories. I'll say it makes for good stories. Have you guys ever heard of the TV show?
The Office? True. Parks and Recreation? One of the best stories is Parks and
Recreation. Mm-hmm. Use a vibrator on your partner. They're going to love it.
Didn't they already say something? They're going to love it? Yeah. They
claim that they're going to love all of this. Number 21, give her a nipple-gasm.
I don't know what that could mean.
You remember that one of those like Swagopino Tumblr pictures where it's like, where like
cushion lyrics type thing.
There's one of them that says do epic shit with her pussy.
Yeah.
That would...
Give her a nipplegasm.
No, I think that would fit well on like a picture of a guy like holding his flat broom up and
like exhaling a giant cloud of delicious smoke.
Delicious sexy smoke.
Oh my god.
Have a quickie in a public place because living life on the edge is exciting.
Yeah, you guys are repeating yourself.
It's a lot of repeats.
Alright, we'll skip the repeats for now.
Number 23, touch each other in a movie theater with people in it.
Number 24, try roleplaying.
Make them your slave.
Get them to play a nurse or a plumber.
Or you can just be strangers, whatever floats your boat.
Yeah, Dave, I've been really wanting to do roleplay recently.
I was thinking you might be my slave doing roleplay as a nurse and just be like, can you can you put your dick away?
I have to make a tick tock right now
You have to go whine on Facebook so hey a slave kitchen floors looking pretty dirty I don't know
Yeah, you have to do whatever I say. Yeah some slave you turned out to be a slave
Can you act as a human remote control and press all the buttons on the back of the TV?
Thank You slave I
I didn't say slave off. I didn't say slave off.
Keep pretending you're my slave.
Number 26, get naked and cook together.
What?
Yeah dude, I love fun.
Aren't you worried?
I love hot oil.
Yeah, aren't you worried about oil at all?
Oh yeah, we're frying, we're frying fucking-
We're making chicken parm with our fucking dicks out.
We're frying brussel sprouts, fucking water content and that thing's going-
Yeah.
Makes the deep fryer go fucking crazy.
I got four frying pans or frying bacon in each one of them. Yeah, and ice cubes. Ah, ah,
ah, fuck, ah, ah. And then you get to eat bacon while you're doing it. Yum. Yes. Yeah. Number
28, try a remote controlled sex toy. Imagine making your partner squirm in public at your
will. Interesting, right? It's like a RC car. I'm here to finger you. It's like a dancing
robot you know yeah the like what's that robot called you know the one I'm
talking about that Robo Modo yeah the one remote control robot get one of those
back flipping dogs yeah it's like can you just sit on this in like a weird way
I think it might work yeah Oh Robo Modo is the video game company that made Tony
Hawk ride that's the same thing take penetration out of the equation and focus
On foreplay that you just added that for the rhyme dude. Yeah. Yeah, I didn't know you were an MF doom style rime sayer. Mm-hmm
Blindfold them devoid them of all their senses and see the magic unfold
I'm all the senses. I'm gonna plug you up like you got the stars
That is like that's that's a that's a saw monologue like that. That sounds terrifying
Yeah, that sounds you void them of all of their senses and see the magic unfold
half of these sound very evil yeah I you know just nothing wrong with making a
girl picture number 32 here use the jet spray to give her a quick orgasm trust me
it's amazing what is the jet spray you know the
chair is you know on a garden hose you can turn it to get a hose you yeah you
you take the hose bring it you know your guys are getting busy you'd you'd you
get up you back in here you bring her to the kitchen and you turn on the
sprayer from the sink and you go yeah you say okay now get up in the sink cuz this
is not a very long hose smear edible paint all over each other and give me
frosting you can always put up the masterpiece on your bedroom wall just
like red just like blood splatter all over your apartment yeah we basically
ate each other's paint wear a dress without panties and let him know in the
most creative way without taking anything handing him a like a card that has like a
pop-up on the inside when you open it up that you like made out of like
construction paper that's just yeah have sex on the beach but make sure you carry
a mat you don't want sand in certain crevices now do you maybe I do why you
fucking on the damn beach then bro yeah I mean if you don't want sand in your
thing yeah do it in the parking lot there's way less in there what say no to
lingerie and get wet in the rain together that makes no goddamn sense at
all join the mile-high club because why the hell not well it's illegal and
there's actually air marshals on it who will send you to jail have you not seen
Harold and Kumar go to Guantanamo Bay? Do you not know what happens when
hilarity ensues on a plane? It's never good dude.
Sometimes you're on a plane, before it takes off, you sit there, you
kind of feel the air, you say "this is too funny to be safe" and you walk off. Have
sex in the car. If you don't have one, borrow and have sex. Just don't tell them.
On the sidebar here there's another list by Shailen Jacob which is
eleven short erotic stories to get you in the mood tonight and here's what it says
in the thumbnail starved he spread his breakfast on the table unwrapped as he
took a bite his breakfast moaned what oh dude every day I thank God I'm a Christian
I don't have all these fucking weird I don't know what a rim job is yeah watch
Watch a movie or anything else and touch each other.
Dress up in the kinkiest of outfits and seduce him.
Baby doll lingerie set.
Sexy teacher nurse, whatever turns him on.
Sexy teacher nurse.
Teacher who is a nurse.
Sexy school nurse.
The worst person of all time.
Sexy lunch lady teacher school principal.
Nurse.
Sexy female gym teacher.
The sexy janitor fucked my balls.
Now that's hot.
Yeah.
The janitor got stuck on his broom
and I had to fuck him out of that.
Ooh, the sexy guidance counselor.
counselor school security officer who has to run the metal detector is your
penis made out of metal I need to detect it the gym teacher got stuck in a
basketball and I got a fuck in her face so hot the sexiest thing I could think
of wearing a basketball on my head you're fucking a basketball tonight
school therapist got stuck in her own mind and I had to fuck her out that's
fit with the theme right yeah have drunk sex real diminishing returns from yeah
take a shower together I don't know that's just that's just a chore
inventive how fucking lazy they get number 61 is 63 have sex in front of a
mirror have sex on the washing machine have sex in a room lit with candles have
sex in the kitchen they were just trying to hit 69 yeah I know that's possible
number 69 is gonna blow your mind when we get there just so you know wait 67
sneak into a trial room and do it like at a courthouse what the fuck yeah why
would you go to it how do you have access you need keys you gotta be like at
at least a lawyer. Yeah, you'd have to do some like Mission Impossible shit to get in there.
What the fuck? Well, you know, I mean it is cutting out the middleman there,
because then there's a lot of crimes you committed to get in there. And you're also committing a
crime in the room. Do it in a cheap motel.
Number 69. No, no. No, I won't be doing that.
Cheap motel, the fucking motel owner's got cameras in the room. That's not...
Call out your partner if you haven't had an orgasm in years. Print this out.
your partner and get ready for a sex adventure. Trust us, it's going to be a wild ride.
Get ready for a sex adventure.
Okay, here's, there are two comments. I'm going to read this comment from, from user
Drain Head. Okay, this is in all capitals. I will now follow 69 kinky sex bucket list
idea number 69. My partner of 75 years, David Mordecai Snyder, has not touched me or brought
me to orgasm since Nixon was in office. I have become dry and withered like a saltine. None
of these work due to our heart problem conditions. I am not sure that a sexy new sex position
will be able to last for my sweet David Bordekai Snyder before I break him and he dies. Scoop
whoop dot com I do not know how much time I have left.
It's pretty good from Drain Head. This is a comment from Umar. Media lord help me with
closure on my boyfriend's phone. After all the lies and coming home late nights I was
was able to gain remote access to his phone activities through the spy app sent to me
hackingloop6@gmail.com. If you suspect that your partner might be cheating on you, kindly
reach out to Hacking Loop. He's a legit hacker. Tell him I referred you.
Using a hacker?
This is just an ad for Hacking Loop.
Oh my god, dude. I know that's Hacking Loop himself making that. That's Umar.
Yeah.
Oh, you, oh, let me, I just fucking, I just reversed searched or whatever the fucking
term is.
I looked up Hacking Loop 6.
Yeah, you know who owns that email?
Umar Hacking Loop.
Do you guys want to do a quick quiz to round this out?
Yeah, dude.
I'll do a quiz.
Take this quiz and we'll try to guess which Kama Sutra position best describes your sex
life.
Alright, this is easy.
Are you someone who loves experimenting with new adventures in bed?
Take this quiz and we will tell you the position that suits your sex life the best.
Wink.
Let's start with a simple one. What's your ideal vacation location?
Mountains, beach, forest, desert. Desert. Desert. Desert. Yep. I love the desert.
What's a sex toy you always wanted to try with your partner? Vibrator strap-on,
handcuffs, sex dolls. Is there a sand related option?
Maybe sand cups. Sand cups? Yeah, okay.
What's your favorite sexy food? Strawberries and liquid chocolate, whipped cream,
popsicle, or honey? Cactus.
Sandwich.
probably whichever whipped cream is good out of the damn bottle which which
everyone can really go to a sandwich though i if all right so if i'm in the
desert i'm stuck i have a sand uh fucker as a toy and then i have to pick something
yeah he's watering options i guess i'll do popsicle that's the closest to water
yeah i'm dying out here yeah what's your favorite animal dog cat panda horse it's
gotta be a horse to get out of the desert right yeah probably a horse which color
reminds you of your partner red pink black or golden golden the color of sand yep
yeah what's your favorite drink wine whiskey beer or vodka it's it's all a
mirage I'll say wine I'm you know even I'm stuck in the desert it's been days I
haven't lost my dignity though that's true yeah what's your favorite phrase to
turn your partner on I'm dripping wet I want you so bad do you like that baby or
I need you so bad right now I think I need you so bad right now cuz I'm lost in the
desert I feel like I'm dripping wet cuz she's lost with me right presumably we're
both in the desert so she's also in the desert but I don't know where she is
if I'm she got taken by a sand tornado taken by a Jawa yeah yeah I think they
pieced her out or something I saw one of them carrying her leg yeah probably
Probably I'm dripping wet.
Alright.
What's your favorite romantic activity?
Wine tasting, movie marathon, chilling in a hot tub, or massaging?
Miraging?
You say miraging?
Yeah, did you say miraging?
A hot tub oasis.
A hot tub oasis, yeah, a hot spring, but then you can't drink the water.
It's too hot.
I would drink it.
I don't know if that would be refreshing.
I would just wait for a night time and then I would drink it.
Alright.
You've outsmarted me again.
What's your favorite workout?
Squats, lunges, pushups, or bridges?
Whichever one burns the least precious calories probably.
So, I'm going to say crunches.
Yeah, I mean we are in the desert.
Yeah.
I got to conserve every bit of energy I have.
Crunches is not an option.
Oh, I thought you said crunches.
Lunges.
Sorry, I'm having, I'm having, again, it's a mirage.
My brain has, my brain is a mirage right now.
Yeah, sorry, I'm seeing an oasis.
I had a mirage thought bubble.
I saw a speech bubble coming out of you.
Next time, yeah, next time I have to play something awful,
I'll say, "Oh, sorry, I thought it was a mirage in my brain."
I say bridges. Okay, bridges. Gotta get a bridge out of the desert. True, I don't know what
a bridge is, but a bridge is presumably goes over a body of water. The result is the "ohm"
position, which I'll send you a picture of this in the chat, but the first line of the
description of this is, "You belong to the lazy kind when it comes down to sex." But
lazy doesn't mean uninteresting just like this position relaxing but far from boring your
partner will sit cross-legged and you will sit in their lap facing them for your support
wrap your legs around them and hug each other this is the number one way to not get separated
in the desert true and also at night the desert actually gets surprisingly cold yeah plus
you get plus you're like sitting like that you can use your your partner as a backpack
and keep like gummy bears and all kinds of other things.
(laughing)
- Yeah, it's like a camel's hump.
You just fill 'em with water.
- Yeah, yeah, exactly.
- Whenever you need some water,
you squeeze them away. - No, 'cause you're both
sitting like that, like you're carrying them around
like that, and then sweat's gonna pool up.
You put that through a filter, you got some water.
- Exactly. - Damn, dude.
You can't drink sweat, that won't hydrate you, will it?
- Yeah, it can.
- You can. - Obviously, if you put it
through a filter first. - Yeah.
- Yeah, I guess you're right. - You just put it through a--
- Carry, if you gotta-- - If you put it
into the water machine. Oh, I forgot I brought the water machine to the desert.
Yeah, it turns sand into water. Yeah, also I like the idea of somebody getting
stranded in the desert but they just went on vacation there and they just
like, they didn't like fall off of anything. They just went and got stuck.
I'm sure that's happened. Yeah, dude. I would like that to happen to me. Baby, for our
honeymoon, I want to go to the middle of the desert. Yeah, we put the
the date of our anniversary as longitude and latitude and it took us to the middle of the
Gobi Desert and we are going to die. Hey, rules are rules. Alright, bye everybody. Bye.
Bye.