You're listening to Israel's number one podcast.
Our accounts are on the list.
Crap monster.
Recording now.
Recording live.
It's not live.
It's live.
We're not live.
Live right now.
And then we put it out and then it's to tape.
I think.
Live to tape.
Yeah.
Like the Tonight Show.
Isn't that his show? Yeah.
Johnny Pemberton did a show called Live to Tape.
I think that's his podcast name.
Call it the Johnny Pemberton Show.
I like Live to Tape. I think that's a good name.
I like Johnny Pemberton.
No, because you couldn't...
If you read it, you'd think it's Live to Tape.
Yeah.
Maybe that's the pun.
What is he, a damn painter?
It doesn't make any sense as a pun
because Live to Tape doesn't really mean anything.
I don't know.
I think that he should change it to the Awesome Show.
I think a lot of people have fucked up their show's names so bad.
Yeah, we should give advice on people's podcast names because we got it down.
We have like the perfect name for a podcast, right? Let's go through them.
Chapo Trap House.
Bad name, it's vulgar.
Just call it, just call it Freak of the Week.
You know, something like that.
Or like the Politics Hour.
Yeah.
Or like, like Funny Politics.
How about the Mind Hour?
Yeah.
Well, that's, somebody else could take that.
Poor guys, crazy politics.
And then like, this American life.
I don't know how many posts there are on chat.
How about story time?
Story time.
What about Harmontown?
That's a good name for this American life.
Harming Women Town is what he probably could have called it.
What?
Stan Harmon.
No, I was saying that's a better name for this American life.
What, Harm in Town?
Harm in Town.
I just are like harm in town maybe like like critical role. Oh
Yeah, yeah about the fucking shit
Shit for about fucking
Shitty suck my shit my fart farting in shit crud on my ass shit on my face
Oh, how about that? Oh, that's actually pretty good a podcast called. Oh
Like I'm so I'm so damn stinky. I'm stinked up sitting here stinky stanky just I'm filled up with
I'm smelling bar and my room is full of stink and fuck
Oh, I have a billion smells that come out for me, and I have all them all I'm filled with smells like a bag
I have a person I fill it with smells
Wait, wait, don't smell me. It's about a
a really stinky cock. Yeah, what about "Fart, Fart, Don't Smell It"? Yeah, that'd be a better,
way better show. That one's good. And instead of "This American Life" it'd be "Piss All
on My Wife". Okay. That would work too, there's a story about that. Yeah, what about "This
American Fart" and it's about American farts, huh? What about that? These are all good.
These are all good names. These are too good to be giving out for free, man. Yeah. Fuck.
pay me $250 I will consult you on naming your podcast I did not name this podcast
but this is branch turd okay you could call it that you could call it like
stink is fart fart I don't want to I don't even want to make fun of this is
branch work I like it
show ever yeah baby what's wrong with you
call it fart burger they're gonna get mad they're gonna get a friend
there you know they have fiery tempers
there's anything I know they have the most fiery
I get fiery tempers all the time.
I don't even know them well enough to make that joke.
Do you guys remember that Mexican restaurant that we went to last time you guys were in
town, or last time Cam was in town?
I think so, yeah.
Yeah, where we like met up.
Do you remember how the guy made fun of me for drinking a bunch of water?
No.
You don't remember that?
The guy kept being like, "Oh, you drink a lot of water, huh?"
And then the next time that I came...
a Shirley Temple there and he didn't make fun of me at all. Yeah, I know, and he made fun of me for
getting water. But I guess I drink a lot of water. And he just kept refilling it. And then the next
time I went, I asked for like some more water after I drank my first glass and he said, "Uh,
I think I remember you." And I was like, "Oh yeah, I drink a lot of water." And then the next time I
I went in last week, I walked in and he saw me, he went,
"Water boy!"
(laughing)
I guess I'm water boy at a restaurant in Ridgewood.
- That's just not a--
- If you finish the cup of water,
they're the ones who are refilling it.
It's not like you order like 10 waters.
That's kind of unfair.
- That's what I'm saying.
Like, buddy, you must just be a very good waiter.
drinking this out because I'm polite you know you put it in front of me I'm gonna
take it down plate club I'm not I'm not gonna leave a glass half full fuck no
fuck no not water not now Jesus don't come over and fill it up when you when
you drank like two sit down a bit - you cut oh sorry I'm being healthy call
every fat guy food man when he walks in the damn door every time somebody walks
in who ate their food the last time they went out he goes oh food guy!
Food man yeah!
What's up food man?
Oh let me guess you want food you fucking asshole!
Hey it's napkin guy!
This guy used a napkin last time he was here.
I remember he used a bathroom twice in one fucking trip.
Fuck that waiter.
This guy has the worst signature ever guy.
Your signature sucked on the receipt last time.
Every time I go I feel so guilty because he's fucking shitting on me for my water intake
that I tip him more every time.
I think he thinks that I like being called Waterboy.
Yeah.
Maybe on your next, maybe sign it Waterboy so the check doesn't go through.
Just completely stiff him.
God damn, what an asshole though.
You should go there and just get water.
No food.
That's a good idea.
Waiters love it.
Is that even legal?
Waiters love it when you don't buy drinks apparently.
Can you go in there?
I don't think me and Patrick ever told the story of our date.
Yeah.
Me and Patrick went on an accidental date.
This is like two weeks ago too.
We haven't even talked about it.
Yeah, accidental date.
It was accidental.
Patrick, me and Patrick were walking to find some food.
This is back when my leg hurt way more.
And yeah, he was crying and he was like, "I don't want to walk any further than this restaurant."
I wasn't crying.
Come on.
I was like, "I don't know man, this looks kind of expensive."
And he's like, "Really?"
And I was like, "Yeah, I mean yeah, but we can go in if you don't want to walk any further."
we went in and it was it was like a vibes bar yeah that nobody else was in with
like with like Christmas lights hanging up and like flowers everywhere and stuff
looks like Rex has a like it was beautiful they were yeah they were like
if food is a sin then call this vibes just like everywhere just to like take
pictures in front of and the waitress came over and was like can we start you
guys off with any drinks or like no we're just getting food and then she
like took our order and then five minutes later she came back and was like
- No, it wasn't even five, dude,
it was like 30 minutes later.
Like, we hadn't even, we hadn't gotten our food yet.
Like, it was like a weird amount of time for her to like--
- Yeah, she came back and she was like,
I just wanted to like double check
that you guys really didn't want any drinks
'cause we've never had anybody come in and not want drinks.
- Yeah, that's the upsell, dude.
- And we were like, oh no, sorry,
like we didn't mean to go on a date.
We just wanna get out of here.
- You didn't go Shirley Temple there?
- No, I didn't.
- She would've been fine with a Shirley Temple.
I yeah I should have got something.
The first sign there was something wrong is that the host who like seated us was DJing
at the front and he was dressed like Bruno Mars.
I didn't even realize he was DJing.
What the fuck?
That makes so much sense that's why he was in that little fucking outfit.
What what?
A DJ outfit?
Yeah he was wearing like no he was dressed like he was dressed like 2014 Bruno Mars.
Yeah he had like a vest.
Yeah like a hat that was crooked you know.
yeah all right he was he was doing disco he was he was like a band of style there
was great tables there the turntables were like right next to the door I
didn't they had they I pointed them out to you they had a plastic cover over
there over the records which I can like only assume is because people who come
in getting seated just reach over that's what I would do dude god that's funny I
had no idea he was DJing they should do like a bini hana style or like a bocce
grill style thing where you well I guess it's not the same like a Korean barbecue
thing but instead of a little oven you get a turntable and you can DJ for the
whole table yeah that would be such a good fucking idea dude. If you replace that with
touch tunes and you just up the price or you replace touch tunes with that and
you up the price you're gonna be making so much more money yeah. Didn't your
brother call you Pat asking for your touch tunes password? He did. Which I
I think you made the joke when we were talking about it.
Uh...
Like, it was like, I...
Yeah, I definitely...
Oh, that's how I know that you definitely shouldn't drink anymore?
Yeah.
At one point you drank enough that you made a TouchTunes account?
It's like, fuck, this dude loves The Who so much.
I didn't play The Who on it.
You did, you fucker.
No, no, no, no, we went to that Billiards Club and I would only play Sabbath.
pieces cuz that yeah that's like the dumbest that's the lamest yeah I've ever
done well that's also I think you queued up like a bunch of like a comedy album
like as we left I played the kids in the hall break it up
that's stupidest oh fuck I hate myself so much money on that I know the DJ hit or
hit the hit the the no it was like the only songs and Jim Gaffigan starts
playing. The only song I played off the Kids in the Hall soundtrack was the I'm
Gay one. Nice. Yeah. Funny move. Funny move by me. It's like me and my brother used to go to this
trucker bar. Oh great. I love reliving that. Nice dude. I love thinking about that. You're in a
better place now you know. That's true. Your permanently disabled leg. Yeah. That's better.
That's a good trade. I've had a good couple weeks. We just got back from the lake.
Neal's Lake House. Oh yeah we went to the lake. Had some much needed R&R.
I wore a ghillie suit. We both wore ghillie suits. I was shooting stuff with a BB gun.
Pat is like a... I forget because I haven't been around Pat for more than
like you know five hours at a time. I forget that he is like the worst
prankster in the world who loves it more than anybody. Like a prank to Pat is like
spitting on your ear and he'll be like "is that funny?" and everybody's like "no dude
that sucks dick" or he'll shoot a BB gun at your shoes. I didn't shoot anybody.
Why'd you shoot? Explain this big red dot on my forehead. I didn't shoot you. I did
not shoot you at all. You shot me in the head point-blank execution style.
Stop I did not shoot you. You did Benghazi to me with a BB gun. I made my
own targets out of the empty beer cans and the empty beer boxes and I made my
targets and I was a pretty good shot honestly. You sucked at it. I was very surprised at
how good I was at it. Maybe you should pick up shooting guns. You got a BB gun for the first time and
you took maybe 50 pictures in two days holding it. That's how I know you're not
destined to be a shooter. That's all I'm gonna say. That is not true. Absolutely true. I cannot count how many
pictures I received from you of you look at me I have a gun in the kitchen look at
me it's not that did not happen at all look at me I'm putting it in here look
okay that was funny it was funny he was just like I did all the time yeah I did
screenshot a lot of them so I can Photoshop you pointing it at homeless
people and such so you're gonna have to watch out for that in the future really
good I have those on my phone now I can see Pat becoming a gun guy yeah yeah I
feel like you have an obsessive enough you wait till he moves to New York to
become a gun guy. I know. Not where we lived in New Hampshire for 20 years. You know what the rule is with like
carrying a gun in New York? You can only you can only have it if you're a business
owner and you keep it at the business and it can only go between a business and a
gun range. Those are the two places you could bring your gun. Well I mean we
technically own a business. Yeah and the damn police department. All right. We own
a small we have an LLC we do walking down like like Myrtle with just like an RPG
like oh no I'm going to the range I'm going from the range back to my office
yeah you actually can't arrest me for are there any gun ranges here at all yeah
Yeah there's a couple.
They're probably like way out.
There's one in Queens I think.
There might be one in Brooklyn even.
I don't know.
This hippie city is bullshit.
This goddamn hippie city is bullshit.
I'm gonna show you the best gun range in New York City and go into the hotel room from
Taxi Driver.
It's funny to turn, I turned 24 and I felt like I got really old and then immediately
I was just like I gotta move to fucking like Texas or Wyoming like right now dude. Yeah
I was like I'm done with this this city slick and bullshit
I want to be able to have an entire I want to I want to have a whole layout dude
We already talked about this ATV. No that would never work for you. Why ATV?
I'm not even small doom big you are too small for me to puff bars to live in the in the
That's true. What do you mean?
- True.
- You are way too addicted to puff bars to love them with.
- I'll swap to cigarettes.
- You probably wouldn't have fast enough internet
to play your games either.
- True, too.
- I'd drop any of this any day of the week, dude.
- I'm sure you could.
- I'll drop caffeine, nicotine, video games.
I'll drop everything, dude.
You guys might never, I mean, I could be gone tomorrow
and you'd never hear from me again.
I could be a mountain man pretty fast.
- I'm back on the jewel.
I was smoking cigarettes for a little bit
and then I woke up and I didn't have any left,
So now I'm back on the jewel.
- That is one of the most exciting stories you've ever told.
That was, that's incredible.
- Well, I mean, we were, I don't know,
we were hanging out this weekend
and I just like kept buying cigarettes this weekend.
- Yeah.
It was nice.
It was nice to have somebody with cigarettes around.
- Yeah. Oh yeah.
But I had spirit menthols.
- Yeah. They were, those were not very good.
- Yeah. Those are the worst.
Spirits are the worst in general.
Cause it's just like you light that shit
and you're sitting there for like an hour smoking it.
Yeah dude, it's like a steak dinner of a cigarette.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's still a little too much.
Feel full afterwards.
Oh yeah, dude.
Can't do it all the time.
But yeah man, I might disappear tomorrow.
I'll see you guys in like five years.
I have a full beard.
Don't disappear.
Still with this patch going.
You would not have a full beard in five years.
Still with this little patch.
Yeah, you would not have a beard.
You would finally have one visible hair.
It would look like they talked to a baby's head.
Five years?
Five years, dude?
You'd get a Homer Simpson hair on your chin after five years.
Five years, you would look like me right now.
I bet if I was out there...
getting that vitamin D on top of my head...
eating off the land, foraging, right?
Eating what I kill and shit.
You're not fucking foraging.
You are not foraging.
I could forage. You could not forage.
You guys keep doubting me.
One day I'm going to surprise you.
Anyway, if I'm out there living off that land,
I bet you my hair grows back.
the microplastics in the fluoride that destroyed the top of my head just turned
it into a barren wasteland if I'm out there pissing in a river shitting on a
catfish in fucking 30 days flat I have beautiful hair all right do it I don't
want to let's see hard it's too hard to do that kind of crap dude is a bears out
there I don't want to go out there fuck that but I might do some bow man hunting
or bow hunting we thought I'd be the bow man flex hunting yeah I might get a
little bit we could get some bow and arrows in New York right I think that
New York is like Boston or like you can't even have like a like a long
pocketknife yeah legally yeah I doubt that they'd let you have a bow and arrow
Why not? That's like a gun. You can kill people. Yeah. That's better than a gun, dude.
It's more powerful than a gun. It can kill an orc. A gun can't. Untraceable. Mm-hmm.
Yeah, it's true. You can enchant it. You ever seen in a movie? What if that's the
law in New York is you can shoot a bow and arrow at anybody but you have to
have your name etched into the arrow. You're trying. The arrow has to be
traceable back to you otherwise not allowed. Yeah, that would make sense.
- Yeah, the thing is about an arrow is it can't be traced
'cause in movies, whenever somebody gets hit by an arrow,
they don't know where it came from.
- Exactly. - It's very sudden.
- It came from Legolas too.
- Yeah, or somebody. - We know,
people in the movie don't know, but we know.
- Exactly, nobody knows where that thing's,
it came from over yonder in the bush.
I guess that's the problem with having an arrow and bow
in New York City is that there's not a lot of bush to hide.
- You just do it from the rooftops.
- Yeah, I guess that would work.
But would you get like a, would it be like a,
like a wooden bow and arrow?
Or would you get like a big compound bow that's like a--
Probably.
Do you guys feel like that's cheating?
Yes.
Like that's too close to a real gun.
Anything that you have to like carry around
in a sniper case and assemble?
That's just, I mean, that's people,
bow and arrow people saw a crossbow and got jealous
and they made the big composite metal ones.
They can't just accept that somebody
invented a better version.
Exactly.
That you just click a button with.
Yeah, they're like, oh, we, yeah, oh,
I mean the crossbow is obviously cooler, more powerful, and better in every way.
Yeah, definitely.
It's half gun, half bow and arrow.
They were like, "We're gonna go a quarter gun, three-force, bow and arrow."
And it's perfect for vampire hunting.
No, it's not.
Crossbow?
No, it's terrible for vampire hunting.
What are you talking about?
Because, you know, you need, you want wooden stakes.
Van Helsing has a crossbow.
Van Helsing's a horrible vampire hunter.
He's not, what are you, what are you, what?
I'm way better than Van Helsing at vampire hunting.
I have never seen you hunt a vampire.
That's why I'm so good at it.
Oh my god.
You know what? Good point.
Camera kills him with kindness.
Yeah.
You know a vampire, that's their biggest weakness.
I walk up to their castle and I ring their vampire doorbell
and I say "I baked you some cookies."
They're never going to guess what I sprinkled
in those cookies before I baked them.
Holy lava. Poison.
Wow. Which kills them.
I thought it was something.
be killed with normal shit right yeah you could kill okay like why do they go
through why do they have to have this like special technique also a steak
through a heart will kill like me yeah you know like it's not like just for vampires
a gun could kill a vampire also enough garlic would kill a man right over time
they say if they're allergic those vampires vampires have been they've been
declining I mean it used to be originally it used to be that like you
have to like you have to put a steak through its heart and then chop off its
head and fill its mouth with garlic and then like put a horse over its grave or
something and now it's just like oh you can hand them a clove of garlic and
they'll melt away yeah yeah go to some of these fucking fast casual restaurants
they'll have enough garlic in that shit I mean it's burglary liberals that's
feminizing the vampires and and you know introducing chemicals to their body that
make them susceptible to sunlight yeah probably beyond meat might take one
One impossible whopper.
That's enough to kill two vampires.
Or at least turn them into sexy girl vampires.
Don't even get me started.
Oh my god, a girl vampire?
Why is that supposed to be hot?
I'm sick of getting seduced by vampires.
Why is it hot to have a girl vampire?
Is it just dresses?
Just a goth girl?
They have big dresses and long hair, duh.
Yeah, that is pretty hot actually.
That's the biggest widow's peak.
The hottest thing to me.
Long hair. Long white hair.
With a huge, a huge widow's peak.
Oh my god.
Your hair is so fucking long.
It's so long and receding.
You look so scary to me.
God damn that dress is big.
Please count for me.
One!
Two!
Oh the wooden scaffolding in that dress.
Oh my god.
Shame!
(laughing)
Goddamn, you lookin' like shit, girl.
Oh, you look horrible.
Goddamn, girl, you look like shit right now.
But you're a vampire, so it's sexy.
They don't have a girl sexy werewolf, do they?
No.
Well, I mean--
See, that wouldn't make any fuckin' sense, right?
Well, different strokes for different folks.
I think there's some people--
I'm trying to fuckin' stroke a girl werewolf.
There's probably some--
'Cause it looks like a dog, right?
And that's why you like it?
Not in the dog part you asshole. Are you seriously insinuating I want to fuck a dog?
You nasty crap ass. Man werewolves are so hot when they're not in their wolf form.
See, okay, well here's the thing. You look up sexy werewolf on Google Images and it's all men
showing up. It's because, it's because uh. Well okay, nevermind. It's because you try incognito and then search it.
(laughing)
Might be saving a couple of searches for you.
- All right, let me hit--
- And that's tailored specifically for you, so.
Oh, yep, all women, I can see it.
Yep, in the incognito.
- Oh, wow, that actually did--
(laughing)
I don't think that has anything to do with me, though.
I think that--
I think a gay guy's been using my computer all the time.
I think a gay werewolf has been on my computer.
Hey, you guys been using my computer?
[Laughter]
You better not.
They better not be touching my computer.
Somebody's been using it, dude.
I hope no one's been touching my computer.
[Laughter]
Hold on, I just found a...
Oh, fuck.
This is on smashwords.com
This is a book by
Selena Blake called seduced by a Cajun werewolf
ultra-sexy werewolf Lauren Devereaux thinks that violet the love of his life
died 200 years ago until she shows up in New Orleans violet now a vampire now a
vampire
It's book three in a series.
Wait, wait, is that the moon?
Oh my God, wait, listen to the names of the series.
This is book, Seduced by a Cajun Werewolf is book three.
Book one, The Cajun Werewolf's Captive.
Book two, Bitten in the Bayou.
Book four, Mated to a Cajun Werewolf.
Book five, Stranded with a Cajun Werewolf.
And book six, A Cajun Werewolf Christmas.
Yo!
This has a happy ending.
Yeah.
Right?
At some point, she's like, all right,
this this dapper Cajun werewolf wearing this white suit. God damn, you know what?
This seersucker suit. At some point, I'm just gonna celebrate Christmas with him.
Yeah. Yeah, it doesn't matter how many times he makes me a slave or mates with
me. I gotta, you know, Christmas is for everybody. Here's a review, I'm looking at
reviews of a Cajun werewolf Christmas. Good story for a beginner reader of the
series. For a beginner reader? You started the last one? Dude, you're gonna miss all the sexual tension and buildup
Why is it I guess that's true. What is up with women and there's probably
5,000 romance novels about fucking a werewolf. Yeah, I mean it's the same thing as like when you go on like to be and there's a
Hundred like asylum movies called like giant spider versus ugly crocodile. Mm-hmm. Yeah, this is more sexual
This is the woman version of it is what I'm saying. Oh, yeah, that's fair. Yeah, but like do like
Do women want to fuck dr. Jekyll?
No, I it's weird women want to like like
Absolutely any monster. It's any monster who I try I went to I went to send send some of these two patches
And I sent him some about orcs and yeah, there's there's a very wide selection of what kind of monsters like dinosaurs or
There's a lot of dinosaur ones
Yeah, yeah
Fuck a dinosaur
I'll do this one.
With his penis.
Dinosaur erotic novels.
It's gotta be like a hybrid.
Taken by the T-Rex.
It's gotta be a hybrid.
What the fuck?
Space raptor butt invasion.
Ravished by the triceratops.
Oh they got the horns.
In the velociraptor's nest.
Kissing the coronavirus.
Oh they got horns.
Woah.
I think women just love anything that's like evil.
Yeah.
That's what I'm saying.
A billionaire dinosaur.
Butt fucking alligator.
- A billionaire dinosaur forced me gay.
(laughing)
- What's wrong with that?
- Mounted by the many of us, is what I say.
- Oh, dude, that's a whole new genre I was not aware of.
- Yeah, there's a billionaire, first of all,
he's a dinosaur, but he's also a billionaire,
what the fuck? - Well, I guess that's like,
- Captivated by centaurs.
- Well, centaur makes sense,
They have a horse cock with a man's face conquered by Clippy
Clippy yeah
I'm just looking through that. It's gotta be just a goof the Amazon related. Yeah that one. I don't
Jesus or I yeah
Bread by the ogre King
Rescued by the Seder yeah, there's there's there's a lot here my hot night with the Haribo bear
there.
*laughter*
Hot damn, Toucan Sam!
You're fuckin' eatin' my pussy!
*laughter*
Oh, that's nasty.
That's not right!
Cleveland style, that's fuckin' nasty shit, dude.
Oh, Christ.
Oh, no!
Oh, no.
Alright, um, we have a hip-hop list.
hip-hop list. Yeah, we have a list that's sure to piss Caleb off. Um, already fuming. I can't even
read the title. Somebody else to handle this bullsh*t. The top 10 worst things about rap music.
There's... Rap music is amazing in its influence and popularity. Far more than just a musical style,
rap and the sub-genres of rap have created distinct cultures with specific expectations,
status symbols, and norms. But while some rap artists have worked to buck the trend,
much of rap music seems to be heading down a scary path of intolerance, self-destruction,
and violence. This list seeks to identify the worst things about those forms of rap music
that do more harm to society than good.
That's Patrick saying that.
That's not me saying that.
That didn't sound like me at all.
That was Patrick's voice. It sounded exactly like him.
No.
Why'd you read it that way, Pat? With your normal voice, I mean.
Stop looking like Wario. Knock it the fuck off.
Stop getting red.
Is that scary, Cameron?
I wasn't even looking. I didn't care.
Stop making that face, dude.
You're scaring Cameron, dude.
I don't want to do this list anymore, guys.
That's what you get. You messed with the bull, you got the horns, baby.
Now that's a good novel name right there.
"I messed with the bull and got the horns."
That's good. That is really good.
"Messed with a minotaur."
Number one, egotism.
I fucking hate egotism.
Ugh, one of the worst things in our society.
So, Alpha Q says, "Even good rappers like Kanye West has too much of this.
I think rap is going downhill real fast.
First you had a cool guy named Eminem and old Kanye and now you get a song about a vegetable.
What's so good about broccoli?
It ain't that good."
Oh, I just, I forgot about that fucking song.
What song?
That song, that was like Song of the Summer 2016.
Yeah.
Broccoli?
Oh, the Dram song?
Yeah, he doesn't go by drama anymore either. What does he go by the broccoli guy? Uh, I don't know he changed it
It's uh, no, I changed it to poop. Shelly Shelly FBA
Let's go he goes by Shelly now
That's a girl's name. Yeah, here's a comment. It isn't that I'm not tough enough to listen to rap
It's that I am tough enough not to listen to rap. Whoa
Here's a comment here says it depends if the person rapping can make it clever
I literally have no problem with this and that's from swag flicks
Someone says at least rockers are more respectful and respected
Thank you now I will win the debate for my class smiley face hashtag happy hashtag. Thank you hashtag if I knew you
I would buy you coffee
Here who thought by the way look at the kind of the more of the comments deeper down that these would be so insanely
Racist yeah, did you are you seeing the same one that I'm seeing?
Seeing a couple pretty fucking bad. Yeah
Here's one. Here's one. I love hip-hop music. I just hate the ego and that's a quote from ego by Macklemore
Always talking about themselves that and sex when you really think about it. It's gross. It's like glorifying crime, and I love rap
It's pretty good yeah
Yeah, oh my god. These are so fucking great. I really I don't know why I didn't foresee this yeah
Yeah, just think about like the most racist thing that yeah
- Pretty close.
- If you want to know what some of these comments look like,
text your grandpa right now.
Just say, "What do you think of this rap song?"
- Yeah, what do you think of this rap song?
- Scroll to Patrick's tweets from 2014.
- No.
- You're gonna find.
- Yeah, search.
- Come on.
- Why are you guys attacking me today?
- I'm not attacking you.
You want me to attack you?
- No.
- I'll attack you.
- Well then watch it.
Watch your tone, okay?
- Yeah, stop saying no when I say bad things about you.
And number two is sexism.
And here's the number one comment on it.
I'm a freshman in high school and I love jazz.
I'm a huge fan of John Coltrane, Eric Dolphy, Pharoah Sanders, Albert Ayer, Ernette Coleman,
Duke Ellington and several more.
Songs like Naima by John Coltrane, Namia?
It doesn't matter.
Naima by John Coltrane.
Talk about their love for that special woman in their lives.
Women inspire people.
This is too long.
Never mind.
I give up.
What?
That is like a fucking paragraph.
I don't want to read the rest of that.
Why did you start reading it?
'Cause I thought it would get good.
*laughter*
Okay, wait, wait, blah blah blah blah blah.
These dumbasses can't see anything beyond a sexy body and a nice ass.
It's pathetic.
It's also insulting that people my age listen to this as if it's actually good.
If John Coltrane were still alive today,
he would be disgusted with what qualifies as music these days.
Oh my god if John Coltrane were alive today
John Coltrane yeah
If only dude if I could show young thug to John Coltrane
it'd be like showing a smartphone to a caveman dude he had me crucified
be fucking a nightmare
someone says uh horrifying
I am a mormon and I hate this so much
this is the reason I do not go to school dances
my mom even says it's talking about a party
But I know better when let's do it is repeated 50 times in a quote-unquote song so to speak
You sound cool, dude
Whenever a rapper makes a song about woman
It'll always be about having sex with them or the whole song will be focused on their boobs. I'm sick of it
I forgot to mention that I'm a guy
Although I am male I am sick of them using women only for sex
They just care about their backsides and breasts and I am sick of it
I hate songs like that and they make me want to do a violent protest
I refuse to touch the entire genre for fear of hearing something disgusting
I could appreciate it in spite of everything else, but not this
Surprise that no one has tried to ban rap yet. It promotes more violence drug use and misogyny than any other music genre
Yeah, yes, I'm not one of those psycho feminists, but I agree that some rap songs are bad to woman
They treat females like objects or decorations
You know how rap songs always talk about mounting a girl's head
Putting a star on top of a woman's head
Like a deer
Yeah
Wrapping a woman up in tinsel
Here's a comment here
Just three words
Women are meat hole
*laughter*
(laughter)
Rappers view women like slaves and have no feelings for them, only sexual attraction.
Oh, fuck.
Ugh.
Oh, fuck me, dude.
It's so good.
(laughter)
Uh, yeah.
I mean, I'm sure it's gotta just be like 11 year old kids, right?
No, this is all 20 year old men. That's what I can't tell they have the same type of the same the same rhetoric
It comes to this. This is a secret lives of the pitchfork editorial board
Let's say go give a chief Keefe album like a 10 out of 10 and they're like he's he has a he's he's creating a
Musical tapestry. Yeah, this is more like opera than rap. Yeah, then they go on here and they're like
Right by the way, I'm a guy and even I hate this sex bullshit
Number three pointless lyrics
Okay, so these people have obviously never heard of immortal technique MF doom
Ali
Juice world juice
world
Farting
MC Crazy Rapper Foxy Foxy Lars Preston Lacey
Presto fucker
Balls bread
Rap bill, Briston
These are
number number one cream
bag George rest in peace
presto
pretzel
Xbox Preston Lacey again rest in Lacey's son
Woody Allen
Spose the guy who made I'm awesome Roman Polanski
Salva Harvey Weinstein Bryan Singer is hard with fucking firefighters
Empties
little bill
Yeah
You know, I mean I could go on but it was we could go on forever that's
People with with pointed lyrics guns and roses exactly Rosie O'Donnell
There's this comment here
Cameron, why don't you read this top comment?
I have always hated rap music.
I'm black, so everyone assumes I listen to this trash.
Nearly every rap song nowadays is consistent of controversial lyrics pertaining to sex,
drugs, racism, money, violence, and struggles.
I hate when people talk about struggles.
I listen to rock and roll.
At least they shift their style every once in a while.
I listen to bands like Saliva, Motorhead, Disturbed, Kiss, and AC/DC.
Dude, some of the kings of rock.
I mainly hate rap because of stereotypical views.
People assume that all black people listen to rap.
I don't and I never will again.
Even country musicians have some point of talent.
Throwing disturbed in there is so funny.
Like complaining about like they're talking like they only rap about money and violence
and struggles and disturbed just raps about like being hit by.
First of all they do rap in their music.
Yeah.
They have one they have a rap song about about dropping plates on your ass.
Okay.
So maybe study up.
ACD where every song is like, "Let's have a birthday party! Yeah!"
Disturbed is just about like, it's about either being at your breaking point to become a school
student or being hit by your mother or the Holocaust should never happen again. Those
are the three types of Disturbed songs.
They really are disturbed. Somebody needs to put them in jail.
Absolutely.
You would think with that name.
Remember when David Draymond from Disturbs did an acoustic cover of the Sound of Silence
for Blue Lives Matter?
No, that's shit though.
Didn't he do it on Conan?
Maybe, I don't know.
I didn't listen to it or watch it.
I just saw it and went, "Yup."
Rap music sounds terrible and the lyrics are absolutely ridiculous.
If you could even understand what they are, that's one of my favorite kinds of people,
people who listen to English native English speakers who listen to rap and
they're like I don't know what they're saying that's one of the greatest things
of all time when I listen to music I can't hear the lyric like not like hear
the lyrics but like I paid more attention to the music than the lyrics
okay so you're telling me I just try to like feel it yeah I just like
immediately identify like I'm writing up the score in my head when I'm listening
so I don't really have times to focus on the words sounds like that's what you're
doing
favorite
Well I don't pay, I don't know, I don't really pay attention to the lyrics of songs.
I don't pay attention to the music dude.
Yeah, I'm all about the lyrics.
That's why I listen to PJ Masks.
Yeah.
Yeah, they got a lot of good lyrics.
They have a lot of great songs on the PJ Masks.
The PJ Masks soundtrack, I mean, is untouchable.
Some of the greatest artists.
Bedtime is the right time.
Can't finish the rhyme.
Today's rap sounds like a bunch of down-syndromed crack babies mumbling random gibberish.
I used to like rap, but then I grew up and realized how mentally handicapped and warped
you have to be to think that mainstream rap content is a complete garbage.
You want real music today?
Try some jazz, symphonies, rock, or any other genre that requires talent.
Genres like rap and pop are nothing but talentless dancers and actors using autotune.
It's cancer.
Mentally warped?
be warped but then I got into symphonies because talking about how they're going
to do stuff to 50 girls and shoot up a bank sure isn't pointless I'm gonna do
stuff to 50 girls. In 2018 we have Kiki, Fifi, Bubba, Bebe, Sese, Billy, Kuda, Gummo. Do I
i need to say more and now we have no gumbo
no kiki no kura no hope
they just did exactly what we did
okay so there's a there's a comment here that's in some other language i just put
it's in turkish
i just google translated it
and it translates to ever heard kendrick fuck motherfucker three days grace
listeners. Number four, the sound. That's one of the worst things about rap
music is the sound. Yeah, the sound of it. Yeah, the volume in rap is way too loud.
It can hurt the eardrums as children.
It can be hard on their hearing early.
It's too loud.
Oh fuck.
That's kind of the only good comment on this one.
Everything else is people, because what the fuck does this even mean?
Yeah, there's a response to that comment that says, "This is actually not an ignorant
statement, "Google the loudness war. This way of mastering music is found in other genres as well."
What is that? Just music got louder or some shit?
Yeah, I mean people just produced it louder gradually. I mean that's the kind of thing
you want. You'll want to go on YouTube and search like "the fall of music" and watch like a seven
hour documentary made by a 12 year old. Yeah. If you want to learn about that, there's, I'm sure
there's plenty of good videos. Yeah, where they have a 30 minute thing at the end thanking their
patrons yeah yeah and you're like how the fuck there's five how many yeah I do
this little kid on patreon what the fuck is this dude yeah I'm always impressed by
that it is yeah yeah I want I do yeah it is crazy who's who's doing that yeah
cuz like you get your they're on YouTube dude they're already exactly you still
get them yeah get the videos plus they make the ad money you don't need all
that well that page what do you get to see you get to see the video a day early
how hungry are you for a two-hour video about the making of Half-Life 2?
I have to see how roly-poly only changed TV forever one day early. I need to find
out what episode of The Simpsons changed Homer forever. Where did the
downfall of Franklin the Turtle come from? I have to find out right now dude I
need to know which Cars movie was the biggest misstep in Pixar's history
please dude fuck number five glorification of the gangster mentality
that's one of the best things about rap music yeah dude we do that I feel like
we glorify in a good way I mean it's good dude every you know it's good to be
gangster it's true good mentality I'm we're basically three gangster gang
bangers with from the hood with crazy mindsets and that's like why we started
that's like how we found each other too. Yeah, we went on gangster.com and we searched for
gangsters in your area. Gangstermeat.me. We were on Gangster Bumble and we kind of all
linked up. And we all linked up and then we had a... We were on Hinge and we all listed
our interests as Gangster Mindset. Yeah, Gangster Mindset, being from the hood, being a swagged
out player and that's how we all met each other. Yeah. Yeah. Even though we were all
from different hoods. We still came and we formed our own. I mean that's why it's
such a success story. Yeah and now we're like I would say one of the top four
gangs. One of the biggest. MS-13, Crips, Bloods and then Sullivan the Frog LLC.
Yeah. Yeah we're like one of the biggest gangsters. We're the only one that's LLC.
We have the money mindset. We decided we were the first people
the first people to ever ever combined businessman mindset and gangster
mentality. Exactly. You gotta get the hustle in there. Our Instagram
quotes page went fucking gangbusters. Yeah, which we do not like the gangbusters.
We've been fighting them for a while. But then now we give back to the hood and we go back
into our communities and we show them how to be gangster as well. Which is one of the most amazing things about it.
amazing start a small business gangsters with small businesses yeah we teach them
how you can actually make a thug cry and it's actually not that big a deal yeah I
mean look at this comment here gangsters are a bunch of idiot crybaby ugly guys
they love praying for more weeds and crushing the cracks which that's true if
you listen to a real artist you might realize that they regret their actions I
I love this list it's 100% factual it's 100% factual what a joke shooting people
will get you nowhere in life but jail tell that to the freakin army exactly
this guy this guy supports the Holocaust he didn't want to kill the Nazis sheesh
that's guys evil yeah tells you a lot about people who who oppose the gangster
hustled business mindset.
This is, in my opinion, the worst part of rap.
It completely alienates anyone who isn't part of the gang culture and glorifies being
a criminal.
We know that's the number one consumer of rap in the world and not, like, people who
look like me.
Well, most of it, all of the mainstream at least.
The best part of gangster culture and media is the part where it shows the cons as well,
like the Godfather, where it shows Michael becoming evil and even killing his own brother.
This is nowhere to be found in rap.
Again, they just got it all wrong. I didn't know Michael became evil.
Jesus. He's cool. He doesn't become evil, he becomes fucking sick.
I have seen The Godfather. Really? I've seen parts of it.
I watched it for the first time this year. Yeah, I'll have to sit down and watch it
sometime. You've watched it with my dad? Yeah.
That's a movie my dad used to throw on and then I would like
want to play GameCube or something. You guys remember, I mean
I mean, there's a, I mean, great, great impressions you get from the goth that are like
*goth noises*
Remember how he had the cotton balls in his cheeks and he was sounding like
I loved him.
Do you know him? Yeah, he was good in that. I mean,
Who was that? *goth noises*
*goth noises*
That was Doodle Don Corley SpongeBob.
(laughter)
Doodle Don.
I mean, yeah.
The evil Doodle version of Don Corleone.
It was genius. I mean, at first they had him without those cheeks and then, you know,
Dr. Godfather, the director, came in and he was like, "I want him to look more like a chipmunk."
And I wanted him to sound like an idiot.
Did you know that he actually put poop in his mouth for that?
(laughter)
And he kept it in his mouth like a chipmunk?
Yeah, the director wanted him to take it out, but he wouldn't.
Yeah, that was not even like an acting decision. That was just an addiction.
(laughter)
That's why you can tell at the end of all the shots he goes
*nom nom nom* and they have to cut that out.
They cut out the deleted scenes where at the end he does a big cartoonish swallow.
He says "I sure love crap"
"Delicioso"
Yeah.
You know, cause the mafia.
Oh.
That's Italian for delicious.
Um, no, number six, no talent goes into it.
Alright.
Okay, that's a little.
it yeah they haven't heard me rap yeah fast fast I'm fast I'm fast I'm faster
than a blast blast in blast attack blast like a fast attack attack you fast
blasting attack with the fast attack with your blasting you a blasting faster
faster than the attacker blasting faster than the attacker faster blaster
attacker that's vastly best you want to tell me that that's not a bastard talent
look at that are you fucking that was off the dome to bow down at this man's
feet this I mean I had to practice rap Christ years so good he used to be
trying to be in the hood every day trying to do that I was street it was
tough too I mean people come on they say what think people will never tell you
about the hood it's not easy I mean a lot of media will tell you it's easy to
live there it's everybody's it's so easy to be in the hood all the time and do a
bunch of shit in the hood especially for me while I'm mentally crazy white guy I
mean this is acting there is like rapping there like you're liable to get made
fun of in the hood for that. Mm-hmm. I wear my thick two-inch thick
glasses. Somebody might come up and they roll up and make fun of you from
their car. Yeah and that's the worst. And you might really seriously get
emotionally traumatized. Somebody might roll their window down lean over to
their passenger seat and go "nerd" and then "hey stinker" "hey dummy" "hey your
shoes untied made you look in the drive-on just lost the game yeah somebody
might make a little circle and put it on their knee and say look what I got and
then they can frog you dude for that shit oh my god I was out time there I was out
there wrapping some guy handed me a telescope and he said look over there I
did there was nothing over there everyone's was laughing at me the whole
day I couldn't tell why till I got to the bathroom looked in the mirror I had
black circle are at my eye.
Are you serious?
I mean they'll do shit like that out there. It's tough.
Some of these gangsters are heartless.
[Laughter]
Except for us.
Uh huh.
Um, let's see.
Did we read the comments for this one?
These comments are too long.
Yeah.
Um, some of these are like
I mean, a lot of
these kind of repeat. Like number
Seven here, no variation.
That's kind of the same thing.
- Yeah, that's kind of what I'm saying about this list.
- Yeah, hey, you know, we should write a diss track
for this list.
- That's a good idea.
- Oh, dude, that'd be like the biggest one ever, dude.
- Yeah, number of the top 10 worst things about this list.
Number one, not funny.
- Yeah, some of these, some of these boys,
some of, they suck.
- Yeah, number two, they suck.
- Number seven, no variation.
- Yeah.
- Comments are way too long on this one.
- You guys gotta cut it down.
- Have you noticed that rappers find it impossible
to make a lyric that isn't one, sexually explicit,
two, violence promoting, three, racist or sexist,
four, loaded with swears?
- Look, I just want a rapper who raps very fast
and doesn't swear.
- Yeah, I want a rapper who makes a one second song
where I can't tell if he swears or not.
And it's about nothing, it's about making,
about doing dishes. Ideally it has to be completely ambiguous whether the song is
about God or suicide. Yeah, that's the genre I want to be listening to.
Or bullying. Number eight, songs bragging about having money. For the love
of God, no one cares about how much money you have. Music isn't about having money.
I understand that people need to make a living somehow, but that's not the main
idea music is about expression and inspiration it's there to explain
something to you it has a deeper meaning behind it music music isn't just about
making money that just isn't even music I have no tolerance for that why would
rappers brag about money hanging out their butts
why no that was seven good you have money now use it for something other
than you crack addiction. Whoa. I don't think there's any rappers except DMX who are
addicted to crack, right? I don't know. I mean it's probably not something that
many people would like to be public about. Right. Wait, wait you read one
about money hanging out of the butt, right? Yeah. There's a second one that says
I hate it when a rapper is all money hanging out of my butt. Peasants always
screaming wait what? Peasants? What is that? Is something, is there is there like a
rapper I'm missing he raps about money hanging out of his ass. Sir Mix-a-lot.
He's always talking about peasants. MC Vassal dude. He raps about these
serfs all the time. King Arthur. Can you let them, can you give him a break?
King Arthur. Now I can tell number nine's gonna be really good. I mean I can tell
there's gonna be some great comments. Number nine is racism.
well I mean it just being used in a casual conversation one more time I
think I'm going to go insane do they even know what it means it's not some quote
unquote dope slang term god I'm surprised that we aren't extinct yet if people
talked that way back in the 20th century people would just absolutely be
disgusted people hated using the n-word in the 20th century nobody used it back then
here's a here's a comment here a lot of rap insults whites about being weak and
getting life easy just because we didn't grow up in the ghetto I grew up in the
ghetto we've already been over this mm-hmm I'd like to hear that say that to
early Europeans Europe was a death trap it still is and imagine how Alexander the
crate the root of racism is rap hey this rapper thinks you're weak and he's like
What?
Excuse me?
That's racist.
I mean he would conquer them.
Mm-hmm.
He's Alexander the Great, that's what he does.
Number 10, misinformation.
I mean that's one of the worst crimes.
I mean look at what happened in 2016 with the election.
There was a rap song called the Pantsuit Anthem and it spread a lot of misinformation.
Yo voting isn't till December.
You guys remember that?
Most rappers say things that are meant to rhyme, but it ends up sounding really stupid
and gets a lot of people in trouble.
That is, misinformation is when it doesn't rhyme.
A lot of people get in so much trouble from these misinformed rap lyrics.
Alright, these are the contenders.
Unoriginal lyrics, okay.
I mean, you already said that, I think.
Songs about sex.
Someone says, "You people do know that Crank That Soulja Boy's songs was about ejaculation,
right?"
(laughter)
- Ejaculation.
Damn.
- Number 13, excessive profanity.
- Yep.
- Yes, using the same cuss word at the end of every sentence
does help make everything rhyme,
but really it's enough already.
And it's not just that it is objectionable language.
If you use any word that many times it sounds stupid.
If rap lyrics are supposed to be an art,
then excessive profanity is like
only drawing pictures of vaginas.
Maybe amusing at first and simple minds will have more tolerance for it, but eventually people are going to want to see a picture of a sunset.
*laughter*
That guy has such a beautiful mind.
I'm sick of these pussies!
Can I just see a fucking sunset for once?
Can I just search "porn" and find pictures of a sunset?
Sometimes I want to jack off to something new!
Can you turn one of these into a flower?
Oh, come on!
Christ almighty!
This is the most disgusting vagina bullshit I've ever seen.
shit I've ever seen. What happened to the moon and the stars? Can you just make this look
like an orange or something? Just open an orange and make it look like a pussy, please? God,
I'm sick. Number 14. Number 14, it's just talking. Yep, if I want to hear talking, I
would start a bloody conversation. Excuse me. No wonder both opera and rap are so popular.
No wonder both opera and rap are crazy. Take your pick. Singing when you're
supposed to be speaking or speaking when you're supposed to be singing? Fuck.
That's like a... he's right in the center. Number 16. Kids trying to imitate real
gangsters. I prefer to be a sad skinny geek than be a wannabe weed eater ugly
guy. Weed eater? When a five-year-old is throwing up gang signs your way and
singing rap music you know you don't belong on this planet.
I'm skipping around but number 59 is uh...
pornography.
There's only one comment on it that says
"I don't think that's really rap music."
Uh... songs about getting drunk, high, or intoxicated.
Someone says if you take out the lyrics from rap music there are no words.
really smart stupid dances invented by rappers every time I see one I like what
the hell are they doing they look so damn stupid
most modern phony rappers compare themselves to Tupac and Biggie
glorification of violence offensive lyrics sellouts hip-hop feuds negative
messages it could send bad messages to unger viewers songs about strip clubs
and then evil cute girl Jigglypuff says I hate that kind of stuff number 71 porn
rap and the only comment is what is a porn rap I really loved number 74 yeah
that is like that sounds like a fucking like substitute teacher it's cacophony
and then the person says all they do is say a bunch of pointless trashy words
with their hideous voices to a bunch of awful music in the background.
Uh, crunk, wannabe gangsters, screaming, songs about rape. What the fuck?
Alter egos. Dude, I fucking hate rap because of all the alter egos.
Well, because I can't tell them apart, dude. It's fucking annoying, dude. Is this supposed
to be Victor Vaughn? Who the fuck is singing? Who is this, dude? Is this MF Doom or King Ghidorah?
Yeah how am I supposed to tell dude it's fucked up someone complains it's getting
worse every day that's number 63 ghostwriters amateurs diss tracks number
52 difficult to understand I especially can't understand rappers who literally
spout out wobble dee wob wobble wob wobble dee wob wobble wob I'm looking at you
big Sean that's one of his best songs anyway we've this has been three
gangsters from the hood giving our two cents on some of the most rap ass shit
in the world yep Oh live show tomorrow yeah see you there
Nah, we're not coming. Fuck you.
Yeah, we're sending decoys.
Yeah.
Alright, bye.
Bye.